Christmas
[Music]
day
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
thank you foreign
this is
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
hello my cat also says hello good
morning good evening everybody at this
really awkward time slot
um
[Laughter]
is very talkative today
Jokers don't mind her she's eventually
gonna go away
um yeah good morning uh let's uh uh
let's start up concrete wants to join
yeah I'm sorry off of the self
introductions for my life English uh
hello next you Kelly
it's the mini Sheriff I don't use my
accent all the time but occasionally
okay occasionally occasionally you hear
a little Southern twang
um because today that's right I'm the
fashion sheriff and the fashion Sheriff
woke up and said you know what I want a
mini hat today to accessorize with these
glasses
be honest you put it in into the
dishwasher and it came out this small
no don't call me out like that
yeah come on man they say if you put a
hat in the dishwasher it washes it
really well so like wait who said I gave
it a shot
my dad my dad oh yeah I used to put like
my baseball caps and like for like that
kind of thing yeah my Snapbacks and
stuff like that into the dishwasher and
it made them nice and clean but joking I
built a little ragged no I'm not joking
oh my God that's that's some knowledge I
never had before
yeah that was what Papa reached that it
kind of listen maybe
yeah yeah yeah like a snapback hat into
the normal
um um um clothing washing machine
and it came out not so well should I put
it in the dishwasher
ah yeah yeah that's what you're supposed
to put it that's what Papa Maurice is at
least
you know because he's like he's like
slowly balding into like an even balder
skeleton anyway my name is Maury
Calliope I need to move this along
excuse me no problem today I'm the
fashion I'm the fashion Sheriff I'm
gonna be judging all of you behind these
Sheriff glasses in this tiny share of
hat and I'm very excited to welcome uh
to Kiara's Channel as well we have a
special guest today who could it be is
it is it who I think it is who are you
who is this person
uh I'm okay
is that the omo cat she's kind of shy
what he does the one who does the thing
damn that one come on oh my cat tell us
a bit more
yeah go into detail who is on the cat
you tell uh is uh I draw and she draws
and I made the uh collection
the collection of between whole life and
and yeah yeah yeah it's got her face is
all over it you're also behind a gamer
here
uh yes I made a game she made a game
yeah what's it called
that she played that yeah I beat that
game did you know she made that game
Cali
[Music]
I know
of course you knew of course you knew I
knew but yeah this is
also recently I flexing a flex instead
of you so you don't need to flex about
it but she she's doing a Pokemon
collaboration official an official
Pokemon collaboration
you should be remembering
so humble so cute yes
[Music]
well guys so these are the members today
on my channel we are doing a review of
uh submissions that I asked you guys to
send in for uh so to say fashion review
because we heard a fashion police and we
may not look much like a police but if
you look at the top right that's that's
usually we we lost our uniforms but we
look like that usually and a very
professional judging you can expect from
us uh and yeah I uh there's like a
pre-selection we'll go through them and
then there will be some um winners per
category and uh almost cat is so nice to
uh provide to us some rewards
I give it up to you uh
and I'm going to give everyone
um who's featured a catalog
wait yes everyone who's featured gets
this catalog this beautiful catalog
[Music]
and
then the winners um for each category
will get also a lanyard and five
keychains this lip this beautiful
lanyard where you can put your keys on
or do other fun stuff with it yeah I did
I put mine on here on this lanyard I got
all my friends
these cute keychains they're so cute
Cali with the wine glass made with the
chicken I love it is so adorable and I
love I love Watson's mug expression yeah
it's so good so I'm Brandon she's
investigating she could have been here
too like as a detective but but we'll
leave it to the fashion police she
doesn't know much about fashion
oh are you sure about that though Kiara
yeah I've seen what this is always her
mama no it's always her mama who dresses
her like that
we could have gotten her mama in here
oh yeah true true all right so we'll
have uh the five categories of
um
indeed my cat and um that will have a
general uh General uh uh category where
we go for some general merch that is not
so specifically for one um person here
yeah so let's get this
started shall we
yes I'm ready
in our investigation
where did it go oh where did it go where
did it go all right Officer Kiara yeah
what briefing have you lost debris first
oh yes the documents my eyes can't
comprehend it ah there it is there it is
good at category
look at that pose yes it's a really cute
post you might get extra points for a
pose yes
shark plushies yes they're famous shark
[\h__\h] from a specific company that makes
some meatballs too
yeah yes wait what is the Ikea shark
postinos oh
never mind no no forget I said anything
all right great well I I can't you can't
nice yes oh my God what's your fashion
input on this one
up a little bit a little detail I think
the that the sporty sneakers are a nice
touch and I like how the the blue tones
work so well together and that she
layered like a long sleeve shirt
underneath the pixel t-shirt that looks
really cute the layering do I sound
professional
out of 10 rating or because we gotta get
to a winner somehow
I know right let me come in here with a
fake critique which means it actually
like doesn't [\h__\h] matter
um let's see I think it's really cool
um and I think that it would achieve a
10 rating if it was like if there was
like maybe a little bit more like going
on I don't want to say it's simple
because the fashion sense is on point
but if we're if we gotta choose winners
and stuff like that and we have to give
points we gotta we gotta give like you
know what Let's do let's do um let's do
the ratings in our Discord chat behind
the scenes and they'll just they'll just
find out the final winner and we'll put
our heads together and do mathematics
and see who got the most points yeah we
don't we're the police we're the fashion
police we don't want to hurt your
feelings damn
okay so uh a fashion police uh place
your rating place in the Discord chat
first participant oh yeah oh yeah I have
the names by the way this person is on
Twitter under the name fruniper
f-r-u-n-i-p-e-r thank you for
participating okay
um
okay that means Cali you and I we have
to be more strict all right we'll have
to be more I hate being strict because I
love everyone
awesome
[Music]
well you might it's difficult because
this is the first entry so you you guys
don't have anything to compare it with
um right but don't worry there will be a
lot more okay thanks Cali for the line
there
sure yeah great assistant all right next
up we have this person
on Twitter it's i k k a h o t s u k i
um and yes I love this because of the
gradient skirt it's so cute and she has
the good uh
um Parker look at a jacket and the whole
a t-shirt
if you look closely it on her back she
has the keychains and the lanyard
attached as well wow wow
a lot of effort but that's not all
that's not all I actually have an extra
shot for this one uh if we look
um this
she is wearing these
um accessories looks like they're maybe
self-made and they're inspired by good
as
a party outfit uh accessories
way yeah so cool yeah really cute
now unfortunately I can't go back to the
other picture anymore
you remember the gradient shirt makes it
like so good yeah of course
the merchants
it would be a great outfit to go to the
whole whole life English concert with
yeah I think so too and I love just the
extra thought put into the accessories
yes
okay yeah okay rating uh is being placed
uh let me put the name down too
mm-hmm it's very cute there we go
thank you for that super cute entry
thank you
[Music]
you were very close to being arrested
this is a warning close to being
arrested for cuteness please be careful
next time that's right we only arrest
cute people the chat is always giving
everyone 10 out of 10 because that's the
only uh uh emotes that they have
God
they deserve it all right next
submission here we go this is from all
right
okay i n n i k u k a l yeah this one is
kind of sporty yeah sporty casual like
she's going out on his bike yeah yeah
bike out to like the Cali Beach or
something yeah
yeah
what do you think oh my cat
you can see the ankles again
you gotta be able to see them ankle
are you
thank you
I like
um something here no I just like the
pants that cut off there is
premium Style
yeah yeah that's a good t-shirt we're in
a good category and I I yeah I
personally like um that he layered like
a like a
um thin shirt on top of it makes it look
more like it Blends in actually pretty
nicely my this one doesn't make him look
like a a whole life fan immediately uh
but yeah if you know you know because of
that crazy face on on front in the front
of the T-shirt yeah yeah exactly my dude
is also posing like he would be like an
omocat model yeah yeah yeah gotta give
him some points for the pose as well all
right let's have Fashion Police please
place your uh ratings
well golden fruit is pretty quickly nice
uh very good because we have a lot of
submissions and a lot of categories
and um
okay oh
my God I think I need to fire you sorry
I can't do it
they don't even know what you're writing
you don't have to be so nice
okay
me and Kelly are gonna take care of it I
think you can hold down the fort yeah
yeah I just need to do a professional
fashion input that's all I need
yeah we just need your input okay next
submission here we go from Moana
m-o-h-r-a-n-n-e-r I love this one
matching glasses yes I like the glasses
too the light blue glasses and the the
his watch also matches his shoes are
interesting too because they're blue and
red just like the T-shirt actually a
little different different tone of it
but still cool though he's got some
fancy rings too do you see that Cali has
got like skull
this is awesome I dig it and I like the
jacket too but I just I really like
black jackets So
in theory almost there's ankles but
they're covered by socks what about that
is that okay
you can still see them yeah that's okay
it really matters yeah that's how that's
how we're judging it then can't you
always see people's ankles damn
dress for like like uh confidence
thank you
yeah yeah
lovely pose indeed and uh everything
fits uh it also suits him personally I
think so very very good I think we can
replace our ratings already
[Music]
I will give it are we doing are we doing
dot five and so on
it sucks
that better but I still think it's very
sweet you're very sweet oh my cat
you can give them you can give them
whatever you can give everyone a 10 out
of 10. I appreciate it yeah yeah I'll
I'll take it as a 10 out of 10 later
when we put the numbers together
okay thank you for your submission
and next up we have cute proud dumpling
I don't have to spell that out do I
oh my gosh she looks like that's her
name I don't know what it is about her
but like she had a lot of other cute
photos so you guys should look at it but
yeah what do you think oh my cat
I think I think they look good no
anchors comments because they're covered
up by the boots huh yeah I like the
boots too yeah the boots are nice I like
boots like that that are up to the
ankles
yes I'm like I I aspire to be a person
who can um wear a belt like that because
like I I don't know if I style it
incorrectly but it just doesn't look as
cool when I do it like that
difficult but um
a secret is that it only looks good in
pictures
like a black skirt skirt with a jacket
because like that's I get like nervous
about wearing skirts with like black
jackets but like really that's like
Prime fashion like I would choose to
wear like tights with that kind of
outfit like go like full
full
goth GF
out just out in the street step out to
the city even that what you already are
yeah cringe goth girlfriend yeah I mean
I'm a Crazy Girlfriend maybe not in this
outfit but in maybe in your makeup just
kidding baby
oh I also like that she has like a like
a shirt underneath that sticks out at
the top uh with the color called color
Cola you know what I mean
mm-hmm to make it look a little bit more
sophisticated only in that spot
we likey I like it very much ratings
please for our proud dumpling and
pretty proud yes you should be proud
your stuff me and Kelly have similar
writings what
did I start judging or yes please stop
yeah you have to it's fine we can just
do we can do the number ratings and you
can just give like fashion tips very
sweet
you're not fashion tips fashion input
input like I like that you did this you
don't need to tell them how to dress or
anything I mean if we were to improve
anything here maybe a cowboy hat like
Cali has
yeah like a little tiny Sheriff that I
think will fit you perfectly
question is from pun uni p-u-n-y-u-n-i
yes
yes so cute the dynamic pose perfect and
um you don't see the ankles
unfortunately omo cat but you can
imagine them
I don't like ankles
it's over oh look at you can't go back
anymore
just I just noticed them first
okay we understand we understand
into this
so for me I like how she's wearing that
shirt around her hips wrapped around it
and the pants I when I wear short pants
like that it's usually like really
really short ones like hot pants but uh
shorts like that that are a little bit
longer like over the the thighs you know
what I mean that length I feel like I I
don't look good at that in them at all
so I really really admire that
just rocking it it's good yeah the first
thing that I thought of was um that when
I was younger
um I recall um some of my um like family
members who are my age like would see me
wearing jackets around my waist and
they'd tell me that nobody wears jackets
like that and I'm super Fringe
um which is
like that I know right I don't get it so
I'm like here look at this photo are you
blind like do you not have eyes because
this looks great yeah like I agree it's
awesome
[Music]
too hot
her nails make up for the lack of gouda
teeth
yeah exactly that's that's how she gets
you that's how she attacks you yeah all
right it's gonna get you placing your
ratings please Fashion Police
[Music]
all righty beautiful beautiful
definitely uh a case for a cute jail
cute jail
um I hope someone will bail you out hope
you have a friend it's a Bailey alone we
will win
tonight
Fashion Jail fashion yeah Fashion Jail
like the good kind all right next up we
have
Ragnar wrecked
r-a-g-n-4
r3kt yes oh edgy but I like it yeah the
the long boots make it a little bit edgy
Maybe
yeah this is something I'd wear oh oh
yeah there were some submissions where I
Thought of You Kelly in different
categories though not this one
specifically yeah but yeah
so yeah what do you what do you think
uh I like the flannel and
Oh you mean the shirt
flannel shirt
that's right
yes yes yeah flannel shirt good and the
the cap uh well I have to say uh on you
could put some did we have badges I
think we had badges right
in the collaboration
yes we had we had uh buttons yeah you I
think you need to put some of those
buttons on your on your cap but besides
that
looks nice looks uh yeah it's a good
combination you could put some ice on
there too my dude some ice no ice ice
you know like ice ice
I don't get it oh no oh no you got oh
Kiara do you not no it's nice
uh jewelry chains oh the bling bling The
Bling No I don't know that word
oh the drink and wait a minute then
why'd you decide
as a word for it no never heard of that
oh all right gotcha yeah that's uh it's
kind of like a slingy term um I learned
something new here hey oh my god did you
know what that means
yep oh
[Laughter]
okay okay
please figure it out yourself please
place your uh ratings fashion police in
our official documents
AKA Discord
um
bling bling
bling bling out of ten all right next up
is the next one is the last one for this
category it's a couple shot but we're
only gonna look at the person who wears
the good emerge uh this person is also
in the Ina merge category so only look
at the right side for now
okay
oh I love the lighting and the the um
location yeah the photo is really good
they took some professional photos there
wow so this is the good uh pixel T-shirt
with the good pixel cap and the good uh
uh jacket Desu
very professional yeah looks really good
together
oh you guys are cute yes
so cute I like the white sneaks with the
dark pants yeah it's a good look yeah
yeah he looks very confident too yeah
yeah and and he even matched his mask as
well
yeah it's good I will definitely give
that extra points in my mind for uh the
posing and the photo and the confidence
gets a lot of points for that of dance
comfy dance oh yeah by the way this was
on the Twitter trancing shoes trancing
shoes
t-r-a-n-c-i-n-g shoes
I love
I love outfits that are like outfit
combinations that don't go over like
four colors personally oh that's just my
that's my personal like fashion taste I
guess so like I like that there's like a
limited palette here yeah it's just like
about 50 shades of blue
yeah exactly which is fun
please please your ratings Fashion
Police for only for the right person in
this picture
[Music]
okay
okay that was the last one so now the
next category is I think the Cali
category so we're gonna put extra weight
on what Cali thinks all right these I
don't wear a lot of edgy submissions
Kelly oh yeah that's what I like to hear
we start out with this person this
person I included two outfits because
they were so different
[Laughter]
dude we go into the MCR concert together
go and I mean that as a compliment
because yeah
yeah this person is called crab Nubs
with
g-r-u-b-b-n-u-b-s so holy [\h__\h] like wow
she she know she has probably a huge
closet of this stuff I love your style
dude very cool love the layering the
layering looks sick is that a hoodie
underneath it looks like a hoodie yeah
that's dope and the colors match
perfectly you found yourself a good
outfit right yes and she has even a
spiky choker on did you see that
platform boots underneath
very cool I love platforms shoes slash
boots
extremely fashionable here I'm a big fan
of this yes right here I think she she
has uh two looks but we'll judge them
separately
[Music]
um wait grab Nubs
um also uh the the there is like the the
pinks and the Reds really stand out I
think I really like it yeah yeah I like
it that's good that's good [\h__\h] right
there and the hairstyle I I think
it has nothing to do with it
and the stripes yes yeah Stripes you
like stripes
yes
does it make you curious about
um what the ankles look like
oh my God
I'm just kidding I'm just trying to get
you to speak and look at don't be so shy
I I don't have um Discord Nitro so the
stream is running at a very low quality
oh and I can barely see the photos oh no
oh
in into Discord then for you there you
go wait is that better
yes okay good good let's do it like that
you just subscribe hold on
maybe that's why you couldn't put a
proper rating
like
all right uh Ben let's place your
ratings Fashion Police
oh man all right oh that's that's wow
you need um
I wonder which one you like more but
probably this one Kelly uh okay I went
and I looked through the other ones and
it's like two completely different
flavors but like you already looked at
it whatever you're yes I went and I
looked at it damn you spoiled yourself
oh whoopsie doodle are we judging them
separately yes separately this is
separately there you go this is the the
other one very girly this time
yeah oh my gosh
adorable it's like it's like choose your
goth GF yeah and I like it
I mean I feel like my rating's this name
for both of them honestly would you wear
cute uh one of those two outfits I wore
the first one but I'm a little too like
shy to wear the second I would wear the
second one maybe if I need to match with
you
yeah very cute wow drippy I love it they
look like they'd be good friends yeah
yeah
uh oh my cat would you wear that
uh
it's two is it too fluffy black
I only wear baggy clothes
I always say I see a bag of clothes okay
I also love that she's wearing loose
socks you guys know loose socks yeah
yeah everybody else looks cool with them
but I I feel like I feel cringy wearing
them but when I see other people wearing
them I get like excited like wow that
that person has confidence you know I
think blue socks are really popular in
Japan within like students with their
school Daniel for them uh like back in
the day I don't know if they really do
it that much anymore this year but they
used to combine really really long loose
socks with their schooling uniforms and
they they
um make them short like this so that
there's like these these layers yeah
it's a cute element there yeah okay
right here unless you're writing Fashion
Police we will
we will
[Music]
okay next stop
yeah thank you really creative love it
next one is this one this is from oh
okay or I I say is
you just entered the room okay yeah why
u k i k there we go Chad this is uh this
is a bold move right here um yeah the
white is actually both like yeah I mean
I feel like um I wouldn't like I would
be like a little bit
um like taken aback if the shirt wasn't
as long and I just saw like from the
back this dude rocking like completely
white like jacket and jeans but because
like that shirt is like pulled down more
like you see there's like the layer
thing going on you're like damn that
dude's got fashion sense yeah I saw a
lot of um people combining your marriage
Galley with mostly black clothes so this
one really stood out to me because they
tried something different uh so the
white it is very bold but it works I
think and I also like the jacket it
looks like a jeans a white jeans jacket
with something on the arm as well yeah
and some ripped ripped elements in the
pants as well
he even fell down or he did it on
purpose
yeah I like it he probably he probably
loves you so much Kelly that he kneeled
every day in front of you and then it
turns out like this oh man I'm sorry
dude if you want to refund I can't give
it to you because I didn't sell you the
jeans but I do want to say really quick
I like your painting in the background
kind of looks like we got some skeletons
like Nightmare Before Christmas [\h__\h]
going on in the back I like it
it fits me indeed indeed
and we can't anything to say
he looks very confident he does but I
said shed they they do be called
all right Fashion Police rate your uh
write this outfit please now yes ma'am
yes ma'am
okay I'm setting up the Discord by the
way okay
okay yeah
um
[Music]
next submission thank you Kelly
there we go I think it's
um also another bold one because of the
pastel pink uh sweater underneath
cool Vans
ankles too almost
ankles
I'm also a big fan of like hacking the
universe and I feel like I would like
this is like this is almost kind of like
hacker core to Mecca core like yeah like
I'd roll up into into school and like
hit like the computer lab in this outfit
is that a thing yeah
no that's it's something I made up
literally two seconds ago but like
um like that aesthetic maybe it's just
the glasses and like the hood pulled up
but like I like it it's like it's my jam
right there I wonder if he matched the
background on purpose
because it's also pastel pink yeah there
is kind of like a and yeah with like the
teal and the blue kind of like popping
off yeah I like it yes it works well I
think uh so I just wanted did I say the
name I didn't say the name uh jet
slashed Jet Jet j e t thank you chat
slashed for this submission
he's gonna hack our rating we need to
arrest him oh gosh all right that's
that's uh that's a ticket for you okay I
placed my rating oh my cat you good
yes I
I'm trying to I'm trying to set up this
chord and then
um the stream is still bad quality so
I'm just gonna look at the pictures just
look at the pictures I'm posting
separately okay all righty thank you
next up we have this person
oh my God I told you your favorite
submissions everybody get in my car
we're going to the MCR concert let's go
[Laughter]
I'm not sure how to pronounce lechu
leche l e c h u l e c h e
I like their sister you liked
accessories yeah yeah the fish on the
arms
yes there's so many accessories on her
head so she's wearing a tiara
yeah oh my God princess
oh my gosh I love the fish I've seen him
personally on like the arms I love stuff
like that yeah like baggy fishnet stuff
on arms
would never wear that but she rocks it
rocking it
looks [\h__\h] yeah
very very very cute
um fashion police would you please place
your rating on this uh cutie patootie I
could I could see her like beating the
[\h__\h] out of like everyone
just like just like just like kicking
you like kicking your ass in the
schoolyard
fan
beat me up she says
she's she's actually really sweet
yeah yeah that's the thing that's the
Gap Moe which is why I'm really trying
intimidating but sweet
exactly right yeah all right next up we
have this person unfortunately not a
full body shot but okay I think it's
great anyway
cool skirt yeah Oni I love the the devil
horns on the hat and that's my own hat
yeah yes my little golden one it says
demon on the cap in Japanese and a
really baggy Cali Style Parker to go
with it yeah cute fishnets too I love
dang I'm giving I'm giving everyone high
ratings today
that's okay good is your category do you
like the blue Hood with like oh the
loose Hood with the um like tighter
stuff yeah yes that's something I like
too I don't like to wear everything
super loose but if it's like a
combination of some inner items that are
tight and then some uh like baggy a
jacket a baggy coat or so yeah that's
something I would wear too I feel like
it depends on the day for me like if I'm
going out to the studio I'll wear like
all baggy but still kind of like
fashionable like black clothing but if
I'm going out with like the girls for
like um a shopping day or something like
that or we're going on a day trip then
I'll wear like a huge baggy jacket but
then under it I'll have like like uh
like tights or like super tight leggings
and I'll wear like like combat boots and
stuff like that
um yeah that's that's my style yeah
that's what I'm doing but I I like that
too
have you noticed the pattern here
there's like a lot of people who are
wearing some sort of fish nets in your
category
right it's very popular
oh okay
interesting
this one seems to be of your liking
so okay next
up
sending it in there we go is this person
yo yada
oh my God
and the boots
black lipstick though with the with the
black fingernails except for the one in
the middle that's pink so oh yeah oh my
God I didn't notice that did you run out
of uh the nail paint or or is it on
purpose because you have pink hair Cali
oh that is true that is true maybe some
very cool tattoo by the way I love the
skull it like fits perfectly with the
whole aesthetic the skull and the Roses
like it's the you're Mori Vibe I dig it
and but I'm wondering if the feather
earrings are on purpose and the hint to
me
it looks kind of like their earrings too
if you look in the background uh there's
like Cali posters and also a Kiana
poster oh
I think I see a Cali and Kiana poster
combination oh cute yeah it's adorable I
love that
yeah
you're very cute nice glasses by the way
you're Chad and the flannel shirt around
her hips too I feel like the flannel
shirt is something in that color
something that Kelly would wear
yeah definitely but only around maybe
around my waist possibly or like if it
was really big then I'd like wear it in
like a jacket form
yeah
um oh wait I just saw it's a bit hard to
see but uh I think uh around the neck
that's a Cali keychain not necessarily
oh yeah the key chain though you see
that I'm there I'm there with you you
can wear keychains like a necklace why
the hell not dangling right above your
chest yo very good this person is called
Platinum K9 by the way
[Music]
yeah yeah
yeah thank you put a lot of thought into
this outfit I think
yeah damn gloves are sick too by the way
yeah I used to wear gloves like that in
high school really like I think yeah I
think that they're like Timeless
honestly depending on your Vibe but not
saying you have to be in high school to
wear like gloves or anything I'm just
saying that was like my vibe then but
damn I respect that respect you would
really intimidate me though if I saw you
in school of those uh gloves
alrighty next up we have this uh Chad
absolute Chad showing off my shoes
my man those bright red shoes are
kicking though
no is that a job
yes indeed oh my God my dude is
literally just holding up the Jordans
yes
Bears on his his left hand uh what fits
the outfit the most I think because they
have like a magenta uh pink in it all
right yeah yeah I think that's the ones
I would have chosen but they're all cool
yeah no it's really nice shoes and also
you don't see it well on this picture
um but the the glasses are like like
pretty like I have to say fake uh
um they have like they're not like not
as thin as your typical glasses they
have like a pretty thick layer of like a
gold frame around them yeah you only see
it from the side though yeah but those
are some really cool cool glasses that
he has to run absolute hype Beast
deadbeat and that's what I would call
this yes he does look like Morpheus like
Morpheus from The Matrix oh my God he's
such a red pill you
I love like like those kind of glasses
that are like round and like kind of
small I I I I want to wear those glasses
I think it's really cool me too this
person is
sorry oh no I just said I wish I could
look good in the circle glass yeah this
would be cool yeah right now you have a
very special shape of glasses that I put
on you
yeah oh yeah that's right your Shades
those look nice on you thank you yeah
wow this person is called rulesuki
r-u-l-e-z-u-k-i thank you for your
submission uh we love your shoes he must
have a whole closet of shoe collections
please
so I can rate your Jordans yes
all righty thank you police uh officers
uh oh Sherry
okay the next one is the last one for
this category
there we go here it is
cute yeah man I love you you look like
somebody that like
go ahead Kiara I I love the the short uh
pastel pink pants because they match
their cap as well and uh it's like I saw
so nothing against it but I saw so many
uh people wearing either like normal
jeans or black uh uh pants so this kind
of stood out to me because of the color
combination yeah I like it I like it I
feel like um if I was passing you like
in this in like the school hauls I'd
like give you like a high five yeah man
because um the the school that I went to
um a lot of dudes actually wore like
shirts uh shorts like that oh um like
that same length and like color and
stuff like that and like the same shoes
and sock combinations so like that was
the vibe I got I want to give you like a
high five you know yeah it was so
friendly
yeah yeah and uh very much a summer
outfit oh yeah nice buttons as well yeah
talking for summer and the pants match
really well with a hat too yes yes
perfect color combination so you were
lucky to have that in your closet I
suppose damn noise uh Fashion Police
this one this person is called serious
serious Tony zet series Tony zet please
place your ratings on this last
submission for uh Kelly's uh category
all right
foreign
you know what yeah you're right though
all right Kelly you can uh decide later
which one was your favorite uh yes ma'am
yeah we'll reveal all that later but
next category is
a category
uh there we go this person is called one
second
seven color Symphony yes uh I feel like
Amber's category generally had a lot of
very friendly and comfortable
um outfit coordinations so yeah they
look all like I don't know like good
friends to me
so
yeah what do you think I'm a cat
I think this is the most confident photo
I've seen yeah
[Laughter]
very great pose and I love the the beige
combination with the comfy cardigan and
the beige shoes so I think with Amish
yellow
um beige always works really really well
okay I'm seeing the photo now oh my God
no no no no it's okay I was looking at
the stream as well my dude this is like
yeah if you walked out just into the
world like I don't think like I think
that people who know will know and that
there's something kind of sick about
that and that cardigan is so like Amit
um
I like it nice I love beige I have a lot
of beige in my closet too
unlike you guys probably you have beige
you wear beige I don't own a single
beige item oh my God
I threw it out
beige is nice right
no I like yellow it makes it it's a
happy color yeah yeah yeah and and that
um I think especially the pixel T-shirts
they work so well if you if you want to
like wear a merch but not stand out too
much with it so yeah thank you for that
decent design that doesn't stand out too
much it doesn't out us immediately as
whole lot of English fans
exactly for the shy ones Among Us yeah
yeah uh seven color Symphony please rate
this uh outfit for us Fashion Police
[Music]
foreign
like that is sick as well actually
uh maroon maroon maroon might be kind of
more on the brown side like a reddish
brown someone says brick
yeah not maroon maybe like brownish red
which is Brick yeah I like that I love
all the different shades like but you
didn't put too many shades of brown it's
like just the right amount like there's
like two there's like uh it's all in the
same color spectrum I feel like I put it
in like the same color yeah it works
well together and I also like the type
of jacket that he's wearing
um looks comfortable and baggy enough to
wear on top of a a sweater like that I
have problems with that because usually
when I wear a bulky sweater like that my
jackets don't fit well on top of it but
yeah this works nice nice layers too
which is really nice yeah
yes
he's got some style also
the crony copter at the top uh really
catches my eye it goes like
Chrome very faster yes please rate uh
Arty make cries submission I guess I'm
the only one left brain move
yeah we got all righty thank you for
your submission next up yeah we have
this time I'm gonna post it don't worry
there we go we have Brian gotcha man now
this one is simple this one is simple
but the pose it looks like he's having
fun yeah you know yeah
maybe not tear some [\h__\h] down but like
just go run through the mall you know
it looks like he's doing pumpkin right
now it's a perfect outfit for core
did he jump down or flight upstairs yeah
I think it's time traveling maybe like
Emma he's trying to jumping into a time
portal
I like those because it has like a
sporty and summer style uh like an early
summer when it's like not too not too
warm but not too cold so he's ready for
both maybe if there's like a little bit
of a Breezy Wind going on then you can
protect himself with the Parker his
ankles might be a little bit cold though
oh no yeah
but he gets extra points for me
[Laughter]
I just I just wanna I just want to point
out the details no that's okay gotta
protect your ankles because you could
get sick you gotta you could catch a
cold if you don't protect them
exactly
okay oh that was Brian Gotcha Man by the
way Brian with a Y
b-r-y-a-n gotcha man yes thank you for
your submission and next time Brian look
at this don't those gotchas get you this
one I think really cute this person had
a lot of outfits they made like a
million submissions but I liked this one
the most because it kind of gives me a
retro uh
um Vibe and kind of like an office lady
Vibe as well with a tight skirt and the
checkered pattern love it absolutely
love it
I feel like she'd be like I'm his
assistant or something like that it's
cute I love it what do you think I'm
okay adorable I I think it's cute yes
pretty
pretty pretty nice check her skirt nice
good move I think it's a really original
and creative uh outfit I have not seen
anything like this else in the
submission yeah and the hats that I I
can't wear a hat like that but works so
well with the rest of the outfit I think
the Hat matches the skirt from like
style wise I don't know what what year I
would put this is this like kind of like
the skirt kind of gives me I don't know
70s 80s wipes I don't know
mm-hmm
yes 70s 50 yes
that's maybe when I'm getting a diner
Vibe too yeah but like playing playing
pool or something
oh yeah I like that very cute this
person is called uh c a
a i y n something like
I don't know don't know how to pronounce
it
please rate it officers
[Music]
retro out of ten yeah that's a good
rating I love it very cute I wonder I
wonder how I would say about these
outfits kinda wish she would be watching
I'll send her the photos later yeah
she's sure she would be excited to see
that all right thank you for yours so be
sure next up we have this very confident
looking oh man
read me a story book tell me your
wisdoms
very sophisticated
wow what you're reading what's your
reading what's the book it's Sherlock
Holmes
I love the shoes holy [\h__\h] I love them
yeah they're beautiful
dark brown leather shoes with the with
the really bright so sole you call it
soul
so
so the bottom part of it
I think soles are inside the shoe oh
uh uh outside salt outside
that's it that's it
it's called outer Soul outer Soul oh it
really is
there we go you have a nice stool dude
and if you look closely the glasses are
not perfectly round they are like uh
kind of what do you call it oh octagon
that's it yes and the watch is leather
or something
you looked at the watch I didn't even
notice that
that traveler a teammate must always
know the time after all right it's time
for Amish dream or else it's cool but
yeah I really like the the look he
definitely tried to get a look going
here also with the with the shirt
underneath very sophisticated please
rate this sophisticated uh investigator
look please Fashion Police
I'm a fan indeed
I like like some people really have like
a theme going on and put like a lot of
thought into their outfits so I
appreciate that thank you guys for these
creative submissions that was diet's way
[Music]
d-i-e-t-w-a-v-e thank you for your
submission next time
cute unfortunately not a full body shot
but I had to put it in because it was so
cute
the half overall look
so cute oh my God look at all the Bubba
plushie
[Music]
on the phone I'm really curious to know
if that
um overall goes down to uh sorry to say
the ankles or if it's like cut above the
knees I'm really curious but you need to
tell me exploding dogs is the name of
this person exploding on the bar dogs
don't blow up the dogs please don't hurt
Bubba please
yeah
Bubba did nothing wrong
don't hurt bubble but
um I think it's that's probably not um I
don't know if it's just a filter or
something but that's probably not um a
white but an off-white or something
color and I think it it works really
nice with the shirt and I love how
people make an overall work like this
when they um like fold like that side
over I don't have the straps on both
sides you know what I mean
and it's perfect to show the embroidery
yes good point good point big brain here
definitely knows how to style clothes
this person exploding dogs let's rate it
and
please show us a full body picture later
on I want to see what how you would
combine it like with shoes like what
shoes would you wear with that I want to
see give me a full outfit
please thank you exploding dogs for the
submission next up we have uh
there's gonna be some really cute
submissions now this one
oh my goodness
with the stickers you said something you
would wear yeah
perhaps perhaps
um the hat and a skirt you would I think
yeah I love the hat I love the frilly
um frilly Ruffles around the hat and
differently Ruffles around the skirt and
also the frilly ruffles at the socks and
the shoes
I really like the hat is so cute yeah
it's so cute
very perfect like it combines
um the like two Styles the Parker is
like so casual but the girly style the
frilly girly style
um kind of gives me
um Morty girl Vibes have you ever heard
of that
I think I'm using it correctly no I
don't think it's like a Japanese uh
clothing style I think or like call it
cottage style perhaps yeah I've
certainly seen a lot of a lot of um
people in Japan dressed like this so
yeah definitely very cute very stylish I
like and your hair also kind of matches
the whole vibe yeah just a side note
really really cute this person is called
fuzzy fuzzy on the bar uh draws
underscore on the bar on the on the bar
on the underscore underscore fuzzy
underscore draws yeah
I know it is a very girly Vibe with the
with the way you framed it
love it
Cali we have some very similar ratings
mostly I know right I've noticed that
yes ah thank you for your submission
thank you police officers I think we
have to arrest this person for being too
cute
you're going to jail tonight
take your hat though
yeah all right next submission also
cutie pie
yeah
h-a-n-k-i-r-i wait why a yes
what kind of hair
yeah okay we haven't heard much from you
what do you think about this one about
it
and the uh hair is cool and uh
necklace is cool with the wreath and
it's gold and the shoes are cool
and the skirt is cool um
[Laughter]
the purse is cool yeah
I I think what I like the most is the
the pastel yellow socks sticking out of
the boots
um the ankle boots yeah
um I love it when socks stick out like
that especially with like a short skirts
um I think I I used to really love where
when I was wearing skirts I used to love
uh to layer um over any socks with it
but nowadays I feel like I'm much more
tend to style it like this with short uh
socks yeah I don't know why I like to
wear show my knees these days I guess uh
when I wear a skirt like that yeah yeah
I'm really cute I love all of it I'm I I
think there's a little bit of a
um of a confusion in what season it is
because the skirt looks very thin but
still I love how she combined it anyway
I mean I wear I wear shorts with like
huge jackets during the summer so I mean
I don't let the weather dictate how I
dress I see where you're coming from
hell yeah
all right and oh I also really love
quotes like this I I love coats way more
than like those puffy jackets this is
definitely more of my style
trench coach well that's uh is that
really would you really call that a
transcript isn't a trench coat more like
a different fabric
I don't know it's a coat oh it's a more
like a fuzzy looking coat not a I don't
think it's necessarily a trench coat but
yeah uh h-a-n-cut k i r i y a hankiria
gets uh the points now
good stuff points for you point points
secret points and the next submission is
the last one for this category
[Music]
wowza there we go there we go there we
go there it is
my man no I love that game
oh man right there yes again a lot of
bears but I feel like that that's just
like so easy to combine with this pastel
yellow color to use all the beige tones
yeah and the hat it looks so well it's
like a safari hat more not not a how
they have right
a gardening hat a garden a gardening
head yeah this meaning but it does look
really good
um and I love like how it matches the
jacket perfectly and the red in your
shoes is like a nice little like patch
it like pops you know it like it's like
surprising but like a good kind of
surprising because I feel like the the
color red that you chose to go with this
outfit is like the perfect color
again too yeah the glasses yeah I think
that the whole outfit
matches his personality I don't know I
don't know his personality but kind of
Vibe yeah this atmosphere is
around him and makes everything work so
well together yeah yeah it really works
like I don't know if you really wear
clothes usually like this but I have to
say it works for you it was [\h__\h] it
hell yeah good stuff hell yeah
this person is called tiger MC
FTW tiger MC for the win yes please rate
this submission for us uh police thanks
tiger thank you peace 9 out of 10.
a tough one
okay okay there we go thank you all
submissions have been looked at the next
category is let's take a look
in a category and we start with some
intimidating uh people oh my God
thank you
this is who I imagine two of them
and they're matching and it's like
they're all related Maybe
they're like twins
such strength oh my God they're they're
the ones who are gonna beat their [\h__\h]
out of chat I'm scared mommy pick me up
oh maybe they're super friendly though
look at those little smiles
to protect you forever yes oh my gosh
incredible I'm a big fan indeed
um the the takodachi category I see also
kind of similar to a lot of cute
submissions
um and also very very
friendly and confident people I see here
yeah so this person is called uh what is
Twitter is called Boba ice cream
with double double A yeah nice I love
this Inna sweater so much you don't even
understand
it's one of my favorite items out of the
whole collection yeah I love the color I
love the design on the sleeves it's so
simple so cute you know very Inna very
Inna indeed so please rate uh
paste and taco failed yeah that's the
vibe I get from this
thank you for your submission next up we
have oh couple uh shots you
so cute
oh a lot of pastel colors very cute they
wrote in their tweets that they're never
gonna wear these socks again but
um I respect them for putting it
together in the coordination like that
mm-hmm
what do you think oh look at
I like the socks though yes
socks actually this is so sweet I like
that they're almost matching yes the
partner look is so cute
yeah I love when people go out and part
and look I feel like I only really see
it in Japan or like Asian countries in
general not really in like Europe at all
or I don't know about America but
um I I love when people go out like this
is cute matching with your friends
adorable the shoes match too the colors
yeah they really put a lot of thought
into this yeah they had a lot of really
cute pictures by the way so you guys
should check out the Tweet it's
um the Twitter is ciao Maine five uh
ciao
[Music]
c-i-a-o-m-e-i-n-5 thank you for your
submission please
yes
okay
all right thank you Sherry fake Sheriff
you're welcome next time we have this so
this one
very cute
hard again
it does have lace around the collar
around the shoulders yeah yeah
um
yeah sweet look and a dark and a purple
skirt as well underneath and the shirt
is tucked in you still see Ina's face it
almost looks like Ina is wearing that
skirt
yeah giving me like cute artist Vibes I
like it and I mean again
yes sorry oh the mask has the um the
beads on them oh I didn't see it so well
yes oh is that attached to the mask the
candy yeah
and I like the striped socks layered on
top of the tights I like when people
layer their uh fashion items like this
very comfy looking just like Inna is so
it fits it fits Ina's personality too I
think very cute oh this one is called uh
c-o-s-i-n-e apple
cocine apple cosine Apple cosine Apple
indeed yeah that's a math term
what's the figure they have in the back
though
I feel like this photo was taken at like
a hotel at a convention yeah this
totally looks like a convention look now
I see it yeah yeah I see people going to
a convention like this hundred percent
please rate Fashion Police
oh there might be some
um
maybe some accidental photos in this
folder I think Cali's Sheriff had for
some reason I saved in this folder
prize howdy there you go okay next up is
this one
uh I love the skirt layering and it
almost looks like because of the layers
it looks like the the sweater goes all
the way to the bottom because it has the
same color but obviously that's part of
the skirt beautiful layers
you can't tell from the picture it looks
like a big dress yes yes
optical illusion optical illusion yeah
optical illusion yes yes
the text is backwards so it looks like
it's saying hot
I really like it I love this skirt I
want that skirt where did you buy it
tell me I need to know
from the person
um laurinae
[Music]
l-y-r-i-i-i-n-a-e yes I can spell am I
gonna win a spelling bee like this oh I
I never would have took part in
something like that I want to take part
um yeah I mean like you're right on the
hype
[Music]
okay let's around all right thank you
thank you for your submission very cute
go into cute jail oh
here
that's weird oh and what comes after
that oh that's right because OBS has
like a stupid ugh
like a uh OBS cone like a maximum of how
many pictures you can put in one folder
thing in uh wait we'll fix that I'll get
rid of this I'll get rid of that I'll
get rid of that take your time yeah
all right sorry I'm going through this
really quickly
there it is
sorry about that we're not writing the
hat today
[Music]
oh there we go look at this
this is a UPS uniform oh my gosh
this is the Chad right here
going to work like this undercover yeah
laughs
always wearing that in a merge to always
have her right at your heart close to
your heart yeah and if you look closely
I think that's like some kind of work
related pouch but there's a lot of metal
on
um badge on top of it
so good yeah
but of course a UPS employee must stay
uh Anonymous that's why the face is cut
off completely we don't we don't want to
get you fired or anything uh but yeah
Big Ups
big up like UPS pickups Big Ups
they're infiltrating UPS oh undercover
Taco eats delivery for UPS damn they
have a big collaboration going on I
suppose
um
a little expansion all right please
write this person it's Mendiola Chris
[Music]
m-e-n-d-i-o-l-a k-r-i-s
thank you for your submission and I'm
happy I'm happy there's some chats in
UPS
I wish I knew like how to sorry go ahead
oh my there's a lag so like every time
you start saying
go ahead go ahead go ahead
uh I forgot I forgot what I'm gonna say
um
I guess what was I gonna say no you both
forgot
damn it yeah damn it maybe you'll think
of it later
I love this so much I had to choose one
picture but the other picture was so
funny too the dog
is fashionable
those are cool glasses yes
dog sized glasses or are they made for
dogs or are they like children size
glasses not made for dogs but oh my god
dog made glasses
um I have a question is that a skirt and
the wind is blowing or are those like a
special color
in this case the wind worked in this
photo like that that looks like pants
yeah but I think actually I think it's a
whole dress because it seems like to
have the same color as what sticks out
of the uh at the neck and at the arms I
think it might be a really long comfy
dress maybe looks like this type of
fashion yeah
yes like very free-spirited yeah I think
in order to layer something like this
you really need to have like a fashion
sense I think usually you wouldn't dare
to do that but uh it works if you know
what you're doing
she has a style going on there the boots
it's like a oh it's it's like I don't
know interesting style the boots are
kind of like I don't know how to how to
describe the style of the boots
they're like they remind me of combat
guns that like not edgy they're like not
like the edgy kind with like a bunch of
metal parts and like spikes and stuff
like that they're like kind of um I
don't want to say hipster because like
that's like it's become like kind of a
shitty word I feel like or like but I I
don't know it's like it's hard to
describe aesthetic
modern it's it's like hard to explain
yes
very fashionable and I love that you
dragged your dog into this
yeah I'm sure the dog appreciates the
the glasses based on your Shadow the sun
is definitely shining directly in your
dog's eyes yeah
[Music]
uh this person is called Never Nori with
double I never Nori and naughty n n e v
e r n o r i i please place your writings
thank you yeah
okay next up thank you Sheriff like I
said we have I think it should be this
one yes okay
oh overall overall let's go yeah overall
oh my God that works so well with this
sweater yes it does sweaters under
overalls work surprisingly well guys
give it a try give it a try I love this
kind of short overalls I like long
overalls but I think I like short
overalls more yeah it's a cute early
summer look
um what do you think I'm a cat yeah yeah
that's cute very cute
at the top of of the head you cannot
really see it well but yeah it's a
little Taco Time
yeah and the pose is very good too
confident pose
this one is from Primo 97. yes sir Kelly
that's okay I love overall looks that
have like really um like high like cut
like high cut off and then like you're
wearing sneakers with like short socks
yeah like that's the aesthetic idea you
see so much in my leg I don't like
wearing it but I like seeing people wear
it I would wear it like that definitely
yeah you totally would yeah yeah it's
very um a casual comfy a little bit
sporty look to it very friendly again
the taco Dutch is all look so friendly I
love it please rate your uh of course
right is Fashion Police
we will
please alrighty thank you erased it next
up we have this photo again we're now
writing the left person please uh I'm
posting it again oh that's easy I
already know what I want to give this oh
you've already thought about it
um
I love the skirt the pattern of the
skirt it's a light a blue
um color I really think it works with
the pastel uh Violet and the white over
knee socks very very very cute and even
the mask matches they both matched their
Max masks to the outfit adorable yeah I
love the stalks with the white boots the
white sauce with the white yeah I love
the boots yeah the boots are so cute
yeah they are I rarely see people
wearing boots like that but they're so
cute you wear them with such confidence
I love it yes great at the posts
confidence out of 10. confidence is very
cute this one is again from trancing
shoes uh we're gonna rate them
separately well yeah those shoes are
entrancing beautiful enough enough
listen this is like shitty puns it's
okay yes always welcome shitty pun's
always welcome
um rating
[Music]
yes okay
and then I think we have two more
submissions for this category uh next up
is this uh unfortunately cannot see
um what she wears uh around her legs
here but
um because I had to choose uh one
picture but she actually wears I saw it
on the differ but she actually wears
um like mismatching over knee socks like
one is black and one is white and they
have a they look really cute just
imagine something really cute underneath
there
cute that sounds adorable yes nice view
yes wow the cute Taco that you had look
at the Hat yeah I like the Hat yeah
the collar popping out of the area with
the with some kind of badge uh on top of
the color color yeah I can't say that
word Kelly how are you say it very good
color
yeah like that and then the color color
and color
yeah color and color okay
I don't think she's wearing some kind of
floral earrings I think but also purple
so matching the color again the color
yeah
I think yeah that's a that's a good
point actually
and I like the belt around the skirt
like it I don't the the skirt doesn't
really need it but some people just put
a belt on it because because of the uh
for for the sake of a fashion accessory
so works really nice I like it very cute
and damn wait I thought it was first of
all that was the her real hair but now
that I think about it it almost looks
like a Ina Ena
Cosplay wig I'm not sure oh I think it
is away yeah
but it's
cute
very nice yeah okay please write this
Fashion Police this one is from ushi
pudding
and pudding they submitted some photos
for other categories as well the other
members um but I personally liked this
Ina outfit the most so thank you for
this beautiful yes beautiful submission
the photo gets extra points too
definitely your styling and profiling
hell yeah all right uh I think
this is the last one this is the last
one all right
cute ah you want to jump in the car with
me in the deadbeat
she wants to join let's go
fish snacks The Comeback of the fishnets
oh yeah the hair is fancy too they're so
cool
so cool I had the skirt I like the skirt
very much
not pattern I love it it's not normal
fishing at the top
top tights it's a has a interesting
pattern to it as well stands out very
much
what do you think I'm a cat
it's cool it also has a huge edgy choker
I like it this might be my face oh
really out of the out of the taco
daddies well it's probably because this
one is more black the other ones are
mostly pastel I mean you know myself
okay this one is from under by sherberty
sherbet tea uh
s-h-e-r-b-e-t what
I wonder if that's just a light or if
that's no it might just be the light it
looked like purple purple colors in the
hair but I think that's the light from
the left side but it does look like she
has like blonde and brown uh colors in
the hair cool and like some pink in
there yeah yeah I'm not sure it's an ice
cream oh
chocolate
alrighty rated Fashion Police is the
last inner submission
um yay
[Music]
we're generally giving such good ratings
everyone's addressing so well I haven't
gone below five but if I missed
all right the exclamation Oh this is the
Kiara
um category oh there are some Mimi
pictures in my category
um I couldn't help but uh put them in uh
what you see on the head is something I
recently created in the Stream that's my
my drawing of an employee and he is
carrying eggs
there's just eggs there oh my God JoJo
Pauls Kelly
it could be a JoJo pose actually it
might be yeah I think it is I'm pretty
sure it is
well um besides the meme value I like
the somewhat high-waisted pants uh with
the tucked interior I feel like my this
t-shirt this specific t-shirt works so
well when it's tucked in
um I think that's when it looks the best
and uh I like the jacket on top of it
what do you think girls
very confident
[Laughter]
it's interesting because the more formal
pants with like a less formal uh jacket
very interesting and then you go back to
less formal with the the Nikes so it's
like you get the full experience of
casual to formal to Casual it's
intriguing they look good together I'll
give it an egg out of 10 too just like
um
this person is called frozen chicken a
chicken with
c-h-i-k-i-n thank you for your
submission's a bit faster because
there's so many actually next up we have
this person love love love love love
love love love love love
love
adorable yeah
colors yeah yeah and the jeans jacket
around the waist so cute looks like she
would be going to school like this maybe
comfy school day
um this is very well put together yes
very well put together the skirt too and
she also has one of those chokers I love
chokers as you can see I always wear
chokers in my outfits yes okay Papa
always gives me those chokers
these jackets around the waist are the
best yes I agree
jackets with that pattern of the skirt
what do you call that pattern again
[Music]
something like that I feel like it works
so well with the jeans uh everything
everything I feel like the whole style
it works so well yeah it's probably
style a model like this oh yeah
this one is from Gwen on the bar moon
g-e-w-i
g-w-y-n on the bar Moon thank you
submission please write fashion sense
yes indeed
I'm so hungry I didn't eat breakfast
[Music]
next up
oh dramatic clothing I think like a lot
a lot of people use the jeans to combine
my shirt and I think usually I don't
like jeans that much but it works really
well with the shirt I think kind of has
a retro look
I like the fit of the jeans a lot
yes kind of wide but by rolling it up at
the angles it makes it a bit more
tighter at the bottom so it looks like
it fits really well and I think as as
like some sort of belt uh they use some
kind of white string like it almost
looks like a shoelace but I don't think
it's a shoelace but a ribbon or
something you see that on around his
waist oh I like that very original yeah
yeah and also um I like that the the
orange of the shoes like still suits the
color of your hair on the shirt yes yes
he has nice matching of the colors here
thank you this one is from Jumbo on the
bar J and B
please write Fashion Police
yes ma'am thank you
um please don't be surprised about the
next picture
um I was forced by kfp to put this in
oh
hahaha
yeah it's just a KF shrimp
no no it's just a fish that infiltrated
kfp
um oh my God the name is
Sakana is a
fish and the hint at my name
takanasikiana oh my dude in the gym
though yes
is so confident and I like how how
because the the sweater is wrapped
around the butt and the logo is on the
butt it's like standing out there thank
you for promoting KFC
wow I absolutely I have no words
[Laughter]
yeah yes this one is actually the
special the the Twitter is a kfp soul
s-o-u thank you for your submission
it is definitely uh worth a meme award
um I think that could but that should be
a different category I already planned
on having a a meme category so this
should go there to be honest
um I remembered what I was gonna say
back then I wish that I knew whether to
rate on stylistic choice or like how
much it made me laugh like everything
everything
fine
next up oh dear Cali
what oh my God I'll leave it to you
shy guys
let's check hold on a minute yes I'm
surprised you react to shy guy isn't
there something else
well yeah my okay my eyesight went down
the picture so give me a bit too bye
Jackson yes
it's a Tupac and um they got the
bandanas around I think we can put this
one in the main category too though
um no I'm I know what my rating is
10 out of 10 right
I don't know
um is that are you eating canes Wait no
that's that's it's canes but with
Kiara's campus
yeah it's it's Kiara fried Phoenix but
it uh it's uh probably near canes which
means that what is that you're just a
legend you're just a legend that's all
Kane's is my favorite fried chicken
restaurant I
mean Are you seriously not commenting on
the Shrek Crocs
I I did I commented them the first thing
after shy guy oh they're beautiful I
thought I was I didn't know those
existed I like the colors are so funny
because they have a necklace and like a
bandana thingy around
like what
it was Vlogs the greatest outfit I've
seen today
this one is from Elsie Lapin LC on the
board
[Laughter]
incredible but I'm seriously putting
this in the meme category
um but you you can keep the oh my rating
doesn't change yes okay for the meme
category I'll give it this rating
um
okay next up next up thank you for the
submission next up we have this wow wow
wow wow legs
yep oh my God
surprisingly I haven't seen the our
shirts styled like this before until now
um like in a knot like that very cute
very summery and I I love how the shoes
and the bag have that teal color that I
also have in my in my hair and in other
parts of my outfits uh because like
usually I have this orange teal thing
going on and I think normally orange and
teal are difficult or not the first
thing you would combine but it works so
well and I love the the short uh white
tight jeans love everything about it
cute what do you think very very cool
yup looks good yeah
the colors it looks nice together it
looks so fresh doesn't it
yes it almost looks like a festival
outfit
you dress like um
like my like my mom and I mean that like
the most complimentary way because my
mom is a super like this is like my
mom's kind of she's a she's like a West
uh a West Coast lady and like this is
how she tries to dress to like get hip
with the the times I guess like she'll
dress like this
um and uh it's very cute because like
walking around she sees like a lot of uh
girls dressed like this so you've got
like that summery fun fashion
um going out to like have a nice lunch
with the with the ladies feel
also I love how you added the Kiana
keychain to your pants very cute
accessory so cute and I love it okay
please rate this person it's a
nana17423779 that's numbers
you know it's a compliment because my
mom is a really fashionable listen
she must be very fashionable now this is
really really cute I like how you styled
the T-shirt very much
all right next one is kind of kind of me
me again
kind of
[Laughter]
killed kills Ronald wig
and short The Rock and love it yeah I
think the clothing choice is very
interesting what do you think
[Laughter]
it's a 10 out of 10 out of 10.
I mean honestly though I think that
that's a good thing as a clothing
designer to like like everything because
like you have to design clothes for like
people that aren't into just your sense
of fashion so I think it's cool that
you're like you think everything is is
good because everybody's got different
styles so yeah yeah hiccups dude oh
actually
um I see something uh interesting the
nails also like that other submission we
had is mostly in this case orange but
then one teal nail you see it like just
the one the top left yeah that's the
ones cute detail and I like the I mean
this is not really something I would
wear at all but I love the the bag the
side bag on the hips and the kind of
looks a little bit like bathing shorts a
little bit
oh yeah I think I can see that
I feel like almost you would rescue me
if I was drowning in the ocean
I'm wondering no this is
listen wait are you oh okay you're in I
think you're in your home I was you go
to the store no that's not like take
your that's like a Disney Store oh okay
I was gonna say no did you like go to a
clothing store with your omocat merch
and then try on the clothes at the
clothing store and then take a picture
with it and then put them back
really good idea but I don't think they
sell those clothes in a Disney shop I
love it I don't think so yeah I don't
think so so it must be personal items
this person is called pumpkin pie cheese
p-a-i-c-h-i thank you for your
submission please reach everybody
good stuff
then then we would have three contenders
for the meme kind of going
yeah I think I think it because of the
wig it needs to go there
or you can put it there yeah let me
change my score then okay because it's
cool but like yeah the meme gives it
like an extra point it does
all right and then uh you ready
next up is
I have a lot of a lot of girl
submissions
[Music]
jeans jacket that's kind of frizzy on
the bottom
distressed yeah I love how the arm the
sleeves are longer than the like main
part of the jacket you know what I mean
yeah gives a nice leveling look to it it
has like levels like stairs very cute
and uh I love this skirt also the
t-shirt is tucked in but it's still like
kind of pulled out so it's still it's
tucked in but it still is on top of the
skirt it looks cute
Acres fit well yeah yeah maybe maybe
some ankle socks would have been nice
like orange ankle stuff would have been
cute I think or teal even
some ideas but yeah
and the jacket is so so wide so comfy
looking I don't know single jeans jacket
do you guys have jeans jackets in your
closet yeah I have two yeah
damn ah I don't have any I need to get
one and style my clothes like this I'm
gonna give it a try thank you for
inspiring me
this one is from Korean on Queen on the
bar Bridget on the bar X
thank you for your submission and please
erase this Fashion Police
jean jacket out of ten I would say
how'd you know
it I'm starting to I'm starting to
predict you I'm okay
I'm starting to predict you the next
person is has two outfits
from each other so oh underscore sorry
the next ones are very different for
each other but I wanted to judge both of
them
um sure this person purposefully uh
styled the first one kind of after me
apparently
oh cute yeah cuteness
wait I think I know who this is yeah
it's uh
she did the the deadbeat Adam Sandler
kfp apron with the gun cooking picture
baby oh my God
she does do a lot of uh cosplays that's
what she's also wearing the Kiara
Cosplay wig with the braids matching
we're matching yeah
this is literally so good I love the
coat
coat the red color and I just love
quotes and that style and and then
wearing like a short skirt underneath
that I love it and and the socks and the
boots I love brown boots like that the
ankle boots and the brown works so well
with the the red and the color of the
the skirt matches so well too and the
shirt tucked in inside the everything
and the Beret the [\h__\h] red beret oh
my God yes yes yes yes
this is maybe my favorite really like
the girl outside
I think you're gonna like the next one
too that's my favorite but
this is my second favorite so now the
second submission from the same person
is this
oh
okay do you notice something
I do
is it the is it that it's shorter yes
she cropped it and so sold it like back
together
because normally it's much longer like I
mean not much better
I love that it's so cool that is
dangerous but she did a great job at it
if you're good at it it's okay oh yeah
you grab the hoodie
and and I like how you see like it's
hide away some pants and because she
cropped it you see a little bit of the
belly it's I love that style it is very
confident and long long kind of wide uh
jeans pants work so well here
um
I can wear it but you definitely rocking
it
mm-hmm yeah fantastic very cool yes I
love it thank you
thank you oh I like both but you know
she really got my personal style with
the first one so I think I prefer the
first one
yeah
one vest yeah
you are you thank you Mission next up we
have time
interesting look
I think Cali would like it my man's got
them Cowboy kicks and them cowboy belts
that cowboy Ben you got a vest on like
you're about to go out to the Past alas
no but it still looks really good yeah
hold on you're right oh my God that is a
cowboy belt yes
the big buckle and the and the flare
pants you call them flare pants yeah
this is extremely Cowboys she's from
Texas from Texas right there I like this
man from Texas I'm from Texas
I see I see choco senpai's uh boobies in
the background there's a lot of merch in
the background yes
sir
damn I I think it's so interesting it
really stood out to me oh my cat what do
you think
your eye coming from the shirt looks
really scary
is that really that what catches your
eye
in the background
four great outfit
sorry uh
I like the boots
they are fancy I wasn't sure Kelly would
like it
yeah it looks great it does is so cool I
mean
I just respect you know that you have a
style like I I couldn't wear this not my
style but it's so cool and there's also
a theme here so this one is from sadoma
so kissed the uh
s-a-d-o-m-a-s-o-k-i-s-s-e-d-d thank you
for your submission please rate Fashion
Police
yes
[Music]
howdy ha ha okay two more two more
kiwama submissions and then we're done
here too
um
I like the smile yes it's a perfect kfb
employee and they wrapped the the the
Parker the sweater around like it's
almost like a sash
yeah the sleeve of my sweater
and my birthday merch is implemented too
that's actually my birthday apron that
they also actually tucked in because
actually there's a top part to it too uh
but they tucked it in and then the
slippers the kfb slippers from my
birthday merch as well like everything
is combined and it just looks like such
a proud employee if I go to a KFC
restaurant this is a smile that I want
to be greeted with and the poster like
oh my god oh oh if you look at the at
the little pocket on the on the chest
there's a Kiana acrylic stand sticking
out
yeah the boss the boss bring your boss
to working and it's an employee of the
month definitely
please please read it this one is Swan
underscore flyer Swan flyer thank you
for the submission I love this employee
even if you if you I don't know if you
win but even if you don't win then
you'll you'll be employee of the month
or of the Year even
next up is the last one
[Laughter]
right
oh my gosh I love the um bucket is it
the straps oh yeah I was gonna say that
oh first I love this the shoulder straps
that hold up the skirt yes cute cute
straps yeah and I actually love the
color of the skirt the gray uh I I love
that skirt please give me I want to know
where you bought that skirt I need it
for my collection looks very comfy looks
very high quality
and the shoes are cute they're like
sailor style shoes
oh I didn't know this it was so cute
yeah
adorable and The Mask yeah
um I don't know the bucket almost makes
me want to put you in the meme category
I don't know man the rest is really
serious so
yeah even the gecko a little Gekko doll
that's just like chilling oh my God
I had a bucket steals to show
stop this rate everybody this one is
from You lyrics underscore
y-u-m-i-r-i-x underscore now I'm saying
it correctly finally
okay thanks guys this was the kiwava
category and last but not least we have
the general category
um I actually have
um a little bit of time pressure but I
think we're still fine and let's
continue then
um
this this this goes into the one second
I'll send it in this goes into the meme
category
um so judge it accordingly
wow
all right
[Applause]
[Music]
all of it
says you guys see that the background
though the sign says what the [\h__\h]
it's so fitting
it's absolutely so fitting I can't just
insane thank you someone says the
bloodborne bus
this is what you encounter in bloodborne
this is the whole of Life bloodborne
boss
a huge huge thank you for getting so
much merchandise holy [\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h]
um wow I didn't must be very warm did
you ever Envision this omocat when you
designed these clothes did you think
someone would uh could wear them like
this I don't think I imagined this in my
life
[Laughter]
what it
twist this is what happens when you make
so much good when you design so much
great merchandise they just want to put
it all together they want to put it all
at the same time because they can't
decide what to wear I think it looks
great yeah 10 out of 10. yeah is a merch
category so keep that in mind uh at
merge meme category from claro on the
score
there we go
please put your uh rating
you're hard Kiara there are too many
good meme ones
like making me choose between like this
and like like the the with shy guy mask
and Shrek and the Tupac and hey come on
man like a dog in a bag I'm not sorry
there's a dog yeah there's a dog
cute
okay one second
[Music]
okay oh yeah okay we gotta we gotta
hurry up a little bit what what oh [\h__\h]
wow we're here ah because OBS is fine
again one second the the taco daddies
are taking over again
there we go okay
this one I put almost in a good category
but they are wearing the kfp shirt and
I'm not sure is that uh the Cali sweater
uh the Kelly
MIP or the um hollow hollow myth group
one yeah so
could be that so maybe so that's why I
put it in the general category
yes
very cool
putting it all together I love the skirt
this box I love the socks they're so
cute and you've got like the girl wig
and the clips very adorable cute cute oh
there's also is that the Ikea shark
again in the background
[Laughter]
everyone got that shark yo nice I don't
have a dope and this one is from a day I
can't say that I I don't know how to say
it a
d-a-e-d-r-i-c-l-i-s-t dangerous
something like that yes thank you for
his YouTube submission please post your
ratings everybody
thank you
wait yeah there's a tail there is a tail
now that you mentioned oh cat's got
those sharp eyes sharp shark eyes damn I
didn't notice that thank you for
pointing that out all right next up
yes
wow that that is some style like the
jacket looks very stylish right the
layering under the hollow miff shirt
with another shirt yo
Bo cat what do you think
I like the shoes and everything looks
really good together yeah black black
and white is always it always works yeah
and I think even the Fabrics match like
the the jacket and the pants fabric look
very matching to me so that gives me
like it really satisfies me to see such
smooth fitting matching fabric Kelly
what do you think this looks like
something you would like I love it yeah
this is something I'd wear actually yeah
maybe maybe different shoes personally
but like I would dress like this
um like unironically and you look like a
whole myth type Beast yeah
um I love layering of like hoodies over
jackets
um and stuff like that or like jackets
with like different colored hoodies or
like uh different color sleeves
protruding from a big jacket so I'm a
big fan of this very stylish yeah very
good very good I was impressed by this
it looks like yeah you really have a
fashion sense your closet must look
amazing like inside I want to take a
look at your clothes video yeah this one
is from haruto bureka
h-a-r-u-t-o-b-u-r-e-k-a with those zebra
shoes noise please rate normal cat rate
swag out of ten yeah yeah just just for
uh just so you know Swag of the ten all
right next up we have
this one
um really really great photos like yo
you really put your great scene up there
damn I love this
[Laughter]
yeah it's a main outfit so I kind of
want to put it into the meme category
I'm not sure
yeah
that's beautiful on the on the clothing
lines what do you call it clothing line
This is a clothing line yeah yeah thank
you for getting so much of our
merchandise very cute that way you put
everything here together like it's a
perfect photo set yeah nice atmosphere
going on here and this one is from uh I
underscore ooVoo
EG
[Music]
should we put this in the main category
what do you think yeah yeah
um laundry out of 10. it's just a
laundry day oh that's why they're made
of fit maybe that's why
yeah it's laundry day it's doing the
laundry
all right well we have play star ratings
and next up is a famous family
oh my goodness I saw this it's the
silver tongue slacker family with the
baby is called Zach sander with eggs and
the baby has been very famous for
reacting to my streams uh like in a
really cute way and and they they I
think they taught him even some uh
kiara-ish words or they're trying to at
least
but I was a bit worried because like I
swear so much in my streams and uh I
don't want the baby to pick it up but oh
well gotta be careful oh well
yeah the parents are a whole lot of
English fans
um but it seems like they dragged the
whole family into it I like the whole
family is a whole English fan but at
least the parents and the baby
how sweet you guys are cute
family yeah
maybe maybe we should get them to adopt
us this is such a sweet family yeah
[Music]
sander I'm going to meet sander I'm
thinking she's hungry
in general or in meme I don't know
I think General's good okay nothing too
meme about family the family okay then
thank you for the rating this was silver
tongued the Twitter kind of silver
silver
s-i-l-v-e-t-o-n-g-u-e-d okay next up
I didn't think it would take that long
next up yo
I
have two pictures from this person
oh
I'm sending you both
wait let's just send me the same one
yeah I think it's the same I'm sending
you I'm sending you both a legend
[Music]
there we go now it should be there cool
because the photos were really cool I
had to show you both
a lot of people combine that jacket with
those kind of pants uh sporty pants
track pants so Sports the S40 pants if
this person really rocked it confidently
so I had to put it in there what do you
think gangster
gangster I love the pose he's like take
my hand yes let me take you down the
rabbit hole follow me follow me follow
me down the rabbit hole the glass is so
crazy
yeah you're rocking it yo that jacket is
um like I I personally don't like these
kind of sporty jackets that much but I
think a lot of people really love it and
it works so well for you guys so yeah
rocking it it's dripping yeah
yeah drippy farts oh my cat
uh looks good looks good
the glass is so crazy noise noise it's
cool yeah it's cool this one was from
cool out of 10. yeah Vince underscore
Yuki one zero two six
[Music]
tiger uh submission very cool I love the
posing and the photo is really great
that [\h__\h] next up we have two more this
is the second to last
all right ooh cool pose hey you like
jackets oh sassy I love it hard in this
leaf
there's a Subaru card
[Music]
I almost said Shabu Shabu
yeah
the JoJo hat
oh that's a Jojo
yeah it says Google
it's a JoJo thing and probably a JoJo
pose maybe then two I don't know I don't
I don't know what the official poses are
but it seems like it would be possibly
yeah is indeed saying that yeah yeah I I
chose this one because of the biker look
kind of you know
the tight uh jeans with the biker
jackets kind of gives me a biker look
do you like to ride your bicycle not
your place you know Ghost Rider no
Ghost Rider yeah uh now Ghost Rider
lives in my neighborhood and like rides
a motorcycle by but now I sound pretty
terrible Oh I thought you made like some
kind of movie I know it goes right like
from back in the day and you're waiting
yeah yeah I had a loud guy yeah
okay please place your ratings this
person is what is mang uh what is
m-a-n-g yeah
yes
[Music]
cute wait we've seen that before
yeah she was um she was wearing a taco
Dutch yes this time she switched up a
little bit it's the same same socks uh
same uh tights though but uh some
changes have been made with the striped
sleeves there I'm sure Kelly likes that
yeah it matches super well you can still
join us at the MCR concert
still the invitation stance
which stands out to you
pretty girl
any any details you like here I like the
sleeves and the
the
garter belt thing and the boots and
a lot
the chains
it's a different kind of bling bling
definitely fans are good oh yeah thank
you for another submission please rate
everybody we what we want this was the
overall the last submission so yes
[Music]
okay now uh since that was the last one
we need uh help me girls can you help me
figure out like which one is the best
and which category like which one got
the highest rating oh my God and that's
that's gonna be a tough one uh maybe
let's not have chosen for my category
but
okay shall we start with yours then
the winner of Cali's category I'm gonna
leave that uh because it's your category
I'm not gonna leave dad last decision to
you
you betcha they were all fantastic don't
get me wrong I loved every single one
but my fave has to be
um the very first one that we looked at
um from grab Nubs yes yes definitely all
right
my fave out of all of them it was very
close though there were some close
contenders
um
this is it didn't stand out a lot this
is just the energy that we need
I mean I know that like I'm a rapper but
like listen holy [\h__\h] [\h__\h] yeah oh by
the way I love the vibe all of the
participants please uh have your DMs
open omocat will be contacting you
because everyone who was showcased will
get something uh and the winners get uh
what what again
um everyone who was shown today gets a
catalog the Apollo XML catalog yes at
the specific winners get the keychains
at the lanyard right
yeah okay okay okay there we go okay so
grab them
yay
thank you
okay then I'll
um I'm gonna choose the Kiana one can
can you guys maybe figure out who who
got the highest rating
sure all while I talk
I'll take you know okay and um and omo
you take AME and then we'll figure out
gorilla yes okay so okay one more
category let me actually look I forgot
what I rated the highest I'm gonna take
a quick look
very professional ratings here
hmm
that is
a quick oh yes yes yes I I know okay
uh we have a winner everybody
the winner of the kihuahua category is
[Music]
that was really big sorry
it's the very much Kiana like Lulu
outfit she had two but this one personal
favorite thank you yay very cute
wonderful all of the submissions were
great though yeah thank you I just see I
think it was omo cat's favorite too so
yeah that's in line
wow I love it as well keep your DMs open
by the way
um
contacting all of you yes be careful yes
have you guys figured out some something
yup ena's winner okay um the winner of
the Ina
Ina outfit is uh you didn't put the
username for this one but they're the
takodachi couple
um
yeah with striped socks yeah
congratulations ciao main five
thank you so much for putting so much
effort into this cute outfit
a couple well I don't know if they're a
couple I don't know if they're a couple
I'm just I the the couple of they should
be friends that's fine I understood that
I 100 understood that yeah a couple of
people
um they're very cute I also figured out
girls as well oh no it's too fast
mathematician perhaps yeah I'm a
mathematician do you have a name
the name of the the person that we got
gave the highest rating for gura is
proud dumplings
oh
yes oh she must be very proud now we are
proud of you that's for sure
thank you thank you thank you for
participating and then we have Amir
right
indeed
[Music]
do you know which one it is
it's the one with the stickers
he draws congratulations
that one was indeed oh my gosh beautiful
stood out very creative very girly
thank you thank you you're very very
very happy for your participation thank
you [\h__\h] oh and then we have the general
category although the meme category
should we do that one first I think we
have a clear winner for the meme one
um I'm really torn because really to be
honest with you it's a toss-up between
claro and Elsie Le Pen
um but I'm gonna let you guys choose
from there I think it's it's so tough
because there are my memes like I say my
memes but like you know sure I could
save me for every whatever I can share I
can share Shrek with people it's not
just it's not like I own Shrek or
anything like that I'm just saying
listen but looking at the writing it
looks like uh the one from Elsie Lapin
has one point more
yes and yeah I noticed that
the Happy Lucky winner is
our Shy Guy Shrek okay everything
that sucks yeah legendary
the Tupac socks just are they're the
deal breaker for me I'm sorry and the
canes just ah he just wrote he's willing
to concede no need you're the winner no
no no no no you're the no it's okay and
everyone gets something so everybody
gets something so don't worry
congratulations
and last but not least the general
category that we had at the end I wonder
who got the most points does anyone know
I'll be looking at it too
all right
give her that one
drum roll please
I think
I think it's the family
yes it seems to be the Silverton slacker
family
yay congratulations
[Music]
we're ending it with a wholesome tattoo
picture isn't that beautiful that's
perfect
[Music]
congratulations everyone
they're awesome thank you for
participating maybe we can do it again
sometime
a lot of people are still waiting on
their merch and a lot of people are
still waiting to order merch so omo cat
I'll I'll give it up to you
uh
take it away
there's an announcement for uh restocks
yay yay I can't put my mic over to you
but I would yeah
yeah your respects are coming
um in March and in April so we're we're
a little bit early yeah wait I lost the
picture wait wait wait wait where is it
where's the picture
[Music]
uh so we before we said that um restocks
would come in April but we've been
working really hard to get some stuff in
sooner
um so we'll have partial restocks in
March and some in April yeah so some
some will be coming a little bit earlier
yep oh oh nice so exciting
questions
it's already March though
at least here oh shoot it is oh my
goodness we'll better get on that
yeah yeah
exciting stuff if you guys haven't
picked up anything you get a chance to
pick it up yes
yeah most stuff actually is going to be
in stock but there's some things that
we're having a hard time sourcing
because of like the pandemic and stuff
but we're trying our best to uh get
everything as fast as possible to
everybody so we will continue to try our
best yes yes
I also received merch thank you for
sending
it it's really comfy I really like the
cut and the feel Fabrics everything is
perfect and the embroidery on the pixel
t-shirts is so cute oh thank you that
was hard to get right because the
embroidery is small oh yeah yeah yeah it
was hard to get it look to look good
yeah thank you
no problem thank you omo Cat from
participating today I really I'm so
sorry I really gotta go but well yeah we
did our thing uh and I hope everybody
enjoyed looking at this beautiful
merchandise you guys are welcome to
still uh from now on as well post your
pictures of your merchandise because it
was so nice to go through them and look
how you guys wear it and combine it it
just makes me feel really really fuzzy
and warm inside so thank you for
participating but still continue to post
those pictures and maybe prepare for a
second round of fashion review sometime
in the future yeah indeed last comments
Cali
uh final comments you guys are styling
and profiling
um you guys are all extremely
fashionable and
um also funny and at the end of the day
wear what makes you happy and wear it
proudly
um because your style is I don't know
you should feel happy in what you wear
going out into the world yeah um
that's number one so um thank you
everyone for showing us your incredible
Styles and we love you guys we love you
thank you thank you thank you omocat for
coming I'm a cat with a bit shy but but
thank you it was nice and talking to you
and having your inputs
really really valuable input
um now we have to go through some police
work and arrest everybody who
participated but yeah keep your DMs open
please guys remember that otherwise Oh
cannot contact you you know and look
forward to the restock in March and
Marginal Way yeah thank you thank you
guys
and in German we say our here
thanks for watching
thank you
[Music]
foreign