[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
hello
oh my God that was stressful
I'm sorry
I went swimming
uh fourth time this week oh let's go but
honestly it was really necessary
it was really hot
yeah and I wanted to get a few more
swimming reps in
Wawa in the Wawa in the water
YouTube says you're disabled what the
[\h__\h]
what don't don't let YouTube brainwash
you
you are able
of everything
foreign
[Music]
I've noticed before that they do like
the smell of chlorine I think
when I have like a wet or not really wet
but like unwashed still chlorine
smelling towel or swimsuit somewhere
lying they often will rub themselves on
it
OBS I OBS said to say well
okay I I prepared a water jug
with some ice cubes
but I think they already dissolved and
disappeared wow
wow
I put quite a lot in there
let's see can I pour some water
oh no energy drink today
energy drinks are banned
also and I have
chocolate uh cookie snack or
the uh proper corn sweet and salty snack
huh let's see how cold is this at least
I'm using my my stainless steel tumbler
from Atelier Riza
oh
yeah that keeps things relatively cool
uh silver Wawa today yes
[Music]
hello hello hello
ah you know what I wanna I want to
oh I want to pin
um
you uh or first song ever
listen to it
I've got a gun you must listen to it
foreign
yes
okay do the Holiday Dance
[Music]
ah we'll talk about it during the stream
when I got some
uh time driving
during driving um we'll talk about the
song we'll talk about horogora we'll
talk about the terrible [\h__\h] terrible
dream I had that made me wake up crying
[Music]
200k what the [\h__\h] it's fast wow
it's growing fast Let's go people want
to see holotoli
was it of a huge chicken no that was
reality apparently
foreign
no audio issues or so
there we go
um
oh yeah maybe maybe the deadlines are
stressing me out so much and that's why
I had a nightmare I don't know but it
was unrelated to the to the
uh deadlines
yo you know what my my usual my current
like default amount of lanes swamp is
16 17 Lanes
but it's shorter Lanes is that lame
is
laps no not I mean one length so 17
lengths
I uh yeah they're pretty short though
not not as short as
we pulled from yesterday yesterday
yeah you don't know how long that length
is but it's it's a good amount of swim
swim
um
it's it's it's very it's I'm like I I'm
I am pushing myself like the first
couple lanes are easy peasy comfortable
and then I get to a part where it's like
um okay okay okay I feel I feel it
strongly in my arms I feel it mostly in
my in my whole length of my arm
more than in my shoulder or whatever
so I feel like I'm doing more for my
arms than for anything else is that
normal am I swimming correctly
uh
I'm still out of breath
from preparing everything when I rushed
back home trying to get out of the
swimsuit which is so [\h__\h] tight I
wore a swimsuit that's too small for me
today
um
arms and shoulders guess the arms yeah
my arm
this is my arms is just they're just too
weak I guess
[Music]
um
you could use some flippers I don't need
flippers
but I realized because today's Sunday
a really hot day on on a Sunday it was
really crowded but oh well
I just minded my own business
um
um I'm not in Japan no no I'm in Austria
usually affects your core more than your
arms what does that even mean you guys
yesterday you were telling me Oh yeah
you're a strengthening your core and I'm
like yeah yeah let's go I'm strength
running my core what is what is that my
my hot my like the middle of my breast
cage or what
ABS I don't feel anything happening in
my abs though are you sure
ah
I don't feel anything happening there
um
one day I'll just wake up with a 12 pack
I doubt that
uh I see I see
well whatever I'm doing
there's no doubt that it's
good
I'm I'm pushing myself to get to like a
default of 20
links
now I'm still chilling around 17
and this time I had to rush too if I
could take a little break in between I
can go back and swim a little bit more
but
you know I've got [\h__\h] to do I have to
finish this game today
no matter what
uh solo snare
eh
why the [\h__\h] is my orange car
can you not put two at once here
because I thought you can just put two
because it's a really big parking space
what the [\h__\h]
did they like they can't just get rid of
it where's my where's my car
is this GTA people steal it
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
it was parked wonderfully actually it's
weird that this car survived because if
anything the orange car it was already
confirmed it was parked correctly
because like we came back to it once and
it was still there and it actually like
fixed some some bumps in it
reload safe but which which one
which one
I mean this one
what the [\h__\h]
Roman stole my car
guys
what the is this before I did the thing
which is just before I changed my
clothes
[Music]
uh I want my third place
who the [\h__\h] wears a suit with shoes
like that
whoever does that I'm sure there's like
at least one dude out there who does
that
that person does lack a lot of fashion
sense
[Laughter]
oh my baby my baby oh that's a nice one
too though can I can I borrow
what are we doing anyway what are we
starting with I see an FM and I see a g
but they're both really far hmm
what's FM Francis oh new person
and gambetti I still remember that name
from yesterday
ah wait a second I only added one song
[Music]
uh which is
ah it's the cup
ah okay I'll remember him if I see him
should I take a taxi there or hmm
huh
Nikki boy the peg wants to see us at his
house you talk me up I'll talk you up
stick together remember you owe me ciao
what you want to get any closer than
that to me huh huh you want some huh huh
how dare you frighten me
yeah yeah get out of there okay
can we find horotori dance while I'm
driving uh
no no no no no no no
ah so good but not this one how do you
change songs again was it
no B
itch
[Music]
f j f nah it's not f
but B is working too
well
clap your hands
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
almost
is also electro swing
which is I think very fitting uh genre
for horota I think it was a good choice
hmm
what is it where is it
where is it it's on shuffle right now so
oh I Gotta Get Lucky
foreign
[Music]
was that not it before no I don't think
so
what what do you want
I did a scan a quick one though only
for trial
a complete scan
if you think I passed it are you sure
it's a complete scan complete
maybe
um sequential was just like in the right
order right
oh
[Music]
no no no
the electric thing always makes me think
it's it
what the [\h__\h] where is it where's that
what is it no
yeah I put it in there
let me check it's in there isn't it
uh it's in documents Rockstar Games GTA
4 user Music
and maybe maybe they don't like
that it's a WAFF
because all my other songs are MP3
I think it doesn't like that it's a WAFF
a woof
oh
convert waft to MP3
we have to have it in our radio today
today's release day
[Music]
but what the [\h__\h]
to MP3
select
who already dance
convert I also got the karaoke version
so we can sing it in karaoke sometime
too let's go
put your hands up put you put your hands
up
put your hands up put your okay I got it
in MP3 now
[Music]
let's hope I don't have to restart the
game for that
[Music]
um
it should be after this
nope
where's weird I mean in the folder it's
in that order
[Music]
wait we gotta get through all of it
reason I did I did didn't you see it
no yeah
you know what I'll go to G so then
hopefully we can hear the whole song
and on the way I could go actually to
weapon shop
[Music]
announcement announcement that block is
this all right I hear me
We're Here for a Good Time
birds have a feather feather Hotel
[Music]
he says
we're only getting started
[Music]
dance
announcement
[Music]
noise
give us your best clocking moves we
wanna see you sir
[Music]
anyway
Taking Flight show me what you got yeah
[Music]
okay okay that was actually
yes
good a good guess
yeah it's unfortunately it's kind of
short right two minutes and like eight
seconds
yeah that was like when I first heard it
I was like damn this song is a banger we
should make it longer this is but
honestly a lot of the time it didn't
feel that short to me when I listened to
it
like it doesn't I feel like it covers up
its shortness quite well
um
[Music]
it helps the loop ability
hell yeah let's go
crazy I pitch it I pitched it okay
uh yeah everybody has
like summer parts
[Music]
and everybody is singing in three
different languages we mixed um
we mix Indonesian and uh English and
nihongo sang this
yeah and
there's like
bird puns hidden in all three languages
so the more languages you understand the
more you will understand all the puns
foreign
but I think oh Roman I think in the
translation subtitles it's also like
kind of they try to uh
they try to translate it
no
he's so sweet
[Music]
congrats on your first little group
original thank you
it's out it's out
but now we must do crime
how are you doing
foreign
Crime Time
please I'm an old man I ain't got much
time left our mutual friend told me
everything thank you it made me laugh
oh God to spit blood
oh God people are so damn
some people
all people even you even me an old man
facing the end and I still care care how
I look care that when I [\h__\h] myself the
pretty nurse has to clean it up I think
I would care about that too
we're not a dead age anymore
of rockets my family has run for 50
years you mean 50 years of you bleeding
the city dry might finally come to an
end
I know it's a terrible tragedy
[Laughter]
[Music]
what is he dying from this age or cancer
or looks like it could be just age
nah that's a joke right
it's boyfriend
sounds for real like in like a sickness
[\h__\h] bastards are trying to finish us
what do you want me to do about it kill
him
in exchange for what
police have a file on you an inch thick
in extreme for that
in exchange for that guy you've been
asking about being brought here from
wherever it is he's hiding Switzerland
or somebody [\h__\h]
okay good
what do you want me to do a good friend
of mine is coming into town to give a
speech on the new threat to Liberty City
I should recognize Christ
I got a feeling some people ain't gonna
want that speech to happen maybe the guy
you loved this to meet you
make sure our boy gets the city hall
he's coming in from upstate
the last episode is riveting
people dying let's go
um
[Music]
yum
um yum yum I'm eating proper corn from
England
um
[Music]
okay
um
no cookie maybe later right now it's
filling I was feeling down the Savory
saltiness
[Music]
um
that was a that was a bite full of
flavor nice
all right this mission is fun really it
better beer
[Music]
I love Corona songs holy [\h__\h]
I will learn this song
what a freaking Bob and honestly her
singing it in that cute ooVoo voice
makes it so much better
electro swing with cute ooVoo Japanese
voice
if you think about it oh that's an uber
voice isn't it
don't bump into police car
apparently she gets out of breath when
she sings this oh I love that green
color on that car
there's another one
is it the same green no this one looks a
bit different this one's more metallic
and a little bit lighter
dog is God Street's so good man
[\h__\h] oh wait you know what I want that
car now
it's pulling you up like gravity
I hope the police car yeah
you go
now
following you like a high tide
oh
you know one thought another thought
that I had when
you know we were working on the horror
story dance song
uh was well the chorus were like not
really seeing it right it's just like
instrumentals bopping instrumentals and
um us chanting whole tree dance and I I
think you know normally I wouldn't do
this normally I would want to show off
our singing and all that
and I think it's
an interesting choice
but what we're I think trying to do with
this Horror Story dance is
yeah make it into a Mimi fun dance song
and the theme song rather than showing
off any singing and it's it's also
showcasing the the horratory you know
kind of our like meme dance
that Subaru was made to do and that we
did together in my 3D showcase and all
that
um
it's like an introduction to holotori I
guess and
I don't know I think
if I make a song for myself I wouldn't
normally attempt this I think having um
instrumental chorus but yeah I think it
fits good especially because Electro
swinging instrumentals are just so fun
so I think it's
it's um
for this one song it's it's fine and
I think it serves its purpose and it's a
nice experiment it's different you know
the
the like I don't know the focus is on
something else then uh usual yeah
you guys waiting for me Niko Bellic
right yeah that's me stay in Convoy with
us all the way to City Hall all right
oh taking your car okay get in the car
are you getting into
what the [\h__\h] is this radio how do you
change radio again
it's already too late like my my GTA
streams they got like even when I played
music for only two seconds
they all got
um yeah
Flags marks Mr beats my virtual country
that sounds like an excellent is that a
talking radio I want to hear talking
radio too but um
I can't I'm too uh stupid right now okay
there it is yeah but it's no problem
it's not like I'm gonna get banned or
anything
of course well I'm coming to see you as
soon as I've delivered the speech
let's follow him
don't say that John you'll be feeling
like a teenager again in no time
is that what we're doing following
wonders of modern medicine what's he
talking to oh he's on the phone
look at all
done at the podium mayor Ochoa is going
to be dedicating half his annual budget
to cleaning this problem up he doesn't
want to start getting Reckless with the
lives of Liberty City voters
take a deep breath John
[Music]
okay we were driving driver why is this
road closed is there a problem I didn't
do anything just now
oh this definitely wasn't showing the
traffic report I'm going to go and move
the barrier
okay I'll see what you're gonna do
oh Mr J is this normal let's get out of
here
do these kind of people
oh thank God I was on the side here what
the hell
um
hey this is my sister for lunch
nice
um is this Brent
okay
what the [\h__\h] man okay now let's use the
other guns [\h__\h] the pistol
[Music]
um
where are the memories I don't see them
I'm blind but they should be like there
yeah
ah there
and then one here right
all right
it should be two upstairs and one should
be
huh
shooting me
[Applause]
there should be one ear and then there
look man
at your little [\h__\h] get out of there get
out of there right now
[Music]
I'm I'm I'm I am a little bit upset that
you don't want to show your face to me
bro
okay and here
recommend
[\h__\h] that scared me it looked like a
floating hand out of nowhere
they sent reinforcements or what
wait oh I see I see I see
what's with my camera in general holy
[\h__\h]
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait
[Music]
ah
hey why do they keep
it
wait there's someone here
what this is everybody's hiding so well
oh my God
okay
um
I'm gonna get you I'm gonna get that
bastard push and another one oh I see
him
only one shot necessary
[Music]
ah [\h__\h]
foreign
[Music]
um
someone is on there on the map
on the same level as I am maybe here
all right all right now I gotta run
unless is there did he drop maybe
something interesting like a nope
as I'm looking for
um
for armor I was looking for Ahmed but
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] where what
color are we taking which card we're
taking what do you mean lose the
pursuers okay okay
lose them he says
losing him not uh killing them always
killing an option too
[Music]
Jefferson to safety okay where your
safety is that very specific place
oh now it added the yellow line too
oh I did lose them okay
we lost them
in a good way good Chase music but it
was a very really really short Chase
[Music]
now
this is Seth's best can I get through
with my car yeah
but you got me here goes to show some
immigrants have the best interest of the
country in their hearts I'll tell John
you did well thank you
that was a interesting warm-up a little
bit chaotic though
[Music]
Grand Valley
I took that friend of yours to City Hall
he should
I want to hear it
you always
try something how are we supposed to
compete with the Immigrant Criminal
it wasn't so bad you're working with me
aren't you Mr Gravelly
see you later
oh yeah uh
uh let's go to FM because it's close
yeah back to Holiday topic
I mean so I think for for this time
having a short song with focus on just
being a Bop rather than singing
was fine but I hope next time while
still maintaining a fun holiday vibe
that we can have if we sing again if we
make another song
which I hope for
um that way you can still have a fun
song but you know
also gives the vocals a little bit of a
showcase because we have very good
singers
um
yeah yeah
what
but I would be interested to hear from
you guys what kind of Horror Story song
you want to hear in the future
I I don't think we'll just do electro
swing again
we'll probably try out several
uh genres
death battle
why didn't you tell me Derek was back
Jay Rock why didn't you tell him he was
hanging around with my brother I assumed
if you care I like that idea too I have
found out Jesus you know Derek's not
well
no no he's sick
he always was [\h__\h] it's always off
getting involved in someone else's fight
making a fool of himself betraying
people going into hiding he's an idiot
and a coward it's not my business thanks
for the membership stood for he betrayed
he only left here in the first place
because he was caught stealing from the
mafia
that wretch okay I got it so now he's
gonna ruin my life
it wasn't bad enough having a bunch of
crap across for Brothers now I've got
him threatening to talk to a journalist
oh [\h__\h] about me to be quiet I am trying
to become the commissioner let's silence
him
cop the commissioner of the police you
oh no
you know don't know what they do but
that sounds important
me
we my friend we
so inclusive you stop it
stops
stop
uh-huh
kill your brother he's already dead wow
put him out of his misery [\h__\h] no [\h__\h]
you
I'm going to meet him in the courtyard
park off Bismarck in Lansing deal with
him
became a tragedy deal with your own
family man why do I'm gonna do it it's
your family well I will put you away are
you too coward to kill your own brother
so you gotta make me do it it doesn't
change that basically you're doing it
because you're the one commissioning it
it's on your hand the Block in Indiana
in the end the blood is still in your
hands is what I'm saying
Bismarck I think he's gonna try to kill
me cops you kill all they like do you
know the place are you close can you get
there in time I think I can make the
meeting
enable stuff I'm telling you the
question is which one of us is going to
be wandering the Earth with a mark on
his head and who's going to be six feet
under you know this phone's running out
of battery [\h__\h] look after me Nico wait
I don't know when who do I like more I
think Derek
I think who would you save I think I
would save Derek because that corrupted
police piece of [\h__\h]
um
yeah yeah oh wow everybody agrees
well well why are we calling Francis I'm
ready what is the plan I hope you got
over yourself
I know this ain't nice but neither of us
has a choice it's sounding like I got no
choice one McCreary brother is going to
get me to kill another that's what I
like
cleaning elevator on one of the
buildings around back of the courtyard
get in position and put Derek out of his
misery [\h__\h] I better get ready to act
surprised don't miss Nico you might hit
me I'll hit who I made me get don't
worry oh we get into the same position
but we just choose to kill
Francis then
okay
[Music]
I think I'll take a taxi unless I'm
gonna be effed without the car
afterwards
why not can I oh thank you I feel like
that would be a fisherman
uh window cleaner elevator
wait is it like
ah
the office parkour
I want to recreate parkour
[Music]
fishing mailed
successfully
[Music]
um
popcorn yummy yummy
are you guys jelly what are you guys
snacking on
um
[Music]
Francis had a good perk if he lives what
do we get for letting Derek live
but honestly whatever it doesn't really
matter I guess hmm
oh
um only up to three stars what do you
mean I can never get over three stars
might get
shot Derek nothing okay
seems like the right choice though I'm
nervous about this little meeting
ethically
when I hurt myself sit down why didn't
you call me you could
you could I'm sorry about how life
turned out for you
okay I need uh oh we're already on the
sniper okay zoom zoom zoom
um which one will it be maybe you maybe
you maybe you maybe you
any pigeons out here no
um
catch the tiger by his toe uh I don't
know how it goes
so anyway it's
not you but
[Music]
oh wait I want to see the reactions
get off the roof okay
faster
we have to leave I have to leave I have
to live
oh it's because
he's all the walking controls tonight
okay so now I'm a little bit [\h__\h]
without the car but I guess oh wait it
seems like we're fine
you know what let's go and buy some
armor
nobody cares huh
goes it all right excuse it
let me in
oh
there's that success music
[Applause]
hey
what's up this camera oh my God stop oh
now now you stop that bastard
did it kick me out because of the phone
call
s
who else
that's uh very kind five
that almost killed me you [\h__\h] idiot
ow
e you know
he all scared up
five star Uber
Becky
sorry I'm busy
ah
bowling we're packing bowling right now
Peggy another time all right man
[Music]
I probably was gonna ask me to do
something important
[Music]
but no
ah
okay
we have a Kate
I think that's the impossibly the case I
was thinking of
um G or J guys G or J
um
Kate and Young
we have Kate at home Kate at home
you know I really love that Meme but
it's so difficult to recreate because
why is both the getting into the taxi to
drive it button
and the one to steal it f uh
wow
[Applause]
I really didn't want to do that
that
is
well
It's gotta quickly Escape
who is she
okay
that's it I know I know holding him
it's stupid
yeah
okay where are we going
could you guys also watch the hotel it
came out a few hours ago it's a holiday
and I now remember what it was about
I recorded that so long ago I already
forgot
so we were
I guess
I'm looking for a new holder to remember
but also doing something else at the
same time just traveling yeah helicopter
helicopter was in the script and also in
this preview video I think it was a
helicopter
like like I know what a helicopter
that's the helicopter I know what the
helicopter is
that's the final video just now they
don't send us the final video you know
we watched the final video on YouTube
just like you guys
and I haven't like heard back from them
since I recorded it
is
that was not gonna have to I know that
but it's not only me saying helicopter
right after my line uh Ethan it sounds
also says something about helicopter yay
we got a helicopter
[Laughter]
why did they do does staff know that
what a helicopter is and what that is
that they got me
actually wait it's so weird I think I do
remember like it was just like a
like a paper plane
in the original reference video but it
was like you know said that this might
still change this is just you know uh
like
draft face so
it was just a draft I thought they were
gonna you know do whatever with it
I'm I'm just reading what's in the
script guys
what the hell
what
I got practice Yeah helicopter at home
I got a helicopter at home helicopter at
home
how are you Mr Gravelly good good thank
you Scott
that's the helicopter friend about
fish
like that
then he mentioned something about a taco
breathing what he did yeah he's located
the guy it seems he wasn't in
Switzerland at all but in Bucharest
close enough it'll be here soon
good good and it seems your Russian
friends are getting the message
um oh okay so I think it's our turn to
do a favor for that mutual friend of
ours
seems some Korean has come into the
country and
um
selling money at a discount well buy
money for money I need to tell you that
it's all Fugazi
Faker than a pair of fine wood tits
that's good
listen
I need you to deal with this
eliminate the guy
what he's doing is no good for the
economy
and no good for Patriots like you and me
so who is he his name is Kim Young
he'll be very well protected
he eats it Mr Fook
really are you all right yeah yeah
I'm fine
what was I saying Kim Young he said it
correctly actually right he eats at a
restaurant called Mr folks rice box
yeah an Albany City
don't worry I'll take care oh wait I
understand what they're doing with isn't
that like really offensive are they
doing that on purpose giving him that
name
I don't know I think it's awesome
it sounds like it could be a normal name
in Korean
I just yeah because somebody in the chat
said be careful saying that alone now I
understand
could be
an actual name I don't know
I've I've been studying Korean
so I've been getting a feeling for it
but
hmm
yeah I mean
[Applause]
it's GTA yeah they probably
doing an on purpose
oh I can't breathe man today is a not
breathing day oh hey aggressive
um
okay oh we're going really far maybe I
should have taken a texture yesterday I
barely took taxes
today I could do it to make it even
shorter
yeah yeah
I don't know if it's asthma but
um
hmm
but I haven't had this in a while
actually hmm
this problem
hmm
okay
I can't I can't take a deep breath
that really goes through my lungs you
know like it stops somewhere I don't
know what that maybe it's not as bad I
don't know but it feels weird like it
stops me from taking a full breath you
know what I mean
okay now I got a kind of a
photograph Loki
[Music]
you know in the horikora when everybody
was making
um bird chicken noises
but ain't looking really embarrassed
about doing it and what's so cute
and somebody I was reading for the
comments of the video and somebody
pointed out
um
maybe a logic flaw that you know I guess
I died when I crashed or arrived at the
beach but they still managed to nicely
gather my ashes
in a bucket
think about it shouldn't it have been
like scattered all over the beach in the
set mixed with the sand and yet they uh
that must have been some beach set mixed
into that bucket
hahaha
anything's possible yeah my ashes come
with a bucket I guess maybe wait till
you guys record together no no no no no
no
we record separately
yeah but I watched the final video I
mean Lena looked her animation looked so
embarrassed she had an embarrassed face
did you not watch it
[Music]
um
Horton is used to gather in your ashes
no it doesn't happen that often
a [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] police
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
can I take a taxi when I'm being chased
oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] let me out of here
no
no there's one in the front
ah [\h__\h]
what money
and somebody calling me
[Music]
now we good we good we good
my car is smoking hot but so is me
[Music]
okay let's go what is this Mission what
are we doing Aya
Mr Mr
can I normally also go into this
restaurant and eat hello
he's upstairs speaking with the manager
they don't want to see nobody though Kim
and I are old friends Jim got a lot of
money he don't need no friends get lost
he's UK in Korean what you mean in the
Korean version of this game he's
from the UK
membership
um
uh
you guys are serious huh
oil it just reminds me of Yakuza
which Yak was that was it where we like
we went to also like what was that what
kind of
I think I was uh
um
I don't remember them anymore but it was
probably like it and yeah yeah at the
end where there's like this big I don't
think it's a restaurant but
this big
whatever what what was that it was like
not a restaurant
was that zero hmm
oh did they leave
it's pretty here car quite nice
I have a lock on him
I'm gonna die
oh yeah
uh there's no literally all the cover
options are like see-through there's
holes in them
[\h__\h]
ah let me do it again ah no I'm out of
here
oh [\h__\h] next time I'll throw a grenade
up there
Maybe
this is fine
Just Gotta Buy armor again
um
man we're so far
I'm gonna go here first and then we'll
take a taxi
Yum Yum Yum Yum Yum so uh
boom is not over yet guys tomorrow
um the short is coming out
the short that I coordinated
and planned
and I gave like everybody instructions
and this and that
and I made a little choreography for
Mommy because she didn't know what to do
yeah any woman was so lost she's like
okay well please help me I don't know
what to do
I'm like okay okay try this try this
at the spot I made a little simple
choreo for her
I said I was going to take a taxi into
the month
[Music]
yeah
I helped that mummies
oh there's a taxi
no no that's not what I I swear I was
still pressing F this whole time
even when I was like getting on the
Wheel
the holes I pressed it for like eight
seconds oh that's a nice car
can you take back your taxi and drive me
to where I need to go
are we clear about my intentions
okay now we are
[Music]
ah do you know where I need to go to
like I don't understand this when I'm
not
when I'm not marking where I need to go
doesn't know that I need to go to this
place I don't know let's just do it like
this okay
it's done let's do it thank you
all right
um
ah over there
should I when I go in also right away
shoot the reception person
what do you think
yeah
so he can't shoot me from behind at
least
[Laughter]
oh
it hasn't begun yet
I guess he couldn't alert everybody
is that an option
is that possible
okay you must come out now there's
nowhere to run
what
here we go
this is not a Korean restaurant though
isn't this like Chinese
Ryan
yeah yeah
what what what do you mean what
come on come on I see you I think I see
you on it is that another person
is it not
I see what somebody here too oh I see
you I see it
go to hell did I get him
[Music]
um Advanced slowly okay
I'll go to
I want to go to this the these this
thing is
but it still looks dangerous there
yo
[Music]
now I don't see anybody but once I go up
they have suddenly reinforcements
[Music]
I'll I'll bait it I'll go up
and I'll go down
yeah they're on the other side they're
gonna [\h__\h]
reload yeah okay
[\h__\h]
oh
wait if I hide behind here this way
yeah oh yeah that's good
for shooting parties man
I can't take cover anywhere
am I am I getting him
I think so
okay very calm music here wow
he's going down oh
okay okay okay
what are they all doing
okay in here
question the manager to find Kim
thank you how do you know all of that
don't let him Escape well suddenly
this can't or do I wait
they say don't let him Escape is he
still like in here that sounded like
he's like already on the way to outside
[\h__\h] I don't want to [\h__\h] up he is
upstairs
foreign
nice shots though
oh
this is the kitchen
oh I see him are you do you want trouble
you no
mmm oh I don't need that
[Music]
stand up start your stuff migrate all to
the floor
okay
a bike I can't sell the bike can I well
can I don't know I guess I can anything
is possible
[Music]
wait where's my goal
s
where's he going
bike is so wobbly
I'm used to driving cars uh
[Music]
yeah
easy I came from the other side
oh that was too easy
[Music]
his best his last boss Bill Mr Gravelly
well
I very much agree
all right that went well in the second
try
at least the chase was really quick as
easy
um
and
oh this I can press X to mute the radio
what why nobody ever told me that before
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
I'm at the last stream for this game and
now you tell me we told him
I don't know
Mamma Mia
all right what's the next mission let's
go
to the next thing
really close by ah we're here again
[Music]
happy don't tell me you want to go
bowling
Liberty City what do you mean Becky I
mean that my cop Brother Francis
McCreary is no longer with us oh I
wonder why you must be very upset
that said the only celebrating Jerry is
going to be able to do will be in prison
he got hauled in last night [\h__\h] is it
serious charges ain't gonna
thank goodness it's at the church in
Suffolk today I'll stop by man I'll see
you there remember
did you look at me or something
to wear a suit
a funeral I mean are we um going to have
a quiet calm funeral or oh
um okay
why are you calling me how do you have
my number hi Nico hi Nico hey Kate I'm
sorry to hear about your brother you're
probably the
accept him and too much of a gangster to
be accepted by the cops what did you
think about him to be honest
happened earlier then again I expected
to get a call from the court
y Brothers every day
sure I'll see you there Kate goodbye
funeral date yeah
um
I was already empty guys
I emptied popcorn
wait is this not where I was supposed to
go what the [\h__\h]
did it just trigger all the calls that I
just got weird it told me to go here
didn't it
or did the funeral override
the other thing
ah
okay priority Mission oopsie
well then
[Music]
let's go to a funeral
I've been to only two funerals in my
life I think
one was
my mother's signed
uh uh Grant my grandma
but I guess can you call the funeral
when it was like
um you know we Phoenix's we like to
make ourselves go up in flames
[Music]
is that do we still call it a funeral I
guess you you do don't do you because
well
in German the word for funeral has the
word for you know putting someone in a
grave in it
like literally putting uh Earth on top
of someone
hmm
[Music]
we had to go I guess there's another
word for chattel now
yeah the other funeral was like
really freaking uh unfortunate I'm not
gonna talk details but it was no one
related to me
but it was a child
not related but like work work related
it was a well now I'm talking details it
was a car accident
and the family was like so affected by
it obviously damn it was like at work
everybody was like freaking depressed
for
a long time and whenever we would see
the family
person
at work the atmosphere was like
immediately like so sad
yeah that was that was crazy man
that was crazy
[Music]
oh
but that's it that's it
so maybe
maybe I've been still more or less lucky
so far to have not experienced too much
loss
[Music]
yet
Hold Us in there
oh I arrived yet
and while no one is suggesting he was an
angel
none of us are that is why God put us on
Earth and not in heaven
Heaven trials Humanity
but he was he was committed family man
uh-huh and the corrupted work man
asked so much of himself and will be
sorely missed by us all
totally I miss him so much
amen now if you will all please join me
in the procession
the cemetery
is there food did anybody bring food
I'm uh sorry for your loss I'm not
sorry for Mom
well everybody deals with grief
differently and I'm hungry oh [\h__\h] it's
never expected
to put flowers on their
mother I don't know
[Applause]
what the [\h__\h] leave us alone at least on
the funeral yeah
hey
I need cover I need cover I need cover
what do you want that why are you
disturbing our funeral now he might have
been a really really bad man but come on
have some decency what kind of human are
you you're going to hell I'll tell you
that
[Music]
what do you want what are you getting
out of this
he's already dead like come on
you're taking revenge on him or so it's
already dead
[Music]
gets down who's running is that
no problem I'll take care of all of them
yeah we're having a big math funeral
let's go
oh I said that's a lot of paintball
ah this is normal person right yeah yeah
yeah
you killed us
Overkill
talk about Overkill
there we go
get in the hearse is this a hearse wow
cool car fancy car pretty Frankie's plot
is in the graveyard on Colony Island
Nico could we put them in the ground of
course foreign
to the cemetery
this honestly is a pretty car hey what
the
[\h__\h]
that wasn't your fault
God damn man what is going on
they're still not done
they want us to eradicate all of them
what the hell
I do not recommend these actions
please leave us alone we just want peace
what the [\h__\h]
literally what the [\h__\h]
oh my God New York today is absolute
insane chaos
[\h__\h] I never thought I'd be on the run
from some Albanian gangsters with a cop
in the car can we call for backup or
something are you suggesting that I'm a
[\h__\h] today every day
European [\h__\h] I'm in my brother Francis
it was a joke hell of a [\h__\h] time to
be making jokes about your dead brother
you know I'm still not that fond of the
guy even in his death I guess that's
what team cop will do to a fraternal
relationship I get yes you've got enough
Brothers to hate one of them swiftly
running out Nico ain't got that many
left is on his way to the graveyard and
Gerald is behind bars all I got left is
that smackhead Derek you've got KD I
could have [\h__\h] guessed you'd bring
her up I was thinking you only kept
those Hitmen away from the church to
protect my sister I did it all for you
tell yourself you did it out of the
grace of your own heart rather than for
another piece of your Anatomy which
ain't gonna get used
yeah no I I I'm not interested either yo
I wasn't planning on using it [\h__\h]
here let's bury this bastard
are we gonna get attacked again
hopefully none
of um
graveyards are so
scary
and depressing
but also history only scary at night
really daytime is okay
so scary at night it's not that I don't
like cops you do what you do to get back
you think they're peaceful regular guys
do you go to them often because maybe
that's why I'm not here for Francis
I'm here for you maybe you're used to it
like I said thanks
give me a call sometime Nico
[Music]
oh they fixed the back door
I didn't even know they had a graveyard
built into the city
the game ships Nico and Kate so hard
yeah I don't really feel any chemistry
though what the [\h__\h]
I don't see you where they're getting it
from it's like so forced oh what is this
well I don't need that there must be
pigeons
there must be one pigeon here
they they glow red so I should be able
to see them
[Music]
it's your funeral today as well
I can't see any
roxa doesn't have Romans Riders that's
for sure
in GTA 5 I felt some love here and there
GTA 4 no
hey Jerry I heard you've been locked up
I'm sorry to hear that we got
ta put
you
pigeon no pigeon
I guess no pigeon then fine
not like I really care
I wasn't really collecting them anyway
foreign
this one right Jerry
again really far but there's no taxes
here
oh Packy gave me a thumbs up oh let's go
this one this is your car lady
what the hell
oh my God
[Music]
I like it
Roman gives me free texting I know I
know but
I don't want to rely on him I want to be
an independent lady why is this one
still here
I want to be independent
you know
oh okay I thought you asked me to call
you and now you're calling me again
you're kind of clingy girl
Nico has been invited to your cousin's
wedding wedding I think you guys knew
each other
is that true Nico I guess it is I'll see
you at the wedding then
Bonito
is that thrifting
can you call that drifting
drift off
[Music]
is that your thing oh my God I'm doing
it let's go
oh this car is made for drifting
[Music]
oh
almost got a star
so by the way the dream that I had
I was like dreaming a lot of things last
night but
it was like really chaotic lots of mixed
stories
running at the same time somehow
at some point
um people who are like ganging up on me
to steal all my things for some reason I
was kind of outside and I was trying to
uh yeah protect my things and then
people actually came to help me
like normal pedestrians
[Music]
um which was nice everybody was like
helping me running over to help me and
eventually it kind of turned into a
Chase on foot so I was chasing this
person who had my fangs
and then
somehow I don't really remember this how
this
transitioned into the different story
but suddenly it wasn't really about
those things anymore but
Apparently one of my cats movie
was
already dead
for a while in this point of the dream
like for several days or weeks and I was
still getting over it and then suddenly
chunky wonky I see chunky wonky on the
street kind of like
in front of me and then disappearing and
that kind of meant to me that oh my God
she's dying right now too and then I I
break out in tears and I curl up on the
street on the floor on the ground
and I cry and I cry and then I see her
again for a moment and I thought oh my
God maybe she's not there but then she
disappears again and then then I cry and
curl up again and became fetus Wawa
just law and yeah it turns out there's
no
um both of my cats and I woke up and I
was like
chonkers was sleeping right next to me
and I touched her to make sure she's
real and I was relieved but then I
started crying a little bit but I was
telling myself wow it was just a dream
it was just stream obviously it was just
a dream calm down but it really upset me
and I feel like it's kind of like um
like that reaction that I had the way I
acted when I I realized chunky monkey
was dead
I think that's like
me
seeing like a little a little
um sneak peek into what it will be like
you know I don't know six seven eight
years depending on how long my cats are
gonna continue living
the pain
whoa whoa no my cats always sleep next
to me so they're always there but yeah
it was good that she was right there
when I was waking up
it was a big relief
baby enjoy the now yeah but damn that
was so painful
that's like one of the worst dreams I
could ever have
honestly what the
truck
a can of Coke
yeah it was a pure nightmare like holy
[\h__\h] first I was being actually not
Chase for once I was chasing
somebody stole my [\h__\h] and then it was
about my cat suddenly
[Music]
um
damn I haven't had such a bad dream that
makes me
cry when I wake up in a long time
enjoy that katos yes
yes
once again
um
[Music]
really bad dream
man so that was rough but besides that I
slept pretty well
I slept so well but then I woke up at
some point at 9 00 am to show a smoothie
that you know there is food you just
have to look for it
there is food automatically now and then
I was so tired I wanted to sleep more
but I was curious about all the things
that released and had to take a look at
my phone I was just kind of feeling
anxious
and Restless so I checked it and then I
couldn't sleep and then I just ate
breakfast and then I went to sleep after
all for a little bit and then I woke up
and then I went swimming and here I am
now streaming yay
so
so far so good
I think your tweet's bugged out
why yeah I noticed it did send some
tweets way later like hours hours hours
hours hours later than I originally sent
them
but it didn't send them twice again this
time didn't
mean I tweeted twice
that they were different tweets right
I'm sorry but those were supposed to be
tweeted hours ago before I went to sleep
he believed in something once so quiet
that's a hell of a lot better than
it is
how are you in here
he actually looks happy
you like to drink but nothing more gotta
say that really loud
like like a soul
thing is I think I should make some
changes in my life my life stop with the
drink put it down
stop hanging out with the wrong sword
whatever you want I will do my best to
help you serious
sarcastic I
[Music]
or I have strayed furthest from the past
see ya I don't understand what he wants
from me
he told me to call you Jerry wants us to
kidnap old man enchiladi's daughter fake
tan diet haired Guido loving [\h__\h] by the
name of Grace she's selling her tasteful
pink felter on autoerotica at the moment
when you got her bring her to a place we
got on an Alleyway off Sacramento I can
do that you can do anything Nico don't
let her on that you're kidnapping her
near her place so play along with a test
drive for a while to get her out of
there it's a real mopped up area and
they'll come down on you damn heavy
aren't you going to hell
another one's in the pan
my mom
catch up car go to a computer terminal
yeah we even have one at home
where's my home
it doesn't show my home now does it
that's so weird
I can go here
oh wow
it is what it is
I got a Google
um later what my dream means
I'm interested
I don't really build even like
horoscopes and stuff but I find dream
anal analysis interesting
hmm
oh it's a prison of course there's cops
around
uh makes sense
I should
fearing your cats um
you think it's just a reflection of my
fears
um but it makes no sense because they're
still so young why am I dreaming about
this now
I think it it does it must have to do
with the stress but I just okayed um
before the Stream
I okayed uh some final mixes final
versions
of two songs
I am just missing one more uh the
deadline is kind of over but
I am I'm still waiting on one more that
I gotta check uh
and then we good I think I think if it's
there by tomorrow
it should be
somewhat okay
yeah I I'm pretty
pretty curious what you guys are gonna
say about the genres and the Styles and
everything and the lyrics and my way of
singing because I think
I used different ways of singing here
and there
I tried singing more dramatically and
mature in some um
in in maybe at least one song You Know
no
oh wow I wonder if it will sound good to
you
uh it sounds decent to me what 25 males
what the [\h__\h] I'm a lot of winner no way
I don't believe it don't delete this
without reading like I did because it
was successfully trained what the [\h__\h]
water water
what the [\h__\h] what what
are these men else
Roman
Mallory agreed to marry me this is old
isn't it I'm really old
okay
anything else we want to reply to
ah
thank you for your help my company has
been very pleased with your work now try
to stay out of trouble a word of the
wise the people you're consorting with
and elderly are fools and they're not to
be trusted
where's the person I'm looking for
is this even like syrup
oh well click on the link of the car
sales Advent although a rather car tired
of holding your breath waiting for the
right card to come along hey it's my car
other radical Vehicles aren't for just
anyone our customers want the best of
everything I need a ride with first
power and potency style and says
performance is everything feel free to
cruise around the side and check out our
taught bodies run out your eyes
all these word choices
uh uh run your eyes over our perfect
curves into high maintenance finish we
know you'll be begging to buy
we assure customers that our automobiles
have only the highest qual
[Music]
ity
what am I looking for uh oh I haven't
okay what like this one oh cute it's
pink
I'm not gonna finish reading that what
the
mob daughter okay let's get into the
Tomato car
call the target between 8 and 21 mm-hmm
8 p and 9 p.m oh [\h__\h] we just missed it
can I do something else in the meantime
Jimmy
something let's go marinara car yes
what on Earth what did I expect from
a dealership that's called Auto erotica
[Music]
yeah
oh
are you guys sad that today this is
coming to an end I saw you guys writing
in the chat that oh my God the last time
I was seeing this uh opening but it
might not be
because I might be doing a DLCs at some
point
so you could still see a bit more of it
and yeah
about the last GTA it'll be playing
either
but we'll be taking a little break of
course
because there's many other games
that have been
more and more lining up
for me to play
mm-hmm
San Andreas
yeah most people wanted me to play GTA
San Andreas anyway
in the beginning when I made the poll
started with this one contrarian
discussing Pest Control well I've given
you my advice Peg you do what you think
is best
I mean I don't agree with what he says I
agree that you know best excuse me relax
I didn't mean nothing Well eggs can we
make the right cool we all end up in
prison anyway well you're a crap anchor
though me no favors be careful see you
later boss gentlemen you're only an
associate Phil remember that yeah yeah
okay I gotta tell you this he's not
straight right before I came in here I
saw him talking to Angie again
you better leave
I need to speak to Nico sure boss
but uh think about what I said I will
you know trust me on that
we got real problems
police are all over us
maybe you heard I got served papers
today congratulations Phil yesterday
we got a couple of boys
somebody's talking wants us out of the
picture Not Me Maybe John Gravelly
what an enchilades
somebody got to my people so what are
you going to do about it I don't know
I gotta shut someone up and show people
I mean business
I've known Phil a long time he's
straight more or less
I know him and answer your friends but
that don't worry me too much
hmm
maybe he's too straight
then there's Rey
I don't know I don't trust him if he's
too straight we should just break some
bones I know he's got his eye on the big
prize
but he's no dummy
find me some legs
and he'll be curved
whoever I say to go see go see him and
shut him up
oh
look at him
Corner down there
oh
sorry and the camera cracks me up every
time why was I in the grass
oh
why does he always Park like this
artsy camera angle honestly it if it was
on purpose it would overall be kind of
artsy the way they choose the camera
angles yeah
I I I can see that
if that was the actual purpose yeah
um I guess we're going to G but it's so
far is there nothing else gonna come up
right now
any phone calls
look at all these Bunsen Outdoors
German for expensive as [\h__\h] cars
yeah I should take a taxi if I find one
but I don't want to leave this car
behind its nose
what I know I'm gonna travel before but
bonking into a human
is that a problem
[Music]
no I'm not going to get out of the car
Italiano
get stuffed
Otto
I'm gonna go straight anyway even though
it tells me to go as well
I don't care oh wait but I have to
actually
yeah let me get rid of the cops first
stand up start your step migrate onto
the floor give us your best clocking
moves we wanna see a store karate
wow
hey we should listen to it again
you know what we'll use this long car
ride for listening to
eat
one more time but you guys make sure to
listen to it on Spotify or wherever as
well whatever you're if you have like a
description to something
and on YouTube is fine too
[Music]
if that's your decision Mr pecorino it's
done
oh
wait so this is also like priorities
because suddenly
we gotta go there
looks like it
hello
[Music]
I wanted to hear horror two weeks
can we find it
[Music]
I like I like those I don't know what
you call those I think
the a the a sound in the background
and now since the block has arrived
hearts in the cage we have for a good
time
birds have a feather feather who turns
thank you
[Music]
impeccable we're only getting started
because
do the Holiday Dance
announcement
[Music]
and the juice of the party is not though
but see that's it
could walk away
get your stuff migrate onto the floor
give us your best we wanna see you soon
[Music]
we're only getting started
taking Flyers show me what you got here
we dance
[Music]
ah
nice
hey oh I need a car oh
[Music]
all right no problem I got one
so fitting the Moonlight place after
this
[Music]
but I can't listen to it now I got [\h__\h]
to do
I see his car he should be heading over
to a chop shop in Forever
don't get too comfortable with him they
go like every red what's a Chop Shop
it might create a good opportunity where
kill him at the gas station
can I blow up the gas station with my
rocket launcher
exterminate Ray and his bodyguards
um but yeah should I wait for the gas
station not shoot yes
[Music]
I want to shoot already
foreign
[Music]
thank you
Get Wrecked
the meeting went to plan Mr beggarino
's tight
um
you're welcome pecolino really
I'm always So Satisfied whenever I can
stay in this part it makes me so happy
what's going on here
[Music]
oh they're playing my music I like
movies music my playlist
oh
[Music]
maybe I should take a taxi from here
take me with you for free of course
or else
speed speed speed step up the gas let's
go okay yes emergency emergency
fans in Liberty City perfect maybe
should have a concert in Liberty City
you guys they know each other Nico good
to see you interesting friendships you
both keep yeah very interesting the
mayor will be here in a minute
senators
by later
everyone wants to pay homage to a dying
Legend everyone wants that homage
everyone
now that you hear what I said yeah I
heard what you said Nico our friend here
is telling me that the enchiladas are in
League with the Russians guys how much
time how much hours do you think
73 years I want to spread out my snacks
nicely I killed his uncle
spare them and this is how he repays me
one two five two three what the [\h__\h] and
now we stealing drugs right from the
goddamn terrible
so what we're saying is this is a matter
of Security National normally maybe free
about cocaine keeps controlling some of
you guys are exaggerating probably
all right what's my role in this the
distribution network is a fleet of Vans
parked in a group
product is packed into the frames of the
Vans ready to be moved all over the
country and everything whatever it is
and for me for you I've got a real gift
for you
get this done then we'll talk
as long as I don't fail emissions maybe
free
you're pink
hmm
well usually I first try most missions
and now I'm also speeding by taking
taxes all the time so
[Music]
we might be pretty pretty fast
I wouldn't mind
it's freaking weekend
I feel like celebrating the weekend bye
cuddling my cats that are not dead
because your business is just a cover
for the drugs so the area is heavily
guarded
looks like fun with the thingy
staple staple car thingy
oh [\h__\h] this looks like a big one hey am
I supposed to take out all of those
it's a grenade party
and I just where am I coming from
you got Sharpshooters find a way into
the compound to destroy the vans
should we take a car
or should I walk
find the way
maybe for here
probably just right here
or left actually ah
you did that it looks like I should
maybe go left
okay
we're here I don't know is it here or
there
both could work
um I'm scared
and it's okay just do it like it just do
it like you always do it Wawa
where's this person there's supposedly I
I see him can I take him out quietly or
is everybody gonna react to it
immediately
if I just take my sniper
could I know
no quiet in this one I wish we had
silent like in GTA 5 I was able to take
out people really quietly nobody would
know this thanks to my silencers
hmm
but okay
uh destroy the Vans it says don't even
destroy the people
well I can destroy the bands easily with
my rocket launcher
is he still alive
where where are they they're shooting
but like at what I don't even see them
take this go up
he said you're surrounded are they who
are they talking to maybe they fought
for the the shot came from somebody else
yeah
and they're fighting someone else right
now who are you fighting
can I get anyone from here I don't see
anybody I think it's all behind
bock bock
but they're still
he's just is he not just lying on the
ground
wait oh
can I parkour up there
oh can I do this
oh
wait I don't even have armor I can't do
this Mission without armor I just
realized also that really spooked me
[Music]
wait I'll be back guys just wait for me
am I gonna fail this Mission if I go
away
best car
I just want the arm I I really need the
armor
okay I have to do it before I mention
that's okay that's okay
um
I don't think I would survive it without
the armor so
uh okay
first oh there's actually one close by
too
foreign
thanks for the membership
no it wasn't a fail I went away on
purpose
it doesn't count
doesn't count and you know it
don't worry guys I'm not shooting
anybody we know how to use
okay can I buy any more RPGs I think one
yeah okay
wish me luck guys
I did it wrong I did it wrong again
why why why why why why why why why why
why
why why why why what
ah very dedicated to your job if you
just let your car fall down there to
chase me oh [\h__\h] I
uh
yeah bye
oh I'm losing it right now in this very
spot in this very moment oh
it's right at the edge of the circle
uh Taxi
very convenient
uh okay
I'm actually I guess if no taxi is here
I'm gonna call
is there really no taxi here
I need the cab there's one there no
longer there's a cab coming to you it's
okay
[Music]
it is shown on the radar by the blue
marker
oh
oh oh oh oh oh
it didn't look like a taxi hey hey
let me why are you stopping hold F hold
we're not stealing it Flemings
you know where to go right
liquid noise this is the point where
normal customers big go away
okay thank you I appreciate it thank you
should I still go from the same side
should I attempt the
um
same thing again
oh wait there
yeah that's where they all are most of
them
hmm
yes okay yeah now I know that there's
another Sharpshooter like
about to shoot me when I go up that
fence thingy that wall
so
or actually what if I don't shoot until
I am up there
um
let me get a good headshot in
climber okay okay
because then like someone was up there
but not from the get-go apparently
someone was there shooting ah that guy
is that not the same guy
as the one who shot me
uh who I shot first
oh well
look at this parkour wow
okay okay
we're in guys we're in where's Owen
hey oh
one here one here one here one here oh I
got a good view from here uh
um
are they gonna see me immediately
they just have like a GPS for me it's so
mean
uh
okay they're bad at aiming and they
don't all have a
ah
they don't all have a sharp shooting
thingy
was that a good kill did he die
there's one more
noise okay oh one over here
where you want to go here
okay
wonderful I think that's oh
there you are
is there anything left that I can do
from here
don't see anything
what
something came from here no or did it
like just bounce off oh there's uh
oh
they're smart these NPCs are really
looking for me yeah
okay
there's supposed to be someone there so
it's weird
where did that come from where did it
fish
that took my HP not my armor what the
hell
and then if I reach the top I can just
maybe
um shoot all the cars with my RPG
maybe it's like X because it was extra
fatal
oh
we can take some Sharp Shooting ammo
well let me switch here
you're gonna see me aren't they
wait wait wait wait wait I didn't see
any cars oh there's armor
but my armor is full isn't it oh no not
quite
where are the cars
okay not quite grenade time yet
come on
what are you guys doing
okay that's when I get oh there's a
first aid kit dead
making sure
[\h__\h] oh okay
okay
oh
[Music]
can they escape both the cars if I'm too
slow
oh
I got the shoulder
mommy got his face
bad choice buddy reloading is always a
bad choice I is this one
hmm I'm on kind of on the wrong building
I can barely see
what I need to see
I see a guy down there though
but now that I eradicated so many of
them maybe I can go down
hmm
um
gotta be careful maybe there's somebody
in here even
but right now I'm feeling pretty
confident
now it's good to get close I think so
too pretty safe especially if we get the
first aid kit that I saw
I remember the position
okay now they're all on my level
someone's right there
bug
there
is this one of the car wow it's the car
that uh well again it's showing me the
car okay
um
maybe I'll throw a grenade
is that gonna work
yes okay yes of course
what else
oh
[Music]
okay
[\h__\h] this is so over
here it takes ages for his
oh my God I swear even when he was like
standing back up you can't move for a
little bit
holy [\h__\h] I was pressing W Lincoln like
a maniac
oh man
what Packy I need to restart the mission
all right we'll speak to you soon
I love me let me redo it ah yeah
that was so unfortunate yeah he is not a
phoenix apparently
[\h__\h]
it was going so well and then I just
walked into the fire and I'm like kind
of like paralyzed forever
because I fall down the drive where the
car is the moment I get up I catch fire
again
great
time
so close though
I am cuddling with cars candy
yeah no no I'm getting armor what do you
think I'm doing
um do I have to get this again too
no okay
oh
shh I am going in for a try
first times the charm
do I need Roman again to help me out
here
possibly
buy more grenades
everyone's gonna be fine on grenade
like what five six cars
eh what did he just say no
ah but there's a taxi here
press F long long very long okay
he's got free will
the hell
it's on a cooldown
47 sheesh
okay
here I am again I'm gonna do it the same
way dog because I think that was
the best way of doing it
very expensive car ride
oh you know yesterday uh
um narissa sent me really random I don't
think there was any particular reason
but she was sending me European uh
what kind of songs and like dance songs
and I think it was called the group was
called I think toy box
I don't think I was really aware of them
but I listened to a few songs
and yeah it's like it's like they're
trying to recreate those Barbie songs
like with the aggressive male voice and
the ridiculous lyrics and the squeaky
female voice mm-hmm
do you know do you know it I was
listening to the the Ahoy song
and another one
that I forgot but yeah interesting maybe
for future karaoke
yeah the Sailor song that was funny
they certainly don't take themselves
seriously I think
but yeah narissa told me she loves these
kind of
European dance tracks or whatever that
is
where is this guy
okay I'm gonna try my
patient again
nice shot
foreign
cover that's not taking cover
oh there should still be some oh yeah
yeah
yeah are you going also one here
[Music]
was that a Kill
pentacle
oh ah he's up same guy same guy
what was it okay now we're good I think
but are they gonna be some people here I
remember some people showing up there
[Music]
come out there
or else I will come out
okay
it's like I can see the future
I have the advantage
the future is
success for me failure for all of you
the funeral for everybody today I'm
gonna have a funeral for like basically
all of Liberty City
it'll be beautiful I'll I'll have lots
of flowers and everything I'll make it
nice I'll make it worth it
who can I shoot from up here
oh
yeah yeah yeah what what these shots
they love that they're coming from the
top
so weird
someone you
am I getting hit nah
you'll get a shot and who else wants a
shot yeah
oh you you don't want a shot okay okay
okay here take this nice beanie though I
like the beanie cute
I could take this one out quickly from
now here so
oh oh oh oh I wish I could shoot that
guy I don't think I can
who's this fingers in the lightweight
ah oh well okay let me blow that one up
but then they'll already be like alerted
is that a problem are they gonna drive
them away
that's my only fear if I start now
I'm good
they will run away with the cars
get him away from the stuff that means
like they that sounds like they want to
remove me not um
the cars
run run
make sure
and I'll I won't blow up the van right
in front of the door immediately I want
to take some uh distance
um
should I I um
[Music]
oh they don't want to shoot because I'm
at the van
you are not getting away [\h__\h] they're
gonna try to get away now
foreign
okay
go next go next
of course
you're late to notice really late
and another one
um
wow
in the GTA music let's go
some extra pocket money
everybody's dead but I have a star no
wait what what happens just now did I
get a call didn't I accept it did I
cancel it
many questions no answers I have to run
I have to run I have to run
it wasn't me
wait can I get out of there
uh
I skipped it now I didn't want to
let me get up here and then get to the
other side really quickly
that RPG in my head no no that's that's
a jrpg not a not what you think it's
it's not what you think it is
you misunderstand RPG I don't know what
you mean I don't know what what do you
mean there's an RPG in the shape of a
gun
and now we got two stars
okay okay time to leave
quickly quickly
all right easy easy peasy lemon
squeezing yeah we did it not good job
how much money did I get for that I
didn't see it
but that feels like it should have
brought me a lot of money did you guys
see it
14 500.
okay
[Music]
what's next oh
I actually don't see any letters on my
map so I guess we're waiting for a call
ah there it is
speaking of the devil
no more jobs
you've done good things right I'm out
I've given you a lot of protection
[Music]
sounds wonderful but there must be a cat
because apparently I'm still playing
this game for three hours
uh what you said what airport am I not
getting a marker give me the marker
please ah I'm calling Roman
into the country for me this is almost
over I'm going to finish it it's going
to be a Twist isn't there
fly Island all right when I see Darko
there's gonna be a Twist maybe pick up
Roman ah we're picking him up but we're
not going bowling even though the
bowling alley is really close to that
it's so far too it's so far
but we need a car anyway I'm gonna drive
I'm gonna do it
a darker twist
dark twist dark coat
okay
well if there's a taxi right here I'm
Gonna Take It
okay there we go ah [\h__\h] what the
no no
no
[Music]
that's really not what I wanted to do
when you press F so long that it also
makes you exit I guess this is the
problem
can someone please drive me to my
destination
okay come on no no no no no no no no no
no no
I'm not driving myself
I want to be driven
[Music]
okay finally
why are you saying that this just new
finale I don't know they're manipulating
me it's not my fault and being
manipulated oh
what's he doing
they are bringing it to the cargo bay at
Francis International I do not want to
be late after I've waited so long
head to the Rendezvous but you want me
to get a car done soon
uh car shopping
they all don't look so nice here I guess
I'll just go with a normal one
he is immune to car stealing all right
I'll take this one
with friends from the village we're
lucky I lost myself that day too
everything that was good and innocent in
me died along with them if I could live
those hours again
I think I would have preferred to be
buried in the pit along with everyone
else this is all that is left of me
what am I good at Roman
what is my trade like dealing that [\h__\h]
because that is all that is over to me
the good friend you still have integrity
no matter what you say there is Humanity
you still have the power to be
important that you believe that maybe I
will start to believe it when Darko is
there yeah I never did but at this point
what does it matter it's the playground
think about your future instead of doing
horrible things that have happened to
you to us to all of us in the past after
this is done then we can talk about
forgiveness and Redemption now is not
the time when I say another death won't
matter but this is probably the death
that will matter and get me in big
trouble who knows
anyway if you guys want to see me uh
playing with the
playing with the swing uh I did that I
think in the second GTA 4 stream
thank you
sneeze Super Chat incoming oh wait
there's ah
I'm gonna are you gonna
put them for another time
How will I know that you're wishing me
gazunta
How Will I Know
[Music]
ah some of you guys still got the
members messages
ready to go
very very good
oh thanks for the gift thank you okay I
didn't mean all of you you didn't have
to thank you
thank you
[Music]
thank you soon guys thank you wow
she snows
she sneezed she's nosed I snoozed
out of my nose
let's go
it's gonna be dangerous
it's gonna be a bye
it's gonna happen
okay oh [\h__\h] oh
ouch one last bunk or the first book of
many
you remember me
I don't know you
all right
damn
oh is that swollen
oh
let's see
friends
that guy's killed
my [\h__\h] neighbors
[\h__\h]
lies
[\h__\h] lies
so that makes it okay
to stab your friends in the back
Sean to be [\h__\h] it makes strange choices
[\h__\h] you strange choices how much
[Laughter]
a thousand
you'll kill my friends for one thousand
dollars how much
that's really not much what the [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
me then
[\h__\h] hypocrite
trust me
between me a favor
Nico come on
let's go
let him suffer he knows what he did
doesn't look like he enjoys life too
much
[Music]
does he regret it
does he want to oh it's a choice to
I don't know I don't feel like I know
enough I need to
see what happened to me
I need to know more about like his
feelings
um
[Music]
you're not really making a good argument
in my opinion
but Roman
he looks cute Roman is
you know I don't I don't want to upset
Roman
and he's you know sweet guy
well I imagine instead I just shoot
Roman
what's the better ending
kind of lost
[Music]
walking away the one-eyed shoes
go bowling
yeah
you lose nothing for doing it and the
execution is cool
I lose Nothing by doing it
it doesn't matter
I just have to
do I'm lost
then I want to do it
okay not so many just one dude
damn Jesus
oh
that oh
thank you hey thanks me
okay calm down hello oh
I'm not doing this I was just gonna
shoot once make it quick
everyone sorry woman
we should go
yeah quick quick quick
coming come on get into this car
Nico is now hopefully satisfied
and has uh quenched his urges or
whatever
I'm turning this [\h__\h] off I can't take
listening to those annoying eggs same
it's already off though anyway don't I
I'm feeling you you've got your revenge
I don't know how it feels
try to take it all in this is the moment
you've been waiting for you
what do you mean you don't know how you
feel I feel like you know we built up to
this so we have to kill him
I feel empty it's something and now he
feels empty which is you know character
development a realization that it was
this is what that was not worth it but I
think that's also necessary
[Music]
this makes sense
does that make you happy of course it
doesn't make me happy but
maybe this is good for you maybe now
that you know that revenge is not what
you are after look for fulfillment in
other places healthy works Maybe
maybe I think it makes sense this action
makes sense for the character Nico
[Music]
I don't know maybe I'm maybe I'm
misinterpretating his character but this
action and then him regretting it and
realizing oh that didn't help is exactly
how I would imagine him doing it
so what now
what now
I don't know
yeah we killed so many people why why
spare the main target mm-hmm
well you know if if we were an ethical
being that doesn't kill then we wouldn't
do it but we do kill that's our thing so
you know
epics have
if ethics are something that we don't
know is that something you can eat what
is that
[Music]
also he came all the way from Europe I
mean the Darko guy
just for this so
I see I see your little [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
flying red is dead that was more
satisfying Maybe
than the dark or death
Tony or Tony violence
that one is not joining I can tell you
that
that big chicken isn't joining holotori
ever though do you want to come in and
hang with Brucie no
I need to be alone
thank you for being with me cousin
good man Roman call me Nico the wedding
is soon I'm excited
will you you you he also gave me a
thumbs up so
all things are well I'm just waiting for
a call now
hey puppy puppy pop
[Music]
Florian I thought you should know Darko
is dead He's finally paid for his crimes
that's good to know Nick
's forget the past yes that's what I
would like to do
so long you look after yourself
those two are my favorite characters
him and Roman
I feel like a lot of the others are just
like character wise not
that good a lot of them were just really
shallow
angry mafia boss
blee blah blue I don't know
um
yeah so many filler characters that
don't matter
and are not really special either I
think GTA 5 had so many more
characters that matter then they were
interesting and that I wouldn't forget
about and that kind of
um burned themselves into my brain you
know
I remember way more people from GTA 5
and what kind of people they were than
in GTA 4.
Nico give a call if you need some cash I
am the Batman usually got some jobs is
this side a side thing because that
doesn't sound very important
you miss Trevor no but I mean he had a
lot of personality I hated him I still
hate him but I I can remember him and he
has an interesting backstory I mean also
he was a main character but you know
even the other non-main characters I
think were interesting I loved the the
family of uh what's his name I loved his
daughter his son was interesting too the
wife was interesting
um
Michael Michael
Nico what the [\h__\h] I ain't heard from
you how about you
I went to the strip club already plenty
of times coming to the club for killing
and for watching
you better not get offended but an end
yet you give me a thumbs down you
hypocrite
no
wow most of us melted yeah I don't even
know how to touch this
oh no
God damn it
[Music]
that's how hot it is
oh don't worry I don't even want Side
Story stuff
um
again a reminder for races okay
fandom
the races were fun
okay one more
what am I doing
um
[Music]
the girl oh yeah what happened to Dad
um ah
there she is
I'm uh calling about the car come to my
place
it's a present for my daughter
laughs
my daughter's got her
sweet 16.
[Music]
and You Know Rich parents buy their
daughters a pink car for their sweet
succeed it's a thing it's the whole
thing
otherwise they're gonna throw a freaking
tantrum
and tell me
that she hates me
and that I am not supporting them in any
way and that I am ruining their life and
that I'm the worst person ever
[Music]
I'm just making up things but
yeah remember that show on MTV
stain it's my chance to shine sweet 16
now
I watched all of those MTV shows not the
sweet 16 one not so much for some reason
small small Wawa
who was interested in watching all the
dating shows
like the the next where they were all in
the bus and the one that I talked about
before where they impersonate your
favorite
um whatever singer
usually singer
because small Wawa
was so far from being a popular good
looking
girl in the right age to be in the
dating scene
that all of that I don't know it was
really fascinating to watch I guess
oh and Tila Tequila that one I didn't
watch that much though
um what's what's his name that old dude
who had a mansion full of young
somewhat pretty looking ladies
yeah falling over him so fake Flavor of
Love yeah not Hugh Hefner
did Hugh Hefner have a show like that
too and talking about Flavor of Love the
most ridiculous show to exist on MTV
huh it was so obvious that all of them
were in it for the money
like how how can you man all these gold
diggers all these black
hungry money hungry [\h__\h]
[Music]
and the guy was obnoxious and stupid too
Flavor Flav his personality
um
how can you like
it must be even for him surely he must
be aware right that nobody there is
actually really into him right right
because he thinks if he thinks that any
of that
is not because of his money
then I feel bad but
I I hope that everybody everybody
involved is just doing it for the clout
and the money
then they're all bad
and I guess birds of a feather flock
together
[Music]
um
they know but it makes good TV sometimes
they had those reunion shows where they
would like scream at
it on stage and make big big drama one
more last time and this [\h__\h] that
always
New York I think was her name
was in the first season and then she
kept on coming back like as a guest
later and and then for just for the sake
of drama because she was the most
dramatic person
they would leave her and make her
compete again and then every time she's
like getting ditched in the last round
in the finals because yeah she thought
she's winning so confident and then he
did just her but
she up like she actually like acted like
she may really like him
I wonder if she really did like him
or if she's just good at acting
like that kind of person
unbelievable man crazy [\h__\h] on TV
[Music]
but it's a little bit different
I love Riding in Cars with you like that
show that I was watching in the hotel
room with rmt
no somewhere in the south love Island
was it where it's like random couples
being put together
and then they decide who to
kick out
backstabbing each other
depending on
so supposedly I didn't think a manly guy
like you would drive they match or not
you got a wife or a girlfriend or
something I'm picking this up the
paintwork was real feature on this car
yeah what a gentleman you don't need
guys like you in the city no more all
the good men are gone is what my dad
says that sounds reload School
you and him close nah not really I'm one
of the good guys ladies I don't like his
tough guy friends I only hang out with
gay guys you know at least they won't
try and get your pants every 10 seconds
not that I don't like guys trying to get
in my pants I appreciate fun as much as
the next girl maybe even more than the
next one you having fun at the moment
maybe too much fun call me Gracie by the
way sure thing
need to get body work done
oopsie sorry you have it I have spooked
Gracie take it
[Music]
could fail it doesn't seem like that's
over pull it up control stop the car now
[\h__\h] bird no
oh no oh I'm dialing my
mind he's gonna do more than test drive
your ass try to call him without the
phone
am I [\h__\h] this up
she should be in a reality TV show uh
many many many GTA characters
[\h__\h] that was her
and many GTA characters would fit well
into reality TV shows especially from
GTA
5. [\h__\h] [\h__\h] that [\h__\h] you're gonna
kill us
[Music]
[Applause]
all right we're staying on this Lane I
guess
[Music]
when you grab the wheel the [\h__\h] she's
so stupid what's in there chill I dare
you to drive us into a police car
yeah
you can see so much trouble lipstick my
daddy loves his little girl
[Music]
I'm Gonna Make You crash these things I
don't think so yeah we need some duct
tape
was true you ain't getting out hey
help you're [\h__\h] with the wrong girl
[\h__\h] see you later you dumb [\h__\h]
that's it
should I kill her
goddammit okay
oh
we'll try this again
[Laughter]
she did it
of course you did
if you're messing around like that
Gracie Gracie Gracie
so do I not spook her if I just am very
very careful with the car with the sexy
I'll do my best
seems like one scratch is okay maybe
even two
but free is absolutely no no Grace why
are you selling this car see you see
pretty good let's just say
okay it's not that far you've got a few
disagreements about blood alcohol levels
how's Grandma to get back to Albany
after a big night out in Algonquin if
she's not drunk Drive she she could be
sober you sound like my dad anyway you
clearly have not been to Mason at night
there's no such thing as sober in that
place no [\h__\h] way if I stick to booze
it's a miracle I keep on talking lady
keep on talking I'm totally listening
[Music]
wholesale we'll see
time to initiate the kidnapping take
care
I changed now
is she still gonna manipulate me then
not after the car I'm after you say that
I'll say it so clearly control yourself
remain calm and you might just walk away
from this with your life oh my [\h__\h]
God you [\h__\h] pervert I'm dialing my
daddy he's gonna do more than test drive
your ass try to call him without the
phone
what do you mean Nico I don't understand
okay we gotta be quick before she takes
over
all right
it's much trouble lipstick my daddy
loves his little girl [\h__\h] this is
difficult anytime she could just turn my
car around and then I don't know how to
get how to turn it back around again
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[Music]
you can't get out right now because of
the car's position
wait okay okay okay okay
[Music]
I'm good I'm good
I don't think so
God damn it
I'm not just letting you take me yes you
are no no
no no no
oh
[\h__\h] I'm not hanging around here
oh this mission
I'm slow
[\h__\h]
you think that's gonna help okay
stupid [\h__\h]
the guy who calls about the car the one
with the sexy ax just let me kidnap you
man
why are you being so stupid about it
so you like the car I didn't think a
manly guy like you would drive something
like this I do like the color for a
girlfriend or something but I don't
think I would get a car like this for
myself
cute colors but on the car I wouldn't do
it
what my dad says your dad sounds reloads
would you not resist if you were
abducted I mean I don't know probably I
would try but I
put the guy like Nico he would scare the
[\h__\h] out of me so probably eventually I
would she said I don't like guys trying
to get money that happens maybe oh do I
have to try to see if he's got his gun
if he's got a [\h__\h] gun
it's still fun at the moment maybe too
much fun call me Grace you're [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
okay that counts for one right
those two things come for one right okay
we're initiating the kidnapping
yet even test driving are you used to
driving on the other side of the road or
something
all right test drive's over oh up yeah
control it's not the car now [\h__\h] bird
how does she know that I'm a bird and he
ain't gonna treat you as polite as I do
that's for sure you're not calling [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] you're coming with me you
[\h__\h] you sick
that makes two of us
she already started I'm not even on the
highway yet on the bridge I am not just
letting you take
me
stop punching me
okay I'm gonna do it slowly okay
[Music]
like this
chill out before I pull this trigger and
make you real [\h__\h] chill you are in
so much trouble lipstick my daddy loves
his little girl
hey I don't have patience for this but
if I go too slow she just wants to get
out
I don't know patience How Are You Gonna
Keep Me
slow it down let's return the wheel okay
okay okay okay okay
[\h__\h] I am Gracie ancelotti and I
shut up peace oh okay why didn't we do
this earlier I didn't know that this was
gonna happen
wonderful
[Music]
I haven't heard from you in a while oh
Jacob I've got
don't think it would
let's speak soon though huh okay
that's that sounds like a pretty
standard dialogue when being with a girl
didn't you say this before when he
wasn't kidnapping
[Music]
I feel like I remember that though
taking a nap now yeah naps are nice
I am showing her how great naps are
she will only benefit from it
[Music]
ah we did it
I thought we would have to fight her the
whole ride
what she's just sleeping in my car
do not report it it's not your business
there we go
there he is Stevie dumped the car I'll
take this piece of ass guys
the beach better be worth the trouble
I've got some serious cash and he pissed
off Gerald
that's reason enough for me well it
better pay quick I hate to think of the
fight she'll put up if you try to cut
her fingers off
I go
all right okay I guess no car for me
orange is better anyway
Orange Is the New Pink and the New Black
and the new everything
Gordon has the [\h__\h] I'm done with her
thanks
my brother will be a happy man I'll get
things in
them
I see you little [\h__\h]
I've I've uh developed an eye for the
flying rats
yes orange is the new orange
and once again I don't have anything
left
somebody call me and give me something
to do
it
what do I do
I get another call
um
I don't want to hang out with these
idiots
this life is too peaceful it's boring I
wanna I wanna I wanna rob a bank
I need to do something
sleep okay house is close
I will walk them
Maybe
let me go to my shitty apartment
oh who's shooting
maybe it's time to become Batman maybe I
should save all these people
from the crimes that are happening every
day in New York to The Cross by me
I'll play two roles I play the the crime
person and I'll play
the hero
get the best of both worlds
is there a superhero movie where that's
the plot
Deadpool
really
oh interesting
surprisingly no
sorry man I can't do a show right now
I've got the problem I've got to deal
with
kind of okay if that pool isn't even
quite the that plot then I think they
should make one
party how come nobody ever made a movie
like that before
or a show
[Music]
Megamind
I've heard of that
all right
game
good morning hopefully this day is a
better day
with more crimes
I'm getting really bored here
any crimes to satisfy my craving also
let me check my DMs I got some DMS it's
important
okay
okay okay last song is
they're working on it they're working on
it
how's my favorite girl we need a picture
of Chris
her mom's still upset so I'm gonna go
there to take a [\h__\h] photo okay I'll
send you it on my phone you guys take
the photo she's not alone is she
for real
okay I'll take my pretty car
[Music]
where is my radio
ah
now it was right there
there it is
[Music]
[\h__\h] where's the where is it this one
huh
Ransom
what
is that it
[Music]
okay
I'm a pretty pretty beautiful card
I hope nothing happens to it
but today is the last day I might as
well take this car out for a ride
[Music]
a dangerous scratch on that police car
damn
lucky
[Music]
oh it's right here it's actually close
to my home
new
[Music]
I haven't used the phone photo taking
function in a while let's see if I
remember
go upstairs
to the safe house okay
how far upstairs oh I hear someone
crying
oh it's this
the fancy doors is always where the
story is happening
say somebody's there you could have
taken the picture
for some fries for about five hours
sorry your shift ain't over Gordo I'm
just smile for your daddy
[Music]
beautiful oh [\h__\h] I should have sent it
right away can I still send it
like in a different I'll just take the
picture again
hey you've been missing me look up here
I'll just take it again
it's easier
[Music]
you're not really looking at me right
now but okay
foreign
bye bye have fun listening to the cries
thank God it's not me listening to it
I'm out of here
with my
where's my car wait it's in the back
back of the building must be in the back
of the building
won't believe his girls hold up with a
guy no more nothing less that guy is
into some sick [\h__\h] later on Becky
the other side
you look like a little slice of cheddar
cheese my baby
what now I don't even have anywhere to
go do I
what is this end game it might keep on
having to wait for them to call me
[\h__\h]
blah
blah stay out of my way
[Laughter]
yeah maybe those three hours are mostly
waiting time that's what I'm thinking
I don't know what I'm doing
I'll spend some time in here fixing my
car oh
what do you do after that
what do you do once you're inside
oh there we go
I don't want to change the color is it
random
oh no
I mean it looks nice but what the [\h__\h]
my orange
give me back my orange
man announcement that block has arrived
Block in your hearts and the cage We're
Here for a Good Time
or this
that is oh interesting but now
[Music]
ain't no start ain't no starts
this is something else
[Music]
sexy
hey I thought I'd just drive in to fix
my car I didn't know it forces you to
change the color to a random color
do will I ever get back my orange
that doesn't look like orange to me
it's white though
[Music]
foreign
it was a unique color
wow from black to Black
what what
Gary hasn't tried to get a hold of you
it's about your girl go see him in the
can
okay
ah finally something's on my map
the white was nice too yeah
oh wow
regrets
big regrets
[Music]
that looks like a Batman mobile
Batmobile right
[Music]
where am I supposed to think I'm above
no man
someone else yeah yeah must have been I
was in the shower and I heard the phone
ringing so I thought you might have
called or something my bad
let me try to
change the route
hello I'm not up there I'm over here
okay
[Music]
um
[Applause]
I said clap your hands
[Music]
oh
what's up with my driving right now am I
drunk
[Music]
foreign
means clap your hands
in case you haven't realized it
is
[Music]
clap your hands
clap your hands TV
[Music]
pop your head
taco
time
we are here
welcome to prison what's he got to say
this time
finally our own song
hey yeah
yeah a friend of mine in here tells me
that a close friend of yours girl you've
been spending a lot of time with
recently so I have to clean off for feet
okay yeah
desperately and quickly and he's looking
for
I think you and Herb should go out in a
glamorous state in Algonquin
but move your [\h__\h] ass pal
like a chump you get me
uh-huh
okay
is this like
um
the only storyline I have left right now
because
it seems like
it's the only thing I still have going
on now
[Music]
three four four let's go
I'm sorry
oh yeah
[Music]
how far
yesterday I committed murder
IRL
pretty aggressively
[Music]
killed a really fast snack that was on
my ceiling
and I
slapped it
three times even when it was already
dead
um it's like long long leg flying thing
no spider
what's it called in English again a
crane fly yeah I hate cream thighs
[Music]
I know how they even fit through the
window
of their big ass legs
no don't kill screens I know they're
harmless but they are
an eyesore in my eyes
okay
[Music]
they disturb me
you know enjoying my my apartment
calmly and they freak me out because
they're so big I'm going to insect jail
well only if they are able to take me
down hey
few days later if you don't hear from me
guys that means that the insects have
gotten to me
I've already
felt the after effects
something has bitten me stung me on my
my hands she can ride in the trunk
you're coming from you guys
at me not talking about the game you you
are amazing oh
oh what what the [\h__\h] everybody
suddenly getting such random compliments
so sweet
I'm leaving behind my car what the [\h__\h]
oh what the [\h__\h] oh what the [\h__\h] don't
damage your car you will kill Gracie uh
maybe it's better that way I don't know
let me take this path oh there's no Pap
there never was a path oh wait there's a
bath
[\h__\h] okay path please
[Applause]
I'll never get my car back again
[Music]
wait I gotta remember where it is like
it's close it's like somewhere here next
to the paint spray
average day in New York obviously are
you from New York
[Music]
I know like maybe one person in New York
and I live in Ohio Ohio
good morning to you too sir
ah sorry
missed my turn oh they're involving the
police now you guys better not sure that
the police
sorry let her keep on talking I don't
understand I don't speak English I don't
understand what she's saying
just gotta blur it out in my brain
[Music]
he's taking her on a on a fun ride you
know
she should appreciate it she's seeing
more of the city thanks to me
[Music]
I'm giving her a tour through New York
not only places but also like
experiences you know what I mean
this is the New York experience
so I'll be watching this griddle [\h__\h]
for you where is she in the trunk
she don't play is she dead now she's too
quiet
it's gonna punch me
I knew it
she's wild one
I'll try to calm it down
see you later Nico come on
please call me back quickly because I'm
waiting literally just for this mission
[Music]
maybe I should look for my car
where exactly why does it not like show
me where I left my car or is it
do you think it's despawning already
is it like here
you think it's gone
this game should just bring me back my
car
that's so stupid
yeah
[Music]
like especially if it's a special car
that I got as a reward
they shouldn't make it so that these
phones they should they should they
should let me have it
forever it should be safe from
despawning
that's so stupid
okay get in properly otherwise we're
gonna get in trouble
where can I do
and they say it's teaspoon and here we
are thank you
yeah I'm pretty sure I didn't have this
issue in GTA 5 but I'm not sure
I'm pretty sure but I'm not sure that's
Wawa duality
I agree but I also don't understand
oh
hey what's wrong
it is good news and there's bad news
uh-huh good news is everything's coming
together wonderful bad news they're
gonna make a blind bit of difference to
me
okay
uh-huh
no I guess not thanks no I want to have
it spelled out explain
the ex-boyfriend or your girl is going
to agree to the divorce terms
unfortunately turns out he wasn't our
only problem
some of the crap is turned up
I don't think I'll be getting out any
look after yourself
Justice
that's what you get
for getting caught Nico me and Gracie is
waiting for you just off of Frankfort
Avenue in Northwood looks like our
joyful time with her is coming to an end
that's a [\h__\h] tragedy we should throw
a goodbye party that's the plan
hopefully someone might bring a big
present for us to this shindig as well
maybe a big bag and diamonds will help
us get over the pain of losing her we're
waiting for you man
what kind of diamonds are we speaking
this time
get go to pack his car in Northwood or
why wait what here
Taxi
I just picked up something
what did I just pick up
a pack of gum
what is this
because I wanted the taxi
it was like Flats
all right let's do it
weird
here we are thanks a lot easy honey
okay uh
[\h__\h]
ing here
big difference
right here
I
how you doing nothing suspicious in my
back teeth not nothing nothing
suspicious at all
maybe we shouldn't have heard
in the back seat with that thing in her
mouth
Becky my man driving next to the police
the stream's happening in my car she was
just telling me how much she loved me
what do you think of Nico Gracie
Gracie understood have a nice day Nico's
a good friend of mine don't say that
about him
follow orders girls
sometimes a guy has got to hang out with
lowlifes like people here he's got his
uses
that's right he is definitely a bad
influence on you [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh music [\h__\h]
wrong radio channel let me just turn it
off
I kind of starting to feel bad for this
chick
we've been treating her like [\h__\h] for
quite some time now
yeah
are we killing her
does it sounded like we're gonna kill
her
oh wait it's a masuka
trading her okay good
okay she really doesn't deserve to be
killed
go
what you waiting for huh
vamos vamos
oh it's that thing again
but it's not a flying rat
[Music]
I need to pick up more Spanish words I
only know vamos
gracias
amigo
the uh
[Music]
uh hasta la vista
what else do I know
[Music]
um
buenos dias
and that's right
no just from everyday life I have
Patrona you guys told me Patrona
oh Diablo is Spanish
oh yeah Community let's go
oh
despacito
[Applause]
despacito go around the back to the
exchange point
[Music]
s
foreign
[Music]
give her back you animals
suffered enough hand over this stuff
hand over crazy
I'm here for you we didn't over the
[\h__\h] stop all right calm down both of
you are you
we put the ice in the middle
we walk back
dang to send over the good
we leave and to pick up this stuff
at the end I don't I don't comprehend it
show us the goods
why are they hand holding like that
where's he hiding it
that's us very [\h__\h] sauce
come back to me honey
Let Her Go
we gotta check if it's real
shoot shoot
okay boring
Montana
welcome
huh
oh
Angel who is this
friend
my friend how was it that's whenever
something is stolen from me you're not
far away I've never stolen anything from
you oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
the Dominican Beach they stole my
diamonds and you have been trying to rob
the eggs to rob me
I don't care what you did to that man
but we ain't leaving here without them
diamonds
I think I know who's got the eyes
what did you he's already moving on
takes so much time to freaking reload
man
I'm staying in the back you're my tank
please thank you
foreign
you go right side okay
let's see
anyone here no where is where's the ice
oh
nice position you got there
am I doing oh no I'm not even doing
these shots I felt like I was doing it
shooter
oh that was a leaf
okay okay only one left
does he have it
[Music]
[\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] okay
[Music]
foreign
that's a very fancy way of shooting man
can you teach me how you do that
nice Hedgehog thank you
I am cracked
at this at this point
I'm just too good at this
guy with the ice is trying to be this
way oh I'll take the high road and you
take the little road oh okay
make your way across to the walkway oh
no no no
no no
of course wait wait wait you know what
it's time for again
but I might blow up the diamonds with
this too
ah
it's fun
what there's so many many more well
where do I go
wait
um
here okay
that's my friend oopsy
wait I'm coming to you
running alone ammo oh [\h__\h] yeah this one
is really looking run yeah okay back to
my beloved SMG
[Music]
knowing run
I love words I am the greatest speaker
of them all
foreign
what is English I can't speak English
my timestamps are getting big
oh
give us that [\h__\h] ice you're trapped
of course the very last person out of 50
people has it
yes
I don't know
yeah
some [\h__\h] sucking [\h__\h]
God damn it I should still kill him
though
yapping
all I gotta do is pull the trigger on
this one anybody got some ammo who my
beloved weapon what is that what do you
call that weapon anyway that I kept on
using another
[Music]
small house okay thank you Game for
telling me about lift chips and S
to slide down after I fell down thank
you
for everybody the [\h__\h] I blew up all the
cars I can't use them
is this usable
uh
my brother Gerald is gonna be one of
them
just drive by just drive by can we take
a taxi
is he shooting at it because it Bonks me
good night
we wanted to take the taxi I guess we're
getting a car then it's gonna be a long
way
yes oh my God
okay so we exchanged Gracie for some
diamonds well the Bros
oh [\h__\h] then everything goes to [\h__\h]
that's about right isn't it there's
nothing right about this situation but
that would be an accurate description of
what went down the Russian is called Ray
vulgari I worked for him on the Adriatic
oh isn't it
I guess not get out of here these
diamonds let's get a better car [\h__\h]
they're nobodies now the only thing that
makes me smile about this [\h__\h] is
does not have the ice
[\h__\h] does nothing pack it don't shoot
him
just leave this voice
I can see how he thought it was covered
this is not the first time
that I would be killed by some of his
employees hopefully one day I'll be able
to teach him his lesson by putting a
bullet to the back of his head you're
not meant to say what you wish for out
loud it won't come true if you do that
rule even worse I wish as cheerful as
yours
I don't know about that
I think if you say it out loud
in this case it should only help me
it will keep me motivated
will keep me determined
[Music]
I wish Kiana has a good day wait wait
wait wait wait wait are you saying is
because you're like thinking it won't
come true
now I don't quite understand
okay
yeah I thought it was like you know not
always it's just like birthday wishes or
when you see a shooting star
then you shouldn't say your wishes but
any other wishes I mean
I don't think it applies to all of it
as well go in Pace I like it
thank you guys I wish you all a sincere
lovely day
every day as well
and I've been it
[Music]
did you guys see that what I tweeted
about the 3D printer
[Music]
that's like so crafty I love it
and it turned out so beautiful like
official merchandise and I love how they
use like like the most popular
um way of transportation that's that
bike from totk
[Music]
o story of a lot of lives pretty
printing cute rabbit hole yeah a lot of
my friends have 3D printers but they
don't use it I think for like Hobbies
stuff like that making their own
merchandise
they
that's what I thought that's what I
thought
you got it right now do your job
I'm not part of your job
okay
okay uh yeah yeah my friends
the ones that I know that have one I
think they only really use it for like
cosplay stuff but I love the idea of
like making your own merchandise from
like thing like games that you really
like but uh she didn't only just print
it she also
um
made the model herself apparently and
she airbrushed it and the airbrushing
when she did it it looked so simple but
man
but I was thinking like the way she was
doing all of this I like the whole time
thinking hey maybe this could be like a
stream
you know
air like okay 3D printing takes a long
time so that's not gonna be part of the
stream but
like putting together and then
airbrushing it or airbrushing it first I
guess
if I get a little box like she has
but only if I get good at it then it
might be entertaining
3D printing itself slow but painting Etc
yeah yeah yeah
you should I just show the printer and
that's it for hours yeah but it's a
relatively small thing then maybe it's
done in what two hours three hours
um
sounds like a gum plus dream that was
always interested in airbrushing because
like things turned out so beautifully if
you're good at it
that bike turned out so nicely
all right Mr pegarino I'll see you there
it legit looks like official merchandise
I want it
things I could make I could make an army
of cake pizza kings
[Music]
where are we going pecolino
is it J
is that what I gotta call it so far
I think I'll take a crap you can have
back your car
there's one
[Music]
yo
my truck wow oh when I say Army I don't
mean you know Army to fight something I
just want a big amount of uh peaceful
chickens I don't want to force you guys
to you know
fight
it's not necessary
oh twerk it girl Brooks
good to see you we're back in the strip
club after all
legal problems all kinds of crap you
know things have gone I've heard some
things
roasty a dream and something holds you
back
no
a mission a no commission I ain't gonna
starve people don't want me around
occupancy by more than 625 per persons
it's dangerous
[\h__\h] you I looked out for you and I'll
pay good real good but I need you to do
something I need you to collect that H I
got some Russians who ever buy it
Russians yeah
Dimitri rascalon Mo we've got these
three I know but this is real I need you
real what the [\h__\h] is real real because
it's you real because it's my last
chance dang good luck no I need you to
get that age I need the money
I looked out for you you know people
wanted to whack you I said no now I need
you and I'll pay a lot of money listen
Mr pegarino I already told you I got you
oh you listen you dumb immigrant [\h__\h] I
ain't asking you I'm telling you dude
get over your principles these guys
don't hold grudges
do what do you and me are gonna have a
problem
[Music]
Phil will look after this reaction
you're telling me I'll have a problem
no you
[Music]
he is not amused
hey how about that drink
telling him
that
he's got a problem he feels like so
insulted like you just said like
something really really
insanely insulting to him
thanks for the membership fools
one woman for the rest of my life this
is serious Roman I have been asked to
work for Dimitri rescolov again that
could be a lot of money in it no but I
gotta go to the wedding
he's on some boat in the East hook right
what do you know about this he's on the
boat in East hook yeah I heard you had
forgiven him
now that I know where Dimitri is I might
just go there and take him out instead
have you forgotten that he burnt down
your apartment in business that he
raised you're kidnapping now I
know what no I haven't
even decided so you give members
so does that mean you know the ending
does everybody here know the ending
anybody here who doesn't know the ending
just me oh helicopter
a real helicopter hopefully
yeah I don't I don't I don't I know it I
don't I don't a lot of people don't know
what okay I thought most of you guys
played it for some reason
uh
wait so what I don't see a goal on my
map yet
there we go Kate okay
hey Kate
I have a decision to make
and I don't know who to talk to about it
but it's really not cake though who
betrayed me in the past I don't give a
[\h__\h] about Kate to work with him could
be very profitable but it would mean
going back on an old I swore to myself
you shouldn't work with him Nico you
don't need money what is it going to
change about your life I don't know
it'll make things easier for me and for
Roman I'm not going to respect
you believe in for money Nico goodbye I
don't care about you anyway make your
decision yeah uh
uh was this
um the other decision Revenge
[Music]
well
the money is closer
it Revenge Revenge
okay
but okay
um you want you probably want me to see
I want to see both is this like
is am I really close to the ending is
this the ending
then
makes sense to save and do both oh this
is the last thing oh [\h__\h] okay oh
early early ending today
it's good I have to cook today
okay
done then we can do the money first and
and then
perhaps the revenge
for GTA 5 we also did all all the
endings ahead
yeah we're gonna sleep we're gonna get
uh chop up our armor I guess
although it's almost full
where is the entrance oh
[Music]
I'm a first and then sleep ah so that I
can
I'm not holding that but I'm I'm already
here
too late now
got a lot of ammo oh I do have to top up
on ammo I barely got ammo for that one
weapon wagon what was it called
I didn't look at the answer I asked
questions and then I don't look at the
answers assault rifle okay okay
if it isn't the consequences of my own
actions
okay
even try it without topping up my mind
well we gotta go there for
we gotta go there for though
ammo though
oh Dimitri
are you disappointed that I have not
found and killed you yet Dimitri Rascal
off do not worry your time will soon
come I went to the store work lunch
Island thanks for telling me
yours was not amongst them very
disappointing sorry or maybe the Thugs
who failed to kill me should be blamed
though I cannot believe the
quiet first in Europe and then these
diamonds and Liberty City you are in
debt to him Nico why don't you just pay
him what you owe I need to make another
safe
and the only thing I own is to pull it
to the temple you will be paid in full
fear not you have a sharp tongue give me
a call
out of your mouth bye
I had a taxi man
you really don't want to go to wrench
I'm getting both both
[Music]
since the ending is already so near and
it's just been four hours I got time
didn't I ask you an hour ago how much
more time I need and you guys said three
four hours or maybe I said it two hours
ago
[Music]
after this don't reach out I have to I'm
stupid I'm blind something five yeah
you guys always
chickens have a bad feeling what time it
seems
all right taxi ah nice
all right
[Music]
you do
you admit it you do you do
better overestimate than underestimate
and be stressed let's do it
but if I know that it's gonna take me so
oh yeah so long it's also kind of like
yeah
feels so
endless stretchy
okay time to use my bunny
is this some assault rifle stuff
carbine rifle rounds okay
[Music]
um
sniper
do I need some sniper around too I don't
think we'll be really sniping much
[Music]
yes
is it this one oh okay
tops it up and
got this one
all right
okay
sir you told sir I mean I won't be
coming back probably until I play the
DLC
so you'll surely miss me
you know what I'll save one more time
to so that I don't have to buy all of
this again
[Applause]
Mr taxi taxi taxi
I think I'll do
the deal first
or
because you guys want me to see the
Revenge at all costs so that seems like
that's the
um the most popular
[Music]
which one is canon
is it really matter
do I need to sleep again to save this a
second time
[Music]
better sleep another night over it think
about it really hard what to do
okay yeah yeah
yeah
am I really sure about this
yes
revenge is canon
okay
I mean we're gonna do both so it really
doesn't matter
or should I take my old car this time
might be useful
in some situations
I wanted that car are there any hotdogs
around
Folk
damn it that hurt really bad
this little Porsche
[Applause]
the physics what is are you saying
that's not realistic
I'll take this cute car
and on the way maybe I'll find
too late
oh Charlie
[Music]
what's wrong with
them
[Music]
maybe I should make a rap song
like this cute wrap
cute it doesn't even feel like rap
Ed
I wanna hear Cali wrap this
is
[Music]
as she attempted it
wow
[Music]
yeah I know Callie had similar songs I
know I know
[Music]
she tried
I want to try too
I'll do it
I love this so much
oh what and wait can I actually get some
there's no person there
[Applause]
give me some nuts what the [\h__\h]
no one is
working now what the [\h__\h]
November
I guess we'll go into it handicapped
we'll be fine right
huh
I like pistachios I don't like nuts
especially pistachios I don't like
walnuts so much I don't like
cashew nuts so much but I can eat them I
like pistachios and and Anderson and
peanuts going to Portugal let's move
salted very strong salted please go to
the docs
uh-huh
can I also drive to the docks
car car
honestly this is
this is maybe a car I would
Buy
just because it looks very functional
Dimitri's given me and I like the shape
it's friendship
then the buyers will handle with the
funds couldn't be simpler how come
everything we get into starts off simple
but I don't think I'm the type of person
for a sports car but I do want one where
I can take off the roof
something about
move peanut I worked with him at the
double crossed me sold me out to someone
I had history with I nearly got killed
because I never thought I'd cooperate
with him again money makes people do the
strangest things don't it
I mean
money makes a world go round as they say
yeah the soccer mom
I'm just picking up my cats from the
daycare
news cats I'll have the full van full of
cats
that's right where is it that the brown
is good we'll give up the cash the
ground
the nuts or
hmm
red
this doesn't give me such a big hype
feeling right now it's weird
bring me some hype story give me good
cutscenes come on
I cannot say I have the same enthusiasm
for this partnership have you given them
the H I want to get this money and go
home you know
what easier for who what the [\h__\h] are
you doing
their compound what's going to happen
when they find out if I was
go and get the money of them it has to
be on the side that's why we all win
good luck
[\h__\h] Dmitry he's killed the guys
collecting the stuff [\h__\h] we're screwed
they ain't gonna let us leave all right
if we're fighting we're fighting for the
money we got to jump on them right now
follow me
let's do this first try guys
I Love Phil
Nicky sneaky
raise the stuff
where's the money
Up on the Roof Nico let's see if we can
figure out what's going on inside okay
oh welcome back guys how you doing
you guys are taking too many breaks
these days I'm I'm thinking that I take
a bigger cut from your
from your uh uh paying but I mean you're
already giving me everything which you
know what that means you're just gonna
pay me more just kidding yeah
don't take so many breaks man
the pay is imaginary guys
your pay is imaginary mine isn't
it all right the money's in there once
we're in It's All or Nothing let's go
then
come after me okay
can I take cover behind you
I didn't even Zoom amazing
what
was that
it's really tiny
even more from this side okay
a grenade and may have been a grenade
should I throw it is it telling me to
throw it but I already killed them all
right okay
isn't this like a normal worker I kind
of feel bad
oh
[\h__\h]
off gotta make sure
what are you saying that I'm not seeing
on here is one
here we go
[Music]
then what next
Phil where are we going
nobody seems alive Phil
I think we did it
ah
[Music]
I got one of the running ones I'm gonna
go down Phil I think
oh yes following me okay I
oh
they were right below us
okay okay okay okay okay okay
uh how to not throw it at me okay oh it
went up in here that was not so good
[Music]
I feel like
yeah that only blows up one no the
behind the one behind was a little bit
affected but not really
oh
because they're so scattered
[Music]
oh
who's there
no one okay
what
he was still fighting for his life even
in the last second
what now Phil
um should we jump down because this is
going up again I want to go down no
I think the other way goes down here
cards on
we're not doing a Tarzan here even
though that would be very very
entertaining
why are you still moving stop folding
[Music]
he chooses the worst moments to reload
I'm almost out of armor there must be
some harm laying around right
or like should be able to pick up some
easy
don't stand in my Lane
I shot off his nose I got you now A
different kind of I got your nose
oh no
[Music]
you want your nose back
oh my God you're not getting back your
nose no no no no
let me look for
oh more if I find someone why is he so
slow
I have a beacon out of nose
I got you I
[Music]
turned him into an anime girl
did you guys see
a certain uh browser YouTuber
debuted yesterday aura
interestingly she seems to
um stream in European times
oh she also likes music that I like
[Music]
I think we'll get along greatly yeah
like what it's so rare to find hello
project fans out there
so rare now she's cute too I really like
um
the art style of her design her face is
so cute
um
just a shame that she's on Twitch I
don't feel like twitch is so
like
for me because I'm not used to it it's
just not user friendly for me
[Music]
I might be biased because of being so
used to YouTube but
be afraid friend
can you drop me some armor please
now
please never move to Twitch
yeah I don't I don't think I will
uh I mean I'll I'll I won't say no to
maybe one time experimenting like amen
for like one
stream I see a medkit
did I miss some armor somewhere
this will be nine come on
oh wait my where's my chat scrolled up
I had to use apple to disable audio
modes oh wait was it lagging
in Germany No One streams on YouTube
yeah I I I do think that twitch is more
popular in Europe
definitely like most
most people who are looking for like
live streams to watch
in Europe I think they'll go to they'll
go to Twitch for streaming and for
watching
I mean it might still be Implement my
majority for that in
North America too but for Europe I think
it's especially like that
[Music]
we'll take that
um
don't [\h__\h] with me
it's not true everywhere not Japan maybe
huh
in the future I expect it to be more 50
50.
I don't think like
whole life is helping to spread out
the streaming culture
we are forcing you guys to be on on
YouTube
and that brings
a lot of people
over to YouTube and I feel like by a pop
a popular company like whole life being
mainly on YouTube makes other companies
also think maybe YouTube is the place to
be as a YouTuber I think it does
influence the
the
markets a little bit
mm-hmm
oh
sneaky
[Applause]
nobody's dropping armor I swear I
checked everywhere what the hell
this is rough
who said that
what class you're gonna play oh we
talked a little bit about it so turns
out
um
I forgot what it's called ah BJ's gonna
do a sorcerer but starts out with a
cleric but it wouldn't stay as a cleric
I guess that's the thing you can do
uh and Cali is still not 100 sure but
Bijou is like giving her some ideas
narissa said she's she was considering a
bard
but we're gonna play in probably easy
mode because probably will take less
time and we're gonna enjoy the story and
all that where's Phil
um
yeah and then Bijou was saying maybe in
class won't matter so much
I mean I really don't know how difficult
it's gonna be
what to expect
can this be opened
well there
so yeah maybe it's good to stay on easy
not difficult it's very short one well I
mean two hours
oh yeah I'm covering you but from what
nobody's here anymore it's a ghost house
ah the other side opens huh
I just don't want to play a tank I don't
mind playing like DD or or instead of
cleric
because some people ended up telling me
yeah cleric might be strong if you play
it for damage but as a Healer you don't
actually get to heal so much
because you have to sleep to recover
your heel or something I didn't know any
of this
I see where is he
[Music]
gotta go down come come come come
yeah I don't know what to do I'm still
unsure
[Music]
okay here is Carr
and beautiful orange bike
[Music]
come on come on
what is that
we are getting the case
no no this is not going to make me fail
this Mission I cannot oh no this no no
no no no no no no no no
I don't care I'm gonna use a cheat code
or something if I must
what can I do I'm stuck
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
hit reverse
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay
thank you for helping me in this Panic
panicky moment uh left and right
nice what's he gonna do where is he
gonna go
eh
nice safe yeah
[Music]
should I killed driver instead I ain't
come this far too come on Nico
don't worry don't worry uh
sorry I I it was a distracted
okay okay he's leaving this like area
Okay once you guys
you got okay that was funny though
I mean
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
don't lose control I know it's not this
right I know guys I know it's this one
is this one I know
[Music]
foreign
I just want to take the money and go
home yeah same for you for real
[Music]
um
no not a level oh he's doing it on
purpose we need that money
stop
is there money in the barrels
what you think about the misery I killed
this man with our money
[\h__\h] your money's getting away
[Music]
let's see the dollar signs I smell it
it's green it's so green
[Music]
there we go
there we [\h__\h] go
oh
my money is on the floor
Phil I got it it's waiting for [\h__\h]
seconds
thank [\h__\h] God that certainly wasn't
simple
thankful back to tutor okay let me just
uh I mean I get in any car honestly no
not that
I guess we're tagging at
this
is he inside Dimitri I ain't never been
put in a situation like that before
I was pressing F and they just went for
the taxi I guess because it was too
difficult to get into the other one
playing wall look with Eldritch blast
what what
um
I thought it would be good but maybe it
doesn't matter so much
keep safe and enjoy the money ciao
I just
if I are they all easy to play
five oh
oh again let's go
Ramen
well cousin somewhere easier than others
screwed me over and nearly got me killed
thinking
[Applause]
[Music]
the batteries
let's go bowling bowling bowling bowling
no
um wait so what happens I go to the
wedding
I don't see a wedding on my
screen
[Music]
uh one last crime before we go to the
wedding one last
those awkward moments
with the police I will miss them
I will miss it so much
why this is going in Endless circles
[\h__\h]
this is not the way
I'm coming back police
I don't even know where I am they're so
confused
now
who can't tell me what to do you're not
my mommy but even my mommy can tell me
what to do because I am
an adult
very independent adult
no one can tell me what to do
only myself
thank you
and maybe I don't I'm waiting for a
phone call
Moshi Moshi
wedding decodes
this is perfect I hope your partnership
is a fruitful one good luck goodbye
okay I guess I'm just saying goodbye to
these characters
that spent a lot of time with us
no I'm just trying to do Rito while I'm
waiting for the calls
I decided to work with that guy I don't
know if it was the right decision but I
did it they screwed me over again
you should have gone with your instinct
I don't like it when somebody's lying
to survive hang up hang up and do Romans
with I don't think so Nico I don't want
to know
yeah
the nuts
the nuts are being invented
oh my God it will speak
it's real
what are you I'm at the church now I'm
getting married
to New York I'm on my way thank you guys
I'll bring some nuts
can I eat nuts even when I'm full
ah
let's
oh yeah I'm so happy about the nuts I'm
going in circles again
I'm not touching my keyword he's just
really excited about today
let's go
get those nuts bubbles bubbles
it's gonna take a while huh
um
I can't do anything
we have to wait
now we have to wait
um
no even before when this happened with
some patients it worked out eventually I
think he's slowly moving more and more
to the left of the nut car
yeah yeah maybe eventually
I can't jump when you're in this it's an
endless loop and I can't change my
direction or path there we go see it
that's all just so that's all to believe
in the happy circles
for service thanks for the nuts man it
was so worth it
okay
[Music]
oh here
I'll take a tickety Taxi
Yum Yum Yum Yum
take me home
Country Roads
to the place
where I belong
Romans
yes let's go what are you guys dressed
as
no jeans
not new jeans no jeans
I Now pronounce you husband and wife you
may kiss the bride
wow oh my God it looks like a Sim
that makeup and then smile she looks
like she's straight out of Sims
2 maybe
it's so scene
and now
keep
um
oh my God whoa
oh no
oh okay
he told me to leave it
okay
[Music]
oh no
romanovich my friend
no
this is the only good one
romanovic
I think I understand why this is not the
Canon ending
Roman
I'm so sorry cousin
what happens then
[Music]
this does something still happen or am I
like
free
except
not free from the sadness
one more mission on Mamma Mia
[Music]
uh be strong side I'm going to find this
bumbaclot you get need forget to some
hardcore weapons and thing while you
waiting for me call
Ryan got my car or I'll bring them to
you
eh
you say
I pick him up
buy more ammo and do I need ammo
is it gonna be a rough we have we didn't
fine
armoredoia
armor and we do need armor
car please if there's just one cop
walking by does it still
like put me in the danger of getting
us I'm building a chorus
[Music]
Demetra there wait for me I'm on my way
okay we will do this for Roman one
Lovely One Love
okay Jacob is waiting for you in the car
in Albany
that is so [\h__\h] far
if he's waiting in the car I might as
well take a taxi
let me in
Jacob is yeah one of the better
characters but
still is this city better than me
still
not quite there
oh in here okay okay
thanks for waiting for me
no you've been following for some time
[Music]
thank you Jacob I know you cared for
Roman but he was my family you do not
have to do this Roma was my boy alone
I'm doing this for him rotten
you have to stick to him Bridget
no armor run let's go
follow them do not blow them up is what
they're saying okay
[Music]
okay
you're dead enough if Dimitri and
pecorino are so on top why would they
care about me why would they bother to
send the Hitman to the wedding you think
they'll be afraid of my brother the
major trick so you forget about what
happened on the dance
I did not forget about this
sending an assassin after me and killing
Roman on his wedding day this is
something I will not ignore true I ain't
gonna fill it to go a night up
yes
I agree
I wholeheartedly agree I also understood
all of that yeah yeah
[Music]
I'm right behind you look behind you
shall we
um
[Music]
I just need those bastards to know and
understand what they did to me
right Dimitri at degarino will find this
out as well they will find it out when
they stare down the barrel oh my God
your mind recording and you don't be
able to take clearly enough you want
some weed I do not need that marijuana
Jacob oh my God clearly enough is he
coming over or what all right
I let that desire build up inside of me
and let it eat out everything wait
I cannot allow that to happen again not
to me not to Mallory and everyone it's
so hard to focus on both dialogue and
driving and reading especially when
Jacob is talking because I can't
understand him without reading and even
with reading it's difficult
oh my God I'm trying to take in the
story but the driving is making it
difficult
you can't I might
have a captain is this is this the thing
that people mentioned okay okay but they
are capped I made some changes in the
very beginning
[Music]
and I was nothing but the curse to him
he was beaten because of me he was shot
down yeah it was a bad influence on
Roman that's for sure
I don't think about child support
he's like
but Nico is not brother
Roman is sound but Nico is not
pronounced to misunderstand don't ever
forget
look the area where my house is in GTA 5
no not quite only like the hill
well if you fail it's okay because I
need armor anyway probably
look I'm still on it
eyes on the road
[Music]
please
calm curbs okay here we go where are we
going
[Music]
where are we right now oh
that is not how I drive
fake news
oh my God okay that scares me
uh I have no plans
talking about
suicide Roman was my cousin
you want to help me find a way for us
hello
okay
I will die
I will die but I will try anyway I'll I
will not give up yet oh it's like a he's
like a like an adminton why are we not
shooting dude
why is he not shooting
oh he wasn't
properly covered I think
should I oh maybe I'll shoot a rocket
where maybe here
[Music]
[Laughter]
wow oh there's some more people up there
but they're kind of spread out
oh is that my sniper oops here
oh
[Applause]
God
[Music]
thank God I wasn't in that area
okay
um foreign
I hate that
oh his ear
I shot his ear
s
hey so far I don't think I've even lost
any HP yet
um
but the remaining ones are hmm
a little bit annoying to get
can we get a big one
come on come on
land where I wanted to land
that looked pretty good
[\h__\h] now I'm going there
[Music]
but no there's still someone in here oh
okay did that hurt
can we do it guys
can we do it first try
hey goodbye to you too sir thank you for
at least greeting me so politely
maybe some armor this time
if you see some and I'm missing it let
me know guys
[\h__\h] you depends on when you get hit by
the book or not when when exactly does
that happen
[Music]
uh
I got a message now
Escape Plan for Your Star keep your eyes
on oh oh oh uh I
should not keep my eyes on the phone
that's for sure
because they hate what you do and we
hate your whole crew so please don't
stay until
[\h__\h] you
[\h__\h] you very very much
other words
it's getting kind of late so please
don't stay inside
[Music]
I'm fine
mostly
I guess I'll take it now
having fun
I'm having fun thank you what about you
or was that me actually it might have
been me
I'm just talking to myself I'm talking
to Nico
me and Nico
having conversations one last time
and this is easy guys I didn't need
armor
I'm fine
but seriously why are they not dropping
that though
maybe here what's this
nope
nope nope nope nope nope
reload
hi thank you
I didn't work this hard to share The
Spoils of a victory goodbye I haven't
seen him in a while
yeah I saw that Dimitri you and me is
gonna end this you're a [\h__\h] person
you're worth nothing
I missed you I
Dmitry
I went the wrong way
is he the only one left
oh no
oh how do I still have so much HP
ah
this I hate this kind of situations
because there's just no no cover
what was that Thunder
oh
I could have just used my rocket
launcher and it would have done the
trick but okay no
okay what if I just shoot with the
rocket launcher can I shortcut it
ah come on come on come on can I can I
okay bastard where is it
no scripted okay
[Music]
yeah okay
we are in the so deep we have to finish
this now
come on
rocket launcher please
it's not even worth shooting is it
[Music]
um I'm here I'm here don't cry
oh it just nothing happens when it goes
into the water good to know poor fishies
though
oh another helicopter
whose side is this one on please
[Music]
it looks like it's going after it
maybe it'll intercept the Rockets oh
[Music]
it's you Jacob wait it's really hard to
get close to you like this
and get underneath I was trying to [\h__\h]
where are you going where's what
what just happened oh is this the the
bug
what just happened he just zoomed away
no this is different
huh
huh they they're gone they're just gone
that was the stuff
[Music]
that I was full speed
the [\h__\h]
I couldn't go any slower with that
stupid wobbly water and that shitty boat
the [\h__\h]
uh I'll try it another time but if not
then I'm just gonna go move on to the
Canon ending
[Music]
it's my ammo
still the same as I just had or is reset
to what it was before I started shooting
because
I think they reset it they didn't reset
it I mean it's like not what it should
be
that's not nice in turn when it comes to
Rockets
I don't have so many
how far can I show the grenade I don't
think I can shoot a dead Parts too much
Olivia
ah wait let me shoot the ones up there
first
all right
okay
[Music]
show me your beautiful pretty face again
thank you do you stop this time we don't
have all this beautiful explosions
you're so sad
would you maybe hide what the [\h__\h]
foreign
even if we had armor I would have
probably failed at that point
and then I would have had to restart it
without armor and now now we're just
like doing it the same way and I'm used
to it to doing it without armor
yeah I was thinking maybe it was a like
the problem was that I was going
like straight at it and
because of the whatever the air or
whatever that the helicopter was
creating you can't really go at it
straight
but I don't know if that's really the
case no
oh what the [\h__\h]
I don't think they placed play tested
this ending as much because they knew
nah and things are important if you give
people to endings a lot of people are
gonna play both no no no I don't think
that logic really applies
hmm
foreign
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
thank God there's a medkit right there
I'm very aware of it that's why I don't
really care but uh this place is
terrible
[Music]
who who who are you
oh yeah
yo
got him
are we in the clear no not quite this
one and then now we're in the clear I
think
we should
time to check out
the cutscene again
but we're not gonna watch it again
never had this issue on the clinical
version but this was the tunnel of PC
ports having spotty points Spoils of a
victory goodbye hi FPS messes with
certain things
Dimitri you and me are getting to the
helicopters
oh you still end up having to go to a
helicopter all right oh [\h__\h]
sorry pecorino I didn't mean to shoot
you
ah this one's difficult
way
no huh
what
what the [\h__\h]
what up
[\h__\h]
uh if I restart like if I now get armor
and then restart
will I then restart with armor
well let's look at this just go for
Canon cutting kind of but I'll try one
more time
[Music]
um
we will keep them okay
foreign
[Music]
take me to the armor place thank you
[\h__\h]
okay yeah problem that was a difficult
situation um
uh here
I couldn't even see them last time they
weren't so close at the door right away
so that was unexpected
[Music]
some ammo here some ammo there
SMG rounds not necessary but this one
[Music]
no I think this is
wait for me I'm on my way we will do
this for Roman
wait
I'm still pressing redo right redo the
mission
eh
no stay safe stay Second Amendment did I
mess it up now I have to start from the
beginning
I shouldn't have answered what
what I know
ah this sucks wait that means what do I
have to redo
cheat code time how what how would that
help me
like making it easier for me with like
crazy
cars or weapons the car chase
[Music]
I don't even remember the cartoons
anymore was it difficult
uh
let's try again yeah
one last try are you in one last time
[Music]
all right my brother that blood clot is
another pizza right now I've been
following for some time you think his
next step is with pecorino
okay we got this let's go
don't let a lot of Tanks fall on you
we cannot kill him
try my best think about how much stay
calm you're not in a hurry yeah but it's
so close I still gotta do a number
ending which will probably take for the
same amount of time if not longer
[Music]
bust his [\h__\h] them up I can't believe
I did that deal with Dimitri
how could I trust you
money with hell broken in the people oh
my God
a man stepping on the back once you're
gonna keep stopping until the job is
done say I finally learned this lesson
if taken the death of my cousin but it
is something I must accept when you get
to the boat just focus on driving I was
I mean I I just I was just going
straight anyway I didn't even have to do
curves or anything so
I don't know
[Music]
um
my FPS are limited why does this take so
long where are these idiots hiding out
this is
split up the large amount of money with
them get from the business deal you know
everybody live in the city water
sometimes
I'm not stressed about that
he was a good man no matter what
happened to him he would never be angry
or be separate more than a minute there
was any way I could change my action so
that he would not die I would do it I
would sacrifice anything that's fine I
didn't know where to change what
happened earlier you all right I'm not
stressed do I look stressed
probably tomorrow
days now
also I'm taking tomorrow off
I'm making the schedule tomorrow
he has reason to be nervous
[Music]
oh my God
well then I am looking forward to
disappointing his expectations
[Music]
the other day I chose not to take I
wanted to be winter time again man
see I'm not stressed I'm just kind of
exhausted from the heat in my room
yeah
[Music]
okay even not winter this fall is okay
oh
yeah same turn
well we're almost there
I got you I got you I got you
got any ice cubes I use them all up but
when I was filling up my water jug and
then they what [\h__\h]
[Applause]
there we go thank God thank God for the
cutscene
super over steering yeah
all right I am kind of sick of this at
this point
but let's do it again
um
[Music]
oh where's that going oh
I saw a shooting star
maybe here
foreign
[Music]
tell me they light the flame
and do this and that yeah that's what
sparks do
all right let me let me use the Sharpie
as close as I can get
Sparks let the flame to the dark of
night and today
sounds like a spell from Charmed
I'm almost I'm in the 7th of eighth
season of charm man it's taken me a long
time to binge watch this one episodes
are pretty long but
generally the show gets better
the more seasons
uh go on in my opinion
but
I I feel like I've been noticing a lot
of logic and plot plot holes
yeah anybody here who knows Charmed well
enough to talk about Charmed with me
Jesus that that's a blast from the past
hell yeah
it's totally is
stay down not well enough
an episode or two
you know iPods with Eight Episodes eight
eight seasons that I would
watch or find a lot of episodes that
I've never seen before but
it really seems like every episode I've
kind of seen before but just never
really properly binge watched it in the
right order
because I used to watch it on normal
German Austrian TV
and it was running on there for years
and years and years
but watching it in the proper order
noise
it's just makes you realize some plot
holes
one of those you can just watch a random
episode yeah I mean I wouldn't really do
this nowadays [\h__\h] this
watching serious culture has changed now
you want to watch at least as an adult
maybe when you have these subscription
Services you want to watch everything in
the right order
except if you already watched it and
you're watching it for different
purposes if you watch it for the first
time you want to watch it in the right
order no
but if you're like watching I don't know
South Park or Family Guy or the office
for the hundreds of times and you just
wanna you know
enjoy a random episode yeah yeah
not that I watched South Park like
honestly
I'm sure there's many South Park
enjoyers
here in the chat
but I
I can proudly openly say that is so not
my thing
one thing I will never understand is
the charm of South Park
and similar shows
oh [\h__\h] I slipped
it's edgy humor
[Laughter]
[Music]
I've seen some of it like randomly in
the past
and yeah I mean maybe some of it can be
somehow a little bit funny
but really as a whole
trash
thanks for agreeing
I'm back in
foreign
not cool
I think it's funnier for Americans
yeah I guess we have different uh humor
it's a cultural thing I guess
different kinds of humor too I like
Japanese humor I like European I look
British British humor British and German
Austrian humor is different too I would
say
I like all of those though and I I
watched so many American sitcoms and I
love them though
I have watched so many American sitcoms
okay now here comes the difficult part
what do I do
[Music]
you better just say uh wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait
where is it where what
I'm [\h__\h] seeing ah you got back up
you got back up you [\h__\h]
but now they're not coming from this
side at all
what
where are all the people that flanked me
before huh
bastards
I was watching out for them
damn it's random
okay here we go uh it's about time
or is it yeah
get in the boat
Sean
press F again how about you walk a
little bit faster
okay
[Music]
I'll get it for you
I'm so [\h__\h] slow what the [\h__\h] do I
do hey hey hey hey if I fail again then
[\h__\h] this game hey
louder because louder
[Music]
can't hear you over my freaking loud ass
motor
[Music]
okay see I can't go any faster than this
I'm going straight as [\h__\h]
this has to work okay it did I'm doing
the same exact thing but okay
uh repeatedly tap face repeatedly I'm
tapping nothing's happening are you sure
I should tap it
it is it really tapping is it really
tapping
I'm tapping like crazy he's like having
a seizure
I'm going to catch the Matrix
uh am I also controlling wait am I am I
I can't tell am I controlling the the
helicopter
yes oh [\h__\h] hell where's where's the
other one
okay
I've I mean I failed
what do you mean that what do you mean
he's gone
I just started
what
foreign
[Music]
I have a cat
I am not afraid to cuddle her oh she's
she's up
getting wet a
smoothie she's moving to me this movie
to be Ellen
[\h__\h] you Jacob
what [\h__\h] boss huh I was literally
only in the helicopter for
two seconds
and it says I lost him
what
you saw how well I did in tug of war I
was spamming space
man I TR I did my best
and then it resets you again wait I
wonder where would it reset me
can I still check
is it the same checkpoint because then
that's absolutely
terrible
yeah this ending sucks
oh same checkpoint
yeah I'm not doing that again
now my fpsr cap well I think they're
capped at 60. I don't know if that's
gonna make a difference but I don't care
I'm gonna do something else now
I guess we didn't really need to in the
end but
[Music]
uh
this is not the Canon ending you're
welcome to tell me though what happens
later
little little
you needed a 30. do I also need that for
the coming ending
there's no Cannon
[Music]
yes
hmm
I don't need to do one more stream but
this is not like I have five hours of
gameplay ahead of me
is it
refresh rate 60 is this it 230 refresh
rate
okay
[Music]
Oh Mamma Mia
it'll play horribly but it will work
okay
uh
[Music]
what uh
shitty shitty
[\h__\h] situation
foreign
[Music]
okay
oh
Dimitri
[Music]
uh
laughs
is this the load that I chose
no different one right
I should be in a different apartment I
think that doesn't look like Freddy
[Music]
does it look too good to you
wait uh
let me check all that quickly
no I put it to refresh rate 30.
man yeah it's still kind of the same
[Music]
should I turn off vsync
oh no
uh in the game too oh I did it with the
the start up
uh where is where where
ah I hear this one
ah
how about this
okay
that's not the right
is this true
too wide
isn't this widescreen
are there
let me check
oh
I need
foreign
1400 there's no 30 what the [\h__\h] this
third is different size but let me try
this this is square
it's kind of square
it's like it's really like in the good
old days
what
yeah
[Music]
what about this one
ah
but this one's the one that's kind of
too wide I guess but I I'll try to yeah
is this not yeah
I just have to it's just adding a weird
bar in
OBS but it's actually
it should be fitting here
kind of
good enough
oh okay
[Music]
yeah yeah
yeah
no car no beaches
um do I have armor right now yes okay
we are going to take revenge aren't we
I just missed [\h__\h]
you
yeah
okay he's actually he seems kind of like
apologetic eh
oh he's running what are you running for
let me in I need your car I need Revenge
[Music]
so chill
I totally understand
let's not listen to this
crappy shitty talk from that guy
listen to Muna hoshinova instead oh I
just felt some
fun FPS lag or something maybe
but it still feels very very smooth to
me yeah
I don't feel a difference
what do you see
oh
it's pulling me up gravity
now it's more cinematic
on it
[Music]
sorry I didn't look at the police
oh it's the meme
yeah but
I tried to put it to 30 FPS it just
wants to look really pretty for me and
can't help it
I did all I could
if things are still messy now then I
can't help the game I gave it
[Music]
everything in my power
wow
[Music]
a high time
it was
an inspiration for me
um to like look out for more like
k-pop-ish producers
but I was really lucky with Kira being
able to produce
so many
different kind of songs
Sparks was not 100 capable fish I would
say you know
and I wanted it to be even more
k-pop-ish
and then thankfully
we were able to create do you
together I was looking for some K-pop
artists but I capable of songwriters but
most of the time they're like not
credited or it's like hard to reach out
and all that
yeah
but Kira is capable of many many things
we sure
oh yeah
well turn
[Music]
[Applause]
he had a gout
let's go
[Music]
foreign
I wish I could join right now but I'm
kind of busy
[Music]
I know
hi oh hi oh hi
I need more cookies
[Music]
why are more cookies
that cutscene with the explanation
looked very familiar to me just now
confused me
fathers was a different different one to
make supervising operations
[Music]
this looks difficult
what do you mean the the fact that it
says oh
no smoking on the boat with wearing your
own
like outside is that ironic
[Music]
okay
I guess boats don't normally have a no
smoking room
[Music]
do I go up here
goodbye Wawa in the radio
hope to hear you again sometime
huh
I don't know if I can make it on top
there we go
you put snipe from the crane
oh what is this leading me up to oh it
does lead me up to the crane
okay
I feel like one of his guys might be
inside
I hear her every day
damn
she must love you
all right perfect position
now let's snipe the hell out of this
guys
yeah
maybe I should have made myself a little
bit more aware of my surroundings before
I started this
because I don't know where all these
people are
oh
they can barely reach me there's shitty
guns how are they gonna reach me
this is good this is good
ah
yeah he's more careful now but you
really think you're gonna get a hit on
me like that
I'll take him
yo I can take out so many people from up
here
this is a superior strategy
like
peekaboo so cute
you pissed me off man
foreign
if I get his foot
oh wait somebody got me who was it
wait let me see if somebody's done me
over here
[Music]
no
uh ah oh
on the street
oh oh over here too
a [\h__\h]
I have The High Ground now
[Music]
oh
where's this coming from
maybe I should go down now
you look like me hey he looks like me is
he using the same character model
eh what the [\h__\h] where am I shooting
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh my armor and my HP gone
gone
ah [\h__\h]
I did a lot of ground work so maybe
we're fine
only he would shoot when I tell him to
shoot and what how do you get down again
I'm gonna die
I'm I'm trying the buttons
you can do this even with one HP I
believe wow
um
what was the sliding thing
I guess we're not sliding
oh okay
[\h__\h] I hope I find
armor
do we have some armor
hand it over right now
looks bad oh despond but not armor
anyway okay how do we get in here oh
there's some stairs over there okay
I wanted to be no dream it's so cool
and 1 HP oh is that the grenade
I'm going in I did do a good amount of
groundwork we might be okay
uh put down by the depths yeah yeah
would they so kindly baby oh there's
some cool stuff here but
I would be very grateful
some armor
I'll keep my eyes open
I don't want to get sniped
there's
still someone alive
I'm still looking for armor though
where was that
no
oh thank you oh my God sometimes
sometimes they all just blend in
um
to reload reminder
no smoking
if he sees me I must be able to see him
too where is this coming from
ah there okay oh I see him peeking
first
let me see if the depths were nice here
and maybe
hi oh
stumbled
um [\h__\h]
money
ah
yeah bye
should I go left side or right side
Nico is cute when he squeals that's me
though who's squealing
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] I'm terrified
medkit
is it empty now here
[Music]
okay
I've got the low ground now
[\h__\h]
nickel screams always confuse me man
grenade is dangerous here because uh
there's a high chance I'm gonna you know
flick it against myself
um that looked like it was one of those
moments
[Music]
oh
I don't like this View
[\h__\h]
this is I hate this position
ah okay maybe yeah Grenade now could
work
am I safe
go
up yes let's go
[Music]
[\h__\h]
I'm just gonna try to quickly go from
room to room
Maybe
it's really confusing
he's gone
ah camera and sometimes there's
movements when like I want to make a
curve or something he just walks so
stupidly doesn't he
destroying yourself okay
where did that guy that I saw go is it
is it this one in that room did they get
together
sometimes you just gotta go in you know
look at those bunk beds just like
bits is that
what is this camera
[Music]
now we're talking okay okay okay full
health full armor
nice
I hear screams
screams of my memories
left or right hmm
I'm scared I'm scared
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
baby
baby when I know where my enemy is and I
feel better about it
he had The High Ground he could have
easily shot me there
hey
oh
all right all right all right
all right kids everybody
[Music]
um
inhumane reaction in human well I am a
phoenix
not very human
[Music]
nice shot
having fun I'm having good fun now it's
going well
just gotta stay calm
okay
should I can I go in anyway okay no
thank God
I don't want to go inside these small
tiny rooms
oh
small small
ER smart girl
okay that clear clear
is clear
there's another vest in there
oh [\h__\h]
okay what am I operating again
this ship is basically big big metal
tattoo house
oh
he's not dead
well I mean he's not interrupting me in
my cutscene
so we're good we're good but
foreign
are you sure he's not dead his body is
even gone what what Dimitri
where is that bastard
I go down yes
God Bless America
[Applause]
I was just blessing you guys
is what I get
what the [\h__\h]
I'll say about that
you catch me alive because I will also
succeed
would be efficient meld if I wasn't
alive by the end of this
oh they all response
did they get some kind of
Revival potion or what eh
losing confidence
okay okay okay
they have two uh best bulletproof vests
so close to one another
hello hello
look at me
okay are they on the left side again too
no
say hi to Ivan the Terrible
be afraid friends
[\h__\h]
they're all over man they're all over
maybe I don't even have to go for I
could just jump down one level but
um
come on come on
come on you're surrounded
all right
[Music]
I'm gonna use my little SMG A little bit
now
they don't respawn the vest today
he punked me
[Music]
faster
die man die I should have left one of
these vests I didn't know I would go
back the same path
so left one of them here
okay
freeze
down
for Android take down gun
oh no respawn here but
uh see mad kid again medkit respond
no no no no no
every time Nico says something I feel
like it's somebody next to me about to
shoot me
no violence oh no
let's be friends
You Wanna Be Friends
where are you shooting from
now I know
you still here
yeah
this is also like such a difficult angle
ah
friend
who else is there
only him
what about this side
grenade
what now anyway
um
do I have to go like inside the place
where it opens
this isn't open
hence my my hands are so tensed up man
I missed something in the kitchen what
is the armor here too or what
I don't miss anything
um
it's back again how fast does it respawn
I took it once though I swear when I was
walking out this door right before
pretty nice
stove yeah
what's on the stove
what
what do you mean there's no armor here
what are you seeing well tell me to pick
it up
um
chat is just hungry you want some pizza
huh
[Music]
um had had the rest of the rest West
over let's let's left left over
from my Hawaii pizza last night that was
really yummy
blessed what the [\h__\h] man language where
how do I get there
where do how do I uh
I hear a fishies
uh
jump on the cargo
which cargo
which cargo is called
[Music]
front of the boat
suddenly peaceful right
is that a person no
I'm blind I don't know
open the hatch yeah but I don't see
these things open these are all closed
isn't this what opened
these are all closed
what's up
I didn't see anything over there with
the Red Dot I thought maybe I have to go
around until I reach it or ah this one
opens
ah only one
supposed to jump in there wait wait
chill chill chill
I think I just saw a person there too
like I will jump immediately into some
Danger
tomato
okay
okay okay
he's he's so done
is getting very very aggressive
why Always reload and work
[Music]
yeah
[Applause]
he's having a good time
I wonder if there's any more
you guys are welcome to look up a guide
is there any more vests in here in this
room
if anybody knows
having fun
what was that last shot
[Music]
what get down stay down
camera is
yeah questionable
oh oh
hey Dimitri I don't think I'll be doing
this deal with you we have other
business to finish Nico it's been a long
time we should talk face to face
America does not change everyone is this
angle on purpose
oh no
what the [\h__\h] man
that was so unfair they immediately gave
me a headshot
that was so [\h__\h] unfair
yes
prison for you
if you wanna
if you want to play unfair let's play
unfair
here's another person look at this one
maybe he'll prefer that one
time ago yes
anyone alive go to the cargo holes exit
Okay seems like they're dead
what
what yo
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] go back to the medical
yeah
[Music]
run faster yo
it's not you now
what the [\h__\h] before it be
hard
but I remember the sound when it when I
took it the past time the previous time
and then it responds so fast so I'm
pretty sure I took it twice
oh my God
this is really dangerous
it could be over any second now please
tell me please tell me that there's not
much more to do because I'm low on HP
[\h__\h]
okay
you're good on HBO
just don't want any more stupid shitty
confrontations like just now because
oh it's also really unfair you guys even
saw
all of you are my Witnesses of the
[\h__\h] they just pulled on me after
that cutscene
[\h__\h] I'm running out of ammo maybe SMG
for a little bit
get off the ship
oh wait in here again
[Music]
okay is this like a time thing no right
everybody's dead right not again respawn
right
okay
uh
should I jump
[Music]
I don't know if my low HP oh wait it's
full now never mind
okay
and now
that was weird
huh
[Music]
I killed Dimitri it's over he was on the
Platypus the boat I arrived in Liberty
City on so it seems it ends where it
began I guess
you don't have to do
um
you won't die in this timeline I think
wait don't tell me how many people away
[Music]
maybe I'll die instead I'm okay with
that if you're looking for work call me
no no no no no no
[Music]
so we're waiting for the wedding
location information again
good
[Music]
I love Lena you know after the game we
played
everybody just scattered
but Lena when it was about to leave and
I was like we were the last two in the
voice chat I was like wait a way to wait
in a name kept her hostage
and we talked alone just us two
I did what I had to do anyway you know
you fall apart
yeah about nothing in particular but I
just wanted to talk a bit longer with
her even though I was tired and wanted
to go back to bed and eat breakfast as
well and everything
[Music]
beautifully
be at the church at 10 A.M tomorrow I'll
see you at the church I'm looking
forward to it I have to sleep once
how close is my home
[Music]
um
now all the taxes left hey
[Laughter]
that's purse oh
I mean close enough
wait
okay
I have problems I am I have commencement
issues with taxis okay
oh
that's so mean they just made me think
that that's my car again
you thought so too didn't you wait is it
just a different car that I put there a
long time ago I guess it's a different
house so maybe I did that it's like a a
cheaper version of that beautiful car
yeah orange muscle car
good enough I guess
different block of cheese it's a really
old piece of cheddar not a fresh one
hmm what the [\h__\h]
okay
next stretches
[Music]
good morning
this is the day
what did he say 10 am I so free
what is it though
did I miss it
okay I thought it was gonna be like dude
you missed my [\h__\h] wings
man he's fine you better you better be
better than mine cousin get to the
church for tonight you just told me this
yesterday I guess I did miss it
and then that's why he's telling me
again they moved their wedding just
because of me it's so nice
okay
but he still didn't mark it on my
uh
uh map
so
I guess I'll wait
oh I know
sleep again but doesn't it how many
hours does sleeping reset
armor the question is do I need armor
for what's to come
probably right
[\h__\h] right because where the wedding
isn't the ending huh
for a moment I felt like that's the
ending
well I guess oh but I mean somebody will
dine because I have to chase someone
again probably
[Applause]
Cutters I do something special with that
Lionel peace
exactly
oh one last one
[Music]
uh
I want the best
[Music]
okay
oh
[Music]
should be enough
uh
[Music]
sniper rounds okay
let's go
how many hours does that take one
[Music]
um
I don't know what can I do
what would I do
donut somebody just spoke Japanese I
swear
somebody just said do not tell no how's
this what's going on
bowling could I invite Roman to go
bowling one last time
just asking if it's possible
I don't want to go
I just activated that
a bachelor's night
Bachelors go bowling let's go oh no I'm
gonna go back to my house yo
hey hey you
Wonder no no no no no no you
know
[Laughter]
[\h__\h] Park so close next to my cheddar
cheese okay
careful
watch big rank
and watch me go
and can I like what if I sleep now when
when will I wake up
it's five now
be late
ah
okay
[Music]
let's let's just uh
you can be fashionably late
well maybe it's
actually the right choice to be late
so that all that
tragedy won't happen and nobody comes to
kill me I hate baby me too me too it
doesn't have to be this Comedy Club
the kind of baby you want online
the next day no core to God no morning
sickness no going for nine months
I think that you called that just
adopting
customers wait if you don't like the one
they send you just throw it in the trash
and they send a new one no questions
asked I definitely use them again babies
[Laughter]
um okay let's go comedy comedy
is it gonna be the same
he must have another routine right
now
[Music]
let's get close to the wedding I already
have it no no I just have to wait
[Music]
wow
that's too much Dorito not good
oh
that's a way to wear a Gucci belt
[Music]
bleeding you try
to Bank of Liberty
that sounds inviting sounds promising
I love hearing that from a bank
not concerning at all
okay I wanna I wanna be amused amuse me
give me a amuse Bouche
coming to the split sides comedy clubs
give it up for Mr Cat Williams
is also a person that's uh real
I don't know this one
day he's hustling
whoa whoa he funny
Liberty City how are you good to see
everybody out there tonight
it's a beautiful night DJ's playing my
favorite song could you just play it one
more time it makes me
makes me feel strong like I don't know
if you've heard this song or not but it
makes me feel strong holder just play it
one more time let me see
okay hold on hold on hold up a song like
this you need it you need it as your
alarm clock so you can wake up in the
morning to some gangster [\h__\h] you just
be in the bed just waiting on it just
[Music]
okay don't play it again sir I'm just
saying it's the [\h__\h] it's all I'm saying
the song is the [\h__\h] that's the national
anthem for anybody who ever hustled at
all even if you're a librarian play that
song in the library and see if it ain't
the [\h__\h] you just be in the library just
minding your business yes
[Music]
okay so don't play it again sir don't
play it again just saying the songs
all I'm saying if you went to heaven
that song was playing you know it's
going to be a party in heaven you're
just walking heaven
[Music]
okay stop it sir I said don't play it
again just saying it's the [\h__\h] saying
if you went to the grocery store
everything in that [\h__\h] knowing you
ain't got the 78 Liberty City dollars
you just in the store just every day
okay the repetition is making it a
little bit funny now
I said don't play it again but not
really saying it's good for everything
fellas if you're having a problem in
your relationship stop [\h__\h] your
woman in slow songs
tonight try some special [\h__\h] some [\h__\h]
you picked up from your friend Katt
Williams
as soon as it comes on you just buy the
bed every day
[Applause]
excuse me looking at you like this like
I gotta go to work in the morning what
the [\h__\h] is wrong with you
you're saying the song is a [\h__\h]
just saying
if you worked at Burger Shot somebody
came through the drive-through in order
you lost my body
[\h__\h] lost me
French
[Music]
you want more
a Girl Wants a real show from him
hopefully he's got another job jokes
besides that
uh should I re-roll should I go in again
but I don't know how much how much time
did that actually take
two hours
I got a phone call oh okay what's up
are you the one that I just watched I
got my connections with that man I'm
really proud
hard to turn down the money and stick to
your principles well it was the right
thing to do are you coming to Roman's
wedding can you pick me up and take me
there I'll be at my mom's see you soon
it was really not funny I'm sure he can
be funny but this routine is just not
funny like like okay you play the song
in all kinds of life situations that
makes it like so much more what wow
it's better live I I can see it maybe in
yeah reality would be
maybe funnier but generally I
I don't appreciate the humor at the end
either
you know you can be a comedian without
making sex jokes all the time
look at The Marvelous Mrs Mary Miss
maisel
so good
all her routines in that show
were so good
so well written
she's a genius
yeah it's a comedy but with you know a
really good really good story
kind of like you know a very cultural
setting because of
her uh
descent
and the like her family you know you you
you really see what culture she's
living
that makes her family so interesting
her father was so funny her mother is
crazy but so funny
now every character is so lovable in
that show her manager I love her manager
and her managers got that New York and
accent
um what's the actress's name I think you
guys would know her
where did I see that actress last time I
feel like I saw her in a different show
too
many
[Music]
uh the voice of Lloyd's Griffin in the
Family Guy
yeah Alex Borstein is yes
that's her she is hilarious my God
picking her up in a nice ride that's
almost broken you're looking really nice
guys shall we go to the church so so
what so
this is weird why is this weird because
I'm going to the wedding of a couple
I've never met with a man I barely know
okay now you want to leave I can go
alone I'm happy alone I want to get to
know you properly I have tied up a lot
of loose ends in this
and they feel like it's time to move on
start living my life right but you're a
tough guy with a Death Wish A thieving
murdering drug dealing idiot do you
think you can just walk away from all
that I can try good luck Nico I really
hope you can walk away but do you think
the men you've dealt with will just let
you leave and walk into the sunset they
will hit I thought that when you do the
work that you do that people get their
hooks into you and then there's no way
out I was good once I was a normal kid
who got sucked into a war he didn't
believe in who forced to watch his
friends die ah Nico's two nice man
in order to survive if I can get pulled
into distance I can pull myself out
Grail of tries to make the right choices
to surround myself with good people
bad ones but people like you
that has to count for something tell me
have these good people been hurt by what
you've had to do has your cousin been
caught up in your mad life
yes very much so he has lost a lot
because of me someone without his good
naturedness and optimism would have been
broken by what has happened to him I am
lucky still happy to be part of my
family I have in this city he might be
your only family but he's not the only
one who cares about you Nico for real
don't be stupid I'm not coming to this
wedding for the free nibbles I'm coming
because of you why would there be free
nipples stupid I think this is I'm
willing to take a chance on you willing
to take a chance on the possibility that
you can walk away from the crazy oh my
God thank you so much I'm like so
honored thank you
otherwise
oh food oh okay
I'm Irish Nico where are people known
for strong whiskey Mystics and
Catholicism rational blood doesn't flow
through these veins oh he won't regret
this King
protect you
is Kate the one who's gonna die because
they're they're kind of like building it
up right now
when he just said I'll protect you
okay gonna die instead but I really
don't care about that like not enough to
go on a rampage like when Roman died
that is like such a huge difference in
importance
I guess that's what makes it the better
ending because no one important is dying
I know
I know if you may kiss the bra
whale congratulations
[Music]
[Applause]
congratulations
I never liked her since the beginning
[Music]
you missed
Nico do you really care
you were not in love Nico
as hard as the game is trying to make me
think it now we were not in love
oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
told me to leave it
I thought I had the thing is like with
romance you are like he's a main
character
you feel for him
but this girl you're not forced to deal
with her
solve
D
I will take care of this one okay okay
so much less
important
[Laughter]
so I don't care because I didn't date
her
it would make more sense if you like
dating her a lot but I ignored that
I don't care
can I just move on
that's just because of the script
writers
you have your own mind Nico and your
mind should be telling you to not give a
[\h__\h]
don't let the scriptwriters control you
that was in the very last minute before
the wedding they told you that you have
to protect her and care about her but
you don't really for the whole game you
her you don't give a [\h__\h]
let's be real yeah prank your
programming get out of there you don't
have to be controlled by it
you have your own feelings yeah let's go
yeah slaying those shoes let's go
[Applause]
Nico Nico Nico Nico
you are a slave of game programming
I'm I'm so sorry
I guess I'll help him just for his own
peace of mind
[Music]
car please
okay this car please
brought to you by the bank of Liberty
City
wait for me I'm on my way what this
world been doing there this is not the
place
oh my God
and
for the news
here goes the painful part
[Music]
that's a nice car the blue ones
down
[Music]
I like side content in certain games for
example I like side content in until 2K
just for the sake of the stream I wasn't
doing all that too much but for example
I am watching a full 100 playthrough
from a different person AKA
yeah and I don't I want suicide font and
all of it there
uh yeah in this game I'll be honest with
you it wasn't interesting to me
to play the side content
and I always
think with a stream of brain
I want to continue the main story to
keep the audience interested too
you know
yeah there may be some interesting ones
but
[Music]
honestly in GTA 5 they were also way
more apparent to me
if you mean side quests
not just like games like bowling I did
bowling I did strip club
dad
I did the comedy club
some things are you gonna play together
people keep on asking us how many times
are you going to ask this question
I think so but not right away
if I need a fellow game I'll do a DLC
[Music]
yeah the side mission markers I feel
like in GTA 5 they were
way more apparent so I think I did a bit
more in GTA 5.
[Music]
but generally I have to say
GTA 5 did
a hundred times a better job at catching
my interests and attention than this
game I'm sorry I enjoyed it but
it was
wow
very different
yeah I prefer to focus on the story is
storing the characters in GTA 5
definitely I remember that that blood
Club in other places and I've been
following four times
maybe but I do not think this is the
place for you Roman this is too
dangerous yeah you get what I mean and
Kate died at my wedding
day you have a stick to remember mainly
two wonky car physics that's on the way
back the problem I absolutely didn't
have something that people warned me off
[Music]
but I didn't I didn't have a problem
with the controls how do you know with
the car at least sometimes camera when
shooting was walking and stupid for
darker and more serious
man will lead us there we'll get him
cousin I assure you the story was still
pretty like
shallow in my opinion
there's not that much depth to it
San Andreas better in that regard
I hope so
but with that improvement from four to
five I am
positively looking forward to GTA 6 one
day
I don't think you paid much attention I
definitely tried though I don't I don't
think it's necessarily that much my
fault
I did I
don't know I've been trying to pay
attention a lot of times
but
whatever you say
sure sure that's what I'm feeling Nico I
want to get this guy I just don't think
we want to take any unnecessary risks
while we're doing that
huh
[Music]
mushrooms at least we're seeing some of
all their names I don't normally come
this side I know this half very well by
now
[Music]
you want some tourist sightseeing tour
we're chasing a scumbag back to his boss
then to make that [\h__\h] that pay for what
he did to Kate understand sure cousin
sure rise to the front mind on the job
with hands and all that [\h__\h] he's going
to stop sawing on Echo me if I'm
assassins
okay we're making some progress then we
will keep on this guy and hopefully he
won't [\h__\h] kill us we'll crash before
he leads us to take a Reno I'm about
ready to see that will I be facing
another helicopter ride tell me Dad
so I can get mentally ready for it
[Music]
no
different rounds
still though is it still from both to
helicopter oh my God
[Music]
wow yeah I don't even it's been so long
since I even flew our helicopter
okay I think the the biggest reason was
that uh I didn't pull myself up fast
enough so
um
[Music]
leave me one behind to help me come on
him as well
[Music]
yeah it's the same Mission just
different person dies
all right but hey this time we're going
in with armor right away let's go
and I have experience with this
oh hey the music's playing
fireworks yeah
more
nice
there was somebody still up here no I am
gotten better at action games since
debut
yeah I think I
improved like I know
a bit more a bit a tiny bit more about
guns
and my aim is better how are you [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] alive
unbelievable
endurance
I hear pictures
cute
[Music]
and pigeons oh I should make an
impatient video
um
try it one more time come on
yeah
I think she's ready for from soft wait
from stuff do you mean the Elder ring
games and so on I mean I'm playing album
wrinkles
I wouldn't mind in the future trying one
of those games again but
hmm
can't make promises
but I'd be happy to maybe go back to
Fantasy weapons again
I I've got enough of guns for a little
while you know what I mean sometimes you
just want to go back to the basics why
is he smoking
I was so cold
yeah I want magic I want I want uh
swords I want hammers
no more
come on
all right that's stupid what are you
doing
maybe I should just go in
I don't leave people alive
no Witnesses baby
all right
sure
I remember there's people right there
right away
oh
I remember all the positions
yeah
I just are they still alive no oh
[Music]
shotgun
I already downloaded the mission into
our head it's
muscle memory at this point yeah
I don't need that hey look look still
look at my XP and my arm Mercies
Mamma Mia
making extra sure
all right
scene time I think
you [\h__\h] don't think for a
second that this was anyone's fault but
your own you're gonna work with me and
everything would have been gravy gravy
and you killed someone I cared about
it's over for you now Jimmy
[\h__\h] I wish I'd hit you with the wedding
wait that's not what you were going for
oh he was but he's probably saying it
like
come on come on
[Music]
if you were going to stop me from
killing GBP
says
chat dead guys wake up are you dead
shake that is for me shake that ass for
me
Shake That feathery butt for me come on
[Music]
where is
where is it
whoa
here we go die already I want this
show me the ending or else
who's talking who's talking
oh you little [\h__\h]
you think you're safe down there ah
didn't I already have a cutscene at this
point
previously
weird
I feel like I did but
I didn't
I know I gotta get into the boat I can
hear you guys even when you can't send
me the chat messages
all right scripted why am I even trying
it's not worth it
huh
what I'm taking a bike
what you're not getting away figurino
nanny
stick to the coastline they say Chase
pecorino they say it'll be fine they say
it'll be just another boat ride in a
helicopter right they say what they
really meant was
I'm not in the boat this time
[Music]
well am I actually
I I know I'll just stop shooting
what the [\h__\h] what am I
what would that be your bike is not
meant to be stupid
[Music]
where am I getting picked up
she didn't do anything to you can you
pick me up now okay okay I'll be there
okay let's go
all the music the copyright
[Applause]
thank God we didn't have to time that
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
I can't put this much better okay I mean
no thanks to you
I don't remember can you guys quickly
tell me the controls wasn't there
something on the numpad I was supposed
to push as well
yeah right it was uh numpad and then
oh man
shut up about F I'm not pressing F you
idiots
um
I think the main controls for the numpad
and then A and D for turning right and
left a little bit I think
okay no I don't know [\h__\h] I don't even
[\h__\h] know
and
what's with the camera how do I control
the camera oh my my keyboard that
switched to Japanese [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] hold 8 to go forward W to elevate
uh
can I just
it's so over now
I don't know
[Music]
oh
I don't know if I want to finish this
game anymore
I'm not doing all of that for the 10th
time again
basically finished it yeah
it's just
wow
I I don't like leaving it at that
but I'm not gonna
finish this if if I am going to finish
it I'm not going to finish it
anytime soon
how are cheat codes gonna help man
is there a cheat code for speeding
forward in a mission
no I don't wanna
no
[\h__\h] that
shut up
yeah uh that just really sucks
I'm done for today that's for sure
um
damn
so unfortunate I worked so hard to
friend today
nah
it's so Beach over
I don't know if I'll ever get back to
this I can't promise right now I'll have
to sleep over it
and consider it
um
don't
don't say stuff that's obviously
taunting me
no no no the game finish up again
hmm
that's where you're going right now the
usual room
mm-hmm
[Music]
if the ending wasn't so
bad I would have finished it two hours
ago
three hours ago
um
I don't need the controller just for
that part then I'll just have to get
used to another new set of controls
um
I was fine flying with the helicopter
before
but
kind of sucks where they spawn you too
and it's so sudden
I know
um
oh that was like so annoying
I tried so many times I really wanted to
finish it today
if I noticed this is what how it was
gonna end I was I would have just not
tried so many times
man
I'm so hungry
[Music]
yeah
Final Fantasy will be better
Final Fantasy won't hurt me like that
um
[Music]
this is so unfortunate because it really
sours my experience
my feelings about this game
too bad
[Music]
I
just had the fauna one on the screen but
ah
and now I understand because I switched
over here
switched over here
I read the Pokemon unite tournament ones
and what about the Minecraft ones did I
not read the Minecraft ones
[Music]
that one let me check my back it's not I
did read those I think
oh yes
oh nice nice nice nice thank you past
wow
then it's Hollow talk
[Music]
where is it
I want to say when I'm dead and we'll
crash oh man I I get you good night
please take care
and rest
[Music]
I'm so hungry
they just shoot down the helicopter and
kill a bad guy at the Statue of
happiness
and then
maybe I'll watch the video I don't know
out
oh wait where's mine
[Music]
did I ever get my own talk merchandise I
don't think so
what when did you guys get your whole
talk merchandise
wasn't that a while ago
[Music]
a couple months ago
I wonder if maybe my my part just wasn't
ordered
[Music]
let me ask
was there ever on a tank merch put aside
for me
[Music]
Jeremiah's not awake right now anyway
s my old merch
emergency reminded me junkie junk
can I enjoy your whole talk with mug
it must taste so much better drinking
out of that mug
[Music]
so I don't wait 15 15.
blue light blue Super Chat thank you
foreign
[Music]
and I'm so happy to see your new cool I
love and adore you too I'm very excited
for this episode of whole talk you're so
good at interviewing people
thank you it was uh quite a challenge
this time but
yeah I totally worked out
was fun I think we had a good time
talking about a lot of different stuff I
mean it was more about like
um
I purposefully put in a lot of like
segments and Corners because of games
because I bought
um you know there's not much
you can ask about
there's always plenty of questions you
could ask but still I thought it would
be more fun to
have some games that also
for example test their knowledge about
each other
by drawing each other and all that kind
of stuff kind of testing
testing if they're strong enough to be
in whole life a little bit of a
challenge hmm
yeah
yeah so I don't think I'll take those
segments to normal whole talks but if I
ever have a like full generation Hollow
talk again
then I think I'll repeat those segments
[Music]
so thank you Kiana fried Pebble I'm
still not sure if you changed your name
and you're someone I should remember
what if you're new and you just started
super chatting recently then thank you
so much to
um
okay I know we've said this before but
best whole talk ever
well this one was kind of very different
from the usual ones I feel like you
should almost count it separately
Maybe
[Music]
just maybe
appreciate it
glad you enjoyed it
I did my best to prepare it so well that
would be enjoyable for everybody
um
thank you for the pinky black with
flowers
what do you know
foreign
I may be wearing that one right now
what a weird coincidence
but I wasn't then
[Music]
[Laughter]
one Joke Man TV table tree Duncan
putting channels in top secret
oh your name
funny funny whiskey Ninja
[Music]
Goss thank you for the pinky thank you
so much thank you for organizing a
special edition of whole talk we really
helped us knowing Evan better keep up
the good work we are so proud of you
always forever thank you
hat in your profile picture but okay I
will believe it maybe you just thought
that picture was cute but wouldn't a
picture of me been cuter if I'm your she
anyway anyway hmm
[Music]
what we get yeah
and it was fine I guess
oh he did say Ian Oshi oh truth true
you're right
[Music]
Tammy Duncan Mario's entire family
questions
[Music]
I remember Mario's entire family
I remember them too well
I remember their faces
they're terrified faces in the last
moments
[Music]
these aren't much so I'll read them also
quickly
[Music]
thanks guys thanks everybody winning
badminton let's go
let's see
[Music]
thank you
lucky profit
lucky Prophet Evans
[Music]
game corrupt myself where I didn't want
to ever bother with it again it's so sad
when stuff like that happens I feel like
a lot of people can relate maybe also
with other games
where you leave it behind so close to
the very ending because something is
just not working out
it's so sad yum
so such a waste of so much time you
don't get to see the ending man
[Music]
you always come back even if it's much
later
[Music]
that's the way you say that makes me
feel like
you would never go out to buy milk and
never come back that's beautiful
good to know
to know girlfriend will appreciate it
[Music]
I mean as long as you have as much
passion for your relationships as you do
for games
as much commitment
hopefully
making a lot of assumptions here yeah
laughs
you know what I'm gonna Skip One for a
moment and read this
I love how the fun thing I didn't expect
anything I just chose this art because
it was cute
and then it's funny because in the end
Subaru
was losing in the beginning but then one
in the end
and here in the Arts the boat was like
you know the weird weird little duck in
the middle and we're all like so curious
about her hmm
probably not expecting how dangerous
this little duck really is
underestimating her full potential
and afterwards regretting it
[Music]
I have a garden Kiana
I have a gun I have a gun
Patsy danger soon for the pinky
thank you so much thank you
I have received it
gratefully thank you
two one three five thank you soon
hey happy birthday once again
yeah what a coincidence man
did you schedule your birth
for this collab
because we certainly didn't schedule it
for your birthday
calendar
[Music]
soon
okay
yeah
I'll leave it at that there's like two
streams left uh the hollow kill one and
those games one
I sent a pinky wait did you
oh my God I'm so sorry I almost missed
it I'm colorblind at this point sorry
I'm sorry
Jim Tracy says this was such a fun
collapse so glad I got up for it oh what
time was it
was probably like 3 A.M
so excited for all the holiday news
especially the new original song is the
best yeah now you have already heard it
by now I hope it lived up to your
expectations 2 am you got up at 2 am so
you took a nap
well at least it wasn't too long
it basically
[Music]
was just like a little little midnight
snack of entertainment and then back to
sleep at 4am so I would say that's
that's pretty decent then that whole lot
how we dance
I stayed up for the start and then pass
out that's okay
thanks for trying to be there
it was a really bad time
[Music]
just reached 300K
it's growing so fast actually wow wow
that makes me think didn't I oh
yeah I'm at 1.49
okay
10K left guys
foreign
that's a lot of people
that's a lot of people oh guys one
question is uh a group session of
Baldur's Gate free should that be
streamed from four point of views
what do you think
cut the beginning and end of it oh there
you go
[Music]
I would recommend it sure please do you
could get away with one maybe not all
four
[Music]
not really I reckon okay it's like a
very split opinion
foreign
I have to be in the multiplayer station
to create my character
but we have to be like connected
while I do it
oh so we do kind of have to do it even
before
we stream
or during the Stream
it's so sad and I don't really have time
to play it off stream until the first
stream
[Music]
I think
yeah can you not create it in single
player and then use it for multiplayer
[Music]
no
okay
I wonder if we can start a bit early off
stream
foreign
start
[Music]
s
but then then the n a girls will have to
get up even earlier
[Music]
okay okay
we'll see we'll talk about it thanks for
the advice guys
I am going to see what I'll cook
hopefully I have something simple
[Music]
oh
live
they should have it on now
check
I saw they started Ocarina of Time
based
base doubles
I want to play that one also maybe
within this year even
Brain Brain Brain not working
here
wait no it's not working eh
did they turn it off I told them to turn
it on
didn't they tell me they didn't
[Music]
I told them to turn it on
I feel like they told me okay we did
I think that's a misunderstanding
[Laughter]
there has been
a misunderstanding I see
[Music]
[Laughter]
disturb them in the middle of the stream
and be like turn it on now yeah honestly
there will be many many more times where
I can read them
if they start the stream at this time
yeah
um let me I will I will tell them they
will maybe even appreciate this
misunderstanding for their
misunderstanding corner
um
you guys
wherever you want then even go to the
doggos or go to Ina I don't know or go
do something else
do what you want
I'm not gonna force you to do anything
you can stay here too sure wait wait
from wait for whatever I'm not streaming
tomorrow though
uh wait I can give you maybe a little
bit of an Insight let me check my
schedule
of what to expect
um next week the problem is
that
I was going to start Final Fantasy next
weekend
until I realized the amount of
streaming restrictions
on the weekend for me
foreign
because I am performing on day one and
two so
on Saturday
in my time zone I can only stream
between 5 p.m and 9 00 p.m that is
four hours
and then I am I must
stop streaming at 9pm
[Laughter]
and then on the following day on Sunday
I can start again at 5 pm and then
stream however long I want because then
it's over
[Music]
uh yeah and then also on Friday
the day before the concert
I am also not allowed to stream past
9 pm
[Music]
so I have to end my stream pretty early
two
so it might still change but what I'm
thinking is on Friday
oh I'm playing Hotline Miami too
[Music]
yeah starting a little bit earlier in
the day so that I can get at least a
decent amount of streaming time in
maybe 3 P.M or 3 30.
[Music]
on going backwards on the first day I
wanna stream the Korean stream and the
members stream
members maybe 9 p.m Korean maybe 2 P.M
and on Wednesday I want to play
oh Holo cure probably starting a little
bit early to
sure yet about the time
and on Tuesday at 4 pm my time so the
original starting time for today
is Baldur's Gate
[Music]
sounds like a plan so
the other way around Baldur's Gate
Hollow cure
Father's Day Tuesday hola cure Wednesday
first day Korean and members and Friday
Hotline Miami Saturday
well Saturday Sunday I don't know what
to stream yet because it's uh I can't
maybe
I don't know I don't know I might
actually decide what I stream
spontaneously I will probably take the
time to stream
but I don't know what yet maybe I'll
keep it oh open
for interpretation maybe even another
Hotline Miami or
I don't know we'll see how I feel
what I want to do I might keep it open
okay so that's that
um
[Music]
tomorrow I have to do
a recording
and
[Music]
something else why not family fun is
because it's not really a lot of time
maybe on Sunday
since I can start at 5 00 PM I could
maybe start Final Fantasy on Sunday
[Music]
but I think as I said I'll just keep it
open for now
the intro for 16 is about four hours
long
[Music]
you can make decent progress in four
hours oh all right all right
four hours
how are you okay
[Music]
you think I could even squeeze it into
the the sad day the four hours on
Saturday
maybe I will
yeah
that'll be a short stream but
um
I'll consider it
I like my jrpg streams to be very long
so that I can have as little Parts as
possible
little amount of parts
but I'll consider it if that's the case
that's interesting
if I can't think of something else that
I want to do than you
well
I will see what to eat uh and I'll see
I'll I'll be on Twitter
you'll see me around
um
[Music]
tomorrow tomorrow
schedule okay bye bye
have some please don't wake me up early
it was honestly my own fault today
she only woke me up once I think I don't
remember showing her the food
more than once
and she ate twice though
and
it was my fault because my brain was
like and then I gotta check my phone
foreign
anyway
[Music]
drawing
please
what is that is I'm just bad at making
the first Contact that I've always
[Music]
we have a case of shy Senpai who's
waiting to be invited
to a collabo
we're being watched valcus it's like I
feel like I feel like if I wasn't an
anime and Halloween was like it was like
that like a like a school anime I'd be
one of those people who are like
who like seem very quiet and distant but
instead I'm just like please wait
victory
but honestly on that topic
I think the whole
uh dynamic
um for when you join hololive as a new
member
it's I think
from what I also experienced it's
normally expected for the new members
to at least in the very beginning for
the first one or two collabs reach out
on their own and say hello you are the
Senpai that I want to collab with would
you be so kind to collab with me
um yeah there's maybe some exceptions
for some really really eager samples but
normally normally you're the one who
reaches out I reached out to Subaru and
um
I was one of the eager senpas who
reached out the other way around to
Bales I guess that's that's it's not the
rule but it's kind of the dynamic that
I'm feeling the atmosphere that I'm
feeling and
uh uh yeah because think about it like
honestly me as a Sim by now when new
girls come out I I almost feel like oh
uh they probably have like a lot of
senpa is already messaging them
so
I I guess I'll hold back
so I mean I didn't do that for Advent I
I overcame that feeling but that's
something I maybe
you can see others feeling and also felt
a little bit by myself
so generally I think it's expected and
also better for the cool guys to just
you know they just they just joined they
should whoever they're the most
interested in whoever they really wanted
to collab with they should hit those
people up and be like hey
[Music]
instead of you know
waiting for something to happen because
then maybe surprisingly nothing happens
either
um
yeah for me and narissa it was kind of a
mutual understanding
right there is
we had a mutual understanding
I held you at gunpoint
yes yes yes yes yes
would you have asked me
even if I wasn't so openly saying like
hi
[Music]
would you have asked me anyway
for first collable
or would you have been too worried
eventually see
these chickens
chickens they're all too scared but they
have to get some courage and go out
there and ask for a coolables of samples
if we haven't collabed first I wouldn't
have collab with anyone what what
oh my God
these chicken coolers
wow
well bibu had collab of Cali I nerissa
had collab with me
she already well she only had the the
holotalk right besides that nothing
one-on-one yet was Senpai but while
she's also gone I'm surprised didn't
plan any Senpai collabs yet
um but I think they they want to take it
easy they want to take it slow
yeah they're always collabing with
themselves anyway
no but I'm curious like I I would like
to see who they would
head up and who who they want to collab
with and what's what they're gonna do
what's gonna happen
um
Perpetual collab permanent collab
Channel yeah it's
it's so convenient man
so fun but anyway okay I'm Gonna Leave
You guys so good night it's midnight I'm
I'm Cinderella oh my God help yeah
oh oh
yeah right this is a thing maybe you'll
see it again
I guess
if you're lucky you'll see it again
[Music]
[Applause]
there must be some delay because I'm
playing it through obs
I love that ending wait I was trying to
uh because I can't read I was trying to
set up you know raid
um
I'm gone guys I'm not here anymore la la
la la