[Music]
[Applause]
me you got 1 2
[Music]
fre going
[Applause]
you got that
[Music]
pineapple going you know me
pineapple
[Music]
hey I I I I woo
[Applause]
[Music]
a dream like a dream
yeah
yeah how it goes how it goes
you already know you already
know me want to go and
[Music]
party is always
and it tastes good
[Music]
[Applause]
you got that
[Music]
pineapple
going pineapple hey
[Applause]
[Music]
so
Hypno my you
[Music]
be I try down I'm going one 2 one 2
three it tastes so so so
[Music]
[Applause]
you got that
[Music]
pineapple pineapple hey
[Applause]
[Music]
two one
two
[Music]
[Applause]
s you got that pineapple
[Music]
keep going you know
me pineapple hey
[Music]
[Applause]
K welcome to holot talk no no
no don't worry we're not doing holot
talk um but I thought the background in
the game looks so much like holot talk
wouldn't you agree it's like they copied
my whole set huh no no I'm not claiming
that the late night talk show sets are
all of my design because they all look
pretty similar no no yeah but the vibe
was so similar but hm I have a screen in
my holot talk sets
so actually could use it for once in
this kind of way why
not
right k
oh yeah let me first and foremost rant
and vent about my
ISP cuz my
[Music]
ISP is doing stupid things again very
very very stupid things can we all hate
isps right unless is there anybody who
works for an ISP somewhere around the
world
if
yes then everybody kind of hates you I'm
sorry but you do you do
oh well hopefully you can be the change
or the one good helpful employee in your
[Music]
company um that would be really nice I
wish you were like here in Austria
working for the one that I'm getting
really angry at
again ah no I have never heard anybody
talk positively about their isp's
service ever before
maybe like in Japan the internet is
really good but I don't know about the
ISP service honestly cuz I had issues
too with like
service so I don't know maybe service
for Ice is just [\h__\h]
everywhere people don't talk about their
espan yeah unless something's wrong yeah
but this that's the problem like because
they're like incapable of helping at
least in my case like H I understand
like having outages and stuff here and
there um that's fine you know I mean not
really but that's fine but in not being
okay this music is really repetitive let
me mute it
first not being able to help at all
so for like over a month I didn't
realize it's been so long I just didn't
really have the mental capacity to
bother with this so for over a month I
haven't been able to take or do any
calls or receive like SMS or whatsoever
uh unless I go like
outside so I've Mi been missing a lot of
calls that I don't even know I don't
even know that I'm missing them because
it's not like I see that I missed a call
no I don't even get
that and I also can't call anybody so
yeah that really sucks and like for
stuff like when I have to when I when I
get into my um accent stuff and then I
try to export the motion capture that I
did I have to log into this like um
Cloud that they have and in order to
sign in into the cloud they always want
to send me an
SMS and in order to receive that
SMS I have to press the like send me an
SMS
button with my phone already like
outside I have to leave my phone
somewhere outside go back inside press
the send SMS go back outside look at my
phone see if I got it and then yeah I
can only receive it while it's outside I
can't have my phone inside the moment I
press the send SMS thing it will not
arrive uh so that's been kind of
annoying and I talked a month ago like a
few days after I noticed that this was
happening I I I talked to my ISP and and
they were
like like first of first they were like
H can't find any reason for it
weird and then after pushing they were
like oh yeah okay so I found something
um it will be fixed uh 5 days later if
uh not then contact us again and then
the next day I get a like automated
message that they have something
something going on and uh it should be
done by this day which was the 5 days
later and I was like okay okay at least
this seems like to be inside of their
system now okay I will wait of course
didn't get fixed on that date but I
couldn't be bothered with
like it was just I I didn't want to I
didn't want to follow up again so I was
just waiting it out but even after a
month it hasn't been fixed
and then around the same time I don't
know if it's connected but like I've had
a lot of like every day during my
streams I've had a lot of Internet
outages too
right sorry been drinking Coca-Cola a
little bit to wake up didn't have a nap
that's why I
needed so yeah today I decided to follow
up with them about the phone thing but
also also tell them about my internet
thing but they like hyper fixate first
of all they hyper fixate on things that
don't even matter cuz I been like they
were like okay is it just your Lan
connection or your uh W Lan connection
uh and I said uh oh the Wi-Fi wait do
you guys say w Lan that sounds very
stupid to say that in
English do you even say that yeah you
just say Wi-Fi don't
you uh um yeah I was like well I don't
really know it's it's been most
noticeable for my land connection cuz I
do I said I do home office I just always
say I do home office so I need my
internet to work at home um and I say
well it's been like really bother some
while I'm doing work because on my PC it
just has so many outages several times
each day and the the Wi-Fi I don't know
like on my phone generally it's working
on my iPad too maybe on my Smart TV it's
been acting up weirdly recently but it's
mostly My Lan internet and they hyper
fix it because they can't find a reason
why My Lan is not working they hyper fix
it on the Wi-Fi and they like test it
and they're like oh your speed's like
really fine though it's really good I
just did a test and I've did I've done
three diagnosises now in 40 minutes and
your internet seems really fine and I
cannot find any any outages whatsoever
and I'm
like well first of all it's really not
so much the Wi-Fi should shouldn't have
mentioned it at
all it's mostly the
L um and then and then they're like oh
did you try um resetting your router and
I was like yeah well actually your
colleague because I was like in this
like online chat room with them and
first I had a conversation with a lady
for
like 30 minutes or so 40 30 40 minutes
and then she was like okay I have to
restart your router now and I'm like oh
okay but my internet connection will be
gone so the chat will probably
disconnect and uh but I can try turning
on my mobile
data and she's like okay do it and I'm
like okay I did it and then I lose
connection to the chat and when I try to
go back in it connects me with someone
else and then I asked can you connect me
with this other person I knew her name
and they were like sorry we can't
connect anybody I'm
like don't they think when they ask when
they
bro what kind of customer service is
that when you basically kicking them out
with no way for them to ever get back to
you
anymore that's so dumb that's so dumb oh
so I'm like okay well if you can't
connect me I guess we'll have to start
over even though I just had a
conversation with this lady for 40es
minutes and we were hopefully getting
somewhere so I had to explain everything
again that it's my phone is not working
unless I go outside and it's been like
this for a month and they had this thing
where they said they will fix it in 5
days it's been a month since nothing has
been
fixed um and so on I explain everything
again I spent two hours on this today I
think and then I mentioned the internet
too like okay so besides dad my internet
also has been weird and so they they
can't find any reason why my phone isn't
working so they fixate on the internet
in the end the whole thing is just like
sorry I did I tried everything that I
can do but you have to call the hotline
next Monday and ask for a technician
because that I can't do anything for you
but I will send you a new SIM card and
I'm like okay okay okay wait wait you
know SIM card that was a solution that I
thought
might help because I talked to somebody
a month ago in this chat room before I
realized that when I go
outside it works fine so what do you
really think a SIM card exchanging a SIM
card would
help because it seems like a different
issue to
me I mean I'm not it but I'm also not
stupid I think I have logical
comprehension to understand
that this is not a SIM card is broken
issue yeah but they they literally I've
had plenty of experiences with this ISP
customer service so far they just they
have to they seemingly have to go down
this list of solutions even if they make
absolutely no
sense and after all of that because they
they want to avoid at any cost
that you go and get a technician I was
so mad this
year
honey thank
you thank you my beautiful
[Music]
beautiful okay flashback flashback
music in February I told you guys this
during my break I had a lot of
problems um with the ISP
um because I moved I told you this I
moved in secret and then I came back and
I thought I could come back but I
realized wait my Internet isn't working
so I couldn't come back when I wanted to
come back um now the the weird thing
back then was that my my glass
fibers were apparently broken but the
until like understanding that because
you
know I would I would would um have the
expectation that my internet works I
would like install it and so on cuz it's
self-installation it doesn't work so I
called the hotline and they're like try
this try restarting your router try
doing this and that nothing helps right
and they're like okay we will send you a
new router and I'm like I don't know if
that will work because this is a new
router this just just doesn't feel like
it will help but okay so they sent me a
new router I try with the new router it
doesn't work I call them they're like
well try resetting the router again
doing this and that and this and so many
stupid solutions that just don't work
and then I don't know I don't even
remember this so well anymore but they
were like um going to send
[Music]
me yeah one I think one lady like
promised me to send me a technician but
when I I didn't get any contact or so
after days I call back and nobody
remember remers the story it's not
anywhere in the system like not
registered anything no information so we
start over from zero again and they're
like you have to get a new router and
I'm like I already tried with a new
router and try a new land cable I'm like
I already tried different lwn
cables like it's so [\h__\h] annoying and
they they then even though the previous
staff uh like said they will send me a
technician this other staff will not
accept this and says no no we cannot
under any circumstance send you
anybody it was so
annoying it was so annoying and I was
the whole time I thought like all their
Solutions are so stupid and nothing
makes any sense I I'm not an IT person
but I have this feel I'm really bad with
tech and anything like that but I had
this feeling that there's a deep deep
rooted uh problem right but they just
always scratch the
surface and I'm telling them like I need
this for my job like I I gave you like a
month or so and still
nothing um yeah and
then eventually after a lot of fighting
a after going to an IRL shop and they
were like oh yeah this is a lot of
[\h__\h] obviously the things they're
saying to you on the phone are make make
no sense I can see that this is a
different kind of problem we'll send you
a
technician but then I think even after
that nothing followed nobody contacted
me and then blah blah blah blah
eventually a technician came by and the
technician was really nice and
everything but I was like yo it was so
hard to get you to come here and he was
like
yeah yeah they the the ones on the
hotline they don't know what they're
talking about says the
technician technician tries out
everything and even the technician
recognizes that this isn't even a
problem that he can
handle
huh and sends me um like some kind of
like uh what was it like construction
engineering whatever person days later
because yeah it wasn't even a technician
thing it was even deeper it was the
glass fiber cable that was
new but uh even though it was new when
it was like planted it must have
like I don't know had some defect so
they had to replace the whole thing but
getting to this point and for somebody
to take me serious it took
forever so now now when they are when
this chat person is telling me to call
the hotline and ask for a technician
next Monday you know what I'm thinking
I'm never getting a technician to get
here again and help me this I don't know
do you have some like secret password
that I have to say on the hotline so
that the the workers are actually like
okay that is the magical word that is
all you had to say um spaghetti cabonara
that's the magical
keyword like my God I don't want to call
them it's so
annoying and I don't even understand how
they're like not even seeing
anything like I don't I don't know I
will still get the new SIM
card and I will try it out so that I can
say on the hotline I tried this do not
attempt to send me a new SIM card it
doesn't work it doesn't even make any
sense why would a SIM card help me with
this
issue
yeah yeah so that's what I wanted to
vent
[Music]
about no there's other
providers but I mean you know I have a
contract and [\h__\h] so
the password is I love
am right I forgot about
[Music]
that yeah it's not even like nothing
happened
to like I nothing changed it was just
all of a sudden I don't
understand I mean over a month is just
ridiculous so yeah who knows maybe my
stream will crash again
today I have this constant fear
now
well
[Music]
um I love
Amy yeah they're breaching their
contract because they aren't fulfilling
their end of the contract they don't
give a [\h__\h] when I tell them that kind
of stuff on the phone they don't give a
[\h__\h] might just go to the store again
because they seem a little bit more
understanding first the USB problem now
this well the USB problem is solved all
okay all is
okay well I don't
know even at the store like they don't
normally like assign technicians that's
not what they normally
do they just made like some kind of
exception I guess back then I don't know
even at the store there's like like
people who don't know what they're
talking about sometimes I had that too I
had that
too I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I
dealed with this for two hours today I
had to let it out okay today in this
beautiful holot talk Studio we will play
voice mimicry show I I thought you know
we need a USB microphone so I have a USB
microphone so I tried it out with that
of course that that one doesn't work you
have to get a specific USB microphone
that is um Nintendo approved so I got a
a cute little cute little tiny
microphone it's cute okay it's not that
tiny it's not like a tiny microphone
with what you do like tiny interviews
with tiny animals like mice or so no no
no it's like a small but normal size
microphone it's cute it looks like a
Koka microphone and and uh I tested it
it works so
uh we're going to play this little meme
game now I know this game cannot be
taken too
seriously
so don't judge me I can do I when they
say 0% or so zero points they're full of
[\h__\h] we're going to try well as you can
see I tried the first one jump into
water total score 24 which I don't think
is it's not fair we can try it again to
test the microphone again hello
ah can you hear the
feedback I'm a
dog how
fun okay okay
can I do better is it
better I mean I was yeah I started kind
of late I started kind of late let me do
it
again
Bru I would say that's
perfect try it's worse than before
um I can't do that better how the [\h__\h]
do you do it better at least it's not
[Laughter]
zero let's do another one I I can hear
myself even when I'm I'm holding the
microphone further away from me spring
loaded do you K
ah Bo
okay surely everybody in whole life has
has done it like that but I hesitated
it's a weird
timing now let me try
again
Bing what why maybe I it was too long I
guess they need to I think they're like
matching the frequencies I
guess so I need to be loud at the right
timing and I need to be quiet at the
right timing it's it's probably mostly
that and
not uh not really recreating the sounds
but let's just pretend that's what it
actually is
will this be
better I wasn't loud enough but 30
points I
mean
h maybe one more time one more
time that's probably not better oh wait
oh okay
I'm happy with that
honestly it could be much worse let the
air
horn oh [\h__\h] okay
[Music]
easy that sounded pretty
long oh yeah it was way too long but
still 35
H
[Music]
wait now I matched the length I
think 60 almost
n a how dare you take the 69 like dangle
it in front of
me
uh I I guess I was still a little bit
too long I I kind of had a feeling
[Music]
oh it felt it it sounded better but it's
still too long one more time one more
[Music]
time too long too long too long too long
ah
[Music]
61 okay even though I talked at the
end okay
[Music]
okay that feels so short
though but it's it's ah 68 again
oh
[Music]
wow I like being an airor porn this is
fun should be my new job
83 okay okay I mean airor is kind of one
of the easiest ones I
think pretty happy with that how many
are
there oh so many well then it's not so
bad if we kind of Zoom through it right
[Music]
okay uh what how the
[\h__\h] I don't know
cake let me try again it could be better
but not so
bad I don't
know I don't know that's so difficult
that's ridiculous a human can't make
these
sounds this is a good party game I need
to invite some friends over and played
it with them
kicks kick oh man how do you improve
this I sound like a cat I sound like a
cat bird a cat is it a
bird now I sound like Golem
[Laughter]
I can never get
better
[Music]
oh I don't [\h__\h] know this one's
difficult what what [\h__\h] it's so
[Music]
rigged but you can see the frequencies
or whatever that is matches it I guess
better than what I did
before this game is full of [\h__\h] I love
it I love it AER quiz ah
bams I knew it I knew it we love that
kind of
stuff wait one more
time do I have that I have that hold
on should we try feeding it through my
headphones wait do you hear
that oh you guys don't hear it I I still
don't I still couldn't figure out how
to how to R it so that you guys can hear
it well let me let me just try let me
just I can do it myself perfectly fine
but I want to try
out for my
headphones wait it's so quiet it doesn't
get picked
up uh it was it was certainly there but
okay ah one more
time okay I can do it I can do it
butons it's not quite boms
but
dun okay okay okay here we go here we go
yeah oh yeah oh
yeah I was a little bit too loud at the
end there maybe we can improve it that's
certainly really good
though here you
go just more hold it
back a bit too quiet
100 break
s all right all right all right all
right easy
next easy I have done a sheep or goat
impression before I think in my Amo
series should be easy
Easy Come on first try oh beautiful bit
too long bit too
long still maybe a bit too long but I
reached yeah reached a peak earlier
pretty good pretty
good I'm already kind of happy with that
honestly but one more time one more time
oh that was beautiful what a
sheep oh [\h__\h] that looks very diff What
here it doesn't match as at all like it
matched better
before and yet they rank me almost
interesting maybe there is some
technique to it maybe this is a skill
issue as well I
am no no no no no but I understand sheep
I understand them on a different
level shall we move
[Music]
on oh we can go to the next one like who
who whoa
whoo oh easy easy I like these easy ones
ah so
easy oh my my pee at the
end was was way too loud one more
time I add a little bit of an
F
oh one more one more
oh it's worse
hello that is really
good I'll take it I'll take it I'll take
it I'll freaking take
it
t easy more of these game show sounds
shouldn't be too difficult
[Music]
how what do you think
parrot 42 is that the answer no it is
[Music]
not that was way too long I think was
it I tried
to kind of sound s like I'm boosted I'm
I'm I'm a sound effect you know one more
time
[Music]
earlier that's pretty good that feels
pretty
good oh look at
[Music]
the all right all
right let's
go oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
do they use this kind of sound effect in
like American TV shows and so on too cuz
I feel like maybe a lot of these sound
effects are just
very they I guess so yeah but maybe not
So Much Anymore is it
outdated but yeah this sounds very La
Law and
Order okay
22 that's so bad I mean I guess I can be
generally louder until the end
[Music]
the rhythm is
difficult I need to be more more
smooth [\h__\h] oh no oh no it gets worse I
need to be more smoed
out I don't know I tried to move away
from the microphone like somebody said
in the chat but I don't know it makes me
[Music]
[Laughter]
nervous yeah come on come on
I'm I'm a
beatboxer yeah 60
okay I can't quite fix the
beginning
oh okay I'll try
we'll have to work on
that shut
up what the
[Music]
man I really want some kind of but I
can't follow it up so
[Music]
fast that's pretty good
no come on give me some credit I can't I
can't make those two sounds in such
close
succession
[Music]
oh try to do it differently now
recreating that sound in a different
way oh
okay pretty good Prett
good that looks a lot closer now to the
original
graph maybe good enough maybe good
enough tell
me really you're hitting me with the
chicken
already all right I'm very well
practiced in this
one here we go everybody
K oh if this is not a 100 k
[Music]
cut you don't even
understand what a chicken sound even
sounds
like all right I'll do it more like you
you faker
that was
legit y y y
y what look at the graph bro I even
implemented the last little peek at the
end the [\h__\h] is wrong with you what do
you
want the [\h__\h]
you're going to make a fool out of
[Music]
me I'm trying my best here yeah I sound
like a strangled chicken poor chicken
I don't think it's getting
[Music]
better
what that didn't even really have a good
peek at the
end how is this better it still sucks
we're improving we're improving with the
big
[Applause]
peek it's not so much a peak in loudness
but in like it has like
[Applause]
[Music]
a okay it's like a um what do you call
it
like when you go like it's kind of like
a a voice break thingy uh what do you
call it
again uh uh uh uh
uh uh uh yeah like the
tomorrow a voice crack yeah it has like
this voice crack somewhere in
there at the the peak there at the end
listen
yeah I was way too late I'm sorry I'm
sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry shut up shut
up shut up shut up
[Music]
oh what do you mean look how accurate
that
is what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
nah nah now of of course there were
other tries that were better but this
game is not raiding me
correctly not chicken thank you not CH
can confirmed there we [\h__\h] go I've
been telling you guys for a long
time oh dear oh
dear not sure how to do that
[Music]
I felt the
Zen pretty bad 60 for that don't think I
can top it
[Music]
how about that is it better than
60 it doesn't look like it at all in the
graph
[Music]
yeah I think I need to be louder
maybe looks very
different yeah I know I
[Music]
know yeah I tried to make it louder
what go [\h__\h]
yourself how is that better just because
I screamed into the microphone because I
was eating up the microphone my lips
were literally touching the microphone
and we heard it
breaking okay we see the strats
now
oh oh it's like somebody's getting
whipped
should be
easy let bit
longer I too
long
zero
what can't give me a zero for that
oh oh 55 that's a 100 that's a [\h__\h]
100 don't
care
next oh we got a funny
one I like this
one oh oh why do they not want to give
me a
69 it's like it's a ban
number pretty
good even better I think but they're
going to score it worst aren't
they 65 oh pretty pretty
similar if it was a bit shorter
[Music]
69 there we go okay we got it it wasn't
banned oh dear
[Music]
I want professional beatboxers to play
this
game I feel like they might be really
good at
this what do you mean too long look at
this look at this and
learn first try 100 yeah I I even
implemented a little bit of it was
really slightly and it was really faint
and it was really quiet and at the very
end there was like a i I heard that I
was like oh that's going to give it the
extra little spicy little extra that it
needs okay moving
on what the
[Music]
[\h__\h] okay okay
feels like feels like they give us a lot
of time for that one but we don't need
that much
time that was very
wrong
65 really I mean okay only the graph
looks very different but it felt kind of
similar yeah it gives me alien Vibes one
more time one more
[Music]
time I don't know I don't know I don't
know I don't know about that one maybe
previously it was better
[Music]
oh what oh
what Boo's
bed oh [\h__\h] I think I'm I'm the one
behind the counter saying boo binted how
what do you mean
how yes because Bo's
bed perfect makes me happy
oh oh cute oh cute what a romantic
sound
a oh you know what I just
[Music]
realized turtle dove in German is Turtle
tum which the Turtle part is like
basically looks same but turtle dove
turtle is a turtle right so it's like a
turtle Bird right in English language
the turtle means
Turtle but in the German language Turtle
the turtle of turtle
talum I don't think it's a turtle at all
I don't really know what it's coming
from but in German this Turtle T I maybe
in English too but you call it to uh you
say it to a couple who's like really
like T
yeah oh you're such Turtle dubs
basically do you say that in
English yeah like love birds I
guess but I never never really thought
about this so much and realized that
there's a turtle in that word anyway do
it
again
okay okay easy I'm a bird
[Music]
girl that the delay in my voice makes me
kind of go slower it's
[Music]
confusing it's like I really want
Callie's cats to come over over
Tut Tut one more time oh oopsie no I
skipped by accident oh well what the
[\h__\h] is that con shell is it like
um what
[Music]
shell the horns the horns of I know
Gondor
[Music]
okay okay we can
try yeah g calls for Aid Helms
Deep could be
good 58 I mean not bad for first try
[Music]
Rohan will
answer I want to watch
Rings rings for Lo Rings Lo of rings
shut
up what can I do if I'm so funny to
myself
[Music]
please please PR
him pretty
different yeah okay it has to be more
like o
[Music]
oomph got do it with
confidence bit too
late but
D but it look so
[Music]
good sounds like an alarm
honestly oh my
God that was
good yeah okay next next
next that's a win in the bag
[Music]
easy okay could be
better this pretty cute though
[Music]
yeah Dad no no no no I can do
better I can do better the believe me I
I I can do
[Music]
better I can
better
0 yeah the graph looks pretty damn good
too there we go
[Music]
okay oh damn
oh lot he
coming oh [\h__\h] I'm not
ready that was
[Music]
loud how about that
oh got a 69
[Applause]
baby nothing is better than a 69 not
even
100 let's
[Music]
go these ones are
fun wow
should been
louder does it
[Music]
matter six yeah it felt
good I'm happy with
that oh not it's more
like
[Music]
delusion 48 is okay but let's do it
again
[Music]
little bit
cuter you like
it do you like it
[Music]
yeah nah I don't care what you say fr
two n that was 100 uh-uh next wrong
score oh [\h__\h] that's similar to the
other one which is more
[Music]
extreme let's see if this works
[Laughter]
[Music]
I'm cheating
basically yeah yeah that's how you do it
guys that's how you freaking do it
next oh oh little bit more sophisticated
than the other one that we had
oh that was
good oh but the grab the grab is very
different 57 okay
okay now that seems more precise
s okay okay okay I'm happy with that
moving on
oh catch me outside how about that
no what really
huh [\h__\h] that can't be
good
huh what's for the cut
scene will that be better
very different
technique H it's about the
same
[\h__\h] sounded like I said
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] I I can't really get out of that 50
range so let's move
on whoa
I just punched
myself I punched my
[Laughter]
stomach okay I'll take the easy wins
oh nah how how can I be a beatboxer I
need to do better if I want to be
beatboxing in my next original
song nah
too much F and weird
sound that was good that was good that
was
good ah
[\h__\h]
[Music]
no I don't
know I was almost like a kitty
key huh um I don't know
next is the constant like music going on
and off making you guys go crazy a
little bit cuz it's is making me go a
little bit crazy cuz we're so fastpaced
with
this
no okay okay okay okay okay crazy crazy
crazy on
no not quite not
quite oh okay
we it's like it's in your head but when
it comes out of your mouth it's just not
quite the the way you imagine it to be
[Music]
okay
okay doesn't get much better oh
[Laughter]
dear come on 100 100 I feel it I feel it
I told
you it just feels right when it feels
right you know it oh oh
there could be many
techniques okay one more one
more that was way softer the softer
approach
oh no
[Applause]
please what do you
think
44 that's like a rattles snake oh
[Music]
know didn't quite get the r out there
H H how is this also
44 I don't know
man
easier sounds more it's more difficult
than it
sounds I believe I believe in the snore
mhm yeah y y y y y y y y y that's what I
thought oh
[\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] oh dear
[Music]
trying to blow really hard into the mic
here give it some
air
yeah even with all that air
[Music]
need a flute
yeah oops sorry we went to the next one
can't do it better anyway I feel like
[Music]
all right short
sound can we nail it first
[Music]
try all right
maybe a bit too
late no actually timed well but why does
this game hate
[Music]
me that's
perfect for human making those
sounds
nah
next oh cute I like these sounds thank
you for the raid
let's let's hear one one more
time it's just pong real pong moment
right
there or is it a a Don not a
p oh but I mean the number say this was
quite good so moving
on ha
Perfection is what this
is don't lie to
me you know it's perect
don't [\h__\h] me I even started quiet
gently yes yeah okay that was way off
[Music]
huh that was my worst like I I I was
doing better when I wasn't whistling
[Music]
n [\h__\h] it doesn't come
out what ah whatever
next
oh dokie doie doie
dokie well I don't think my heart is
pounding loud enough for me to put my
microphone to my heart and try to
capture that so we'll have to do it
ourselves I don't know why it's Donkey
Kong Don Kong Kong Kong [\h__\h] I kind of
got the timing really well but I is it
because I laughed at the end is that why
how about that now it's just do not
[Music]
dong to punch the mic now
that was right
timing the previous ones too every
everything look at my feeling of timing
free it even like what it even I don't
mean I I
kind of giving up
honestly not going very doky doie for
this one du du du du it's better
before
yeah doy doy doy
here we go cute style will it win doie
doy doy it's too
early wow what a punch in the face I'm
out of
here whoa whoa
whoa um
[\h__\h]
okay now my neck recently the way like
it's so weird right now it hurts there's
some
weird
nerves
being [\h__\h] over so now I can't really
I'm trying to crack my neck but it's
somehow stopping me because it's yeah I
don't know which is I guess a good thing
but at the same time it's it feels so
bad so yeah can't use that to my
advantage
very on
topic or or not because we didn't race
yesterday unfortunately I didn't no but
I I played even more off
screen and I think I I got pretty
decent now if we ever do it uh in the
future I think you know everybody's open
to just like rescheduling it but now you
know why it was a racing game in the
first place because of the whole Euro
beat
remixes and the
merchandise so yeah for people who
completely missed it yesterday who don't
don't know what's going
on uh a lot of Holo Ian members
yesterday were going to stream AET compe
the racing game and we were practicing
for it and it was going to be a big
collab and then the servers were down uh
right before the collab like an hour
before I don't know how long after but
yeah then it had to be called
off yeah unfortunately like all of the
aeto servers we had our own server but
like the whole game server was
down for 5 hours oh my god wow that I'm
glad we didn't like delay it for one or
two hours and waited it out because it
would have still not been finished with
that but anyway um they still announced
the uh Euro beat remix album which
features like almost everybody of Holan
it even features Amy am Chik taku yeah
everybody got a Euro bead
remix
yeah that's why it was um the racing
game but I think you know everybody got
excited about the racing game so maybe
we'll still play it sometime in the
future if we can find another good date
and time
[Music]
yum yeah I was playing the Euro beat
remix in the
beginning my pineapple remix I chose
pineapple because I thought it would fit
it quite well uh and because like I
don't know he know told he had a EUR be
remix fanmade before a long time ago so
that's other of the question I just
thought pineapple would be really fun
because it's like the it's when I listen
to it now it's like it gives me Barbie
Vibes or something like that I don't
know no I didn't re-record
[Music]
anything it's cute right I like
it I mean in the end you can make
anything into your your beat I guess um
but I thought pineapple is a good base
for it
yeah yeah I wanted to hear it I wanted I
wanted to hear pineapple you were beat
okay my poor pineapple
baby not it felt very
different felt like a downwards curve
rather than an upwards curve but you
like it huh don't you like it game I see
I see how it
[Music]
is
70 wow is on Spotify now yeah I think
the whole Europe beat album is on the
streaming services so check it out if
you want to it's pretty pretty hype
quite the Bop song on there is really
well
done and yeah there's merchandise I just
don't really uh like I I I know K like
we have our own my anniversary merch
still uh on sale right now which is more
important to me I'll be honest um and I
know a lot of you guys have been
spending a lot of money on merchandise
recently so it's a bit hard for me to
advertise merchandise like that but if
you have too much money and you want to
throw some of it some of it
at me uh you you can get some of the EUR
beat merchandise if you want to but I'm
I'm not going to push too hard for it
let's focus on my Anniversary
merchandise and hint hint hint You might
want to save your money big time cuz
November you might need the money just
saying
there's some
stuff several things that you will not
want to miss out on I will
say
[Music]
yeah yeah like I'm very
excited
next oh [\h__\h] this is the sound of your
jaws
dropping when you find out what you want
to buy when it's time in
[Music]
November if this is the sound of your
wallet then congratulations you must
have a lot in there that
could perhaps be used for
something pretty
bad but I can't be bothered with that
one
next oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] Japanese instrument giving me a big
win I don't even know what that is
clapboard my butt is a
clapboard but well ideally it's not a a
board anymore
um it used to be more of a board now
it's a little bit more of a clap Bridge
no I mean you know like butt slab like
slap like a little little bit of a slap
from
[Music]
Ollie
anyway moving on focus focus
[Music]
how about
that it's it's a little bit too fast I
mean I'm too slow the sound is very fast
in the beginning the the the thing that
I tried to recreate there h
[Music]
I don't know I tried to make it go
kab
next
[Music]
cute oh that was adorable wasn't
not what the [\h__\h] is wrong with you
that's one of the cutest sounds I've
ever made in my whole life and it was
pretty
accurate the hell but this makes me feel
like I should do an M CUO
CUO I want to do a video on that now add
that to my future M Zoo ideas list
please
that would be pretty
cute triy to do it a bit
differently
fre I mean okay the sounds like this and
the doie doie that are really quiet in
between they seem very very timing based
but it's going to be almost impossible
to get that
timing maybe
now yeah yeah even with that n that's
[\h__\h] that's too difficult what do
you what do you want from me
[Music]
that feels very
wrong too
long not even that long 67
wow
[Music]
okay thank you
spares sexy okay whatever I'll just
that's pretty good I'll move on oh
Indian PE
foul interesting waya has a a sister in
India cute
cute cuteo
not me but the original
sound oh getting
[Music]
there Nan
D why is it getting
worse started very early now maybe it
was cut
off no no what it's such a short
sounds try to do it
shorter but it doesn't end up that short
[Music]
okay now it really did it
shorter
what it's too
difficult that doesn't even sound like
it was an actual gust of wind that did
sound like a person recreating a gust of
wind
[Music]
that waso too
loud oh [\h__\h] even at
what
wa that was
good n that was better that
before you're scared it's a monster no
it's a g the wind it's a g of
wind it's really gentle
too
yeah it's like
ASMR wow beautiful ASMR this is what it
will sound if I get my own ASMR
microphone
come on come
on ah started too
loud very different yeah understandable
understandable
that is so good that is such a good
Recreation the graph says something else
add a zero to that because that's what
it
[Music]
deserves all right all right all right I
heard that many times not in my school
but in anime I think
[Music]
very
confusing with the delay the timing is
hard to
get yeah too late at the
end what s n this game is so confused it
doesn't know what it's doing but okay
for how much was it five bucks that's
okay
like I've done better for other prompts
but have gotten judged less points
scored less so
yeah it's a meme game
yeah oh Magic
Stick I'll show you my magic stick
that's what he said
[Music]
uh I don't
[Applause]
know that was an orchestra in my Thro
right now
[Music]
that was 100 but okay pretty good
score
okay
next o another Japanese
instrument should be doable
[Music]
kind of
disrespectful okay I'll do it
[Music]
again okay okay okay okay now we're
talking yeah that's what I want to see H
I switched from dun to buom oh w w
woohoo it
[Music]
chaa
oh oh 61 for first try of something
that's very timing based again pretty
good t t
t got worse
[Laughter]
yeah I hate tofu actually but uh this
time tofu was very helpful to me so I
love
[Laughter]
[Music]
tofu
Co why does it sound so
sad oh it started way too
late
yeah okay
[Music]
it got baby one more
time I closed my eyes for that
one felt like I was falling
asleep he
Le okay then then I'm moving on I swear
those scores are RNG not for
real w
who is this
friend what a cute friend
warbler need to Google that right now
cuz that's
adorable warer bird oh
cute oh they're like green or yellow
mostly yellow oh so cute I see some gray
ones too though wa what a
picture wow
adorable they're so
cute oh I guess there's yeah a lot of
different warblers
huh cute a so
cute oh cute and now I'm just bird
watching birds are so cute I kind of
like I when I see videos of people who
have birds as their
pets and seeing how adorable they are I
get a little bit jealous I wish I had
one but then again I feel like birds
will make you go
insane as a pet like oh my
God yeah very
noisy and I need a pet that I that is
big enough that I can like give it a
hug bird is too small even though kind
of cute and
fluffy puffy like when they puff up
their
chests so
cute yeah can an
ostrich that that's a little bit extreme
before I get an ostrich you know I feel
like the ostrich is just a bird version
of an alpaca I'd rather get an
alpaka I'm sorry but I love alpacas you
know
it okay yeah chicken is pretty huggable
in terms of size that's why I have you
guys that's why you guys are chickens
cuz it makes you
hugable you're like a pretty perfect
size yeah pretty like you know ball
shaped very
round pretty much the the the D Di meter
par I what's the
word the
circumference of
a pretty big ball maybe
basketball maybe bigger than a
basketball
usually fat
[\h__\h] d d I said
diameter it's a good size is good
fluffiness good shape very huggable I
like what what are we doing oh
God nah too much
air oh [\h__\h] what's going on in that
let's try it without uh whistling
it's like somebody tickled
me got to end it
[Music]
fast one more one
more n n not so
good started too loud and too
[Music]
early how come okay it's better than the
previous 60 but how come I cannot just
end it so abruptly
I tried I tried I
tried oh
yeah I did it way more abruptly all
right all right Birds baby that's where
it's at oh the [\h__\h] that's more than one
that sounds more like more than
one yeah that's more than one how the
[\h__\h] is one person supposed to recreate
five
Birds the
[\h__\h]
what
okay I tried my best to be many birds
but it's impossible
all right it seems like the middle one
there was unnecessary are you sure I
heard something
[Music]
there a little bit too much of a
difference there in in
loudness at the
end
ow I almost feel like I can do better
but what
whatever oh here we go oh here we
[Music]
go I would normally do it differently
but I'm trying to recreate it
so
wow rude
[Music]
that was better
no
yeah
H that was a sound effect
too
oh okay I move the microphone away while
I was doing
it oh that went too low too
[Music]
fast that's how I would do it but it's
very different from the OG
[Music]
[Laughter]
how about that how about that it gets a
little bit louder at the end I
think
oh how is the graph even so zigzag in
the original when it's like pretty
smooth how am I making it
smoother how do they have less zigzag
lower
[Music]
range I don't know about lower range it
sounds pretty high to
me sexy okay I'll take it it also sounds
like a sad sad
cat but also mostly a sad dog I guess
what kind of bird is that the bird eats
flies how tiny is the
bird that's too difficult come on how
high level is
that no that's so complicated
I don't know we can try a
[Music]
whistling
nah wow really really that's kind of
lenient that's very
generous that's more like the human
approach
[Music]
oh that sounds exactly like the
bird
oh right all right let's try combining
them too
[Music]
combination where do we go with
this I don't even know if it's because I
started so early after the middle
because like I did that before and I was
rated
60 but okay one more time
[Music]
time my waist are kind of weak right now
I can do it
[Music]
better timing timing was so good
whatever I Tred my best it's a cute
bird oh another bird didn't we already
do it we already did it
but this one does sound a little bit
different oh [\h__\h] the timing was
good I w't do it better than that that
was my best timing for cooku ever whoa
whoa whoa whoa
[Music]
maybe
shorter oh that so
good now that was better than
that it's a little bit high in the
middle I just noticed
[Music]
no no no no I don't accept
it I know it's very similar what I'm
doing but yeah I I
know [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I I I can't get so loud
at the
[Music]
end dad that's it that's it that's got
to be
[Music]
it that was
beautiful robot fight
really that that could be anything but a
robot fight that sounds like everything
besides a robot
fight n no
idea the graph is pretty similar I'm
losing my inspiration now though feel
like
[Music]
chill I'll take it I'll take
it my
b h
[Music]
easy but it doesn't even do much of a CA
it's more like a
Wawa what the timing is so good look at
the
[Music]
grass kind of goated
what what do you mean
what look where it starts like it's on
point what's their problem
[Music]
nand actually sounds more like a duck to
me than a crow right
now I mean the original sound what
that's [\h__\h] this is this one's
rigged this one's 100% red I I've done
perfectly but doesn't it sound like a
duck
[Music]
sh okay judgment has come upon us it is
not a shba shba it is a crow we have to
accept it I was wrong I'm sorry I was
wrong sorry for thinking you were a duck
it was a crow I
agree the zero tells me everything I
need to
know that sounded a little bit like a
like a Homer Simpson
D all right for first
try bi is that you
[Music]
okay I'm on a roll right now let's
continue the roll oh
Sparrow this this uh game is very bird
focused
huh
okay you're going to rip me off
again they're going to rip me off
[Music]
the last one was a little bit off but
look how difficult that would be to get
but the first ones were absolutely
insanely
good I feel like a started too late
no
she I might not not be a good Rhythm
gamer but my rhythm for imitations is on
point what the [\h__\h] that hurts just
listening to
that who the [\h__\h] wants to hear that
so
loud I don't like
it here try to be
loud ah very very off very off how can
you not give me a zero for that
[Music]
N I don't want to do that
again elephant I am elephant I've done
that
[Music]
before but nor I would do
yeah yeah that's what I'm talking
about that's what I'm talking about I
know I'm good
[Music]
okay I'm chainsaw
incoming oh
[Applause]
wow
67 have you ever seen a graph like that
before holy [\h__\h] one more time
maybe oh that was good that was good can
we top a
67 oh [\h__\h] so good s yeah 67 turn it
around make it a 76 even though I
started out a little bit too
loud
yeah me a beautiful star don't me a
beautiful star why are you singing
that yay
76 next
[Music]
I'm guessing that's a
bird um
what I just
screaming oh
God oh God
[Music]
[Applause]
all right I might be a Tom
be it's an
[Music]
eagle
wow yeah I deserve more than that I
think that was pretty good by the way it
seems like they cut off the grab for the
sounds that are too long cuz I do think
it it was trying to count the whole
thing but it cuts off a bit too early
there but I'm sure counting the whole
thing not bad not bad maybe one more
time although 62 is already pretty
[Music]
nice that was kind of worse but I was
trying to get higher
[Music]
yeah okay maybe I'll try one more
time now my break in between was too
short now
probably too
bad oh
Maybe not maybe it was
okay
okay nice
one
um
H interesting
bit too
slow
what
andore I'm a
door I'm a
Dumbledore
W
whoo I did not expect to be so good at
being a door
I guess I'm changing my
occupation
who
Andor thank you
adorable thank you oh my god
adorable nice
pun I hate that that I really hate that
that's like the typical Japanese modern
apartment chime for when when you're
getting post office
mailman coming by or anything really but
I don't like
[Music]
it yeah could have could be 71
to
what M door and M door
chime both I'm a full
set I come with uh
extras buy door get door Chim for free
what a deal
I'm the whole
system I'm probably the key too the key
to your
door
n insane I'm the whole package I'm the
whole
[Music]
house I've never done an igon before huh
cute I love
[Music]
pigeons what would I need to improve
on I
[Music]
wonder no wait that was so wrong I
started too late as
well oh
[Music]
what I'm
pigon and perfect pigeon oh my God no
more Phoenix and pigeon forever don't
call me chicken at least call me pigeon
if you're not going to call me Phoenix
then call me pigeon cuz obviously I am a
pigeon hold holy
[\h__\h] wa bird perm saved yeah I wasn't
doing so bad on the other birds
either some birds in there were
crazy uh I don't know how any more to do
like I could do this forever but I don't
want to I want to give myself some time
to read super chats too okay another
one
[Music]
huh m
something was
tumbling
[Music]
what what the [\h__\h] is going on what the
[\h__\h] is going on that's four times in a
row that is I mean the previous one was
not quite first try but almost it was
second try but it was almost four times
in a row first try
with three of them first try and one of
them second
try hello
hello oh
[\h__\h] I'm so many
things
unbelievable the wow wait the wow emote
that we have is exactly what the parent
does when I get 100 I just realized
that's so cute the game gave up and the
game wants to be left alone
no wait wait let me redo CL
no um
wait maybe too quiet on the last
one and too late ah wait wait wa
[Music]
wa cl
cl cl oh what
but no like how's another
100 how is that not
[\h__\h] they could have continued my
amazing
run my streak is
ruin
whatever oh
oh okay I'm going to have fun with that
one
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
okay was that too many times I didn't
count
[Music]
that was funny let's
count oh [\h__\h] ah I skipped it okay oh
cute we got a che
a was it spot on the
ending I think it was overall pretty
good especially for first
try a baby
a got sad at the
end oh [\h__\h] I skipped again sorry I'm so
dumb um but this one's fun
[Music]
the [\h__\h] was that sound in the bag
65 oh
okay I was waiting for a
Dipper that's so fast he how what there
should be 100 honestly
[Music]
get out of
[Applause]
here
okay
chaos CL
oh way too
[Music]
long a
strike come on come on come on
come
no okay okay okay
[Music]
how about that beam
Cannon going to destroy Earth with that
one Earth is getting [\h__\h] destroyed
we are no [\h__\h] more let's go to the
Moon right
now or it's so over for Humanity
is so over W beam strong as
hell dangerous very very
dangerous was fun riper goodbye byebye
bye bye my beam is coming for
y look at him going wow wow wow wow just
like you guys in the
chat why am I a dog this whole time
anyway I don't like that what the hell
anyway I want to look at the I want to
look at how many we've done so
far let me see let me see see you next
indeed so deep so
true
waa wait how many is in one row is it 10
one 2 three four five oh wait I could
uhuh oh wait uh 24 48
72 oh
we've done 76
things we
could I
mean
halfway no not really
halfway uh 110 more until uh
fully getting there what there's so many
Birds Ed penguin melanic penguin and
Emperor Peng three different [\h__\h]
penglin Mony oh I got to do these two
come on come on gorilla and
monkey I already know how it's going to
go
oh wow it's so
deep that's very different from what I
imagined
[Music]
sorry what what what
what zero
didn't deserve a zero for
that what but now it's broken come on
why am I getting
zero way too long I'm sorry okay
what wait wait what come on
what is it broken right now must be
broken that's not the kind of monkey
that I know that's not a monkey I've
never heard a monkey like
that but okay I'll try
50 yeah I mean judging by the graph that
really was just 50% of it
[Applause]
[Music]
apparently 5 went up by one
H not hold the
monkeys I guess the Monkey Business this
is not my kind of business I should go
back to the bird
business is it because they're Japanese
[Music]
monkeys he how can they be so
different what kind of monkey are we
talking
about H know what gorilla I mean gorilla
is just gorilla the the other monkey
okay the other monkey could be a million
kind of monkeys it could be like I don't
know tiny monkey or monkey with the the
like weird
butt or it could be P Senai
monkey who knows who knows where they
got it
from cat intimidation which is probably
and then okay we got to do the cat ones
and maybe we'll end it with the cat ones
those I got a nail we know I've become a
cat
practically even though I look like a
dog right
now my cats literally never I don't
think they ever made this sound before
no maybe maybe when they were stepped
on but a little bit more
dramatic oh [\h__\h] I was way too late
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry they were
more
[Music]
[Applause]
like
Oh I thought that would be worse I mean
for a dog imitating a cat that's pretty
good now let's do cute cat
okay
cute I'm so
cute go
[Music]
go how is mine so different on the graph
sound too
long okay okay okay
[Music]
okay cat maxing
again what it l
[Music]
okay
yeah I I tried to feel that
sound in my soul and recreated in my
soul we cat maxing
yeah okay okay okay I
think that was satisfactory
yipp yipp yipp we've done so
many oh
maybe in a year or so maybe I'll do the
rest but not so
close after this could be a let's try it
again in a year kind of game cat
confirmed no door confirmed pigeon
confirmed door time confir many things
confirmed actually I'm very proud of my
achievement
today I I'm pretty proud honestly like
wow that was that was quite the skill
how have I done how have I fared um
compared to other members who played
this game I F I saw some funny clips so
far funny sounds being made but overall
I
wonder did I get many 100s or close to
100s
you did good Jetta got 100 for cat
impression ah
sasuga I guess I'm not quite a cat yet
need to cat Max some more Japanese
clapboard confirmed what what was that
again I don't even remember
anymore yeah I mean yeah in the end it's
pretty random although actually I
thought it would be way more random this
game I honestly thought it would be
like
more unpredictable and
unachievable there were there was some
kind
of
proper programming and system and
recognition behind it I expected more
animals no I honestly did not because I
already saw some clips where I was like
oh I
see you you're trolling us like how the
[\h__\h] would we recreate those kind of
sounds but some birds are really
difficult to recreate
too so sometimes maybe non-animals are
easier than
Animals still pretty impressive for $5
for SC yeah actually I agree for $5 this
is kind of a crazy good party
game with your friends or so when they
come over especially when you're drunk
or so I don't
know okay now let's mute this and let's
close it and let's read Super Chat let's
let's I know I'm really far behind so
let's read some super chats shall
we give show I had a good time though
with a with a nice little oneoff fun
game you welcome to stay for some uh
Chit Chat super chats um I'm going to
stay here
maybe cuz it's kind of rare to be here
and my outfit color-wise matches this
background so well doesn't it it totally
does okay let's get a I don't know oh
that's maybe that's not change that
[Music]
one yeah Super Chat rating here we go
here we go I can put the thumnail there
too I'm hungry though I have a banana
right here can I eat the banana I had
the banana here thinking uh might need
it oh but [\h__\h] it's always
like I kind of
unlearned forgot how to [\h__\h] open a
banana without like using a knife or so
like I can't I can't twist it properly
anymore and then I just smush it and
then it just gets worse and I can't fix
it anymore once I like [\h__\h] it up once
here let's try with the pen here got
like a little bit of a scr
scrotch in the
banana how about that [\h__\h] I didn't do
it it's just going to make it
worse whoa
okay
destruction [\h__\h] I can't
te trying to peel a banana yeah from the
bottom I've never tried opening a banana
from the bottom before I don't even know
how you would do
that my fingernails oh I don't really
want to use my fingernails usually for
that kind of
stuff but I'm okay I'm
trying squeeze yeah squeeze and then
what pinch and pull
what I don't know what the hell you're
talking
about I'm squeezing it
but anyway and then I'm going to do I'm
still going to go over the
top wait wait maybe
maybe oh there we go yeah I think you
even heard
that banana a some
more okay B let me find some
bgm no
[Music]
no
no that works for
know while I'm eating a
[Music]
banana 100 points
this is so Luigi's
Mansion you want to recreate sounds you
should get the game it's just five bucks
on switch
[Music]
it's pretty quiet for you guys going
make it
[Music]
louder how much for the ah right you
need a ah you need a Nintendo microphone
but it doesn't have to be a Nintendo
microphone this wasn't like sold by
nintend like not the brand wasn't
Nintendo but it was
definitely like listed as compatible
with PlayStation and
Nintendo it's just like one of those
singar microphones
[Music]
whatever I think there 20 bucks which is
kind of expensive for the kind of one
time only
use m
could give it
back no I tried I tried plugg cuz it
says in the game try plugging in the USB
microphone and I tried and it's like if
it doesn't work if you stop hearing the
in-game music the moment you plug in the
USB microphone then your microphone is
not compatible with it and yeah that's
exactly what mine did I was like okay
guess this doesn't work got to get a
specific
one this what it is no no it's not any
any USB
M but if you have one at home try it
with that one
first how do you know it's compatible
only by
trying unfortunately
[Music]
no that sucks a little bit like if you
have to go out of your way to buy one
then you should just go and buy the like
the one that says it will be compatible
with Nintendo switch
games even though you're used for it
will be very
small but you can give back maybe after
you're done using it I don't
know yeah usually like this one it was
in the in the game section
I just bought an IRL today cuz I thought
oh I have a USB microphone I'll be fine
and then I tested it today and it was
blah so had to go out and buy it but
that's
okay but it was like in the Nintendo
switch
accessories section I think more or
[Music]
less okay so guys let's read some Super
Chat shall
[Music]
what day is it is it Friday it's Friday
Friday oh yeah it is Friday we're
already getting to the weekend next
weekend next week is
Halloween this week is already almost
over tomorrow is Zelda right and then
Sunday what what what am I doing on
Sunday our members only okay I'm excited
for Zella tomorrow I I think we can
finish
it pretty sure we can finish it I did a
little bit of extra gaming off screen I
did like maybe one or two or three more
small side quests maybe just two I don't
remember
anymore didn't do anything
big um but yeah I looked around for more
of those blue
stones so that I can exchange I did
exchange I upgraded one of the things I
think the
sword I I upgraded two things The Sword
and the bombs sword was like
the second n third upgrade bombs were I
think first
upgrade so the bow and the sword maxed
out now I think but the bombs can still
get upgraded but yeah I ran around
everywhere ah yeah right I did I did um
I did the Great Fairy side quest where
you got to go to two cities and get her
some fancy necklace made with like
seashell and some Goron Stone whatever
and if you do that you get a neck or no
some accessory that makes pal palim
sounds whenever you are close to a blue
stone one of those energy
Stones yeah the sensor so I have that
now that's one of the quests I did which
was like a several steps Quest mhm and
then I went around the whole map trying
to find uh more of those
stones didn't want to get spoiler no
what what do you mean have to I'm done
talking about it anyway I just there's
no spoiler that wasn't really any
spoiler
there
oh yeah and then I paid for the last
accessory slot and I think I got another
accessory through another side quest
maybe don't remember
anymore but yeah you'll see I guess what
my progress is let's play
tomorrow okay now uh does somebody want
to tell me
where do I that was a crack where do I
continue reading Super
[Music]
Chat thank you oh the first oh
really I feel like didn't I read ah I I
wanted to and I put it up on the screen
and then I tangent it about cats and was
like I'm out of
here I remember now
Zelda post game marks heart pieces and
blue
stones oh oh but I never play post game
I don't like playing post games it's
like too late too late you're offering
me these benefits now it's too late you
should have tried harder before it was
over our relationship you and me Zelda
we had something but you wasted it you
freaking wasted
[Music]
it uh okay
thumnail my that's like something's
wrong with my neck and I keep on saying
I should go get a massage but I
continuously don't do
it which is interesting cuz normally I
used to get so many massages now I don't
my last massage was in Japan and I
really need
one next week next week for sure for
sure but I'm also in November going to
you
know Spa Little Spa vacation so I'm GNA
spend a lot of money on special massages
there they are going to cost way more
just because they are in a special fancy
place no so maybe maybe I should no but
I don't want to wait that
long yeah I'll still get one I've waited
so long but I'm going to get so many
massages there too one per
day I'm
excited yeah oh by the way you know how
I told you
there's this like
Place special place I guess there's a
special place I want to take the
mysterious visitors
to um special special
restaurant now turns
out during the time of the special
visitors it's
closed
so I found something else that's
interesting interesting but it's not as
interesting it would have been so good
it would would have been so perfect I'm
so
[Music]
disappointed and I'm like for the
longest time I was wondering oh I want
to go to this place but I don't know who
to go with I was always looking for
someone to go to it with and those
visitors would have been
great great people to go with h oh well
oh well booked him the next
flight no this is probably a onetime
[Music]
thing also they
they never mind I'm not going to say
anything I'm going to read super chats
now whether you like it or
not here I go Jacob 47 d py D zip d d d
Shan
D thank you thank you no but you're so
good at this so cute it looks so
official so
adorable it's really nice to have like
my own version of these
[Music]
covers Psy D and Steven Miller honu Ry d
beas
d just not this game has some hilarious
cheese skips you can do once you get
some
items ah Wonder are you probably mean
not not so much like huge skips but just
the for example the the flying uh floor
plate stuff like that that's really
helpful sers D chocolate Insomniac dun
candy stamps D
[Music]
Mountain Master Nate
you Extinction it's hip to wear soap to
wear
soap why would you wear soap how are you
wearing
soap kiik Jackson FB Mr Game Boy thank
you uh happy belated birthday
also hey Waba do you think you'll play
that voice mimicry game I feel like that
would be a fun pick for
you it was destined this is why I
haven't been reading super chats because
I needed to time this particular Super
Chat to this stream that's why I've been
slow on reading super
chats all according to
Kaku sorry this one Super Chat delayed
everything thing mhm and then me
delaying the voice mimicry game also
delayed it otherwise I would have read
this super chat last
week Emily Sky El hey
yo you changed your name just for the
stream
huh D tendo's number one fan I see how
it
is I do not actually believe it I
actually really don't believe it because
you don't even speak
German
so how do you say that's a hard Buy Hard
Sell A Hard Sell I'm not buying it
ger D Rick Raptor D snake thanks for the
pinky always happy when I can catch a wa
stream wait your snake picture is the
snake from the
game cute
but it wasn't
always what was your picture
before it's 300 a.m. and Aussie haha and
work makes it hard to do so a lot of
time but it always brings a smile to my
face seeing you enjoying yourself and
carefully supporting you thank you I'm
sorry I I stream it's a shitty time for
you
guys I mean at least it starts at a time
that would
be okay and then it goes into let's go
to sleep territory I wish I could stream
more for my
Australian buddies I love Australian kfp
you guys are so
nice you guys are just so lovely and so
charming and I love your
[Music]
accent
a one what Australian kfp really like I
think everybody can like you know you
don't have to force yourself to watch
everything live watching bods is fine
but I understand you want to watch live
but the ones who commit to watching live
and live in those kind of countries with
those time zones Mama M Mia I'm sorry
for ruining your
life thank you for your
dedication thank you
snake see I'm snake
but that's B I
guess
[Music]
no that's more snaky oh
yeah
H dark King D supreme leader Beetle D
fur D Cruise Dan slide Sasquatch
d a Joby or
ad if you don't mind me asking how often
do you go to France if you don't want to
say just say what you had for breakfast
instead wait did I answer this in during
the stream it almost feels familiar now
um yeah I don't care at all saying it uh
I did huh a few times maybe three
times unknown thanks for the pinky hey
boss I have bad news ah get out of here
I read this too didn't I and I was yeah
I
was you you scared me and now you scared
me
[Music]
again didn't I send you to the usual
room for that for the first time ever
cuz I'm thinking of sending you
again just now in my head I was like oh
you got to go to the usual room but then
I thought wait didn't I already send
you I
didn't are you sure well then now is the
time double scare not acceptable usual
room possibly for your first time
ever 3 weeks pretty long but I'm sure
you'll enjoy your time
there okay okay I'll make it two
weeks it's October please forgive no but
this was sent in
September doesn't count at all m- that's
not an excuse
mm- it's a cute super chat but you made
me worry about
you that's not not
okay you have D Rama B thanks for the
red super chat it's okay while we're
letting it out is better than saving it
don't be
sorry oh what was what what did I let
out hopefully no
farts that was a monkey
[Music]
thank you very much RAM
B and
[Music]
monkey do you like my monkey noises the
ones in the game were kind of ridiculous
they didn't really let my full potential
out they didn't let me shine like the
monkey that I
am fock d
all the all the
complaints death
re
what
what uh wow nice good job tempat
D all
right
um that one's finished let's go to Team
Fortress 2 which was one of those games
you guys were like what I can't believe
she's playing this
game but I really just played it for Amy
so this one I really wouldn't have
played for any other reason
ever but it was all right simply D Jacob
47 D Bill Wilson D branded clown D thank
you
be steel Moon dun thank you space
waterful dun somebody somebody wants
D sir F the third dun I like your name
and your profile picture super biley
danash Unity chat dun Cruz dun lemon a
Dun is that picture a character from the
game I feel like it is Sado 94 dun
V
Mish t tempor the steel dun cup of tea
dun it's hip to wear soap oh you again
dun Matt thanks for the pinky mat here's
a tip K right click with the flame
thrower flamethrower to Air Blast you
can reflect rockets and projectiles back
at the enemy and push them back yeah I
don't know if it was through your super
chat but I did I was aware of that I
just um I think I used it more later on
but then people were telling me to to
not do it or do it less in the chat
confusing Vibes first people tell me to
use it and then they tell me to not use
it I don't
know use it too much you guys never can
make up your mind
uh oh cuz I kept pushing them out of my
range oh oh well
well it was my first time playing it's
hard to get the balance okay
R so free thanks for the pinky as well
vo I hate engineer meanwhile me a
mechanical engineer by trade well that's
completely
[Music]
different the engineer in the shooting
pew pew pew game is very different from
a legitimate proper engineer like you
who can actually do
things you deserve respect H so don't
worry I I respect you and I like you and
your job I guess I mean I'm not 100%
sure what you do what a mechanical
engineer by trade
does but I'm sure it's something
cool that I wouldn't hate on as long as
you're not a carpenter pretending to
make floors or like wood stuff obviously
that's just you
laring carpets obviously make carpets so
I'm sick of all the coke
that I'm hearing but yeah engineer
totally
fine okay random colos thanks for the
red super chat Air Blast is really
versatile first you can reflect enemy
projectiles or even push people off
cliffs like enemy spies and Uber charged
Medics like haha ruined your back step
assault push it's like you're enjoying a
physics Buffet don't you want to spam
air BL yeah well I think I
definitely I guess spammed it so I I I
followed you inspired me random
collusion thank you but then people got
mad at me random collusion explain to
me chocolate Andia D dead protector D
for the red chat thank you K as a 10,000
hour TF2 player I have never been so
excited to watch this game damn Dam you
must have been so frustrated if you if
you play a game for that
long then you are so good in that
game I see how it can always be fun to
see other people play the game that you
love for the first time but that must be
more refresh uh frustrating I think than
refreshing actually you were good well
when I was changing the class run I
didn't want to go with that class the
the da da da um I I wanted to do
something more interesting you know cuz
like I felt like that was just like such
an Easy
Choice the heavy yeah was e too easy and
boring I wanted to do something more
interesting and I thought okay I I
trained all this time with the with the
flame guy I should commit to it but then
it was it was way better and more useful
when I played against those CPUs
and then against the girls it was
suddenly so useless and I was like what
the
[\h__\h] I should still commit to it
because I should I should commit to
it but yeah that was
um lame it was more fun when I was able
to do some damage for
sure and didn't die all the
time like literally oh my
god oh
I was stubborn yeah because I didn't
even know we were already in the middle
of the collab I feel like if I did it
before okay I should have I should have
tried out more stuff before but before
it was going so well that I saw no
reason to switch and then during the
collab it was like N I don't really have
time to look at everything now so if I
switch then I won't know what I'm doing
but then eventually yeah I just switched
around and tried to wing it
yeah um and when I saw how like several
people were already playing that heavy
and were basically Invincible I was
like maybe I should play
that can only counter with more of those
heavy da guys right that's the
solution but apparently that was a real
strategy
yeah you say I was good at it but that
just seems like a really easy
class really no skill
[Music]
necessary not really I don't
know aiming is a
skill yeah I mean I will say I think I
aimed pretty well but with heavy when I
was playing heavy I wasn't moving around
much because I felt like a tank
so aiming was easier because there
wasn't as much movement on the field
both from me and from the opponents cuz
they were also Heavies a lot of
them right so that automatically makes
it
easier heav was my main with
medic as say weakness you can barely
move while shooting so you're sitting
duck yeah that's true too mhm anyway
thank you dead protector dingan d d m
creeper D anime life d life than ma
thanks for the pinky hi T since the
collab hasn't started yet there's a
unique opportunity to tell you that as
of right now only you am and P have
stream TF2 oh quite a coincidence oh and
I had an Insane luck of pulling your
sign whole life ocg card oh thank you
congratulations P Senpai really over
time over her over time has picked up a
lot of surprising interesting games huh
like I would not have expected her to
have had played T of two that's that
feels so
Random is it popular in
Japan M Dr helas Dan Daniel dun thank
you so much Koopa 215
Dunes make fall out dun super bear hero
thank you space wonderful thanks for the
red super chat
uh she fell down the Dragon Ball RAB
what's what's what's
the what's the connection there Dragon
Ball and TF2 huh thank you so much for
playing my favorite multiplayer game wa
ah yeah you were really excited I'm so
happy you had fun it means so much to me
that you enjoyed it you played so well
for your first time and not being an FPS
person hope you'll play it again maybe
with us too I don't know I I know I'm
I'm already like mentally that that
chapter is mentally closed already in my
brain also because I don't know I didn't
even figure out how to play with you
guys did I cuz I didn't even figure out
how to play with herb did
I or
did cuz I think what was it you guys
were like oh no don't don't server IP
blah blah blah everybody was so worried
about
it everybody was getting so dramatic
like no don't
don't he
dangerous yeah we
[Music]
didn't it would just be picking up a
server host as long as you don't s host
that's what I
thought unknown you were so worried you
were like
no you were like you were like doubl
door calmly telling me to not use the
server unknown calmly told kiar to not
use the
server to not play
online
[Music]
[Laughter]
calmly don't play
online calmly
[Music]
I knew it I knew that as long as I
didn't host the server or so or no as
long as I did host the server whatever
doesn't matter anymore thank you space
waterfall Cruz g j SW D thank you did
you put your IP in the Goble of
nah I didn't if I did that and that's
the cause of why my ISP why my internet
is [\h__\h] well then I would know the
solution just take it out but I don't
know the solution and I don't know the
cause it's frustrating isn't
[Music]
it
next I have like some
um I don't know I don't know what it is
um
some a a tiny bit of
my
um s
flash is
either inflamed or something
[Music]
else my gums
felt it like starting yesterday and
today yeah it's like it it feels
weird I don't know it's like deep deep
in my last tooth at the very back like
above my La last most fous back
tooth maybe it will go away on its own
but I was kind of uh thinking of going
to the dentist soon
anyway it's been a while
while don't want to
[Music]
go sorry weird sound I was trying to
make
the um Star Wars thing sound cuz I just
sounded like that to
myself
no you know what I mean yeah chewbaca
[Music]
no
no oh yeah I think that's kind of going
into that
direction 12 100 hey give me 100 at
least a 69 come
on have to gargle
how can
I how can I do both at the same
time I don't know it's impossible
difficult Jack 47
d Road
toer your name is so cool have I told
you that before thank you for the red of
chat kikiki your hair is so pretty as
night Jo but when Ki am Zelda dot do Dot
it what do you mean well I'm glad to
catch you to power up before I got a run
fantasy tabletop RPG's in a few hours oh
wow we have a
uh what do you call it again something
something Master something Master
dungeon dungeon
master a Mose is there wa NBC somewhere
yes
what is there you made a wa
NPC do your friends know that this is
not just some random NPC you fought of
but it's actually inspired by a YouTuber
that you
like tell me more about vaa
MPC tell me
more I need to know more you not you
don't seem to be here right now but tell
me when you can if you hear this reply
to your super chat a month
later let me know stupid booty D
Jus teny D SWAT thanks for the pinky
ah so I think I I read this one before
or or was on a different occasion when
you talked about your wedding again I'm
not
sure hey boss good news it's my wedding
next week we've had so much fun
traveling for ctw cons and meeting
amazing kfp thanks to you
a going to our events and concerts
together with your fiance that sounds
cute in the evening we'll even be
playing Chima and some Holo songs wish
me luck oh yeah at the wedding you mean
wish me luck and keep an eye out for Su
photo wait did I see it where is the
sumon photo tag me tag me I may have
seen it already but tag me
again upload it again or re re quote it
you haven't gotten them yet okay I will
be awaiting them eagerly that reminds me
of something
[Music]
tippity tappity
okay should be 4 weeks 4 weeks from now
wow they take a long time huh wedding
pictures ended up going for Sparks in
the evening with the DJ saying that
saying and that was tank oh no Tang
cashi Castle did he think it was
um T what what Castle Takashi he he
makes it up with Takashi Castle or
so oh my God oh my God that's not even
so far off it sounds kind of like
similar no more tanak kakaria I am
Taki's Castle
now oh how did we never think of this
before H that's pretty butchered
yeah seems like your DJ was more of a
butcherer in his previous
life but that's funny
[Music]
Galaxy
uh wait was
it at the endin
is this person here in the chat by any
chance Jin yes are you reading with me
thank
you thank you
okay thank you for the red super chat
[Music]
thanks for the pinky you wouldn't last a
day without chat bet
me I mean what of course I would on my
off days I'm lasting a day without you
guys what do you mean
I've lasted plenty of times without you
guys you wouldn't last without chat you
yeah I once survived the whole month
mhm true you guys are trying to
completely delete that memory from
history so that you can make this claim
Nathan right no no no no no
no I did have the urch gorilla recently
yeah but then the same time I also have
the
self-control to not do
[Music]
it s you read comments but that's not
chat but yeah I'm definitely
like looking too much at but but too you
I I would say too much but then again
it's my job so I wouldn't say it's
really too much so yeah
watch don't tend why do you caps lock
the first three letters you don't even
what are you trying to you trying to
what that's not what what are you doing
that why are you doing
that you don't need to do
[Music]
that I don't know yeah you don't know
German so stop
watching his videos or being in his
[Music]
Discord by the way um I know you don't
really care guys but I I I I noticed
something funny so the other day when we
had the Mario Party collab uh was it
narissa who got two stars in one game
out of those secret blocks that's really
like what the [\h__\h] and now I'm even more
what the [\h__\h] because at that point I
already watched a few of his
uh Mario Party
videos and now there's even more out
like he's uploading free per day he's
going through every
single
um map and they have had him and he's
playing it together with his wife and
they have seen and uncovered like 13 14
15 secret blocks so far and they're like
what the [\h__\h] is there ever a star in it
because every single time it was
coins
so I'm like how did n like it
what it's funny how upset you got a g i
i I hope you don't really think I got
upset at
geeky obviously it was jokes me
saying I will un orange I mean that's so
unserious how how could you you didn't
take that seriously did
you an orange is your
[Laughter]
ory I love love
her there is there is literally nothing
that could make me not love
her also
[Music]
maybe uh in the past in other games or
so maybe there has been times where I've
experienced saltiness but let me tell
you I was not salty in that collab at
all maybe that one time when I lost like
one or two stars like was was denied the
opportunity to get one I wasn't salty I
was just like I don't know uh dramatic
for the sake of the entertainment of the
stream yeah but I wasn't like angry or
mad or
anything I don't know people trying to
paint me as the saltiest [\h__\h] ever but
some people also don't understand like
like
[Music]
banter yeah especially in Mario Party
also Mario Party is the
saltiest like Nintendo game ever it's
literally meant to induce salt and
that's the funny thing Mario Party is
meant to destroy
friendships
so yeah that's what you should expect
when you watch and play
party I would be
disappointed if there wasn't like big
drama about oh my God how dare you steal
my star no I can't believe you stole my
star you suck I hate you yeah it has to
be like
that yeah we need more of that
drama and there was a lot of back and
forth of like stars being stolen or
denied and so on in especially in that
second Mario Party stream which was good
was a good
[Music]
thing
yeah I was thinking if orange fails
again we'll do another one of these but
orange won so I think it's a a good
opportunity
to leave it at that not saying I will
never play Mario party again but it's
not like I'm doing another Mario Party
stream next week just
saying the Monopoly of video games so
many destroy when you say that when
Monopoly is also a video game
though
H but uh we talked a little bit about
Monopoly before the stream I think and I
think both crony and Nissa were like we
hate Monopoly and I'm like
why monop
fun I
mean it's
always kind of messed
up like I
don't I don't know something keeps on
calling me back to
Monopoly even though it always makes me
suffer yeah but something about
it I think I think it's
some I think it's kind of the role play
behind it cuz when you are young and you
like play with Barbies and dollhouse and
stuff like that and like baby dolls and
[\h__\h] like that now Monopoly is kind of
like
pretending to be an adult who invests
in uh houses and
stuff and that's just fun feels so
adult you know yeah and having like this
fake
money it is kind
of it it really kind of I think
subconsciously gives you this roleplay
feeling oh it's just me
maybe perhaps could
be where was
I and AC Z and thank you D oh already
free streams cleared guys
wow okay next is Deep Rock Galactic
wow this one yo this I I'm really proud
of this thumbnail because I was trying
to look for fan art of all four of us
that kind of matches like so from the
same artist but it was was hard to
find um because like okay nobody has
ever drawn this group together in one
picture before like just these four so I
would have to separately somehow find
like if I had the knowledge that there's
this one artist who draws all of us
there's a few artists who draw all of us
but then yeah I don't know I only could
think of a few uh and then yeah this
artist though changes their style a lot
but I find found this like recent style
of them uh in a few pieces of Art and it
just so happened to match quite well but
I think I
[Music]
think I think yeah uh some of these are
from the same illustration and some are
not yeah I think me and crony are from
one
illustration and Thena and am maybe from
one one illustration and I had to like
adjust normally I don't want to change
any anything to respect the artist I
don't want to change any like
colors and lights and contrast and so on
but for this one I had to because it was
very different and it wouldn't look like
it was meant to be one group
picture so I had to adjust it a little
bit but it turned out so nice I really
like this edgy
style edgy fun chibi style very
original I think it was very
[Music]
eye-catching
yeah did anyone draw you guys together
after this
collab
maybe but like nothing too intricate I
think reminds me of panty stocking yes
yes yes yes yes
I get
it okay let's go Che 47 naction
[Music]
W Ric dwarf thank you for the r of chat
who just first un store
it's rock and stone got to be English
here what first and store first and
first store first I don't know what you
mean I don't remember anybody saying
that thank you though for the Super Chat
first the the the generous donation
um very much
appreciated rocking
[Music]
Stone um
thank you
Unwritten thank you again D wave Chan
dun Sky dun py dun earlier sphere D Cru
D and space wonderful D thank you yeah
four streams out of the way
next would be the unarchived
[Music]
Cara yeah that stream that was really
kind of last minute
cuz I think me GAA and
am uh like we talked about this game at
some point I was like cuz I think they
said they played it before and I was
like oh I kind of want to play it too um
and then there was some kind of Promise
up in the air that we can we'll play it
someday and yeah like the last two weeks
or so suddenly came and it was so out of
nowhere and so fast and am's schedule of
course filled up so fast with so many
collaborations and I kind of saw that
coming U but then it was there and I
felt like ah I don't want to I already
had H talk of her and you know I don't
want
to demand too much of her
time um there was actually even more
that I still wanted to do with her like
when we were in New York we talked about
setting up a Fallout 76
server um for a couple of
us
yeah cuz we were talking talking about
Fallout I was like oh yeah isn't there
Fallout 76 couldn't we play it online
she's like yeah now we need to get a
server I'm like can we make it happen I
feel like there would be a couple girls
who would love
to but there was just not really enough
time and uh yeah we were all
busy during that time
frame there still so many things that I
would have loved to do but squeezing
that one out really was a
miracle cuz I I really already gave up
on it happening and I was like that's
okay it's okay
but somehow it still came together so
I'm glad we got that
last collab with like no tears shed and
no no sad Vibes just pretending like
everything's
normal I am glad uh that I could do that
at the end because I know I know I know
I know
like I really f
um and that was definitely originally
the plan that myth being the last collab
is how it should
be but we did Leave It Off on a
very sad
note maybe mostly because of me I'm
sorry
so I'm glad we could squeeze in
something to lighten the mood a little
bit at the end
H
yeah I swear that ending that was so
difficult I I I really couldn't I'm so
sorry but I could redeem myself a little
bit with the
collab thank you
guys anyway the next one is the uncraft
K where where's the
thumbnail what I must have
like did I ah is it this cuz I I was
it's so far back because
I no wait where's what what
thumbnail where is
it maybe I saved it in different
folder
accidentally oh yeah I
did AR they so
[Music]
pretty so
pretty all right here we go boohoo 72 D
j7 zip D Dr Professor Patrick d y m AR
Filipino to CN o d k d vola d Jackson FB
thanks for the pinky I didn't get to say
it at the time but thank you for the drg
collab I think we all needed that agreed
yeah
um we just talked about it so yeah thank
you thank you and you're
welcome our no forand is d
but why
[Music]
D hi sorry for being rude but I started
watching Halloween since the Halloween
VR collab I really want to know if there
will ever be this kind of collab again I
really want to put this all behind but I
really need to ask you mean um just any
kind of V project thing like the ones
that like I'm mostly used to organize do
you just mean if we'll do we our stuff
again I I think we will not as frequent
anymore but I mean even in the past one
or two years we didn't do it as
frequently
anymore but yeah I think still here and
there but not as often
and maybe not as crazy
ambitious I don't
know people are coping that am will be
involved in those oh it okay okay well
if that's if that is the question from
this person if amble just show up for
random VR collabs I doubt
it
um yeah I mean maybe she'll help with
planning if I would ask her for some
advice or something but will she be part
like a like any other collabing
member I would doubt it
that feels a little bit too much like a
normal
stream yeah I'm sorry but VR things I
don't know what exactly you're asking
but VR streams can still definitely
happen so much
C thank you for watching
snowy oh thanks for the membership mat
look at those
eggs those beautiful
eggs
yeah yeah I got to be a little bit
[Music]
realistic yeah alun has been
really focusing on VR content I find it
quite
interesting
mhm from
ru anyway moving on a smart for the
pinky to quote a show from a long time
ago it's hard to let go so don't not
entirely the memories of the people who
who helped the find you keep a piece of
them with you always and even though
they may be gone you're still here and
that's what
matters what show is
this are you Rick Rolling me it's not a
Rick Roll
right what show is
[Music]
this does anybody know
it's hard to let go so don't not
entirely could this be a
recel
no Shrek too that would also be funny
giving me the most emotional code ever
and then it comes from [\h__\h]
Teletubbies or so
yeah let me Google
it Crime and
Punishment No wait not necessarily is it
no that's what that's just a
random they just used some of the words
of what I typed in there I don't know
yeah I guess the OG super chatter would
have to tell us who knows if we will
ever be told but yeah good words good
words so 94
dun 117 dun just another sushii D gr J D
hunky
dunk thank you for the red super chat
today and on that day you melt my heart
y
no
you reverse
card she's so
sweet
wow definitely not watching anymore but
she's so
[Music]
sweet I want to meet her
again youf moreia
how
sight of
fancy Ron thank
you
vagon
K
Cesar
anime
vam s thanks for the red super chat K we
are with you for am farewell it's hard
to say goodbye but no that you're not
alone and everything will be okay you
brought so much sure and will continue
to support you stay strong and remember
we're here for you you're amazing thank
you I don't want to go too deep into
this because it's been a while already
and uh we don't need to go into that
again but thank you very much sh D Cruz
d v thanks for the pinky thank you so
much for asro girl I love that
song I just love it so much but it
definitely hits harder the more time
passes
somehow good song What A Bop Jackson FB
D Elie la maros sen dakor D she the ging
of the red Not Alone the universe the
universe is found
now I love the lyrics and the
instrumental ah so good
ah so [\h__\h]
good thank you
[Music]
Jesus s dun system c d site sapling D
wave Jam D signal x d El La d nkb
d and Dusty thanks the pinky I thought I
cried enough yesterday guess not you
trained my eyes dry I love your voice so
much a thank
you you're so nice and I'm so sorry but
I I thought you know
like especially
because like even though okay I cried at
the last collab stream and and all that
maybe some people were able to cry there
I feel
like there um cuz of how Amit is there
was like maybe in her last stream there
wasn't so much
M like how to
say tear
inducing moments which is not a bad
thing at all she wanted it to be more
like of a happy Vibe thing but I I
thought surely there's like some fans
who are really sad and maybe they need
something to give them the push to let
out the emotions and that's why I wanted
to do that
k h
yeah and also
because I I wanted to do a stream but I
wanted to do one one that
feels respectful like I'm not going to
do like a happy gaming stream right
after or like a happy kok so I felt like
what I could do what the best thing
would be is like giving people a place
to Just Vibe sadly twerk sadly
and um also pay my respects so to
say yeah sad
twerks
literally tearful
yay shakes booty while
crying Tassimo than the pinky am it
brought me into myth in the beginning
through her I developed my passion for
whole life and kfp so it feels really
strange and sad to see her gone but I'll
keep going for it like always stay
strong W and thank you for being here
thank you I wonder what stream brought
you in if you say Amma brought you in or
I guess Clips probably were first the
first sign of life for
you but interesting I didn't know
that thank you Amy for bringing me
Tassimo
yeah D thank you so much for the sweet
words yeah I'm still
[Music]
here there's so many hidden skibbies in
there and you don't even realize it
Teresa Agnes D thank you P gags thank
you for the pinky I joined kfp after
watching you and Amma off collab in Amma
Studios the energy you both had was so
fun and endearing I truly believe Amma
has a special Charisma that brings the
light out of others goodbye for now am
and you'll be missed oh I wonder which
one which stream cuz we did a
couple those will
always stay in my memory and in my heart
those were great memories thank you for
joining kfp through that and supporting
all of us thank
you DX demon d CC D BR I'm Miss say
somewh only REO in her last K oh my God
you mean the members
one celester dun unknown dun thanks for
the pinky I absolutely love the set with
so much your singing is always so
incredibly beautiful you are just best I
love you w thank you I'm glad you
enjoyed the settler enjoyed can you say
enjoyed
or enjoyed enjoys enjoys sadly enjoys
[Music]
depressingly thank you Nathan Clon than
of the pinky Miss Taki we've received
some reports about you causing some
emotional distress to a large quantity
of chimpin I'm going to need you to come
down to the station to answer some more
questions please don't make this harder
on yourself this seems to be like a scam
one of those
scammer males because why the [\h__\h] would
I need to go down to the police
station like what then this just doesn't
seem like a realistic scenario Nathan
again rejecting your super chats
thing that you are doing yeah I
reject not doing so well Nathan these
days I mean those days are a long time
ago but not doing so
[Laughter]
Wellness ex O2 Supply D AK sf2 d d
thanks for the red super
chat decoy John thanks for the pink
thanks T I think we all needed that keep
on keeping on I'm told you forever me
forever thank
you I'm glad you were there thank you
for watching and supporting big an anime
dang Lucas Universe D Mr M dun flyman
dun Jackson FB D fried screw d space
wonderful thanks for the red super chat
I didn't cry at all I wanted to cry
though
see people wanted to cry I'm sad but I
mostly feel empty I cried every day till
her last stream no I thought Astro girl
would break me like usual but no and the
last songs I actually vibed with a smile
like I'm I wanted that's good we're not
alone yeah I I cried a lot during the
practice but then and I think I told you
guys before sometimes even though I'm
like a super emotional person and I
think you know that by me crying a lot
here and there on my streams but then
there's some streams where I'm so like
locked in especially Kadoka streams
where I'm so emotional not emotional but
I'm so tense and
like focused and and and like
nervous that I can't really feel the
emotions of the songs that I'm singing
anymore and then I
disassociate if I would have cried
during that stream I'm sure you would
have cried too space waterful a lot more
people would have probably cried if but
you hear somebody cry it's like a domino
effect kiss me m
Kiss
[Music]
Me Beautiful song yeah well well thank
you space waterful Mr Block adduction
the L Dallas D for the pinky hey number
one
Gosling a selfish request from a
teammate and day one myth fan can you be
sure at least some of the Japanese hem
see the aquarium I need to know they
will see how hard am I worked right up
until the end
doesn't have to be a stream my forever
if five
ever
uh sadly I I don't really think I have
that
much influence over the Japanese members
um but I think some members went yeah
like okay at least alun um went to check
it out and I'm sure the other members
like saw it on like Twitter like some of
them surely saw like screenshots or
uh clips and stuff
definitely
yeah but going into the VR world that's
like a little bit not everybody really
knows that they can go into a real world
with just like under computer without
using a VR
setup yeah Ana and Zetta also went
mhm Al said I'mma was really big
inspiration for her cuz she's so
interested in VR stuff ah
I thought there must be some kind of
senpai respect
there mhm had a
feeling well well thank you anyway deal
Dallas I'm also really uh happy to see
so many fans checking out the world
afterwards I saw a lot of clips of
people of fans hanging out there really
nice really cute wholesome Emily Sky D
your nor clips D Fafa D UF d alv d
Justin lamber passion d space waterful d
GD d c beads D flaming pants d a zombie
d and I'm a t beep
D thank
[Music]
you all right that's like five streams
out of the
way are you happy
CH are you proud
I zoomed through
it pretty
content good junk quite so very
proud no why are you angry called on
them great thank
you that's my
inen more
no I actually I promised chagy to do
some moap to today so I've been charging
my equipment probably going
to we already reached like uh uh I mean
I told you guys you know it will come it
will all come it's just going to be like
a little bit
[Music]
delayed so where are we reached I think
750k but the iris short isn't out yet so
um still working on that please
wait we'll get there and it will it will
be you know it's not like there was that
much time in between it's just going too
fast but the Mone short is only like 2
days ago
so you know
I wanted to give it some time anyway to
you know let it
grow before I slam another one in
[Music]
there a bonus one that's everybody
dancing together no but I I was I am
genuinely open to doing even more
afterwards yeah I'm really happy Mirage
is like growing steadily I haven't even
been like promoting it that much like in
terms of like stream it stream it like
yelling it at people I've just been
uploading the
shorts yeah but I think it's growing
well that's
good stream Mirage faster I mean I'm not
saying you guys should stream it
slower just because I can't keep up just
continue U I will try my best to keep up
my will certainly not catch
up but we'll we'll get
there at least the model for the 3D
stream is ready to go and ready to be
used don't have to wait for that I can
do that one probably on
time and then like some of the shorts
like Coboy and coyote might still be
like
afterwards judging by how slow where
everything is going so far thanks for
the 20
memberships wow thank
you wow right at the
end
[Music]
than
okayy do you think chy will be mad if I
chy are you here chy will not be mad
anyway but I I said I would do it today
and then I was like two hours chatting
with
[\h__\h] IP I did not expect for that to
go on for so
long you promised didn't you yeah I did
but CH is already sleeping anyway I
think or maybe not sleeping but it's not
like chy has time to work on it anymore
today
yeah he'll
understand tomorrow tomorrow before
before my Zelda stream
right and now I have to make a thumbnail
and then I have to cook at the
food I think I'm just going to make some
pasta I made a lot of chili
con
uh the other day and I froze like three
portions
I already unfroze one yesterday but
turns out that Those portions are
basically two portions so it's basically
like six portions that I froze or maybe
like
five
yeah but I'm kind of feeling Basta today
so I think the
unfrozen chili that I now put into the
fridge could eat it
tomorrow or could eat it today then I
don't have to cook yeah yeah chili con
car is so
easy yeah I made it like accidentally
lowkey spicy I didn't even throw in any
chili but I think it comes from the what
was it that one spice the one orange
looking
spice what was it is it even the same
name in English I'm not sure not pop
papra not
kuruma cayenne pepper Cayenne Chen cayen
in German we say Cayenne I think do we
Chen Cayenne I would say cayen
probably but yeah I put a lot of that in
there I think it made it a little little
bit spicy but not really as long as I
can eat it you could guess it's not
spicy yeah I like beans today I
something in my algorithm showed up and
I was
like why is this so popular maybe you
you guys always get the same things on
your algorithm so maybe you saw it too
was like a video of some food truck in I
think
England yeah the potato The Baked Oven
potatoes they bake it in foil and then
they put it in this like paper food to
go container the beans and then they
throw in like they have three different
choices like chili con
or uh
beans or the beans are always a topping
I don't know and then
cheese and stuff did you see it and they
have like a huge line every [\h__\h]
day and I will admit I love oven
potatoes so I kind of like a part of me
was thinking damn I want to fly to
England just for that but that would be
ridiculous
uh
but and also because you can so easily
make that at home why is that place so
popular some kind of gimmick food once
something is popular and has a line This
is the I don't know what kind of what is
this
mindset then you're like
oh yeah Trend food need to stay in line
as well and get this super easy
food yeah this literally just
potatoes
beans sometimes they throw in some chuna
cha or like they had a bunch of
different things but cha CH chah
cha cha in it
really
good I I I think most of the enjoyment
when watching several of those videos
most of the enjoyment probably came from
the accent just really like listening to
that
accent ytube uploading that video to
YouTube okay that went a little bit too
far uploading video to
YouTube how is
[Music]
that how was that was that
good her don't listen
hey it's embarrassing I don't I don't
have the confidence to do my accent
really in front of Herby and also don't
have the confidence to do my Italian
accent in front of um except when I am
speaking Italian words because you have
to speak the Italiano words with this
kind of accent otherwise you sound like
a [\h__\h] idiot oh maybe you don't but
no no for real though like you need this
intonation and uh and but uh but uh
otherwise you sound like a tourist which
I mean I guess I will sound anyway
because I'm not perfect Italiano but
um yeah you know uh
yeah I think my I think my pronunciation
was fine when I was speaking
Italian call did hands in front of L and
now it's too embarrassed to do it again
I wonder how L thinks about it like
she's probably nice about it maybe she
thinks differently about
it there wasn't an issue making the
accent in front of Aura just channel
that
again yeah that's true that's it they
have different
auras
literally
like I'm a I'm I'm not scared of herb
but
um I and maybe especially because she's
so good at imitating and impersonating
other people's voices and
accents I feel even more embarrassed
trying to do my
my British accent my British accent in
front in front of
what it's so sad
because I people tell
me that apparently I used to have a more
natural and
unforced British accent when I was
speaking a
English where the [\h__\h] did that
go yeah I don't even know
how I don't know where it came from I
mean I think I already kind of like
picked it up when I was in
school but it's not like my teacher was
like like that hard on the British
accent I don't know how I did
it don't think I know yeah of course you
didn't notice because I'm talking like
preh
Holo Holo Holo Holo
life no herb says it like Hello Life
hello life I think she pronounces the
the first ho
pretty
strongly Olo no she she does say the
H hello life
I'm so glad she joined I need more I
need more British
accents maybe some Irish accent or
Scottish accent would be
lovely wouldn't doubt be
lovely
I Irish oh yeah we already have Irish
I why do you need an Irish member Ki we
have IR is at home I no why didn't you
an Irish member K we have Irish at home
Irish at
home points to Iris show picture of Iris
but I will see myself out show myself
out walk myself I don't know how how do
you say I can literally not do anything
right right now so I will show I think
show myself out do I show myself
out I I'm feeling I'm I'm on this whole
talk stage and I'm feeling the booze I'm
hearing them and I'm seeing the tomatoes
in your hands right
now yeah I'll see myself out
then thank you you were a great audience
um okay okay okay okay okay uh
uh in German we say
no I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm
sorry I swear I can do better with my
comedy I I I okay okay okay okay I'll
see myself out
uh German
we oh you guys are so nice you guys are
so nice
for see you tomor fora if you'll have me
[Music]
yeah a
h
[Music]
the way she looks into the
camera it's so dorky
[Music]
H let me
see let me perceive
[Music]
I can't ra
V even though she's starting in four
minutes oh
well she's literally playing
Z well well goodbye