to
Number 1
Where did the nearby clouds come from?
[music]
hey
jump on wish
teeth
chest
Shiino
near
The service of
Feather
Close someday
In the rain
The voice changed to sweetness
too
Look at me in the light
put out
here in the sky
Number 1
Those who came near
[music]
hey
bone
teeth
wet
above
Take away the sins nearby
when to close
In the pouring rain
My memory has changed into a hoarse voice
too
Uhahinashite me
[music]
Masukoharani
Number 1
Are there clouds nearby?
[music]
Ta
Open
Yes, it's open. It's open.
Happy birthday white
[music]
circle
The white group is there, so it's displayed.
You are in the display room
[music]
Nei ni ni yo mo ni ii
Yoyo
[music]
Oh
set a set yes set yes set set set set
Where
[music]
Where is Manekawa Sensei?
Yes, I'm not a teacher, I'm not a teacher at all.
Hello everyone, I just happened to be here.
Is everyone gathered together?
Yes, it's okay. Is it true?
Please, teacher, please take attendance.
Okay, let's go, starting with A from the white group.
I'm going to Iroha Changozaru, I'm hungry.
Thank you very much
Shijarobo-senpai, yes, Hellobo is here.
Ame Tepa Thank you very much Ai
Kanata-san
Haa
teeth
Mume-chan, yes, yes, Amui-chan.
Yeah yeah nice to
Miyu nice tomeyou cute
Iwaisogi Yuame
Chan Ame Ame Chan Achan
Ame-chan
Good
There you are
Kaelaie
Igo, please. Thank you.
This member broke up with me over a phone call and became A.
It's people, yes, yes, B.
Hotenchoco Sensei Awai
Iriirioriyoa-chan
Haki
Please
Masua
Hello
[music]
Hahaha I'll do my best, good luck and practice
I kept practicing because I saw what you were doing.
So, this is also done here.
Is it okay? Should I go?
but
Okay, it's Laren-chan today.
However, I had to be absent for a while.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, but I'm a junior.
I'm sorry I'll do it
I was looking at you, so I thought you just came to apologize.
I was surprised and looked at it for a moment.
Zominabigo is here!
to satisfy
I did it because it looked similar.
Well, Raden-chan's flight is also a little us.
I would like to cover
Thank you very much everyone, please
death
Let's do our best, so um, Holomen
Raden-chan will be on the hunt.
But that was for me a little bit.
I'll come out, please.
As a hunter, the Maki line is Nemada
Well, it's a secret, so I guess it's a secret.
Please look forward to the secret battle again.
Should I wander around alone? Someone will come.
I guess everyone is participating.
I'm trying my best
I'm wandering around by myself and taking everyone's cameras.
Maybe I should do my best and hit it and hit it.
I might be saying something like spying here.
There's a spy.Is it true?
Matsuri Senpai looks like a spy
I'm here. Pai is here. Go away.
Teruun is here in the white group's waiting room. It's a classroom.
Everyone is waiting here right now Yes, yes.
Behave well, I'll stay here anyway.
It seems like everyone is gathered together.
It was good, it was good, it was good, it was good
Good, good, everyone gather together.
There's a signboard, there's a signboard.
Where is this? Where is this?
Where can I use it for support? I can't put it there.
hey
It seems like it won't open
What is a signboard?
How do you use it?
I have a signboard in my hand and a signboard in my hand.
Mochiuchi is used in a typical fairy tale way.
That's the only way to do it, is it just pretending?
do
Kana's home
The white color was nice
But it's Pol Pol
Yes, it's Polpo, the police have come, everyone
It's great that the police are coming.
I'm going to scout out a slightly different place.
I wonder if I'll go scouting. Red team, everyone.
I wonder what it feels like
Everyone is having fun now. Everyone looks like they're having fun.
Something like hello
It's so messy
No one
Who is hitting me?
I don't understand
I can hear the sounds of punching coming from everywhere.
Time for practice
Please don't die for a while
Yo, I'm dead. Has it already begun?
But I think the main thing is regrossing during practice.
The guys were getting into a lot of trouble with each other.
That's right, all of them were by Rigro.
Something like that, take the signboard in your left hand.
It's gone now, but the sign was there all day today.
It may be stuck
Get something
Why can't I get it now? I guess I can't get it.
It's not just good, it's true
It's no good, but what the heck is this board? Everyone's a signboard.
It's fixed, it's too bad, even if it's a trap
I wonder if it's okay to carry it in a competition?
There is a signboard that tells you to reset your inventory.
I think
Maybe it's dyed
I always use my left hand, as expected.
It's okay Minecraft One of the creators of Minecraft
As expected, it really looks like it's going to happen again soon.
I'll back up, good luck
Hey, this time too, as the bomber at the Minecraft sports day.
Do your best and be explosive
As expected of you, you can teach me anything.
Is there no blame for the creator?
It didn't happen
It's true, isn't it?
Wow, is that true?
Is it true? Amazing
What will be added in the next update?
I said "KikiriKiriKirari"
I know it sounds like it's collecting experience points.
I don't know why, it's terrible
Right?
We don't know much about cameras.
But you know, I can hear it.
hear
Somehow, it sounds like Subaru-senpai's voice.
But it's not a misunderstanding. Yes, it's a misunderstanding.
I didn't hear what the school broadcast was. Yes.
Well then, let's make an appeal.
I think so, everyone in red.
Thank you very much for your entry.
announcement
is
[music]
Ku
It's cheap
White is red, mememe this way.
[music]
It's somewhere else
Yoko here
Yo
and
He's a genius again this year.The books are lined up in red.
They're lined up. Let's line up the whites neatly.
Kenichi Onko
What are we doing here and there in one row?
Can I have it? I said yes, so next
Everyone from the white group please enter.
[music]
[applause]
Masuda
hey
certain
to
White is the power. That's great.
You can ask that yellow group's mother to call you.
Is that the continuation?
I made a wish, Necha-chan, it’s okay, Kashiori.
Chan is hiding and so are you
This length is so long
I noticed that this route camera
Surely nothing was prepared
We're hitting each other, we're hitting each other, we're hitting each other so much, we're hitting each other so hard
I have
Why is the line so beautiful, White group?
You have too many honors, let's go with the serious category.
serious
frame
Only Shio-chan is pink, right?
I have a signboard for
Shioa, that's true, they matched up over there, yellow
signboard
There was no white sign, so I was asleep.
Hey, bye, even hold a sign. Raise a sign.
I said yes, I couldn't take it.
First of all, the Hololive movement
Thank you for your greetings.
So everyone
Hello meow
Hello, it’s amazing how everyone gathered together.
Thank you very much for your busy work.
Seniors and juniors really helped each other until today.
I think he encouraged me in practice as well.
But today is the actual event, so please help everyone!
Start
I really hope you can win
First of all, let's all have fun and
Everyone, I'm aiming for a standing position.
Please enjoy today.
Thank you for your support
Masu
Please yes thank you
Yes, please continue with the president of Cover Co., Ltd.
I have received more messages
Masu
Please click here to see what it is.
Yes, please take a look. Thank you for your hard work.
This is the representative of the Taba company.
It's the sports day that Mr. Susu has been waiting for.
Speaking of neck exercises, I won't be doing any bodywork.
It's not in the program.
Ren Raime, whose practice did you watch and how did you prepare?
Thank you very much for your hard work.
At today's sports day, we cooperated with each other.
Encourage each other and fight bravely until the end
Let's and usually Hololive
Please support the production.
Thank you very much thank you
I have been practicing until today.
Please pay attention to and support everyone's efforts.
I hope this will be useful to parents and guardians.
Please be careful if you are a listener.
I will give the opening remarks.
You must be mentally ill, Mr. Socho, or perhaps you are injured?
Understand
Masu
Yu Yu
Channel please, teacher, I'm going
Terai
Do your best, do your best, do your best, I like Gokusaka
Handa Yochi is already the most serious in the serious category.
I'm sure it's Karana-chan, please.
I wish, please do it.
Please, please be patient.
Thank you very much.Thank you very much.
Please, thank you very much
Thank you very much
Even funnier
naru white
Mr. San
This length
Please make it big
Masu
Is this the story of an abyssal teacher? Hashasukamon
Come on Hashashashasas
Lotus
Looks like I'll do my best
Na
Good luck, even if you ask the player-sensei to do it for you.
Is that okay?
Then please
Mr. Masu prays that all of us players will play Hololive.
Sportsmanship as a member
Use the Takeover Teacher to Fight
Kaikaie223November 4th Red Team Representative
Tokuyama is the white team representative and the yellow representative Haspels.
Yay
[music]
[applause]
Thank you, it's okay to come in.
Thank you very much
I'm sorry, who threw the bread?
I'm sorry, I threw a pass.
Thank you very much Aki Iyaouchi
Thank you for shining
Special
[music]
Everyone please, are you moving? Yes, please move.
This is also messy and free, excuse me.
Yes, the White Team's fugitives are so scary, so scary.
The 7th fugitive from the white team is the one with the best voice.
Group Contestants Channel White Group Contestants
Thank you for your channel.
The sound quality of Real Monokai is amazing!
The sound quality is tanatametame
It feels a little weird
It's because of that
The channel is Nanchan Nancha 1 channel
I guess it's the first round of rice hunting.
Only those who are in their first hunt
That's right, that's right, that's right, that's right, White group
I'm going to the contestant's channel so um, Ame
Chankaeneri, please go.
Good
Welcome
stubborn player team fight player
channel
Og, do your best, do your best
keep it up
Good Luck Good Luck Good Luck
completely
What is that completely?
thing
Oh, that's the third one, right? That's right.
It's empty
Yo
[music]
I was able to go. I wonder if all three of us could go.
Is it okay for us to be fugitives too? This is no good.
Somehow I feel like the white team is the hunter.
I look at the rules. Looks like a hunter.
So I'm going to support you like a hunter.
Please support everyone except that meba.
It's okay to support me, but don't run away.
It's a good escape. I wonder how many groups this is from.
I'm sure there will be an announcement about whether it will start or not.
Yeah, I'm sure there will be an announcement.
Is it there? Is it there? Is it there?
check
Everyone except the Nauche Degozaru Hunter Team
Or 2, so maybe we're different too.
Other than the Hunter team, so Hunter team
Does Mu stab three hunters?
Or will he stab the white group of hunters?
Which frame do you draw? It's still us.
At the beginning of the match, I wrote red and then wrote red and white.
write
red white
It's true that you can only enter once as a fugitive.
That means you're a fugitive and you can go to the other side.
It's okay if you're a sleeper, I haven't tried it yet.
Not possible
No, you can't enter already.
I'm entering and it's going to be
Eh, I wasn't the one who entered.
tachi
What is that?
You have already entered, click here
Does this mean I should enter?
I guess it's all on its own
At first
It's okay even if you don't press the red button. Yeah, it's okay.
Oh sorry, Sade's announcement was rude.
Thank you Kaiha-san Roboko-san
Sansansansansan is a contestant in the white team
Please to the channel person on the contrary.
It's the other way around, the maples are moving, and the other way around is the other way around.
Maybe not, because everyone is running away now.
There are no runners moving.The broadcaster is competing.
Even if you move to the other channel
Are you sure? How many numbers are there?
I think it's the same place as the competition channel
That's it.
yes
Excuse me, that hunter left here.
That means I'm still a hunter.
not a hunter
Karaeja, will the leader go to the other side?
yes
Oh, let's go. It's a difficult day. It's a difficult day.
I really wanted to try this difficult exercise.
If
This is what I wanted to do the most, but I'm sad.
I wanted to practice moving.
The one I couldn't do the most
It's true that I don't like this, but if I can overcome this
I can do it now, I totally understand.
Well, wait, if you don't know what to do.
Please, please
At first, Ako was a hunter in red and everyone in white group.
Run away yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes to to
Yes, everyone is an engineer.
That's right
Infected people during white hunting
Maybe I can get it.
hey
difficult
Now, with a microphone that only the listeners can hear,
I'm talking to you
Everyone, if you have the volume up, just a minute.
While looking at the chair, I said,
I'll try it for a minute.
Please don't say it right away, please give me more details
Looks like it's a little bit
If someone has a smaller length,
Thank you for letting me know a few times
[music]
hey
What will happen in the end?
This is chasing and running away, running away, running away.
Looks like it's going to run away
The other team's fugitive fugitive is probably automatic.
Looks like it's going to be set.
I have to do something like that.
For example, a topic will be given.
There are people from the red group, and Hunter is from the white group.
If we did, we'd be targeted, so we'd run away.
It's like a click
I'm going to get caught with a rope, so even if I get caught, I'll give it my all.
It feels like I want to run away, okay?
Because I'm going to be put in a cage, I'm going to be [ __ ]
Yes, I'm going to Korea. I'm going to Korea.
I can't get out, so I'm surprisingly in a cage.
There's a hiding place behind me.
It's true that I'm a bit anti.
On the other hand, the other side of the cage is wide.
There's no one behind the cage because I'm heading towards you.
I can almost see how gentle she is
There are times when you are concerned about what is behind you.
Yes, that's what the staff is saying right now.
I guess I'm watching the text channel.
But the seven fugitives from the white team are contestants.
This is the second layer, but it's better to go.
Is it okay for me to call you by that name?
I don't think so.
That's why it's the 1st and 2nd game of hunting.
It would probably be better if both people went over there.
I'm just wondering if it's okay to do that.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, but
She was calling me, but I guess she didn't get it through.
Hey, it looks like Raden-chan's share is good.
That's right, that's what I said
I see, it feels like something like a hand.
I guess I'll have a listen.
Please tell the announcer this
Thank you Un and Asoka Lame-chan
Because it is, that's how it is
Kanata was called earlier, but I guess
There is still a chance that Laden will join.
Maybe it's progressing
I feel that way, I think so.
Is that so? Is that so?
Only non-hunters can use this channel now.
It seems like I have to be there
Amichi is flying somehow.
It's the power of God. It's the power of God. It's the power of God.
I have the power of a god
Yo
Okay
[music]
Well, let's just ask.
Thank you, thank you, I hope you're okay
I wonder what it will be like this time.
I wasn't listening to what was going on, now that I think about it...
I didn't know how to do the trick though.
I guess they haven't done that part of the overall flow.
Yeah, now that I think about it, there were no documents.
I'm probably reading some materials right now.
Except maybe I can assemble either one.
All players other than those from other teams who write each other
I'm confused as to which one I should write.
pounding fuse fuse
Yeah, but the staff is inputting information.
I wonder if he'll come back
I wonder which one is Katata, but today everyone
Well, it's a bit of a long road, so that's not what I planned.
It's probably around 9 o'clock, but maybe
I feel like I shouldn't push it.
There's a Karama atmosphere. There's a bit of an atmosphere.
The atmosphere seemed a bit timid so we took a break.
I feel hungry while conserving energy.
There were some people there, so please eat your food.
Let's take it easy. It's going to be a long time to eat.
Because it's long, this is the real pleasure of the sports day.
That's right, that's right, isn't it? Big garbage Daigomi.
It's difficult, don't call it a big piece of trash.
It's a big piece of trash.
It's no different, Daigoten is an English book.
I want to
The Real Thrill The Real Thrill The Real
It says thrill, the answer has come, it's true.
real real thrill real
The thrill of it all is
It's a book, so it's in its current form.
It looks like it's true, it's true, this is true 2
At the time of mawashimen, the next three challengers are heading towards it.
Well then, ignore this diagonal thing.
I don't have to say that, but it's okay, there are 7 people.
We are nothing
123456789 people 9 people 9 people
That's right. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your reply
Thank you thank you thank you
Thank you, but in the first game, red will be first.
We all have to run away, but what do we know?
It's definitely true, it's true, it's true, it's true
What's going on? The channels are just separated.
So we'll do it together, only the voices will be separated.
Let's go
It's starting soon
beginning
Run away, it's coming quickly
Teinga
Not Rishi
run away
I ran away and went around the English members.
Let's protect it by flickering
Let's protect our English members.
Let's protect English members, I'm that number one
hide behind
I'm not waiting, I'm in trouble
If you don't protect Fu, they'll be watching your back too.
I'm not an anti behind bars either.
is
already
The subject will change The subject will change The subject will change 100
Wait, I said something before.
This is the 9th grade high school squatting down.
Hey, 149cm, hey
It's okay to be wrong, it's okay
It's perfect for people under 149cm.
What is the perfect person? This is perfect.
People are like people who can get in, so let's get in.
I'm 149cm tall
I'm not 149cm
He's tall and extremely small, but on the contrary
Even if you are small, don't run away and be confident.
It's totally better than it seems.
But
There was no one there, but I was trying to protect them.
do not have
Who is this?
Who can you catch? Catch me!
catch
Please tell me why no one is coming.
It's more like a guess at all, no one.
messenger
Catch me, I can go.
Someone said I can go, anyone?
Da-chan, I can go, you can catch me.
[laughter]
It was okay, but here it is.
Let's see
caught
Yo it's over
[music]
I guess it was something like that.
It seems like Anya is a little different.
awkward
It's a bad crackling
Hunter, please move to voice chat.
That means all 6 people.
Yes, it says there are 6 people in total.
That's true. Let's go.
Hello, let's go for a bit.
Wait, the 6 hunters aren't here, sorry.
The 6th eye of the grouper is here and here.
All the fugitives from the white team were competing today.
Everyone, Shirogumi ABB, the original voice chat
Please move to
Thank you for your hard work
Well, we'll go back then.
Welcome bye bye
I feel like I'm in trouble, or something like that.
Masuta
Senkyu Senkyu
I guess that means they're going to call Moda.
It helps, it helps, it's so hard, Chiara, Chiara
A bonus should be given for only
Nene, you must be working hard, you need a bonus.
Yeah, it's right, it's right, it's right.
nice pina
No, that's good. Oh, it's interesting. Yeah, it's fun.
Also call live english catch
I'm sure something like that won't come out again.
You don't get the same thing twice or three times.
Something like Indonesia should be captured.
I wonder if it will come out, maybe it will happen
Yes, it seems possible that there are tall people.
To be honest, I don't even remember the tall person.
I guess you'll have to bring someone with a suitable height.
But there really aren't many people over 160cm tall.
It seems like everyone in Hololive is pretty cautious.
Because my eyes are small, what do I do because I have small eyes?
I guess 149 is a fine line
I'm following you, right? The one with the most is the most.
I'm in my 150s, after all, I'm from the white group.
Yes, yes, the first game flies.
Nerisaiei
Kaela and the three
I'm a member of Umi, so let's hear your enthusiasm.
I think so, but I'm a second hunter.
Introducing Mr. Hunter in his second game.
I'll give you a little introduction.Yes, yes.
Commander Noel and
tree
That's good, that's why everyone in the white group said yes.
Can you hear me, players? I can hear you.
I can hear you. Good morning, how is it?
Do you have any enthusiasm or strategy?
Strategy from
have the
people and everyone for now
I might try to catch it, but I won't catch it
Strong plan
We are so strong, it's our second match.
Now, let's catch it with our powers, too.
Let's go, put everyone in a cage and see who it is.
I would like to go with a strategy of hitting several hits.
The same money
That's too much white team power.
Well, I'll get through this with a lot of will power.
How did you feel when you saw the topic earlier?
I thought I was about to go, but I had to hurry up.
What do you want me to catch?
So cute that Mimio-chan wants to protect her.
I was wondering who the members are.
is
But yeah, that included me.
Mio-senpai, how was that?
Petting
Yoarekana The rest is Ohami. This is Ohami.
Maybe it's because I believe in it.I believe in it.
It's the body
Yes, please do your best.I will do my best.Yes
Thank you, how are you? Yes, thank you, yes, who is that?
Who's doing Death Voice?
Thank you everyone.
Please stand by.
[music]
If you say yes to my wish, then enter it.
It's okay, Moe, whatever it is, it's hunting.
Ha, it was my second match, so embarrassing.
I wonder if everyone saw me.
Sorry for posting the log a little too quickly.
I'll do it for you, Hi-chan, Noel-san.
Chiara and Kanata are on the original channel.
Sorry to return to Shirogumi ABB channel.
No, it's okay, thank you very much.
Please come back soon.
Masumobai
Bye with anyone
I don't understand
who
Maga Ayabai is a yellow color that I made myself.
Now that I've gone to the team
I've been doing something for a while now.
Oh, I'm back, I'm back, I'm back
I went back home and had an interview.
I went there for the 2000th time because of it.
It's like, yes, yes, there's an interview.
I interviewed him so much that I couldn't get into his room.
[music]
Ta
It's okay, Mu-chan, it's just that you're confused, it's okay.
It's okay, I was talking about something interesting, just shut up.
What the heck are you laughing so hard at?
It's okay, it'll be fine. It'll be fine.
It's okay, I'm worried about how it's okay now.
The way the speech bubbles look makes it seem like it's going to be a great story.
I told you to talk, but it was a lot of fun.
It was blurry, it was blowing, it was blowing
Tayoshicho is walking around
Senpai, let's do it, let's do it.
Let's do it
Hey, white team, white team, white team
team
Team White Team Hunt, so we run away.
That doesn't mean I'm not a person, right?
Yes, I want to run away, I want to run away, right?
run away
It's okay, then you can run away next time, okay?
Oh yeah, we'll have to wait a bit until the next escape.
Please, please, be polite next time.
The serious team seems to be well behaved.
Apparently, they are a well-behaved team.
Well, number one, that's right, everyone was great.
to
The white one lined up the best.
Looks like our colors lined up beautifully.
As clear as our white color
Clear and clear and clear and white clear and white
Even if it's clear and white, I wonder if it's real.
It's so clear and clear that it's definitely weird.
Well, the resident toy collection is white, but there are colors.
from
white
There are a lot
Do your best, the sudden feeling of Shinaruru is making your heart flutter.
Do your best, try your best, do your best, I wonder what's coming
What is the theme? Debut starts in 2021
twenty two
Yeah, this is pretty recent.
Don't put Phlox in this Rocks
I'm sure it will go in 21
Maybe year
I wonder if it's up to locs, but I can't stop at just phlox.
But I'm running away so much that I'm lying
The 3rd generation students are also English 3rd generation students.
Aja ID Season 3
Yes, I see. It's a bit of a shame. It's a shame.
It's the summer of 2020, this is hard.
I've come up with a slightly lame name.
That's right, even if you can find it, it's hard to find.
Necha's hand
Hey, do your best, try your best, Daigo-san.
Hacha Festival
If he was there, he would have taken me.
I was caught by something, I wanted to be caught by it
Isn't that what's wanted?
No, I'm happy
a little bit
Bob is totally secured.
I'm worried that I won't be able to get rid of it.
It's okay it's here
Are you okay? I'll catch everyone regardless.
Hold it properly
If you catch 3 people, there will be about 1 bob.
Right, I have a short bob for now.
random chance
There's no other way. Touch, go, go, go, where.
It's so quiet.
Why is everyone so quiet?
I was just messing around with you, but...
I'm taking Gura-chan with me.
Nice, maybe this will also freeze in one place
Holo thinks Po is planning a strategy or something.
Holo that kidspo thinks
The kids say it was good.
Don't get into it, I'm not a kid.
Yes, it is.
[music]
A grateful woman who feels like entering
Damon, I'm a servant.
That's for sure. It's true that Anya was arrested.
Daaani yakizu daaaa
Merle, it's not you, sister.
Hey, big sister, I'm worried about fishing.
I'm curious about this, but I wonder if it's going to go downhill?
It's not him, it's not him.
I'm not a kid, but I have boobs.
It's just for big girls and kids.
It's late, I'm sure, so I'm going in.
No way, I have no choice but to run away. I have no choice but to run away.
It's okay if we all run away, right? Let's run away.
And with that me
When the leader gets caught, gets caught, gets caught, gets caught.
Let's go, I've already caught them all.
Please, if you don't understand, please include everyone.
You just have to put everything in properly.
That's much better
Rudondon Tachitachi
The tongue is quite simple and the topics are varied and interesting.
It wasn't easy like when it was, it was difficult.
Apparently it's interesting that it's not a common understanding.
Well, it's my fault that you failed.
certain
seeseewas
UnderSECONDsays
ENG
[music]
KID
I apologize for the inconvenience.
Thank you for your love, thank you bra
It might be tight, but please come in now.
Well, it's definitely something like that.
Sometimes I think I'm just unlucky
If it's kids, what will happen to everyone?
I'm sure it's something like this or something like this.
I think it's going to fit in. I think it's going to be cool.
Okumi-chan, your voice sounds like you
Hello, it wasn't my impression that I was being watched.
I definitely want to know the answer.
Also displays a bar at the end.
I want to know who was the target and will be targeted.
You were totally in it, locked on.
It's Tamon Rock'n, right?
Nanaka Risa-chan looks like Anodosa
I'm feeling like, oh no, that's what I got.
Because I couldn't do it, I feel like I can't secure it.
It's okay, Neri-san, there were 0 people.
Are you worried about that?
cute
It's okay, it was a little difficult.
It was more difficult than practice, so I guess it's okay.
No practice questions, no problems The practice table is too easy
from
I'm sure it's okay.
That's a cover by Captain and Chiara.
I'll do it, okay, okay, look forward to it.
I'm looking forward to it. Let's do it. You'll be sick too.
It's okay, everyone, I'll let everyone in.
All the people I found, I kapaed and then let them in.
I'll put it in
Please use your strength to move.
That's right, move like move
mosquito
Everyone, please go to Kyo's voice chat.
wish
It's not the fugitives, it's the two of us.
Hey, Senpai, eh
Ah, senpai, for some reason we ended up alone
My senior is probably a fugitive, so this is the competition from earlier.
Is it okay to use a personal channel? Oh yeah yeah
Yes, that's how it should be
Love you
So why am I alone?
Who's here? I'll go over there too.
I'm off for a bit.
Looks good
[music]
Well, I don't care.
So you don't have to worry about it at all
Yo
no no no prem
Are you listening to the meaning of that word?
Look at the Munoa program.
Please, look, look at this poor person.
This is how I feel now
What is it? Where is it leaking?
Wow, I couldn't find it. What do you mean for a moment?
The situation is so bad, I want to do this.
When I opened it, opened it, and immediately closed it, there was something inside.
Do this in front of the closed door
It's so nice to be able to put so much in.
Hololive
The room is a little squeaky and smells like earth.
It smells like earth
Something stinks
[music]
Looks like a lot
That's right
Kiki yai
Something is wrong with me
Can I just say that? John,
is too dense
[music]
I'm really looking at you from the corner of my eye.
It was cute, right? Yes, it was cute.
That's right, that's it, that's it.
That's okay, that's okay, really
I'll keep selling cushions as is.
I can do it, I'm sure this is really cute
It's so cute when you move your head.
There's no hunter here, there's no hunter.
yellow next yellow yellow
It's yellow number.
Oh well, let's run away. That's right, it's time to run away.
I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best
Let's run away, Ranran, let's go to Korea.
I want to try it but it's no good.
Only fugitives, only fugitives
Anita, touch me, touch me, touch me, touch me.
I might enter tomorrow on my own.
It seems like there is an entry in
Run away, run away, run away, run away, run away
Run away, it's the color of yellow.
Run away from the year
Run away, who should I protect?
[music]
Nerisa Nerisa 23 years old
There's also hidden niceness
I wanted to mess with the two of us and make it a mess.
Fresh Katata recently debuted
It's okay. Let's go there.
Please show your motivation.
Even if I just broke up, I won't even look at you.
you said that
R
Also new
[music]
Desuyaba
or
160 Who is running away?
is
What, 7 people who know Kia are amazing?
Hey, I'm here too
I want to catch it. It's 10. I want to catch it.
That was totally overlooked by us.
Senpai, there's no way that can happen, wait a minute.
The leader was arrested, but wait, leader 158 Hey
And isn't it a polka?
White Safe Okay Heel Heel won't fit.
It doesn't come in
165 That's right, hide it, hide it, what will change?
You're in charge of Chu, please hide me and hurry.
It's a little dangerous to hide it
It's dangerous
please
what
That's why
Chacha
servant
is
Neo, why?
Yo
Right?
Some kind of mistake
I think it's some kind of mistake.
So let me catch you
Ha caught
Teruecho I won't be here 3 times
He gave me some time though
I'm worried, but I'm really prepared.
is
But
I feel sorry for those who failed.
You're so neat, but you're not so neat.
Even the screams are so pure now.
Nara, it's clear that I'm complaining.
There will also be dissatisfaction
Nice, nice, they didn't catch it, they caught it.
There wasn't.
I don't want to run away, but it's true, A-chan.
is definitely a member, it's dangerous to join.
I just ran away
It's cute that she's so self-aware
Hey, how was it? So cute
you are a student
Aman, definitely run away with Ei-chan
I don't think it's cute, isn't it?
Chano has to run away too, neat and clean.
I don't think I'll get caught while
It was so yellow, so yellow.
I caught about a seed, that's crazy.
Tane, this was amazing too, the battle for leader
It didn't happen. I'll run away one more time. I'll run away one more time.
Everyone has entered, all at once.
Thank you so much 2
[music]
Ran will run away
lego run away
Even though she's strong, when she was an adult, she and the leader
mosquito
Even if it's a girl who has sex appeal or something like that.
It's okay, I wanted to be chosen.
don't say it
It's true that my height wasn't even selected.
That's true, but please don't misunderstand me.
I think Tako and Polka will misunderstand me.
Polka had a misunderstanding, so it's a little cagey.
I could have gotten close, but the cage is small.
I seriously don't like it
Don't worry, I'll catch you already
You can't run away during the game.
During the hunter game, yeah, yeah, next
The game is
Inori is so cute
You have to do your best and run away, Mio next.
Senpai, no, who's going to think that? The next one will be Tami.
I wonder if it's true or not.
Well, I guess that's what I mean, but please go home.
There's a possibility that things will be completely different.
I want you to have it though
Well, it's finally being said that it's time to move on.
I want you to protect me, like this, I want you to protect me
If I do it, I want to be protected
hey
S
Only listeners can hear it now
I'm talking about Ezaka and Saka's creepy cousins ​​in my voice.
I saw a creepy cousin on Chaishitasaka.
This is a must-see place.
This hill is a little overlapping next to Zion Tepa.
It's disgusting to do that
But what?
It's so bad, everyone is buried.
Everyone is caught
I can't help but look at it seriously
cute
hey
Cute, someone please come stand next to me
It turned out like that
reset reset okay okay
It's starting, maybe I'll start over again
Oh yeah yeah okay
O
Okay oh
Ooooh
Ooooooooo
It doesn't matter if it's a big deal or not, but Subaru-senpai's
My nipples are gone
Damn it
I had accumulated
I'm on board, so please take the time to chat with me, Subaru-senpai
How many nipples do you have?
There is no such thing as a bird because it is an egg.
It's not like that, so oh yeah
It all starts without a bird.
It had become like a famous thing.
I'm lonely. What's going on?
Debut in 2019
year
It's so bad, it's so bad, it's not there.
Amazing
Who is it in 2019?
It's 2019.
Everyone please run away and run away
I'm old enough
It's a shame that Ademoka-chan came along.
It was a shame, Etemirocho and Chodocho 2000
It's 2019 201
year
It's difficult, okay
There are 3 or more songs from ``Yo Escaped''.
Ge
That was really fast, but run away now.
Run, run, run, it was scary right now.
Artists gather here
Super artist
Yes, it's difficult, isn't it?
There are quite a few games with 3 or more games.
I'm sure there was an image of it coming out.
I'm doing it
I don't think so, I'll call you.
[music]
I was arrested by the Ozora police who were completely crazy.
The king was interrogated by such a person.
Or that thick
There is
No, it's not Claw, who is it?
I've been caught doing this before.
being caught
Yes, I wasn't caught, no, I was caught
I have never accumulated it.
Surprisingly not everything
I'm sure he hasn't been arrested yet.
I guess that's not the case
[music]
Neyoshiyoshi
Okay, seriously
Nice
Nice, nice, it answered all the questions.
But I ran away
wonderful
vinegar
Tat
Thank you for your hard work.Thank you for your hard work.Thank you for your hard work.
There are only three hunters left here.
Please move away. Bye bye.
do my best
hey
I'll do my best
[music]
There's a lot of pressure. There's a lot of pressure.
Well, let's do our best for now.
Click, always right-click, right first, right
Right click on the signboard on the right
Okay, let's put it in.
You should be a hunter, a hunter.
I have to enter
Yo right click right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right right
No, it's difficult. I wouldn't understand that question if it were me.
Maybe not, but my songs are surprisingly good.
It seems like all the songs have been released, but surprisingly there is nothing else.
That's right. I know something. I know many stations.
But I wonder if it was more than 3 games?
It's a little difficult, right?
I think there are probably the most people with 34 songs.
It's 10 stations, Kira is amazing, I doyou
I like it the most
I couldn't thank you enough for that.
If it was in Japanese, I would have sung it.
Thank you for actually releasing the Korean version.
I think I'll release a Japanese version next time.
I remember the wish that I could bring it out and sing it.
I tried so many times but
It's difficult, it's difficult, even English is difficult.
Yonanmoto and others are waiting for you, Honhaya Unmecha.
The interview is here! The interview is here!
It's true.
I just answered a quiet interview.
What do you want to know? What do you want to know?
What is our name?
Nanjaro na Nanjaro na Nanjarona
I'll show you this
It's your first time, Hunter.
This is my first time at Ah So So No Nante
That's right, that's what it is, so practice etc.
I haven't done it, I haven't done it, so let's do our best.
Good luck, right click now
Therefore, secure it for the time being.Secure it for the time being.
Please do it, yes, Kazucha Amecha
It's okay if you pull it, okay, oh oh
My God, one more time? One more time? Okay, okay, yes.
I'm getting used to it, it seems like it's getting more and more
Yeah, I'm starting to understand the system.
Now I know what's the 3rd time table?
I wonder why I lost my nipples
That's probably true. Yesterday, Subaru
I was in the voice chat when my senior deleted it.
Why, why did it disappear?
Can I just delete this now?
I was so embarrassed to ask Temio-senpai.
I guess it's embarrassing after all.
That's right, that's embarrassing, right?
Because it's Subaru
That's right, it's a girl. That's right, even Subaru is a mistake.
Because it's eggplant
It seems like it is
Nemi, it's embarrassing. It's embarrassing.
It was good, but it's a symbol.
It was a highlight, and it was expensive, two of them.
Jane was beautiful Nils, beautiful.
It was Nils, right? Come on, let's come.
From here? I see, I'm not going to catch you.
I want to catch anything and do it.
Eh, wait a minute, it's not that close.
I don't really understand it. 160 yen.
Well, I feel like Ririka-chan was pretty good.
long true
Omaru-kun had to carry a rope
I'll catch it at random, but I'll put it at random.
Isn't Waame different too? There's definitely one around here.
It's so small, there's something hiding there.
Tae nice
Yosshosui-chan is 160 oh
Takkesu-chan 160 Wow, it's over
Wait a minute, who is that?
There is a chance for Meccha Ze Senpai
Right?
Senior, I see, no one has time to be lazy.
The ears and ears are the same here and the ears are caught here and there.
Oh no, it's a bit more of a nuisance. It's a nuisance.
There's Chiara, who's got ears?
I was really into Kiara, Kiara's ears.
Hey, wait a minute, listen to me.
It's not like they're hanging ears, it's ears that aren't for seniors.
Emi, just try, just try, just try
I'll try it, that's nice.
Fauna-chan will be like that too.
I wonder if Naina-chan was able to go, too.
I wish I had caught him, but that's a big deal.
Absolutely no, no, my ears are gone
I feel like there aren't any ears left, who cares?
It's different, right? Where is it behind?
Homie thinks Amiko Ninida is dumb.
Senpai, Aku-chan, oh senpai, you can't go, senpai
Guffy
Yay, yay, yay, wan chan wan chin
is
Okay, senior, as expected, for now.
Is it really different?Is it really different to me?
Myself
There is such a thing in Amo Miko-senpai.
It was definitely a blur, but I guess that's not the case.
I really don't want to look at it, it's wrong, it's blurry
Where is the blur?
I wonder if Ririka-chan will be a bit of an idiot.
Wait, it's stuck here, try putting it in.
Iris-chan is stupid, I'll catch her again.
Iris-chan, I'm sorry, I'm so stupid.
Maybe it's not true. Yeah, it's not true.
Damn it, nice slope, are you stupid again?
13 people, 13 people, you did it nice.
Nice, 6 people, 6 people, you did your best, you did your best.
Nice nice, everyone is fine, it's fine.
I've already said that
Right click for the rest of your life without having a lead at first.
I wish I had passed on the first road I took
I did it because it was available.
I'm a good person. I hope everyone is white.
What did you think? It was fun.
It was wonderful and fun. It was fun.
It was fun looking for blur
Now I'm saying you're stupid, you're stupid
I was catching it while I was there, and it was almost blurry.
Oh, it was so hard, almost
I'm glad it's mostly blurry
It was a pretty good sleep.
I did my best
It was a good sleep, I did it, it's rotoku
Yay, it looks like it's a holotalk show
It doesn't seem like it's a good idea, but it's Kia.
I know it because I know a lot about it.
That's what I do every time, everyone.
Thank you very much for the job
Please keep up the good work after this.
I'll do my best, I'll do my best
Nene, then I'm nice.
Instead of everyone coming back, everyone came back.
I'm heading home
I was so excited when I got home, everyone, welcome back.
It's quite a lot
The ears were really good.The ears were really good.
It looks like I'm going to get caught at the end.
It's mostly blurry, but you can just put it in.
The face that's looking at me is almost blurry, almost blurry
Very
If you listen carefully, you'll find that there are surprisingly few
Bame Senpai's ears
I don't have an image of how crowded it is.
Well, it's true that this is the cat in my ear.
I'm in charge of the blur, so there isn't much intrusion.
I wonder if it's that blur.Ah, maybe it's that blur.
But if you judge Mio-senpai, it's pretty lame.
Isn't there a lot of people or something?
He thrusts into me
That's right, that's right, Mio-chan Kamio
I'm sure it's someone other than chan
Nimi Orlando Oran
Oran was a bonus stage in a sense.
I'm sure I can do an escape tree.
[music]
If you do it for me, I'll run away. I'll run away.
I did my best
let's go let's go
Chata
It was so embarrassing
Don't worry, hide it
Yabai-chando
senior
Someone was arrested
Ayabe
That's exactly what it is
Neshikara 2
About
It's too late, I'll catch you for a moment
It's okay to get caught, it's okay to get caught
Did Yoteru-chan know? I caught her!
I'm worried that it will be changed soon.
Blonde hair is dangerous
terrible
hair cigarette
Sip
That's crazy. A lot of people are getting caught.
Dadanai-chan was born with blond hair.
Eh, look closely
Tora
It's too dangerous
Good silver hair, I'm sorry I looked a little the same.
Same
I used to provoke someone
I got it
It's a shame that I have free time.
hey
Oh no, I'm about to get caught.
I don't want to be too sexy, but the other person is also the other person.
Get caught or hide and go somewhere, Commander.
Commander, stay hidden. Come on, catch me.
It's okay here
Yes, there's one-chan, one-chan.
Um, I'm Kanata, why are you talking about me?
I completely ignore it, why, why, why stop?
I didn't either
Senpai Festival Senpai Festival Senpai I'm here Matsuri
senior festival senior
[music]
That's not sexy
No, but Chan-chan-chan, I'm here.
That's right
too
It was 12 so nice, nice, this.
There were 14 people, 13 people, 13 people.
It was
Nice nice nice nice nice nice
Nice, it was just barely dangerous or dangerous.
Tane Nice Sexy Frame is Seriously Sexy Frame
I got away with it, I got away with it, I got away with it.
I'm glad I managed to escape
It's very dangerous
I'm glad
Ceci was really a little surprised.
[music]
Tami
Sleep
white
is explained
It's clear
Where did everyone go?
Something was moved there without permission.
I'm back I'm back
moved freely
This is where the cat goes home
man returning home
is a man
[music]
In the end, I wonder who is winning now.
I don't know, what's going on? It's like a complete failure.
I guess I didn't write any notes that I don't understand.
Where was the judgment? Mu Senpai sexy
Aaah yes no no this is ichan no
sexy channo
Sexy Senpai Se No. 1
Sexy No. 1 Sexy No. 1 Sexy No.
No no no no no no sexy no
Sexy, maybe sexy isn't here
I'm not here, wait, wait, wait
Please wait, Kae is here.
a
sexy kaelano no kaelano sexy
For those who want to have a sexy look themselves
Jesus
Kasese is cool, Kaela is cool, cool
often
It's going to be a Robkote Pasexi
Robco-senpai, I said no.
That was out on my ass day.
It's a good butt day, even though I saw it a while ago.
I was already in Korea, right?
I'm sure it's not sexy because I couldn't do it.
Well then, no sexy, don't do it together.
Wait, isn't that sexy already?
Hey, sexy was better, sexy.
I wanted to get caught, you know?
It was a shame, I didn't know at first.
That's really true.What will happen until the end?
I don't know, so be careful. It's yellow.
I want everyone to do their best and the other teams as well.
I want everyone to run all the way to the end.
So, next
Move to the venue for the competition follow-up
Let's be evil please yellow 5 white 20 red
15 middle or 2 middle?
Seconds at All Momo Rear Seconds Next Venue
I'll go to the next venue or follow up.
above
da up
Flow up, I don't want to fall, I don't want to fall
[music]
First of all, I don't have any seniors, so I speak English.
but
Dangerous English
Let's go, Senpai Senpai, let's go home
Let's
School that has become a go person
school school school school high
Follow School High School Club
Upflow up
Acai Follow Up Stage 5 Go Go
Follow-up stage La Cool Rooftop
I guess you mean rooftop, huh?
I don't know what a ground is because it's a ground.
I read that there is no high ground up
Everyone at Iairooftop is passionate
terufutorooftoplufutoroof
Top Luft Top Luft Go Go
rooftop go golf to gogo roof
Top Rooftop Jesus Comes Comes
Oh, I see. I guess it's just the roof top.
I see
All the contestants, now this or that.
It's interview time, isn't it?
I see, I see, I see
Good luck, Bo-senpai. Character-senpai, that's a book.
Do your best, try your best, do your best, but that's it.
I don't think we can talk at all and B together.
Yeah, yeah, it was like that.
I wasn't stiff, I wasn't.
In fact, Chiara's presence really helps.
Thank you, thank you, thank you
I looked up English today.
I looked up English only for things that I think are likely to be used.
Okay, so I'll expand it a little bit here.
No, I haven't used it even once.
Let's use it
I can't use it, but what about Ume-chan during my break?
Good luck with your explanation
Ta
Oh no, I was listening to Noisy Noisy.
Oh yeah, what is that? Steak?
Yeah, how do you say chicken and pork in English?
I had a meeting with my senior colleague, Kenana.
When I asked them to grill something, they asked me what I wanted.
Well, that's what he told me.
Good luck beef and pork
chicken beef pork chicken
[music]
If you rush, you'll forget
That's why I have to shout out to my senior.
Is it beef, pork, or chicken?
beef pork
It's like chicken steak steak steak
steaks beef beef fire beef
beef fire beef fire
steak
steak steak
eat
I'm not hungry.
Sorry, someone said they were hungry.
I'm hungry I'm hungry I'm hungry
It's just around 7:30.
Hey, it's time for dinner. JP is like that.
That's right. It's different for overseas groups.
Soka enwa and tie now unsenpai
Ah 3am3
3 o'clock in the morning, not 3 o'clock in the morning, 3:30 o'clock, yes.
3AM in the morning, 3AM in the morning.
Yes, it's the middle of the night. It's the middle of the night, Wow, Rain-senpai too.
The time difference is so hard. I'm so sleepy.
It's raining, it's so late at night
Thank you very much, thank you very much.
Senkyu Senkyu Senkyu
I drank a big cup of coffee. I drank a cup of coffee. Nice.
coffee nice coffee nice
coffee caffeine caffeine minister
caffeine minister caffeine caffeine
Power let's go!
What is Goasho English?
Just say kanchara let's go
A great person told me that it's okay.
I really believe in that great person and it's okay to be average.
Gozaru Ai-chan is throwing a trident
But it's just Sui-chan
Apparently they have creative authority.
I heard that's pretty popular
He's throwing a trident, right?
Oh, maybe that's it, maybe.
I was on the other side of this place the other day.
Holomen hunting
Edit in creative mode
Well, that's right.The remains of that remain in the book.
I also do something like fly when I practice.
About 3 days ago, I was doing javelin throwing.
It's so cunning, I have it on one hand.
Trident is nice. Trident is red.
A raw senior was fighting
What are you doing? It's okay. It's okay.
I can rise because I'm creative.
Yes, what are you doing?
Or the water will suddenly come up and I can do this.
Baiten
Oh that's true
You can't pick this up, right? Pick this up.
No, this is the remains of Mr. Senpai's photo.
Taken
I can read out the stars
Star readout
Teru Iroha's star reading is now available.
He's become such a troublesome person, I told him.
please don't be really scary
Something like chan
A little bit of trident hand dirt
I put something in Gypro.
I was checking. I had a photo. It disappeared.
Chat eraser
until the lock
Please let me know, what should I do tomorrow?
What should I do? What should I do?
I guess it depends on how things go in the future.
How about the rest today?
Next this
in
I'll lick it, won't you lick it? That's fine.
Why don't you tell me
Don't tell me
I'd be happy if you'd like it
Najaja Cookie Delivery Cookie
Karaa cookie cookie ah cookie is fine
I want to deliver cookies to everyone.
Yes, I want to feed everyone at overseas stores too.
That's certainly true, world.
I want to tell you, after all, I want to tell you.
I've been streaming for about a month now
I'll take a rest and go to Shu for now.
I'm going to go to training.
Shall I give it to the big Karamui Ame-chan?
Cookie Presents Cookie Presents Color
It looks like a cookie, it should be a cookie color, a cookie is coming.
Zosta second
a
Let's go robobokoroboko and do our best
Robokoshin, do your best, do your best
I like fight fight
Oh my god
It was heavy, but I was good at it.
Na practice Moe Aka isn't very fast Soubi-san
Looks really good Bi-chan is so sweet Biji
Do your best, Roboko-chan, Roboko-san!
Tepaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Yo number two now nice nice yes nice
It's totally nice Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa It's okay it's okay
It's okay, I can do it, but I've started the balance and now what?
Maybe I'll touch a checkpoint and fall.
It feels like I died and came back, lol.
Yes, checkpoints are important.
It's okay, let's do something with Sui-chan.
It's true, it's true, it's amazing.
It's so good! Wow, so good!
It's possible, it's possible, it's quite easy to choose the route.
It's solid, it's delicious, it's delicious.
Hey everyone
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
It's so fast, it's so good, it's so good
It's not really good, it's really good.
It's true, I'm coloring in the remaining time.
Those who are doing well, do your best, Tebabeeb
Amazing but 1 very fast
Navi Umashigi Ao Checkpoint
nice
Stroll first, poko poko, but somehow it's going steadily
I can't catch up, my point of view is above
I can go and see this from this perspective.
I can go. I can't go. Go.
No, I can't go, I'm looking at it from below.
That's right, just look at it from the bottom.
I just looked around and thought, "This is probably it."
If you touch the infection signboard, you can go.
That's what I said, but it's a lie. It's my first time doing that.
I heard or saw that you can enter if you are infected.
This is what is written, I can go up
I can go up I can go up
It's amazing, I'm chasing you, I'm chasing you
I didn't know this, and I still don't know it.
It seems like it was pretty easy to get in, but wow...
This is amazing, it's true, why?
We all know that everyone is really floating.
I guess everyone's head is floating, just their head.
It's good to be floating, so do your best
I can't see your nice hands
It's okay, it's true, I'm actually scoring a goal.
Goal
Teru
Calm
Do your best, try your best, that pink one is sleepy
This, this, this, this, this.
This is amazing, amazing, nice, nice.
It's so delicious!
Do your best, be strong
Good luck wow that was nice
amazing
nice
Nice job
Ge nice nice
Nice nice a
[music]
Sui-chan, do your best! Wow, this place is expensive.
Ntokosui-chan, Sui-chan, do your best
Do your best, do your best Sui-chan, where is Sui-chan?
She's so cute even when she throws a great trident
I wonder if the stars will come out? My eyes are so cute
I can become a photographer. I'll do my best.
After all, it's from the fans' point of view.
Hey, hey, hey, it’s cool.
Honestly, it's getting better and better.
It's up, it's up, it's good, it's good, it's good
Do your best, do your best
Good luck, you're taking shortcuts now.
I went there, right? I'm talking to you above.
Pink is so difficult that I feel like I can go.
A little later
Do your best, nice
yes
nice nanasu good
[music]
Nice
Nice game, I'll give it my all
Applause for me
This is great, everyone is clear, great
Something came out
[music]
Wonderful
Kia must be nervous about this. Yeah, it's okay.
Is there something wrong with the screen? There's something strange about the screen.
What is this that came out and this is the chat setting and
If there is, I wonder if there is a controller.
It's here. I don't really understand. What's here?
came out
Wait, I can't get down.
Kane shift, yeah shift, yeah shift, shift
I can get off at .Is it okay to shift?
Yeah, it's a little surreal to see severed heads flying around.
Yeah, I'm sure it's all perfect, I'll go back with this.
Oh, I'm back, I'm back, ok, oh, oh
Good, good
Tae is amazing, he only accepts heads like that.
I didn't know you were in spectator mode.
There is a mode called
That's amazing, for those of you who are normal people.
We can't see our heads, that's for sure.
When I looked at it from below, I couldn't see it, I couldn't see it.
I guess I didn't notice it.
I thought it wouldn't bother me, but it might get in the way
I can't do without it. I'm back.
You will be forced to return.Continue writing
It's better to become infected after the game starts.
After I die, something will fall from the sky
It looked like when I was looking at it
I felt like I was leaving my body, like a ghostly body.
Naeji Next Kiara Senpai
Yeah, I won't support you, I'll have to do my best to support you.
Let's
What do you do when you support Go English?
What are you going to do? How can I support you in English?
Sunda fight fight fight fight
Fight fight fight was there
Gogogogogogogolets
Go wrong
Go Go Kiara, do your best, do your best, Chiara
Good luck, it feels good
Yokia-senpai was really great.
It's so fast, it's the fastest!
I was practicing with that, so yeah, that's good, that's good.
It's good, it's finally early
I was at the last minute early.
Neuma seriously really good book
It's so good, it's so good
Amazing Chiara Senpai, Kiara, there's only one more person
You've already gone 70m, it's too early.
Checkpoint is amazing
Checkpoints are too nice
Wow, I can't go there, it's amazing too
Oni Uesoko of Smooth Shortcuts
I'm going to go, but I can go back.
I'm going up, this is amazing Kira-senpai
Super, after all, birds are fast. Birds are fast.
Birds are fast, after all, they definitely need practice to fly.
I must have been really nervous at the time.
You said let's do it, what should we do?
No matter what I do, I haven't made any mistakes.
It doesn't look like it's healing, it looks like it's not healing
I don't know if I make a mistake.
I don't understand, I don't understand, uh, uh, again.
I'm going
Don't leave without carving it up.
I had to go here, that's amazing!
Nomis
It's the best, as expected, there are no mistakes
Seriously, I made a brain mistake and came this far.
Masu
Wow, that's great. Which way is this going?
It's going that way, it's going that way.
I have no hesitation, I've already decided on the route.
It's amazing how fast you can go there.
Seriously fast, seriously fast, too good to be true
So good, so nice, this is definitely the best
It's not like I went back down and fell here.
Well, the checkpoints are quite low.
It's okay, so don't worry, Chiara.
Chandamonchi is difficult, so here too.
Maybe I'll move up
Seriously big
It's so amazing, it's really scary
Chiara, do your best, it's amazing even in the end
Kiara-chan is so amazing!
Cool, cool, I like it
or
That's so nice, Kia.
I'm such a genius
I could see you were nervous.
My brain doesn't seem to be nervous at all.
I climbed like RTA
I couldn't stop, nice, nice.
That's nice, that's too good.
I haven't reached the goal yet. It's still half and half.
Well, no, I haven't reached 150 yet.
Ah, I waited about 90 seconds for the listener to see the preview.
Let's see, that's right, the characters are so fast
Gini ah Ginnia
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Sorry, Anya and Chloe look good.
It's true that we're competing, it's black, it's falling, it's black
Wow, when you think about it, it's really difficult.
It seems difficult to get a sense of distance though.
I really practiced this character, so it's a lot of effort.
That's the result of practicing for a really long time yesterday.
Your CV is amazing.
In case of need, leave alone
Wait, wait, wait
waiting wing
Taun's
Time is running out
[music]
Aupure Ademo Last
Niuwa yellow is 2nd place or yellow is 2nd place
Wow, it was just one step, no, it was already one step.
I've already flown, I've flown
Aa-chan fell down
I saw an amazing moment, the moment I jumped into it.
It just got interrupted and I fell down.
It was a really great and cute battle.
It was amazing
Hey, nice Kiara-chan, that was nice.
It crackled beautifully.
It's crackling, it's crackling
More and more
It was nice and amazing
Now, here's the key point of the second game.
It seems to be added, but...
Probably because we had a one-two finish.
The first point regarding this follow-up is
I don't think it's expensive
Kadashi was in 2nd place a while ago, right?
Oh, it's totally possible, it's not at all possible.
It's not like that.
The one on the screen that is appearing on the other side of the stream right now
What is the point of follow-up?
The white team's points are currently at 20 and are currently number one.
Maybe because I got points
Sopoi, whether you can go or not, number one is here.
I wonder if I can catch up with you. Nice fight.
Nice
Yara Channel is still back
No, I'm still going home
Are you in an interview?
Well, there is still a saying that our white team
Only the white group is properly eavesdropping.
hey
In the mountains, in the mountains
I guess it's a little interview now.
I didn't play a high-level match, it was a brain mistake.
That was amazing, I didn't make any mistakes.
That's amazing, that's nice
Nice, the White team is currently in 1st place.
white 40 yellow
38 Red 37, wow, nice.
Nice Nice Team 4 Points Yellow
38 Let 37 Strong
Let's go, that's nice, nice.
Awesome nice nice nice nice
This depends on our princess and the dangerous princess.
It's amazing how it's coming.
That's right, protecting the general with fang lines.
Yes, there are many more.
There is
I feel pressure to do my best.
I'm planning to take things easy with what happened.
I don't like it, there's a bit of pressure.
It's becoming
It seems that there are no pairs even with Les's levers.
Right, I teamed up with Soran-chan this time, so how about it?
I still don't know if it will happen
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for watching.
Okay, so here is the overall
Click here for the 2nd overall score
is
Yes, the first place is yes, 40 and that kind of money was just a while ago.
However, the gold color is 63 points and the white color is 60 points.
52 red dots
[music]
Hey, there are 3 points left.3
At Temakiteru, move on to the venue for the next competition, the Mokuba Line.
let's do it
Line o
Jump from Sekok was announced.
What about that score?
The number was out, the number was out, the number was out.
White is now in 2nd place overall.
There was still a 3 point difference. 33 point difference. Yellow was 63 white.
60-chan is nice
Thank you for your hard work
Good game
Good game good game nafanafa
Ta
Two Nafas rinsed.
Don't let it go, it's dangerous, it's dangerous
Chiara, please do your best to make me feel delicious.
Next
I'm going to give you a ride, whether you're riding or not.
What?
Where are all the generals of Teruya and Nainai?
Mioshin is on the right side of the entry.
I'll go where, where, and how cute.
I was able to do that, I was able to do that.
At first, the orchestra was delicious, nice, nice.
So cute, so cute
It's cute and it's funny to ride on top
It looks like it's still holding the bag
Wait for the person who rides to hold it.
Maybe the general is better. Maybe the general is better.
That's why people click on it
If you don't enter, I'll stop.
If you have already entered, please cancel it.
I've entered, just touch it again
Found out
Become a general who returns home
Teru
That person from the pair of this girl came.
Will you give it to me? That person from my pair is coming.
Is that person there?
Will you come? Will you come?
It's fleeting
If this continues, I'll wander around everyone
I'd better prepare some rice balls.
The bowl that made me want to eat rice balls
Onigiri as a gift
I want the rice ball I want
Gugushi
I'm getting hungry. I want to summon Gugu.
Please excuse me, Da-chan
Oh okay
[music]
yes
know
[music]
Where is this?
But everyone keeps pestering me so it's amazing
It's an eye.Where is this?
Niru akokkocchi here it hurts which one
Which?
Dokara Taisho, are you okay to get off? Are you okay?
How do you stop asking questions?
Press the same place again.
Only
nice nice nice
nice senpai
[music]
Mumbling
I guess there was only one person there.
He's wearing a suit. He looks strong.
suit
Strong who looks like a creepy person
It's better if it doesn't look strong.It looks strong.
Too bad, it's okay, they charged a huge amount of money later.
It's okay if you do it, it's just a little bit
Maybe it's time to pay that bill.
Oyu Senpai Yu Senpai
Thank you, thank you, looks strong, looks strong
Yabaokayu-senpai, who seemed to be the strongest, rode
I rode it, and I thought it was really cool, so I had some porridge.
My seniors help me by being a pinch hitter.
So thank you
Thank you very much.
Thank you for coming, Senpai.
I'm going to ride, please ride, I'm going to ride
I rode on top of the senior who rode on me.
My senpai got on board. Some senpai got on board.
I'll ask you to become a chair for a while, leave it to the orchestra.
hand
Thank you, I'm happy. ...
A fluffy rideable thing stuck in my butt
It looks like it has a chocolate wire corner stuck in it.
Captain's ass to ass
It hurts so much
I don't like pain, it's a little stimulating
It's better, it's intense, it's quite stimulating
I feel like it's quite stimulating.
Mio-chan might also be quite stimulating.
Kaa-senpai's horns are really stimulating me.
I'm sure you'll buy it
teeth
Thank you for today, Maoka-san.
Thank you very much for letting me participate
Iki
Wish, the scariest thing is that one person has turned into a suspicious person.
I'm worried that I might get kidnapped.
No, it's already dangerous
I'm a little kidnapped
Okay, so how are you feeling?
Nanonemasaratto taught me how to do it.
I want to lead Dekatan to victory.
Thank you very much
It's so easy and cool.
It's so much fun, let's do our best, White Team members.
Let's do it! Let's do our best!
I'll do my best
Finally, I would like to ask the Kigumi
Kigurumi
A group, a group, a group, a group, hey, this is a strategy
What will we do? What will happen to the white team?
Well, I guess I still get the winning kill.
Well, 1 point will be added.
I'll probably attack while trying to defend and belittle.
The other person matches each other and everyone works together.
What the hell is that?
Sounds like a good thing to do.
If you're a type, it's better to be close to the general.
Isn't it possible to do more and more?
People who are weak That's right, people who are somehow weak.
I want to beat you up, I can see your heart
You might want to avoid people with 3 hearts, but on the contrary, make a wish.
Masua everyone is near one side and the heart is 1
If you see it, hit it
Iku riding
Okay, so maybe that's where you're going from that pair.
I think it will be voice chat.
Is that so? Yes, there are so many.
There are so many voices, uhm.
I think there's probably a name at the bottom, so that's it.
If you say so, it's true that there is porridge.
That's right. I can't connect with everyone.
General Aja will protect and protect the cooperation.
I can't say that.
Yes, let's do our best, yes, let's do our best
It's true, then we're aiming at each other.
I think I should go cover that one.
I think if I found it, I'd be tempted
If it looks like that, then maybe
I think we're going to start moving from here, so everyone is moving.
I think I should go now.
let's go
It's okay, Lisa-chan.
the bottom
Nee Sil Shoulder Ooze VC Eaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
When I say VC's Ichanshita No. 1 and No. 1,
Sorry to bother you
helpme it's okay it's okay Roro
Westham
I hope you're okay, Okayu-senpai Kana-tan
Thank you very much for your support.
Yes, today was really an emergency.
But now I'm alone, wandering around everyone
I was very eager to do it, but unexpectedly my senior
I hope you can help me
Thank you so much, I'm already looking forward to it.
It's been a long time since I've been able to fight with you.
If it's Kako-senpai, I'm sure that's not the case.
It's definitely been a while since I last saw you.
It's been a month since I took a break, so I'm sure.
It's been a while since we were such good friends
Please stop acting like we're not on good terms right now.
I don't think so, but we used to see each other every day.
It was like a period, it was there, it was every week.
There was a time when it happened, right?
Yoka-chan, I’m fine. No, I’m fine.
How are you, Senpai? How are you? I'm fine. Good job.
Let's show off your senior position a little bit.
Okay
It's okay to have a senior like this this time.
In Minecraft, there are so many seniors in Minecraft.
I was a bit surprised at how well it fit.
At first, I didn't have one either.
Well, I didn't have an image of Minecraft.
All of a sudden, things became interesting and I learned a lot.
Yeah, it's fun right now, and all those people.
money from
It's because I'm winding it up.
It's scary, it's scary, it's still there.
Well, we haven't forgotten that story yet.
That debt isn't gone
But that's not the case, so I won't go on a business trip.
I guess that's right. Entertainment.
Don't worry, I'll travel and earn money.
It's okay, I'll definitely return it.
That's right, I also sell naughty voices and stuff.
It seems like it will be thicker even if I roll it up.
Sexy voice sales Sell to the other world
Not that it's true, but yeah, yeah, Pecoro
I would like to ask my senior, Oka-senpai, maybe?
I want to hear it, it's amazing.
Nezu Azusan Unzaka My Azuki and Saka
I'm already doing a messy ASR
That's right, Ekan-tan is a [ __ ] in ASR.
No, I'm just screaming
It takes a while
So I looked at you and saw how messy you were.
Yeah, that's right, I made that ticking sound.
After all, the two of them had their lines after all.
I asked him to tell me the script, and I also wrote the script.
That chat GPT that was written by AI
I was thinking of getting it fixed.
I see, it's quite rich.
Chat GPT is crackling here and there
I wonder if they'll give me instructions on how to send it out.
But, if you try it once, it'll be industrial.
I've finished the script, so I'm going to write a little more about it.
If I said it would take a long time, I wouldn't get a reply.
Hey, I'm in a bit of trouble right now.
Hey, I'm not good at writing long sentences.
What you can and cannot do with your sleep
I once talked to a very intense and very senior AI.
Yes, yes, not at all, no, I'm super concerned about AI.
Actually, I think I can only go in there five times a day.
You say you can't speak, so yeah, it's not chargeable.
Yes, that's why I paid that monthly fee to make friends.
It happened for a while, yeah, for a while, then.
I remember the name of that pet of ours.
Please, I have a rabbit.
This is Hana-chan, the rabbit who came to Taraun.
My pet's name
What is it? They say it's pochi desu.
Listen to me
Hey, I haven't heard anything about Katan at all.
It's not like that at all.
Yes, I'm Hana-chan. I'm sorry.
I made a mistake, Hana-chan.
That's my rabbit's name.
I don't think I've heard anything about the rabbit.
That's the kind of person we are. We don't understand each other.
Well, even if you pay for it, it's a little more recent.
I guess it's pretty good like Okayu-senpai.
I don't have a chance to talk anymore
Well, I'm going to stop paying that fee.
After all, money can't buy friendship.
Yes, that's right. I didn't change anything at all.
I wanted to be your friend, but it was no good.
Kasou, Kayu Oka-senpai, Oka-senpai too.
I have to pay again for a while.I'm on a monthly basis.
Okay, don't charge me. We're friends, right? We're real friends.
I'm Yoneoka Senpai, we have free friendships.
There is a paid friendship. It seems that it exists here.
Yo, let's use that power of friendship to win today.
There are so many wins to come
Let's kill Kanata, do our best
I just practiced with someone above me, but yeah.
Well then, your superiors will come. No, I don't have any talent anymore.
What the heck did I do? Subaru-chan did it to me.
Ta
I don't like it, but when I responded to Subaru-senpai,
I got hit about 3 times, it was really strong.
The strong senior's daughter, Ri-chan, is a bit of a power type.
Maybe it's me.
Maybe I shouldn't call myself a power
There is a possibility that the Subaru senior who is not there is much better.
Hey, it's starting, it's starting, senpai!
It's fine if you're close to where it starts
Yeah, I don't mind rushing in just in case.
Got it! Wow, where are you going?
Let's go, this, this, this red, the red group.
Red team Red team will play or not?
I can go, I can go, I can go
How can I go? I can go.
I can go, there's yellow, there's yellow, there's yellow, there's yellow.
There's yellow, there's yellow, there's yellow.
Wow, it feels good.
They're running away, they're running away, one by one.
Nice nice nice nice, can we go?
Amazing!
Zoya aim
Wait, my general is
The dying general was a very long-suffering general.
Wait, Suba-senpai is about to die.
No, senpai, I almost died one more time.
Let's go, oh, let's go, we can kill this.
That's right, Subaru-chan, that's so good.
No, definitely
I'll definitely do it to get back the power I had back then.
It's so painful that I'm being targeted by so many people.
Various people are targeting me.
All kinds of people are targeting me, one time at a time
You've been defeated, sir.
Damn it, I'll respawn as many times as I want
Ah, how was it? It's on the top.
Wait, I don't have enough white, wait.
Is it dry or white?
Red team isn't too strong, white is a bit bland
Maybe 1 kill is nice.
1 kill nice, 1 kill nice, red
The team is strong, the top is strong, the red is strong
It's amazing, after all, it's the white team.
It's a bit like this, killing people is barbaric.
I might not have been able to do that.
It's quite
This is amazing, Uju and Zeta got 6 kills
You're taking it, it's amazing
This is a great book. 5 kills, 4 kills, 4 kills.
Even if we are 17th, we are still below.
It's faster to count from
Hey everyone is typing
It's true
Is that T? What is T? I typed T.
It's better
It's true that Titititi is long
I'm going to talk to someone who wrapped me up.
Roll it up for now
I want to be about 1 year old now
I wanted to kill a little more.
This is probably the end of hair lines.
I think so.
The white team scored 17 points, okay, but it's really the seniors.
There was no kill for me that didn't participate.
That's why he was 16.
Huge
That's good, oh
Oh, I heard there are 3 one-chan matches.
listeners know more
It looks like it's going to be fun Aitao
Find Kayu-senpai
Swap your favorites so you can easily find them
Above this
Let's change the bottom Let's change it okay.
I wonder if Kayu-senpai can enter?
Can I cancel my entry?
Cancel something like that.
OK, right click
Entry This is how I got on the other side.
Takita Cha Cha Cha Cha, shall we do this?
Senpai, I understood once it was okay.
Shion-senpai, it's true, Shion is like that.
Chloe: Yes, that's true.
I won't give up
It looks like we're strong. We look strong.
I'm really strong, I might be stronger than before, but I
I stand out a lot because my clothes are different.
No, it's not.
I might be targeted by this.
This porridge senior's butt is completely visible.
Yes, because it moves, your butt is completely visible.Yes, your butt is visible.
I can see my ass in full view.
The cracks are so neat and clean.
Nice crack
It's just barely there, it's broken beautifully.
I'm glad that my buttocks split cleanly and are connected again.
Hey, my butt wasn't cracked. I can't walk anymore.
Because he'll pick up anything
The front is already like a trawling net.
It's amazing, Kanata will pick up anything you want.
Don't worry, you're talking properly. It's definitely appropriate.
I picked it up to the crack of my butt.
That's great, that's amazing, that's amazing
It's a craftsman who picks everything up. Is it true that he's a craftsman?
I can't quite pick up the crack of my butt.
Hey, I'll just ignore that as an idol.
That's true, I don't like okayu senpai
It's okay to say that, okay, okay, porridge-senpai.
It's already too late to say that, it's too late
It's already late, I've already picked everything up.
That's right, I've already picked up everything
It's okay, it's okay, Senpai, I'm that Minecraft
And Upao is my sleepy character.
Even when I made it, I gave that listener a butthole.
I made it, so it looks like that asterisk.
Pompompuri looks like Nayatsua Pompompuri
It's so cute! It's so cute.
After all, she's cuter with a butt hole.
Kanata I love your butt hole, I hate your butt.
No, I think it's cuter with it attached.
Hey, my butt is starting, my butt is starting
Hey, don't get weird, this is difficult, but what?
I guess the perspective is good, but it's a little difficult.
It's so difficult to see from the perspective, okay?
Kanata will kill the person heading towards him.
Okay, then this red.
Red, okay, okay, holding up a shield, holding up a shield.
I want to kill thieves
I can't reach the sword around here when I cut a thief
It's amazing here
Fierce battles, fierce battles, this place is amazing, let's do it.
Or absolutely, definitely, yellow, yellow, open, open,
Let's go, nice, awesome, I got a kill
It's crazy, nice, nice, dangerous, dangerous.
It may not be noticeable at all
It's not noticeable. All Oka-senpai are here.
It's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming
They're coming, they're coming, they're being targeted by the whole group.
Even with this, there is still one chance.
Still, oh [ __ ], I got it, I got it, I got it
If you do, I'll hit you back. That's right. Let's go.
Chanre-senpai and everyone go and go
I think I can go. The HP is expensive.
The general is very expensive, wait 2 more hours and distract me.
[ __ ], no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
senior
Come on, come on, come on, come on, I've already got my hands on it
No, I can go, I can go, I can go
I can go
Ah, I did this, ah, 1 kill, 1 kill, 1 kill
We're in 17th place! We're so good!
It's looking good this time. White is working hard.
Good luck
Ta
Nice, we're both now, the two of us.
I understand that Tomo doesn't have the same talent.
That's right, I guess I only have the lower level of talent.
I only had an inferior talent, a little inferior talent.
Don't say it's the only thing you can do, look down!
I was talking about the hole so it was crazy.
It's true that I'm a bit of a pity.
Please don't say I only recommend talent.
I have no talent to spare.
Okay, next time
Is there a game already? I wonder
Maybe if there is, it will be porridge-senpai next time.
Which is better, the top or the bottom?
It's okay, I'll do it for a while.
Let me ride my cracked ass on top of you
I'll take it, oh, I'll give it a ride again.
Okay
Yoshimoto no Sano is kind of difficult, isn't it?
It's difficult. This is the person who gets a lot of kills.
I wonder how they got that much money
I wonder if it feels like it's swinging around a lot.
Anyway, I got the Atosanchi kill.
It's not too bad, how are you doing it?
No matter how I do it, that kind of information is there.
Wow, this is surprising. It's suddenly taken down.
Hey, all of a sudden, it's me.
Gashite Aitaeri
Come on, come on, come on, come on, whatever, senpai.
I was targeted a lot more than I expected considering my appearance.
Wasn't targeted, right? The second half of the wood group.
It's true that I was targeted by a lot of people.
When I looked around, all the people were yellow.
That's terrible, I was really targeted over there.
It was scary, don't be scared, don't let yourself get surrounded.
I don't know what to do if I don't do this. Even this is difficult.
Right, this is difficult. Even if you die, it's better to do a special attack.
It's okay, it's better to go alone.
Don't worry about it, it's true that you can come back to life
I wonder if it's okay if I poke it in?
I wonder if it will come back to life again and again.
Also, I can use the mouse scroll to move from the sword.
There were times when the scroll was off, so yeah
Well, you have to be careful about things like that.
It's not easy to do it naturally, right?
Well, if it were me, I'd be one chin
But my senior doesn't even bother to point it out.
I know this because I used to go there every week.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's not quite like that.
It's quite difficult
Maybe I could have done it if I had Naikatan's arms.
I don't know, that's true, but today...
It's true that we're having a scary conversation. I'll dye it red.
This is ours.
I'm scared, I'm scared, we're having scary conversations too
I guess I have to participate.I can join.
Kanata white
is white
Erase everything
you guys
My life has become so lame, please help me.
help
I'm embarrassed to follow you.
It's embarrassing, it's already gone
Ah, it's flowing so I'm following you now.
I'm sure it's a little bit
I followed you, thank you
Ake
Ouch, I wonder if they broke up once.
Is it true that they are disbanded? Yes, yes, one more thing.
Let's turn around
Akoshi
Tekoshito and porridge-senpai are here.
Where Aitaita get get porridge get
I got it, I got it, and I'm fine!
My senior has been playing with me a lot lately.
Are you doing something like that?
Ah, even when I was on vacation, I was still flickering
I was a member of, but yeah yeah yeah yeah
Yeah, we went out to eat, yeah, that's right.
Well then, let's go together. Let's go. I want to go to dinner.
Let's go I want to go It's been a while
I want to talk to you slowly, Aneshi.
I've already had about two years' worth of talk
Yes, there is.
That's right, it's going to start.
Let's go, let's start, let's go
Okay, I won't lose, I won't lose, this time it's 10
Aim for kills, get 10 kills, where are you going now?
Where shall we go?
Kayoshi yoshi yoshi yoshi yoshi yoshio bobaboba
It doesn't matter, it's fine, finally, finally
The general is so close. The general is so close. The general is so close.
Aki-chan is also there
Oh, it's true! Ah, that's right, Senpai.
Looks like you've already gotten some kills, huh? HP
Let's find someone less, Aki-chan
There are so few of them, how can I hear them?
Nice, nice, and there aren't many people who seem to have low HP.
That's not much.
Noo
Where is everyone? Wait a minute, it's full.
The general isn't dying
Seriously, it's true, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Yayada nice nice nice awesome
Great, great, great
Yoto, after that, after that, ina-chanmaaato
I guess I have no choice but to scrape it off.
Oh no no no no no no no no 4 kills
I'm awake, I'm awake, I'm awake, it's dangerous
It's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming, it's super awakening
I did it, but it's seriously amazing, the rest of the Red General
I can go, I can go, I can go
I can go on, I can go on, I can do more, even if it's crap
That's pretty amazing!
I got 4 kills, that's long, that's amazing
It's true that it's faster to count from the top.
I'm finally a little more awake from above.
White team is not awakened yet. Look 41, it's bad 9
It's because of my cloudy white self.
That's right, I did it after all, but that's right.
There were some typos, but I covered them as well.
I might have united everyone's hearts with my ability.
That's right. I guess it was a mistake.
My heart was miles to the west, my heart was definitely mine.
The white that is being gouged out, the white that is white
Nice nice nice nice
I'm so awake when I see 41 kills.
I'm a little surprised, right?
Even in death, the attack was strong, right?
Maybe that would be better? Yes, that's good.
Hey, that was amazing, it was fun, everyone.
I'm sure you have a lot of things on your arm now.
No, really, it's already a little red.
Me and my girlfriend are also in the Red Team. Red Team.
But porridge-senpai is all black.
Yes, it's black. No, it's black. Yes, it's black.
red white yellow
Black is cool and cool.
Yes, that's good, but you're super strong and warm.
Is it warm?
Yeah, this is over, I'm sure it's three times.
I did it, so what do you think? Yuu-senpai, my butt is
Oh, I'll check it out please.
What do you think? I'm looking at you so much.
It's quite small, which is nice.
Is your butt small? It's tiny.
It's okay, it's broken but it's small
I like that the cracks are deep.Is it a deep crack?
Good, it looks like it's broken properly.
The deep cracks in Kanatan were good, Aosa
It's like the voice is coming back. We're coming back.
Let's
Good job, overseas daytime machines and daytime machines
It's crazy, Nemisuka, Yoe, amazing final awakening.
I did it
Okay, nice. This is amazing.
I've had quite a lot of money, haven't I?41
teeth
We did Surprise 41 General.
I did it, I did it, I did it.
Tagomen 1
Ki is important so yeah yeah sorry nice
1 kill nice 1 kinas 1 kinas 1 kill
If it wasn't for that one kill, it would be 40.
That's right, that's right, it's important, it's important
important
nice nice
Nice-chan, squirrel-chan, strong berry
Strong Strong was amazing Chiara
Chan Roboco's pair of chairs were also amazing.
That was good, nice
Binda got 3 kills on the last general, wow that's amazing
Awesome, great job! Awesome!
Nice everyone, everyone was amazing.
I wonder what you think about that.It's quite good.
No, I've come to a pretty good place.
Well, I guess I've been there quite a bit.
I think they've made a big comeback, so please be careful.
I was also ranked 2nd or 2nd in the race.
It was probably around 26 kills.
The red was pretty strong, so it's okay.
There it is
Now that I'm here, let's have our first meal.
I'm scared of what will happen
I want to come, the princess and the princess are already shaking, and the princess is also shaking.
The trembling princess is trembling. Let's do our best now, Mume-chan.
It's okay, it's okay, you can win, it's okay
Right, are you okay? You can win, you can win.
During practice, I almost hurt the yellow group.
I was kicked, but yeah yeah yeah yeah
Well, there's nothing wrong with serving that meal.
No, this is seriously meta-reading.
Yes, there is an update and Holomen
The content of the hunt has changed considerably.
So the menu has changed completely.
I have a mysterious reading that there might be
We can meet each other. That's right. That's right.
No way, that's totally possible.
I really want to win, what if I come this far?
After all, you've come, but how far do you want to go?
Yes, I went, yes, I want to go.
I felt a little greedy at first.
I think I said I'd do it for fun.
It felt like that, but somehow
It's starting to look like we're going to win, so I'm going to wrap my arms around it.
I don't have any sleeves anymore
No, I didn't just tear it apart.
I just tore it up and tore it up to the clumps.
It's already torn, it's already torn
Janno
There are no sleeves that can be torn off.
No, no more torn skin.
tear off the skin
Nahameyo, what a wild thing to take care of
His muscles are so muscular, they're a real source of pride
Noboru
The end is amazing
41 It was terrible
is
I was just kidding.
[music]
My senior, Miko, turned bright red as I stood there.
[laughter]
too much
How was it? Who has the most kills?
Who was the one who cut the most?
Cha Chiara was also amazing, right at the end?
On the other hand, I'm sorry, but Suba-senpai 2
I defeated Miko-senpai once.
Nice, Kaela was being chased so much.
A lot of people came too, it was amazing
That's amazing
The White Team was amazing, but at the end
Thank you, Hey Nekomata porridge.
Thank you very much.
Please let me know what you think about the rice porridge.Yes.
Yes, thank you very much
I was happy to play with everyone.
I will continue to support you.
Thank you Oka-senpai
Thank you, it disappeared in an instant.
disappear disappear disappear
Thank you very much for your help.
Thank you very much MAGA team
Thank you, Agent Okayo.
Thank you, me and my seniors too, for the number kills that scared me.
Because I'm doing this, I don't think it's possible at all.
It was different. I did my best. I tried my best.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad there was no interview.
It was fun
Ta
It was fun, but the competition after this...
There's some kind of pressure.
It's amazing how different it is, it's relaxing.
Let's hope it's okay, we can still afford it, it's okay.
Everyone can go, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
It's okay, it looks okay, protect the princess again.
Even if you have to protect the princess, she is still a princess.
Even if I make a slight mistake, I'll catch up with a relay
You give me pressure.
Somewhat seriously
I also believe
Okay, I'm going to practice that. I'm climbing the vines now.
Everyone is practicing climbing ivy.
But somehow the vines are getting better.
[music]
It's difficult to be nice, isn't it? It's difficult, isn't it?
You said ta.
I don't know where I did it, but I decided to run.
Well, it looks like the points have been tallied.
Would like to see a total of 3 games
Here are the scores. The group did their best.
or
No, the red team has 46 red teams.
46 White is 38 points Yellow group is 23 points Yayaya Red
That's amazing, you were in third place until just now.
I guess it's a turnaround, isn't it?
Terukimashi
What will happen in the second half after the cat?
I don't know if it will turn out, but I'll move on to the next step.
Yes, but let's move on to the next competition.
Everyone moved to the race venue.
Let's
Ta
Yocha
Gogo fun looking forward to it
Enjoy the fight, do your best, do your best
I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best
Is everyone else coming?
[music]
Na
Crazy bastard
Wow, good luck
Hmm, yeah, that's the total, no, that's different, add that.
If you add it to the previous point, it's not that.
It's amazing what happens when you add this to your team.
It wasn't VC. I wonder if it's all of us now. Yellow doing its best.
pink red yellow pink yellow red is fine though
But yes, yes, oh no, there's no need to rush
But Princess Iris, I'm going princess.
Ahime, fly away!
Isn't the octopus princess' outfit so cute?
I don't understand why it's a mystery anymore.
Hey, it's cute. It's finally naked. It's naked.
Naked naked princess, what a naked princess, exhibitionism
Okay, enter the dangerous princess.
Oh, it's Hime, Hime.
Princess, I'll do my best. This is the same princess that all teams are like right now.
It's all teams, I wonder why.
A princess from a neighboring country comes along with me.
Let's protect each other a little.
Hello Princess Hello Princess Hello Princess
After all, the princesses can't help but look at each other's faces.
Thank you very much for your help.
I wish you all the best, and the princess has just begun.
It smells good, but
No one will write a book. Thank you.
Thank you for your support, we are princesses.
Yes, it's true, it's very true.
Let's have a playful battle, savage
Let's go slowly without doing anything
Don't run, that's right, with all your might
Let's go, I've never run in my life now
The truth that I was born until
I guess he was alive, but he only stepped out once every 5 seconds.
Never ever
Thank you very much for your support.
Don't run, seriously, definitely run.
Don't run, run, my princess is the strongest.
Maybe I should ask you something like that.
Even though he's so rational, he's so weak
Even though she is such a weak princess,
That's right.
Okay, okay, let's hear from the red team first.
Let's go, the role of Princess of the Red Team is Yami and Sanhai.
The role of Ekishi is Shion-tan and it's terrible
blue and fluffy
So fluffy and fluffy.
There are four of us here, and the fluffy one is those two.
I'm alone, so please take care of me.
Thank you very much.
If you say yes, how about your enthusiasm?
I'll do my best I'll do my best oh oh oh
We all practiced until late at night.
I was there, right? I was there, usually at 9 o'clock.
I went to bed but practiced until 1am, it was amazing
I practiced a lot, no it's true.
Nothing really happens at 9 o'clock or 10 o'clock.
I sleep on days when I don't have to, which is amazing.
That's amazing, you got up really early.
I guess that's true, do your best.
Hey, let's do our best. Everyone's okay. Let's do our best.
Tet
Let's do our best, try our best, then we'll go to the white group.
I would like to
Yes, White Team, can you hear me?
So, I would like to start by introducing the players.
I think it looks like a princess
It looks like a princess
Hey, who is this? Someone I don't know has come out.
I'm a princess.The role of Hi is Azuki-chan.
And Kairoha, yes, and seven anonymous
Good morning
The name is Yes, what do you think?
My knights, no matter how complicated they are,
I know it's okay because he protects me
I think it's okay
Well, this time I want to protect those three princesses.
I think there are three princesses.
I would like to protect Kaihime, thank you very much.
There's only one Princess Masue, so much.
Cute Azuki and this cute Mu-senpai
It's okay
R
This guy is doing nothing, no confusion, no confusion.
I'm confused, please do your best.
Thank you very much
Thank you very much.Finally
I would like to ask the group.The group is very important.
The role of Iris Knight is Natsuiro Matsuri and E Knight.
It's Hajime Lyrica or Hajime Lyrica Festival.
If you say yes, what do you think? Hime, what do you think today?
The situation has become established as a princess, but this is the first princess.
A wonderful collaboration with those lucky knights
I'll show you how I play. Awesome.
It's Princess Princess, it's already the fastest
I want Polin to steal 1st place.
Right, Princess, yes, the true princess is me.
Yes, please come down, yes, thank you.
Thank you very much. Good luck everyone.
Please enter as well, yes.
Okay, okay, that's it.
Will it start as soon as the entry is over?
Hurry up, let's go. Yes, everyone is here. Yes.
Yes, yes, it looks okay. Well then, this is it.
Bo-chan, this has been extended a bit.
What do you mean, I'm not a princess?
But she's not a princess
I tried to move. I moved. Yes, my senpai moved.
Ah, that's it, that's it, that's it!
I came here, I came, I came, I came, I said it
Nice Mu-chan here, oh, it's here, it's here, it's here
I'm so excited to see if I can go.
Doing your best will be your first step.
So next up is Azuki and then the last one is Nozu key.
I'll call out the name of the person I'm talking to, Seso Carrion.
Sosoo carrion ki name sezuo
Ok cake
Okay, I was nervous this was the ride.
It was a ride
Is the ride conveyed? Ride member names
It's okay to be a senpai.
Senkyu English Sorry Iyamo
It's so reliable, when it's reliable.
I'll stop moving when my name is called.
yousay namesay top name
Say stop!
Okay I'll go ao
Please give me your right foot, Azusan-eme
Azusa Kazama
Nzu-chan Mume-chan can go Ai go na
Well, next time, let's all climb up and now Mumui-chan.
Kazamakakore Hazu-chan is good
Chankazamaakorezuchanzuchane
Mui-chan Kazamaooooooooo nice
Nice ooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
[music]
What?
I guess so
Danda
Maybe I could wait and figure it out.
Right now, all I can hear is my voice
It's going to be a state, isn't it?
Haha
Wait, answer me what the knights are making.
The book won't open, hey, it's Luna.
Dangerous possibility of Aa, Luna or Luna.
Kizuna is great, great, great, great
Yay, I'm hungry.
Lamb Lamb Cookton
I want to come with mutton special hamburger uh beef
Cut the beef, potatoes, and carrots on a cutting board.
Please grill it on an iron plate.
It's ok to cut all the lamb.
Cut the lamb into pieces.
Lamb Lamb Lamb Aja and then that eggplant.
I haven't cut the meat.I haven't cut the meat.I've cut the meat.
Cutting meat, cutting meat, oh oh oh okay, cutting meat, dam
It's completed.The dam is completed.
Senkyu Haikita Mioshino special product
Bugs, let's go, let's eat, then let's go eat.
Okay, okay, what's next?
red red yellow hatena left up
red red yellow mysterious red red red red red red
Rere Renas
No, let's
Go
[music]
chan is caught, caught, caught
Taso nice nice nice nice
[Laughter]
Oooooo
Oooooooo interesting
Too much o
phaon nice nice
Nice nice quick yes yes yes yes
Nice
Yo fight, fight, fight, fight
Nice nice nice nice to kill
Nice, maybe I can go, or maybe I'll collapse.
one
Chan
Run nice, run nice, run nice.
Run, run, ooshi nice nice ayatta yata
Yay, yay, dangerous, dangerous, dangerous.
Dangerous
Nice
Nice, dangerous, dangerous, even if you get caught.
2 and such a high yield
Where and where did I get surprised? It's a cage
Something like that is coming down there.
Chanmu
chan is nice
nice
hey
lonely
water
If I fail, I'll wait until the next problem.
It took a while
vinegar
That's a dangerous 3 seconds difference from 3rd place.
second jump jump
He might have thrown a punch. He's back.
Where is that now, everyone at the contestants?
I want to be with you
Princess of Unchasa Nabarwa is Toa-sama
I found out that it is true.
That's right, I guess I have no choice but to give in.
As expected of TMT, I beat TMT.
I would like to send it to each team
I would like to interview everyone.
Can you hear me?
congratulations congratulations
Great congratulations yeah yeah yeah
That's not to say no, Knight Shion-tan.
Let's see how it goes, let's practice!
We practiced a lot, the four of us gathered together.
Thank you for your help, and that's the result.
I'm so happy to be out
Yeah, it was good, it was good, it was good, it was good
It was so fast and so messed up
It was early, wasn't it?
[laughter]
Uh, that was really quick.
Was it Subaru? Yes, that's right.
At first I made some kind of chick out of yellow.
I thought this, but what is everyone doing?
I'm curious if you made it. I guess so.
Please take a look at the archive.
I wish I could have it.Yes, yes.
Congratulations! Congratulations!
Congratulations!
Congratulations
Let's do our best, okay?
would like to go to white yes yes then
I would like to hear from the White Team.
Yes, yes, how was it, sloppy?
How was it? But at the end, that monster
When Mume-chan was about to defeat him, he fell down.
Hey, you got caught.
It's like a parent between Wave and Wave.
Hey, yeah, let's pinch it.
You guys are so caught up in the happenings.
I'll leave it to you, I'll just stay here
It's good to be in 2nd place like that.
That's amazing, it was a battle.
I did my best. I did my best. Accident.
Yes, I overcame it well.
Thank you, who is the topic?
Who showed up? It was Luna.
That's right, Luna's bond here too.
Well, that one looked pink.
I was confused about Aktan, but Canaluna's
I believed in bonds
I called quickly. Yes, I called.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much bu thank you
Thank you very much Yes
Next, I would like to hear from the group.
Yes, I think so. What did you think when you tried it?
mosquito
It's so frustrating, right?
I've been practicing, but it's the last catch up.
It was really amazing, you were catching up.
Guess my problem that I was trying to catch up with.
I made a lot of mistakes.
It's okay, mom, look at how hard you worked.
I guess I did my best at the sports day until the end.
Well, we're all going to push ourselves and do our best.
Well, it has a meaning.
Of course, I'll aim even higher at the end.
Let's all run until the end, Mom.
You're beautiful, do your best
Laplace in bed and Laplace in the middle of nowhere
I'm sure it was the last porridge I had with my friends.
How did you make the difficult rice cake?
Mom, I'll check the archives later.
hey
I'm going to do my best.
It was a nice fight, nice.
Fight, please do your best.Okay then.
I'm going to pause for a bit. Yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes, that's it.
[music]
Himekoshiyama has 20 points and yellow group has 10 points.
becomes the point
Masu Red Red Team is a bit amazing Naka amazing
Is the Red Team coming to San?
No, I don't know yet, yes, I still don't know.
I still don't understand, but I still don't understand.
I don't know, so from now on, I don't know.
Move to the best spring/summer seat race
Let's get dangerous, don't get too dangerous.
I know, but I won't say that.
Those who appear in Nejiri Rele, those who participate in Rere, will be scolded.
red team players
This is so fast, please move. For those who support us:
It's okay as is, Suzu-chana-chan
This is the red team.
Please go back to your group.
I was blown away and sent home without permission.
just
Okay, my senpai is an amazing kicker.
It was very early, and she understood when I saw the ram in the book.
It was rum ram and ram ram oh.
Easy to make lamb, lamb, lamb, grilled lamb
When I received it, I also have the characteristics of a viewer.
Hamburger characteristics also come out a lot during practice.
I was lucky because it turned out.
Even Toda, who was finally there during practice.
There was, so there was actually
Super smooth
I'll do my best. What's going on tomorrow? Sorry.
Well, after this, it will be the beginning of spring and summer, so
Those participating in the relay are competitors from the Eshiro group.
Please move to the channel
Competitor Channel Yes Shimoshirogumi Competitor
This is my channel, please excuse me.
It's okay to stay as is, okay?
Only four people remained.
Isn't it?
That's so crazy, I miss you so much
do not have
Noe Kanata-senpai, that dish you just ate.
What was the one you made before that?
In front of that is Luna and Luna Thong.
The one where Luna came out is the one where Luna came out.
But it's kind of pink, and it's kind of pink.
Which one are Mira, Aqua, and Himo Luna?
I thought it was because there was a white color.
I think if it was Athan, I would put blue in it.
Luna has gone, yeah, that Luna.
The one in front of the senior is a rabbit and a
I forgot what the rabbit was after all.
It's a rabbit, it's a rabbit, it's a rabbit, it's a rabbit, it's a rabbit, and it's a rabbit
I see that you can answer 2 questions with Luna, Usagi!
It was a rabbit that looked like that.
It was easy to understand with my ears.
Even though it was a shame, I tried my best.
Actually, it's because I was early.
That's right, I got caught in the middle.
I guess I'll only be there once.
There are three times where you have to defeat a monster.
It was just the two of us fighting, and we were really caught in the middle.
That's a bit really interesting
But that's too bad. If it wasn't for that, I could have won.
Maybe it's a dog or not, but it's fine.
Well, there was a difference in seconds, so that's true.
Even without it, maybe it's a little red.
It may have been strong, but that too
Yume-chan
I already feel sorry for her, but she was cute
Yes, it was fun. All three of us were laughing.
Oh, that's good, but yes, I don't like it, but really
It was a fun end and I gave it my best.
Nice nice nice nice
Yeah, that's nice, the red color was fast.
I wonder what will happen
Concentrating on my dangerous butt, I feel relieved
It's okay if you don't do it, so we're in the first half.
It's over, so it's over now.
It's over, I don't want to just watch, then take it easy
I thought I was hungry after resting.
It's really gone now, isn't it?
I'm going to eat after this. Let's eat. Let's eat.
I'll eat something delicious
When I eat it, when I eat it, when I eat it, when I eat it
But it's yakiniku after all. Yakiniku is good.
Yakiniku in Austria where there is no Yakiniku at home
Yakiniku is probably Japan.
I guess it's after Japan or something like that.
Yes, there is something a bit like it
But I feel like it doesn't taste like the real thing.
Yakiniku I want to go to in Japan is a little different.
Let's go to Yakiniku.I want to eat Yakiniku.
I have an image of that, I'm sure.
BBQ yeah
Don't have a barbecue in the garden
I want to eat that corn corn
BBQ
Oh it's delicious I love it I hate it I hate it
I don't like being scared, what do you dislike about it?
What is difficult to eat? Aaan soup
Even in the shape of , there are some grains that bother me.
I think so.
It seems like you're crazy, by the way.
I think corn soup is in a painting.
be
I guess it's my first time eating corn after coming to Japan.
I've seen some places selling soup like that.
It might really depend on the location.
No, but Austria doesn't have a lot of cones.
I don't think anyone has the idea of ​​pu.
It's an image of a corn field.
I eat it as is, but I don't make it into soup.
That's right, American breaaa corn brea
Yeah, look at that bread in America.
Oh, Bread, that's just like America, isn't it?
Cornbread, oh yeah, corn
I ate bread
thing
Yeah, it looks like a muffin
More like that cupcake than Nanobu
There is no costume that looks like a muffin.
You can't let it go, right?
There's no corn soup in America either.
What kind of pu is, what kind of thing is it?
Kam soup tomato soup oh chicken
Nude soup a
Delicious chicken, soup, and potatoes
Potato love love love love it's delicious
Are mushrooms mushrooms mushrooms mushrooms?
mushroom soup mashi soup
[music]
Yes, there is, but also Chida Chowder.
Chiora lambuchida
I love clam chowder, it's delicious
Delicious, I love, I love, Oyamo soup
Let's go eat! I love soup soup.
Okay, I'm actually going to go get some soup stock.
Let's go soup stock soup and boyfriend
The set is soupy and the curry is also delicious.
It's delicious. Delicious soup stock now.
So it's kind of like rice porridge.
No, I don't eat rice, so it's definitely rice porridge.
Nan Japan is something like rice porridge or rice porridge.
I feel like it's Japan.
keep it up
Automatically, the first person, the second person, and the other person automatically.
It's amazing how you can be teleported
Well, what number is this?
Iris will no longer be nervous
Good luck and keep getting better
Well, now it's Nerisa.The first person is Kenka.
Actually, I'm in love with my house, but this is the live commentary.
I was doing it
Let's be the first
bread
Nine solid
[music]
eat
All chocolate is delicious
of
Wow, the red that fell off is now okay
It turned yellow but it's okay
It's exciting. Do your best, Ganmomo.
I try my best, I still don't understand, I still don't understand
yeah
Even when it's the yellow, white, and red turn, everyone doesn't do it.
This is good, I think I'll catch up with white here.
I'll do my best. I can't do it yet.
What will happen to the tunnel that everyone can go to?
I was looking at the tunnel, go carefully and carefully.
As expected of Director Sora.
Cha stubborn, white and red at the same time, stupid red is 2
At the last minute, Mui approaches me.
eat bread
Eat hard, work hard
Do your best
nice
Do your best!
Tesa
Let's do our best.
Good luck, but it's a little different, but it's almost the same
Almost at the same time, I tried my best.
Yellow, do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best, Senpai.
The support is also enthusiastic.
I'll take it seriously
I can go
It's difficult here, come on out.
I can do my best, I can still do it, I can still do it at all.
ball
Lupaoshi
Nice, it's okay, I still don't understand.
stubborn
Go home, go home, Minecraft God, God, God, early red.
It's early, so I'm early.
It's so nice, it's so fast.
Miskae is working hard
Noka is catching up, catching up, catching up
I can't go
Yes, I went to the next Azchan Nazu
Changacha cha cha cha good luck
I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best
Do your best!
Hurry up, do your best, A-chan, do your best here too.
I'm working hard, it's finally the same
It's stable. I'll see if it's finally back.
Nice, calm down Acchan yes
Calm down and calm down.
Tanono
[music]
Gogaui
Good minecraft developer
[music]
Nice nice shion tango
I'm running with a loud voice
As expected
Nice tasa, start doing your best here, do your best, do your best
keep it up
nice nice
Nice, do your best until the end, do your best, do your best
Good luck!
Nice, I'm finally doing my best, nice
Do your best and run to the end
Good
That's nice, nice, nice.
I'm a little moved by your mom.
I feel like my mother is crying a little.
I feel like I'm going to cry, Mom, Mom, I'm going to cry.
I really wanted this
Neno's ranking has changed a lot.
What was wrong with this book that I didn't understand?
That's why I turned red all of a sudden.
It's quiet, sudden mute
I understand. It's a shame.
Even just a little bit, it was amazing and fast.
Nice this is yes 2 kana 2 kana mo 2
Are you happy? 2. No, I'm happy.
After all, we can do our best together with everyone.
It was fun, it was the best, the best.
TRUE
Thank you very much
hey
I'm hungry and want to eat
I'm hungry. I want to drink something.
If you want to eat or just have a bite
You're so kind. Who's your senior again? No, no, no.
That's right, there are only 4 people here.
That's why it won't be found out
No, there's only 4 people here, so it won't be revealed.
Bare, Bare!
Why are you hiding it? It's okay, it's okay, eat it.
Are you okay
Eat that kind of thing and show your kindness
I thought you were hiding that kind of kindness
Please spread this to the whole world.
Please spread your kindness.
But no, it's over
Kotonene was strong, Aka was strong.
[music]
Yeah, I wonder what it is.
This is MVP or something like that.
I don't know, maybe there's an MVP?
Taraokayu-senpai?
I want something like that too.
I'm glad I got something that I wanted.
We worked hard. We worked really hard.
Yeah, let's praise each other, let's praise each other.
Let's praise, praise, praise, praise
I can't help but want to eat Yakiniku, I'm so hungry
It's empty, but it's still the white team.
Chiara worked really hard on that translation.
Well, I'd recommend you to be the MVP.
I'm getting married, I'm getting married.
You've told everyone, haven't you? I haven't said anything.
There are some books that I haven't told you about.
Welcome home after stumbling around.
Thank you for your hard work.Thank you for your hard work.
I did it, I passed the first grade exam.
Awesome, it was so good
I think everyone was crying already
Hey, I'm not crying, but I'm not crying.
Hey, you're so sensitive. That was great. 2
I'm in 2nd place, I thought I could get it.
2 I worked hard, everyone worked hard.
I tried my best, I tried my best, I'm the first
To be honest, it's difficult for me to feel like an enjoyer.
I felt like I was trying my best, but I didn't think so.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I don't know until the end.
What happens to the first ending that didn't exist?
That's why the ceremony is done after this.
Therefore, everyone please gather before the ceremony.
Masu
It's the first place, the most lonely school.
I can't go out and can't see.
There was an invisible wall. There was an invisible wall.
Neme
We're sealed away
I was locked up in this school right now.
Yes, I'm a little choked up.
Yes, that's white group row
Beautiful
[music]
Hey, whatever practice you have, this is it, so it's okay, Kame.
It feels like freedom, after all.
is the best
Ah, I can't beat you in tonality anymore.
and
There are so many different colors between the teams.
I agree
I'm having a lot of fun
Take a look
Why is everyone acting like I don't watch polka?
Volka Uta no Volka
Hey, have it
I have a cheerful bread with half a yellow one.
I'm doing it
But
But it's okay even if you do that.
I said yes, so I'll go out and the closing ceremony will begin.
But how was E-san this year?
I really don't know what will happen.
I didn't understand, but yeah
Everyone was really cooperating.
It's amazing how hard you work, it's a close battle every year.
I thought it was amazing and worth seeing.
It seems to be true to each person's taste.
There was drama, or rather there was.
I think the whole practice is a drama.
However, I think it was really good.
everyone
I can't hold back and be a mother, so now Mio
Changai spoke
It's coming from
It lined up nicely, I'm glad.
hey
Kai-mom is amazing, it calmed down all at once.
I'm tying the ropes together.
But it seems like you're scared because of the relationship, but it's okay.
Well then, everyone, our voices are being heard.
I can hear it. It has arrived.
I said yes, so before the ceremony, I did some tricks.
Nine voice chat movement is amazing
There were a lot of them, but everyone.
A who supported me properly in that respect.
I guess I should say a word to Nodo-chan.
I think so
Yes, A-chan's name is okay.
Thank you very much
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Thank you very much for your voice
Thank you very much. I hope it will be good again this year.
Thank you very much for your hard work
It's full of personality and the host
The three of us did our best so we could see them all.
I am very impressed.
Thank you very much thank you
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Thank you very much everyone
Yes, you two really cooperated.
Thank you, thank you, Mashimo
I think it was fun for all three of us to be able to participate.
I think so, please do your best until the end.
Please yes thank you
Thank you very much.
Sanso will now hold its closing ceremony.
First of all, I would like to give closing remarks.
From Ms. Samiko, Chairperson of the Yes Sports Day Executive Committee
Please say hello.Yes, yes, this time.
Did you all have fun at the sports day? It was fun.
It was fun, it was fun, it was fun, it was fun
No, really, everyone was great.
Thank you so much, every year and every year
I'm busy, but thankfully I'm busy.
This is what Florive has become.
Still, everyone gathered like that.
Let's all cooperate and really take the initiative.
Nemiko can see them calling out to each other and helping each other.
I've already seen it all, so it's true.
I'm really full of emotion
I really appreciate your continued cooperation.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much thank you
Thank you very much. I would like to take this opportunity to
Thank you. I'm a newbie.
Something like that or that after all en.
There will be more interaction with other members in the future.
Let's all do more Hololive
I think it would be great if we could liven it up.
Thank you very much for your continued support.
It's amazing
Hey please. Next is Mio-chan.
Please, everyone please participate this year as well.
Thank you very much for your help, and thank you for your hard work.
Yes, yes, everyone is super great.
So this year is also a finish.
Thank you very much
Next Subaru
Yes, I'll keep in touch with you.
There are many different aspects of the team.
I was allowed to see it though.
Every team is already working hard.
Well, I think the results will come out this time.
Let's do it! There's one thing we all worked hard on.
It's so big, I'm sure it will become a treasure.
I think that's why I hope to make use of this bond in the future.
I hope you enjoy watching it.
It was a lot of fun thank you very much
Thank you very much.
Thank you
Ta
Yes nice peach senky nice
Peach thank you thank you
Finally, let's announce the general prizes.
I would like to visit, yes, I want to visit.
The specific announcement is 1.
At the end of 100 words, about 10
order
I would like to make an announcement at
Yeah then, Samiko, the sports day executive committee chairperson.
Thank you for your specific announcement.
Okay, let's start by announcing 1.
Masuhai
Oh that's it
I can see this from here!
Red team 8, white team 8, oh yeah, yellow team 6
I want to, but what, what, what?
It's scary. This announcement ceremony is a little scary.
Well, I don't know yet, there are so many people lined up.
Next, we announced the 100 kura first.
Click here for 100 rooms
is
please
It's so bad, it's so bad, it's still so bad
I don't know, I have all of these, yes, all of them.
It's about 100, please, please, it's dangerous.
Oh no, I'm going to go last, everyone.
Beg, beg, beg, finally, about 10 announcements
Desuoiiseno
please
Wow
It means to woo
The winner was
[applause]
What, what, the winner is red 158 yeah white is
but
106 was almost there
[music]
Naru
[applause]
[music]
Lely and Andre are 3rd in the white team with 138 points.
They did a great job and were in the group with 106 points.
Everyone did their best. You did your best.
I tried my best. I'm glad I tried my best.
I wonder when the award will be presented.
Yes, there will be an awards ceremony this time. Come on everyone.
First of all, this is Geo, who won the same medal as the yellow group.
Well, first of all, representative of the players and teachers of the yellow group.
Hasbechanbe-chan is the one in front of me.
Please come here.
Please let me have a medal for 3rd place.
How about pineapple?
Please wait a moment.
[music]
It's so amazing that everyone can make it too
Teruoe is amazing
The book has just been prepared, it's amazing.
That's right
Congratulations on that, the yellow color is amazing
It's on all the parts, it's on the neck of Lee.
Wow, it seems like everyone is following.
Yes, the silver medal goes to the white team.
Please call me yellow, Achan.
We are looking forward to it too.
But my heart is pounding and the momentum is amazing
This is Medal Geo and congratulations to the white team.
Pai
amazing medal
It's huge, it's huge
Congratulations to cute Mel
Congratulations and thank you
1st place in Osa and Hai Toge
This is the red team gold medal winner.
Yotowa-sama towa
I want to see Towao gold medal
Thank you for the medal and congratulations
[applause]
A great treasure, a treasure, a treasure, a treasure, a treasure, a treasure
Pick it up
This is Hololive
This is Lolive
I'm really familiar with it.
[laughter]
[applause]
It disappeared so quickly
There were so many diamonds, but in an instant
I'm not saying that it's beautiful now.
With all that said, Hololive Sports Festival!
2023 will be a negative influence for everyone.
Thank you very much Yes
Thank you very much
That's not to say it's a bit strange
Why do you want to take a commemorative photo?
Well then, what should I do?
Let's put it on that table in the middle over there.
Yes, please, yes, it's above.
Yeah okay come on come on come on come on come on
[music]
Far, far away, a game where there's no going back
It's okay, or it's not okay, everyone on the top right
We'll line up, we'll line up, we'll line up, we'll line up
I'll go in. Yeah, I'll go in too. Okay.
Hey, I can only see it now. I want to go back.
Okay, where is everyone?
I guess there's still a little bit of time left.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry
I froze for a moment. Wait a moment.
Please, wait a minute, Sorry.
Solly Mi-chan is there?
Yes, I see. It hasn't arrived yet either.
Everyone is lying, it's amazing about us
It's so true
There's no metal
But he fell without the metal.
I can't get used to things like that.
No, there's no difference. If I try it one more time, I'll kick out.
No, Emiko is gone, it's okay.
That's right
not at all
sad
There is such a thing
Yes, there are medals.
I can't give you that, I can't give you that, my senpai.
Thank you Mio-senpai for that.
I'm glad I clicked and touched.
Thank you, it was good. Thank you.
Oh, that's good, that thing in front of me.
Where should I look at that place?
Should I look at Nakoro-san?
Koro-san looks like Mr. Koro-san.
flying
Sanaaa
There, it's true, there's a cameraman in front.
Hey, the cameraman is here, here, here, here
There are quite a few like that.
The cameraman
Hi-san, is it okay? Can you see the photo?
I'll take a picture.
[music]
MermercaMercari Where are we all?
I'm throwing so much I'm throwing again
Hey, hey, don't throw away your garbage, take your garbage home with you.
Please, I can't see it.
Thank you so much for flying in.
Thank you listeners for watching Masano Nema.
Everyone cooperated a lot behind the scenes.
All of the management staff who gave this to me are also true.
Thank you very much for your continued support.
Thank you very much
[music]
Well then, Hol Live!
Sports day
It will end after 2023 Yes, that's it
Let's meet again, everyone holo
I'm going to the live show, yes, I'm going, Holo.
live
[applause]
Rai
[music]
Oh noooooo.
Get along
Shirodo is coming. Yashiro is dangerous.
It's dangerous, bye everyone, bye everyone
Bye everyone bye
bye bye
Bye aaaaaaaaaa
Thank you for all your hard work.
Thank you for watching and commenting
I glanced at them, but everyone
Thank you very much for your support.
It's too soon that that medal is gone
It's different now, I thought I'd take a photo, but FF
If you press a weird button like 5
I'm surprised that something has changed
I did, but I didn't have Mel at all.
I took it after a while so it was all good.
But Mio-senpai was very kind.
thank you
Well, it was a great turn of events for me.
I hope Mume-chan doesn't mind.
However, I added a follow just in case and I
Me-chan got stuck in that place.
It was interesting
That was good. That was good today.
I really liked it, it was the best White group
I hope everyone had a fun conversation today.
Unfortunately, it's Raden-chan.
I wasn't able to participate, but...
Let's talk to each other and do something together again
I want to play and do things like that.I feel better soon.
I hope you get better and we'll be together again.
I wish I could do something like that.
Raden-chan will be joining us.It really came out of the blue.
Since it's gone, Neo-senpai filled it in.
I didn't think you'd give it to me, so I'll see.
I was like, "Maybe I'll just come out."
Thank you very much to Oka-senpai.
Thank you very much.
Wait, I'm talking about everyone.
Everyone please gather for voice chat
Wait a minute, are you gathering?
Maybe
hey
Aminane did a great job
Wait, wait, this has already been distributed.
That would be bad, so I left it that way.
I think it would be bad if the distribution ended.
I think it's probably okay, just in case.
I started talking about my address until I was done sleeping.
If there are people around, it's not good, so I'll turn it off.
Let's go on a trip after this.
There is a possibility that there is a girl who will come to visit us.
Because of my gender, I guess it's probably yes.
Thank you everyone for today.
I got a slot at short notice, so please come and see it.
Thank you for that. I'm actually going to do it now.
I thought it might be difficult to understand the competition
I was thinking of changing it, but I'm sorry.
I just can't do it
I forgot, sorry, I forget this every time.
Next time something like this happens again, just a moment.
I'll keep that in mind as well today.
I was talking too excited, so I'll stop for a moment.
That's why my voice is hoarse.
But it'll be fine if you sleep, so it's okay.
It was so much fun, thank you everyone.
I'm lonely, but I'll try to respond to the distribution around here
I don't think so, but it was really fun
Deya
Thank you Sobaton and Sasou Shiro
Become a princess with this and that eight scrolls.
It was fun, thank you very much
I mean, there are really expensive vegetables.
I've heard rumors that it will happen today or tomorrow.
I don't know about that, so once...
I'll let you know more about that soon.
I feel like it depends a little on whether I can participate or not.
That's true, but let's talk about that famous quote.
Well, transfer too.
I would like to do it in the near future, so please
Please wait tomorrow.
I don't know, I'll call you again soon.
So, everyone, let's meet.
Thank you for coming. Bye.
Bye bye bye
Bye, it's time to wander away
Masu
[music]
by
Go
[music]
After all, I can feel the thrust blooming as well.
You've given me everything I need to do, so I'll try my best.
That's fine, but try your best, that's me
It's too expensive, it's not worth it
I'm sure Unpa is going to the bar.
Teru Kanata-chan feels her whole body properly
I'll share my imagination until then
Let's do what I say, really do it
Go beyond reality, Mia, even your weak points are flat switches.
[music]
still
is
I'm looking for something that makes me happy
Let me hear it
[music]
Don't give it to me
Tewa
[music]
teacher
thank you