[Music]
so
foreign
[Music]
so
sorry
[Music]
uh
oh
yes everyone's been waiting for this
week oh my god it's monday
hello everybody
[Music]
oh
yakuza tonight not your host
[Music]
whoa
i saw that before it's so shocking
[Music]
cat hair cat hair in my mouth
that that dude the bald head
did he show up in
[Music]
did he show up in like a dragon
maybe not
you cuddled before his room ah i cuddled
but i also
brushed
a lot
i brushed my cats
intensely
and
uh chased
chunkers
a lot
no he wasn't oh
oh so
mistaking him for someone else
everyone's know someone
making a third cat soon coming soon
the name will be
monkers no
blockers sunkers
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
bonkers
because
the cat will make me go bonkers
what a stupid name ah i should use lucky
arsenal yeah
[\h__\h] that [\h__\h] those heads although they
were beautiful
uh was it this one yeah
i have a new weapon
you know what this means don't [\h__\h] with
me the hands are kind of small
i should use the other one that looks
the other way
[Music]
if i turn it the other way it will look
uh
it will be in the gaming
screen wait a second
this is
uh made by miffen
my beautiful morningstar because i was
asking for a cute morning star
and this is
i guess a pretty cute morning star
one of the spikes is wearing a hat but
it's like
po the spike is poking through the hat
if you can see it
kusa
now
i can wield two of them
but that would mean i have four hands
[Music]
it do be big
it do be kind of in the way but
let's see how it goes if it's in the way
we might have to remove it uh
i wish i could like like freely freely
um change the angle
of things in obs but it only lets you do
it like in
[Music]
big steps you know like uh
like not 90 degrees
90 degrees
180 degrees
that's too too much i want it to be
slightly
adjusted
oh well now my hands are so small but
the bigger omega the bigger this thing
gets
[Laughter]
who wants to get bonked a bunk
what's up who's the bad chicken bunk
this is what i used to make my schnitzel
flat
and now i use it on you boom boom boom
boom boom boom boom boom boom
it's a massage it's like a acupuncture
massage
[Music]
thank you for the right super chat
yes i'll make you into a schnitzel
is it supposed to hurt um
it's a good good good kind of pain now
so with this morning star today we will
uh continue
uh
playing um
[Music]
uh
i i know the title maybe makes you think
that i'm gonna be dancing a lot tonight
but no i want to do story uh not no
dancing episode today
thank you
thank you thank you
glad to see my korean bros are still
here
i should do a korean themed stream again
soon i should study korean that's the
thing
okay hopefully my batteries are okay on
my controller
uh
yes
yes yes yes
let's continue
taking my shot
this week we're doing uh yakuza two
times uh today and on friday
um
so
let's see what's gonna happen tonight
yeah cool
now
also i put up the weekly schedule guys
on twitter and on the community board if
you didn't see it yet
all right last time we helped these uh
people for their side quests
and our current goal let's go straight
to the main quest our current goal is
somewhere
over the rainbow
here
the champion district
all right i'm on my way
i don't know if i remember how to play
[\h__\h] i probably don't remember how to
play um
are there some
yankees who want to fight me
oh
what buttons what buttons do i need to
press hmm
oh okay good
you wanna fight sure
uh uh
square and triangle okay
thank
you and we switched to the other wait
how do i okay
okay
and wait how do i focus on one of them
again that wasn't that possible too
maybe not
no it should have i'm sure it was an
option
oh yeah triangle after doing a crumble
cuckoo combo
r1 uh
[Music]
uh-huh i do have to keep on pushing it
what
what's with my head
what's this
[Music]
how do i open
uh
why was that was i already low health
when i went into the battle
[Laughter]
[Music]
let me step on you let me step on you
step on your weak asses
let's go
let's go is audio too
quiet or um probably might be a little
bit too quiet thank you for the right
super chat felix i want to focus l once
but another taunt you've got to change
and uh was it was it circle to
hold their
uh
hold their necks
legs
i just saw something
oh wait wait what was that button again
to do that
[Music]
it always disappeared so fast but okay
there we go
i want to do it again
wait
did it show up again
you kind of have to remember
it's an uh each move because uh
otherwise
they show up
kind of too late and disappear too fast
for me to register in my brain
i literally need to remember at what
time
the moves are available and on which
buttons they are
wow 20 kilometers
now ah
what's going on there
are they trying to enter
it's like they're in the middle of it in
the middle of what
sorry did you guys say uh it's always
trying a little bit but but the throwing
him down was zero
it's around the circle and still still
even then
uh i don't know when it's available man
sounds like touch upon this real estate
has been doing work in the champion
district if i go there i might find
something oh thank you for telling me
that because you were um idling
idling for too long how
how come you have no patience i want to
eat some food though before i do that
wait a second uh was it the orange
stores or the purple ones
i'm hungry
don't mind me oh whoa i found a nice
secret small place
oh ramen
please food
oh
ramen
and oh nice and they hidden hidden alley
oh that i'm sure it's really yummy here
[Music]
and
well we're going all in this man is
really hungry
itadakimasu
yummy negi
ramen
sanju is the meat
by the way
and niggy is the the
spring onion i love spring onions
[Music]
okay oh the boys are gone
i guess they got hungry as well
what's gonna happen oh are you in the
main quest or something else um oh boy
please what what is it
it is a sub subquest to stop and search
specialist sure
i was about to go to the main quest but
okay
what's your name what do you do for a
living
mmm cute you
i'm in a hurry i am indeed in a hurry
well we've had some trouble around these
parts lately just to be sure would you
mind if i checked your belongings
my morning star is is just a toy uh
it's not a real weapon uh don't question
it otherwise i might smash your head
it's just precaution can you show me
what you're carrying
well about 10 bottles of some energy
juice
what do you mean hand over is he gonna
give it back to me
[Music]
he's good he's going to give it back to
me right
hi is the granny on there
oh
it doesn't look like you're carrying
anything danger yeah i'm i'm i'm
i'm not carrying anything dangerous
no no no
yeah you're welcome yeah bye bye
now maybe so far the police officer's
not for me to i'm only doing this
because it's all i'm good for
never mind about me i'm the one asking
the questions here
it doesn't make sense i was sure you had
something big on you i've got
i've got a nose for these
things well i guess your news failed you
this time nothing here
i'm not sure
my sixth sense tells me i'll find
something huge if i dig deep enough
no
no please don't look at the key arsenal
hashtag
i don't know what to say i'm gonna prove
it stop in searches until i'm sure
you're not afraid i'm going to keep
questioning you okay
not okay no no he's not amused look at
his not amused face
oh come on kitty sound be a good sport
how do you know my name
it won't take long i just want to be
sure
uh-huh
okay
[Music]
yeah bye-bye
friendship you have to know officer stop
and search kikuti interacting with him
will gradually fill the friendship cause
you can check a
gauge you can check the status of this
guy gracie
at any time in the pawns menu's
completion list build your friendship
with obviously
and see what happens
it's guy's love between two guys
now
what is this
where are we talking about this story
what are we talking about
wanna go inside
all right we got to go here
the champion district the tattoo real
estate guys have apparently been coming
here a lot lately let's work to walk
around uh and see okay
wait
let me bring out my
oh
oh i wanted to catch
daddy
my nose is bleeding
where's left you're still alive okay
[Music]
i'm gonna call my mommy
she's gonna call my mommy and tell them
about you
she won't like it she won't like it at
all
she will not be amused
because
i like all these little tiny places man
season
wait what peek-a-boo
can i can i take a look
good job thank you good job to you too
not much place to fight here either
smash
[Music]
oh he's mad oh oh he's mad
superhuman strength yes because i'm from
whole i've myth man i'm a mythical being
syntax error
red eye outer space
so detailed
um
wait how do i get to that
huh
is this a maze i want to get there wait
um here
ah and then here
um but before
[Music]
okay
thank you for the pinky
push it it arrived for me too it's
around for everybody now for me too
i got it too it was in a really really
really light weight
[Music]
we do be
it
it's on
the battle is one
foreign
um
on
i want to really really really want to
pick up that [\h__\h] oh that trash can okay
um
bat oh [\h__\h] i always push the wrong
button i don't recall it so loud
stop me
watch it
foreign
um
[Music]
foreign
sure
also
foreign
so are they good people
[Music]
remains of potato chips i love it
um
one second i'm almost done
ah cat's hair [\h__\h]
what is it with these cat hairs always
mmm
[Music]
kenji
okay
cat hairs have protein
i have found out about that
cat are literally
made out of protein
i'm happy where are we going
um
where are we going over there all right
can i play with this dream machine
no
hmm sad
okay time to leave guys
they don't want us here
for some reason i don't know why i'm
such a nice guy
sorry
sorry i was looking at the signs didn't
i look at those signs and men
in uh
like a dragon
didn't i see those signs in that stream
that exact street and like a dragon
though i'm going crazy right
it's the same thing
oh
[\h__\h] matrix man
impressive moves
they're always there but change every
game yeah but this this is like gives me
deja vu oh hello
kamoji
i forgot who that was was that the guy
who told me moves uh i think so
[Music]
what the hell is that baby
well
damn that was harry styles thanks again
for before this is where you do your
thing huh a punch-out artist was it
ah that's right that's me that's my job
couldn't make much sense of bakla's
explanation what is it you do exactly
um the rules are simple you knock me
down or knock me out and the price money
is yours price is double the stakes
customer puts up ten thousand yen and if
they win i give them twenty thousand oh
half of that's up front free so we only
need to fork over the other the other
health huh may come with an amount equal
to the entry fee in advance the time
limit is 60 seconds if you get knocked
down or knocked out you lose if you hit
the challenger you also
i'm just supposed to dodge until the end
of 60 seconds
trying to run away from him what
yeah
okay
i mean i can do that i think i can do
that
just run away it can't be that difficult
um punches are garbage too very
advertised to everyone i seized
so most challenges are guys looking to
blow off steam by hitting someone ah not
tough guys looking to win some cash now
okay
it sounds easy enough
wait you can make a lot of money from
this
[Music]
that's right looking for ten thousand
more don't even have one
hundred percent no no no no
it was 10 million and million
[Music]
that's to make sure you is covered if
you ever lose if everything goes smooth
the money will fly come playing in
uh-huh
okay
it's not to make money is to learn
special news yeah okay okay i'll get
done don't get done should we do it
right away but my my health is kind of
kind of low so i need to eat some food
first
oh
yes please oh fancy restaurant korean
yucky nicole
cat hair as [\h__\h]
[Music]
grade a hot on me please
yeah baby
oh yeah
yummy i'm holding a morning star is that
not obvious
thanks dude
[Music]
where the [\h__\h] is my honey toast
where's my honey toast
all right now we can try
uh
one of those challenges
how much money do i have
two million two point seven million
okay uh we have to start with the ten
thousand okay
of course what
i need more training
oh so i can't even do it
okay we'll do it another time imagine i
thank you
thank you what
is your money
well i'll read that in the super chat
rating also suica i don't know if you're
serious but
uh
sheikah
yes
yes marriott's proposal necessary yes
congratulations
sounds uh
well like
you're very happy in your relationship
good for you good for you
um
i have some tendency tangents for you
guys later by the way so how [\h__\h]
long are you going to follow me okay
they left just down
what's this
oh
pizza
pizza and pasta
[Music]
am i dashing right now
oh yeah i think i think i'm supposedly
dashing someone's following me again
wait where do i go here here here here
here
the penthouse here tachibana will show
up anything i'm forgetting before i head
up
should i buy you more healing items or
am i fine
[Music]
safe
by healing oh really
okay
uh
welcome home
you didn't miss much we just started
and
there's gonna be a long stream
i should have enough oh well guess some
of that as long as i have space in my
in my
uh
inventory
which one is the best charges up your
hair
um
let's do this
i hope that uh made sense
did you just say that the bentos are
really good too
pharmacy has the best healing items
okay stamina best okay
good good i feel like i remembered you
guys saying that
jamasunna
and we will save
wait hello you save again
what have you saved in this game
ah the phone booth
i'm for gore this is my second episode
okay i don't remember [\h__\h]
was there one over where is where the s
is what is he's right safe safe safe
said
no no no no no
no
[Music]
yeah next is you you didn't see that
coming out you thought i was gonna hit
your friend but he's just jumping around
wasting his time
ah a normal day in japan
forgive me no i'll never forgive and
i'll never forget
steve
it's weird why don't we always have to
use these phone booths man
yes
did you ever witness fights in japan no
but i also when i lived in japan i
i never really went outside in like
like late
night
and i also didn't go to places like this
much
so
yeah i was kind of playing it safe i
guess
ancient saving method yeah
hello
it's like a mirror
but it's not
i want chocolate
but nice nice uh
nice floor
um
[Music]
hold up my man
i was having high hopes for us
oh but i guess they're bringing the
party here
all right let's fight
do you guys also play like this like
once you hit someone you run like in a
circle i always because otherwise like i
feel like it's better for me to
um change
who i'm fighting
instead of awkwardly turning around
in the middle of everyone
it's like good habits well let me get
out of here though
no
sometimes
i'm gonna
do it automatically
oh
get up
get down again get down
[Music]
foreign
i'm gonna watch the vlog
the option button
what's the option button i push the
middle one and then the item thing
button
whatever
tell me afterwards
what happened
[Music]
come at me bro
options with three lines i clicked that
too what the [\h__\h]
what is that
not chuck no that's not a nunchuck who's
dead
oh come on no [\h__\h] way you can dodge
a table
no no no no
not a [\h__\h] night so far
wait why am i laughing i love him i
don't want to hurt him oh my [\h__\h] [\h__\h] i
missed it
that was a chance
[Music]
there we go no no no beautiful hair
his beautiful luscious hair
coming
so oh oh [\h__\h] get okay get away get away
why is glowing he's glowing
come on over
come over here
huh what are you waiting for
what you waiting what you waiting what
you waiting for
wait how the [\h__\h] does he still have so
much health
it's pretty
guy huh
a little helpful uh heat and health
okay oh [\h__\h] why do you always press
that button
where are you where are you where are
you where are you
woah
mom
[Music]
oh what was that
hmm
no
no problem
what does he keep on throwing
[Music]
yeah
learning dodging from eleanor maybe a
little bit yeah
what the hell
that's right
believe it
or not
foreign
[Music]
stylish glasses man
oh my god it's like he is from star wars
or something
the lights
no
how romantic
and he's using a voice
[Music]
and in reality it's just someone in the
back pushing a button
and he's just a [\h__\h] chew knee beal
acting like that
so he's flexing that he's like in
control of all the electricity right
not that he actually can use magic
foreign
[Music]
you can see in the future
um
[Music]
it's a clock
what watch
from from him
what's this oh family
[Music]
foreign
now
i guess with that creepy ass guy
you're on school
three million
noise three million chapter two done oh
we were so close to finishing the
chapter two last time
omaha is
it's time time for what what what what
what what what is this time for it's
something
climbing spouses that's what it's time
for
was which was
a gilded cage well i mean everybody's so
excited
what's happening oh he's coming
is he coming
with the eye patch
is he from osaka
[Music]
that's the kind of couple right i was
looking for in later alligator
probably
oh
i like them
jazzy
beautiful
[Music]
you look like an idiot
let's pick it up yes on your knees um
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
enjoy
enjoy enjoy
um
[Music]
are
me
your first time here
is it your first time here sir
oshibori
arigato okini
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
no problem no problem
these girls be making money tonight
[Music]
around
m
whatever
[Music]
uh
oh [\h__\h] here we go
gucci
[Laughter]
you guard a word
when he has long hair i didn't realize
that
ponytail hmm
short legs no
but they'll hit strong
did he have this long hair and
and like a dragon too
food
uh
is
[Music]
um
turn
[Music]
here
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
when julie has a soundtrack
[Music]
i'm fighting i think i'm fighting okay
oh i like that interesting
oh
avoid the customer's attacks oh the
first law of management the customer is
getting even a puncher kick to reprisal
is out of the question for now watch for
the customer to make a move and evade
their attacks using x okay
[Music]
oh should i stand still
oh [\h__\h]
okay
a little bit drunk huh
second law management the customer is
king even in the worst times you must
never forget to provide only the finest
service possible
patience shall be rewarded as now it is
time to show all your customers the
ultimate in hospitality
[Applause]
[Music]
oh in front of the attacking customer
with a heat gauge at the okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
what's up
oh
i know i'm from like a dragon
being a really crazy and aggressive guy
this can't be real
[Laughter]
foreign
[Applause]
japanese customer service
always polite don't lose
don't lose your eye
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] is that a screwdriver
wow
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
uh
m
i feel like i would find this less funny
if i didn't know him from like a dragon
then i would like believe his act but
now it feels so ridiculous
like acting
like he's hiding something deep inside
uh
um
[Applause]
[Music]
um
i'm very confused and i did not
expect
that
like is it an act where's he
did he go crazy until like a dragon what
happened
don't tell me i'll find out
hey yo let's play that game that we
played in like a dragon
hello
hmm
thank you for the pinky
that's sweet
ready here 30 years from this game
yeah i guess a lot of stuff can happen
in 40 years i was wondering what the
timeline is
30 years
[Music]
so young
oh
okay we're playing with him now for real
oh this is cool i guess we're gonna like
is the game gonna be let us switch
between them every now and then
i mean like not let us but but forces
is this gonna be a thing
not a hotel
oh that's cool
i like that
gives us some different perspectives and
then one day i suppose they're gonna
meet
and then
i don't know what that what then what
will happen then but yes cool
every two chapters
[Music]
so today will be all about majima
okay stop saving now what the [\h__\h]
let's go
yaga simulator oh really
i'm gonna manage the girls
oh fun
are we gonna like for real manage the
cabaret
where am i going
we're going down
ah there we go
oh
got a minute
he looks sad troubled waiter
oh sir so sorry about that what can i do
for you
can you call cannon for me i need to
talk to her
yes sir of
course oh he's wearing some nice shoes
yo
spacing out y'all what you doing focus
focus
hi sir nice workout there tonight
thanks good night john
so you wanted to talk to me
you said she was looking horns of sakura
looking corn so sakura where do i start
[Music]
[Applause]
oh not like that the hell do you think
you're doing dummy
what i
what what's this about
that's the question isn't it think long
and hard anything come to mind
oh i'm sorry but you've gotta be a
little bit more specific
but why are we not being specific why
are we being so
i vague that was a little out of loop
nah
it's been about a month since you came
on here yeah how's it going think you
can make a real go of it at the grand
oh i think so the whole is much bigger
than the last club i worked at so it was
pretty daunting at first but i'm totally
used to it now and more customers are
coming here specifically to see me
that's great to hear not surprising from
the number one gal from one of the
oldest cabarets in the kita area guess
that was imagining things then huh
what do you mean
one month marks actually when i see that
most girls up and leave i was a little
worried you might be getting the itch
too
oh have no fear of that i wouldn't dream
of quitting now
that's hacked sucker uncle has been
trying to play the seniority card on me
but i don't even notice her
damn girl hag it's pretty serious
don't be like that sakurako is a vet
here she looks after the other girls too
most love that about her trying to get
along yeah
oh i hate nosey topside dad she's gonna
hold entourage but whatever sooner i
have my own clink and i won't have to
deal with them
does she even realize she's getting
lectured here
dense as a door this one she's even
giving me a little tune
i wrecked y'all
welcome to yakuza direct
better make it loud and clear
that ain't right cannot change you gotta
learn to read the room huh
doesn't matter how good you are at your
job or how popular you get keep snubbing
your seniors like that and you'll wake
up one day with nothing but enemies here
fine by me not like i do this job to
make friends with the other girls really
that's the best you can do i'm
disappointed i doubt you'll be around
here long enough to make those enemies
then
wait what's that supposed to mean is
there a problem with my work
now then she's the competitive time put
her pride on the hook and she'll take
the bait
look i ain't asking you to be friends
with sakurako in fact you two make much
better rivals
rivals
but not the kind that shanks the other
in the back compete push each other to
get better you'll bring up all the other
girls with you
right now you're just tripping over each
other and that makes it harder for
everybody around you to step up
customers may love a girl like that but
i got no use for him here the grant
needs girls who are popular with guys
and the girls
the guys and the girls
but
but i'm not into that kind of stuff
[\h__\h] stupid girl that's not what i
meant
that's the only reason i'm coming down
on you about it like this
you really think i'm sorry sir i was
acting like a spoiled brat i will work
on being that girl on being more
considerate
please give me a chance
yeah say you do get it i knew you were a
keeper kid
i hope you'll keep helping me improve
when i need it
bye-bye
uh what was that way to steal it can
happen don't count having zoning out on
me like that better go have a chat
all right where is he
uh he's zoning out again
what happened dude
why the long face need to use the
facilities
oh sir no i i got a letter from my
little sister back home
yeah what's the word
that my father's sick unfortunately the
dog says he needs to be hospitalized but
the procedure they want to do runs 500
but i ain't got that kind of cash
started hearing you try asking the floor
manager for an advance
another emergency a while back already
forced me to ask for one i'm afraid if i
ask again i'll get canned especially for
so much
you're in the habit of breaking mirrors
kid here i'll spot you what
but sir i can't
don't sweat it you can always replace
money same can't be said about people
once they're gone that's it
wow
as i recall you ain't been back home in
a while you had to take a few days off
too go visit your pulse oh wow
oh thank you sir
that's kalu
only thing that matters right now is
keeping this place running smooth i'll
throw as much money at it as i need to
looks like that's it for today's staff
troubles it's all about it's about time
i checked in one on the whole i can't
read anymore sorry
oh sir there's a problem
well [\h__\h] what now
one of the customers is placing in the
same orders now that he knows he isn't
paying for it of course they're gonna do
that was that obvious
we went down the line of our top vintage
wines to start and started in on our
best whiskies and brownies he's already
racked up about four million worth holy
[\h__\h]
sorry at the prices and working our way
down the list huh a real class acts come
out in times like these
indeed i figured we should stop him so
where is he at show me
oh this way
should we uh
dodge him as well to teach him a lesson
[Music]
foreign
he's got dumbo ears
he can fly with them
oh [\h__\h] yeah i'm sorry about that you
look fine
look cute ears
i really like that they're using like
real people because
it gives them like it makes it so much
more real like
i don't know in other games people are
just too perfect and even when they're
supposed to look a bit more ugly or
whatever
it's still i don't know it's just so
perfect i found the pause yeah
yeah but this like every every person
looks okay except the npc's running
around on the street but yeah these
characters they look like surreal and
they have like skin problems and [\h__\h]
and i like that
they have
um
uh
pores and
and
[\h__\h] like that so yeah
[Music]
blemishes yeah yeah yeah and and and i
forgot the word moles not moles
skin of thingies
mother
marks no that's the german word
not acne no no i don't mean acne
not freckles birthmarks birthmarks
perfect is what i mean
yeah i feel like in in like other games
the people who make the skin
for characters they always forget about
birthmarks always
really good attention to details
in these
you seem friendly
foreign
[Music]
interesting
owner of what
foreign
m
who wearing the yakuza but are no more
in the yakuza
society
[Laughter]
he's using the force too
five hundred million they're speaking in
yendao
[Music]
foreign
i was meaning in japanese because of
what he said
um
your jokes are not funny you should not
join whole life because you're not meant
to be a comedian
foreign
why
[Music]
ah gotta be aggressive
best coffee
street
who is this number one girl
my
[Music]
[Laughter]
a perfect nose even though he's one of
the main characters
i just really
i really like the character designs and
like the detail
to them and also detail to the streets
and to the inside architecture and
everything
um
was already fascinated by that and like
a dragon i still like it it's still
impressed
[Music]
oh
yeah i mean no no it's not like a like
an ugly nose or anything but you know i
just mean it's not completely straight
um
time to pay them a little visit
what [\h__\h] trash
is there so much trash
let me look at the map uh
there we go
looks familiar
yeah that looks very familiar now
we're going here
so over the bridge okay
where's the bridge
looks familiar
looks like like a dragon
ah
hello oh my god
what
a
beard
you know myself that a lot of the grand
yes
yeah that's me
why aren't you eating even the way you
walk is refined guarded you have no
blind spot despite appearances
i'm sorry sarah have you met
my name is some taro kumaki he heir to a
certain form of martial arts and its
present mustard
martial arts
yes but lately i've felt my technique
slipping my edge has been dulled so i
left the lights of tokyo in order to
train
yet even here i find this age of x's
gluttons and fool's gorging on carnal
pleasures nobody hungries anymore and
then i heard talk of a lounge called the
grand they say it was the home of a most
interesting man happy white day happy
day
all right am i asking what have you ever
visited our establishment
what kind of question is that cuz when
booze we've painted ladies hanging over
you but wanton exists of course i
haven't been
well then why the hell am i doing the
song and dance if i if you ain't a
customer oh
besides what's a washed-up martial
artist wants with me
that hungry air about you it is far
beyond the man i fought in recent years
would you do me the honor
hungry for violence
a deeper strength sleeps within you i
refuse to let it lie dormant and unused
any longer
uk upstairs pal fighting you don't earn
me one skinny ends profit i'm a busy guy
hide behind you merchants guys well you
like i know money isn't what feeds that
hunger whatever other stuff you make a
show of living
i can see the demon gnawing and human
sign
there's only one way to appease the
demon's son face to strong in combat and
set loose those fighting instincts
struggling to burst free
are you telling me you're that strong
guy
oh yes it happens i am no do you see any
reason to face me not that it will stay
in my hand either way
there is no talking sense to you is
there but you went i was just thinking
it would be it'd have been a while since
i really cut was not here though
okay
violence violence violence we need
majima to let out his frustrations
this place should work
you're awfully unhesitant and agreeing
to this i am starting to think you keep
the true extent of your strength hidden
away you must have your reasons i know i
have mine
but the fist is like the sword leave it
in its sheath to rest and you will not
be able to draw it when it's needed
what say you
ever feel an urge to shrug off your
restraints and fight to the full extent
of your abilities for a change
let's do it
what are these ladies in the back
looking at go somewhere else ladies look
their grandma is clapping poke him in
the eyes [\h__\h] style incorporates a
number of merciless attacks one of them
is the poke eye attack if you land an
eye poke attack the enemy will turn
their back to you in pain okay
how
ah
[\h__\h] i only i did damage three times
[\h__\h] i did it again get up
okay
again
pull up the essence of choking one of
the special moves of the [\h__\h] style is a
heat action called the essence of
choking this heat action triggers when
an enemy attacks you or when you circle
around behind them
ah i'm good at circling people
uh
show
oh [\h__\h]
did i do it yeah
oh now i did it oh
oh [\h__\h] that's how i crack my neck too
my training is complete okay attack with
all i got
what's a new one
get out get out get out
sheesh i'm speed
get out get up grandpa
yeah
i'm not sure he could really
survive a cracking nick like that
i in that face yeah i saw the craziness
that i saw uh in his eyes and like a
dragon i saw it a little bit
glad to know i still have an eye for a
challenge you will surprise me one day i
can promise your dad
hey grandpa just what kind of life have
you been living
one of unarmed combats were entering my
life on my own bare face for the last
few decades not that my opponents have
always been so gracious i have faced
swords firearms and you think i'm gonna
get stronger
oh that was him much even now i see
there's been a change in you i spoke
with you and regained the strength i
once had you spar with me
yeah
um
okay
so
both of our heroes protagonists have
someone teaching us how to fight nice
i feel like we're connected it's like a
different it's like their lost twins
soul mates
shuffle good job
show fukucho
[Music]
no
not now
i'm uh immersed into the story i need to
continue
[Music]
so far he feels a bit more faster than
kiryu
and more flexible
[Music]
hey more fun right
oh wait where's the other guy ah
feels good
and i'm feeling good
boom
[Music]
all right where are we going
i'm thinking we might need to go
we're not sharing inventory i guess so
we need to go to
buy some groceries as well if we see a
shop
where the [\h__\h] are we
uh can i get there
you know what we'll go this way
we're that little stream because there's
a shop there as well apparently
wait i went the wrong way i didn't want
to go there i wanted to go this way
oh i like this street yo
in that
what is this
cp exchange
you're
you are clown
oh
what is this again what was that again
fun pack
dlc uh-huh
i thought i could get some uh healing
items here i like this place
[Applause]
i can buy stuff at don quixote
donkey
[Music]
yeah yeah
uh ooh
xx
significantly noise
do i have more
hp
wait
is their lookout
in this game is there like a system
where you kind of like
i think there wasn't a leveling system
you can upgrade usp
do we have this to me
magical and kid you always have the same
[Music]
we definitely don't share um
money though apparently a bank account
upgrade using money not a whole door
oh yeah wait there was a skill tree i
forgot about the skill tree
uh
um
okay
you're welcome bye-bye
invest in yourself what can can he
already do that though
i don't really have money though
yeah i guess he can already do it i
don't have the money
okay
now we go this way
when i eat chocolate okay
okay no chocolate
christmas trees at christmas time
i want chocolate i want to go get snacks
[Music]
i found
chunkers junkies say hello
hello say hello
hello
she makes no sounds
so cute
stack
did you hear her a little bit
she stopped purring once i put her
closer to the microphone
i found her on the floor looking like a
button so cute
i have
chocolate rice waffles
obviously this is the place ready to
make the magic happen majima oh
[\h__\h] should i get more healing items
this is like a dungeon again
i wonder if i should get more you guys
think i'm covered
didn't buy that much
i wish
i'll be fine
okay
let's get to work
can't just charge in and blow my cover
uh-huh
oh no his eye
he took off his eye patch
hmm
i'm kind of bad with looking at stuff
like that
hmm
different character the third character
the first protagonist
all alone
all by
myself
[Music]
oh by his self
so
sad
use the lipstick to look around the club
interior and then press x to x button to
observe areas of interest
okay
[Music]
oh um
um
that is interesting
is he wearing look no that's not a
diaper it's just a big ass
oh my god oh my god
so cringy
um
wait
camera
tip that table's hopping let's look at
that table
one old guy flash of clothes a
middle-aged playboy and a kid in regs
mm-hmm
gotta be entertainment biz the director
the talent and the young ones a pa or
some peace boy job no no
three customers and only two girls feels
off balance
longer so they can't afford more
probably
the hostesses feel all the old-fashioned
but that girl is cute
with the golden dress
i mean the way she laughs is weird
like the closest screaming let's relive
the college years maybe it's a classic
look but i say it's straight up outdated
um
guys their own age probably don't get
anything from it but i bet it makes the
old boys feel right at home the fact
that all the girls got the same look
means it's probably club policy not
their personal taste mm-hmm
uh what else is there to see
did they look at everything
at the empty one
really
the table is wide open but this place
was booked solid could be they keep a
kill at the entrance even when there's
space to make it seem like the demand is
high hmm
well i'm done
was there something popping up here
oh
huh
enough time has passed apparently
because they wouldn't waste notes on me
on the first time i still i can probably
pump good intel out of this girl
[Music]
oh
mm-hmm
very smooth
very smooth yes
what do i ask for that info
[Music]
first
wait who's taco
wait who is taco
um
[Laughter]
oh my god
why is no one stopping him
[Music]
um
they're running out of steam i'll bet
that i'll kill for some fresh clients
[Music]
hmm
let's go shopping together
[Music]
[Laughter]
yep we forgot what we came for
well there's only one question left
soreness
cute girls
[Music]
oh
just kidding i'm just joking
around sorry
[Music]
don't fall in love you'll meet you soon
and then you'll fall in love for real
he looks so huge next to her
[Music]
on you
um
hope you guys are entertained anyways
[Music]
oh
he sees
like how he lost it
[Music]
is this the first
if this is the first one
the first yakuza game
will we find out
you'll find that okay
hmm
um
[Music]
this feels like the the trade i was
trying to do with good uh in monopoly
um
recently i hear that a lot what the hell
doing making someone
no do doings
what's that the other day
that's what i was thinking of yeah
it's been a hell of a day time to get
some grub crap going crap
monday
monday you're awakened something inside
of me where's the lasaga
oh what happened to the la saga who ate
those food oh there's taxis here
[Music]
i really want some lasagas
would be nice
i don't have much to lose
wait if i kill him i get 8 million
[Laughter]
run risk it
fight fight fight fight fight fight
fight fight
i don't have much money to lose anyway
lucille oh he's making fun of me
it's really hard to narrow
damn it yeah it was so narrow it looks
difficult
uh
why was he suddenly just standing there
damn where am i going ah up here
uh okay
menacingly exactly
intimidating
up here
okay
[Music]
thank you guys i needed some practice
with majima thank you for
helping me out tonight
he enjoys it i'm sure of it he's into
that kind of stuff
and another one
this is this is like my uh new video of
cubsies
it's just a bit different just a tiny
tiny difference here
did you really because you're really
not
i wanted to use the thing when you kept
interrupting me
and another one bites the dust
oh
oh by the way guys um
tomorrow i'm supposedly doing the snack
box review right
uh
it's a little bit gotta be honest it's a
little bit um wobbly right now if i'm
really doing that because
um
it's already in this building that i'm
in but it's apparently
uh with a neighbor
who took the package
and i have yet to receive it um
yeah i'm trying to get it in time
if if uh
if if i can't get it in time then i'll
do tomorrow off and then do the snack
review on the other day i was about i
was supposed to take off
tomorrow is my day off
no
you guys are looking at the schedule
wrong i think
huh
hey now you're confusing me did i write
it did i write it wrong
uh
yeah you're looking at it wrong
no first day is my day off not tuesday
you're reading it wrong you're reading
the order wrong guys
no look it goes from left to bottom and
then right to bottom and then sunday
guys
it seems like a lot of people got it
wrong
top to bottom top to bottom guys
look at the
the weekdays
he learned is that shut up no you
learned reading first that's more
important
also graphic design is my passion
it says first day
[Laughter]
of
so yeah but okay that means some of you
guys were already thinking i was taking
tomorrow off well we will see if the if
i can't get the snack box in time i'll
do it on thursday okay
okay well good that we talked about that
because otherwise a lot of people might
have missed the stream tomorrow
uh
what
there's a fight
um good luck with snack box for trivial
mission yes apparently it's been uh with
my neighbor for a while but i didn't
notice
wow what a knife
well i got an ass clown girls on the
right with a big honking story like this
you're [\h__\h] don't you girl got any
daggers or guns you know normal weapons
you can't see the appeal of a chinese
broadsword that is why i was hesitant to
sell to you huh you're making just about
me awful cocky for a two-bit black
market for on the whole point of
business is giving your clients what
they want
and i'm still
indeed only with clients i respect if
you would prove that you're worthy of my
weapons undergo my test
test tell you all about now you and i
will spar
defeat me if you put and you pass i'm
getting real tired of your high and
mighty talk
fine you want to fight i'll take you see
how you like your precious can opener
when i'm using it on you
indeed that's the point this is a test
of your proficiency with a weapon
ain't gonna feel sorry when you lose an
arm or if i straight up bend you
am i just watching this
oh am i is it gonna teach me something
wow
[Music]
oh oh he's got those moves
yeah
that's red
oh he says holy [\h__\h] instead of that's
rad
i like that holy [\h__\h] i say that a lot
too
the hell are those moves with that stick
that's no martial art i've ever seen but
he's got the other dude's sword looking
like a damn chopstick
hmm you failed
he's wearing a camouflage suit man he
looks like those bushes
i'm out of here
that's a weird way of walking stairs but
okay
oh you
again oh my god here is meeting you here
it's you again don't spook me like that
i was merely wondering about in search
of a place where the two of us could
spawn uninterrupted
riverside's occupied at the moment a
real nasty customer that no they're
already done we can use it
wait his neck seems fun
don't know how he healed that faster
i knew his father for ages back when he
walked this earth checking in on him was
half my reason for coming to sultan
bowie
as long as we all are here why don't i
introduce you
yeah
don't be so stubborn this will be good
for the both of you yeah
the time the time to sneak off has long
passed it seems fake who has been aware
of your presence from the start
about his comics on but i do not trust
this man he has an air of danger about
him
now don't you go stubborn on me too
delay no longer and put him to the test
okay
baseball bat
i already learned what what i saw though
you don't need to teach me again
his name
is written on his doghouse
hey i was reading that sorry you gotta
read faster then
keep up with me
dog go dog
dog
to the right
okay try monster into strong defensive
potential oh wait i always get the bat
do i get it automatically
hold l1 to guard
[Music]
okay
i like dodging more avoiding
but okay
oh [\h__\h] do i have to look at him to make
it successful or does it even work when
i look the exact opposite
okay
i like the other style more feels more
i don't know strong for some reason
if you hold that one you yeah um
okay okay
all right so i always have the bath in
that style i don't have to pick up
anything
oh using weapons in the weapon shop okay
okay
so i can replace the bat with a weapon
that i buy there
did i get that right
i want the morning star
oh can i have some ramen please
dragon and tiger oddworldly a chinese
restaurant operated by myself and my
wife
she looks like she's not alive she looks
like a doll
yahoo you laugh lady
yes okay
new customer yes many happy returns
you said it wasn't your average weapon
store what exactly is it then most of
the products we're still here are
meticulously hand forged by me bespoke
arms you might call them
made to order can you make me this one
this one please
now if i may i would like to explain how
it is i go about making weapons
enlist a host of agents to locate
weapons gear and other equipment oh they
can be hired to hunt down the following
three categories oh i don't have to do
it myself
okay
slippery eel
oh hungry
hmm
your customer for that side of business
too you wait i'll fix your feast
please please
mmm
it's a mini game that's passive you're
paying and does it over time okay
sounds good
should we start right away
a favor nanny
i don't need to tell you that you're not
spread word of their business and i'd
also like you to keep vigil over them
i don't share the details now but in
time their shop may draw the ire of a
terrible fool
nothing to worry yourself over just yet
but just please
keep it secret
bye bye
thanks for teaching me those sick moves
man
should i go in
okay
we ran out of eggs again you were
supposed to be out shopping oh sorry kfp
wasn't opened
you guys seem busy want me to come back
later
give me food
back to eggs best prices at market
next town over oh
oh
you want to say who to do what we told
you about agents like treasure hunters
but find equipment and parts for you go
find good things for maji manson make
lots of money
is this work really such good money what
do you do exactly this is what we do
what
outside of japan
dispatch agents to locations in japan
expenses are lower when compared to
dispatching overseas
oh right now i can only do japan
okay
[Music]
uh
huh
extra funds increase the success rate
and shorten exploration time
all right how much should i put in there
i'll give you five thousand yen how's
that
weapon gotcha
it's like gotcha
and 5000 yen is like nothing
ah
search request done next time you choose
agent and destination to search oh and
don't forget you can pay a little extra
too
extra funds motivate agents get better
things and also come back sooner
a little tip to get him to work harder
huh makes sense all right good luck for
you
final
you have this passion agent to see how
long the search will take press options
button to and highlight equipment in the
pause menu you cannot dispatch another
agent until the first one returns
okay
[Music]
there's no stealing involved i'm sure
it's all done legit
okay
now
uh i hear audio crackling
let me fix
um
there we go
uh where do we go where do we go where
was i supposed to go
down here oh
this man is a very busy businessman
trying to make this world a better place
totally
oh does this have some nice aoe oh he's
got the moves
got the moves like jagger got the moves
like dragons got the moon
black jagger
oh
[Music]
what happened there
most satisfying style to play
i know one more to be honest
this one's fine too
but
i think i prefer the other style that he
had the basic one
need to make more money though
not making enough money
[Music]
no
yes
another secret
place here
oh martial
huh
it does ring a few bells
my place and see her there where's the
problem sir
[Music]
shut up
wow
[Music]
let's go
oh [\h__\h] i missed that
[Music]
super smash brothers
i'm gonna smash them all
this is your invitation to smash
i know it's a dream come true
yeah
wow
that's rude
don't call him dad it hurts his feelings
um
[Music]
run away quickly
hello thank you for watching
sorry i'm i'm not talking that much
today because there's a lot of story
but thank you one day
my page he's got a pager too
six five eight one zero two nine
dragon
uh
i guess so
tiger and equipment something wants to
come in
oh okay okay i don't want to go there
now though
can we go
do i have to no no i wanted to i want to
do main quests
the chinese restaurant
oh nice cutscene oh
is that where he lives
yeah with all that money
but i guess it's all being taken away
from him
oh
that's really creepy oh creepy as [\h__\h]
this
[Laughter]
i must be dreaming
ah
oh
this guy again
but now he sees me
in my poor state that i really am
bro
oh we finished the chapter again
how many are there guys
it's chapter three now no we finished we
finished chapter three
gilded cage
seventeen alright
oh the money's coming in high-end swiss
watch
safe yes
economy
[Music]
during the dialogue so there's not no
not much kiwawa talking time
why you always gotta save so many times
huh
fourth chapter proof of resolve
omaha
who the [\h__\h] is that
oh you'll die
oh
what
a way
[Music]
was him like a dragon too he looks very
different
because they came uh together
in that battle he was
foreign
[Music]
i'm imagining how they take his eye
right now and just freaks me out just
thinking about it for a millisecond
oh no
[Music]
oh
um
[Music]
oh yeah
um
[Music]
i wanna give him a hug
oh
it's not the usual room no
no
[Music]
i couldn't do that no no
munchie mom
why would you want to go back to that
[\h__\h] no
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] yakuza
you suffered so much that must have hurt
so much what's your mom
what's your mom
you just know what happens besides your
mom
um true
[Music]
no no no
oh i did find out about it pretty soon
didn't i
oh
yeah
where we should be singing dummy right
now
um darts and pool
[Music]
casino
arcade
huh
where is it where is it
there it is
oh it's so far away
ah
we will wind if we wind up in that
direction again i'll do it then
we have some food oh bento oh bento no
it's all gone
oh man
that's yummy fresh
street vendo
wait you want to fight
good
i
just want to get that out of my head and
now i'm thinking about baseball
wonderful
i got those moves yo
wait i'm so sad
i'm always of course i'm still sad
but anyway
uh
back to work back to work guys war story
time
i don't know how to play my jungle but i
remember
uh when i was younger my mom played some
mojo game on pc and i tried it and
but i don't think it was classic majong
so
uh when i tried to play it again like
many years later i realized it's really
really really really
difficult and i don't really
i don't really know how to play it
that's my jungle solitaire
yeah yeah
yeah yeah probably something like move
matching yeah yeah so that was not real
majority
it was like trying to
it was some old game where when you were
trying to um
oh it was like a like a
mountain of my jungle stones aligned
nicely
i thought that was my tongue
um
yeah you know that's right but with no
luck yeah
you remember
was that a windows xp game was that
included
i i want to play that again
[Laughter]
just for the
uh for the sake of nostalgia
i'm quite surprised to wake up to why
didn't you tell me another girl was
coming besides zoos on me
i never what now well
two
girls
okay
we gave up some of our girls in the
trade but considering what we gained i'd
take this deal any day
okay
we got two good girls
space cat at pinball
[Music]
uh a little more research ahead of time
or a closer look at the insides of the
club might have given me a few more
cards to play with no sense worrying
about it now though
this is a good time i'd like to work out
the new shift schedule
am i gonna do that
now
sorry dude
sorry about that man i gotta go
somewhere even if i don't want to
classy spot for a classic guy no telling
what [\h__\h] he'll pull if i'm late i
better get moving okay
i'm on my way but let me say for maybe
should i save
let's save while we're here
[Music]
uh yes
pakistan okay wonderful
[Music]
perfect you guys just want to hear
majima not me right you're just excited
for matching my singing you guys i wish
you guys were just as excited about
hearing me sing hey
hey
i was hoping for a duet oh i'll do my
best
both of us okay again
a good answer
good job correcting yourself chad
24 hour cinderella yes let's go
um
[Music]
uh
so where is the park here okay and the
karaoke was not there it was i think
this place yeah okay
wait can i take a taxi
to
show who yourself
um
there we go
easy
these are at that shop you do that in
your private town
nah not with me i'm say so straight edge
idol i can't go into a shop like that
no no no no
but i'll make your dream come true i'll
do a duet with majima
hello get my scene i mean i don't really
like kadalka bars i
prefer
uh
the little rooms but okay
one thousand for a song okay
he's going so la la la la la
show us what you got majima
what the what choices do they have
view rules clock is a ripple game when
you press buttons okay
okay
ah
this one i kind of know
kind of
s-o-s now
[Music]
oh
oh my god
[Music]
i like this one a lot
sounds like an idol song
[Music]
okay well most of the classic
it's me sunshine
[Music]
what
oh [\h__\h] what is this input
[Music]
[Applause]
nice
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
wow
this is his real destiny man not being
yakuza he should be an idol
shush
who's calling me karaoke
don't even know what that means they're
saying i'm bad i think
the input feels terrible
uh
i prefer going to the dance floor man
i'll try one more time
so not only oh
[Music]
foreign
oh
[Music]
hey
you love me
[Music]
uh
[Applause]
that was at least better than before i
think
yay
how much more how much more i went from
76 yay
and i'm still a [\h__\h] bozo
[Music]
but it doesn't feel as satisfying as the
dancing
uh
game
[Music]
oh
yes
[Music]
oh
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
is that better i'm not sure
someone
oh
two points or so better
[Music]
that's so fast
i want to try the the one
the the the one of those girl songs
and the one that i liked
heartbreak made
wait what
by the way that is this more difficult
lively interjections
[Music]
oh life
is lively more difficult
what's girl who the [\h__\h] is this
that is
[Music]
he doesn't know how to be otaku
hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi
hi
[Music]
lovely night
me
[Music]
supporting that girl trying to get her
to
like him perhaps ooh 77 i try i try
again with lively interjections
[Laughter]
you're so good at kind of okay i had
lots of fun listening to you
yeah
i hope you'll come again i'm not done
here girl
do i look like i'm done here
why does he say he's gonna sing when
someone else is singing
makes no sense
i was looking forward to him singing
this
it goes up
i can see her video now
rocket girl hey let's
uh
[Music]
is
hi
[Music]
hey
yes
what the [\h__\h] is much modeling
[Music]
i can't focus because of majima
what the [\h__\h] is this
you say when you pick up a phone yo
this is better than before no not really
this is about as good good as it gets
guys
what do you mean if i can watch your
video
what does it mean watching her video
anyway uh no more cuddle
no no no no but it's always nice to have
a little fun time in between the serious
time
why are you all so serious man why are
you both pressing your arms huh
loosen up a little bit
um
her loot video at the video so what
no way
certain people trigger questions if you
cannot go though
oh
anyway
no no no guys we're yakuza
we're yakuza okay
wait who are we talking to these people
or that guy
oh that's way ah i see him
well
okay
sumathan
oh
i have arrived
i saw places like these in japan but i
never really felt the courage to eat
there
usually because it's so small and then
there's already some people sitting
there in groups and it's like really
awkward to go alone
yeah maybe with a friend i wouldn't mind
going
oh i didn't upgrade his skills yet now
oh odin
like a soup with stuff in it
he seems fine right now
oh
not so
scary
nice description
you're welcome
you always learn something at my streams
don't you
[Laughter]
hot hot hot hot
it's funny
[Laughter]
that [\h__\h] seafoam boy
seismic
[Music]
isn't even his real brother is it just
like
like he just
um
[Music]
too
foreign
but he's still alive 40 years later
impressive how did he do that
four games from now damn
why is the water moving so much
okay i'm listening
foreign
oh
um
it's hard to figure out if he's on his
side or not or like somewhat neutral man
um
[Music]
foreign
let's do
[Laughter]
um
one two three four five six that's not
really a difficult order to follow
i know hold up
well
let's see if majima really
has
uh
the courage to do it although i think
it's also courageous to not do it but
after the worst thing i can do is rush
it and screw it up i'll start similar to
do it right tonight i just need to get
to bed okay
where was my home again
man he has a even even if the apartment
is [\h__\h] in the inside it's the apartment
right at that little river
it's a famous river though
in osaka
to be honest pretty pretty good location
for
an osaka apartment
yeah he doesn't get to say no
ah wait um
abilities
do i have the money for it i do
increases the power
boost his hp
and let's go here too
[Music]
might want to do a few sub stories uh
really
it takes on everything it touches hold
hold triangle
these are basically the same abilities
on there
okay
you're finding a mainstream yeah i feel
like main story today
mostly
and i think what's a good um
pacing
is doing two chapters
per
stream if they're all around that length
last time we were close to doing um the
second chapter two i just didn't realize
we were that close to it
if i knew i would have finished it maybe
but we also did a lot of cyclists
well yeah approximately two chapters per
stream if if it works
check videos what in here
no you mean in that hot video store
no no no no no no you guys
you guys are down bed once again
it's not really hard
and nothing's as hot as me obviously
safe to watch i believe that but
mine's a [\h__\h] break okay let him
sleep
let him sleep
i love you morning's attention oh thank
you
it's beautiful isn't it
[Laughter]
i guess you can't see it from this angle
but i'm i suppose that the mouth of the
face is also a spike
maybe
i'm ending makoto
steph once finding a guy
sangha said to try hitting the telephone
clubs for girls in makima's ring what is
a telephone club
they're in the club and just calling
people
having
sensitive interactions on the phone or
what
how does that work
oh
okay that is basically it oh okay
[Music]
70s 80s
i looked up some 70s songs
uh
yesterday
night
and i kind of want to sing them in
karaoke soon
like uh
and girls just wanna have fun and
long girls just wanna have fun girls and
watch the video for the first time
actually holy [\h__\h] it's so derpy
that the the scenes where the girls like
move forward to the back and over to the
back you know what i mean
that's 80s oh i don't know man it's
approximately the same
yes real boomer karaoke you guys already
called me boomer when i was doing 2000
songs
but now when i do 80s songs you can
really call me boomer
cindy lauper yeah
heartbreak mermaid was written for this
game was heavily based on a real 80s
song
i love it i love that one yes
pocket tissue
that's gold wait which one is this one
oh this one is it
why is your mouse
whatever you're saying when you shut up
boomer
shut up
how much time would you like today
you're saying that as if i've come here
before it's my first time man
two hours
oh wait you don't call them from home
you go there in order to call them
i thought they were huh
i thought they were just there and then
calling you call them but
guess i'm learning something here oh
wait there's there's uh rules on the
side
please pay first at the reception
and then wait until in your single
moment until some until the phone rings
and pick up the phone and please enjoy
your conversation
uh as long as you're within the time you
can also leave
i guess not a hotel
oh is it something because like calling
it home
would
be
i don't know why i don't get it
college age girls hope i can get lucky
and find one
okay
oh hi hey there
hey your voice is pretty damn cute who
are you up to
no
just
lying around
oh so there they are at home maybe
we're all there are they in the same
house
i'm jealous you got the day off
the baby finally the baby
i guess it's not a college
girl yep
nope
next girl
read one word i'm done
19 minutes later no luck or what
[Music]
he's speaking in a charming voice
this is not how you do it girls
this is not how you do it i think
what you're
being on the phone talking about your
baby and then oh talking about how tired
you're
that's not gonna get this guy interested
in you
the [\h__\h] aren't you like work what
discipline girl
[Music]
but they don't exist yet
foreign
[Music]
um
it's just her testing if he's a yakuza
i think cause like back then especially
only yakuza had tattoos
she's no ordinary student i might have
some criminal connections
i'm running a long time i better make my
move do you move
[Music]
maybe he's listening in on the
oh
[Music]
um
it seems so friendly
we got a girl
all right
if what was it eva bus yeah i forgot
already
thank god there's a map that tells me
where to go
oh
he's always
oh no not you
not you
he has nipples though
didn't they have no nipples and like a
dragon why does he out of all people
have nipples
why didn't they lose their nipples in
the course of 30 years huh
he's modeled after his voice that oh
dear
the anus are different
wait what the f oh the name
uh
name
uh you're the manager of the grand irons
on
uh
wait it's glowing
you were enjoying this epidemic last
night oh i saw you there
surrounded by pretty girls all day and
you still go to a cover right on your
off time you're real
well that was straight live business
yeah wouldn't believe that either now
you're running for the telephone club
first pick okay it looks sus okay okay
okay
wait what's your story the fact that
you've been everywhere i have means
you've got business with all these
establishments too don't it so wait if i
would have explored the cabaret more
would i have seen him
three rounds a day just isn't enough for
me so i wind up just going from spot to
spot most days
from massage parlor to porn huts to who
knows where and [\h__\h] three times a day
and that's not enough how much
uh mom i get asked that a lot my livido
has a reputation to uphold
literally
but i feel like you and me are in the
same boat
[Music]
he's got the feeling we're birds of a
feather no no no i'm a bird you're not
no no don't put us into the same boat no
no
about where the cutest girls in town are
who was gonna what shop that sort of
thing
that's our real shame so there's way
more hotties around lately huh if some
of them put out videos
uh
you want me to give you the videos
you've been to the private video poof
spot right i'm talking about the soft
core space screen there
uh
good aviana
every time i pass a cute girl on the
street i make a note to check whether
she's put a video out
oh there were nipples you were
particularly happy whenever they showed
oh i guess it was somewhere else then
that they didn't have nipples
thank you for reminding me
goddamn you're one certifiable pervert
i know you'd think the same thing if you
saw some of these honeys i'll let you
know where to find some of my favorites
go have a look
maybe
maybe not
it's pretty i'm pretty much always in
one of the spots around town come find
me if you ever want some fresh
recommendations
um
what the [\h__\h]
but i have to say so far
uh like a dragon
seemed
crazier
than
this one like in general
so far though it could still change
i'm supposed to meet uncle on ebay
alright evil
just you wait okay
okay i feel uh scared already but okay
uh
the car is here now on it why is it here
sustained car
maharaja
ma
let me in let me
[Music]
my dancing
urges somebody
[Music]
move
sad
dance with somebody
this is where i'm supposed to meet uncle
i'll just have to wait and hope she
finds me
oh she just wants to see my
she wants to see my
tattoo
show her tattoos
the
we gotta get deeper we gotta dig deeper
[Music]
i figured i probably wouldn't get this
info for free but well gotta do what you
gotta do i'll pay whatever it takes
sorry
am i following you or are you following
me
you following me
okay uh wait uh you need some tissues
tell me if you need some tissues girl
pretty close all right this way girl
this way
her face her face like
looks pretty bad if
she's like a doggle
constantly staring at me
[Applause]
it's a way to say that your
stomach is empty to say my stomach is
pickle pickle did you guys know
okay this sushi place doesn't look too
expensive
[Music]
um
foreign
we
[Music]
don't follow me anywhere girls don't
follow me even in the sushi place
[Music]
yago
she'll be more eager to talk she's
gorgeous on sultan bonnie's finest yep
yep yep
fill her up with that sushi
do i really have to pay to oh no
okay but that's that's not so much okay
i mean that's uh about 200 bucks
[Music]
um
yet
you guys know what it is
oh it's right next to it
[Music]
i lost control man over my controls
don't get me started
hi taglin am i supposed to enter from
here
hola
only in games
[Music]
foreign
one second
uh
okay sorry hi
we will insert coin
let's go three turns okay
move claw to the left wait wait she just
wants one of the birbs right
are they different sizes there's one
relatively big one just wait did she say
she wants the big one or
or is any any of them fine did you say
green slice one green
any bird
um
[Music]
let's try the second row
oh
the claw is not
not very good
oh
first try
first ride
[Music]
is it really that easy am i just good at
this
[Laughter]
wow
impressive huh i can get more if you
guys want i still have two games left
[Music]
where can we go
can you get one for me too
i will get one for all of you a bird for
you and the bird for you
this girl that's not called
you
but i don't mind going to the disco
let's go
can
you don't realize what you got yourself
into
[Music]
it
needy girl
[Music]
vip room the disc goes in shuffle i'm
sure they got a dress code there but
hopefully this guy will look the part
enough
wait so ah did i
am i able to go to the disco afterwards
as much as i want is it like something i
had to
unlock
during the
during the game
are we going to mahalante
oh
i ain't telling you against like the
sour patch always has been now clearing
out my yardstick huh
you're hot i'd lie on this bridge for a
while now no matter who was dancing here
before that don't mean you owned a place
they're gonna fight did they have to
take up the whole bridge i got a disco
to get to
oh it is main story
oh yo what's up
mm-hmm
teach me a new move
please
sorry guys i'm going to skip the text
because i think it doesn't really matter
much
breaking dance you mean breakdance
dancing to assert dominance
i like the sound of that
oh
[Music]
holy [\h__\h]
really
watching my breakdance
you're gonna ruin your suit
don't touch the floor okay
the floor is lava
that's sick man radman holy [\h__\h] that
was dancing i've never seen moves that
sharp wonder if i could pull some of
that off
it ain't over
seems the boy in the red rock won
sparked something inside me yeah it did
it did
out of one of those dates with a young
lass are you you're a formidable man in
many areas it seems
it ain't like that
i found our venue i just have a park
i'll drop by when i get some jam okay
bye-bye
hey
sorry girl about that uh stuff let's
hustle to the disco
the hustle
what is that what's that melody i have a
melody in my mind
the hustle memory
i can't i can't come up with it
yeah what does it
uh sound like again
i don't remember
oh well maybe we'll hear it inside the
maharajam
bell come back i'm back to where i
belong
hello sir what the [\h__\h] are you wearing
hey i need to paint that too
yo they got the same dance moves in
osaka as they do in tokyo
okay it looks exactly the same inside
i'll get it back oh
[Music]
foreign
they don't
no way
will majima still kill him even though
he's pretty decent um
[Music]
no thank you
okay
foreign
there's a dance floor here what the [\h__\h]
why do we need to go outside i have to
pay again if i go
the roads of maharaja are you pay once
and if you go outside you have to pay
again to get back inside
making me lose all that money
[Music]
if we're gonna dance we could do it
inside switch to breaker style okay
extra attack from freeze pose trigger a
square attack pull but a triangle combo
attack to finish with a freeze pose
uh unleash an additional attack a
finishing blow called the double breaker
okay
while attacking what
is this what you wanted no
looks dope though
[Music]
i don't know how to do it
is this it okay i got it now
holy [\h__\h] the music what's going on it's
like a rape party or something like that
uh uh defeat okay
[Music]
but yeah the pose at the end is um
pretty dangerous because he just waits
there for a moment
damn
that's red
[Music]
yo be careful he might break my bones
well it was a nice evening with you lady
even though you took a lot of my money
[Music]
i
no he
would
oh
[Music]
okay we know where he is but
how's it totally scumbag explaining
women for cash turn into the saint going
around saving them and what's the deal
with this bathtub doesn't matter saint
or scum i'm killing my kimono that's the
job really okay
okay can i go for a round dancing though
why uh uh
petite you
nanny
are you again
you're the guy from evil bridge who was
duking it out with a big dude whether
you're break dancing or whatever
boom son i felt dead
the hell are you exploding for
the battle was sick yo those moves got
me serious in bugging i thought that
seemed the best to them we had to offer
but your skills are to the curb man
this is uh
i feel like i'm getting close to how
bail sounds
well that's what this is about look i
just tried out some random stuff that
came to mind it's nothing
the hell are you talking man it was like
a boat from the blue to me it shouted
from god you gotta join my crew we need
you and we need jesus
crew
a russian crew if you joined up with the
kings of certain worry no question i'm
in my man
alright she's the crew name and the rest
is my name so yeah welcome boy dogs
not so why should i waste my time
playing around with you and your friends
go find somebody else
i am playing fool me and my crew in this
for real i'm throwing down every day
we're gonna take over this town in japan
in the world you feel me hallelujah can
i get a hallelujah
hello yeah
that's great that's just how you plan on
taking over the world by dancing on the
side of the damn street
hey lots of folks come through so
temporary entertainment bigwigs gotta be
in the mix hallelujah bags guys
get one of those cats attention who even
knows
i suppose it's not impossible got plenty
of guys like that coming from my club
every night
well i think
if i want the big boys to take notice
i'm gonna stand out more than anybody
else in this town to death and getting
my ass on tv is totally possible
it hit me while i was watching you
battle dog we take your oil moves and
pump up the volume a bit we'll be
crushing every other crew in osaka
i already got ideas for a whole bunch of
sick new moves you get those under your
belt
and you might
be burying
the holy gods son jesus soon
[Music]
you don't gotta give me an answer right
now think on it when we practice in the
aloe vera and shuffle your west
and this side you ring
why is the music like this
so dramatic i just want to dance
where was the maharaja
ah here
let's go this girl disco disco disco
fever fever
i'm on my way
tension rising yeah
um
i'm learning some new moves on this
dance floor but i suppose they have the
same songs probably huh
same songs
uh
or is it like a little bit different
cute dress
let's see if i still got it
what do i feel like
i was really into this song man
i just love this song
last time i had to quit because i
couldn't feel my fingers anymore right
now they're okay
[Music]
all right all right it's squares from
triangle x
[Music]
oh
look he got more moves than kittier
it goes down
oh
[Music]
is
i need to put some oil into my uh
um
thingy in my controller
wait what
[Music]
oh
i get stuck all the time
no
so bad yeah boomy it's okay i deserve
that
do you guys not feel like the
the ps5 controller the
d-pad i i'm using the d-pad but like
yeah
it feels so stiff
um
yeah
i wouldn't know i don't know i'm in pc
hmm
through ps5 really exists yes
in my home
i haven't touched the ps5 controller
oh well
it's time to recover if you bump into
that too but uh not even
only then but just in general
they're they feel like i don't know
maybe it's just me
but i don't know they're kind of tough
to use
is that is this chapter ending soon guys
because um i'm actually feeling a little
bit a little bit sick
uh
just wanna i'm fine but i just want to
know
not really yes it's basically about it
okay
and then i'm motivated
in that case let's do it
should i save
that's safe
uh
oh where's the
here
[Music]
it's not that bad it's probably just
because i didn't eat
like much proper food today i had like
two pieces of
toast with jam in the morning
and and then i basically ate potato
chips and some
chocolate rice waffles
so so
i think i might need something proper to
eat
like the food that i ate in dusseldorf
and my daughter called eh nani
side quest my daughter please let my
early go
what is this about they look like
they're part of some cult
let her go
your daughter is with us of her own free
will your accusations have no merit
you people duped my daughter into
joining you you
new order yeah
fanatics
have you persisted you ever know mr
blasphemy i am afraid that sister you
will have to serve atonement for the
sins of the mother oh [\h__\h]
money
your adherence to pacifism makes the use
of physical atonement is tasteful but it
is at times a necessary evil now would
you please let us be
what did i get myself into lasagna
[Music]
um for the super chat
oh like blitz japan
not quite but
um
did i basically accept the quest already
i don't know let's see
what am i going to do
couldn't help but overhear you giving
lip to those pajama clad scrubles
something up
pardon me and you you are nobody special
like i said it sounded like an argument
and i wanted to make sure you weren't in
any danger
so you're just passing by you're not one
of them that
that cut
those people i was talking to
those people took my daughter euni
what do you mean tuck
i don't know much about cults at all
like i don't know [\h__\h] i don't know you
gotta explain to me what is a cult
so you're saying your daughter got swept
up in the pajama party and hasn't come
home since
yes i don't know who to turn to anymore
how old is the only tongue 20.
she's right for the picking and girls
her asian looking for freedom and they
must have had it on offer but eoni isn't
like that she's been dumped by those
people
by that cult
oh sure they are called not just a bunch
of
cooks in pajamas
i didn't know anything was wrong until i
got a call from school saying eoni was
missing classes but she left home every
morning so followed her one day that's
when i saw her going into the colts
building when eerie came home i
confronted her about it rather than
getting upset over my following her she
said well perfect timing you should join
the order too
um
never seen my daughter so vacant she
gets this far away look in her eyes
whenever she talks about this new
obsession of hers
damn
the next day the copies just showed up
and took my daughter away and they
didn't resort to force but they weren't
going to leave without her evil
i've gone to see them many times waiting
to see my eelie but they always turned
me away at the door
just recently lost my husband oh no
um we gotta help
[Music]
please help
would you mind joining the cult for me
why are we joining them
oh i said
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
oh my decibels are allowed inside
turning them is the only way to get in i
would sneak in myself but they know my
face now they would never let me pass
the doors
yamaha
understandable
okay
i can't say no
oh it's not in my vocabulary
shanina
you will hold money
please be careful there's no telling
what the order of the
show helped
us what
is that does that mean something
chat
you must learn their name if you can't
even get that much right those cultists
will never trust you
i mean i got this i'll sneak my way and
make cognitive illness sneak my way out
what is it the way he takes it
a handmade amulet
tentacle basically oh [\h__\h]
don't say that so loud
just a little chime i made to one of
people i think you might need it for
protection
okay
well
i do worry about your daughter
but
where are we okay
i'll take care of that another time
maybe we can do a stream where we focus
on cyclists
all right
i am here
whack him and i'm back in the family
you got this no reason to hesitate i've
been playing lap dog this whole time for
a chance like this
i ain't going through that humiliation
again this time i'm gonna do it
okay
i saved before the beginning of the
sidequest so
let's see
oh nice cutscene again
please
massage my body
oh sheesh what did you bring
[Music]
it doesn't like it
why be so direct you should have like
kind of been like oh i'm a customer
please
be
you think he's in there but then he
comes from the back
not sure about that
oreo
look around matchima dinosaur look
around
there he is
that's not a picture it's him it's just
him standing really still
[Music]
huh
uh
she must have heard that when he said
something they were so close
no way she didn't hear that
should probably even smell him
[Music]
he's cute
um
he didn't have a reservation
he must have been taking improv classes
when he was younger
[Music]
is
stop apologizing
[Laughter]
is
[Music]
huh
she doesn't have god hands though does
she she has angel hands
oh
okay are we gonna see it too
mighty
and my massage therapists never talk
like this
oh my god
oh you're not even massaging properly
what is that technique
i think you would know looking at his
back
uh
[Music]
it's not a massage
that's her doing push-ups
[Music]
she'll just keep asking questions this
is my chance to turn the tables and get
some info from him
is that to direct
[Music]
foreign
blind people also know how to do their
makeup i've seen videos of like um
[Music]
a
cute blind girl doing her makeup on
youtube
i mean
yeah you can do it it works it works
oh
is
that is the worst massage i've ever seen
guess i'm just gonna have to meet this
fella in person and see for myself
if i keep quiet she'll just keep asking
questions okay
[\h__\h] and we all just watched netflix and
stuff
[Music]
is
foreign
she seems pretty grateful toward him
just who is this guy
um
[Music]
i don't think we're killing him anymore
well now he's at least getting some
relaxing time
oh
what if he suddenly walks in
um
[Music]
she
good for him some peaceful
moments
nipples i see nipples
[Music]
this
foreign
[Music]
oh
all right i think we're about to fight
are we
gonna
m
massive man
at least call him god hands come on
i know the other eye come on
don't feel sorry about the blind girl
you want to make this guy blind too
whoa
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa whoa
whoa
maybe
okay okay okay ah okay okay okay okay
okay go go go go go get
is
hello
[Music]
that was a good combo yo
that those combos worked really well he
had no chance
oh phase two
oh it's not her if i was here
on which side are you
depends on that
huh
oh
[Laughter]
hmm
[Music]
it is a girl's end boy's name
what
[Music]
oh
foreign
uh
[Music]
he got jesus
[\h__\h] killed godhands
i want to switch to dancing kind of but
oh well
[Music]
um before
ah [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] man
[Music]
finish him up
there's a bat all right all right
let's go
nice nice nice
making some switches in between the
battle to adjust
what girl where did my girl go
yeah did they go that way
find the kind of girl run run run run am
i still oh [\h__\h] i need to heal i need
healing can i
can i take a break at the restaurant
[\h__\h] i don't think so i need to heal
myself
um
doing it significantly uh
ah
can i buy
can i buy anything
uh wait i can eat here right now no no
no i can't that's why everything's
blocked
you're cheap yeah yeah
how much is a little
oh well i'll use this
okay okay
foreign
it's on i protect this girl
i'm in love man
wait i can't hit her too or can they
only hit her
wait wait wait wait
wait no no
[Music]
[Applause]
she's the one with the god hands
i need her to heal me
from those nightmares
don't worry about it i'll explain later
christopher
go
um
do we need to be sneaky now stealthy oh
we're a couple
if you pursue a spot you and you caught
you'll have to fight to protect makoto
uh approach groups of people standing in
the streets and press x to blend in and
hide yourselves
places you can hide are marked on your
map with the
sign okay
when fighting off first years keeping
makoto safe should be your top priority
if they grab hold of her and try to drag
her up they'll she'll spend her energy
to resist if makoto loses all her energy
the game is over move for the street
scaffold and stay hidden okay
okay
interesting stealth mission
[Music]
so we hide like this
for how long
is there anyone even nearby
there's no reason to hide gel i guess
okay
wait where's the end goal
all the way over there
um we should go
oh we should actually
go
here and then down because here there
are no hiding spots
uh oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
no more people are making out on the
side of the
alley oh can i look if they passed
they still standing there
i feel like i have to fight them
[Music]
much
around the backhoe oh
oh okay
okay
that doesn't look like a girl from 40
years ago that looks like a
new girl
okay and they're currently at the bottom
so now is it going to be hands
[Music]
wait until they go
down again
nice fine dude
that was pretty obvious dude okay they
go down down down down down
time for us to run
this way this way this way this way this
way this way this way
here's pretty safe i see no
no no one who could put us in danger but
i'll take care of him
scout the area
i might have pressed two buttons at once
[Music]
okay
i thought i might fail
was that a fail
i don't even care about him
let's go
don't have tacos she's not a baseball
bat baseball
i always mess that kind of stuff up
always
uh
do we go
around
i go around here
now
it wouldn't even work
i'll just hide here
and when they
i see a route when they go back up i'll
go into that small
alley to the right
time to move
go go go go go go
oh wait i guess we just wait until they
pass we don't have to go there yeah
there's nothing to hide there and
there's enemies so
uh
how many
[Music]
no
i saw that coming i was waiting for that
oh [\h__\h] they're still coming
no no no
um should we go straight
no
all right this is have to go straight
because like there's so many hiding
spots here it feels like i shouldn't go
straight
uh yeah i shouldn't i shouldn't i can't
this way
[Music]
i'll wait
oh i guess i could have gone straight
and then just killed the guys standing
there
oh wow
wait how much is there to go okay let's
go back and go straight
take it
[Music]
go go go go go go go go go
now it is safe
come with me princess
i really want to know what you did to be
uh
a target like this
but
yeah i can only
make up stories right now i have no idea
but i know one thing
i need to protect cute girls
ow
um
eat my feet
eat them
they stinky aren't they
yakuza feet are stinky they're supposed
to be like that
oh
holy [\h__\h] these moves are so thick
don't hit the golden car though
i'm sure the owner spent a lot of money
on it let's not make the owner man
someone who has a car like that
he won't just forgive me for
making a scratch into it i'm pretty sure
yes
[Music]
oh
what
she still had energy
i was literally about to fight them off
again there were so many here i thought
breaker style was kind of fast so i
could move faster
what it looks like you saw she still had
energy
eh they take big chunks the [\h__\h]
what what's loading dragon huh
and do i have to start from the
beginning oh no from here oh okay okay
okay
i thought i had to strap in the
beginning
um
oh she starts with the full bar okay
no
no no no no no no no no no
[Music]
almost there
i'm stressed don't tell me to tell my he
to use my heat moves now ain't got no
time for that
gotta have quick
flexible moves
up here
okay
let's see
part two
[Music]
if you're fast we're gonna make it to
the
next
hiding spot
or even the one afternoon
[Laughter]
[Music]
no problem
yeah i prefer you hitting me and hitting
on my grill though
oh
she doesn't reload the energy though
does she
so
uh better not run into the enemies again
did i go wrong
yeah let's go left let's go daddy and
that was where i was wanting to go
anyway
i'll carry you if i have to
no more stairs okay okay
but there's stairs here if you're a
princess character
what are you doing here
how do you know i'm here
tickles
stay in the back
far in the back hide in the bush or
something
like
that
like she has no idea what's going on
[\h__\h] died
are you good okay
[Applause]
power stump
um bringing in the heat
frodo in the river
i have no choice
here
is first skill
nah
majima can't kill
he's too good of a person for that
[Music]
where did we escape to
um
[Music]
she's scared
oh
[Music]
more
um
hmm
you can't you cannot you're not like
that
no
[Music]
he
wouldn't
don't worry he would never do that
[Music]
chapter four done those
we will we will listen to
uh the beginning of the next chapter
is
safe
i guess in fear i could also just
end it here because i'm saving anyway
hmm
okay yeah i guess oh should we ah
cliffhanger no oh i want to know too
let's listen let's see
oh oh no [\h__\h] [\h__\h] we're back to killian
magikaya
no
why would you do that to me why why why
why why
why would you do that to me
stay tuned for the next episode i love
video
but i can't relate that's that's just
mean
yeah i need to complete two chapters
and i need like a whole stream for two
chapters manchester
[Music]
ah
i'm hungry and the hungry nose is making
me feel sick
if this is how yakuza
work
with cliffhangers
and [\h__\h] them
those yakuza
no no no wonder and no no no i'm gonna
eat proof
yeah one second
one second
oh
i'm not sure if i should or could read
super chats
um
i want
food
ah
but there's quite a lot of super chats
save them for the snack box um
yeah because that will be a shorter
stream but i'm not even sure if i can do
it tomorrow for sure
[Music]
go eat go eat
uh
[Music]
but i
i
i also
i owe you stories
i owe you some stories
but it feels like right now because like
we're so
busy with like dialogues and [\h__\h] it
feels like almost elden ring is the
better place to tell you about my
stories
just don't want to forget until then but
i didn't write most of the things down
that i wanted to tell you
oh
ah
[Music]
i feel bad because i barely talk to you
guys today
let me tell you one story then maybe one
one story
oh yeah um
one story i'll tell you okay
so
uh on on our way back uh home after
arriving at the airport
me and rmt took uh an uber um to my
place because uh rmt left something a
while ago
in my apartment that um
she needed
and i wanted her to pick it up so we
went to my place first
and we got into this uber
and the moment i got in i was like yo
yo
because the whole ceiling of the uber
was covered in sparkling leds
uh
yeah no i did not tell you about that
yet no no no no no
the whole like a lot of small small leds
with like um
two to three centimeters in between
not only two centimeters yeah a cash cab
i don't know about that but i was like
what's what's this uber what the hell i
was like i was i asked because like
there's different uber tabs right
there's like the normal uber and then
there's like a little bit more of a
fancy uber and then there's the big
ubers that you can order um but i was
like did i did i order
the fancy uber by accident i i didn't
realize and and the driver was like nah
nah nah nah this is normal normal
and
then because i was so fascinated by the
leds he showed me some effects because
they could change color and he was like
what color do you want and i said um
they're blue right now let's show let's
do white so it looks like the stars and
the sky
yeah and then he turned them into what
and then and then he said oh star is
okay let me show you and then uh it was
like
because it was the whole ceiling of the
car uh suddenly from one side of the
back to the other side and the front
uh there was like shooting stars you had
a shooting star effect
yeah
it was so cool i was so fascinated i
kept on looking at the ceiling i was
like this is so cool this is so cool
this is so cool and then and then and
then and then he showed me uh he pointed
out that he has a
um he has a screen a tv screen in the
front
uh
uh of the like next to the steering
wheel and i was like
well we are watching netflix and all
that's nice maybe when you're in a uh
when when you're in in a in a
traffic jam and you can't move on much
and you said oh even even during driving
i can watch because my car actually i
actually also um
uh
put in a dlc and then what i mean uh so
that it drives on its own and was like
what
all of those things he has been like
installing himself so then he showed off
while we were like
driving
pretty fast uh that the car
recognizes
uh first of all when it's too close to a
car and then it slows down and then it
recognizes when uh it goes to the left
lane that it can drive a bit faster
because on the left lane here you drive
faster
um like a boot like tesla yeah it's
[\h__\h] crazy i thought only tesla's
have that
so it was a normal car
um
yeah holy [\h__\h] and he did all of that
himself but that's not where it stops
guys that was that was cool
um
uh yeah it slows down and it goes faster
and all that and and it stays
straight it stays in the lane and all
that yeah like a tesla diy tesla
fascinating
uh uh yeah and i was i was still like
fascinated by the lights and everything
and then and then he told us that
uh he
like i was like
doesn't this all of this cost a lot of
money like doing this stuff and then he
told us that he like he works for uber
but he's like the he like leads
he has like a company kind of like a lot
of cars who drive for him and and and
they kind of drive for uber you know
what i mean
and then and then he told me that he's
doing that because he needs to save up
money
for
uh his flying license his commercial
flying license and i'm like
what
and then he kept on going and going and
going about all these licenses i was
like more tell me more to me more this
is interesting he told me that he
already has a private flying license and
told me um uh uh oh yeah that he's
working on getting the commercial and he
showed me a photo of the plane that he
likes to fly
um
uh it's not not like a huge plane just
like a small one yeah and it was like
what
what and then he tells me he has like
pretty much a license of everything that
you can control and drive and i was like
okay
why like
what for it
but
but yeah it seems to be his hobby to
like
control everything that can move so i
was like okay when are you doing uh
underground boat
u-boat uh wasn't there a proper word for
that in english um
a license and it was like
maybe someday
um
yeah submarine submarine
yeah he kept on telling us about all
these licenses wait what else was there
uh he can drive trucks and
uh like everything everything
a space shuttle one day probably
bikes of course bikes
um
trains i asked about trains too what did
he say he said he's not really
interested in trains because it's boring
because there's not much to do but he
does want to try once only
but he's not interested in getting a
license or so for it oh but he did say
that after getting the commission
license he wants to be able to do it as
a job uh he wants to work as a pilot but
that's so weird like the the whole
i don't know it was was a really weird
character i felt like i met a really
interesting npc
and and and and oh he also said that he
um how do you call this in english uh
when
uh tiffany when you put a car
lower when you make it so that it's
lower to its tires even showed me uh
once we arrived and parked that
there's like the yeah really not much
space to the tires i was like i don't
really see a difference he said yeah
it's just two centimeters i was like who
really notices that
yeah he's [\h__\h] crazy
[\h__\h] insane
i was so fascinated by by like having so
many licenses that i asked how how old
he was because like how can you do all
of that
without being like pretty old you said
he was under 30
i don't know the exact age didn't ask
exactly but under 30
no that sounds freaking crazy
[Laughter]
but i didn't tell him
that i had quite an interesting life
myself but it's it's nice to hear some
interesting stories sometimes
sounds like a yakuza character
oh oh
yeah
need to finish the quest yeah the side
side quest i don't know i i uh i
cancelled the quest because i
will probably never meet him again
sounds like he has rich parents
yeah i i wanted to kind of know like
where he gets all that money from
just out of interest you know but
apparently just from
having those other people drive for him
for uber or so like for his company that
works for uber
um
but i'm like can you really make that
much money because the commercial um
the commercial flying license costs
about 85 000 dollars
and considering all the other licenses
he has and him having to also renew them
every once in a while
huh
it sounded fishy to me
no
[Music]
yeah
definitely rich parents
but then danny wouldn't really need to
work uh
that much to
get that anyway it doesn't matter but
it doesn't matter but that was a weird
uh i had a lot of weird uber drivers
guys had a lot of way too much rappers
in the past few days the one with the
with the window on the ceiling talking
about
stars in the sky and beauty and all that
and this guy
flexing all the things with his car and
his licenses and all that
yeah every uber has a story normally i
don't want to talk to them you know i
just
just want it to be quiet but um
this one was actually interesting to
listen to
better than awkward silence
i don't think silence in an uber is
awkward
that's the one place where i don't think
silence is awkward
if the uber driver doesn't engage in the
conversation it's an instant five stars
yeah
i appreciate it when they don't talk um
and if they talk
then at least have some interesting
story to tell like that that one guy i
told you about uh yesterday the the guy
who was just complaining because i
triggered something in his memory
[Laughter]
kept on complaining and ranting and
ranting
yeah
shut up just shut up
silence in the right share is the ideal
yeah wait in a share you mean with
strangers not only the driver
that would
again feel awkward to me because i just
feel awkward simply sharing a ride with
strangers i did that before uh
long long time ago
and it did it was kind of awkward
um
uber and lyft you just mean okay you
don't mean that
carpool that's carpool i guess
yeah
anyway i'm really hungry that was my
uber story
i'm really hungry so i'm gonna
make some food now
yeah thank you for understanding
um
i'll have to figure out what to do about
tomorrow i was hopeful that i would get
my
um package today
um
[Music]
but um
yeah
i left i actually left um
um
uh uh at the door that was supposed to
have my package according to the
tracking number
uh i left a contact detail and during
the stream i actually got contacted
and the that neighbor told me that he
doesn't know what i'm talking about
he doesn't know about the package but
supposedly there
they
have it since a while ago
so
i am confused
um
that's so weird because i uh in the
tracking number it said the last name
and the room number the apartment number
from the neighbor who supposedly has it
so i don't think there's a mistake there
both the number the room number and the
name is correct
yeah maybe my snacks got eaten but why
would you no i don't think they would do
that
i don't think they would do that
um
in any case
um i was thinking
worst case if the snack box really
just disappeared into the void i can do
the
that hot glue
stream instead that i wanted to do
um
the delivery guy made a mistake i doubt
it like it makes no sense like it's just
like if there's a typo in the name or
whatever that makes sense or
i don't have one num if the number
doesn't match with the name okay
then there's a mistake but the name
matches with the number
um hmm
yeah think about it um
yeah and see if if i if that person
figures out where the hell my package is
i want that package i'm curious what the
hell
snacks in guatemala are like
yeah did you guys wonder what the hell
is that country i don't know why
it might have been a surprise to you
guys but
um that's the snack box i currently have
available or not really i don't really
have it available
i think your neighbor just stole it no
no honestly i don't
believe
the people
here
where i live would
steal
a [\h__\h] snack box
because you can even see on the
packaging
it's not like a normal
um
a normal cardboard box that you don't
see what's inside you already see what's
inside from the outside it's just a
snack box
there is no worth in
stealing that
i don't believe that
and especially if they signed their name
with the delivery guy otherwise the
delivery guy wouldn't have the name and
the apartment number if they signed that
then
it makes no sense that they would steal
it
maybe they lived with someone else and
they accepted it but then the person i
was in contact with didn't know about it
that's something that would make sense
um
yeah
i'll i'll keep you guys updated on my
plans
and
yeah we might have to switch out the
snack box
uh stream to something else but i'll
keep you updated
[Music]
i'll hopefully find it yeah
i i did confront them don't worry about
it
i'll figure something out
sorry starting to pick up yeah yeah yeah
yeah i really wanna
know more about the majima storyline
right now but
um i'm sure that the keto storyline is
gonna offer something interesting as
well in the next episode which will be
on friday so if you want to see more
yakuza then please watch on friday as
well thank you for watching today
everybody hope you have a lovely day and
evening and i'll see
you
soon
follow follow on twitter for updates or
just wait for the reservation slot yeah
and wish cronie a happy birthday
everybody i already did but
go wish her a happy birthday
croissant
yeah
when we say
we
sing we need food i need food i need
food food food food
[Music]
you