[Music]
w
that's the is running fine right
[Music]
second okay with the shitty XO
microphone let's go
[Music]
it's not a hot night moment but I'm
literally asking you
[Music]
questions
y k
frog quack
frog where's your camera
there they there do they see there you
they do
I see
you this is this is my little sister
today you're so
cute we're just we're just getting to
sorry sorry we just met we just met hi
hi Chad hi welcome to the stream this is
our first date because we met on Tinder
for frogs right
Tinder for frogs Yeah yeah what what
could it be called what could Tinder for
frogs be
called
[Music]
um uh Tad tadpole uh i t like yeah tadle
t yeah Frogger Frogger oh Frogger right
that's game though that I love good yeah
that's kind of ruining my childhood
right now stop it guys
yeah I don't want to think that like I
mean Tinder has like a pretty like you
know it's pretty scandalous you know
Frogger Frogg is just a cute guy what
we're doing is scandalous
too are we
I come you guys stop get your mind out
of the gutter what was um what was was
so interesting about my profile that
made you swipe to whatever side it
is um whatever side it is um I think
definitely the gun is really attractive
really you like
that
yeah it's a good gun very good gun it's
a good gun can you see her little frog
sticker on it yeah it's so cute
well also I I can even though you should
be the one protecting me but I can
protect you with fly sweat
sweat oh are you catching our dinner
tonight I guess I could do
[Laughter]
that okay so we are going to go on a DAT
this is the the winter World Of The Well
of us like whole live English that we
used the first time last year or last
last year I can't even I don't even
understand
time me neither I think it was last year
it I want to show you guys I think so
there have been some updates made for
this date specifically and there once
again more than I could have ever
imagined first of all uh how do I angle
the camera like oh yeah
look wait this is this oh look at the
norn lights holy [\h__\h] I'll show you guys
too wait how do I angle it stop looking
at me wait is it sideways oh sorry guys
I'm
[Music]
sideways there we go
wow oh my gosh wait it's The Big Dipper
the big di Big Dipper Little Dipper
Little Dipper Little
Dipper what Dipper St no
di there it's a dip oh gosh I can't let
go oh my hand so
shaky you guys oh gosh the camera's
stuck are they shaky because it's so
cold I don't really think this is an
environment where frogs should be
anyway no I'm I'm nervous that's why
they're so shaky understandable well I I
I was um such a beautiful frog right am
I more beautiful than these norn lights
oh yes so much more really yeah I'm
going to put mine there
too oh it's why is it sideways
again why is it sideway you guys this is
so
scuffed nice booty oh my God you're up
I'm upside down oh my God I want to look
I want to look between your legs let me
I mean I mean I mean I mean I don't mean
it in a weird way yeah
okay oh it's like um it's like
a oop oop oop oop yay I pass I passed
yayer I don't think you can go through
my legs un no no you oh I can try
probably try give it the
try okay I'm willing to try anything
here
okay here I go here I go everybody I can
leave my bed like this
um every kfp is probably screaming at me
right now that's
okay I'm I'm it I'm crawling I'm
crawling I'm crawling is it
working
oh okay
nice nice nice nice okay I think that is
a weird start to our date I feel like it
shouldn't be like this
but maybe
yeah uh well anyway this is by the way
in case you guys don't recognize her
this is Pomo rain
puff hell I'm pom to first wave L and
this is Froggy AKA Tak I guess but
that's a secret don't don't tell anyone
don't don't tell anyone or else you have
two choices of weapons to be the dealt
with what oh I think I'll take
the on your but butt show me a butt let
me
okay but you're so
flat hey that's not bad very kind of
look at my
butt that is a
rpti she
can
who look at her
[Laughter]
[Music]
go but but frog bir where is your frog
bird
voice I was just about to say I don't I
don't know will you love me even as a
frog Bird that's exactly why I brought
brought you over
[Laughter]
here hello bu my name is frog mer
um I'm a pretty uh swell guy I'm ready
to take this
lovely froggy lady on a a spicy dat
don't
you oh my God I love your voice so much
I love it greetings Canada oh we're in
Canada it's pretty seems like I don't I
don't think it's
Canada I think
it's oh so un M
Mia sorry I'm pass geography or Biology
one other charms you have besides um
being tall because knowledge doesn't
seem to be one of your charms so
far um let's
see
um uh dark you mean I'm using the wrong
mic I'm using the right M I think wait
wait wait wait wait sorry I don't notice
the comments that much oh [\h__\h] no oh
yeah I was using
to you are that's why
it's that's why it quiet yeah that's why
oh my God sorry it took me a while I'm
fixed now I'm fixed
how loud is it now pretty loud okay okay
it sounds I think it was fine in VR chat
yeah it definitely
was yay
SC well froggy waa hasn't streamed for a
while so I'm not used to it
anymore when's the last time you used
frog
bird um I think frog bir had like a
comedy special um
Ed it
yeah's a really sought after
guy the ladies are like knocking they're
punching they're kicking everybody to
get to him
actually wow but you don't want anyone
but this cute froggy lady
right yeah it's funny cuz they like
punch and kick I can't tell um I can't
tell if they're like trying to get to me
or run away it's a
little I remember that one stream where
you were like doing a dating show like
you were participating in a dating show
and I was
thinking these ladies are not right for
this frog man she needs he needs someone
like
me so we're going to go on the state now
and we're going to show you guys this
beautiful winter World which is now
updated for these cute frogs so let's go
let's
go
go I'm going to grab the camera me
too hello everybody I'm going to move
you up a little bit I'm going to do
activate
wait I need to set it to follow
me come on terrifying next to you
mhm okay oh it's a little bit low wait
one more one more try
oh yeah oh that's good and then T let's
go oh this way oh but then it's behind
me wait this wait how what if I oh my
God frogua is leading you on the date
okay come with me this kind of cute come
with
me rock bird follow
me
okay
come with
me beautiful
man oh sorry I don't want to get in your
camera oh it's fine go come side by
side why you following you hold my
hand oh okay I don't hope you don't like
[Laughter]
Cheetos can I can I stick your fum in my
mouth
yummy wow that's the first time anyone's
volunteered to do
that okay come on come on come on this
is the main area with the
tree cuzz it's almost Christmas on
everybody yay Christmas do you know what
Christmas is frog
bird uh yeah it's the time when uh the
the world is a
blaze the trees are all on fire and oh
yeah it's a beautiful [\h__\h] yeah I love
that kind of
Christmas that's the best kind of
Christmas oh oh my God this this girl
knows how to have a good time mm I know
finger two of have a good time
especially frog related games on Steam
frog detective my favorite game are you
a gamer too wait you
did you play frog detective yeah I
did yeah it's so
fun frog bonding over frog
games oh my God I didn't play two or
three though only one what well you you
need to get up to my level which is this
high it's a real
gamer I'm a real gamer mhm so if you
want to you know if you want to get with
me you need to be you know a a good game
or can you can you do that can you get
good at
gaming I'll be good for you
girl why is she so cute
you're no you're so
cute F you look at me I'm not cute I'm
dashingly
handsome yeah okay sorry sorry of course
you're really handsome like I I've never
seen such a long frog like this
especially someone who can stand on two
legs besides me I've never seen some
some frog that can stand on two
legs yeah it's pretty rare actually I
think yeah maybe we're freaks of nature
I think I think everybody else is a
freak to be honest n not to us not to us
so true
okay let me check
over is everything okay besides the the
thing in the beginning I think
everything is okay now okay so I want to
I have an idea for your first quest to
impress this frog
lady follow me
okay all right guys we're going this
way this area is um already familiar to
the viewers of me I think this is not
new but I want you there's these pens
right we we used to use them to draw on
the on on top of the
Snowman these p and if you like okay uh
if you if you push the right button then
you can draw oh yeah like this but I
want you to draw me like one of your
French frogs with this pen
okay any of these pens with the pen all
right there's just one catch there's
just one catch you can only use uh 30
Strokes then it will start to disappear
but you can do 30 strokes and then get
another pen and continue the art with
that
pen so just use several
pens H what do you want to draw maybe uh
like against the the nice scenery you
can draw in the air you don't have to
draw on the Snowman
oh okay okay I think I think let's see
um let me check test
oh hold on let's get rid of
it oh but everything will only disappear
slowly pomu just take a new a new
pen okay I made a mess how do I show
it
h okay I'm going to to draw her likeness
wait where should I stand so you can
watch
me uh here right I wait I'll put the
camera
here okay I
guess I'll do sexy pose anybody can see
dra me like one of your French
frogs sounds like a french
fry French frog excuse me don't turn me
into a french fry I'm more than that
okay let's
[Music]
see well are you an
artist yes
really yeah oh I'm also quite an artist
myself sometimes
so I have a best friend his name is the
pumpy the pumpkin pretty well renounced
yeah the pumpy the pump
is that just the Vinci uh AKA pain
puff uh no are you counting those
Strokes by the
way three four 5 6 7 8 9 10 okay okay
I'll draw the rest in one
stroke wait let me put that here oh oh
that that's good that's good
oh oh oh what what's what the [\h__\h] is
that it's you doing this okay my arms
are not that
long hold on I forgot the
bow I Dre you a little bit more froggy
like cuz that's kind of my style by and
I'll give you some long fingers too just
like me it looks like a
[Music]
[Laughter]
monkey what do you think guys what does
it look like does it look like
me come
here I'm going to turn the
dramatic it does it doesn't what do you
think it's it's it's it's pretty nice
it's pretty nice yeah I mean we maybe
have to work on that on those artistic
skills but as long as long as you have
passion for it I guess I guess I can see
room for
improvement well if you're looking for
an artist maybe you should be at a
museum and not on
Frogger um excuse me wow wow you even
want to be here you should be fighting
for my
lung you're right sorry I am an
artist so [\h__\h]
cute it was so cute I love your frog ver
voice it honestly turns me on like
wow my guys I think I'm
in don't say that I can hear that okay I
can hear that sorry I can hear
everything okay frog uh drawing mission
complete
complete for that you get one hug come
here come here big
boy I can't even touch her I have the
hover hand I'm too
sweaty to change
the that's what you should have done why
did you not you stinky stinky
frog okay they think they can imagine
the smell can imagine the
smell okay next uh wait let me move the
camera
again
a uh can I reach the
[Music]
button your arms are so small so small
but that doesn't mean that I don't have
a a big ego
okay [\h__\h] I can't I like that in a lady
a lady who knows her worth
yeah that's
attractive I I have so much worth I'm
worth I'm worth more than your whole
frog uh a pond
I have six PS by the way six
points and push I think I'm marrying
into
royalty okay yeah now now I can reach it
uh so there we
go so pretty oh wait I cracked the code
let's go p a rock bird let's
go okay wee
we're going this way this
way so starting from here there will be
a new area from
here yeah oh gosh wait cuz this this is
this existed before it was a nice place
where you can Grill some
marshmallows like with this yeah did I
show you this area before
I think so sausage sausage oh you you
you like the sausage huh explored it
myself wait
oh I actually I thought it's actually
getting um darker just now but it was
just a shadow the
contrast very filling
indeed wow holy
[\h__\h] wow
okay I don't want to I don't want to say
anything about that but that was kind of
spicy
wow follow me was just really
delicious wait the
camera uh why does it not turn with me I
don't understand this
camera what are you doing stop that
stop don't I was just trying to protect
you my lady no no no we don't want Grill
frog tonight maybe another night can you
can you kiss my feet to make them feel
better I'm going to blow at
them
did they feel better now Mr Frog
bir much better
really okay good follow me I'll make you
feel even
better wait hold on this path is new bit
there we go guys this is new yeah follow
me do it from behind the ball you guys
can
W oh wait hold on oh I messed
up I'm on the ball now I'm as tall as
you give me
a
the the no why are you trying why are
you always trying to be taller than
[Music]
[Laughter]
me all right that seems to be a solution
for our height
problem yeah now you're actually taller
than
me how does that feel huh finally a lady
that's frog taller than you wow oh my
god get your crotch out of my
face I'm not trying to harass
you sorry I just was excited about the
ball one leg let me carry
this okay stop doing stupid stunts frog
bird how did that
happen why are you
there that was a that was a big jump I
don't know what happened be careful
you're going to destroy the
snow okay we're not going to destroy
come with me this is New Path
okay wait uh I got to do this there we
go now you guys will
follow
[Music]
okay it's so beautiful in this winter
wonder
land wow running through the snow with a
frog by my side Will he win the love of
froggy
waha we will see oh my God and she's a
lyrical genius yeah and now surprise
turn
around oh oh my God
wait
Christmas Christmas Market cute
AKA J and V not Market in German it's a
Christmas
Market it's my first time ever going to
Christmas Market really yeah yeah come
come here at the at the entrance I want
to let's take a picture of like you guys
will have to take the picture
though oh nice
nice this is good this is
good yay welcome to the Christmas
maret frog
[Music]
date look at look at me frog frog B Look
At Me Hold My
Hand beautiful
moment it's like our prom
photos so cute
okay okay let's go in I I heard that
it's not officially open yet so there's
no people actually doing anything there
but uh we can still go
anyway yeah first thing look at
this
[Music]
Anor there we go FR take a picture with
me
[Laughter]
here can you
fit
um wait I think uh hold on let me move
it cuz
uh your camera there we go oh can you
see it oh there we go there we go yeah
yeah
okay Crouch yeah yeah yeah
am I in oh yeah pretty much yay
y so
cute
bye what are we
oh oh yeah we're we're holding a a rain
little
frag what would I want for Christmas all
I want for
Christmas is
you
baby and some cute the Christmas Market
oh really my Advent calendar
video yeah I watched it oh you're so
interested in me are you wow you can say
I'm a little
obsessed oh I like that I kind of like
that on you
okay let's go through the
market there's there's I don't know what
they will be
selling not looking at me we'll look at
the market yeah look at me presents
Market where's all the food oh my God
there's some creepy dolls and one of
them is
M what the
[\h__\h] I didn't notice that hello can I go
in oh no I can't
go why is why do they look like
[Music]
that they I think they want to be
adopted but they got to try a little bit
harder than
that no I've seen that clip of like the
doll from Resident Evil that sounds like
her ah yeah I watch that too it totally
sounds like her it does it
does crazy that's why oh there's another
one here I would like to purchase oh
there is yeah you would you would like
to purchase
one yes
please I think you're a little bit
delusional because there's no one
actually selling them right
now they're right there what are you
talking just take them just take them
you don't have to buy you can just take
them take can I take you're so
close
so close now you're just grouping
them oh that'll be
M oh this is a anti anti- theft policy
this is how you just make the
merchandise fake and then you can't
steal it perfect for frog bir and froggy
waha trust me trust me you don't want to
take this doll home it's going to turn
into a horror doll life dies that's
going to haunt
you how how do you like horror games by
the way frog
bir I'm a big fan of horror games really
if I do say so myself I don't really
like them but yeah maybe you can hold
me while playing
them and protect me so that I'm not
scared
yeah if you don't mind a little bit of
slime I mean I'm also slimy we're both
slimy that's why we're be
together oh wait what's here oh there's
a microwave and I think you can get uh
like punch and mold wine
here o and coffee M I want some I want
some the good juice the hot Christmas
juice juice give me give
me I want why is there no one serving
the frog
princess go uh um I can serve you give
me one moment
really can you reach my arms
really you can actually reach
amazing you're the man for me I love
I love this
guy just get you guy really lanky arms
and you'll forever be
okay that's kind of hot that's pretty
sexy no the beverages are served
hot but you also pretty
hot it's it's cuz it's really in
here
are you okay so far like are you not
freezing from the cold cuz it's like -
10 C
here I'm stuck in the building but I
think I'm all
right get out of there come down here be
careful you're going to Bunk your head
you beautiful head you're so
cute the more I look at you the more
Charming I find
you how did you think when you first saw
me
i i i let's just say
that might just ruin our relationship so
far so let's not mention that well
froggy wa you hopped right on Frogger so
you
know I do be hopping on
Frogger hopping and
twerking looking for the right man got
me into
her okay frog come follow me
let's go let's go this way
first this way there's another little
section here with another
Bridge oh there's a nice little private
Hut behind oh
no you know where it is now they're
following okay yeah yeah I reserved a
private uh Hut just for
us
over here she moves
fast I'm surprised you don't move faster
yeah there's a hot top and oh yeah here
here is the hot look with
candles
wow
w we do a swim in the hot tub wow and we
don't even have to take a close off
because we're already
naked ooh it's kind of cozy in here
I'm feeling really self-conscious now
why you already naked
before yeah but there's something about
being in a tub and
then getting even more slimy
huh chat has like the stalker looking
around the corner
view
where right over that
way hi can't oh there we
go how's it going oh I keep on standing
up let me sit down really
cozy oh look
cute it's so so warm in here maybe we
can lay our first eggs in
here this is a perfect place for laying
eggs right I think they will be well
protected in you don't drink it no no
don't drink the water where I will bur
our children
friend sorry we need a good amount get a
little I'm going to get my camera real
quick okay come here you guys all
right yeah I got something for you if
you are so thirsty uh you can either
have me or this hot chocolate preferably
the hot chocolate oh oh
okay Alis take
one
you ah
drink everybody
compai
[Music]
come I can drink
handsfree
she's so talented thank
you glitching
in me too me too you know I think frogs
are meant to be glitching that's just
our Natural
State it's true I think actually the
funny thing is I think in German
slimy kind of uh you you do say uh slimy
is glitchy
which is like
glitching yeah wait I just realized that
holy [\h__\h]
what what the heck so it is
real you like a marshmallow
ma'am it's so
big actually like in oh my God so don't
go oh my god oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] Crossing some boundaries here but
okay slow slower please can we take it
more slow Mr Frog bird I'm kind of
shy oh my God I'm frighten
you we're both
glitching so frog bir tell me a little
bit about your your frog family do you
have any frog family that I I have to
like know
about um I don't know I was born in a
tub similar to this
okay I think I was the last guy to be
born I'm a bit of a slow Bloomer but uh
you know um by the time I woke up
everybody was gone oh oh that's really
sad
wow but I think that's what made you so
strong to be such a such a strong
independent frog bear
today it's true I had to learn how to
fend for myself and that's when I
created fire you created
fire how
yeah um I just
uh and somehow it just you know there
was also a lighter that was close to
where I was born
so okay a lighter that was a lighter
close to where you were born interesting
yeah can you teach me how to create the
fire another
time oh yeah I'll show you already one
of my techniques and even how not to get
detected by the cops oh that sounds
exciting I I I want to destroy more
things you know and fire seems like an
element that could be really helpful in
that oh Franky waah I think you have
your priorities in order I think you got
a good head on your shoulders a big head
at yeah yeah I know
no I said did I say big a good head yeah
but but also a big one I'm proud of my
big head that's fine you can you can say
it yeah it's very
round that's a good shape thank
you wonder what that skull looks like in
there my skull my skull I I think my
skull should
be pretty similar to yours but we can
figure it out sometime maybe if you open
me up like they do in the
schools I'm going to look right now no
no not now I'm not ready yet no oh
sorry not for not for television but
yeah actually never mind because one of
my one of my family members they died
because the they were um taken apart in
a school by some children those [\h__\h]
humans yeah they spliced up like my
whole family it's kind of
like I don't know I that's what the day
when I decided I have to be a menace to
society and teach them a lesson with
this water
gun how dare they kill my whole family
how dare they how dare they take all the
frogs apart how dare how dare they those
stupid ass kids it's school what did
they learn from that anyway what did
they help them at all rise up yeah frog
let
frogs unite together against the schools
yeah Rule the World We Rule the World
rule the world R the
world I like your I like your political
Ambitions frog
Bird yeah I'm going to you should run
for president honestly me only if you're
my vice president
baby oh frogu and frog B president and
vice president of of the
world sounds good okay follow me follow
me we're going to go to the next we're
going to go inside a little bit and warm
up we're going to go inside scooting you
over guys we're going to go
inside wo where's my chair
there
dad oh it's so nice it's so cozy I legit
want to um sleep in
here this looks really
cozy oh the window everything the
windows are so pretty this is actually
so
cute wow lay down right here or I'll lay
right here can I actually lay down you
could
oh um you're
disappearing frog bir are you still
there
[Music]
frt come come back
uper help me this just you just trying
to see my under skirt but I'm not even
wearing a skirt I'm already you don't
have to do these kind of things to stay
more a you caught
me froggy waa sit
down do you know those videos of like
whole Live members in Fredy just sitting
down cuz that's so special
wait just sitting down yeah like some
people clip the moments of whole life
members in Frey just sitting down
because that like sometimes they sit
down in a really cute way which is
probably just a really normal way that's
so cute yeah so here's froggy while I'm
sitting
down oh my God it's so cute I know I
can't hold on try to capture it on mine
so I can show everybody don't at me look
at
her look at her hi she standing
[Music]
hi wow so wait let me give obsessed with
right now yeah you tell
me I was going to say the one where Mar
son is going to the bathroom ah I love
that one
too on stream it's so funny that was
really funny the will be
[Music]
disasters okay let me let me tell you
something the this this um building that
we're in right now is called
aota it was originally a six sided tent
used by the Sami people of lap land but
nowadays these are often built out of
wood for outdoor recreation it's a it's
it's also good uh to go there when you
going skiing uh on natur nature trail
and then you take a rest at a public kot
yeah there you go hitting you with the
Kota
lore no where did you read that no I
totally knew that on the top of my
head I'm very knowledgeable I can share
a lot of knowledge with you you know oh
I just realized yeah so knowledgeable if
you show this
window wait oh God this is difficult oh
yeah you see the norn lights through
this
window yeah yeah like this oh yeah
W pretty both of them so beautiful so
pretty this place yeah looks pretty uh
flammable
flam don't even mention it get out of
here don't think about it don't destroy
the the Beauty just yet maybe another
time no no no no no I'm watching
you we have to we have to you know be
careful because they built this just for
us we can't burn it just
yet it's so true it's so beautiful
there's a lot of candles
though look maybe maybe in summertime
maybe we can jump into the water from
here actually wait you can go into the
water here there's there an
opening wait isn't this
familiar the
camera
P I fell do you know how to swim I know
help me I I I fell help
me oh um I'm coming I'm going to drown
give me a moment like in Titanic oh
she's going to drown ah help
hold on I have to film your
drowning what the [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
generation of YouTube man they all need
to film everything on Tik toks and [\h__\h]
man I'm dying and you film like a Tik
Tok
hi that's so cute I look like like a
[\h__\h]
baby wait how do I get out of here wait
how do you
jump there okay okay I think it's a yeah
okay here you go oh I stole your thing
from me oh you can take it nice okay
okay I got it I got it I'm back out okay
danger danger zone this is the danger
zone oh you're doing a swim oh you're a
good
swimmer
wow how did you get so good at
swimming uh you know having to escape
one too many times from the
swimming Alat alcatra wait I went I went
skateboarding in Alcatraz once
what skateboarding
yeah I went skateboarding in Alcatraz
have you never been skateboarding in
Alcatraz
I can't say that I have that's really
impressive I think tr's game was it a
GameCube
game yeah Pro Skater Pro Skater four
something something Tony Hawk yeah yeah
Tony Hawk Tony
Hawk yes yes so this there okay follow
me I have I think one more spot to show
you okay yeah we're we're dipping into
all the nice pools and
Waters now is enough
swimming do you guys think he likes
me does he like
[Music]
me okay over here what did you say you
said
something what are you
saying
what are you
doing what did you
say
[Laughter]
nothing there we go okay come here
what's she saying all the time
okay oh oh oh look here frog bird there
there is a cozy area for us to sit in
and oh what is this water bottle doing
here on the
ground ooh I don't know what it could it
be before Oh we will'll have to find out
maybe come sit down
here
okay next to
me
okay yeah
yep we're both on the
[Laughter]
ground nice okay so oh wait I have to
move my camera I'm sorry no grab them oh
[\h__\h] is it because I moved my camera
there it's okay though don't worry I'll
just put it right in front
Okay okay I think maybe I should spin
the bottle or you should spin the bottle
and wouldn't it be so funny if if if it
points to one of us we we should do
truth or
there
oh yeah sorry is
so okay there we go truth or de all
right then you you no I spin it
first okay okay you spin it no you spin
it oh oh okay I'll spin
[Music]
[Applause]
it oh oh
well
oh what do we do about
that then I guess you have to ask
yourself Truth for there and you have to
choose truth or
there I dare frog bir
to oh
yes yes
yes turn the whole building down no
no I know it's our our inner inner
voices you have to turn down your inner
voices just for a little while longer um
I dare you I dare you to uh run in a cir
W turn in spin in a circle
uh 10 Rounds 10 turns spin for 10
turns no not like that
no
two no not like that three
[Laughter]
no FR stand up I'm messing with me oh
yeah oh no this spacious enough
all spin frog spin spin spin the
frog is there a cable there
yes faster
faster I know exactly where the cable is
okay I'm going go the other way six spin
[Music]
spin
oh no no accident
please no we're okay oh what was that
eight something like that nine nine 10
10 yay W how dizzy are you really really
I'm pretty I think like VR makes you
even dizzier than you should be I think
so too I think so
too okay
you can sit down again that was good and
I guess because you spined it last I'll
spin it
now
spin will it be oh it's on me no
way you can uh you can you can ask me
truth or
dare um TR Truth or Dare truth
truth
um what's your favorite way of world
domination oh favorite method favorite
favorite way of world domination um
using Takara as my puppet making her
think that she is in
control because she's quite a strong
lady I will admit so I let her do all
the ground work and then then once she
is close to dominating the world my plan
is to shoot her
down yeah
yeah and then take over the
world we got our priority her room
before yeah yeah yeah I I've invaded her
once but I I thought she wasn't quite
ready to like finish with her work that
I have planned out for her so then I
backed down but I will be coming back I
will be coming back so you just wait
watch yourself watch
Tu you better yeah she'll be back not
copyrighted TR Mar phrase from you can't
get rid of me just yet okay you spin you
spin the
botle
okay
okay it's it's not to really do this all
the time wait spin it again spin it
again
okay oh my God it's on
me trth dare frog
bit um we go truth m
do you is there someone that you
[Music]
love
oh question mark
um
[Music]
um my
mom I love my I like my
mom
[Music]
and
was it something I
[Music]
said I'm going to spin the bottle
now why did you just spin it you just
ignore that I left the room do you not
care do you not forget about my feelings
you just spin the B you alone here
anyway what's going to happen are you
going to ask yourself TR there again huh
what the hell you don't know how to
treat the
lady I um I was gonna say Truth or
Dare yeah I I dare frog birt to propose
to miss frog
you I'm going to get on one
knee done oh wait that reminds me I
actually there's something missing here
okay whoa is that a com com
huh
do you oh
maybe do you take these Cheeto
fingers I will take them CU your
lawful I will take you I'll take
you are you doing
that wait wait and then I TR or dare I
dare myself I dare myself to kiss
you okay I can't close my eyes oh me
neither maybe I
can't well then I'm just going to die
real quick oh what the [\h__\h] what what
the [\h__\h] no [\h__\h] why I was about to kiss
you you kiss me you have to kiss me to
wake me up but that didn't change
anything about your eyes so I don't
quite understand why you did
that I know I don't
know okay I'll kiss you I guess you're a
little bit submissive
[Music]
huh one for you guys I get up how do I
get up wait how do I get up use your
legs what you got them
for I can't get up wait that's how this
ends this this again Romeo and Juliet
all over again oh you okay okay
okay
woohoo we're married we're married
W do a backflip or at least we're
engaged now maybe next time we can have
a
wedding what do you think about that now
that we're engaged we can have a wedding
next time a wedding
yeah
yeah we can we'll we'll find a really
toasty place next time no too cold okay
oh really well I kind of like it here
though well okay we can find some we can
go to the desert next
time the desert yeah go to the
desert well then everybody congratulate
us for our engagement please me hear you
say congratulations W
congratulations W wo he congrats on the
engagement thanks and fin Found Love in
This you did lovely
frog me too I didn't think I would meet
someone like you I thought I would be
alone
forever when my world domination plans
but I found someone who understands me
and my hate for the the world truly from
the deepest of their heart so let's
let's destroy the world together power
frog
power frog power what's up with frogs
and wanting to destroy the world that's
a
little well you don't ask me I this is
how I feel I can't help
it I can't I can't really move my hands
cuz I'm always holding
something I need to be prepared I need
to be prepared for for for destroying
you guys if you cross me oh or even
you okay so with that I I I guess that's
we're going to have our secret alone
time now because you know engaged people
do what engaged people do maybe we'll go
back to that hot bathtub and lay some
Tad
PES oh my
God yeah yeah we better get some good
baby shower oh yeah uh presents baby
shower
M send the check to here yes a gold bars
gold bars
Please gold bars only gold bars that's
the only baby shower gift that we
accept Okay yeah let's let's uh take a
cute picture uh at the end come here
okay put your arm around my head like
it's my shoulder
yay y thank you
guys peace PE peace I can't oh
peace
byebye see you next time when the frogs
are ready to either dominate the world
or get married one of those things
byebye something's going to happen
byebye byebye byebye
by oh and and wah wah
wah can I can I say this girl that's
doing the world termination for me
Takara on Sunday she has oh she has a
free uh birthday concert half a year
late and and um well froggy waa won't be
in her in there Poma won't be in there
either because your model wasn't
ready
but yeah I hope you guys can check it
out I'll be dancing a lot and pumu will
be watching too
[Music]
right will probably be
watching all right then thank you guys
thank you so much
bye-bye
bye-bye check out P's Channel if you
haven't yet it's in my
description quack
quack have to check out kiaha so
[Laughter]
that all
right my compter is over here by Mom by
m going to turn
OB loading screen ending screen loading
screen
I have my ending screen
[Music]
up
ah by the way ah seone boy and no R
thank you so much for the help see model
this beautiful Christmas Market and the
addition of everything and and no thank
you for like changing some things up and
implementing it thank you sh it was
really nice perfect date location thank
[Music]
you