[Music]
so
uh yes i have moved
uh the stream to start a little bit
earlier
uh because there will be an among us
stream uh a bigger collab with
between some japan members and i
did not want to overlap too much
not saying that i i'm not allowed to
but yeah um so that's why we're starting
30 minutes early today
thank you for adjusting my friends thank
you for coming early
thank you for coming to your shift early
i was just out shopping after the
membership stream i was
i went out shopping quickly because i
needed to buy some things
and oh my god unexpectedly unexpectedly
i found um there's a shop in i live in
japan and there's a there's a shop uh
chain called plaza prasad
and this plaza store they usually have
like
uh foreign things like uh
foreign chocolate and so on but in in
summer
they didn't have so much foreign
chocolate uh variety
because they told me ah yeah because it
will melt
okay makes sense i was a bit sad but now
i went again now for the first time in a
long time
and they had so much german chocolate
they stocked up so much
so um i spent
seventy dollars
[Laughter]
i got so excited i was like this and
this and this and
and this and this and this and this
because like there's no other place
in in japan where you can get like
so much variety or like at all any
german chocolate at all
so i got a bunch of kinder chocolate and
i got a bunch of
leibnitz balsam chocolate chocolate
i'm so happy ah and also usually i don't
eat much gummy but i did buy some gummy
that i used to eat when i was a children
a child
today we are playing again among us
normally i played among us yesterday and
normally
before before i played it yesterday i
was planning to play fall guys today for
the first time in a long time
uh but yesterday i was like damn among
us is fun
so don't need fall guys anymore so i
i went for this instead i hope
everyone's happy with that
well well also i changed my settings to
mouse and
keyboard so now i it should be easier
for me to like open the map
and we are today going to play on an n a
server
chocolate chocolate yes german chocolate
is a good investment
n a server let's create a game
this is how i do it right maybe today we
should also try to go to the others but
then i need to like figure out
how they work first why does everyone
play on the scaled battle is there any
reason
why do i never see people play on the
other ones
try polos scale is the best
basic easier
okay we'll start out with a scaled again
by the way
this time i'm going to um open a new
room every time because it seems like it
bugs out
when uh the room gets reused
and and again the rules oh [\h__\h] i let me
you know i have the rules
here leave after you played one game
with me after you joined one game and
the round is over i'm sorry but you
gotta leave
it's time to say goodbye and
don't watch the stream when you're in
the game okay
because otherwise it wouldn't make sense
that you join
you know just stupid don't watch this
ring i know you love to hear my voice
but don't watch the stream please
got it all right
let's go i know you guys are really
quick with the code
here we go let's see how fast they are
o h q p q q
holy [\h__\h] how is this possible wait i
can't move
ah okay now it's with the keyboard oh
okay so i guess
i use those keys okay okay oh my god
the eggs are plopping did the rules i
said yesterday make it more fun
hey you went in yesterday
okay well you can join this round but
after that you leave
give the others a chance please er
i don't know which rules you mean like
the the cool ones and [\h__\h] yeah
no oh very samaritan you were also in
there yesterday
um i guess it would be nice
to leave but it's okay
i murdered well are you wait were you
the white one before as well
oh the one i stalked
oh it's you again um
i would like to apologize
my killer instincts really kicked in
there yesterday
i'm sorry um
but um i would i think um
[Music]
okay this round is okay but after this
round everyone who joined yesterday
please don't join anyone
oh okay please don't join in wait
without we need someone one more person
join please uh oh is it
is it one two three four five
six seven eight but it's only eight
oh i is it only eight now
i try to move with the mouse because i'm
so used to it but doesn't work
how do i use something with when i'm on
the keyboard
ah space how do i get out of the window
how do i get out of the window when i'm
on the keyboard
i'm full see this is what happens ah
[Music]
escape oh that's far away yeah but wait
uh
one okay everyone scatter in the room i
want to count you
one two three wait no stop scattering
stop stop moving stop
one two three four
five six seven eight
nine i only see nine people i
[Laughter]
let's go it goes it goes
okay
let's see if i will get more chances to
be the imposter this round uh also let's
be fair
let's be fair let's be fair okay uh
don't kick me out for no reason
bye bye let's go what do you mean bottom
left shut up
don't know what you mean no two left god
damn it
um with the guy i killed before
uh wait so how did i okay okay
wait wait why do i have tasks though
okay wait i need to get uh
how do i how do i can is there a way to
uh use the kill button um
with a key
cue okay blend in just blend in
should i just kill all of them not
impossible right there's a cool down
goddammit
[Music]
ah okay let's let's not kill in the
first round maybe i i know the white guy
is gonna do a good job
oh [\h__\h] there's a report
oh my god oh my god oh my god
free bodies what the [\h__\h]
oh my god what i found the
blue body
he killed free he doesn't even need my
help let's just help him
win this and the spacey
room with uh on the right side
[Laughter]
oh we might win this round oh no two
disc
ah okay too disconnected ah
oh sorry too disconnected i guess
uh navigation i think
i will try my best to like hold back a
little bit and and
to be a be a good imposter
eh can you vouch for me being safe from
that kill what does that mean
i'm vibing i was locked in starch
wow he's so like okay you gotta give me
a break because i'm also streaming okay
uh anyway let's skip okay
yeah i can't do so many things at once
i'm bad at multitasking
by the way riddle rattle you here too
but he hopefully is closing the stream
so he doesn't hear what i'm saying
green sauce totally green sauce
definitely not miss us okay it was a
tab i see the map okay oh i can see the
map while moving that's awesome
no don't don't kill him no no no okay
okay i'm totally doing this here beep
beep beep beep
beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep
beep
oh oh i'm totally doing that can i
actually help
i guess come on someone do it with me
i'm just not
being an impostor at all oops oh god
it's already over uh okay
uh what whoa whoa
[Music]
oh god what do i do
i'm too scared to do something okay
let's go up here
hi riddle oh there's ooh it uh
okay
let's close doors for whatever reason
wait okay let's i'll be doing something
here
[Music]
oh my god the oxygen the oxygen where do
i go where do i go
oh my god the oxygen the oxygen the
oxygen
ah is it here is it here all the oxygen
oh oh [\h__\h] that was not where you fixed
the oxygen
oh
oh [\h__\h] i hope they don't think it did
was something suspicious
did i do something what up
peeps
i need some more time for tasks
red and green are friends are you
suspecting them to be imposter friends
[Music]
green watched red didn't get oh oh well
i also didn't kill anyone yeah
who have i been following the whole time
live and
yeah keep on an eye for a live right not
me definitely
what about i'm probably too quiet
eh oh yeah is someone
someone locked me in like did they i
didn't even notice no let's not write
down
i did not know it was i locked in
i was did i wait did i lock myself
in oh did i lock myself
[Music]
it skip
i think we're skipping
[Laughter]
okay okay what should we do what should
we do should we try to maybe kill one
i'm just too scared to mess up just
choose
okay if we will kill him we will kill
him
what is there a shortcut for killing
oh god oh god okay wait there's a
killing shh
what do i do
cute okay okay okay cute that's good
that's good that's good
okay okay let's kill him
um
[Applause]
[Laughter]
that was a good kill
how to not be suspicious where what
where's administ
yes me good girl
look loretta is vouching for me what the
hell
why are you vouching for me
i didn't see you
he's a simp i i
barely saw anyone
i keep on staring at the map
because i learned how to have
it open with keyboard
but that's like real actually
that's actually like three like i keep
on looking at the map
oh i am
bottom bottom left right now
like for real am i am i i think i'm
actually bothered
[Music]
it's going well it's going super well
you guys
[Music]
let's vouch for these boys
uh i'm gonna just go in here for a
second and think about what to do next
let's close something
about we close this oh wait ah why can't
i activate that
i thought that cool cooldown was almost
done
double kill to win okay i'm coming i'm
coming
i'm coming who should let's kill some
let's kill someone i'm coming
um hit
yes everyone is running away
[Music]
oh god my head hurts maybe
i should turn down the volume a bit a
little bit i think i'm laughing too loud
oh that was that was good that was good
wow this is so exciting okay but i'll
reopen the room guys sorry
i told you i told you i told you
i'm reopening the room that was fun man
that was fun
yes kda jq
how the [\h__\h] are you so fast i
you can't you cannot type
that was like one second
how the [\h__\h] do you do that guys
what we closed the game on accident
for real though hey someone left don't
leave
okay so can someone you join
come on someone you come in come in come
in
why people leave you you made it so far
how do they do this
wait are we full one two
three four five six seven eight
nine in oh maybe we are ten one two
three four five six seven eight nine ten
oh we are
okay yeah but someone left
okay let's go
don't watch stream boys
let's go oh yeah that's fun that's fun
that's right that was a really good
first round though i must say
um i'd really tried to be better at this
time
by the way where are my tasks anyway i
will try to do better
um
oh wait how do i open this it was so
fast
speed kill
you guys are so fast are you like all
drinking lots of coffee
chiana says self report possibly
wait so black reported
i like your names by the way kfp
also why does white have no name
yeah yep pink was with me
i think it was pink i don't really see
your colors that well
um
i don't know man we should skip i have
no idea how to stick with me
okay
in the center sure
is he really though is he really
[Music]
skip order
skip button
i saw yellow walk from weapons to cafe i
don't even know what that
means does that tell me anything at all
i'll leave the thinking to you guys that
investigating
too bad that amelia fanboy
was killed maybe he could have helped
with investigation
which by the way i really love oyakodon
it's actually like this dude is called
oyakodon but it's actually like a really
good
ah really good uh japanese uh
food what
didn't even get to do it yeah
okay how do we do i
i still didn't figure out
gonna be suspicious again because i take
too much time with these things
nice two at once even
up to here just doing my job what
how do i how do i
ah space okay
[Music]
glue that
probably oyakodon by the way it's like a
rice bowl
with um eggs
and some chicken
so yeah maybe that's some of my members
yep
[Music]
trust me i'm trustworthy
um do you guys have any clue who it
could be
wait so this time red reported i feel
like these two might be working together
uh so it's not pink
it's not me uh
it's probably not black it's probably
not black
could be brown could
be yellow
[Music]
i don't know what it's called i don't
know what it's called
skipper
i how do you guys all know the names of
those rooms by heart
red is accusing too much and kind of
stay with me
stay with me pink pink boy
kind of go here to navigation please
don't kill me
okay so ah
reactor meltdown where's the reactor in
where's the reactor
where is it
i followed that guy i'll just follow the
guy
oh and then okay well i have to win
electrical
that's all good okay so
okay
here i'm downloading my loot oh by the
way i was a little a little bit late to
the stream because i was just looking at
um some loots of marine senpai
uh her mama drew uploaded a new artwork
oh my god yellow leave me alone and it
looked
so so good
what the hell here are the loots that i
have collected
queen is dead
and
he got him in camps who got who in caps
red i saw what who got who we're in
cameroon
red reported cameron i baited him ooh
nice play nice play
red butt might be self reporting
oh i watched you kill it
what walked away came back and saw him
yeah who killed
him yellow
what they what are they both like
uh
uh be sure again each other
oh we can vote both out in one vote
wait i ran past yellow before but he
didn't kill me but
it was very fast so he didn't really
have a chance i guess
accused accused accused are they
accusing each other
oh [\h__\h] we have no time
yellow
i guess
my hr department i don't know ooh yellow
bye-bye
hopefully that was an impostor i don't
know i have no idea man
i really don't know what i'm doing
[Music]
bye-bye
okay let's go to navigation
[Music]
well i'm really slow with my tasks i
i apologize
red goes to red blue goes to blue
pink goes to pink and yellow goes to
yellow
by the way at the end of today's stream
i will
be showing you a
a little thingy for amelia's uh
halloween uh how do you call it uh
schnitzel oh but my tasks are done
with calms are sabotaged
wait let me get there
i'm scared
report was that body already found
before
is brown old body or true
on the way to uh
um anyway red says
reactor on the way to react actor
oh yay that's fair okay
okay
wait bye bye love you
you won't win
i don't even have any reason for voting
him out i'm so sorry
okay we'll be we'll i'll hold this l for
kfb
bye bye vote black vote
[Music]
what's happening suspicious of white
i wonder but with that at least we got
one
imposter out no he voted even for
himself
[Music]
and let's see let's see can we still win
okay wait it's it's down there
um
oh here
okay wait it's finished
huh okay doing my tasks i hope we win
okay we gotta really like do those tax
tasks otherwise we might lose right if
we do the test we might win right
okay okay okay doing my best test
uh oh wait i have one more okay admin
swiping that credit card thank you
for your purchase
why are they following me do your tasks
we don't have time for you sims
don't have time for simping you better
be working
total tasks completed it's blinking
again why is it blinking again
my white is not here the whole time oh
wait it's not here
oopsie sorry guys what are you guys
doing
just go straight to the task instead of
following ooh uh-oh
it's done again it's definitely why
don't kill us
boy
we're staying together now that i guess
that's a good thing oh why are you going
ah don't leave guys when you go don't
leave me alone with the white dude
no no no no no no ah don't kill us
it only has four left now come with me
come with me
why is something down there again
what is this how do i do this [\h__\h] i
don't know how to do this
[\h__\h]
ah
oh i did it i guess i did it i'm not
sure how i did it
okay quick quick quick quick we gotta
win this
[\h__\h] oh god why is no one with me
why are we not winning it i did almost
i'm alone
i'm alone emergency meeting how do i do
an emergency meeting
i have to
[Music]
okay let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go
quick quick quick
no no no no why no
no no no no no wait wait wait why why
why
yeah it was white man i felt it
run out of time [\h__\h] stupid ocean
but we kind of had to stay together
right otherwise if only one person would
have
one third i would have been killed i
guess ah
but was it it was a good round anyway
three seconds not do this chiara top
three
blessed hick i see an emilia fan
niceu we're not complete though there's
one missing got kicked from last lobby
it's n a server n a
ah one left one came in
um wait is this bugged
why are we not 10 why are we not 10
room blocked um
we're starting room guys or should i not
should i keep it i guess nine is good
enough
nine is good enough right
oh yeah oh there we go oh nice oh
let's go close the stream
boys
i think next round i want to try the
[Music]
a different map but i would probably be
really bad because it will be my first
time trying a different map
no problem feeling i feel
i feel a bit more comfortable being a
crew mate so that's all right
okay and this one
sweep swap oh no my card got rejected
no i'm out of money
bank hates me i don't even know how how
these things work
wait how do i get there i don't even
know how credit cards work that works i
don't even have one what
oh body is dead
or two two oh no
no
two i am where am i or where am i
two people died why are you fixing in
japanese
okay so white found
cyan but the other one wasn't really
found the blue one wasn't found
so we don't know where it is red saying
upper left which means he could have
rented from
electrical to medpay start wow these
guys are so smart
how does your how does your brain work
you guys are so smart
changing the start register
is here
red sauce skipper
but they seem to think it's red
could be
if white or black die next round then it
might be the revenge of red
south report think it's red for the
means oh okay
okay i have free tasks over there gotta
go fast
oh it's kind of sad that i'm not having
any mario kart streams just
this week maybe i'm maybe i should do a
gorilla
gorilla so weird i didn't learn this
word
or its usage until i got into
retrobace such a weird
why did i never hear that being used
before
little but there's so many
did purple just come out of the wind
vent
[Music]
so lime vent on cameras
nice
okay
i will believe you
no i'm not believing you i'm not
believing you lyme
lime is a real color though
betrayal
wait was i supposed to vote for yellow
i supposed to vote for yellow no okay
it's fine okay bye bye
even though he was he's one of the
people who think i'm top right oh no
i feel so bad now oh
the only one who believes in my
top right position the only one by the
way this meme is so old now already
there's like people even i mean old i
mean one month but
quick
flynn that what is someone called flynn
what do you mean with flynn what
ah what's up
huh wait a minute
hey what
i don't understand
ah oh
so who is says yellow
oh you dressed yellow
what if it's white but then he wouldn't
call the emergency meeting would he
oh thanks
stop flirting get
a room
anyway
no i belong to kelly
kelly i miss you kelly has been so busy
she has no time to
to to love me
chicken says shut up
does he but he doesn't get kicked out
like this right
[Music]
nice so it was red and
when whoever read and what
nice and i wanted to get my tasks done
feels like so uncomplete incomplete
red and lime oh
okay room restart
but also uh i will try
in the different map now which one would
you like me to try guys
which one is relatively easy to grasp
although i will be [\h__\h] if i'm become
imposter again
polis is it is this the outside one
i saw that in one of them you can go
outside
okay many people want me to do polo so
let's do that one
would be interesting acy htq
speed paint deco
did i not kill you last time
pain pickle pain
pickle
why is that getting censored why is my
my greeting being sent down
[Music]
okay let's go friends
don't watch stream
are you guys ready are you ready
thank you so much for what for what what
are you thanking me for
for opening the room you're welcome
[Music]
please don't make me imposter i i don't
think i can handle being an imposter
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no no i don't
know
i'll leave it to my friend okay wait
where the [\h__\h] are we oh
uh sorry this is my first time here i
don't know what to do
uh what is this okay
i don't think can i fall down here no
okay i don't think i'll be doing much
wait where's my where's my eh
i don't understand where is the task
wait oh wait i can't do tasks right oh
yeah i'm an imposter
wait what
where are the tasks [\h__\h] i don't know
what i'm doing who's my partner anyway
sorry oh that black one okay please do
something
wait let's get both of them
wait what where did that dude go
um maybe not kill him
[Music]
uh how do i kill again
[Laughter]
people are busy with something else
nobody's gonna find him ever nobody will
find him
what is going on here
[Music]
okay interesting
is that the body that i killed i don't
even remember
okay shh where
damn i don't understand this map
at all yet
i have a good feeling it might go well
if i if i do it if i hold back a little
bit i might it might
it might go well wait
paintback was dead no
pain pickle life always very short
eh you didn't see anything
just trying to find
figure out this map
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
stop watching the no no no
no no
stop watching the cameras for god's sake
[Music]
skateboarder for now hey what
for the emma word for the killer who are
you voting for
yourself what
what where the [\h__\h] are we
ah okay that's that screen yeah
but he can't be the kill he can't be the
killer
oh what a nice uh dvd
[Music]
what is this just it reminds me of lord
of the rings
yeah where am i
[Music]
lord of the rings frodo frodo
frodo what can the camera see that is
something i need to think about
i'm just running i'm just running just
trying to find out where the [\h__\h] i am
actually wait i do have why does it show
me tasks
wait am i supposed to do tasks
i know those are those events that i can
use
is it for me to pretend
no no no is this a task here
fake task ah
[Music]
just blending in just blending in
i'm running out of nowhere let's follow
those guys
we're going there oh it's over
ah okay let's go up
i definitely look suspicious right now
i'm just running around like
like an idiot
follow black okay
where where is o2
oh um
bottom left
i am indeed top right
omitted me to
yes yes i am with black
nothing is suspicious about that it's
the truth
truth top right always has been
believe me believe me
oh
any suspicions
not on me i mean someone else
skipper is safe i think
maybe next time
why does why does yellow always vote for
himself
yes okay he killed us all we can do
we can do this okay
this map is really big
i'm going to electrical wait i should
have stayed with black but okay
where's the electric task here
okay let's kill someone
wait someone is close shouldn't do it
now shouldn't do it now
okay wait i should go up uh-uh
don't kill kiara i know you like to kill
a friend of lots of people
oh everyone's together everyone's
together
yeah bye bye i don't know where i'm
going
i don't i'm so
uh six that's still that's still um
black sauce
yeah yeah black sauce why does
i don't know what to say to not be
suspicious give me a give me a good
phrase guys
self report self report
who reported ah yellow
south report i think i think so
yes yes it must be self-report don't lie
to us
lying is not good not good did your mama
not teach you
lying is not good
[Music]
did it smell
[Laughter]
did you take the wallet
okay for real who is says
[Laughter]
yeah bye
i can't do this alone
[Music]
let's go here focus
no
[Music]
you you you have to die no okay let's
stay together yeah totally because that
i'm not the imposter oh yeah let's just
stay together yeah
yeah yeah
oh yeah
[Music]
i know why do they stay together
[Laughter]
hmm
anyway i am top right
it was a difficult situation though they
were never alone
it's okay just do it
it's okay
bye-bye it was not bad for for playing
the my first time though
[Music]
yeah yeah mama
it wasn't bad for the first time i
played this map okay let's go to the map
again and hopefully i'm just a crew
member next time
new room
please don't make me impostered i need
to get to know the map first
oh they be fast they be fast
zad finker seems very um familiar to me
must have sent
some super chats before
uh hello
x
k of port kf
hello eggs
please let me be cruel i wanna
learn this map to conclude
you might
ready to rumble
no why you leave that finger no
no oi wait but we're ten ten
we're ten ten all right oh let's
go but f oh man he probably got like
kicked out or something
i'm sad for him mary said
close the stream my friends let's see
what
friends oh because there's a task there
okay i'm doing this desk
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
[Music]
emergency meeting
what don't do it eh
what what what what did i do
what
you didn't do the kiss what what
what keith what what what do you mean
i'm confused
is it is it bad that i is it
is it something i have to do
yes kiara is very new oh
what
should i go there now uh what
i'll i'll go down there i'll i'll go
there now okay i'll go there now
i'll do it now okay i'll do it i'll do
it i didn't know about this
i didn't do it in the first round either
everyone went down
[Music]
okay i'm here again because i didn't
finish the goddamn task
they'd be watching me they'd be watching
[Music]
me
scared they're so suspicious of me what
do i do
[Music]
is
where is it
how do i get there anyway
goddammit
yes i'm totally doing this ah this is so
stressful this is so stressful
what are we doing here
let's follow this dude oh yeah let's
follow him wait we could have killed
that dude we were both killers there
no one would have ever known oh yeah
let's have him follow us
scared caramel i'm scared please protect
me
i'm scared i'm so scared quiet
is it suspicious that i follow him too
much
i'm so scared show me the way
okay okay bye-bye we gotta say goodbye
i gotta go my own way high school
musical
um hello
no no wait didn't red suspect me
i shall kill him
[Laughter]
oh yeah i should sabotage what the hell
totally forget about that but i should
stand somewhere probably
red is dead nice
it wasn't me okay
nice kill wait red was the one who's
okay very good goodbye goodbye
i can vouch for it
um not done
with tasks yet
definitely not done oh yeah kiana is
safe
yes i'm very safe i'm a good girl thank
you for acknowledging that
i think i'm safe too
[Laughter]
oh i have no idea what i am
i i really have no idea
i'm even more clueless than on the
normal map
[Music]
it's blue purple and cyan
oh purple yes definitely it's definitely
purple yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah you have a good brain
um if you're accusing it
i was with scala were you really
i don't even know but okay let's skip
okay gotta kill uh
is the key thing only in the beginning
let's just follow some rand oh we have
to go up again
okay um
why are they watching me why are you
watching why are they watching me
[Music]
why are they watching me why are they
watching me
where is the task i don't know where the
i don't know where the task is
don't follow me don't follow me i need
to go there i totally need to go there
i totally just need to go there okay
oh apparently we all need to go there
oh [\h__\h] we gotta go up oopsie oopsie
i gotta do my tasks though what do i do
well it's already over what
oh
i gotta go my own way how do i get there
here here here
here okay okay let's do this
electrical oh
oh [\h__\h] we should have killed blue ah
but they would have joined in so quickly
wait why am i oh wait what
what
ah what why
why are you saying gg task queen
me
it's zion no it's not zion
i i was with cyan a few times and he
didn't kill me first few rounds
i i i can vouch for him
eh what i
what is my answer guys what is my answer
what is my answer
i already did it
what
i am um almost 400k
youtuber almost
[Laughter]
very close please support please
subscribe
please subscribe to my channel
i'm like uh 8k away from it i need your
support
i accidentally just pressed a q
but thank god the cooldown was on
oh [\h__\h] okay okay
yeah task win okay
nice got tonight i want to go okay last
round i want to do on the normal map
again because i have no idea what the
hell i'm doing i should practice that
one
that the police i have to practice
wait was i imposed three times now
almost
wow nice name you
got there
no no not kicking ricky no no no i don't
like that
don't really like that name
and one is missing and my hat is
what do you mean my head is scary i'm
wearing an egg
it's not even a hat are you seeing
waiters you can have you can have
chicken eggs
on your head
i want my babies on my head
my members i can carry them on my head
and then drop them
and they're so cute and so cute
oh kawaii
why why only nine
[\h__\h]
hey i did not kill your children i would
never do such a thing
oh well let's let go
don't watch stream boys
let's go maybe maybe depending on how
long this round is this might be the
last round and we do a super chat
reading after that oh thank god on the
crewmate
i've been imposted too much in this
stream
[Music]
wait i don't have to act as if i'm doing
the tasks i have to do the tasks now
two times and two times i was an
imposter i have no idea man what i was
doing
already it's purple
how do you know i stopped rubbing blue
going to react together
oh i believe
i believe i believe
it's not me
i believe about skip boy
but but i remember
chiara says hey why
why would i be says i didn't do it
why wow it's not fair there's nothing
suspicious about me that's rude man
rude keep an eye on purple yeah and i'll
keep an eye on you
my friend i'll keep an eye and he keeps
he is one of those people who votes for
himself huh
my hat my hat you mean the egg hat or
the one that i'm wearing
my hat is not on sale
unfortunately
why is there one of them blinking i
wonder
okay i just
have to not die that's my only mission
and download the loot oh yeah oh
wait i'm busy you guys do it right
i'm busy wait a second i'll be there in
a second
where is it oh it's already over
oh one leaf julie hey it's awesome guys
did you notice it's awesome there's
it looks so pretty when the leaves are
on the ground
and you hear those cracking noises when
you walk
you know what i mean by the way i'm not
a fan of pumpkin spice latte
it's not my thing not my thing
[Music]
oh
do you guys like pumpkin spice latte i
like pumpkin soup but i don't like
pumpkin spice latte or like coffee in
general
red is dead
oh
it's green and who did we suspect before
purple
but purple also says it's green would he
would he i forgot the word again
be short again his friend
brownie too okay uh i think
yeah seems legit a q is accused
i thought it's green didn't see proper
difficult
it
green not friend
ah i don't know who was with me by the
way i don't remember
how do people have such do they take
notes like how do people remember all
these
things what's going on
i guess i go for brown
i go for brown
oh wait we're still seven i
didn't really need to vote but oh well
[Music]
like practice oh man you guys are too
good
oh ty [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
i might be targeted now it's not good
oh wait cafeteria
[Music]
okay oh what's that dude
trying to protect me so that i don't end
up being alone
oh oh oh okay i go up oh i guess you
don't need my help
okay oh well einstein i fear
[Music]
someone closed the door on me
scary
i'm all alone oh don't kill me don't
kill me
huh you you don't dare to kill your boss
do you
that's the good game thank you soon
well i don't have many tasks left that's
cool
very fly sick today a lot of german
words are coming up probably because i
ate the german chocolate oh my god
somebody's dead
what actually i didn't get killed
the whole stream can someone kill me i
would like to be killed for once
i want a vehicle can the killer
kill me next round i haven't
been a ghost in this stream
yet kinda sad man
i wanna do some spooky things
she's very yeah thank you thank you
uh
[Music]
who says
is that different for kiana so she never
gets close no i wanna be a ghost i wanna
go
boohoo it's almost halloween are you
guys dressing up for halloween
[Music]
i'm actually streaming my first horror
game on halloween night
but probably for most of you it's it's
halloween morning or something when i
stream
i'm really um scared of playing
i don't i'm not looking for word for it
if you didn't see my schedule i'm
playing
craven maynard maynard maynard
vote okay
i'll do what you said
okay oh wow okay bye-bye
this game is uh actually uh
it might be the last game because by the
way someone killed me please
because oh
because it's uh 10 o'clock almost here
in the the japanese
manga stream is starting with some cool
members i don't want to overlap so i
would be
doing super chat reading after this
thank you julio
oh look at that little baby wait i
should still be doing task stuff
i will help you win i will help you win
i will be speed i will lead you to
victory
no no no why
why no oxygen oh no
oh no
so it was purple and uh what is that
color
is that what is that looks like orange
but i'm orange
what is that what is that color why does
he have a
cyan dog is that brown
or rhino
thank everyone for playing with me
okay
uh three times four times
two times in that uh po po polar
world polo world and uh i think one time
in the other world
and yeah i was imposter in the first
round now
and i won yay there was definitely some
improvement
i did very well in my first round i must
say um
well for everyone who wants to stay i
got some super chat catching up to do
and we can do some small talk in between
and
otherwise thank you for coming today and
in german we say
i say it to you now usually i say it at
the very end but oh well let's say it
now
to everyone who wants to leave avidas in
see you soon econo
[Music]
we got some catching up to do from last
stream
into this stream so let's go
to the screen i had
fun this was fun this was fun this was
fun by the way i'm taking tomorrow off
and by the way the art on this side is
the one i retweeted from yuna
yunali she drew me a cute
uh aight to celebrate today because
today
uh my the members who joined on the
first day during the announcement stream
hatched show you faces hatchlings where
are you where are you at
there were a bunch of them who came out
of the shell now
today which was really adorable so we
did a membership stream where i watched
them
hatching really cute
yes okay
let's get comfy my friends
okay
and let's turn on some music
all right let's get the super chats
where are they
[Music]
so i think we all we need to start from
the amanga stream i guess
from yesterday everything before that
i'm pretty sure i'd already read before
so by the way um you guys have been so
good
so always sending me nice messages and
nice names
nothing bad happening so i'm just gonna
go ahead without checking oh yeah oh i
forgot
oh well the people who stayed
um will get the trick-or-treat thingy
the people who left too bad for you
how do we do it on a black screen i
wonder
i wonder one second
should i show it on a black screen
let's hide that
i hope i do it right okay you better
screenshot this
[Music]
screenshot
it's a part it's a piece of uh like a
puzzle
to this week amelia um i mean i made
like a trick-or-treat
thingy and
put it on my top right
top right there's something in the way
let's just keep it there
and it's like a treasure hunt
so you go to all the halloween member
streams
and then you collect these uh candies
and then in the end it will become a
picture
yeah it will become a picture that one i
don't know if i'm allowed to say but one
of the members drew like a
halloween picture of us
and yeah if you collect them all if you
go to all streams you will find
uh out that it's becoming a a
big puzzle
trick or tweet halloween happy halloween
happy
am i doing it right okay i'll leave it
on the screen then
hope everyone took their screenshots
bye bye i'll be waiting to protect
now that we have that done
remember
[Music]
hope everyone enjoyed the manga stream
today and yesterday
did you enjoy it
you're free from your egg prison it's it
hasn't been 10 000 years though it's
been only a month
man it's been a month you know um kelly
and some other members though they're
like oh it feels like so much longer but
i honestly don't know it feels like
it just feels like a month i
i don't guess it doesn't really feel
longer but how does it feel to you guys
oh enough is ten thousand years i didn't
know
i don't know if it felt quicker or
slower to me felt like just
just about a month
but but in that one month i haven't been
this productive
in one month for like a long time
i did so many things this month so many
things happened to this day
actually oh it's been a little bit more
than a month the membership has been one
month yeah so it's been like maybe one
month in the week
[Music]
oh
thank you happy birthday
all right here we go
space the final frontier these are the
voyages
of the imperial spaceship assassin to
kfb
what i can't read oh starship carefully
to explore new recipes
to conquer new worlds to boldly go where
no chicken has gone before viva la
[Music]
okay pekka ring general tackling i
stumbled over my words too many times so
this wasn't very impressive i'm sorry
thank you love 67
i'll be the donkey no no you're not
making your own company you're staying
in kfp forever
you love 67 vancouchen i'll be the
donkey deal off 67
playing cats thank
we are the kfp we are the we are the
kiara's finest we are loyal to empress
kiara glory to the kfp
[Music]
very motivational thank you always
wild can't join stream today due to work
but i hope you have a great time kiara
but i'll
oh but i'll be sure to remember to prep
for the upcoming cafe layoffs and send
my paperwork
hey there's no layoffs
and in mode of a chicken saluting
oh i'll think of it
i'll have it in the back of my mind okay
plus one for that emoji that's okay also
support that idea okay
same i love refrigerators
slayers
what are you talking about always
talking about some
weird stuff in the super chat before the
stream starts
confusing me albino was fired
anyway how can you be dressed after
everything jenna has done for you albigo
what the hell happened in pre-chat
did i fire elbido i'll be returned to
trader
why not i love refrigerators
walter jackson general piccolin
pancakian
albedo has gone too far this time the
war ends today he has pushed
me to even fly piccolo's flag in the
pursuit of ending this goodbye i'll be
to my old friend
what
sorry i might have to come to this but i
cannot stand for
this mistreatment any luck what
mistreatment are you talking about
take your men and flank the left wall
discord bros cut off the exits i'm
taking the fight
oh my god what the [\h__\h] is happening in
the super chat
[Music]
this is like a whole a whole like drama
episode
oh because he opened his own business ah
he opened jfp no that is not acceptable
oh i guess i did fire him yeah i kind of
remember something about that
yo el dido
i don't know if you're listening but
you're hired back so
so stop trying to open the rival
business i mean you could you wouldn't
have
gone very far with that anyway that's
for real you didn't have a chance anyway
kfb is too strong put your heart back
against your will i don't care
okay it's probably not here
we're
[Music]
if you want to open your own business
you maybe should stop giving
your ex business super chat
it's not the best business strategy
you're
on to right now
don't you dare don't you dare cheat on
me guys
kfb is the best fast food chain in the
world
why would you even think of leaving me
hey
[Music]
thank you thank you so much for your
support
amongst us
by another player thank you then echo in
your backyard
captain please stand patrick
[Music]
i'm reading you you just sent another
super chat just in that moment
thank you
[Music]
thank you frankfurt inspector thank you
congratulations on finally getting your
internet and getting back in your house
thank you thank you finally it took so
long i moved three weeks ago but didn't
really move in
until yesterday yeah
it was a long time coming isps are a
pain no matter where you are
but not to be honest i didn't have any
of these issues
previously when i lived somewhere else
on my own
but yeah kind of annoying here thank you
also chat don't stack off on the
tangashins
got it
i want to see the danger and your little
eggheads popping out of the egg
my babies uh i don't know how to say the
name
[Music]
oh by the way the the ghostbusters came
today
and they have found two
two dead ghosts so
it's working it's working the
ghostbusters traps are working
yeah hopefully it keeps on working
they're coming back in another like 10
days or so
captain please thank you and sunrise
valley thank you and oliver breading
i'm so used to being super close to the
microphone even though it's not
necessarily
necessary now anymore i keep on like
trying to get closer to it
i can stay away from it now
i don't have to be so close nice
friends night old kitchen dragon jma
duncan
optimus prime optimus prime thank you
patrick chen pakistan
kiryana schmidt thank you and why did
kiala cross the road because
chicken was sad that's a stupid reason
oh good morning
ah the talk show it will it will start
once i have all the things done
uh
i commissioned like a bgm
and the logo and the whole like
background
like a studio background
so it might take a while
i'll turn it up then if it's too quiet
what about now
what about now am i too quiet
what about now what about now whatever
now
hello hello
sneak peek of the talk show name
it's easy i didn't think much about it
it was the second thing that came to my
mind so um
but i don't know if it's smart to say it
now i feel like someone will steal it
but i don't
know it's kind of whole life related so
i guess stealing it doesn't make much
sense but i'll announce it
when the time comes she get the clock
no also i just scratched my neck
i'll hold it as a secret for now
it's very simple it's very simple
where was that optimus prime
[Music]
made sound like a word to teach polka
like pomade oh
wait that sounds like pollinate import i
don't understand it
thank you muchacho
[Music]
thank you so much wow
can't go fast enough to sleep in games
so i would instead sing for super chat
yeah they're just too fast for real
i could never i mean i'm a fast typer
but
wow that's crazy
basics thank you shane cameron's
strategy
the casual commander thank you
yes
[Music]
that was quite the audacity to kill
someone in front of everyone
said i couldn't join in on your games
though maybe next time and orange is not
just those who doubt here i fight
yes thank you for protecting me and yeah
that first
time as an imposter was um
it could have gone better
[Music]
that's too much multitasking thank
please don't please don't i'm like
please don't i don't know how to say it
in english
[Music]
united
if she can be my japanese teacher unless
you would like to are you aware
could i speak some zero japanese
why do you you're not gonna get fired
with kuda as your japanese teacher
you should probably ask me but um
i don't really wanna teach any languages
i don't wanna oh don't push yourself oh
yeah skeleton lives don't push yourself
don't push yourself
now it's just like teaching isn't that
easy just because you can speak a
language doesn't mean you can teach it
er i think you need to like
really
have like a plan on how to teach someone
a language and it's not like anyone can
do it yeah
at least not anyone can do it well
oh yeah being able to sing in a language
doesn't mean you can speak the language
i can probably sing in some other
languages too
it doesn't mean i can speak that
language
i think you guys are misunderstanding
something
i want you to teach your english okay if
she's asking then i'm teaching her
english oh yeah
definitely i would love to
i will have to think about how to teach
her something useful but also
be funny about it but i'll do my best
actually i already
already um uh offered it to her
so i told her i i will do my best to
help her with that anytime so
yeah she's aware
yeah she would be my senpai and i would
be here sensei
kiana sensei
and with some slang in between i guess
because otherwise people are like oh
this is funny that sounds like teachers
some swear words maybe me
so close to 400 you sure about that
are you sure about that
still 7k
a way to go i i don't know what to do
for 400k because for 300k we did um
karaoke but i don't want to do karaoke
every
[Music]
drinking i don't drink alcohol
i want to do something exciting though
interview yourself q a yeah we haven't
done
a q a in a little while so we could do
like a celebrationary
marshmallow session possibly
cooking but like are you guys aware
you're not gonna see
and also that's not possible because my
kitchen is on the first floor and i
stream
on the second floor ah but i do have a
actually i do have a portable like a ih
heater thingy i guess but that's
i don't i wouldn't have a sink i don't
know how much i can do with that
also i couldn't even show you i couldn't
even show you
does that take pictures yeah
drawing stream for but yeah i want to do
a drunk stream but not for celebration
that's
i don't think many people will
enjoy it like that
german snack stream oh
but then i have to eat them all at once
i don't want to eat
70 dollar worth of snacks all at once
i want to enjoy them like slowly chest
ah this is difficult
[Music]
chest with viewers but that's that's
kind of boring
like uh it will be very quiet i wanna
like celebrate
collab but kelly is too busy for collabs
at the moment i mean we don't i guess we
don't really have to do the 400k
celebration right away we could do it
later on as well like not it doesn't
have to be right away
i guess
[Music]
or we could do an unarchived karaoke
where i
sing the songs i always wanted to sing
i mean songs that i wasn't able to sing
before because our list of karaoke
songs is actually pretty um small
so it's always like the same songs if
you listen to the archived karaoke
streams
of other members as well as well you
probably hear a lot of the same songs
again and again
but then oh if i do that then there's
also no super chats i think
yeah cause i can't monetize it
well i guess that's okay
[Music]
i could do and i unite karaoke
uh without monetization and then
after that i guess i could do like a
small super chat
reading stream even though no super chat
were sent but for whoever who wanted to
send the super chat
during that karaoke we can just open a
new stream
and have that monetized if you know what
i mean
and just do that for 30 minutes and read
it
right away i guess that works
oh yeah i guess that works big break
yeah
planning a super chat stream just to
to accept super chats during that super
chat stream
stunks
stunks okay okay let's continue i think
that's
that might be a good idea but even then
i probably will mostly be singing
japanese songs because i just don't
really
feel so good singing english or german
songs but
i might sing one german song
mario 64 rta over my dead body
the elemental 98 dan kashin thank you
for the good stream kiada definitely
won't forget when i laughed at that
first impossible
looking forward to more mangas as always
that was excellent thank you thank you
i
so now there's the membership um
membership stream
oh super chat i think i'll just read
them now
because yeah i will be fine
should be fine
it might match
[Music]
thank
thank you for your support but please uh
take care of your bank account
you have been sending a lot of
red super chats over the past month um
kind of suspicious looking for the top
sauce
i hope um you don't you know
please always put yourself first okay
and some you should treat yourself to
some things too
okay
i have a bad feeling he might be sending
a red super chat right now
i'm rich no problem oh dear
thank you you as well sending too many
red super jets
please put yourself first
okay prioritize yourself but thank you
very much
i really really really appreciate it
you've been getting a lot of kisses
thank you thank you
today we continue our love and support
for our glorious feelings as we hatch
from the bonds of our past and chirp to
the future
as kiara leads us through the night and
into the light together we are
strong together we are kfb
that was a good one that was a good one
yes kfb kfb
kfc kfb everybody jfb
kfb kfb kfc
kfb kfb kfb
march my friends towards victory
towards 400k
thank you everyone thank you general
piccolo
thank you i'll be coming to you soon
[Music]
i was traumatized by the chess game
versus ame let me stay in my ex six more
days i'm scared jokes decided i couldn't
join the first thing
no problem i'm looking forward to seeing
your hats tomorrow then i guess
i'm so happy you guys are hatching and
to everyone who is not able to
to be in the membership no problem
really just you being
here you being subscribed to my channel
is already a huge support i really
appreciate
it thank you so much just keep on
sharing the stream
if you cannot uh like donate or anything
it's no problem just
um help the algorithm by commenting and
uh
i'm on low battery right now one second
what
okay what was i saying oh yeah and you
do the thing uh do the do the sharing to
the notification bell
do the uh commenting and do the thumbs
up thing
[Music]
that's that's really a big help and show
the stream to your friends
and also watch uh
also support the clippers because
many people have said that they
got into future business clips and i
also really enjoy watching clips
so if we share the clips the funny ones
then more people might get into kiara
and kfb
so clips are a very very good way to
support me as well
like making clips or watching clips
sharing clips
you know clippers
i'm looking for the top why are you
thinking about cheating no
no no you're mine don't leave me
we've been together so long now
today has a few clips do you think so
eh there's nothing to clip today my
gameplay was too
good today i was quite good i know last
time
me killing in front of everyone might
have been a bit too bold and was quite
funny for a clip but today i was just
why are you laughing
there's no content to clip today
but i did jinx myself yeah no
stop stop replying to jmfino
oh stop don't you love me anymore
no
kfc is the one and only
are you
don't we have the most wholesome
community
for real though
for real though we are the bestest i
love you all
but don't cheat on me don't cheat on me
okay
vibes not at all
[Music]
depends on what you see as healthcare i
can give you kisses every once in a
while i think that's a that's a good
healthcare system
okay
okay where were we a side quest
here's the to one month of memberships
yay thank you peter hatching begin and
the new chicks be floofy
viva glory to the cave yay thank you
too much sky thank you so much
we shall be born from the flames of the
phoenix
you weren't really born from my flames
though you're you hatched i adopted you
all
don't think about your real mommy i'm
your new mommy
why am i tired i took a long nap
i do have something to do tomorrow for
the first time in
in months so i'm not streaming tomorrow
but i hope i can sleep early today
okay continuing
we shall pay off the way to worldwide
pass for domination yes
and trample anyone that dares to
challenge us just like jfp
we shall be her sword and shield where
can i be yay thank you
no problem but i've been enjoying your
awesome content and beautiful
personality from day one
you're too sweet you're too sweet you're
gifted you're very gifted and
intelligent entertainer who i will
always support oh
thank you thank you
starcraft marine kitchen
darren wade's dankeshen alex auto thank
would you like to join the swedish squad
what the swedish squad brings love and
joy to everyone and i feel like you'd be
a perfect
what what is what is the sweetest one
is that some kind of meme that i'm
missing out on
no one knows
no one seems to know probably not i mean
sounds like a scam
cult
a bad meme i see i see
thank you shane anyway thank you for
watching my stream
general pekka linda broke my
surroundings
sadly only joined recently so it takes a
while to hatch but you dragged me into
the rabbit hole of her life me
it was me it was me
wow you're welcome
[Music]
does that mean she's ground finding you
no because she means you're real moms
and i'm your adopted mom
my biggest story please help oh i hope
did you get out yet
did you get out turkey
[Music]
walter jackson thank you very much
foreign
imagine if i am 3d one day
and i want to do so many things like
like doing a proper
like live concert where i dance
and can you imagine with
not only me being freddie but kelly that
super sexy hot ass [\h__\h]
being in 3d and me together like a
collab takamori 3d collab
you know i will not be able to
leave my hands off of her
i'll be like touching her the whole time
and you can see it
this this must happen it must happen or
like twister
twister me and callie doing twister oh
yes please
but just tell cali twister is an
innocent game
that humans play uh children play it
it's like true it's true it's a fact
it's not even a lie
so it's an innocent game
we will get cali to play it with me
but uh actually
my skirt might not be suitable for 3d
ucci
sleepy
[Music]
it's like um
it's gonna be interesting
i'm excited for that day to come
clipping noises spots
very short shorts yeah but even then
no will be interesting
i don't know what to say to that love
and nicole thank you what about
permission for cancer
impact i have no permission
it's never going to happen mh singing
thank you
thank you i want to write something
heartwarming but brade needs to sleep
in short kyada you're the best thank you
so so so so so much
thank you okay
now
you help keep me motivated and working
hard at my job because you make my day
that much happier just keep
doing your best and make your friends
happy we'll do our best to supporting
you
and there's no kfp without their
attention afterwards that's right
that's right thank you so much for
following me on my journey
thank you
[Music]
australia is feeding me
will will there be crocodile meat
i think i tried that before
is that a normal thing they eat over
there
i don't remember the taste tastes like
chicken
what crocodile is sweating
is there crocodile beecher i wonder
how tama cooking oh
i respectfully refused
[Music]
um
i'm really happy being introduced to the
community you have you make my day a lot
more enjoyable and give me something to
look forward after my class oh
thank you it's very wholesome community
you're welcome to be a part of it all of
you
catch monkey
thank you called m wong
you will have plenty of chicken and
23 months you will have so many buckets
you want me to read
thank you thank
i still have leftovers from yesterday
gonna eat that after the stream
friendly neighborhood lesbian dankeshen
congratulations on hatching
over the past month you've become my
favorite and have brought many smiles to
my face your streams are so much fun
thank you so much
yeah i'm really glad to be someone's
favorite
i was i was hoping that i could be
at least someone's favorite so
now having people tell me that i'm their
favorite
makes me very very happy
[Music]
glad to be a member for a month now
really glad i became a member of ucana i
will love you and be safe shopping thank
you thank you soon
i wanted to hatch more puns but i
cracked under pressure good luck today
kiara
i know you'll shell out some excellent
moves
okay that's enough
thank you playing cats
ps5 with my celery osakiara on second
fault i'll buy the entire stock of
german chocolate from the store
seems accurate
thank you
i'm done
but i'm not paying for an uk yet no
uh maybe maybe in two days
yeah we'll see we'll see we're getting
there
thank you
[Music]
i recommend having a mouse cursor on the
bottom right of the screen to manually
click ah
huh i think i still have to get used to
that
because i always have to move the mouse
to do the tasks
so yeah it keeps on being in the middle
timofi offland
black friction
i was the last one killed in your first
imposter when you betrayed me when i
totally vouched for your innocence
however it was an honor to die by your
hand
i happily give my life for the kfb viva
la quina
thank you for uh playing with me now
good job on joining the room
yeah did i miss the stream yeah you kind
of did
she's doing a super chat now but you're
welcome to stay until and we're almost
done
with thanksgiving also thank you for
joining the membership
thank you
yeah that that one task the key task
damn it chrome thank you just wanted to
say love you and i wish
i could watch more but i mainly watch
vods on me too me too
because i live in new zealand and your
streams are usually at 1am
i'm a big fan and i hope to see more of
you and remember you're amazing thank
you so much it's totally fine
watching archive is also a big help as
long as you're watching
don't forget to comment and leave a like
and turn on notification bell thank you
soon
thanks thank you
yeah now that i didn't want it i got it
like two times on a map that i
didn't know yeah kind of stressful
i've ever sent thank you being able to
watch your streams after work cheers me
up after a long day i always look
forward to watching you and look forward
to watching more thank you so much
thank you do you love 67 thank you
skit
still inside the egg but the train
chickens should be able to deliver to
simping
for an even greater caffeine we shall
rise above all the competition yay
thank you christina
is this how i can get an early ticket
for canada talks exactly
seriously i absolutely love that idea
also any plans for halloween costume my
vote is
for barmaid even if oktoberfest is over
oh
ina actually yeah i would love to see
myself in a
in a diandel one day oh i would look so
cute in the jungle if you don't know
what that is it's a
it's um
[Music]
how do you say a traditional dress
for uh germany austria and
maybe some other countries too
very cute it really um
pushes uh or showcases
the chest area
yes and there's like a lot of pretty
ones
but um they're actually a little bit
expensive
so my whole life i never earned one and
never owned one before
but like all of my friends
they all own the dandel dress like
everyone literally everyone every girl
has a dental uh in where i come from
every girl so when there were like
parties or whatever sometimes you you
wear your dental to it
to all kinds of occasions and not only
to this oktoberfest
and i would be the only one who like
didn't wear a dental or
didn't go there to begin with yeah
but maybe sometime soon i buy my first
channel
i would look so cute in a little yeah
eating sausages and and
bread pretend
captain's girl her dress yes
ah no my mom made like um
like dresses for like medieval
that we went to as a family she made me
some
medieval dresses but those are different
the endless are
much more complicated and special and
expensive
not as expensive as like japanese
traditional clothing but
you hatched welcome
to
[Music]
how does the hatching work it's just
about the membership because i set up
the membership
so that you start up as an egg and then
after one month you hatch
you see some in the chat that are like
little chicks
that look outside of the egg those are
the ones that just hatched because just
one month ago i started the membership
so they remember since day one and now
they
they are on the second level you know
and eventually they turn into fried
chicken and fried chicken buckets
but we don't talk about that right now
let's not talk about it let's just
let it happen
[Music]
so now i reached the end so i shall
refresh
scrolling
[Music]
okay there we go
let me change my sitting position
[Music]
h
i'm going to law school so that i can
defend your loyal
employees in court when we sue kfp for
unfold
excuse me that is illegal
suing kfp is illegal
no no no no nine nine nine nine
nine zero twenty five thank you soon
i keep on yawning
and heading in the resignation soon i
gotta change my dreams
of being the best girl are you for real
are you telling me you're leaving a
membership over a super chat
that's sad
[Music]
you're the reason why i'm really
motivated to try again oh and i'm very
thankful for that you always brighten up
my day keep on being amazing
thank you thank you
jb
[Music]
so i guess i'm forever the white guy now
thanks for being my fellow impossible
this morning you did really good thank
you
yeah we did well we did well
thank you bottom left thank you out
control thank you sixty-seven
what do you get when you throw a
dictionary into a hole
deep and meaningful
[Music]
oh thank you shot 29.
very funny yuzura
very funny thank you
thank you for your support i appreciate
it
so so so so so much so much
in i am clumsy dancing also thanks for
joining the membership
thank you hey kara i had recently
dropped out of college and i was
wondering if i could get
some words of encouragement oh don't
worry about it
i also didn't go to college i had some
educational bumps in my road as well um
i guess depending on the country where
you live in it's
uh in some countries it really just
doesn't matter at all
and others it does i hope you're in a
country where
it's not not a big deal but
i generally think yeah college is not
um your life is not over
if you don't if you drop out of college
of course education is important
very important
but yeah i mean college i don't know man
i don't know man where i come from
where i come from half
of the teenagers
stopped going to school after junior
high school
and instead we have a system we have a
system called lehrer
and you kind of like go to a different
kind of school like a like a specialized
school for three years while also
working full-time for three years in
that specified
job and then at the end of those three
years you have like a test
and for the school you go there like two
months in a year for three years you
know so it's like uh
i don't know apprenticeship and at the
end of the
those three years you have like a test
and then you're like the boss
in that kind of job so that's why like
half
half of the
students it go to high school and the
other
half goes to have that kind of
apprenticeship but it's really not
not nothing weird like some people even
after they did that apprenticeship uh
even those people sometimes go to
university afterwards
there's like so many ways to do it um
but yeah um
i did that apprenticeship for me so i
didn't even go to high school
yeah and see what what happened with me
i'm bringing in the cash
yeah it's not that bad you're a bad
bird i just read burp in the chat so i
said it's not that bird
you just gotta find your way you know
there's uh
even if there's like i i have some
problems
with my education here and there but
[Music]
don't call me stupid by the way
i had to make money i kind of had to
make money
um because i was living alone
so going back to school wasn't really an
option for me
but look where i am now look at where i
am now
um
yeah everyone's life is different you
don't have to go the same path as
everyone else does you can choose your
own path
suzuki
no
okay yes bird brain but bird brain is
big brain have you forgotten
no problem you can watch the archive
hopefully
use it
i'm a nurse working nights in uncovered
i see you wow
thank you for your services must be very
stressful for months
your streams help me distress before i
sleep since you just oh
i am happy i can help you
just so full of positive energy i would
love to say hello and collab karaoke
please one queen song holo yen collab
karaoke
ah that's difficult um but i think
one day maybe if we are all 3d
we may be we will all sing together if
we're like all at the same place but now
we're all over the world scattered
and so it's kind of hard to do those
kind of things you know
but thank you and fight through
i don't know where you live you're
donating in uh us dollars
so good luck um
i'm in low battery mode woof
let me fix that okay low battery
no battery help help
hopefully it will be over soon and you
can
relax again hopefully hopefully until
then
fight oh
when the 3d cloud happens spare has no
detail
since you'll then be an agent for us i
don't understand
what
try doing british accent
uh okay byron
say joe wait we are adopted
wait we are adopt chats
and i just can't do it
oh
adopted moms real moms but without
a joke you make my day with every
stream keep up the great
work
[Laughter]
i tried okay
what do you mean queen shut up yeah
i love british accents just can't do
that myself
british british accent
[Music]
can we send your letters to the oh yeah
you can to the cover crop address on
their website yes you can yes yes
yes yes please do ah i want to receive
letters
you love warms our hearts and i hope you
find your new home cozy sending love
from new york you're my favorite you
thank you that accident was worse than
the chess girls shut up
[Music]
i am so happy to have hatched with
everyone today this is the best
community i could have asked to be part
of
i love you all especially my favorite
youtuber in phoenix
thank you
and last refreshing everything that
comes after the refresh
i will not read are you understanding
what i'm saying
10 9.
[Music]
i
i just refresh
okay no more no more
sorry some of you are too late but
thanks for joining the membership
where did i stop here i think
i'm so happy to have hatched with
everyone today
instruction is unclear this is the best
community i could have asked to be part
of i love why did i
already write that oh thank you at the
time
next time you have brought me a lot of
happiness oh thank you for all the
videos thank you for all the editing
like every stream pretty much
i really love your editing it's really
great
you're basically my daily motivation
thank you so much for everything you do
no thank you
thank you for your best clips thank you
guys you might have seen me retweeting
his clips
and if you take a closer look there's
usually a longer version of those clips
on youtube so there's always a link in
those tweets
check out the full version it's worth it
all right oh next set g
n e x a t g always making those chiata
clips
with zoom ins and stuff like he's really
putting work into it
like he's doing pretty much all of my
streams so you better watch it
he's doing it like every day watch it
n-e-x-a-t-g google hey youtube
put it into youtube watch the kiara
make your dream daniel dress your whole
costume
miss the stream but thank thank you for
making my morning better after work
you're welcome thank you shane
plus container arturia pendragon thank
you
very rapha please sit on me more
thank you soon
yes for members it's a plan for the
members
i'm thinking of getting into streaming
to gain better confidence in my voice
do you have any experience prior to
hello live as a starter that you can
give
as advice for streaming
advice for streaming
[Music]
if you want to stream games then play
games you want to play
and don't don't just play the most
popular games because they're most
popular
because then you also will have a hard
time standing out
but it's hard it's hard nowadays to
start out as a streamer i guess because
there's so many
so please don't feel bad if like people
don't watch you very much i know there's
like a [\h__\h] ton of streams like on
twitch and so on
where like there's nobody watching or
only one person watching and the people
the thing that is important in such a in
such a
situation is to keep on talking even if
there's no one
no one watching there might be someone
like joining into the stream at some
point and if you're just not talking
then they're gonna leave right away i
know it's awkward to keep on talking to
yourself when no one is watching
i know it's so awkward but this is the
most important thing to talk to yourself
every mo
every every thought in your brain
just say it out loud everything every
thought in your brain
is conversation material yeah you gotta
keep on talking
i hope you will go much further than you
have so far i really enjoy your live
shows and i hope
you can go much more ash i'm always
already so much further than i would
have ever
expected ever today is my birthday maybe
you can wish me happy birthday
yes
[Music]
cook
everything that came after that was too
late i'm sorry but
thank you everyone for your donations
thank you thank you
thank you my fruit is dead now so i
shall rest
on today
let's eat some dinner
[Music]
almost 400k
yeah let's see when it happens
next stream is uh the day after tomorrow
i think fire emblem so that will be
relaxing
also depressing because petra turned me
down and
i don't know what to do with my life
anymore
that's just how it is that's just how it
be sometimes
right
anyway thank you everyone for watching
i hope to see you again soon again thank
you to all the members thank you to all
the superjets thank you to all the
normal viewers
i and i really really am happy to have
you all here
you are the best community i could ever
ask for i love you
guys so much
and in german we say
auf wiedersehen
bye bye
neck exercise
ah getting dizzy
[Music]
no no no no no
bye
[Music]
okay
mom