[Music]
hmm
oh
[Music]
do
foreign
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
me
okay
hello hello
hello
hello everybody how's it going
um
welcome to today's endurance stream
[Laughter]
i didn't know what to wear
should i do a pole pull a pole
because you're gonna be stuck with my
face for a long time today
i'm still pull what should i wear today
uh
kimono okay
um
casual
uh
empress
or party party embrace
imperteous
uh
wait how many what what other outfit do
i have
just just the normal one right that was
the
or wolfie but i'm not gonna be wealthy
for the whole day that would be weird
uh
but we could say we can say cash
i guess yeah we can give an og option as
well
og with zelda
link hat
nani
uh
um
okay let's go
here's a poll for y'all
please vote oh santi
and
please make your choice we can then
further on choose the hairstyle because
it doesn't have to be this one if you
choose kimono
because
we could also do a straight arrow style
if you don't like the twin toes i mean
who doesn't like the twin tails they're
[\h__\h] fabulous
party with a pacifier hell now
oh hell no we don't we have uh i think
seen last time
that i'm better at the game now i don't
need to be a baby anymore
oh kimono is winning the [\h__\h] i didn't
expect that
can you still hold sword and shield nah
not with this one this is the only
outfit where i can't hold it oh [\h__\h] you
can see my hands sometimes
just don't look
oh i just realized has it always been
like that that
the
the green screen yeah there's actually
that's pretty cool the controller is has
a see-through part that's pretty cool
it's pretty pretty cool i think that's
um
something that
would look pretty cool in real life if
you had a controller like that and the
middle is just see-through
that would be pretty dope
it's on purpose of course four hands god
mode well kimono is winning
[Music]
okay then i mean
i think last time we did a poll about
which hairstyle you prefer wasn't it
kind of 50 50.
um but well maybe specifically for today
you want to see something else i think
um
well at least if i do the
if i do the straight hairstyle then the
link hat would feel better fit better
but i don't really want to wear the the
link hats today
hairstyle
hairstyle question mark come
thank you for the memberships yo
we're getting ready for a long stream we
gotta get comfy and make everyone happy
demo demo democratic decision
democracy democracy
twin tail straight
go
oops
the great has taught me
uh something about
the time when
the swedish king was kind of overthrown
by democracy that he kind of
uh
they that he and his queen kind of
started themselves but then
then the the folks they enjoyed
uh democracy so much that they were like
[\h__\h] you king now we have the the way to
get you out to [\h__\h] you out of here um
don't know if that's really accurate but
[Laughter]
very interesting yeah that's how they
thank you that's how they thank you oh
twintel is winning we can switch you
know what we can switch in between we're
gonna have a little bit of a you know
when my when my head hurts too much
because
having your
hair um
in a twin tail or a ponytail uh in a
pretty um tight one actually does give
quite the headache sometimes
so maybe you want to maybe we want to
open it up
a little bit um
[Music]
it's not good for the skull people i
think i i
i am
when i lived in japan before
that reminds me of something when i
lived in japan before uh like before the
last time before that
so quite a long time ago i was working
with this girl who
let's say
due to
uh
the jobs requirement
and she
had to wear a high
ponytail
every day
um
and afford the job and she often
complained about how
tight
it is and how how it hurts her uh head
yeah
pretty tough apparently
and uh yeah she was not happy about it
because it gave her headache and it made
her hair shaped weirdly
and it's pretty difficult to also have a
what kind of job is this honestly i feel
like a lot of jobs uh require a certain
hairstyle like for example if you're
working in a in a hotel or as a flight
attendant or so as a woman often they
want you to put your hair up so like
actually yeah you know it's not that
rare it's pretty
pretty often like that but
um
maybe
not maybe not everywhere requires you to
have a high ponytail yeah maybe a low
ponytail is good enough and that one
doesn't hurt so much why are we talking
about this that's a weird topic
yeah
not only to be like hygienic but also
just as a
to to make all the employees
look like you know when they're in a
uniform you want them to
look
uniform
yes yeah yeah yeah yeah
why don't you have a pointer what kind
of question is that i don't know i have
to win the house because i want twin
tails
excuse me
okay so uh
for now
okay
we are playing
[Music]
psych we're playing zelda
and and off screen i played uh to get uh
i did the color dungeon
[Music]
they're off off-key they're off june
what the [\h__\h] is this fire them
who gave them that job ridiculous
uh
sounds sounds terrible
um
so i made a different save file uh this
was before i think before the color
dungeon and this was this is now after
the color dungeon
[Music]
i have red cloves now
look look look and uh after doing that
i was running around uh wait i'm playing
on obs
i was running around oh you see i have
19 shells almost 20. i was running
around trying to look for seashells
um and i i was using a guide uh to find
as many as possible
uh at least the ones that are available
for me at the moment
um
so i uh i got a seashell sensor now
there's one up there i think but i can't
reach it i realized that after exploring
a little bit
so
wait i don't even know where i need to
go next i'll remember
more than one safer yeah i know i was
like i guess i'll make a new one for
whatever reason
uh
yeah with upstream gaming i always say
like oh i could do it and i never do but
here i am
uh i did my homework yeah
[Music]
important conversation saved what
you mean with x memories
oh
i don't know about that that's cool
it's so wait how does that work ah
you must dive into the waters of
martha's bay is that what i need to do
right now did i already do that martha's
bait enter the yeah catfish's mom the
closer you get to the wind fish the more
restless he sleeps
shrine
no way i already did it
the island's secret in the shrine see
that tells me nothing though what does
that mean
ginger
[Music]
which ones i did collect
ah
apparently there's really not many in
like the middle part of the map
or at least i couldn't access them
uh
oh oh that's so cool
that's pretty vague exploded right i i
was trying to get there
um
the large section i haven't explored ah
i i tried to get there
i don't know how i couldn't but okay we
uh shall teleport somewhere because i'm
kind of stuck up here
[Music]
let's go
where where is the easiest access point
to get into this middle part
i was trying to go there from here but i
couldn't
i don't see any way to get there from
here except maybe there
but
[Music]
maybe there
the waterfall
what which waterfall this one how does
that one lead up there
um
total
try swimming around the waterfall
that waterfall
we will finish this game today
no matter what it takes i've got a lot
of snacks i got yummy snacks and i have
i'm powerful look at me one hitting
those mobs
and i also have tangents prepared
like literally prepared because uh
they're
ah
they're on my phone although i'm
changing my phone right now so it's not
with me
can't believe you didn't go for defense
i was thinking about it but then i first
i wanted to go for defense because i got
hit a lot but then i realized by now we
have
a lot of hearts and we're gonna get more
so
i was thinking
damage is probably better that way we
can end the fight
quicker
hook shot to the right what
[Music]
i didn't realize that was a possibility
ah
inside
that is genius thank you sometimes i
really don't see these kind of things
even though they are i guess pretty
obvious for zelda players
but for me it's like
how the [\h__\h] do i get over there
oh i guess i need some kind of item or
something
some item like a feather that makes me
fly even further probably
they all have such nice houses man what
is that is that a fruit like is that
some kind of coconut
[Music]
or not
what is that
so you are going to give me a raft or
what what you got
[Music]
will you will he be angry if i throw
this i can't put it down anymore can you
put it down
i can't sorry
and you dare want to go on or after i'd
400 rupees
i guess so there are two ways to ride
the rapids of the rapids raid the goal
is to pick up as many items as you can
the other way is the rapid race where
you try to get to the end as fast as you
can oh rap rabbit right oh yeah rabbits
uh
which course will you be setting today
uh i know that i think there's a heart
piece uh heart container piece somewhere
well we'll have to probably look at it a
couple times do the raid first raiders
uh yeah to get the items right okay and
with the hook shot i saw um while i was
looking at a guide on the seashells i
saw that
um
you gotta use the hook shot a lot
to control yourself the raft is ready
for you go outside and joy thank you
get your feather the feather is well oh
[\h__\h] okay uh
yeah okay
okay
do we go left
or what if i go okay that doesn't work
no hold up okay
let's try this
i'm going down
what if i go left
oh mommy
yes
[Music]
can i make it back to the heart piece
you are a far from any secrets what do
you mean
from do you have a seashell here
are you kidding me i am far from what
about the seashells
no okay no seashells
i got this
sure
totally
oh wait
i want to get to that street
i can't reach that tree on the left
yeah the the stones block it
wait we have to go there like a second
time or i don't know maybe maybe
ah no
shining oh wait there's there's
seashells there
uh
okay
[Music]
i don't even want the hearts uh oh wait
maybe we can go
this is fun this is uh
fun
um
what the hell
what is what is that stream on here
okay whatever [\h__\h] that stuff i don't
want it i don't want it um
[Music]
okay that makes sense
that is a seashell i swear it is a
seashell
let me go there
please um
[Music]
[Applause]
so
now we have 20. that probably means i'm
getting something for like another
present i'm guessing 20 is a special
number
can i have those can i have the money
please
[Music]
what else is there to get oh
[\h__\h]
[Music]
am i gonna be like judged by how many of
these items that i get or does it not
matter
i wonder
greedy me no no no
[Music]
yes yes
hey
rising
i have arrived my friend
now i'm grabbing stuff the rabbit's raid
is over do you want another goal
yes because of the heart piece
[Music]
wait how much was that how much money
did he take from me
which course will he be setting rapids
right let's go
great is good
yes
in this game yes
so how do i get the
piece is there any way to go here by the
way
that is very slow is there some secret
there
well
[Music]
probably there is not anything
just walk there
what i can walk there now
what
the heart piece was somewhere on the
left side
i think it was here i can't walk there
what are you talking about
so
when i come from
wait where where will i be coming from
here
oh
will i be coming from here
okay i don't know
we'll just we'll just roll with it uh
maybe maybe do i wanna go this way
top left go all the way left all the way
left
okay
[Music]
that's all i really wanted now
all
[Music]
no i wanna i wanna go i wanna go to the
very
[Music]
no oh it's so difficult to go die oh god
nelly
yes yes yes
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh
oh can i go back now that going back is
probably impossible but
[Music]
we're going up
interesting
can kind of go up here holy [\h__\h]
i'm gaming
kiana's doing everything the hard way
what i'm just hanging out here
i'm having a good time
yeah
give me that money
how much is one red rupee again 10 10
rupees
[Music]
okay
okay i'm happy with that we got the
heart piece i don't i don't care for the
chest right now i think or should i
do i need that chest because there's
also
um a path there
that seems to lead into some kind of
underground
pretty good profit yeah i can't get it
oh
oh okay
i get it later okay okay now that's good
to know then i don't need to
uh try to force it okay
okay
oh [\h__\h] no
sorry that was a mistake uh i think i
want to quit
do i keep the raft for now
we're always open okay oh i'm keeping
the raft i'm getting the raft i'm
should i go here
oh it stays there hallelujah
wait uh uh
leave me alone
i'm just looking for seashells
[Music]
nope
uh i guess it's above me
what is this place have i ever been here
kokoheitaku
have i been here before
heart piece
i have not been here before
huh you need to the you need to race
what i have to do the race after it's no
support hard please under 30 seconds
oh
i can get that one now what
[Music]
oh huh
oh [\h__\h] ah
wait can the hook shot uh hold on to
that stone
oh i didn't think it would be able to
hold on to the stone for some reason
[Music]
okay well in that case uh we'll do the
race and then
yeah
[Music]
use the feather
i don't think i can get up there anymore
can i anyway we're gonna try to
race
and yes yes yes yes yes uh
i don't know if 30 seconds man what is
the quickest route
route
[Music]
[Laughter]
hundred rupees for that
i don't think i i can really like
collect
a lot of money when i'm focusing on on
the race you know
go of the flow
i don't wanna waste hundred rupees
that's quite a lot of money okay so you
go down here
um
take the first
take the first uh thingy
but the question is does the flow go to
the right side here
or to the left side if it goes to the
right side i'll go here and then i can
try to go straight down from here
and then left
and down
but if i if if the flow goes left safe
before ah
that is a good idea
okay
saved
yes okay
[Music]
okay then testing
this will probably not be it oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] wait wait wait shoot
shoot wait wait
okay
30 seconds
yeah 10 seconds it's not happening
[Music]
fifteen
okay we're reaching 40 seconds now but
okay
[Music]
is that even the shortest route
that was 45 or something
new record though
are you at least going to give me some
rupees
oh wait a piece of heart
wait what you'll get on the ferry then
fruity is doable but
why why am i getting what am i what do i
get for fruity then up maybe an
idol
if you go down the center you'll
probably yeah yeah
hey gutsy
do i want another girl
i guess
[Music]
hmm
separate safe
yeah
let's just make i'll just save again
i don't need to read a little to save
like i want something so we're good but
saving again
i swear it was fruity
wait so it was
34 chamber piece 35 seashell
what if i do 30 does he only give me a
seashell then or does he give me both
stone part for the dungeon oh i don't
even want that and i just want the shell
the dungeon builder is like an optional
thing right
i've seen that function yeah yeah yeah
yeah i remember you can build your own
dungeons i guess but i don't really i
don't i don't care for that we're not
going to be playing around with that
um so i just want to see shell let's try
to get the seashell 35
35 i'll see if again
for good measure
go go
[Music]
i hate it
okay i was i was trying to go down
huh
did i not
what
did i is that did i save before
[Music]
didn't i save after
i loaded the rights the game no
but if i save before the game it works
right
oh so
[Music]
same
ah
i wasn't cheating
i was just doing what you guys told me
to do
[Music]
[Laughter]
try to get the other hard piece i got
all the hard pieces here there was two
hard pieces one on an island and one if
you get under 40 seconds i suppose right
or is there another one not as far as i
know
shout out they'll call me t there don't
call me that
yeah i wonder if you're safe before
talking to him
which
i guess i don't even need to save now
but
i was following orders yes
ah do i really care so much for one
seashell we're not gonna get all of them
anyway i think realistically speaking
okay
i'll i'll i'll do i'll try it again
let's hope that
uh
i'm not gonna be [\h__\h] over again
[Laughter]
in the cave there is a hard piece in the
i mean like after the race
yeah
yes yes
oh [\h__\h] man
go
that doesn't work
what the [\h__\h]
[Applause]
um so what's gonna happen
hook the facts that what
how much money do i have
okay okay okay okay
it's just i mean it makes sense saving
in between the minigame
um when it kind of like it didn't really
start yet but i guess i already paid so
now
let's try again
don't use the hookshot to get oh just i
was trying to float over it in the
previous
try i didn't
just need some several tries
[Music]
[\h__\h] what i don't know where to go from
here uh
hold up oh it's going pretty well
yep
[Music]
[Applause]
oh it was not that difficult it was
nothing difficult if you practice a bit
more i see 30 seconds as a possibility
but not today i don't want to do it
[Music]
thank you
only cost me 200 [\h__\h]
rupees
okay so now we go here
and get a heart container
[Music]
um
i've been in this kfp before what do you
mean
did you lose your memory chimpkin
[Music]
and then we go the same cam oh we can't
go the same way back
wait but then
how do i get another raft don't i need
to explore a bit of the raft
ah can i not get a free raptor
go on a free raft
i gotta are you kidding me but i guess
if i do the i can swim oh
what if i would do the the the
um
the item one then i would at least get
back the money probably
man's gonna make a living i suppose so
i can't go through
[Music]
where where am i even going now
where do i want to go we did this we got
all we needed here
i guess we want to go down here down
there
but i can't maybe if i s
because i can't go through here
you can reach the area from the south
can i
ah is this something i can swim through
or
[Music]
or from the very south
swim all the way here is that connected
can i then go up
from animal village
go north from animal village
i'll try but i'm not sure
[Music]
where you mean because i feel like i
explored a lot of that area already
uh
just pay no
if you say there's another way but first
let's go to the seashell mansion and see
if we get something
is there really another way
do i really not need the raft or are you
guys just bullshitting me
i'm wasting my time
hello
what do you say seashell mentioned
look at something no
god damn it
maybe after 30 seashells again
[Music]
um is there a phone booth
yes can i ask the phone booth what to do
i'm i'm still a little bit surprised
that there is no
dashing in this game i mean there's that
one dash but it doesn't really
help much in my opinion because if you
bonk against the wall then you're losing
time again
have you been to the face shrine it
that is a very interesting room click
it is north of the animal village but is
it also accessible from the animal
village because from what i've seen it
isn't
then let's take another raft
oopsie
um
so
awake
yeah i can get that from here
okay
it is accessible kiara please believe us
really
from animal village really
[Music]
i don't remember though where i would
yeah is it it's not here right you said
you said north right
north is there
and i'll let go enough
that music
here this one
where does that one go again
i might have never been here before
or have i
not there
where where where
where
where this zoo
there's a harvest in the water what
in in in the cave
oh i didn't see that
what
i'm so blind i'm so blind i mean it it
does
hide pretty well i must say
much he did
okay
um
so you guys said not there
[Music]
hello
you're gonna help me get over there
maybe
oh there are two
shots one two the door
the other to the soho
[Music]
first had soho for ancient ancient ruins
speak of the wind face
you won't learn much much there okay
south
um
okay
but you mean like this south or
or
or is that north and then this this is
already south for you what what is south
to you
what is south to you
i'm surp i suppose i just got a
continue on here
hopefully
in your
[Music]
[\h__\h] face [\h__\h] off mate
i hate you
i hate those enemies man
what are you going to say
the wind face slump is long the hero's
like gone
you look around
there must be
seashells here
ah but my detective would tell me huh
what's down here
is
oh dear what
[Music]
um
should i go
down this way
round the tree oh
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[\h__\h]
what
you are a genius sir you are a genius
come here
come here you [\h__\h]
i can't use it in the air oh he's gonna
kill me i'm not gonna waste
i'm not gonna waste any more time with
you you little [\h__\h] wait let me throw a
stone at you
it had to be i mean
[Music]
way
way way way
okay
[Music]
is there anything here
worth exploring
go south yeah yeah yeah yeah don't worry
i just want to see you i'm going
go yourself
are these gonna
um suddenly attack me
let me drink some i got some fresh
orange juice freshly pressed orange
juice here
oh my god
hmm
let that sink in
i love that meme
when someone says let that sink in and
someone replies with an image of a sink
in front of a door
i love that so much that's one of my
favorite memes
no no the korean pineapple juice is long
gone
but i do have pineapples here with me to
snack on later like cut cut pineapples
[Music]
i love that so much let that sink in
it's so cute okay what are we doing here
uh
what is what is the is there is that a
riddle
do you have to kill them
they probably want to eat bombs right
oh
nice so these don't
these don't come to life okay good fun
with me
nice hello
hello
he's running away
where are you going
yeah
okay i don't need arrows but okay a boat
would i that's what i drop them probably
okay
um
okay i'll try i'll try next time
but i guess i gotta shoot into their eye
yeah you are in the way oh oh no you
don't have to shoot in their eye okay
cool
yeah
you look like one that would come to
life
[Music]
um
yeah i
when i was doing the color dungeon i
remembered that this game originally was
on a game boy so originally there were
no colors right and then having the
color dungeon was like a really really
huge
exciting thing
like it was a
rebel
revelation revolution
resolution it was everything right to
see colors suddenly and that changed the
way that games are being made so much
because that that makes you realize holy
[\h__\h]
that opened up so many
possibilities that didn't exist
[Music]
in
[Applause]
the possibility is limitless that's
amazing i didn't i didn't i didn't play
it um i didn't even know about this game
when it came out
uh
at the first zelda game no actually you
know what i i did i did play with my
brother uh we did play on the nintendo
64 we did play
ocarina of time i guess a little bit
although i was mostly watching you know
um but i was not aware of link's
awakening on the gameboy no
what came first the lynx awakening on
the game boy or or or on on the 64.
prepare your spin attacks on yo
well why is this the dungeon
better safe okay
i'm scared
wait but
is it am i gonna suddenly be attacked
with from like an i need i need some
healing though if that's gonna happen
sheesh
[Music]
game boy is way older oh
okay that makes sense i thought they
were maybe like around the same time
oh hello what a nice greeting mozzie did
spin attacks with this boil what
your fairies that is right uh
oh [\h__\h]
wait [\h__\h] no
that's not what i wanted to do
i know i need to jump when he jumps so
that it doesn't stun me i suppose i've
learned that in the color dungeon i
think but how would i prepare my spin
attack so quickly
oh
i don't need to charge it that long
need to do it from behind though i feel
like he blocks it
oh [\h__\h] there you go
fairy tale
oh wait
uh
[\h__\h]
[Music]
wait wait everyone's work from behind as
well okay
i thought i was pressing jump
timing
find it difficult to get behind him oh
oh [\h__\h]
aimlink
your aim is so [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
oh no
[\h__\h] arrows it's not gonna work run
under
does that really work here's a bump
[Music]
yeah jump on the bomb please
oh wait i don't have to hit him from
behind oh tell me that earlier
we should
okay oh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] get out of here
i don't wanna waste all my [\h__\h]
fairies
is he getting faster
i can jump while charging
what
can charge
i could jump while charging
is she
underneath scratch
i should
[Laughter]
oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
i am
no
just no
i'm redoing it on purpose because i'm
not gonna
no
no no
no no just know
items
let me try that
oh oh [\h__\h] i jumped on him
that is [\h__\h] amazing i didn't realize
you could jump
oh [\h__\h] i'm still too careful because i
don't want to get too close to him
nice
me
that is like a million times better than
the prettiest
yeah it was good that we redid that
whole thing
well once you know what works and what's
the best way to tackle it obviously it's
gonna be easier and faster and more
efficient
yes
okay
oh do i need magic powder here
it's vanilla oh the whale
is wasn't there
like a basically a sky whale in skyward
sword
whales seem to be a popular
animal
in
in silver games as well huh
yeah right
i i guess i get it because like whales
they they're pretty ancient they live
for so they have existed for such a long
time huh
um
makes sense just like just like the
owl the whale seems to be a very
popular choice of
animal to present represent something
there's also one in phantom hourglass oh
i don't remember that
[Music]
yeah popular trope yeah
they have something
mysterious about them i guess so because
you know on the water there's like so
many mysteries
so many
secrets and animals that we don't know
about on the water there's there's just
so much that is hidden from
humanity
and um
so much evolution going on there too
yeah
so um what voice do we want for this
to the finder the isle of covalent is
but an illusion
i know what you mean i know what you
mean game
human
monster
sea
sky
as seen on the lid of a sleeper's eye
awake the dreamer and coholint will
vanish much like a bubble on a needle
that is that's pretty obvious but i
think if you play the game for the first
time
you probably still don't get it even
with these hints i don't know
i've already been spoilers by watching a
play through
i don't i don't really remember the
ending i don't remember like you know
the riddles and [\h__\h]
that's pretty unknown i guess so but
like i feel like i wouldn't even
look at the title
but no
awakening
i mean yes sure afterwards
you might realize that but otherwise it
just sounds like you know a hero has
awakened links link usually wakes up
from a slumber at the beginning of each
game and it's like oh god yeah i'm gonna
i'm i got it as a kid
shut up you think you're intelligent or
something like that whoa what wha wha wh
how did you do it in math at school huh
you make your smart or something well i
i can say i didn't play it when i was
younger so i don't know if i would have
understood i don't know if i would have
gotten it but when i was playing uh
watching a playful of it
i didn't understand until it was
actually revealed so
yeah and that was me being an adult
already so
[Laughter]
how did you do in math school i
i did [\h__\h] bad and it was dramatic
thank you
like it was really dramatic [\h__\h] you
don't ask me
don't [\h__\h] ask me
[Laughter]
castaway
you should know the truth
what illusion
what wait what this is not a dungeon
i was getting ready for a dungeon here
yeah
we got the key
[Music]
i hmm
you have read the relief
are these obvious signs not enough for
you
link you stupid idiot wake the [\h__\h] up
wake
[Music]
how can someone like you be a hero
it's a no-brainer oh my god
well it does say the island is but a
dream of the wind fish no one is really
sure
[Music]
see prop i probably at this point was
thinking yeah well it might be a dream
it's a dream of the wind fish but i'm
i'm just like
part of the dream not that not that i'm
watching not that i am dreaming but i am
just the part of someone else's dream or
like no i think i was thinking i'm real
but this world is a dream and uh
i'm so real on it i don't know i didn't
think it through that deeply
just as you cannot know if a chest holds
the treasure until you open it so you
cannot
tell if this is a dream until you awaken
well that's like really really [\h__\h]
obvious though
[Music]
the only one who knows for sure is to
win fish and chat chad definitely knows
[Music]
this is a matrix yeah
trust your feelings someday you will
discover the answer
okay
thank you i i got it link's not getting
it but i got it don't worry
hello you wanna thank you
stop wasting my time
[Music]
[Laughter]
where are we going now where is that
dungeon
oh [\h__\h] i'm dying i need some hearts man
need some height
thank you
uh for answering my my call
oh there's your heart there
let me get that
i don't want to use my ferry
[Music]
stream high challenger yes oh yeah um
let's uh
wait once i find out where the [\h__\h] the
dungeon is i will tell you i will start
a tangent where is that dungeon is it
this
is it this
how do i get there
when i get there
yeah that's that's it so i gotta go up
probably
let's go up first
and see if that brings us
[Applause]
to our goal
[Music]
congress and franklin specs thank you
yeah yeah
never mind guys i think i found the way
to go there is this it
oh no it's not it but it's a seashell
rock mace okay
um
good uh i was saying i was gonna say
oh wait how do i get to the other side
what the [\h__\h]
hello
so yesterday did you guys watch that
stream uh from
council
uh
i had some
time i was chilling in bed but i was
like normally i really don't watch like
full streams of other members i don't
have that much time
uh but yesterday i had a lot of time so
um like i was i had some free time in
bed it was already uh i think it was at
midnight or so
so
i had to stream running on my big screen
tv
yeah
[Music]
getting the best view ever
ministry was it was a ministry
i think they called themselves ministry
right instead of counsel
yeah yeah and i was tweeting a lot so i
was
i was uh really having a good time
it was uh not so cool that they had the
same issues with uh jackbox party as we
did um i mean i could have called told
them
uh they should have seen it coming if
they watched their senpai stream then
they would have seen it coming but um i
guess i didn't
gotta learn from you senpai but it's
okay
um that's that was just like the game
just crashed at the very end but
that's still
okay i guess oh what do i say yeah
your tweets elevated the stream really i
was kind of worried that what i was
tweeting was to yeah bye maybe but oh i
love but oh sheesh
honestly what they wear
what
what they were saying in some parts of
the stream was way more shocking
probably than what i
ever tweeted like holy [\h__\h] i
saw that was on a roll like first of all
the
the [\h__\h] rocket oh my god in the
trailer when she said that she made me
laugh out loud
she made me lol
he made me lull
when he said what did he say something
like i might be small but i can show you
my rocket or something like that
that was funny and then
i think i was just
the the whole
uranus
joke
flew over my head and i understood it
later on when i watched a clip and i
realized how clearly she was
pronouncing it that way i'll i'm gonna
smash you
i'm not gonna say it but holy [\h__\h] did
she really just say that
did she really just say that ki no
oh yeah and i also didn't get at the
moment i also didn't
really get the one
shall we compare clocks or something but
i think it's just because um
since i was watching on my tv the audio
was kind of like
weird like
if i was listening with headphones i
might have understood it clearly
um
holy [\h__\h] though everyone's everyone's
attitude
ah
i oh you could have healed me [\h__\h] okay
everyone's attitude was
perfect
but like
i think they're normally also
like it made me realize that counsel is
in general
kind of like
sleepy sounding a lot of them have these
voices that
they they speak kind of in like a how to
say like a slow
slow way what is this place
[\h__\h] hell man
ah
you can't you get what i mean
like fauna obviously
um
but not only is not only fauna
and
cronie cronin speaks like like this a
lot of the time
and bales literally just woke up at that
stream so she also sounded like that
and and sana i guess kind of adjusted to
sound more like a guy
um
it was so good
what is that crony impression when does
that not sound like crony to you
oh where's my hook shot right here
uh how do we how do we get over there
thank you that was easy
yeah yeah they sounded really chill
all of them so good job on that
i suppose
[Laughter]
uh and crony's love
holy [\h__\h] it stood out so much to me
like most of them were really hard for
me to tell apart with the voice changers
they made them sound so similar to one
another
um
but yeah um cronie at least stood out a
lot with a love
and sanna with her accent was pretty
easy to
tell apart as well
face shrine okay looks very
hot in here
oh yeah
elephants
all these are gonna hit me i know it
okay okay is there nothing else to do
here just walk past okay
oh fight
do i just have to oh
ah
endure until the end and darren stream
he goes on
yeah yeah come at me
i'm just gonna run in circles here
clear now
that was easy
i like the music here wow
it's very
cinematic
oh now the eight bit is
now there's some eight bit
another hodo
just gonna dig a little bit
yeah crony has a really raspy
sound to her voice
anyway so that was fun watching um
and
you know if you watched my tweets and
you might have noticed that i was
feeling very inspired what do we have
here
your current
eh what will you want from me
do i need to get an uh an upgrade a
strength upgrade somewhere else
yeah yeah yeah that was obviously gonna
happen
um
yeah i was getting really inspired and
uh
i thought about oh
wow wow
wow
what's the matter with you
[\h__\h] you what do i do with you what a
deal with you
one of them
i use him to kill the others
sorry brain empty
bring empty style ears
okay you little [\h__\h]
you little [\h__\h]
oh
[\h__\h] you
that's so unnecessary
uh oh
oh is that a kitty or what
oh a purple ropey that's fine too
i can't lift them
i need to become stronger
okay back on topic kiwa come on you can
i'm sure you can uh
uh
tell a story
while
while doing a dungeon right
nope
nope i cannot
uh huh
wait my brain is
i can't balance
i can't roll the dice
[Music]
um
so i was inspired
so dark
i was inspired and
and i already yesterday after the stream
i oh
would i turn them on if they go off is
was there one there nope
i can't lift him
okay maybe later
um
so i already pitched my idea to the
girls
yesterday it would enter the boys
oh chess
oh no chess oh no
uh-huh
and well the boys seem to be in
they did say that
uh they also wanna
some one of them said they also wanna
see like a switcheroo and i was like
yeah sure sure but we've got to make use
of
your
beautiful commissioned art
while it's
there
wait a second
what
big brain
[Music]
is this me being extremely big brain
holy sheesh
[\h__\h]
i'm done with you guys bullying me
oh okay wait i got it i got it i got it
i got it i got it i got it
[Music]
i got it i got it though
got it
okay
timing it's all about timing
i'm gonna have an issue with you huh
yeah i can't
i can't reach him from here cannot
if only you were like
positioned a little bit higher than that
and i throw bums over ah i don't think
so
hey
oh i can but
there's gonna be a lot of trial and
error
oh come on ah
the
timing i'm just wondering you know if i
kill all three of them will i get a
chest
i will okay then then we have to do it
this way
oh oh we could have thrown a bomb at the
crystal
i wasn't thinking that way i was
thinking about eliminating the enemy
first of all well okay
um
yeah so
well now i still have to for i don't
wanna i don't wanna
ah
sorry guys
i'm absolutely useless when i do
dungeons
[Music]
um
i'm saying
um yeah i wrote i wrote up uh i wrote up
a whole like
um
how to say
presentation like another presentation
but like uh you know just a general idea
of
how i would imagine such a stream to
work out
already
already wrote together some details
and um
yeah proposal exactly
and
i also
found a way to implement iris
so it's gonna be a full en stream but
only only if everyone you know
if everyone participates if one of the
myth council basically they all said yes
but if one of them if girls says no i
don't want to do it then i think i'm not
going to do it
because
it needs to be five boys five girls and
and one commentator kind of you know
[\h__\h]
am i stuck now
[Music]
i guess that one is easier to ah he said
but the [\h__\h] enemies are back
okay
little [\h__\h]
i hate it i hate it
and then this little [\h__\h]
man
[Music]
i felt like when i was making the
proposal i was writing down
my idea i felt like it might sound kind
of cringe to
the girl so i'm a little bit worried
about um participation
i don't know if everyone wants to do it
some some of them already said yeah
let's do it
but i did think that um
because i'm currently going with
something like a speed dating idea
um with like a rotation system and the
commentator okay i don't wanna i don't
give away too much too much of my
idea
just yet
but
uh
it's gonna be interesting
i'm already thinking everything through
what the [\h__\h] am i what i'm confused i'm
lost
huh
[\h__\h]
what
i took them
oh needs to be
wait wait wait wait wait wait
[Music]
okay
might be a little cringe now i just feel
like it sounds like cringe when you read
the text but uh i think that the i have
i see a lot of potential in the stream
idea
so
i feel like they just need to trust me
on this one
and give it a try
uh it's it i think in in in in theory it
might sound cringe but if we actually
stream it i don't think it will be that
cringey
uh was it a good idea to turn in blue
biff will probably trust you i don't
know man
it already sounds like a [\h__\h] ton of
work this might be a very complicated
stream idea because oh there's a lot of
like
um stuff to think about and to
like the order and the rotation and the
system and blue blah blue
[Music]
and also i need everyone to be streaming
it needs to be 11 streams at the same
time
so
it's gonna be a bit complicated but i
was thinking
since it's kind of like speed dating
um
i was thinking it actually would be a
very fitting stream to do on valentine's
day or like before or one day after
valentine's day
um you know love finding
finding your
soulmate
for valentine's day
why eleven streams well you will find
out why it needs to be that when it
happens if it happens if it doesn't
happen then i'm gonna
tell you the idea anyway because i think
it's kind of genius
it's cringe but also genius ah oh don't
worry that means it's uh of course you
don't have to watch all of them at the
same time you just gotta
just gotta figure out a system or watch
the archives afterwards yeah
at this rate it sounds like it's not
happening no no no no no no no it's a
genius idea i will make it happen
they said mozart was cringe what why
would they say that
you could just do it as one dating show
no not no i have an idea
and
yeah well we'll do it my way
i have a vision and i will
i will fulfill my vision
okay these little [\h__\h] i hate them so
much
okay come on
okay
i'm not gonna let you hit me again
true visionary yes
[Music]
and and that way we'll have a nice cute
event
and stream going on for valentine's day
originally i was gonna i think i told
you guys i had this idea about doing a
um
also something kind of dating related
you know having some girls come over to
my stream and trying to charm me only
and me having a heart rate monitor on
to also celebrate her challenger
um oh but if i'm doing this big collab
then i won't be doing
the
that little heart challenge
part doki doki challenge
[Laughter]
ice cream
i want that stream now honestly my my
heart rate is so healthy anyway i
probably wouldn't it wouldn't have
worked that well probably unless i
figure out how to
fake my heart rate because
the
the idea of that would be that the girls
would make me doki doki and whoever gets
my heart rate
the fastest the highest would
be the winner of my heart but i feel
like it would be so awkward if no one
really gets my heart to go doki doki
then
it's like okay what what are we gonna do
about this
such a failure damn
okay we have a key
ow
um we do have a key
oh cute
so we'll go here i think that was an ah
wait
a moment ah
huh
no
what was i talking about anyway
what was i talking about
no i'm not really lost but it's just uh
confusing i want i guess i want to go
back to this door
because i can't i wasn't able to go here
was that
maybe i maybe maybe now wait a moment
no
i need a pot but there was how would i
do you want me do they want me to carry
a plot from here
but then even then
it's closed isn't it huh oh yeah i can't
go through with it
where do i get pots for the door
that's for later okay well then i can't
go there now
go on there anywhere either i feel like
was i able to continue here i don't know
man
oh
brain problems here okay and then i
can't move on here even unless i go no i
can't
i need to change this again
oh god these mods
and then
and then you
you have to do you every [\h__\h] time
every time are you kidding me
wait wait
yes wait that might have been like the
only way to really do it though
[Music]
where was that key door
where was that
not here
but i do wonder
i was there again oh the big clever beak
of a mink
into the space where the eyes have walls
okay
i said what when your eyes have boils
what
no way you said that
he did say that i thought i read that
wrong and he meant the walls have eyes
wait what
what
well i guess it will make sense once we
find it
um no
no no
um
where was the key dollar
ah
i need a pot here
i can't go down here
okay
huh
yeah okay
[\h__\h] you i hope that will uh help me
move on
in this dungeon now by going to the one
door that needs a key
okay the plates are oh they're still
attacking me interesting
and now we open this door
are they still shooting at me now
[Music]
uh
okay so
where was that what was i talking about
oh yeah that stream idea that i had
so i hope oh i hope we can make it
happen on valentine's day i will still
do some kind of hard challenger
um
he's cute
ow
what if i block it
oh my god uh how do we play with you do
you want to instead take a bomb
no
um
take his ball oh
he's cute i don't want to take his ball
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
as i said i still want to do the
um
heart challenger a one-year anniversary
stream um like making chocolate cookies
but the other thing would be that
you know the valentine's uh
speed dating collab stream unrelated to
heart challenger but we could use heart
challenger as a theme song
and that way get some
get some uh
[Music]
advertisement going there promote heart
challenger one year anniversary by using
it as a theme song like an opening maybe
i could commission someone to do an
opening with art oh sheesh
oh sheesh opening song opening video
always gonna plug my music hell yeah
especially heart challenger because my
challenger was so [\h__\h] you know
when my my
my channel was shadow banned immediately
after the
what
immediately after the release
wait a second
wait a second there
this is repeating endlessly
where are the eyes of walls is this
where that applies
this eyes does not have walls
what do you want from me
what
what anointed
what if i go back
smart it wait what
what
why
toyota
what if i what if i teleport uh what if
i
teleport from here to here does that
change the outcome
what the yeah where the eyes have walls
it said that i know it makes no sense
but
that's what it said did you forget
amateur no that's also coming up so
yeah valentine's kind of cluttered maybe
[Music]
so maybe that big collab should be
even a few days after or before the
before valentine's day like some some
things have to be a bit more separated
anyway oh that looks new
huh i did it
oh
i think
the bombs were new
or were they not no wait wait what what
what what's going on here
maybe maybe
maybe
uh
why they were collab
ah
i
guess that could also work yeah that
would mean that it will be quite a bit
later though
uh
[Music]
they say lift them but i still have the
power to lift them
i can't
[Music]
maybe
uh
maybe here um
no
i don't know because i was thinking
these look like eyes and here's a wall
so
[Music]
but i guess these are eyes maybe two
huh
but i can't reach that room though
wasn't that the issue
i'm overthinking it
what do you mean there's a door i keep
ignoring
that's not true
i'll try to take a part now because you
guys say they bring the pot
you can't though you can't bring it to
me
steal your stupid ideas
where the [\h__\h] am i
huh
and i can't go from here because it
closes
dark room on the left side of
what so you mean i can't move on here i
have to go all the way to the dark room
wherever the hell that was i forgot
where that was
go down after looping where does it loop
though
where does the loop start
oh
[Music]
well
how the [\h__\h]
huh
look
[Applause]
i already killed all the enemies
can't do [\h__\h] with these
you're telling me i can't do anything
here right now anyway
huh
[Music]
where was that dark room
was it this one
yeah
okay so what the [\h__\h] do you want from
me
oh [\h__\h]
i didn't want to burn you but okay
[Music]
i thought i have to turn on the lights
or something here but turning on the
lights is so useless
what the [\h__\h] are you
[Music]
can i fight those
oh god oh god
oh yeah where the hell was i on the map
here
oh sheesh
oh sheesh man
[Music]
really
what a
horrible
horrible bully mechanism um so
what
i'll leave a bomb again wow i need a lot
of bombs here
i left too early
here we go
that would hopefully do the trick
remember the frustration i had with the
last few dungeons
suffer with me
and help me lend me your strength
come on
yeah okay thank god um really
unnecessary bun okay
[Music]
but it's okay it needs to be difficult
right so otherwise it would be too
boring
do we get stronger yes
powerful bracelet you feel like you can
lift an elephant
[\h__\h] you get out of here elephants
must eliminate all elephant
i i have two fairies i honestly don't
need you that's unfortunate man
man
i've got the power yeah
so now we can do so much more
uh where do we want to go first with
this new power hmm
where do we want to go first maybe let's
go this way
go back
elephants can be used like pots on the
door
was there some
place to oh
i'll wait that door ah okay okay okay
okay
that is not a part but okay we'll take
it
oh
yes
[Music]
girls are the strongest youtubers in oh
[\h__\h] here you need it too strongest
feature was let's drop birth or
strongest youtubers in the world
what makes you say that
i did have a
interesting thought though i was
watching seinfeld
and there was that episode where jerry
was supposed to go
um
to
to a junior high school i think it was
career day and i was thinking
imagine having a child as a youtuber
and then
being called to career day in school and
you would go there and have to say i'm a
v2 book my mom's a v2 book
what the hell would everybody say what
would their reaction be i wonder oopsie
so my mom's a big tuba
and
well
she uh she's best friends with like a
bunny and uh
and death and uh
a peacock
and oh [\h__\h]
oh my god she's also a gamer
yes that's a real job
don't make fun of my mommy
um i feel like that
well you would have quite a lot of
issues make people making people
understand
what the hell you're talking about oh
[\h__\h] do i want to wait
do i want all of these to
disappear
will i get like a will i get a chest or
not
is it worth it during this
yes okay it was worth it
i was not sure for a while
rachel
don't question me about my shield i'm
training to be
um a sword only user right now what the
[\h__\h]
wait how do you fight this one again
you don't find it at all huh
uh
wait wait a
second do i throw a bomb at it
sheesh
doesn't work
huh
[Music]
wow
um
i i i have no words that was ridiculous
that was just ridiculous
so what do we do with you buddy huh
can you jump over for you
[Music]
[\h__\h] yeah
uh
wait how do i can i even kill that thing
rude
[Music]
i used the wrong equation got the right
answer the mini wizards yeah i hate them
that's the second thing you did today
that i've never seen done
and i've played this for many hours
how did you do it
i tried all the other things
okay what's going on here out this is
the boss
ah
i came here for nothing good to know
kokoniko
[Music]
what if i go back to the beginning of
the dungeon and then teleport up here
and we continue there but i also want to
go here
speak german why must i picture oh wait
i forgot i had another king why must i
speak german for you huh
[Music]
you sound cuter what when i speak german
i i doubt that but thank you
actually oh [\h__\h]
aim kiara am
because i like hearing your german thank
you that is i guess kind of sweet of you
um actually ollie
asked me
if i can give her a
a german lesson
and i'm like of course ollie although
i've already given so many
so many german lessons to people
so
i know you guys are maybe
maybe a bit
bored
huh maybe this one no i think i think
the black one goes here because of the
pattern on the on the floor that's just
my theory but oh wait
does it actually
move according to
it's robo
no no no why does it not go in
ah no wait yes it does
uh in that case uh i have to throw wait
a second
i have the furthest one from here
ah
i like that that's cute
i bought a chest set
yesterday by the way just just because
huh
i'm there
what
or do you want to be thrown from here
why am i too close
if i was a horse
chest piece right now
and standing here then i could only go
here or or the other way around but
huh
whatever
okay
this that chess set is never getting
used
well i wanted to have some games at home
just in case i have some
someone come over who
is into board games and stuff you know
i have some friends who like board games
rmt actually
um
she likes to play
something like i think it's just
something like yahtzee it's not actually
yahtzee i think
uh
so i bought a yahtzee set
she's gonna oh bunny she's gonna come
over and play yahtzee in reality with me
at some point
i don't want to waste all my arrows
what do we do with
you oh
and how do i kill you though
i'm gonna kill you without using my
arrows
nice up
okay up or down
let's go up
i hate these enemies uh
jump out
and the darwin award goes to
takana
i mean amen
here we go wait could i have jumped
over those thingies
my chest
magic powder turns the fireballs into
fairies what
really
300 a golden ruby
skit
oops
huh
is it not working
makes no sense
what do you mean
from here
that makes no sense
it's a [\h__\h] horse
if i'm a horse chest piece i need to
stand here
in order to get to here
can i switch it
no it doesn't need switching or does it
i don't know
is it does that really help
maybe it does
wait not for me here
yep
stupid [\h__\h] chess pieces
excuse me excuse me
that just soft lock
myself if i had no bombs what would i do
what would i do if i had no bombs
well still what the hell
well i have to stand here
is that what you want you want me to
stand on this blue tile
no
you want me to stand on
this one
all right
i wouldn't necessarily say that that's
my fault that's just
i don't
there there would be more
logically thinking there would be more
than just one way for it to land there
i think but okay you do you
wait does it not that's it that's a dead
end okay we got the reward for it so
wow
i can't keep up with y'all
too fast man
yeah
okay
anyway
we're going down now i think
oh
boss fight
interesting i have more than enough
bombs so this is gonna be fun
uh-huh very slow
very slow oh you did a flip nice good
job
oops
[\h__\h] you
look here
look at me when i speak to you
not polite
sheets
again they were so kind to me trying to
give me so many uh fairies but
i have no use for them
coming down okay
hey
another one
you don't know
thank you for the offer but
maybe another
time is that supposed to be a shortcut
or
why is there
a path there
not dead
thank you that's not really a super chat
but uh it's a green member message thank
you
naru hodo do i have a key
no
do i want to go i have to go into the
water
what do we have here
did you enjoy your tan in front of you
senpai i sent you my friends and you
you little [\h__\h]
no i did not enjoy it
uh for everyone who does not understand
what they're talking about good to know
that you're not part of the revolution i
guess at least
um yeah another topic to talk about i
was on yesterday on tuesday
i was
part of an
official all life official channel
program
uh
which was
it's not it was not a stream it was an
edited video
that was like just 11 minutes
but i think the recording time for it
was like
an hour
[Music]
oh no
oh my god
when i don't even have enough arrows
okay
i'll win there's some errors here uh
i can throw them oh yeah
uh wait wait wait wait wait wait for it
[Music]
save some errors perhaps
out
come back come back
okay
we did it what was i talking about oh
yeah oh yeah uh recently i've been
uh doing a lot with eofy senpai
um there was another thing actually that
you'll be seeing soon another one where
i was together with eofy
so uh your families with me on the new
year's
uh stream right on the official live
channel
and
then uh
this program
on tuesday
and wasn't there another thing
or is that the one i'm thinking of that
you guys didn't see it
oh yeah the
the announcement stream the whole
festival so it has three things and
there will be another one
i don't know it seems like
it seems like the
management
um really likes calling me and eofy over
for these kind of streams
and these kinds of
um
uh missions yeah
i'm glad i know by you hearing say it oh
eofy yeah it's just eofy hop on top of
the crystals to move forward
crystals
ah
this is what you mean nicely i see smart
ow well that hurts
thanks for the hint though
what the [\h__\h] is this secret medicine oh
that's the one where you don't die right
the one that the fairy applied to me
once
ah
well i guess we could apply it what the
hell what oh was it just applied to me
i guess it was
okay
language kiara and elfie
yeah we were representing our branches
quite often which is pretty cool
and now we're back here nice
i'm i still didn't get up here though
we should probably do that first time
and then go back
to the beginning
[Music]
but yeah i've been getting along well
with her so i've been thinking about you
know we should ask her for a collab
sometime
and give me that what do you mean
did i get it okay i got it
never mind never mind
yeah yep we know it's german too
um
so that's something we could do talk
german i guess but i don't know oh yeah
i did want to say something about uh
[Music]
wait is there no is there another way to
get there from here what no
from here
yeah
uh
really
i have to turn the colors around again
uh
um
i wanted to say
uh
oh yeah cause ollie asked me for
you know teaching harry german but
honestly um if i am gonna do that i want
it to be a bit different from my usual
teaching streams so i was wondering
whoopsie what could i do
like it would need to have some kind of
theme at least or
um
some kind of special system like turn it
more into a into a game
[Music]
rather than just a simple teaching
stream because i've done a lot of those
by now and it's just it feels very
repetitive to myself
i mean if we only do it on ollie's
channel
then to her audience it's at least
something new
um
german chess terms
i guess that would be something maybe
while playing chess
but there's not much to teach there
[Music]
you seem more hesitant to ask for
one-on-one collabs recently are you
really saying that when i
on sunday immediately asked for collabs
uh for tues for monday and sunday
last sunday
three days ago i asked for one-on-one
collabs with amit and nina on monday and
sunday
so i think you're just imagining that
it's not actually true
ah okay good there's one here
more than a collab yeah
yeah yeah yeah um the reason i asked
nana is because she was also she's also
in the game i don't know if she's really
gonna be helpful
um
in terms of
you know
mentally supporting me
yeah
during the game but i i think it's a
horror game but it's not really that
scary i think
it's not like there there's gonna be
like zombies chasing after me in in the
in the game so um
um
as far as i've seen it's just you walk
through a school that's dark and there's
no one around and you just collect some
memos i think
and i guess it's just the the story that
kind of is scary maybe
bananas gonna be there to you know
just hang out make it more interesting
yeah i'm glad she said yes
oh
[Music]
location outside
okay so now we go all the way back to
the beginning of the dungeon
uh
i guess because everything else we
looked at here we don't have the boss
key yet that basket is probably in here
so we
no wait do we have yeah we have one
small key so we go from here to here and
that i think leads to here then we go
down then we go left we jump over the
water reuse the key we go up and there
we go
easy
yeah
warm to entrance
sounds like a plan
it's not as scared of horror as you are
i am actually not sure i don't remember
i just remember that the
the new gen
[\h__\h] the 6th gen
really is bad with horror but i think
that she was just like okayish not as
not as bad as i am with it i think at
least
but as i said the game is not really
scary i was just kind of looking
for
um a game to
um play in a japanese-only stream
and i was looking for it for a while i
wanted to have a game that
is only available in japanese because
then i thought it would make sense to to
play it in a japanese-only stream
i thought um
are we looping again no okay
and then i i realized yo who have era
would be nice because it's a short game
and
uh you guys like the horror genre don't
ya you like seeing that too
even if it's not that scary at least
it's something that's not happening so
often in my um
on my channel
and uh it's short
it's short it's japanese
and uh yeah but to make it a bit more
interesting i thought
maybe i i get some mental support from
nenechi
a nice surprise here will you translate
the lesson in the game i was originally
thinking i could even do it as a english
stream where i translate the game for
you but
yeah i need to i need to
uh make use of the few opportunities
that i have
using a
a japanese-only game to my advantage for
a purpose like that
[\h__\h] you
oh you're a little [\h__\h]
oh my god
oh oh my god um i mean
calm down kid your voice needs to
your voice needs to rest we don't want
to
why the [\h__\h] did i get out of here it
does this one leads to the very right it
must
it must
what do you want why do you look at me
like that with your shiny eyes
staff know about the whole characters
and learn ah i um
i kind of told them
um
like
the
i guess the producer kind of already
knew roughly
like they told me
they told me they want some kind of
funny
um situation going on during the call so
they're like
can you think of any funny situation
maybe you're getting fried
no i think it was
i think it was originally uh
it was originally a bit different
and i was like yeah let's adjust that a
little bit
um
and uh then i
added some of my
lure to it i guess
and uh
and um yeah it was it was funny though
because when we were recording it
they already had some of the sounds
prepared but the rest of it was like
imagination
it was kind of awkward a little bit
because um
i would be acting out like the situation
and then
and then um
they would try to play the sounds
according to
what i was saying or sometimes already
played ahead of time and then i would
adjust like for example
i was i was talking
to the chickens right and then
um i was acting as if they were carrying
me
away
and then they turned on the frying sound
and and then i was like okay okay ah
it's [\h__\h] hot
were still adjusting and adding the
timing of the sounds
sound effects afterwards but that was
just at the moment to kind of
give us all a little bit of imagination
help and kind of a guide too you know
and
yeah
it was a bit awkward but it was fun and
um
i
i didn't know how well they would edit
it like
like you know
if they could really
get my my image my vision across but it
worked pretty well like the whole
thing with the chickens
more and more surrounding me and then
carrying me to the fryer was pretty much
how i wanted it to be
so yeah
it's just a skit guys it's just a skit
to promote kfb
you are not getting anything out of this
unions are still
ng i have the control i have the power
you have no power here
this is all just imagination it's joke
no it's not real
but i think it was pretty funny
they did a great job editing it i really
like it i like my part
and i was listening the whole time um i
was in the same channel and i just muted
myself listening in while
the other girls were doing their part
um
we were recording for pretty long i
think they cut out a lot like especially
vata and bhutan
were going on and on and on and on they
cut a lot from that
i mean they had to we knew that it would
be a short video but they vata and
bhutan
vatama gave them so much to work with i
think
[Laughter]
imagine her skit her part but 10 times
longer
we'll get her one day no you will not
yeah whatever in bhutan is also
a combination
that has been doing a lot of stuff
together lately huh and also me and me
and senpai we were also together at the
uh whole live third fest um
uh
online food fest announcement stream
thingy we might have revolution no none
well nice numbers that you chose though
release the latkami cut
what
don't cut off some meat of vatamis and
vibrance
computer packing lion yeah
on it
[Music]
you mean because yeah i said that they
cut so much release the watermelon
ah okay sorry i didn't get that
to open the treasure chest use the parts
around it okay
[Music]
[\h__\h]
come on
[Music]
wait
you're telling me i have to go
down and then
is there no shortcut
oh come on
it was this moment
[Music]
no
wasting my own time like none other
could where do we go
once
[Music]
what
this one leads to
somewhere
where
where do i go
[Music]
oh my god
ah
what a [\h__\h] pain in the ass yeah
[Music]
i was just happily
see i let go of the button before i hit
the wall but there's a [\h__\h] lag
so it still makes me hit the wall and
makes me bounce back and hit the enemies
is ridiculous
see i i let go around here
and he still keeps on running
and hits the wall anyway where the [\h__\h]
do i need to let go
i am not playing on all the s
sometimes i do it at the beginning of
the stream and then i realize it and i
say it and when i say it is when i
switch from obs
to the game capture screen
[Music]
i am not
stupid
i mean i am sometimes but
okay and the salt the salt is getting
very strong
we are back we are back now
molotov style
that's why there was so many [\h__\h]
pots here
i was thinking it sucks because there's
so many pots
but
like
as as zelda player
as a zelda game player when you see a
lot of grass so you see a lot of parts
then you want to get rid of them you
want to destroy them don't you
understand that feeling
oh my god and especially like if you
need to
um reach like destroy one to reach the
owl first
then
kind of makes you want to clean up
everything before you talk to the owl
but okay
this one's on me i guess
ha
ha okay we have the boss key where is
the bus
when i get there
how do i get there
how did i get there before
why do i have to get unknown
huh
get out of here
how do i get to this
staircase
is it this one
sometimes they're like really far away
sometimes they're close it's really
confusing
[Music]
i can mark that mark them yeah too late
now
[Music]
or
the same one that i took before
you guys say where's the second path
okay
not making the same mistake again
or maybe i am
or maybe i'm not okay
thank god no damage this time oh and
this time
we
go down this time we go down
yes yes yes now i recall
i'm not gonna waste my time with you now
[Music]
open up
safe maybe
finally we're done with this dungeon
let's hope the boss is not too evil
oh
well that looks evil definitely quack
wait yes i need a hint what i didn't
reach the hint
the same i didn't read the hint what did
it say what was the hint
bombs
[Music]
okay
oh [\h__\h] let me go
oh
[Laughter]
so far so good
don't go away
[Music]
oh oh it's not falling down nice
it was like right on the edge i can't
walk on top of it but yeah that's
perfectly positioned well this is an
easy fight
i mean the beginning was kind of scuffed
but besides that it's pretty easy
oh
does that work
oh sheen oh oh that's that's a problem
oh too late okay no problem
yes what
the dungeon is the rambos fight yeah
that was simple it listen up if the
will be wind forever
[Music]
[Applause]
that was not bad
had some problems
with the dungeon but
the fights were all pretty good
wow
the coral triangle
oh listen
[Music]
hey listen
thank you for the pinky
mountain
something calls from the mountains
is it
is it cali
[Music]
i'm gonna snack on my pineapples
now got some cut pineapples oh the many
monsters of this island fear that the
wind feast is about to awaken was about
[\h__\h] time man
that's a long sleeper man
[Music]
the monster's power is real
they may uh conquer the island and
destroy them for who's that they make up
soon
now go to the mountain tower fly like a
bird are you gonna fly
[Music]
am i
a human
gonna fly like a bird are you making fun
of me
you look like a strong old owl
you look like you can help me here
is just a tower that looks like a tower
referring to the other pot what
i need what song you need just what
moment
come on help me
um
okay
what's next if i can't get to the tower
as you guys say
then what's my actual mission i need to
call
i need to call someone
[Music]
oops oh [\h__\h]
phone a friend i'm using the phone joker
uh
i guess we can go there too
how many do i have right now
24. yeah that's not gonna be enough
unfortunately
i think
but we're gonna call
someone
no
wait i just wanna make a call
[Music]
uh
what
huh
wait it's broken
[Music]
ah man whatever
might know some new songs but he charges
a lot to play them
i need songs
uh
a maze
signpost means
[Music]
i guess there's somewhere
here i guess
because where else would it be
oh
okay
uh wait no you're not gonna hit me you
shitty octopus
uh
there was also something a dump his
shack
uh someone said i could do something
there i didn't finish the quest yet
either
but
um who am i supposed to give that
letter to again and also i can get that
heart piece now
today
[Music]
i didn't get that one yet yes oh
okay
i got the heart piece
the song is near the middle of the map
oh
the song that's such a weird way to say
that like the song is lit what does that
mean you're speaking riddles to me
look i'm poking into some of the runes
no
cool link get out of here
stop wasting your time
yeah
signpost maze is not in the corner
writing a fanfic in german are you do
you like have a
one hour delay on your comment or
something that's something we talked
about a while ago but yes i
i will gladly take some ideas
for
what to do
with
only how to teach her german
north east of the beach near une
so
here
uh we were were we ever able to enter
this i guess still i guess we were north
east
or maybe here you know what nothing
looks like a maze here
but i will go to the beach
[Music]
what happened unexplored
oh here
all right i'll go
should i go here or to my first bay
okay
yeah you guys are commenting
in the past aren't you what what where
where is leftover
or up here
oh
i think it's up there
yes yes i get it i get it i get it i get
it i get it i don't know how to get up
there though
where are we oh
oh
[Music]
that's not the way to go there i suppose
congratulations on your one-year
anniversary kit are you are you are you
joking or are you serious right now you
sound serious
are you
joking
i get there from the right i can't get
there from here
[Music]
it must be like this
yeah because i was not able to do that
before so much from going from the right
you go there from above
not from the right
okay yeah that's a lot of signs oh dear
what does it say
start here go this way ah
can i use my thingy yeah okay okay
and that's fun i remember this one
go this way okay
uh should i read this one
go this way
okay
go this way okay
[Music]
oh i can lift those now
whoa
go this way okay
i did not when it was up right was it up
it must be up
[Music]
is it this one
or the one over there
i think it should be this one
oh snap hollow ian looks great
who's it this one the first one okay
go this way okay
well
what is it
am i still on the right track
for that actually or
now go this way yeah yeah that's new
that's new
go this way oh
[Music]
this one
go this way
wow make up your mind
truck
[Music]
what can i not just
oh wait then
should it be this one
what
will they all say this now
[Music]
how is that possible okay i'm starting
from the start and
wait what did it say how cute
go this way
so this
one then we go down
[Music]
man the grass really grows so fast in
this game unbelievable very fertile soil
and dad on an island beach man
i thought i thought beach soil is like
pretty
tough to work with
[Music]
but
i guess nothing's impossible when it's
all just uh um
and
[Music]
wait do they mean
they mean this one right yeah yeah
[Music]
this way
so this is where i'm confused this is
why i [\h__\h] up now
[Music]
obviously it has to be this one right
and then
[Music]
what that's the one i read no
after the rock
this one
[Music]
i guess it's kind of on the same height
okay okay i'll go okay
oh you got that
[Music]
oh okay okay
uh
not that one in the middle but this one
because we didn't have this one yet
either
greg you did your one is this way
well it only took me two tries
no problem
i just wanted to
enjoy this
nice little park a little bit more
all according to keikaku
oh
dinosaur crocodile crocodile
dinosaur frog what are you [\h__\h]
all you froggies don't really look like
a frog okay well i'll talk to you in a
frog language then
um
and why should i pay this
free hun is this
necessary for the story i guess i needed
a song i guess i did need a song okay
yeah okay okay
turning up the volume
[Music]
[Applause]
that's exhausting oh hi smoothie she
looks like what the [\h__\h] what kind of
sounds are you making
nice movie i'm just making frog sounds
she's looking at me very confused she's
like what animal are you
yeah did you hear that
did you hear that she's not a tiny
[Music]
oh
and frog
yeah don't eat me smoothie please do not
eat me do you want to cuddle with me i
miss your smoothie
you want to come here and stay with me
where'd you go where are you i'm here oh
right right in front of me hi baby
hi
hi hi
that was a beautiful song by the way
is this what we'll be listening today in
the super chat reading if we are doing a
super chat reading if we have time for
it and the energy for it
this might be our song today
where did can't go no don't leave me
again
an ocarina
they gave me an ocarina
frog song of soul it's a very moving too
and it can even liven up on living
things
that's not the sound the frog makes
they should have hired me to voice this
character i can make actual frog sounds
i already had an ocarina oh
oh oh i guess i thought it was a
instrument that he gave to me okay true
[Music]
who needs reviving
who needs to be revived
[Music]
hmm
yes
[Music]
wait i want
wait where is that where is that where's
that
is it somewhere down here or is it the
one up there on the right on the hill
run against oh
ah i never do that
on my own
i can't possibly
imagine that there's something in these
random ass trees thank you
thank you
[Music]
okay
we're back in my village
because
i guess we needed to come here
but for what
i should have i should have uh called
the phone booth man
let me do it
[Music]
marine has been gone for a while
so that's not necessarily new
the bluebird ah
well let me see what they say anyway
have you heard of the flying roster of
the village in the good old days they
used to give us rights if we held it
above our heads
ah
now it is lying under the weather vane
is that useful for you i hope so are you
saying that i need to use the chickens
um
to fly over
somewhere are we using the chimpkins
so you guys are the ones who gonna help
me fly
is it gonna be you guys
okay but what about
what about the song
what if i played here
dude
nothing
okay well then i guess i need you but
where exactly am i bringing you to
where do i need to where do i need to
fly
is that a different story a different
issue
or can i bring the chicken down
is that a dead chicken
[Music]
[Applause]
that's a huge skull you got there
what
i'm reviving this boom
isn't that poetic
the phoenix revives a fellow bird and
it's [\h__\h] adorable
what is this
is that is that supposed to be a chicken
a blue chicken
i revive you
and you lend me your power as a thank
you
wow
[Music]
he seems very
friendly oh my god are you cute or what
are you [\h__\h] cute or what how do i
stop flying
oh my god
how long can we fly forever oh
you guys are so strong yo did you like
work out in the gym recently
holy [\h__\h] man
strong bob
where should we go
oh can i fly over these things no okay
man that's kind of lame
you got bob thanks for noticing you're
welcome
you're looking
you're looking different
what what'd you do
i did what did you do
where are we going buddy
where are we going here
we go are we gonna try to go here
we can try
[\h__\h] up
i'm on a date
with my buff chimpkin
man that is absolutely
my dream being
i mean
carried around but in this case we're
being
uh flown around which is even better so
you guys are my private jet now
don't hurt my chicken
[Music]
i'll be careful
so i don't even have to walk anymore
wait where is that where is that
where is where is the
where is the seashell
where is it where is it
see
well we're going are we gonna go up up
here
where
where dokko de ska
come up here
how do we get that heart piece huh
ah
music the fish stirs in the egg you are
there
[Music]
wait a second
house
[Music]
ah you mean the phone house
i know that's not the phone house the
other house okay okay
i just completely give up walking at
this point
fly off the cliff
hello
[Music]
ah you're the one who wanted the letter
finally
i'm so happy yeah
oh i looked a little came with a
photograph oh
what
[Music]
i
i don't
remember meeting peach in this game
is he getting catfished
but was that even necessary wasn't the
person who gave us the letter pretty
cute anyway i don't recall anymore
[Music]
oh she's so beautiful i must give you
something for your trouble
[Music]
we're not gonna be honest here and tell
him he's getting catfished link really
you call yourself a hero you're
supporting this
you're supporting this also my bird is
much stronger looking than your bird my
bird can [\h__\h]
ground pound your bird and make it into
a pancake parrot
just saying a broom
a broom
i guess so
who needs a broom
[Music]
he's freaking out
look how he's trying to escape
[Music]
is there a secret behind oni's part
no
nothing
[Music]
okay i'm sorry about that then
this is a bookshelf what you could see
that okay
oh man i'm so happy to have a chicken
around
[Music]
come on come with me
i need to
where move we go now bird
where should we go can we fly over the
water
yo
where should we go i honestly do not not
all but we see the new area now
[Music]
okay
yeah you can be with me and help me
you're in the game isn't that wonderful
maybe we have to you can get the
heartbeat heartbeat
there was a hard piece here
there was a hard piece here that i
didn't get
out
where out
ow
anyway i guess it's not that not here it
doesn't mean here huh
oh
ew didn't you have a shield a second ago
[\h__\h] you did not steal my shield just
now
disgusting i stink
i need a shower man
[Music]
okay we're going into the cave i guess
have we been in here before
oh
yeah
there's so many places and caves where i
needed to fly didn't i
no
i don't need a comment
yes
and here we have a chest
with more money
okay
wonderful i thought that this would kind
of lead us upwards but it just gave us
some money
[Music]
well then
i am confused
[Music]
wait can i does he no
okay
i wanted to test it out because you guys
said something like fly around or fly
off the cliff
so i thought he keeps the altitude and
we can fly around like that to the other
side but
that didn't work
are those
no
well then i can't do anything
here uh
you can't get that after 700 okay am i
completely wrong here
what what the [\h__\h]
let me ask uri
[Music]
oh not again
i'm taking more damage when i'm flying
than when i'm not flying
don't drop my shield
top right here on top right of the map
okay warp to damp shaft that's not top
right is it
animal village
okay
wanted to go to the animal village
is it because of the broom
i guess we can go to the animal village
very helpful
really are you saying that ironically
i found it helpful
wait wrong wrong wrong wrong made a
mistake
this is animal village
village hidden in the leaf don't you
mean leaf
leaf hidden in the village
[Music]
yeah for the broom perhaps
does someone here need a broom
what did you want
no
okay it does not need a broom
that's another oh
i don't get naruto right wait what do
you mean
i don't get naruto references do you
want a broom grandma
[Applause]
all right are we getting to the end of
this quest sometime soon
[Music]
who needs a fishing hook now
almost done
turn off the beats here
you don't need it you have me
[Music]
so brainwashing bgm
okay
what is it now
ow
orena
herrera
help me
have you visited a head house on the
mountain
there's a cave nearby with something
important in it is it a song
henhouse there's a hen house in the
mountains
a hen house
that over there
all right all right all right maybe
maybe we need to
go through those the cave system again
so teleport to here
go through the
whatever cave is the start i don't
remember
uh i guess
it's probably this one
and then
[Music]
you can go to the left under the bridge
to give the thing you got for the room
left under the bridge what bridge are
you talking about now
go to damp
enough of them okay
go to them
yeah the phone is really useful it's not
a guy though i think
is a lady
oopsy uh
what north north of this
[Music]
wait is there a is there
something here hidden from me
where
huh
how did i never
pick this stone up before
that one
[Music]
are you telling me to not come here yet
oh the wet fish sleeps longer dreamily
in the egg above when you play the
eighth instruments of the sirens in
front of the head we will awaken this my
friend is the only way for you to leave
the island okay
okay so i don't have the instruments yet
i think not all of them
but could i go
can we just maybe blow it up
[Laughter]
[Music]
we don't have enough instruments either
bomb arrow i don't have bomb arrows
but
[Music]
um
so
i guess we'll go away don't go
where's the head house there okay i'll
go up here
perhaps
ah what do you want now
[Music]
but you're almost there go east
the wind face is getting restless
i was just about to wake him up but i
guess he wants all the stupid
instruments okay
uh
are you okay
we can't fly over here can we okay
understandable
i think we have to go through the cave
[Music]
i've been in here before though i think
go let's fly
what was i thinking
oh you have to move those i forgot
i [\h__\h]
ah
what's written on you
[Music]
maybe up here
yes yes
sorry my brain
for a moment was afk
sometimes you just don't want to think
too much about it okay
it happens
come with me my free verb
you and me our potential
is
immeasurable and i just put that i wish
you could put them back in your [\h__\h]
bag
um i wanted to fix the sound the sound
was sounding weird
why do i always
there we go why do i always
always put down the bombs man
oh
sorry sorry burn
money money potential
that is funny
oh [\h__\h]
does the chimpkin ever tire like after
like a certain distance
it doesn't look like it
that is really impressive
that is quite the stamina i wanted to
ask you guys
you guys you guys probably
know the answer to this
let's say let's say i'm going skiing
soon
and uh
i'm worried about
whether or not
i can build
or i can
or i'm worried that i'll have like no
stamina at all and [\h__\h] die
maybe i was supposed to take that one
specific
[Music]
oh what about here
did i never go here before
uh about stamina
let's say i don't i don't know what what
day it was again unless i have two weeks
if i were to work out every day
for two weeks
is that enough time to actually build
stamina or do you think it would make no
difference
in those two weeks is that too short
not enough time
[Music]
really
[\h__\h]
only a bit
man
i need a break every couple of days
i'm saying
you're even white rest periods yeah yeah
please we'll help just don't expect
miracles
how much time would i need in order to
see some difference in my stamina um
i have kind what kind of skin or just
normal skin just for fun
but i still worry a little bit you know
gotta carry all that [\h__\h]
actually i don't need stamina for that i
guess i need uh
i do need some muscles what about two
weeks muscle training for my arms
would i have less problems carrying all
my [\h__\h] or not
how do i get buff guys
how how much time does it take to get
buff
no not enough time i thought so
because like holy [\h__\h] like we're not
going by a car because
rmt and boo and me we both don't have a
license
and um we both don't have a car
so um all that [\h__\h] skiing equipment
that we have
uh
got carried all through i don't know
train i suppose
and to the to the train station and then
from the train station to wherever the
[\h__\h] we're going
and at the hotel
carrying carrying skis and [\h__\h] up a
mountain i already had a little bit of
experience with dad in hokkaido with
with um
cali and it was a pain in the ass
today
no i don't think i can get anyone to
help unless i invite them for a free
um
room in our hotel to go skiing with us
they don't have sk of course but there's
still like certain distance
distances to the ski
lift sometimes that you have to
um
depending on the layout of wherever the
hell you are but some layouts are just
not the smartest and then you gotta
still carry your [\h__\h] around for quite
some time
and
okay
yeah it's been like a year
a year since still trip
of cali oh look
once chicken friends
look at that little
what is that that little
statue puppet whatever
[Music]
you guys do look like you have hearts in
your face now that i look at it
i've never seen that before
at least
with that design
and those eggs oh those painted eggs so
cute we're gonna do the same for easter
you guys are not even eating what he
gives to you
can we bathe them you stinky little
chimpkin oh thank you
are you guys not wondering why the
chicken that i brought here is blue did
you can see color
are you guys color blind
you guys realize that the friend i
brought is blue
look i can fly i'm a chimpkin too
[Music]
i see only orange
we are colorblind chickens do you see
color they see colors the only colors is
orange understandable
oh
maybe the rooster is actually flying yes
yours can do it too just believe in them
when they will believe in the one who
believes in them
um is your slogan oh have you tried to
hold him over your head of course i have
cook
[Music]
that's that's all
that's it
oh i guess you just want me to go over
what did i come here for i mean i could
have guessed that by myself
[Music]
they have better television than humans
whatever
[Music]
what
i guess birds in general have good eyes
huh
okay across this bridge or across the
other bridge where where do we want to
go
where do we want to go
[Music]
well remember then there's a key thing
in here
okay i guess the other one
[Music]
just wanted to check out what's here
anyway
come with me
[Music]
is the legend of zelda
the chimpkins awakening
[Applause]
[Music]
was i supposed to come here first
no
what about what about here though ah
i'll go here first
[Applause]
where is this leading me to
heart container
[Music]
thank you that was worth it
i still don't need to go here wait the
left side you think you mean
do i need to go like down
here no but i already was here before
i'm guessing
east
the cave under the chicken house
this one
can i fly down in there from like here
for example
that leads to the eighth dungeon oh okay
under the hen house
can i like
no okay
what
no
[Music]
what
you mean that one
but haven't i already been here before
it's not
oh no i haven't
ah
let's see
left first ah
oh but that does look kind of familiar
to me
huh
what
it's a chicken key
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay so this is a little bit of a riddle
uh
say remove this and now we move this
and then we move this
oh wait i can i mean i can also fly
so
wait what am i thinking
i can just fly through here
why make it complicated
[Music]
why did they put all those stones there
if you can't just fly there anyway
to confuse players like me
who have a problem using their brain to
begin with
um
now
the bird came
is that for the tower
sorry i'm eating pineapples
it is for the tower okay
how about we just use the blue bird to
fly all the way to the top instead of
going inside
[Music]
i feel like that would be so much
smarter but
okay so how do we get there we go up
can we go down from here
you have to go above or
a little here
i remember
when i started this episode i was here
wasn't i
i went for all these caves just to
explore a little bit and then i realized
i cannot go anywhere from here
yeah yeah yeah yeah
i remember i do
uh but that still leaves me with the
question where did i enter
where i guess maybe here
[Music]
what a heart container
that needed the birds yeah there was
probably one at least but
i don't want to go there now we're on
the track now
and i don't want to go off track
go here
pineapple and pizza is illegal
i do not agree i already did this one
battle it i think i did this off stream
as well
um
the funny thing here is you can only
really i think
i came to the conclusion that you can
only open all of them if you enter the
room from below
and yeah
then if you open the last chest you get
i'll be groupie
but this was not where i needed to go
after all
okay that's fine too
let's talk a little bit about holo talk
with juggle
oopsie
and
yeah so you guys
know by now why i needed to pre-record
it huh
because i
i asked beforehand when we started
talking about
whole talk of jaguar i asked if it was
in any way possible to get juggle
to go into
like a green screen video uh studio and
then record
it on a green screen
because i thought it would be so much
more exciting
so much more special
than having him just on a cut out
cardboard cutout on a png
especially since i i don't even know how
to animate so oops [\h__\h]
i don't know how to animate if i could
animate and i could at least
make it move
a little bit
i could make it move a little bit
on adult after
after effects or like a little premiere
pro and then give it some
some
details afterwards
free strikes you're out
yep i deserved that
what did that happen
ah
it might have been possible to do it
live but the other reason as i mentioned
before as it was in a pinned comment was
that
holo talk is at 11 p.m japanese standard
time and we also learned uh his
one day schedule so
he
oh he would usually be asleep but or not
not asleep but i don't want to force him
to work at that time i don't think he
would be up for it anyway so that was
from the beginning it was never an
option
[Music]
i never even offered it because
i i just felt like
oh
i just felt like it's better that way
anyway
um
yeah pre-recorded is safer
i had to cut some things out anyway so
if that would have happened during the
uh
during the actual stream then there was
no way of
hiding that
yeah
[Music]
he wouldn't be able to do his morning
longs if it was life he got to keep the
healthy routine exactly he's a busy man
and you know he has a
he has a family right he's married so
um
no he's got [\h__\h] to do
the whole thing was pretty cool yes i
said it a million times
he said it so often
thank you for hearing me thank you
can i pick up that fairy later can we
keep it i don't want to take it
what you know he's married no
uh
he was seen with a with a ring on his
finger
previously and then
i even saw a clip of noelle reacting to
it and reacting to the fans reacting to
it
you guys didn't know of course he's
married
he's a charming man isn't he why would
he not be married
he's he's such a sweet
sweet personality link
obviously he's married you thought he
wouldn't be married of course he's
married
isn't that obvious
but it's sad i know for a lot of you
guys who wanted to marry him of course
i'm sorry
i hope you can
get over those feelings without
suffering too much
to me
okay
your visionaries obviously had the whole
thing pictured in your mind and learned
how to make it come true
ah no
well are we when are we gonna get luna
um well you know i try to make it
um i tried to call my guests in a
somewhat
senpai to kokai order so
um
honestly
i've been having some uh
problems getting some members
uh
to
get to holotalk
time-wise or scheduling-wise so i might
just move on to virgin
next where we already had money in
senpai so
we can do
we can do peculiar we can do fourier we
can do lucia we can do everyone
i will i will continue asking
um
those people we are in the eagle fairway
that's a hulk that's all
are bert not coming with me
koneno koino i guess burb is too scared
too much of a chicken huh
marine 2.0 whole attack would be right
yeah possibly we could do that i see
that as an option as well
wow what is uh happening
what is what the what the [\h__\h] is
happening
what is this dungeon
oh sheesh
that takes quite a few hits
ow
i should probably save
oopsie
um what was i talking about oh yeah
hello
um
so
actually
i recorded it like oh [\h__\h]
i think what was what time was it for me
maybe 10
10 11 or something or earlier
oh thank you
[Music]
um
and uh
[Music]
yeah i did not do any small talk with
jago it literally was like
they actually asked me like do you do
you want to talk to juggle a little bit
before you start and i was like
no
i don't know why i said no um
i think i
i was i wanted to focus on
preparing for holotac
no i don't have the boomerang what is
this
what is this
do i have to roll it over there before
oh i bring it over there
before it closes
okay
yeah yeah there were a bunch of awkward
silences as well
a lot of that recording was
wait do i need to throw it
wait don't don't go so far
[\h__\h]
what is it why does it go so far
professional burp yeah
um
uh oh god i don't know what to say uh i
it was fun it was fun in interviewing
him but it was also awkward and um
he
he gave me very short answers a lot of
the time and sometimes
i was like maybe not directly asking a
question but kind of throwing in him a
topic like throwing him a bone and he
just didn't take it he just would not
take it do i need this or what maybe i
don't need it
did he use difficult japanese um
a little bit but i i wrote it down so
it was easy for me to
translate it
i did it
did i need it
i did not think it would um
i did not think it would throw that far
i just wanted to drop it but okay that
was not even on purpose i did not expect
that to happen
on are you just gonna
annoy me while i'm doing this
no you're not
oh sheesh
easy
chest master takanashi
a wonder
here
oh oh you can lift that from above not a
hundo um i have a feeling that i need to
stand
on one of those blue ones
because if it doesn't work from here
[Music]
yeah they probably want me to stand on
that one no
oh
well that's that's why i [\h__\h] up
huh
uh-huh
whatever
[Music]
no no i think i think that needs to go
there
oh
where did they throw this one from
originally
from here
no one more above
now
[Music]
oh chest
going well so far going better than the
the other dungeon so far even though it
looks more intimidating
oh yeah and i'm sorry about the speed
questions i i asked about it but uh
it was it was um
deemed
not professional enough
i wanted to
like change it and then get rid of the
questions that are an issue but that
didn't help either apparently
so
yeah maybe it helps if i put that throw
that over there maybe it helps for later
um
but
but at least we had that little video at
the end um
with
with some
with all the speed questions
compilated into one thing
yeah you will never know what color of
panties he's wearing unfortunately i'm
sorry for taking that away from you
i
i know
it's like
it makes you uneasy
but
some things are maybe just
better left unsaid don't you agree
did you keep who made the talk yes i did
but she probably already forgot
no not you
oh my god
oh
damn it
come here
oh i could have thrown the pot on him i
guess so
whoopsie
the pots are apparently really a strong
weapon wait i'm stuck here too
where the hell was the
like uh like the the crystal to activate
the different color
i don't recall even seeing one
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] you
maybe here
huh
wait i'm stuck
i stared at it
but was i even able to activate it no
oh
it did
yeah i mean i see this one but i can't
reach it unless maybe i can throw a bomb
which i don't know if that's
the solution
they want me to i can't
damn it
doesn't work
now here we didn't really
what did i go up i did
let me see what we can do oh yeah yeah
we've been here before but i can't move
on here either
because of the blue
can you fly over i don't have the
chimken anymore
ah but i can jump over there that little
i did not see that tiny spot
that is difficult to see though
come on
oh [\h__\h]
oh i would not have tried that on
purpose
that was by accident but i suppose
that's
good
okay
so
[Music]
um
okay we now have access to a crystal
[Music]
which
leads us
to somewhere
i will now go back into this room
i think that's that's where we had the
the chess piece ah and this one as well
okay now we're talking i'm doing the
dungeon on accident there's something
mirror
i can now turn back beams
do i have to change the shield or
he's automatically using it okay
ah
okay okay
oh there's so many possibilities guys
i will go this way first
wait is that
yeah wait won't they just be up again
oh they will wait i might have to go for
this path in order to
sheesh
okay that's fine no wait that's not a
path that's it it's not a [\h__\h] path
i'm confused i'm confused
let's just go somewhere else right now
oh
[Music]
wow
it probably wants to eat a bomb doesn't
it
come on
do i have to kill it why would i want to
kill
a kirby huh
cutest baby in the whole wide world
[Music]
wait
how'd i kill it
now i'm on this side and it doesn't help
me at all
not even the lasers can harm kirby
fascinating
you're from the u.s to be studying in
germany
we have tips for living in germany
tips for living in germany well i don't
live in germany but i guess austria is
pretty similar
do i want that
let's let's let's see
tips for living oh in germany
well
speaking german would be helpful
um
oh
germans in general are pretty
[Music]
um
cool
i would say they're pretty easy-going
[Music]
uh
you don't kill it
okay
fine with me it's too cute i don't want
to really kill it anyway
um oh wait i can
do this right yeah i almost forgot about
it
i almost forgot
i don't know i don't know what what
advice to give to live in germany hmm
um
we don't have we don't really have
convenience stores
i guess you as an american
you probably
are used to
uh convenience stores we don't have them
we might have some
that are some supermarkets that are open
a bit longer audit i'm okay oh
but
yeah
that's shockingly inconvenient not if
you are used to it then
it's just a given and
you live your life accordingly you just
how do i kill these again
[Music]
you just wait huh okay
you just buy groceries ahead of time
yeah but i do have to say when i lived
in japan oh no not these bookers again
uh life was definitely more convenient
with the convenience stores
it definitely was
wait are they sending me a sign that
they want a specific sign or does it not
matter [\h__\h]
da yola okay we're doing green now
it comes after the orange [\h__\h]
yeah i love convenience stores i really
miss them they also have great food at
least in japan i heard that in other
countries the convenience stores are not
as good
[Music]
[\h__\h]
charlie
uh
wait does it does it
only give you hearts if you
stop it at the heart sign
or does it always give you hearts
sorry it took me a while to do that
[Music]
um
yeah sorry i really can't think of much
[Music]
but um i i think one thing
that i can tell you is that most germans
while they might have a weird accent
sometimes
oh i need to break that as well they do
ah
i'm so smart
i'm so
i am such a [\h__\h] smart girl
oh but
wait yeah yeah no problem
i'm so smart
what was i saying oh yeah while i might
have a weird accent germans do mostly
understand and speak uh
oh [\h__\h] oh well i guess that's fine
because i can't move them anyway i have
to go over there
oh just the question is how will i get
over there but i i will find a way
eventually
um they speak german and they speak
english they understand english so
communication problems
probably not so much i think a lot of
people
come to study in germany even though
they don't know the language
um
and they do just fine i actually i've
worked with a company in germany before
that um oh there's one here too
look
then
uh mostly
and people hired that speak no german at
all
uh
but
yeah they also said that they were doing
just fine in germany
[\h__\h] i should have brought it down here
before i
didn't realize
oh [\h__\h]
i didn't realize man
[\h__\h]
oh wait i can bring it back can i no i
can't bring it back
[Music]
always better to learn the language yeah
and i mean by living
by living
in germany you will definitely learn it
much faster
than by trying to learn it from home
[Applause]
[Music]
jump off the floor above the ridge i
guess so okay
holy [\h__\h]
the
jumping off certain floors makes us
pretty confusing
but okay
we're good we're good we're good we're
gonna we're gonna mad it's just fine i
just don't know where to go next
ah i need to go on level on level two
whoopsie
i need to go to level two
oh man
so confusing
oh come on
[Music]
kirby man
[\h__\h] you
wait maybe
i can't kill kirby right
because i wonder if i get a chest if i
kill all of them but i don't know how to
kill kirby like i legit don't know
i'm having some problems here
oh what are you saying did i listen to
your opinion yeah the riddle saw from
the police fault oh yeah yeah okay okay
i made one fall
[\h__\h]
gonna be so strong i was a boomerang
and i don't get that in a dungeon do i
that's like an outside item so but
it won't it won't stop me from clearing
this dungeon right
wait what the [\h__\h] am i how do i get
upstairs
oh well
was i already upstairs
[Music]
how did i
oh did i get upstairs there's some
upstairs
let me go upstairs
kirby's death is not necessary well
that's wonderful i wonder if i fall down
here
that
that should that should drop me where
the chest is
yes
[Music]
where do we go next
we could go upstairs again
oh there's a left path here
yeah i need the ball
oh
when i moved
i i had the right idea oh i just moved
it
to a location that's a bit harder to
reach first
[\h__\h] you
what about the left side he thought he
was
yeah let's go up here
oh i was not here before
use my body to open the door
oh yeah
the floor and the floor
yep
come here
oh
heal me please thank you help me heal me
am i not getting a
a chest for that no
okay
it was like a ribbon game yeah
oh i got the ball guys
[Music]
that is two pillars down
now
um
i wanted in this room right
i think it was that room
right
can i
yeah can i push the block
no
put this blog
this one i can push okay okay
hi
let's go bal you and me uh already had
this ah but uh
in the room below here right
yes yes yes
oh
first pillar down
how many words i only saw three
oh my come back and come back in
out
do i still need the ball
the fourth pillar is a doozy what what's
that what does that mean
one more where i'm gonna bring my ball
with me
i don't recall a third pill a fourth
pillar
we did one in this room we did one in
this room ah then it must be in this
room
okay we were there before
let me try to bring you with me
doozy means it's hard
really
how did i get here before
was i even when i got here was i even on
the right side
i wonder if there's an ideal placement
for the ball right now
like one where i could easily pick it up
once i have access to that place
i took the stairs
oh sheesh
ow
inevitable
do these go down i wait i can't take the
ball
[Music]
i'll just explore a little bit
uh
oh wait a second is there a door for me
to open here
this one
okay
i'll try to get there
should i bring the ball
that won't work
what that opening the door
with the key of course it will
oh [\h__\h]
it's orange time
are you just from the ball what
there's a bomb of a while i didn't see
am i blind chill once again
you guys make fun of me because i just i
see it now
oh
i'm gonna get cold blind too again wait
how do i get there again
[Music]
[Applause]
from the other side now
damn it
[\h__\h]
it's hard to notice it is when it's on
on the lower side it's pretty hard to
notice if it's like on the left side or
right side
then it's so
okay is to notice
[Music]
mark that with crystal so that i
remember there's one here
don't know if that will help me
oh
wait
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
but maybe it will help me somewhere else
yeah here now i can go
here
maybe that helps
with something else we can go down
we can go
here
[Music]
wow
do we want to go there
oh i don't care i don't care
that does not help us at all
why do you go that way
too no it's not gonna be a 24-hour
stream
ow i want to throw that at you
yeah that basically blocked all paths
for me i feel like
so
we're gonna undo it i guess i don't know
[Music]
i wonder
did i ever kill everyone here
i don't know if i did but at least i got
a fairy out of it
cool too
no not
[Applause]
thinking tommy i'm running in circles
that's pretty annoying i'm sorry guys
it says it's a tough dungeon man can't
be that easy
it just cannot be
that simple
what i'm [\h__\h] stuck i need to undo
the color
oh i always land on these
okay so we undo it and then
not sure what happens then
i guess i gotta what have i ever tried
falling down here
where would i land if i fall down there
oh
no idea where that is honestly
i don't know if i i don't know if i want
to try
to the entrance
can you not hurt yourself for once
[\h__\h]
ah
we'll go here
away
this is first floor
but
maybe
no
if i go the kirby way
what happens if i do this
[Music]
you shall not pass
i will i will i will i did i did
oh maybe if i kill him from behind oh
no
wait
can i like stab him from behind
look look the other way kirby whatever
spin attack i tried feeding him a bomb
already it didn't work okay now we are
here again
oh holy [\h__\h]
what if i try going up here
not my first time but
i yes i just want to say i don't recall
ever going this
[Music]
um
oh god do i want to no
i hate this enemy
no wait how do i know
wait how do i fight him again
jump
okay
[Music]
what you can literally just spam arrows
at him
are you
all right
well that helps me a lot thank you
so what if i fall down
the very left this hole
will i get to this side i think i will
you didn't know that
but before i go there let's go first to
the right side and see
what we have here okay let's let's clear
this before we do anything else
after the heart comes that sign okay oh
ow ow ow ow ow
yeah
most powerful strategy in the world
indeed can i move any of these
yeah
okay what's here
ah the other side
i'm so curious i need to check out where
that leads to
oh
now here i am uh in a dead end because
the colors wrong but i could shoot
oh
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
i'm doing a lot of things right right
now
but
should i not first go try falling down
here i don't know
ah
[Music]
well here i'm stuck again no i can just
drop down there if i want to what are
these what are these statues
what are they supposed to mean
stop following me
no wait go away
unless you want to die
okay i will fall down now
come on give me something good
yes that's what i wanted thank you
finally some progress being made
stupid kirby
[Music]
a seashell
okay
not really what i expected
but okay
okay well in that case so
[Music]
i'll jump down here
oh sheet
wrong color now
oh
oh damn
ah what about here
okay
i'll try to do something here where the
hell is that pillar that i'm looking for
you guys have any uh
questions by the way about like i don't
know the recent things like holo talk or
the the video that i recorded with those
girls on tuesday
up there remember the crack in the wall
the balance go up helmets was fun i did
want to say something about that i feel
like um
[Music]
i
i am
look at the chicken anymore not me that
is all done by the staff
the editing i didn't do anything
out
i wanted to say like
i feel like
you know how i avoided playing fps games
for a long time and i mean you're not
gonna suddenly be
[Music]
like a really common game genre on my
channel but
i do realize like one reason why i
never really wanted to play those
is
because i always felt like you know with
no experience and no skills i would
always just kind of be in the way
um especially when it comes to like
these online fps games
then
you get matched with random people
who
know how to play the game and then you
just i know how toxic
that community can get
and i don't want them to be like yo
kiana you suck
why
or like not only like viewers but like
random players who don't know who i am
that i'm a streamer or whatever
i'm just worried that they might
uh-huh
that i'm just gonna be in the way and uh
just don't have the skills
it's just kind of scary
it's it's just
it always that
fps
online playing community always was kind
of scary to me like
um
yeah they can also as you know get
pretty toxic like for real and uh i
don't want to bother anyone i don't
wanna be in the way i don't wanna
i don't wanna be a burden to
players who just wanna have a good time
and then they get matched with the
absolute [\h__\h] noob
[Music]
who can't do [\h__\h]
and then they're like what the [\h__\h]
you suck
don't play this game ever again
you're so bad at this me me me me me me
you know
kind of scary it's just a really scary
world the fps world is [\h__\h] scary
but
paladins yesterday i don't know why but
i expected
it to be
a way worse experience i expected it to
be much more difficult i guess for one
and where i don't even know where the
hell i'm going
i expected it ah
how'd it get there
i expected it to be more difficult uh
but it wasn't i wasn't even lagging
behind that much i guess
but yeah that was just one of besides me
generally just
it is what it is i'm more into rpg games
i'm more into games with cute graphics
and cute stories cute characters and all
that
rpg games stuff like that
but besides that i was also just always
worried about the community and
um my skills and all that no yeah
that's how it is yum yum
[Applause]
come down calm down little flower power
monster
um one online
uh online fps game i have a feeling once
ollie hears about it
she'll call me up and be like yo keep
wah what
what it is time you can't hide from me
anymore
[Music]
yeah there will be no more escape
that won't stay there will it yeah it
won't okay
is it time for it
apex with only oh my god
oh welcome comedy
[\h__\h]
oh is that one already dead i already
shot it back at him okay nice um
[\h__\h]
okay okay okay okay
oh my arrows are
you probably going to get red is it
is the
nivo nevo is the level of
skill higher
in apex like the the player
skill level is it higher in apex than it
is in paladins
or is the game just harder
is that what it is so many fairies man
so many fairies and i don't need them
it is oh
yeah
okay i'm not ready for that then i'm not
ready for it
and that's okay
whoa
[Music]
yeah i'm stuck here
stick to balance i i did really enjoy it
so
i wouldn't mind playing it some more
uh i'm just wondering how did i move on
here i'm on the third floor now
do i wanna
drop down somewhere
i can't fall down here
unless oh wait what if i jump
can i do that where would i land do i
want to do that am i going to regret it
what if i jump down here
wouldn't that lead me to the last
oh it shows me where my ball is would
not lead me to the last
pillar
wouldn't i wanna
is the way to get the ball there by
dropping it from here no way no that's
not that's not it right
that's not it is it
but even if i fall down there now ah i
could probably at least reach the chest
maybe
that's right
oh wait i can't
i can't fall down here anyway never mind
unfortunately
what the
fight uh
what if i were to fall down from here
that could still
is that even possible
go to the ball first you can bomb a wall
there
yeah however the hell
i can get back there i do not know
oh i have never been here before
what if i fall down here
uh-huh
i'm
good
deadbeats
lurking now
with the tooth tooth machine
and you think you can take me all right
boys get this book out of my face
oh that's the cute music that you're
playing that beats
what are these what are those
what are those one of those
do you mean
if you leave even one alive i can keep
bringing more bodies to him how do i
kill them
what what do you want what do you want
from me
slash them
but they're in the air
what
i slashed one
huh
i killed one
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay okay is there like a good spot to
stand in
maybe here
[Music]
[\h__\h]
oh
oh okay one one the one in the beginning
okay okay i'll get okay
[Music]
we're gonna do this
i always missed the first one
[Music]
stop laughing
nothing's funny about this
[Music]
what do you say about that you lousy so
i thought these grapes were some of my
best friends well then you shouldn't
have sent them
fighting me
that's dangerous of course i'm gonna
kill
them i do have a song to revive dead
animals and people though so
if you make me a good price a good offer
i could revive your best friends or is
that not worth it to you huh
okay
[Music]
that means progress oh [\h__\h] you i had my
shield out even but the shield doesn't
help with these bodies
um okay i guess i want to activate that
does that do anything
of course
it does
oh i was about to say of course not
yes here we are
[Music]
the boss key already
i already have the boss key but i still
have a uh
chest here and i don't even know how to
get up there
and i still have the fourth up but i
guess with the fourth pillar by
destroying the fourth pillar
everything will come falling down and
i'll be able to reach the the top of the
tower because it will the top will
become the bottom maybe
maybe
where do we go now
um
[Music]
blue better
is that so
i hope it for you edo-san
what did you say
blue and then
go back to the entrance and get to the
second floor from the left what
what
go back to the entrance well i can i can
drive
what
i don't know where i left the ball
i don't know how to get there
blue block that
[Music]
i i see it on the map yeah but i don't
know how to get there
this [\h__\h] dungeon is too confusing
i'm just running into random
directions now
teleport
okay i can
i guess
[Music]
no time to waste this is an endurance
stream
um
oh wait where we were going uh up
was that thing up here
okay
no problem no problem we're changing it
we're changing it to orange
and then we're going back
and
then
we're able to go up here
and where the hell is my where's my ball
i need to go here for my ball
ball
ball are you here
i missed you now where do i bring you
i found you but where the hell do i
bring you what if i drop it can i drop
it here does it land on the no
why would it it's on the same level
oh [\h__\h] i didn't see it again
oh i can bring the ball this time
oh we're getting i see it wait wait
okay no i can't throw it over here
huh
wait what
what
if you can't go over the poles try
throwing things you have in your hands
i tried throwing it
what
huh
i mean that's the only other way that i
see
like
a different path to bring the bolt maybe
maybe that was not it was that not it
no
[Laughter]
wow
[Music]
i like it back oh come back it shouldn't
be too difficult it's just all
over here
what do i do with you though
stupid ball
no
[Music]
wait wait i need healing
no where's my ball
oh
well that's not realistic that's not
realistic at all
kidding me now kidding me
i gotta go all the way
oh where is it what [\h__\h] you
oh my god
no
that's just not fair
this is not there
[Music]
oh
why
okay where the [\h__\h] do we go now i still
pretty close i guess you wait here ball
[Music]
i'm gonna make it happen no matter what
it takes
okay
be careful
careful
and now
wait a second
can i spam hearts here no
throw over
i want to change the color
oh okay so it's here
how do i
how
that
i can't take it for doors so
well we'll just let's just go where the
ball is first
hopefully get there
uh no idea
maybe here
oh my god
i don't know
so
[Applause]
[Music]
that was my rendition
my suffering rendition
what if i go here
the one
it's my life it's now or never
i ain't gonna live forever
it's my life
[Music]
now what are we doing what are we doing
with you
do i bring you this way
sorry there's a lot of other balls here
but you're the prettiest trust me
no one's as pretty as you my beautiful
little ball
wow why do we go ball i don't know
oh can i throw it all the way over there
no
huh
who do you want from me what do you want
from me
what do you want for me
go to this room
okay yeah wait let me think
if i throw it
uh but it put it
how do i get there
i always forget about that being an
option
oh
nothing bb i already i already solved
your riddle can you go away thank you
stop
okay
i get it i can
go away leave me alone
[Music]
has it
feel like my brain melted
during this dungeon
but we are good
oh i didn't see that pack was already
open see it's really hard to see man
it's so hard to see
my ball is there okay
really
what a useless chest that is
that does not really feel like a reward
to me
a single bomb yeah it's falling down
it's falling apart
it's kind of
sad we're
we are destroying such a beautiful
tower
for what
oh
okay
hello
no
there is no fourth floor
and this all dropped down to the middle
and we already have a portal to go there
yeah
um
do i need the ball i hope not
i'm still eating pineapples
got it
i will teleport
this is one amazing puzzle when i played
it on gameboy i i can see how that must
have been fascinating
but
did they not use
color in this dungeon even though like i
don't understand so the game in general
was without color
but there was one dungeon where you
could see color well then why did they
not just make the whole game in color
question mark
that's what i want to know
why why did they not do that oh there
was a rim release in color
so many hearts do you guys see that so
many goomba hearts
it's very kind of them out but and they
also take hearts
wait i can already open it but
oh wait is the whole thing
this is now connected but originally was
not connected or no this is the new part
what
open it good luck should i um be scared
is it gonna happen right away or is the
mission to run out of the tower when
it's falling apart or something
not done yet when i go for the door yeah
i would think so what okay that's that's
weird
having to use the
key
already
because she know
no need
what is it with this one
okay this is connected now
have i been there before
yeah
because it was already lit before
hey shoot me out
okay guys back to small talk as long as
we can because who knows how tough the
boss monster will be
you guys have any any more questions
about recent happenings
if not i might just
use another one of my tangents but i
would prefer you guys to ask a question
small talk remember strength oh yeah
ryan i wanted to ask you guys what do
you want to see because like i didn't
really decide um
did i promise something specific
recently that i would do in the next
member stream i don't recall promising
anything for the next
upcoming one
i don't think i want to do karaoke when
i have a long stream today and a long
stream
on the following days as well that's
probably not a good idea
i've already got some lines let's put it
back
okay i'll pick it up whenever i lose the
current one
um we'll be watching long
has the last one
been a while or
wait what what
what
what no matter how often i look at these
i'm still confused
what
yeah the last one was klaus
i don't know we could do we got to watch
um it would be pretty comfy for me
but
sorry my brain cannot comprehend how to
get there
how do i get there
oh wait a second
oh you can't you can't actually spam
hearts here [\h__\h]
and you can also hurt yourself
but
every time you re-enter the room
what
there's more goombas right so
okay wait a second is there any way that
i can
move this correctly
wait
i think i got it i think i have it oh
maybe not but um
go back go back
where to
[Music]
it's an exit oh
wow
i don't know
but
i'll figure it out i'll figure it out
eventually
is there
is there uh
a color changer anywhere
the hook's up
i always forget but where why do you
want me to use the hookshot
why do i need a hookshot
ah here
[Laughter]
wait i got it before reading the chat so
at least that's one point for me huh no
you're gonna give me that cause at least
i figured it out without looking at the
chest
[Laughter]
will we finish within 12 hours i think
so it's only been five
look where we are
at the top
of
okay
how are we gonna do this
i'm gonna make you wish you were never
born
[Music]
am i fighting the evil eagle i thought i
was fighting you
well what about my chicken
[Music]
oh wait do i use these spikes for
something oh
until i go back up maybe
interesting oh god oh god oh god
hey
i only have balls i'm only have nine huh
um
ah
[Music]
i don't know how my errors could reach
him though because he's like
so high up
it's time to use one of my fairies
um
[Music]
oh
again
boring stop using the same attacks over
and over again
again
it is a super effective attack yeah
wow
i thought this battle was gonna be a
little bit longer than that am i energy
gone i lost but you will be lost two of
the wind fish wakes
same as me you are in his stream
i know i know i know
i know
just playing it
for fun you know
[Music]
so one more dungeon left over left
or two
heart containers
pillars were the real bug hell yeah
one more
easy
this is not even close to being an
endurance
um
[Music]
listen up guys here's my new instrument
organ of evening calm oh
[Music]
yeah
sparks organ version
i wouldn't mind listening to that
ocarina of time
the music of the ocarina leads wait do i
have all the instruments now
can i go to
the egg
am i ready for the egg
is this is this a toilet is that the
outhouse of the bird
oh no that's where i came from
i need one more
wanna hear sparks in minor key me too
i think that's actually what i
originally kind of expected
for sad sparks
i think in minor it would have sounded
much much much uh
sadder huh
yummy
[Music]
okay what now
uh again to give us a little hint
[Music]
uh
what blue chicken's at the chicken house
can i take it backwards it's just gonna
stay there now
very upper left corner here
but i can't get very close unfortunately
i didn't activate that over there
it's a funny scene
huh really
uh it's kind of annoying to get there
though isn't it uh
wait no unless if i just
jump down here
maybe
what's the shortest path to the hen
house
we gotta visit our friends at kfp
kfb but like 5 000 years ago in a dream
kfb
uh zelda
branch
yes link's awakening branch where am i
going where am i
thank you for the pinky
guys there might be
a lot of super chats
to catch up on by now i suppose
um
i probably won't read that many today
but don't worry i always end up reading
them sooner or later so
i will get there eventually
is
yes
kiwawa always
always keeps her promises dream brands
yeah although if i if i
imagine a dream branch
i would
i would make it a bit more
[Music]
a bit more impressive what are you doing
with my blue chicken
[Music]
[Applause]
is the greatest give me that back
i want it back
what's that
how dare you take my chicken away from
me we had a special bond we were gonna
create kfp together
[\h__\h] sad how am i gonna reach that
place without my chicken
okay wait do i have to
is it better to just go
down completely once try to
i can go up here
what it
you're kind of stuck here now how do i
get there
ah
hook shot
keep going left okay
[\h__\h] hook shot i always forget about
it
hey winky i forgot that was my name
thank you
some monsters put me up here what should
i do i'm afraid of heights
then you must
imagine
that there are no heights here it is all
all
not existing
can i grab on to you
what
[Music]
thank you thank you that was pretty
amazing
must have been your instincts kicking in
huh
yup i guess so
i didn't know what i was doing to be
honest sailing canada
i don't know how to say this but
what the [\h__\h] do you want now
we're flirting right now
honey
never mind
i'm gonna go
that's how you thank me for saving your
life huh
this is
[Laughter]
afraid of heights but just jumps down
there with no issue at all
okay
hi boob
what's up what's up i want chocolate now
i still have pineapples but not one
chocolate and of course i have
chocolates with me
oh that girl sat her song in front of
the egg oh is she the eighth instrument
maybe
is she my last incident at voices also
an instrument would you agree
she wanted me to say she probably knew
that i was around him
yeah and then brought herself up here on
purpose
i agree kiriki
agreed yeah thank you
thank you so much
yeah i'm gonna i'm gonna eat a cookie
yum yum yum
i need to play her like a fiddle
you need to
you need to stroke her belly like she's
a guitar
her blood of the wind face is a song of
awakening
did she actually intend to wake the wind
face aren't we all trying to do that
what the [\h__\h]
next sirens instrument is in the worst
play your melodies so that on living
stones might
show your correction finish wait for
your hoot
bye-bye
what will be your next zelda game well
actually
[Music]
let me tell you
actually
do i need to go here now
actually yesterday
i was
looking up um
i was looking up when we use
we use
used wii u's because um new reviews are
apparently a bit hard to get
um
we're not scalable at all
anymore oh she
oh man that's a headache
yeah i was looking them up and um
because wii u was the one right where
you can
play gamecube games right
with the wii u
right we could probably get the next
reward but uh from the seashells but i
first want to activate the portal here
oh
no it was the wii
what
oh okay but thank god i didn't buy it
yet i was getting close to buying one
but then i was like let me ask my chat
again instead of googling let me just
first talk about it with my chat i'm not
in a hurry anyway
i almost bought it but i'm not in a
hurry it's all good where the hell
how what
do i need to go over here
okay
i have four weeds what what the [\h__\h] is
this place
[Music]
it's a pokemon
get your pokeballs guys
okay you want me for my fine lamp thanks
a lot but now i'll get my revenge are
you ready
i like to carry more magic powder
are you ready
can you let me carry something else
that's heavier maybe more arrows more
bombs
[Music]
what if i say onion what happens if i
say onyo
what do i say what if i say it would
[Music]
oh can i still change it can i change it
look at all that jack you have to carry
take care see you again oh he's so nice
oh i
60 what can i get
only one
buff at a time
i would like more than that
[Music]
there's one more of these in the forest
oh
i want one for arrows yeah
she even gave me
like he filled them up for me vancouver
hmm
okay i thought
well how do i
[Music]
how do i
if i fall down here
how do i get there
do i have to fall down here
oh that's that stone is shiny
i want to get to the portal
okay
[Music]
ah
but wait before i go there is there
something secret here yes
[Music]
[Applause]
we got a new heart didn't win
oh what the [\h__\h]
is that only possible with the shield
that i have now
or
yeah it must be right it's like a
blocking me from going here too early
huh
oh oh my god a portal
oh what about
what about this one that's so close
and we have
uh new enemies and we have a shell
somewhere here
but where would that be
nice
nice one
perfect
one one hit well let's let's i hear what
urira has to say even though i kind of
know i guess for
once um
a fish is under a bridge and martha's
bay
that's what you meant with the bridge
he wants to fish his hook
okay
fisher's uh what my for babe uh-huh
[Music]
but wait
someone in the chat told me to play the
song somewhere
the
i hear this one
[Music]
should i play it here
calm down
try me
this is how i enter the dungeon oh by
playing this song
[Music]
no way
oh that's it
oh i'm scared
oh no on
you
[Music]
oh a boss fight to open the dungeon
that's cool
i did not expect it how did i fight you
wait
i have an idea oh maybe i don't even
need that idea
okay
[Music]
um
oh wait i can lift you
what
did it say lift at his head
[Music]
hi there was a cat in my room just now
i need to make him bonk against these
walls huh come here
[Music]
i'll just maybe it does not say lift
because that was just a bump okay
why are you hiding your pretty face with
all those stones
come on show me your pretty face
oh
i'll help you with your skin i'm sure
that hurts doesn't it
why can't i not use my feather oh wait i
can why was it grayed out that was
i thought it was not available for some
reason
it even just hurts to touch you
that's worrisome
exfoliating the skin there we go come
here come here
don't be scared
[Music]
i'm a i'm a professional uh oh [\h__\h]
i'm a professional skin care
professional
let me massage your scalp as well as an
extra free service free of charge what
do you think about that huh
[Music]
cool music by the way
that reminds me of that
fun children's game i used to play you
know the crocodile mouth of the teeth
oh [\h__\h]
he's killing me
hey i have a cream i have a cream i'm
good i'm good
i have a cream but um
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
mommy clip
oh man
i didn't use my cream
fairy
wait
i will capture you
i i honestly need healing but i will
capture you
and i will save
kitty kitty
that was very close
and but
i just did it
to make the dragon feel better and for
entertainment value you guys know me you
guys know me i always think about
my enemies even even my enemies you know
i want them to feel good about
themselves
yeah compassion compassion is a quality
that an idol must have
yeah
you must treat even your enemies with
compassion and respect
and eventually maybe if you're lucky
they'll give it back to you maybe not
always but
sometimes they turn um
turn uh their opinion into something
positive of you yeah
sometimes they i mean stab you right in
your heart in you or in your face or
they stab your eyes i don't know they or
they cut out your tongue or
or they cut your throat um there's all
kinds of ways honestly um or they shoot
you obviously
yeah there's many ways many things that
can happen but sometimes sometimes
sometimes very nice
it's all good go to the yeah yeah
martha's bay here there's supposedly
a bridge here
something i want to tell you no no
why why would there be anything
i don't know i'm just uh
talking about you know life
my sharing my wisdoms of life with you
guys
is one of my favorite things to do
mm-hmm
um i need some healing
help man needs some healing and also
oh no you're not gonna do that
beach
yeah
where is that bridge that
was mentioned i don't see a bridge
under a bridge
[Music]
where is the bridge
is this this is the house
wife's house
[Music]
okay
oh which is outside right of the dungeon
[Music]
making my way downtown
what the [\h__\h]
what are you doing here
and i was swimming in the bay the waves
took a very important necklace from
around my neck wait is that the item i
will get um
after
uh giving the fisher the hook
maybe will he give me because maybe he
fished
uh and caught a necklace
maybe
oh
well that is a nice hiding spot i hope
the enemies are not too rough on you
yup yup
oh
i'll jump on your boat from this side
hello
oh what is that loving your hand you
should not officially
you would better let me have it i'll
give you my next catch if you let me
have it okay
please let it be a necklace please let
it be a necklace
there's no fish down here
should we tell him
because we had a look on the water
i don't know if he realizes there ain't
a single fish down here
oh my god
sorry to tell you buddy he's dreaming
too yeah he's dreaming of big fish
big fish in the sea
did you guys ever fish in real life
before i did not
and i am also
not interested in it at all
that's my necklace give it give it back
what do you mean back i didn't feel it
don't make it sound like i stole it
yes yes
[Music]
mama totally fish oh i actually don't
know if she ever fished before
i
i went camping with my
mom before when i was a child but i
don't i don't recall her ever fishing i
don't think so
i've been deep sea fishing
crab fished crab fish what is that you
can fish crabs
how do you face crabs of a big net or
ah
you could call me a fisher owl
it must be it must be a delicious food
for an owl yeah yeah
fish at my pond you have a pond
move your hands to the basket ah that
sounds fun
ah
you know speaking of crabs i saw a video
yesterday a video yeah of a of a little
tiny ass crab
uh building herself
um a [\h__\h] sand house in like
under a minute and then it was like
a crab propaganda
it was like yo crabs can do this
why are humans the
the um
what was it what's the word
the the uh superior race
should be crabs and then
the people had this whole discussion in
the comments
like somewhere defending the crab and
some were like uh calling out the crab
defenders they were like
well can you build a house
human can you build a house in under one
minute and then others were like well no
duh but i can do this and that humans
can do this and that and then people the
crab the vendors the crap people the
captain
trying to defend the intelligence of the
crap and saying that crabs are superior
they were pretty [\h__\h] serious about
it
[Laughter]
but i have one argument here okay
i have one argument
we humans
might not be able to build a house under
one minute
but we can still build houses and i i
want to say
you must also think
about the size difference
we can probably build a house of the
same size as the crab did in
under one minute
but if it's if you're if we're talking
about a house
i'm i'm a phoenix sure i'm talking for
you guys for for not for you guys your
chickens i guess but whatever listen if
we're talking about
um an equivalent okay
then
if if we're talking about an equivalent
with it being a bigger house and we
should always also be getting an
equivalent of time
one minute for a crab building such a
tiniest house means that we should at
least get one day and that could
be enough honestly probably depending on
what kind of house you're looking for
you could build a [\h__\h] tent and that
still counts as a house i would say
um honestly no we could probably build a
tent in uh one hour that would even be
enough
but yeah you get what i'm saying you
can't expect
us to build a house in one minute
when we
you know we're big guys so we also need
to build something bigger
crab is [\h__\h] tiny so of course it
will not take the crab that long to
build a shitty house for itself okay
crap people understand
stop your crap propaganda now i have
enough of that [\h__\h]
it's all crap hey
crap
anyway
why are you underwater
i'm
i'm taking it
i'm ripping
it off of her tail
it's like i'm taking off her panties
[Music]
i returned the necklace and got a scale
of the mermaid's tail how will you use
this i do not want to know how link
intends to use this
i do not want to know
bye-bye mermaid friend
right
now that we uh cleared that one up
uh what the [\h__\h] are we doing next
uh
who needs to i want to clear this now
who needs the mermaid statue where was
it my white statue
i've seen it before
[Music]
[Laughter]
can i go from the left
can i go from the water
oh
i see it
a big ass
beautiful mermaid statue
will it come to life after i give it a
scale
[Music]
hmm crabs are cool though i'm not i'm
just wanted to have some justice okay
i have no problem with crabs i like them
[Music]
so no beef okay
oh
wait how do i get there
oh yeah
[Music]
okay i saw that one on my own
out what the [\h__\h] go away
[Music]
testing my patience here
[\h__\h] you
[Music]
oh hello me lady oh
you're missing one actually i never
noticed that before
[Music]
oh by the way maybe it's time to change
my hairstyle
[Music]
you guys want to
see something different
[Music]
yo the amelia watson announcer pack is
gone now right isn't it
yesterday after the paladins collab
i
messaged gura
um
i said
i heard you once wanted to get the
amelia watson announcer pack for
paladins just a hint that it's gonna be
gone forever
like
in less than a day so
yeah hint and she just replied
uh
like
today
like a few hours ago so
she's like oh thank you but
yeah she's not getting it
on you
oh man it's too late it's too late to
apologize
oh no
it's too late to get the announcer back
[Music]
yeah i'm a summit not so hot anymore huh
[Laughter]
oh she's missing out on an amazing
announcer back man
i don't know if maybe with how cool
paladins are they could they would
probably if it's possible if it's
technically possible they would probably
give it to gouda if she plays paladins
and says on stream that she wants amelia
watson announcer pack
she would probably but who knows if
she'll
ever stream it
i i know she did it before she streamed
it before right that's like a long time
ago
sorry i'm changing my hair
i think that's a long time ago also i
want to put on my refund can i put on my
reboot
rainbow wow
pretty
paint shark
[Music]
oh sorry you like my twin tails now i
just changed them because i had them for
like five and a half hours
[Music]
just uh
one thing that i feel a little bit
embarrassed about is
my head with this hairstyle
it looks so
eggy
looks so polished and
flat
[Music]
like
it looks i don't know i look like an egg
even more than before
no not not anymore like an onion
i just look very smooth
i look so smooth
like someone polished my head like they
polished a shoe
[Music]
foreign
it's like you combed your hair amazing
excuse me i always comb my hair
real again you're an egghead
[Music]
you're an egghead
if you say that i'm gonna put my hair
into twin towels again
you're an egg
you probably even have more eggs than i
do you have two i have one that's my
head
maybe you have three even because maybe
your head is also an egg
just saying
who's the real egghead huh oh
who's the real egghead among us
is this a bug
is that a bug
i didn't see any enemies
[Laughter]
[Music]
magnifying glass they're too small
just like oh no i'm not gonna say that
we're not we're not gonna go there
[Music]
you're not gonna go in there
invisible
i'm not going there
wait how do i use it
don't what do you mean they're too small
they're just the same size as all the
other mobs are
what
i am confused
i'm not
holding it in my hand it's just
in my pocket um
i don't quite understand the logic here
but
okay
uh
was that necessary for the story
oh is that just an extra item how is
that even going to help me
are there invisible enemies in the last
dungeon
go back to the beach near where you sat
with money
go to the cave on the beach go to animal
village huh
which way which way first
now you go to the beach
from here
let's give it a try
[Music]
m
what am i supposed to see here
huh
[Music]
not welcome you think you're so cool
with your little houses
oh you
are the one that i was not able to see
before huh
huh
i thought the good idea was to put the
beach i'll trade it to you for what you
have in your actual life no
no
well if i give him for example the magic
powder
he'll just take three magic powders
right
and i can always get more
a shovel
well i don't will i not need it anymore
i can get it back okay
[Music]
but i need the shell you can buy that
for 300 rupees
why don't i just give him the three
powders
isn't that
smarter or will he take the whole bag so
i cannot even buy new powders
or collect new powders
it takes the whole pouch oh
you'll need powder more than shovel
it takes the whole bag
okay
oh the bowl around you guys said that
one one would have been useful in the
dungeon that we were just in well it
might also be useful on the next dungeon
thank you sir thank you kindly
and welcome uh thank you for renewing
your membership so
well that takes way too much time to
come back to me
all sit
also on here
okay
okay my zelda fans
we have the item
what is gonna happen now are we gonna go
into the last dungeon
hmm
[Music]
300 rupees for shovel is way too
expensive though
[Music]
the world is your dick side
not a hotel
[Music]
okay library and then animal village
okay
[Music]
library
haven't been there in a while
[Music]
i wonder if marina is here now or
if she's just gone and missing
[Music]
oh yeah by the way
um
wait one second let's see what's in here
why am i coming here oh why is the book
there again
is it why am i going here does it say
something new now
no
workbook
oh
did i not read this before
round and round the passageways of the
egg lift up up right up right up up
write it down write it down
lift up up
right up right up up lift up up
right up right up up
okay write it down let it down it
changes each time
screenshot i'm not going to look at my
screenshot
left up up
right
up right up up okay i will write it down
if you guys don't write it down then i
will do he
oh
nom nom bear
you are amazing that is let me check it
if it's correct your homework is correct
you are now
pinned at the very top of the chat
congratulations
okay we have a secret
which is not a secret anymore
but we will protect it and use it for
good things only
and now we go to animal village
what does
say by the way
tpapers
really that's it just do your best
that's all you're going to say
no more hints okay i guess i i have come
so far that
hints cannot really help me and as we
see marine is not here
is there a useful item that we didn't
buy yet in here didn't we not buy the
hard piece yet
the heart container there we go
how much 200 well that's nothing
john ruby
yes
thank you sir thank you
the rest i don't really need so i'll be
moving on to the animal village
no more
cheaper than a shovel yeah
makes no sense
it would be fun to see your collab and
halo co-op
well well well well we just started
getting a little bit into
fps
check it step by step
um
as i said i had a lot of fun with
paladins so
i do want to play that again
but
yeah
i don't know how frequent it will
[Music]
be where do i go in the animal village
hello
yeah i've heard of the flying rooster it
exists
it is true
should i have brought the flying rooster
here
did i miss out on some special
event
what about you
why he's finally reacting to me
differently
ugh
what are you looking at with that
magnifying lens
stop it at once
there's nothing to magnify to be honest
except the tail on your backside
what stop
oh my god dog what about you
oh
no hold up
hello
there's a seashell here
ah from okay well are you giving it to
me
[Music]
oh okay it reacted to her
no
oh we should go to the seashell cave
[Music]
i didn't go
inky mushroom
why did you enter the house and start
breaking everything because i thought
there's a sea shell in the
and the thingies oh there's one here too
ah you can't see me you must have a
magnifying glass i'm not a troublemaker
i just want to live in peace i'll give
you this if you promise to keep your
mouth shut
another one
i like your chicken doll
i like that you're not using a duck but
a chicken normally people have ducks
squeaky ducks in their bathtubs but
you're using a chicken
makes me happy
are you interested in the fluff remake
what
is there something new that i don't know
about or are you just talking about the
like a phone
game phone version of cliff
what are you talking about what are you
talking about
let me look
floof
luff
remake
[Music]
what do you mean remake
i don't find anything about it it's
probably just the old one that's not new
news
right
oh man i miss flip
i miss it those were some good times man
[Music]
yeah fly for
fun fly for fun
oh apparently
[Music]
i did not know if liverphone originally
was created by a korean company
developed by a korean company
oh i did not know fly for glory is that
the name of the remake
[Music]
um
true yeah korea made a lot of mmorpgs
back in the day
what was it again was it black desert
wasn't that also
was that korea too
and then
was it that one huh
there's so many that i played so many
[Music]
it's all of them holy [\h__\h]
i need to tell the koreans to make more
i miss my pc mmorpgs my
my uh pay to win or pay to get fancy
uh free mmorpgs i need more help me make
some new ones yeah blade and soul
i like that one that one was cute too
can you make some more please like all
these shitty mmorpgs nowadays are being
made for the phone but i want them to be
made for the pc
[Music]
lost ark
i don't think i played that one
but
[Music]
now it needs to be more
cute if possible
lost arc is coming out next month
oh it's a new one
[Music]
oh yeah we are free to play mmo action
rpg
is it coming out uh
like the next
month is that only in korea or is that
worldwide
release
let me look at it what does it look like
worldwide english release for eu and usa
oh who i need to look at a trailer
they're looking pretty hot
i could check it out
is it good do you guys like it
[Music]
even have time to play one not really if
i could stream it yes but if i can't
then
[Music]
difficult
it's gender locked and best classes are
all female let's go well that's good for
me
that's good for me though
looks super solid backed by amazon how
is it backed by amazon
yes we're talking about lost ark yeah
um blue protocol what about blue
protocol tastes forever to be launched
yeah i'm i'm waiting for blue protocol
like
oh wait we're talking about the right
game ryan i'm not we're not talking
about blue archive or or so we're
talking about blue protocol from bantam
uncle
i don't know when it's coming out i'm
waiting for it
i'm waiting forever
would you speak some korean uh
[Music]
uh
where's my memo like my mama where did i
put my memo
i can't find
something something
[Music]
something like that
something
like thank you for watching my stream
i remembered half of the sentence
are you guys still awake
wait choke the weight google
oh papa go
decent
yeah get it safe
you still awake
though
[Music]
are you good you're still awake are you
are you fine
we're almost done with the game yo
you should head out to the cave at the
toronto stores use the magnifying glass
there and you'll find someone else like
me to rumble shores
rumble choice
where was that again no i actually i
want to go to the seashell cave
thank you for being awake guys
fascinating don't worry if you're not a
member then tomorrow is your day off
and even if you are a member then
it won't be a super long stream even
tomorrow
also my throat hurts a little bit so
i don't know man
um
we are going to
teleport to the seashell
thingy
if somebody will be streaming some
mmorpg games it will be great yes i want
to i mean i requested um i wanted to
play that uh
i requested for fly for fun for members
only streams actually but
i have not heard anything so
time for soft spoken events speaking
softly also hurts so
now
um
okay weigh me weigh me and expose my
weight to everybody i don't care
whoa the juice is filling up
[Music]
what is it what is it what is it
honey
[Music]
i don't give a [\h__\h] about that
a [\h__\h] rock man
okay where are the rumble shores are
they
uh
[\h__\h]
what's the closest one i don't know
the map doesn't say where the toronto
shores are
where should i go
i already did that oh
the terremble thing i already did that
oh okay then i guess are we going here
pet rally yay
exciting
the boomerang ah
find some more seashells the next reward
is good
oof uh there must be some seashells that
i didn't find here probably
[Music]
oh wait a second to the way
chotto wait a minute
uh
here
33 um
well this is difficult now
i don't know what i'm missing
i could watch the video again the guide
with
seven more
i can watch the guide to see where the
shells are located
[\h__\h]
want to ride by the chicken coop
oof
you should just do the dungeon yeah
seven could take
quite some time what is it what am i
what would i be getting
out
tell me tell me tell me
[Music]
a sword upgrade oh
ah she's just gonna say do your best huh
the master song
that would be pretty cool for the last
dungeon but i don't know where to look
i can i can watch the video let me see
is it okay let's cheat
we want to
um
use our time efficiently
links awakening seashells
[Music]
how to get all the seashells
which video let's let's use this video
okay
and
i think this might have been the video
that i watched before and then there
were some shows that i couldn't reach on
my own time
did i get that
[Music]
okay
let me compare
that one i got
that one i got as well
that one i did get two
that one i think i got two
that one i got you
that's in the dungeon we got the dungeon
one
i got that one
oh
i think
did get that one too
[Music]
i got that one
i got this one
oh yeah
did i get that one i think yeah
[Music]
oh
i got that one
ah did i
oh did i get that one yeah yeah yeah
yeah
did i get that one
i think yeah
that's in the dungeon
oh that one i didn't get
that is next to the hen house the one
where you throw a bomb in okay remember
that one throwing a bump next to the hen
house
that one i did get
that one i did also get
throw a bump next to the nose what did i
get that one hold it
what what the [\h__\h] was that
where is that that's uh
that's next to their ah
did i get that one
next to the swamp with the thorns in the
water
behind the wall i did it doesn't look
like i got that one apparently
apparently not really
here at the kopanga swamp
okay i guess let me get that one
let's go to hen house and go ponga
gopunka swamp
uh the lake above pothole field there
are two that you're missing the lake
above pothole field
what's what's the official name for that
i know it is called bottle field okay
i have two missing here
okay
[Music]
but let's go first
over here
first dungeon there is a bombable wall
with a seashell behind
is that what you're saying
[Music]
wait how do i
no no no how do i easily get from do we
have to go below
[\h__\h] you
no
you have to go here
[Music]
it did not steal my shield is this
shield
unstealable
wait that's not the right pump
[Music]
well i think the sword would be really
nice to have so i kind of
i kind of want it
oh ow wow wrong way wrong way to go
oh because if you can't buy buy it back
if they steal it not a hotel
[Music]
that makes sense
very useful for me
[Music]
okay somewhere here
there there it is
six to go
i would like to go to the hen house but
it's kind of annoying to get there maybe
it actually is faster
if i go through
[Music]
another route like is it easier to get
there
if i go here first well maybe if i go
here
maybe damn chad can see you
uh i don't think we have that much left
in the game but
uh it's the first time i'm playing it
fully on my own so i'm not sure
maybe the chat can tell you
yeah one more dungeon but i guess uh it
might be a bit more complicated than the
other ones maybe
well i'm not sure
[Music]
here
let me eat a fruit candy wait
my fruit hurts
[Music]
seven was the worst for me wait which
one was that the one that i just did
yeah that one was pretty obnoxious i
must agree
[Music]
i'm missing an instrument i'm i'm saying
martin is the last instrument no
yeah
isn't it just gonna be her wouldn't that
be nice
if she's the one piece that completes
my my band
but yeah probably not
am i going the right way
[Music]
that might have been correct
maybe
yes
yeah yeah yeah and from here i throw a
bomb
[Music]
where should we go next let me see the
video should be pretty helpful
29 alright let me see my map
okay no no no no no
um
oh no i got that one
taconine
warp point up there you mean one that i
did not activate yet
[Music]
i it's i know some of you guys are
writing them down for me but it's way
easier to find them when i also have the
visuals for it
so i appreciate you guys writing it down
but
by looking at the video
i
i can also figure out
how to get it how to get them you know
oh i i know one
in the forest
in the middle of the forest
okay
the middle of the forest
here
is where i want to go
[Music]
unless is there anything here that i
should take before i leave again
yeah the video helps
why is there no teleportation point here
yeah i didn't dig there
why is there no teleportation point i
don't understand
what i didn't activate is there one
you rarely need to go back here and
still it would be nice to have one
anyway like they they should be
they should be evenly distributed
throughout the map man
there's even a fairy here i feel like it
would make a lot of sense
[Music]
it is quite the obvious spot but for a
new blank meet i had no idea
[Music]
you what mate
what
i found that by accident
so
you woke me up from fine now thanks a
lot but now get my revenge should i go
for arrows or for a powder
i think arrows although i mean powder
would be nice too but if i had to choose
you can't choose what
of course i can
i no on you
yes see there you go of course i have a
choice
on you yes
[Music]
oh please you
i feel like i used to have much more
energy for these kind of streams but
after
over a year of streaming every freaking
day my voice is like
my voice and my energy
unfortunately
not much is left but yeah
60 arrows wow
you guys think i still have energy right
now
do i sound like uh do i sound do i sound
energetic i'm trying
okay
let me see
the video again
oh there's one very close did i get that
one
oh yeah that one that one i did get
um
i see plenty of energy really okay
oh an idol meeting yeah i have quite the
iron
the iron
how do i say this in an idle meeting to
him
the iron
huh
i don't know
why bladder was not about a bladder
we're not going to the toilet
at the iron
this position
iron resolve
iron
i have an iron pen
to write down things
during idle meetings
whatever now do you say it let's go on
an idol meeting break shall we
[Music]
see you in a moment
thank you
for waiting ahead of time don't leave
don't leave okay we're we're getting to
the end and y'all should be there for
that special
special moment
of
emotional
overwhelming feelings
the feeling of achievement
because
you guys are helping me a lot in this
playthrough so i need you guys to be
there i'll see you in a minute tsunami
warning excuse me
are you talking about my idol meeting
what the [\h__\h]
you're stupid
oh you mean because they're gonna send
blue super chats okay but just know that
i will not be reading them
okay
bye
so
i captured chunkers
hello junkies
how are you doing chunkers
she looks at me with a disgusted face
[Music]
don't look at me like that
[Laughter]
it's because i woke her up
i woke her up with my sounds
of existence
just the mere fact that i'm existing
no she's happy about my existence cats
just whoop
oh my god what did i just do
cats just
they look wait i just disconnected
something
they look disgusted but they're really
happy okay
also also
okay and i'm back
oh
thirty-six wait we have four four shells
left to get oh
monotech copium no
that's not copium
cats just also especially in photographs
they look very grumpy but they're not
okay let's see 32
ah did i get the seashell that you get
for fishing
ah
wait i didn't right otherwise it would
show
right at the fishing pond huh
i did wash my hands
i did
but maybe she was mad because i touched
her with um with hands
maybe that's why she was looking at me
like that
wait you can get two seashells
at the fishing pond that one is luck
don't worry about that one oh okay
you need to dry them somewhere
exactly and chunkers has an insane
amount of fur it's just
no actually normally i don't dry my
hands at my cat's fur because it makes
all the
loose hair stick to my hands
oh wait did i get that one before what
the [\h__\h]
did i get the one in the
in the dog house
i guess i probably did is that the
doghouse on the map
can i why can i not zoom i want to zoom
into this map i did okay
yeah i guess i did
uh 35
trendy game
ah did i get the one in the game house
the the
crane game
wait i don't think i did the crane game
one
how about the lake above pothole field
well wait wait wait wait
yeah claw game i did not do the claw
game moon
okay let's do claw game write that down
uh
waterfall behind the castle
wait is there two
no no it's just one or is it
is there two
seashells that you can get at the crane
game
it's two
you said there was one in the swamp
it
no i already took that one did i none
has she had this hairstyle before yes
yes yes
i got it with with the kimono outfit
together with the twin tail hairstyle
wait maybe maybe it's just one
no it is true what the [\h__\h]
according to this video there's two
two at the crane game
and then
what about the key cavern oh
oh
okay kevin
oh that one easy that one is easy to get
okay
let's try to get the crane game once
and the key kevin
uh
should i
[Music]
i'll just walk to the village
i hope i can find the exit is this the
exit nope probably not out
oh it reflects the
the spears that they threw at me
oh [\h__\h] nice
so any projectiles any of them are being
reflected that's pretty cool
mirror shield yes yes
i thought it was only like lasers and
beams
well good for me
okay time for some
riveting crane game content
there it is i only see one but in the
video for some reason there were two
hello i would like to play the game
10 rupees that is so cheap now we can
play endlessly guys
i know how it works thank you
it goes out
uh
x move forward a move right okay
[\h__\h] i went too far
oh [\h__\h]
yeah well we gotta get a feeling for it
you know
there's some delay there's some pink
no no pain but there is a
little bit of way and i'm gonna get into
the rhythm challenge again
oh
[Music]
close
it's the ping it's the thing
molly online
molly online i don't i don't think
anyone could complain about molly online
because at least
at least there is a crane game that you
can play online that's i think that in
itself is amazing
like it's a real place where you can
challenge it online
you don't have to go outside in order to
use it that's amazing to me
please please please please please
no
ah eyes so close
and it has a [\h__\h] ton of collabs with
whole life so
i hope one day maybe if they make
overseas shipping possible because i
don't think molly online doesn't have
overseas shipping right now does it
oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
but if they ever [\h__\h]
implement it then i want to say oh then
i want to see her live english collab
you little [\h__\h]
you little see [\h__\h]
that is a horrible position because um
isn't that kind of a position lower than
my crane
and i can't go down
oh [\h__\h]
i dropped my spaghetti
yeah
let me even have it i will try once one
more time
and then i might reset
she had to meet her
oh
it might work but what about the rail is
it not in the way
oh oh you can still catch it you can
still catch it just don't move too much
it's just no matter how
perfectly you grab it
it will
slide out of your crane thingy i hate
that
the physics man
[\h__\h] raid
so slimy why did you put slime on the
seashell
huh to make more money understandable
have a nice day i mean that's just
ridiculous
the way it floats
man
you say the show
okay that that works yes sir
we got it
uh i wanna challenge again but wait oh i
thought you're gonna bring another
one
okay hmm
[Music]
i don't want the doll oh wait what what
does if i get the doll
what do i get out of the doll
will she give me a seashell if i give
her a doll
she'll give me a cute i don't want a
cute doll what the [\h__\h] what do i need a
cute doll for
is it part of the training quest
shanina
perfect perfect
but it's so round it's like gonna be
tough to keep it in my arms
i think
oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh
oh okay
i mean fine with me
she wasn't by accident okay
here we go again
it's not working wait quake go into my
arms
inside
genius
no
give me a hollow whenever the mood
strikes yeah yeah yeah how many how many
are those
ten
that's nothing
but okay
i needed some magic powder so that's
okay pretty strong huh
my secret power
chow chow finger
oh did i tell you guys before about the
husky that i keep on seeing uh not keep
on seeing but i mean i think today was
huh
the third time
you remember when i saw it as a baby and
then i saw it like a few weeks later or
like two three weeks really not a long
time it grew it grew up so much by then
and then today i saw it again the husky
and it was so big now
but you could still kind of
see that it's a puppy because of the
puppy
fur
it looked very much like a puppy's fur
like so fluffy
and and thin
so cute i really wanted to give
that doggle a hug man
yeah what
i i i thought you wanted a doll
what
what who'd i give the doll to
yeah it's kind of a teenager now i guess
do you want the doll no
what do i maybe just put it on the on
the pedestal
maybe i'll just put it on there by
myself
[Music]
yeah i have it
she doesn't want it
well then
what the hell did i get it for
huh
yup everything checks out
everything checks out cool but no not
really
i have a chow chow oh
oh is it a different house oh
wait which one
why is it not this house what the hell
on her table
oh
there was another pedestal i didn't see
it blind show strikes again
that one
a child
yes place it she'll be very happy about
it look at that give me something for
that
nothing
you're not gonna say anything about that
it looks like your dog
girl
woman
women
yeah i guess she wants both of them and
then she will react what the hell
what
she doesn't give a [\h__\h]
onyo hyper chat crashed
ah okay it's to be back though it's do
be back welcome back hyper chat
okay uh
we wanted to go where
uh
what's the [\h__\h]
i want to go
to
[Music]
here
check trendy game again for second show
when i re-entered it wasn't there
i was wondering about that
[Music]
where am i going
the shop
does
does the shop sell uh
the seashells
i didn't see one
um
[Music]
what
think
i think
ow
this is a really annoying path i also
want that heart piece how do i get that
[Music]
i wonder
when in doubt hook shots
[Music]
when in doubt hook shot
excuse moi
for
me
never learning my lesson
cut the bush on the island huh
island
what
which island
over here
one bush
oh that one
oh that's not the one i didn't see that
one yet
oh my god
oh my god well i want the heart
what does it piece here
wait can i get go there from the from
for the house
do you let me go into your garden
does he
feel leave the usual room i forgot why
you're there did i not give you like a
time where you would be able to
leave
i remember going
this path before and i got stuck for
some reason i guess there were too many
holes
well this is wonderful
[Music]
shortcut
oh
[Music]
i'm coming for you
no problem no problem the path is free
uh supposedly
how come i cannot just balance
walking over there yeah
[Music]
yes
okay uh
what else have i been here before
hello
you saw sleep secrets beneath your souls
what are you trying to tell me
beneath my souls is a secret
where where is it
i got the seashell here already okay
that makes sense yeah
what do i have them all or am i still
missing one i'm missing one uh
well
is there anyone close any seashell that
you guys know of that i don't have yet
that's close by
and the third dungeon key was here
[Music]
rock mace east
rockman is this the rock mace
[Music]
cemetery
or is this the rock maze
which one is the rock maze
is this the rock maze is this the rock
maze
that's it which one
the
cemetery bottom
at this one
near the castle that's really far
which one you mean the cemetery or what
ah
the second thing i said
this one
[Music]
i'll check it out i hope that's what you
mean
[Music]
where
awesome
[Music]
hmm
ah
down here i thought it was
thank you
okay we got a beautiful number now uh
we're pretty close so i guess we could
walk
and then what we get the the master
sword
the famous the one and only
but not really i guess some kind of
similar version
of the master sword
a fake
a ripoff of the master sword a seashell
sword oh
show me what you get
give me something nice please
raise your sword overhead
hi
i shall grant you new power
[Music]
is it double power now what is it you
should put your name on it right away of
course
how much how much stronger are we
talking
doubles the damage honestly with that we
could just take the defense instead the
blue cloves
but i'm too lazy to go there so
nope we're just gonna go full power
what's the last thing that you can get
uh in the seashell shrine what would be
the last thing we're not getting it i
think what would it be i'm curious
tell me tell me
a dungeon towel
really
[Music]
okay i really don't care about that but
yes yes it shoots a beam now i think
only when i'm full health right
but that is super cool
cause it's like an a free arrow
call it magic has got a
oh
[Music]
look look at me
i am powerful
okay am i
able to enter the next dungeon the last
one or
or do i need to
like
i don't know do something
i've got the power i'm so ready yeah
didn't i already unlock it because i've
oh
it's because i thought uh i thought i
fought the monster
i guess there's enough seashell here but
i don't need any more seashells
okay so we're going up here huh
last dungeon
in the tall tall mountains
please don't wear your voice out too
much don't end up like my iris
yeah um
i would like to avoid it too but
i mean i'm working on it i'm always
trying to
um take care of it as much as i can
by
doing the things that i can
um
i also already looked up like like a
specialist
in case i need one
uh
and and i
brought out the
um
a humidifier again that i haven't had
out in a long long time
humidifier child is back oh dear what
are you are you boss
oh i can't shoot my laser
hey
come at me bro fight me
oh you're fast you fast boy oh
i see
i see how it is
well you can't even aim
oh my small body is cute
oh they left me
inuka
it looks like a freaking hot dungeon
here what is this
oh
minecraft
[\h__\h]
and it comes back ah
minecraft because um my mom told me
about you know a certain device
that you can build in minecraft to
um
wait how do i go back
okay i guess i don't
yeah a cool
a cool device
uh to build
um
i don't know what what stones it was
again
but some kind of stone to walk over
magma
oh yeah
oh i'm gonna fall down here a lot
unless
um
hold on ted hold on to it
okay only one only one death that's
pretty good so far
what wait i can
i don't have to pick them up one by one
anymore i can just smash them with my
sword
and we got the beak guys we got the beak
oh i picked them up anyway out of reflex
i am back
boyfriend
is that revenge for how i traded you
i'm sorry i'm sorry
oh my head
it's not fair you shouldn't aim for
people's heads oh oh you almost you
almost lost it
no you did lose it
oh
there you go
now you're dead was that really worth it
was that really worth it
extreme dodgeball ball yeah
not on the [\h__\h] head that's like
in school when playing dodgeball
hitting someone's head with it is like a
scandal
like how could you
how could you
it's not cool david
you're playing the game wrong david
it's not fun that way david
oh you little [\h__\h]
why me oh i'm sorry not you we're
different david you're good david i know
that
if only i could kill these [\h__\h]
monsters now but i still can't
[Music]
yeah fairy
nice
that's pretty cool
oh nice to meet you again
come here come here
let me kill you
why are you
why you one monster again did you like
fuse again
the boomerang
there's a boomerang to kill electric
boys oh
i forgot that i have a boomerang
does it work on you
we are not becoming friends i tell you
that
not funny
room clear deposit
ah
not you again
they reuse this enemy quite a lot don't
they uh oh [\h__\h] oh
i wanted to do it no damage
everyone you did not see that one time
he picked me up it did not happen
it did not happen
we're gonna go this way first
a perfect victory yeah
another hotel
oh i want to try
oh
that's wrapped up
oh that is
life changing
just comes a little bit too late it
would have indeed been helpful
to have that in the last dungeon already
oops i guess i didn't need that oops
oh
we're gonna have some fun too i'm
speedrunning this dungeon right now it
feels like
what do i fight you with
wait am i am i redoing every
dungeon every dungeon uh boss that i
have had so far
because they look familiar
hahahahaha
if you slash them they give you money
yeah
i wanna hit them
what
and then they disappear
oh but i still get the key okay it
always feels like i did not really kill
them all but i guess once it's becoming
a baby i did okay there we go they
always drop a [\h__\h] fairy are you
kidding me
like gifting me with fairies
as if it was nothing
does this mean sans will be back
perhaps if my logic is correct yes
um how do we fight this monster again
ah i just uh
did this
which i know might not be the right way
to kill it but it is one way
and that means it is the right way
there's just many right ways
heroin
and that is a big dungeon but i guess it
only has one floor no
for now
that is a big dungeon wow
if it works it works exactly
that's the spirit
uh
there was nothing here right okay okay
elk
you good
you good uh link
are we feeling good we can go
up here
wow
oh yeah you guys are probably wondering
if i'm gonna try terraria like some of
the other girls
um
not really planning on it
it just
doesn't quite charm me
what is that
i don't see [\h__\h]
can i throw the powder over there it
feels like it's too far away
i i think the only way that i'm gonna
play it
if
everyone plays it all the time
like minecraft and if if i were the only
one left out
if i'm the only one
in hollow ian who's not playing uh
terrari yeah
then i will play it just for the simple
fact that i do not want to be left out
oh she
oh so he
he does escape
whoa
i killed one of them he does escape from
the arrows but
the the laser the sword laser which has
approximately the same speed
he is not able to
dodge interesting
probably you'll lose interest in it oh i
don't know i think that the girls are i
mean i was watching the stream a little
bit yesterday
i think
yeah they're enjoying it now but i don't
think it will become
a big craze like minecraft to be honest
so
i think we're good
wait i want that
powder uh
i want it
i would honestly be surprised if
it would become such a huge thing
arc is more likely uh
yeah that's that's another game that the
girls have been starting to play in
groups
uh
but i'm also not interested in arc
either
so we have a little bit of an issue here
we have it
[Music]
foreign
um
i mean there's a higher chance that i'm
gonna check out ark than me checking out
uh
terraria to be honest
nice oh wait uh
what's up
it's just like
but mom
[Music]
no no no actually i'm the mom i'm the
mama says but we have minecraft at home
and then gouda and then the others are
the kids that are like but i want to
play terraria and i'm like but we have
minecraft at home
what else do you want
what else do you want is that not good
enough for you anymore
now i understand a lot of people enjoy
terraria and i guess it has a charm to
it and it's it's not exactly the same i
guess i heard um in terraria there's
more like fights
more
boss fights or so it's a bit more
rpg-ish i suppose
um
but
i don't want to get into that now man
and also pokemon is releasing
to the day after tomorrow so
all the girls will be playing pokemon
then i think
as we've seen it last time
so
i don't see
[Music]
me
i don't see a need to get into it now
but as i said if everyone's playing it
except me then i will
play it out of peer pressure
uh follow the holes of the rock that
rolls this l is the key
what
later i'll see okay
i've been using my left stick i don't
know what they mean
do
have i been down these stairs before
thank you maxwell thank you for being
here oh yeah i have been here before i
where where where where do i go next oh
i have a key
i could open one of these two
i want to go there how do i get there
go back here can i go here
can i go there
maybe actually better to take the
underground
that's not nice that is not nice at all
your little shits
stop frying me you shouldn't be frying
me and told you guys i'll die forever if
you if you eat me
i'm not supposed to be friend
ruthless guys um how do i get this
machine to uh come to me
hello
wait
stick
[Laughter]
oh yeah
it's to be like that
this is i think this is impossible no
it's not no it's not yeah
the map
i've received the map jesus
smart yeah i know
not really though
okay who's got the map oh dear
that looks like
it would be the body of a monster these
are the hands this is the head this is
the
those are the feet and
well
i don't need to tell you what that is do
i
a turtle
oh are you spoilering me are you telling
me what the mob the boss monster will be
damn it going here didn't do anything
for me maybe i should go back to the
beginning of the dungeon
oh because it's called turtle rock i
don't
i don't recall that
i don't recall that at all
[Music]
we shall go
will you let me pass thank you
see that is so smart because now
i can go this way i can even go both
ways
oh which way should i go i went this way
first
oh [\h__\h]
it was a useless path
on yo
[Music]
damn it
well
now i learned my lessons
i learned that i need to go to the right
side
good stairs oh
okay well
which one is better
well now we're going the other way
i'm just scouting the area you know
just scouting
speaking of scout
ttrpgs has been a long time hasn't it
i know it has been a long time i don't
know uh
i don't know when callie wants to
continue it
solid ice
should i come back with fire am i
getting the elemental fire
it has been a long time
last episode was so short too
but i think
i think that it's supposedly
like the first season so to say
is to put
supposedly
um like it should be like finding an end
some sometime sooner or later damn it i
can't move out here even so i scouted
the area but it doesn't really do
anything for me because i can't go
anywhere
don't say don't
[Music]
if i move it to a certain path
could i go to one of the key doors
if i go here
i could go down then
huh
never mind
um
one one last teleportation excuse me i'm
stuck
i am stuck i think or am i maybe i'm not
i'm gonna go left now
oh yeah
no escape link we're gonna endure this
until the very end
this is where i wanna go
this is it because there's a chest here
what it shows up on the map
which means
which means what
why does it show up on the mount
huh
i come here later for that oh
okay um then in that case
i'll try going up again
oh yeah right this was this stupid room
where i also don't know what to do
huh
so much for speed running the dungeon
it's not that easy
i can get it now
do i need to dig
ah
[\h__\h]
i understand
oh
ah
huh
am i am i pushing it am i um
going to the left too late but i'm
actually activating it pretty
early okay well there we go
ah this just has money in it that does
not help me oh but will this stay this
way
wait does this count for all the other
rooms as well that have that mechanism
does the same thing go for the other
rooms because
in that case
then i know how to continue i have a key
yeah yeah yeah
oh wait okay no the path is still there
but okay
and the path is not there anymore but
that's fine that's okay i don't need it
okay
so it
doesn't want me to fill all of the no
but that's not an m that's not a void so
i guess it doesn't apply to this does it
ah
[Music]
wasn't there another one of those rooms
here
was this also a room like that
huh i can push the blocks at the top oh
oh
is that so
but it was a dead end
why did i go here
no
now i'm stuck here again
what's up
so how do you
what are you supposed to do in that kind
of situation
yeah but i i okay i can at least go to
the left side
okay
[Music]
but i didn't want to go here
i can't do much here either
[Music]
i want to go this way
but now i have there's a bomb
what you mean the one i already opened
why is there one pushable block
why is there
that one
should i just warp to the beginning
again
so stupid
but okay
now we know take the middle path and
then push the block away and then we can
open that one door
with the key but i cannot believe that
this is really
[Music]
the way you're supposed to do it
you don't need to but when i how would i
get back here
how else would i get back here
okay
uh
right
a tunnel that takes way too much time i
feel like this is
saving me time
uh
[Music]
want to eat some laser
i can't send it to you
unfortunate oh hello
this is a better place to fight
you a little [\h__\h]
ow
i do not like you will i get a chest if
i uh kill you
ow
well now i can't do my super special
attack anymore come here
oh
i'm fighting you with your own weapons
how's it feel how's it taste
taste your own medicine
come here
ow
stupid children of this oh that does not
do anything
i thought i would be getting something
out of that book okay what's here
what do we have here some stupid flowers
[Music]
oh it's bathing in the water that's kind
of cute
in the water it's a lava magma excuse me
a slight difference
what now
nothing
water
yes that's right
nothing to do here either unless you can
tell me
how i can get to that other side without
falling into the lava
i don't see a way
i don't see anything here either oopsie
sorry
not yet
water in the fire what water in the fire
what
what did i say
nothing to do
okay
i don't have a tea anymore i need
i thought i said something weird
turns out
it wasn't me
oh wait oh shuttle a minute i can at
least go this way
oh
this has to be it
because what else would it be
oh wait i can just jump off here
[Laughter]
but have i not been here before but
there is a bumpable wall at least oopsie
okay that works
uh but what's here
out of curiosity not a hodo
we found something new new
crystals again
i have not seen
any of those platforms but okay
and once again we're stuck here are you
[\h__\h] kidding me
remember this room
hi
are you kidding me
uh
huh
what is this dungeon i only have
question marks above my head right now
oh
have i been here before
probably
yeah yeah yeah
huh
what
this dungeon is wasting my time
is it you is it you
ow
what am i doing wrong what am i doing
what am i doing wrong
i mean that's one thing that i got down
shooting those things down
what am i missing
explore the right side more
really
is that what you want me to do right
side of the dungeon okay okay
[Music]
go away go away
you're in the way
sorry for making such a mess here
the right side
pop up
[Music]
have not been in here before
i've seen no i have been i remember this
room
but
how do i get to the other side
on the other side
ah random jumbo only get oh yes yes
sorry
thank you
no i think i can do it
it has it
i guess i cannot
oh but i have been on this side before
and i can go there from the other side
oh
question
from here maybe
four spaces too much yeah what is that
very
where did that fairy go
[Music]
you think it's possible dianko nelly
we might never know
but
i'm doubting it myself
hello hi steph
i'm still like i'm good
just missing uh
some oxygen
oh yeah okay i guess i can't run die
okay
what are you saying i heard oh what you
said before right yeah yeah
okay
now it totally makes sense
everything makes sense now
so you want me to fill all this up
[Music]
i swear
i went down but oh i see the bombable
wall now now i see it because it got lit
up a little bit
but i suppose i still have to do this
little riddle
anyway
oh yeah
a different
way to get to this room
no need to feel hundred percent it
really
what am i doing this for then
maybe
oh perfect
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh
it stays anyway
wait would i have gotten something if i
feel a hundred percent so close or she
on it
because
right down oh yeah i wonder where we
need to use that coat that we got
[Music]
yes i know where to use it i know where
to use it
[Music]
we are gonna go there we're gonna go
there
we're gonna go there
yeah i i
don't know yet where we are going to use
the special coat but we have it written
down so we are prepared
all right so we now go to the middle
again
and we will walk through that door no
matter what it takes
yeah yeah which chimpkin was it that
said we don't need to fill in her new
person yeah
your memory what happened with your
memory chimpkin
chimpkin brain
whoa
wow hey
oh interesting um
hey this
did i really go here should i go the
other way first
oh
what's going on in here
christmas season it is but i can't get
the chest unfortunately
is
you're not gonna get me again but you
know what i need these and then
carefully quick
move your butt link
oh why are these all so
broken
this rock has many cracks there must be
some way to shatter it
oh could it be possibly a bomb
duh
oh so brian that's why there's bumps
here
who won the font
oh is that a secret path that opened up
as well
oh and the door open
to defeat the monsters who hold the key
attack them from ohio place
gotcha
[Music]
uh
oh oh [\h__\h]
you i is he talking about them
you might be talking about them
i don't know i have more than enough
bombs i think
however uh i need my
boomerang um maybe this
come here
what oh wait i see is this a time
challenge
i need a key
oh no there it goes
there it goes yeah good thing i have a
lot of bombs a little i probably really
don't need that many let's see what what
do we get from that side hello my
friends it's you again
here i brought some snacks for you
oh you're just like my kitty cats
oh oh no are you gonna corner me
oh you ate it anyway you ate your
veggies i'm so proud of you
not like you have much of a tourist [\h__\h]
does their damage reset
oh [\h__\h]
they don't like that one
you turned around
i did not see that one coming
oh come on
wow
it's like that sour cat or do you know
that wasn't there like a like a candy
that kind of like explodes in him okay
not really probably doesn't really
explode but
maybe it has a
it gets advertised as such
pop rocks yeah
fairies
so many fairies
pop rocks hmm
that's that's what i meant i think yeah
yeah
it does really seem as if they are uh
letting us meet all of the previous boss
monsters again
hey madison
this time i got it without you guys
all right
it's
i i feel like all of this is such a
waste i don't want these items to go to
waste i almost want to like
have a boss monster kill me so that i
can make use of this medicine
i would have preferred a key for that
hmm
what about that
chest
i can't even go back
more than easy
but all these items are back that's
wonderful it's like a treasure treasure
room beauty cream for kiwama
that's right
we're oh
i'm going for a swim
we are in this room again
uh forcefully could have probably jumped
oh could i could i have jumped damn it
if that is the case then
once again
i did not use my owl
brain the right one
you want to fight
fight me
stupid skeletons
where are you going now
who says i can't kill
those mobs
[Music]
i feel like i can
i just gotta
be very smart about it
i have to be fast yeah
no not with a bomb
there we go because they didn't they
give a hint to fight them from above i
think they meant this room because you
can attack them from above
here on the left side but i guess it was
not 100 necessary so now we have the key
[Music]
way easier than i thought yeah the four
times damage makes it easier too
it's so dark
uh
it is so dark
oh
and again it is very dark
come on
where are you going
[Music]
what do you want am i stuck again here
oh i don't have a key
[Music]
left
sometimes i wonder do i need glasses
i need glasses
you guys gotta help me choose
some that look good on me
will ya
boy
some proper glasses yeah
it's not a hint
if the statue looks strange shoot it
above the ball
uh-huh
i i don't know is that statue looking
strange
no i guess not
okay
is there a chest here
yes
chest stickles on my side
[Music]
i've been here before and i was like i
can't [\h__\h] light the fire but there
is a
didn't i already killed the enemies in
this
room before and i still didn't get the
chest
i don't know if it's worth to
yeah
i don't think it's worth jumping down
for that
[\h__\h] you
i'll have time for you
but
not a hold of this
when the comp is activated it means
there's a hidden chest there right
totally necessary
these [\h__\h] tiny ass bets
okay
uh we're making progress guys there's a
i know there's stairs there but there's
also a
door here that we might want to open
yeah okay that's so that's the chest
that i tried to open but i already have
cream on me [\h__\h]
should have used it somewhere else yeah
uh yeah
excuse me what excuse me what
excuse me what
cho a minute i saw something here that
we all
need at once
[Music]
[\h__\h] you
what is what is here um
teleportation device
and the house
oh
no thank you
what is this house
honey ah
it's in the dungeon
oh
that's how you kill them from above but
wait
how do you get the chest in this room i
already killed those mobs
or is that what is that what they meant
with kill them from above
that really is not necessary either
though
i spying
[Music]
it reset
yeah
i have to do it again because i went
outside yeah
welcome
oh thank you for eating it very nice of
you
ah
it was easier to kill them from below to
be honest
i'll make it work one way or another oh
[\h__\h] come on
you're waving my bombs
hallelujah
[Music]
eat your stupid veggies
you can't even get the fairies that they
drop if you kill them from above i don't
really think that makes a lot of sense
[\h__\h]
wasting my bums here if this doesn't
give me the treasure
i'm gonna be mad
why did i not get that the first time
[Music]
uh
just because i didn't kill them from
above
huh
what
nintendo shenanigans
i got it but reset the room on entry
well shouldn't the chest at least stay
the ones that i already got what the
[\h__\h]
huh
yeah i [\h__\h] i thought they meant this
room
because that makes sense as well
but okay whatever
okay so we have another key
wanna use it on one of those two
any preference guys
any anyone that you think would be
smarter this one
shoot the statue
statue
oh [\h__\h]
that one i already tried shooting it did
i not
or you mean a different one
i tried shooting it
i missed
oh tiata does not miss
oh no she does not
well i mean from here she probably does
but well now we're [\h__\h]
eh
huh
on a certain square
wait how do i how did i get there how
did i get there
don't remember
sheesh
and what do i get if i hit it is it is
it a key or something like that
guys uh totally random but one of my
close friends
is currently in mexico
she flew from australia australia
austria
to mexico
uh what was it
cancun or
carcon cancun
cancun
i think
apparently it really was not difficult
at all i asked her like if it was tough
like you know traveling there she said
no not at all i think
they didn't even need to
[Music]
wait it eva was that they didn't care
about vaccinations
or that they didn't care about tests but
one of them was necessary
and they didn't care about the other one
i'm not sure which one it was oh
oh the restrictions here are a joke oh
i've never been to mexico but like i've
seen like a few pictures on her
on their social media
hanging there in the super nice hot
weather and i'm like pretty jealous
and
the thing is
shall i tell you some more um spicy
details
very nicely
i've heard a lot about it but i've
personally never really seen mexico as a
as a
like um
um that vacation destination i feel like
where am i going
i feel like when i uh
think of that vacation destinations i
would have always like kind of thought
of other places first
but from what i've seen
from what i've seen so far
looks pretty damn good i'm just trying
to by accident find that room again with
the key
dammit um
[Music]
do i need to go um
i don't know where to go
the spicy stuff let me tell you in a
moment although
this does
where does salsa come from
where does salsa come from guys
mexico
then i can say
salsa from mexico is pretty spicy just
kidding um
it's not what i wanted to say
where do i go
not only was entering the country
extremely easy
but
wait
yeah i know
but
um
what also is fascinating
is that i'm lost and i don't know where
to go
no
um uh
whatever
um
where does where does that one lead
again
fascinating
um where does this one lead again
no what i wanted to say is
use the wave point outside oh
you're smart boy but isn't everything
gonna reset again and i'm gonna be mad
i hope not
okay what i was saying is that
this friend she
flew there
with
um other friends and one of those other
friends
um
is a flight attendant
and she told me
how much they paid for the tickets
and it's [\h__\h] ridiculous
it is ridiculous redonkulous and they're
not even related i thought you know when
i when i was uh when i auditioned
to
join that big big big airline
i guess it depends on the airline but
that that airline where i auditioned to
they told me that um i can take
i can give
wait actually now that i try to remember
it i don't remember that well
i think it was
you can give
cheaper
tickets to family members only not even
free tickets
just cheaper tickets
is it you
or is it the other one or is it both of
you
how can i even how can i even hit that
one
what do you mean
what do you mean guys
what
are you talking about
do i need to use the other engine
[Music]
um
well now i'm here
do we want to be here
[Applause]
i know one how that one
okay that makes a lot of sense
you want me to shoot you from here
no what about here
about here
you [\h__\h] joking
are you joking
stand how oh i can walk on top of it
[Music]
it doesn't look like you can stand on
top of it what the hell okay
hi
let's open this one how about that
shall we open this one
are we okay with opening this one
uh
exactly thank you aaron fina thank you
yes i there is a good clip that
compiled my super long
um airline audition
story into a relatively short video uh
was it cow carrot i think it was cow
carrot
he made a really good video if you want
to listen to that story please listen to
it um
i definitely recommend the clip unless
you want to watch a full episode of my
alice uh playthrough cause i'm a genius
and i i i
lose track a lot when i tell stories so
um oh i have two keys oh
and yeah then uh i forget what the hell
i was talking about like just like right
now i actually wanted to say
that the flights for
friends from austria to [\h__\h]
uh
to freaking
cancun
were like
unbelievable
about
uh not one way but both ways
total
about 450 euro
can you believe it
can you [\h__\h] believe it normally
normally a flight like that would cost
you over a thousand bucks
because that's an insane distance and i
think it was was it wasn't that direct
it might have been a direct i'm not sure
maybe not i'm not sure about the direct
flight but at least it must have been
maximum one one
one change of flight
nice i paid double that i can imagine
yeah
and and that flight attendant got that
price for all of the friends they went
there together in a group
now
i mean okay i don't really care about
that but uh i feel i think it's pretty
impressive
i want to go there too but just because
it's warm
looks warm and nice and cozy
what
sorry link
i'm sorry
sorry link i thought i could just you
know
i thought i could just
walk down
apparently not
oh
what do we have here
nothing for me are you [\h__\h] kidding
me
who
i do not recall fighting a crazy guy
like you what the [\h__\h]
ow
what the hell is the matter with you
fight
should i use a fairy or should i just
have the cream work its wonders and then
get the other cream
[Music]
because there's another cream
that is a lot of damage you know
i'll use the cream here
or maybe
maybe i won't even need it
okay wait a second
chill dude chill my dude
would you chill for one second
wow
what do you want
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] my my boom boom boom boom boomer
beam
excuse me
he's gonna kill me he's gonna kill me
[Music]
oh
uh
okay okay i got it i got it
i got it i got it
it's as simple as that
i understand though it took me a while
but because so many things did not work
not even the
bag
not even that worked
so
naruho
[Music]
float like a butterfly sting like i'll
be a rumble tinter rumble is that some
kind of
song lyrics that i don't know about
[Music]
how did i even
did i jump into this room
oh and now i'm [\h__\h] stuck i have to
use the teleportation device
not a hodor
it's a boxing thing oh
come on the car is
well
back to the beginning but we could now
get us some cream uh where is is this
one
was it this one no
it must have been this one because it's
not
oh no it's this one
how do i get there
i went oh
wait a second
what if i
go here activate the crystal
and then pour it back to the beginning
and pour it here
because the color
yeah okay you guys are saying the same
thing fine fine i knew it without ya
i'm a big
grown hero now
i knew it before you told me
how
it's impossible
impossible impossible okay impossible
call me beat me when
what are you talking about
i'm still doing decently fine
where am i
no
when is orange the blue ones go down
right so
now we can go
to the beginning of the dungeon
[Music]
unless wait wait a second am i close to
no
i get there
whatever maybe we'll make it there by
accident we'll get close and then
we'll pick up the cream that we ordered
he said
this dungeon is basically done now
attention for reasons
you're making me feel motivated
you motivate me
i see
the magic stick
the magic stick now hold on
oh so that makes all the
ice
melts and probably does some other cool
stuff as well
wait
i got the magic stick
oh you don't like the magic stick huh
you're like i'm out of here okay why do
we want to use it
there we go first
i was the eye step was it was it down
here no
no that was not it
loconique
oh
um here
can i use it somewhere here
i don't recall
yeah that wasn't there like a dark room
was it above
[Music]
what is it prison time guys open your
presents close your eyes
here it is a key
i'm
beautiful ah
oh
well the magic stick won't help me here
will it add in
oh okay i'm fine
don't need the magic sticks help
um
all right
[Music]
guys we're down here
are we done
wish you good luck thank you
i need it
it's been eight hours
i i like you know hanging out for a long
time with you guys again haven't done it
so often recently
what do we do here
where do you want where do we want to go
do we want to go
is there something new
oh
yeah where the [\h__\h] is the ice cream
no no no
[Music]
not gonna get me this time
yes we are what do you mean still on the
final dungeon we haven't been here for
that long
where am i
why am i here i had a [\h__\h] in my ear
why am i here
it makes no sense
makes no sense
where's your eyes from
i never ending dungeon
sorry guys he will have to suffer with
me was that is that not where i came
from
what
well that was a little
little
trip that we went on together
for absolutely nothing does the magic
stick do something against these buddies
nope
the magic stick
does not
create wonders apparently
sanity is going down yes crying
how about
going to the side
um
and then
i don't know
one of these stairs
which ones
sheet
hope i don't regret this
yes ice
i found ice
wow fascinating it's a revolution oh my
god
wow wait is this a riddle
can i
yeah can i mess this up
it seems like i can okay now
yes i can yes i can yes i can
wait i want those heights
uh-huh
yeah
is that okay
it's one way to do it no
maybe not
big thinking time
how how do i not melt
everything
use my phoenix brain
sure um okay um
how about
how about this
ah
um uh
no
[Music]
shoot while falling
huh
i shoot while falling
what
ah
[Laughter]
uh
laughs
no no that was by accident okay
i wanted to go back to here but okay
come on
i have an idea i have an idea i have an
idea i have an idea i think i think i'm
not sure
might be wrong
ah
but this time this one didn't go away
was this what i wanted to happen
was this yes wait a second maybe
[Music]
i just fell into it
uh uh
[\h__\h]
already made a mistake
[Laughter]
oops
is this like i think i understand
um
but
hmm is there no way to
like if i shoot
this one then the one on the very left
will disappear as well which is what i
don't want
that is quite the riddle i
oh we don't even have them what's that
what did i what the hell did i come here
for
that was
useless we gotta do this again when we
come back
that's for nothing it just leads us to
the bus
a room
oh man
so that was the wrong stairs apparently
what about here nothing
you
how do i get out of this mess
starting to
little small patients i have to go this
way apparently
not very cool
um
so apparently
these are the right stairs they better
be
uh-huh
it seems as if we're getting roasted
goomba
to eat for dinner tonight
doesn't that sound lovely
no reward for burning them all okay
that's fine
oh
there's a lot of trial and error here i
see
okay whatever
hello where are we i have a key and
there is a door that needs a key
so i feel like we are meant
to be with each other
you and me
adore and the key
tt oh hello sir
that is a new boss too what the [\h__\h] why
are they all so fast oh my god
[Music]
what the hell
better
yeah
we jump over it
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] helmet
oh
a little bit real good
i hate the directions
the controls sometimes
oh no i'm wasting all my [\h__\h] arrows
i can't jump over him he's too fat
that's one way to do it
oh he's going backwards oh [\h__\h] ow ow ow
ow out
[\h__\h] help
well now i'm going to chase you
ow
that was lucky
oh i need that fairy really bad thank
you heal me
yeah that was really weird okay this
looks like a riddle
oh [\h__\h] she's smart oh [\h__\h] kfb
underestimated there
oh [\h__\h] i forgot i will never mind
i see
that was a test run
i know exactly what to do here
or july
maybe i don't want to know maybe i want
to live my life the way i intend to live
it
maybe i don't want to be told by others
how to live my life
[\h__\h] this has to be the last one
[Music]
first try let's go
[\h__\h] up
[Music]
what about this huh we want to be
original [\h__\h]
first time
if i would just stop for a moment and
think think about it then i think we
would succeed
oh that's difficult oh my finger let's
go
oh my finger
you'll be gone you'll be
here we go
i have access to the boss room and we
have the
boss key
the game is ending guys
i mean i i suppose that after this
dungeon we have another like big big
boss but yeah
first one thank you i know incredible
isn't it
uh i would like to go back to that room
um
not that one
okay i need your brain for a moment guys
i want this chest
but i also want this chest
how do i get this dressed
probably also hook shut
um
[Music]
yeah i want the cream i want the cream
now cream is here
but i don't know how to get there
anymore
ah
yeah yeah this one i know i don't know
[Music]
you guys can't explain them properly to
me what if i jump down here you think
i'll be there quicker
maybe from here and then right
yeah yeah
that at least gives me access to this
chest wow wow
which is a ruby
for um completion's sake
yeah useless money especially now at the
end of the game
orange juice
right and up the stairs
[Music]
huh
what
ah
[Music]
my special night cream
i can't go to sleep without it even
though i'm sleeping right now uh or am i
not sorry just just kidding it has
absolutely no meaning whatsoever
[Music]
and now
we go to the bus if we ever find the
path again i i know i know it's that ice
room
that other ice room
how to get there good question
wow oh no
sleep gaming exactly
that's what i'm doing
um
the other ice room
was was it this one was it here
warp to beginning faster aha
is that so
please don't
um
crystal room staircase left next to the
crystal room
aha
not a hotel uh but but the thing is
right that i always try to go there
by going here but i can't so
can i go there by
doing the lava thingy and i'm going to
the right side and then going
no time
no time to waste
we are at
8 hours 14 minutes
well good measure we gotta warm up a
little bit
oh
ah
friend of paladin announced amelia
watson yes it is me a friend of the
famous paladin announcer
and i am now
a hero
of the colors but i do not know how to
do this riddle anymore
[\h__\h]
there we go and then
oh
no she didn't
oh [\h__\h]
that was
something only a gamer could do
pure gamer skills
oh yes you did
and now we just with style
we just float over to the other side and
then here i remember the bottom row
i think i think
oh was it that
i remember it i made a mistake i got
this one this one and
[\h__\h] this one
oh my gosh
is the boss difficult guys do you know
can i like get those arrows
no
[\h__\h]
let's save
i got this of course i got it of course
i have full hp i have a cream and i have
two fairies
i've got a boomerang i've got all the
things
the last bus is hard for this oh you
mean the last last bus not this one
crack of fruit fruit feel finished
i will never let you play the
instruments of the sirens
no no you will oh
you're cute
that's me that's me you remember
remember my my school story when a
phoenix uh gets too hot-headed sometimes
she likes to run into the toilet because
her hair gets goes on fire and then she
plumps her head into the toilet
and then goes back to her class and says
that that looks like me that reminds me
of my time as a high school no junior
high school student
yeah
how do we fight you perhaps with the
stick with the magical stick
yep
i think the stick is useless guys
i mean it would have wouldn't it have
made sense to implement
the stick into the spikes
or am i just too
out
and now i know
now
how do i hit it when i hit it
he doesn't like when he gets close to me
he's so far fast that he's just gonna
bump into me and do damage to me i don't
see how i could
spam the magic stick
okay but that kind of works
what the hell
what are you
straight go straight for once
link is official european now
why'd you come here if it weren't for
you nothing would have to change you
cannot wait to win fish remember you two
are in the dream
sorry i would i would do some funny
voices but my fruit hurts
sorry
that was one of the easier bosses man
one of the easiest
[Music]
egg
yes egg
the egg on the mountain cause okay are
you calling me to breed it i mean
i'm an expert on hatching
eggs i guess
i i can give it a try i don't know if my
butt is really big enough for that but
i can i can try maybe in my phoenix form
my phoenix format would be a perfect
size honestly that egg
perfectly hatchable
size
in my current form
gonna be a bit problematic i don't know
if if my butt is big enough for it
what do you mean what do you mean low
battery what do you mean you are
connected what is happening
what do you mean i connected you huh
i'm not charging oh
oh she
okay
we're charging my body do we charging
i'm charging
that is some good orange juice man
okay
i ran out of now i don't have anything
to drink though
can i bring some water
never mind i'm just you guys always are
like why are you asking because i don't
know it's a reflex
i'm gonna i'm gonna go grab some water
[Music]
meow
is
hmm
[Music]
i forgot the water
hi
[Music]
i'm scratching chunker's belly
holding her like a baby
no
okay bye bye
so cute
chased her across the room
yeah she likes to play catch
it's so easy to catch her though it's so
easy
okay
wow
yes i'm still streaming
but i'm good don't worry chunkers gave
me energy
and kfp gives me energy too
it's just um
my throat may hurt a little bit
but you know what hurts even more
not being with kfp
my love for you is endless
and now i will
hatch the biggest egg
uh that ever existed
how do we get to the ink
how do i get to the angle
how do i get to the ink
how to become angle
wait it is
it cannot be so difficult
how do i get to egg
dump is shaq
where is he
ah
become egg
make scrambled egg out of
can you imagine how many people
we could serve scrambled egg
from dead egg
can you imagine restock on arrows
why you want to restock
you think i wanna use my money
on that stupid shop okay i will
yeah i used a lot of arrows for those
stupid
mobs in the dungeon especially
especially the one uh what i was there
what did we call them
what did we call them i forgot
i think i have to already tell you i
might not read super chats today because
my ear hurts as well it's probably not
good
uh only a little bit
only a little bit
[Music]
yeah
it's been a while
i feel like i've gotten older it's been
a while since i've done um
so
such a long one oh look 446 i guess
we'll go until maximum
powder too he doesn't have powder
where do you play powder
wait what
it's already past midnight what the [\h__\h]
how did that happen
wait i think i've i have enough errors
now
yeah i have enough uh
i have maximum powder anyway
and bombs i got enough too
i'm
good i can't have more powder yeah
how the [\h__\h] is it
okay well eight and a half hours how to
get to egg
how to get to egg
guys we're gonna rock this last bus
we're gonna kill that yoshi baby inside
no matter how we'll ever eat it
i wonder if you can make scrambled eggs
out of a yoshi egg
[Music]
what inside of yoshi egg is just black
cool
oh my
hey if i had one more heart piece i'd
get another heart [\h__\h] that's sad
you guys know of any heart piece that's
easy to get that i didn't get yet
do you know of any
maybe if i look here you remember ellie
did i forgot something
new
maddy
i don't need more hats okay
okay let's [\h__\h] it up
are we going to start a fight right away
don't i don't know oh wait i need to uh
i wait i need to make music how do i
make music ah
this
box like the flame of the
photographer
don't stop don't stop
beautiful
[Music]
are you vibing guys enjoy this concert
brought to you by lin kiyata
can play eight instruments at once i
don't know how but she just does it
[Music]
yoshi's honestly i would not be
surprised if it was a yoshi because
they've been showing us so many super
mario
references anyway in this game i mean
the whole egg must be a reference now
[Music]
uh
owl son this egg is too big for you
trust me
yeah we see mario is in kirby we've seen
um
uh peach
we've seen the the goombas
it wouldn't be a surprise
yeah but i must go home
oh [\h__\h] that that's gonna bring us uh a
tangent maybe during the super chat
reading thanks for the pinkie
i win fears your words you [\h__\h] woke
him up you [\h__\h]
couldn't you have let him wake up
naturally the end of the egg who could
okay
i thought i was gonna
hatch it but i guess it's hatching
already by the music
music does have a
nice effect on
babies i suppose we're in the [\h__\h]
egg
wait this is like good as outfit reveal
stream
i'm inside of kuda's
[Music]
welcome everybody so so uh do you guys
know how shark babies make eggs or
something like that
uh what
is there a secret path there that i'm
just not seeing
no okay
what
didn't i
[Music]
is it random rooms
the cold
left
left hole
up
and up
and right
and
ah
what do you remember
[Music]
november
right
[Music]
visit mine first
eh should should i where is she
oh no september oopsie
i'm going back
do i need to lose that money
keep going
i went i left on purpose
okay
we can come back here
uh
but if you say that there is like a last
chance to speak to marin
it better be worth it
[Music]
if this is not worth it if she doesn't
give me a kiss at least on my cheek
send it that
shoot
[Music]
i don't need a potion i already have a
cream on myself
madden you're finally back to where you
used to be
thank you for everything thank you
you're the kindest boy i know i'm a girl
but okay hi smoothie
[Music]
one day i made a wish to the wind fish
what was the wish it was no it's secret
okay
keep your secrets fine
that was not worth it
oh that sound is stronger scratching the
scratch tree go chunkers go jungkook
show the tree who's the boss
let me pour some water
jonkers is buffing up hell yeah
it does give some insight to the ending
okay
[Music]
i wonder what she what she wished what
her secret wish was
to the wind fish
[Music]
i am so
powerful holy [\h__\h]
hi nice movie
i feel like i could eat
or i could rip out a tree and then eat
it
and you talk to her twice are you
[\h__\h] kidding me
are you [\h__\h] kidding me
you're [\h__\h] kidding me
no
we just gotta go
it's a prank okay
is it really i mean even if it isn't
whatever um oh [\h__\h]
there's no left what do you mean oh i
have to fall down once
huh what is this
it's weird um but okay um left
yeah i'm dying i'm dying
these are my last moments on at least at
least in this world
dying
right
i like the music here though
it is it feels threatening
oh [\h__\h]
gouda
can you tell me what this is
looks very slimy
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
uh to take over this world we made the
wind fish sleep endlessly
if the wind finish doesn't wake up this
island will never disappear makes sense
i mean sometimes i feel like i don't
want to wake up from my dreams and just
want to live in this dream world
we would have been the masters of this
place but honestly
is anyone ever really efficient and
productive in their dreams like i feel
like you can
barely do [\h__\h] in your dreams
so limited and everything happens so
slowly
wake me up wake me up
[Music]
glenn pierce
that is a nice connection there
wake up itself walking dream can't wake
up wake me up
[Music]
from myself
okay
but you have to come here and disrupt
our plans
aha
you can never defeat us
what is this darkness
surrounding me
i need to face it
need to face my nightmares
oh [\h__\h] mommy i'm scared pick me up
uh
what do i need
trial and error
stop bullying me does the magic pile
work someone said magic powder
[\h__\h]
ah
i keep on
[Music]
yes
need to get into the rhythm when he
lands on the ground that's when you
shoot the powder
[Music]
let's go get it
face your nightmares
second form i am i'm guessing you don't
need the powder anymore
what about the stick
[Music]
but someone said reflex but it didn't
really reflect
[Music]
oh with the sword what how did i do that
oh
wait i need some space man buddy
ah
i thought
wouldn't that make sense with the mirror
shield hats
[Music]
easy easy
no
don't want that
i refuse
that's not what i ordered
you're never gonna be
the head of a worldwide fast food chain
if you can't even take [\h__\h] orders
i've seen you before
sliver.iob like
oh [\h__\h] he's mad
like them blah blah blah blah blah sound
man oh oh oh what are we doing what are
we doing what do we do
[\h__\h]
avoid avoid
spin attack or dash
uh against the bats
okay
[Music]
huh
oh it hurts me anyway
it's gonna run it's gonna run just gonna
run [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
how to do damage to him after he throws
the spear
okay
does does the bow work as well i wonder
[Music]
no
oh
well we're in trouble now kfb
we're in trouble we're in big big
trouble when big trouble when big
trouble went big trouble
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
i did a tiny bit of damage
well don't worry we have the cream and
i'm guessing there's maybe at the most
maybe one more one more um
one more face off of this
spin attack when he froze his spear
okay
block it with a spinner tank
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
work the [\h__\h]
how
[Laughter]
i guess
oh i got two hits i mean it was really
not the way i intended it to
do but
i don't have the timing down but we're
not having another skyward sword episode
don't worry
we have enough parts we have enough
hearts
i think i hope
[Music]
oh that hurts that hurts you [\h__\h]
okay i did some damage again it's really
difficult to get close to him man
[Music]
oh that was unnecessary
oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
i'm so slow
[\h__\h] oh we might have a failure um the
first try might be a failure but that's
okay
that works that works that works that
works last face
what is this what are you
[Music]
what are
you is your
thanks chad
thank you
[Music]
that's a [\h__\h] pokemon that's a
[\h__\h] pokemon if i've ever seen one
what oh okay do you want me to shoot you
do you want me to shoot you
[Music]
i'm focused
why do i jump into it
[Music]
easy
easy clap
[\h__\h]
is that is that it
the island is going to disappear
our world is going to get
[Music]
our world
sorry
we did it first
gladly gladly i will i will
wow
[Music]
da
the nightmares entered the dream and
been grand wreaking havoc
then you linkiata came to rescue the
island
they have always trusted you cool rage
i knew that you could turn back the
flight my hair
thank you rinkiada
my work is the horn the wind foosh will
wake so horn
bye
thank you guys
oh wow fancy and looking whale
definitely reminds me of the skyward
sword
um of actually of skyward sword in
general wasn't the last boss a whale
duke
skywalker
[Music]
wait i i guess it was such a traumatic
experience that i um i'm blocking it out
so that's it
that's chloe
[Music]
doesn't quite look like chloe
also i think it's cute how he has those
tiny ass wings
wasn't the skyward sword whale able to
fly without wings so this one is kind of
lame it needs floaties it's like
floaties for a whale
oh i i
long has been my slumber
in my dreams
an egg appeared
[Music]
it was surrounded by an island
with people
and animals
an entire world um
[Laughter]
but
verily
it be the nature of dreams to end
when what what when
i dust
awaken
co-poland will be gone
only the memory of this dreamland will
exist in the waking world
[Music]
someday
though may recall this island
[Music]
that memory makes the dream world real
um
[Music]
let us awaken
together
[Laughter]
play the eighth instruments
play the song of awakening
sorry i'm having a weird moment right
now after nine hours
max the world go round
[Music]
no
ah
with such a beautiful world
[Music]
no
i mean that looks like a volcano
honestly a dangerous place to live if
the only thing that's keeping the
volcano to explode is the egg
that was a wet dream
i mean
you probably just peed himself in his
bed oh that was not a bed
shipwreck
oh sheesh that was not just a normal nap
nap it was
literally
[Music]
he probably lost his consciousness
money
[Music]
maybe it's a whale singing
not mine
but the sound that he heard in the ocean
[Music]
[Applause]
more
[Music]
it's my fault
[Applause]
[Music]
holy [\h__\h] i can't believe i did it in
three streams
that was indeed very short
beautiful
[Music]
but i mean i guess
thankfully it didn't
end up being as long as skyward sword
skyward sword is really long man
yeah since it was a gameboy original
it's pretty sure i suppose yeah games
have become much longer
over the course of the years huh no
thank you
no thank you i'll leave that to you
breath of the wild next no no
no
well
i must say i loved the visuals
um the polished look of
while keeping the original like
perspective and proportions
uh the polished look of it looked really
really cute um was really really well
done
a good example of how you can
improve
um
an old style while still keeping the old
charm of it
and making new things possible
as well
and uh
the story was cute i mean i already knew
you know the dream stuff but
i knew it because i i a long time ago i
already watched a playthrough of it but
i have a
memory like a thief so
i did not remember
most of the other things um
um
yeah
a cute story um
honestly could maybe
use a bit more
[Music]
like i felt like wow that's loud
wow
i felt like i got more story from
skyward sword
but okay that was a longer game
i feel like here the focus was more on
dungeons and dungeon design
and all that
[Music]
the ender
yeah i wouldn't have minded a deeper
like a long not deeper but like more
intricate story like more dialogue
yeah
more dialogue would have been nice
um but besides that i guess i like that
it gives you
um
not much to work with therefore more to
fantasize about and imagine yourself i
know yeah gameboy game yeah no problem
no problem that's okay i see that i
understand that
totally fine i'm just saying um
if i could change something that would
be it maybe
because they are working with such cute
characters yeah
and i liked i liked all the characters
they're all funny
and uh
yeah like the the animal
village was cute
the
trading quest
every character for the training quest
was
um funny entertaining
yeah every character had like a
a nice personality and
an original personality to them and yeah
cute designs cute jokes
and for example also like the the fish
that taught me the the fish song
and they were cute
everything was so cute
yeah it was great for a game boy game
must have been really really
fascinating when playing that on the
game boy i unfortunately did not make
that experience
collected
um
and and finally thanks to this i was
finally able to
experience like like a classic
a classic zelda game but more
uh polish like i didn't have to go
and get a like a like a game boy advance
or something in order to play it i was
able to play it on the switch with
polished looks i really like that
yeah cute very cute game
i enjoyed it
yeah
yeah i also liked the the instruments
and the melodies all the the soundtrack
was amazing
great game
wonderful game
yeah
i like it a lot
i don't really have much to complain
about really the only thing is like well
more dialogue would have been cool
but no that's it's not really an issue
either
um the dungeons were um
they looked so much more difficult when
i watched someone else play it but by
playing it by myself it was actually
challenging here and there had to think
about
where to go a lot like it was the
opposite of linear
i guess
uh
what do you call it like it was like go
here go there go back then go here it
was very confusing it was like a like a
knot of cables you know how under your
desk you have a [\h__\h] ton of cables
and they're like you don't know
which one goes where
that's how the dungeons felt
that's a good thing like i hear people
um i guess when it comes to like pokemon
maps as well like the pokemon worlds
like i i heard that there's quite some
evolution there like older pokemon games
didn't uh were not as linear as they are
now like for example sword and shield
where it just goes from bottom to top
and then in other words it's like yeah
go there or go there go there go there
yeah um i guess
in zelda games like if i compare this to
skyward sword
uh dungeons i mean you can't compare it
you can't really compare it it's like a
completely different format
but this
the dungeons here felt
way more
confusing in not a bad way but like
skyward sword in skyward sword it felt
clearer
on where to go and what to do
than in this dungeon stuff i think i
think so but yeah i mean as i said can't
really compare
2d for the yeah
and the perspective and all that the
perspective changes it a lot too like i
think
if you were to
have these dungeons in 3d it would be a
whole different experience and 3d i mean
like like a skyward sword ex uh
uh perspective like maybe like an fps
expec uh perspective
that would probably be
a whole different
thing to deal with
yeah
best burp had no choice but to succeed
thank you yes i succeeded of course i
did i knew i could do it it might have
been nine hours but honestly
not the first time and and other nine
hour streams that i had before i did not
even call endurance streams that's just
a normal day at kfb and i have a cat
hair in my mouth
somewhere
somewhere in my mouth is a cat hair
never mind
that's okay
ah
yeah no i think it's a really good
choice as a game to pick up
it was short it was fun it was cute
and nostalgic as well
so a good filler game
to play uh in between
yeah if you guys didn't play it yet you
should play it
it's fun to play it on your own now you
unfortunately already know
the
secret is there something that happens
after i save
oh [\h__\h]
oh well i won't be
did i just what did i is it was that bad
oh
oh that's just the opening
wow
okay yeah that makes a lot of sense
there was a storm and then
his ship or some his boat fell apart
and
he fell into a long long slumber but
thankfully he woke up and
i guess
if he didn't wake up
he could have died
right
but he fought he fought to get back to
his consciousness
in his dream i guess that was a fight to
survive
he could have like if he didn't have
enough power
enough
mind power
he might have died
[Music]
which
good to know i'm glad he's alive
yeah
maybe the whales helped as well
and some sharks
uh
i'm trying to
bite off some toes
that was nice that was beautiful
it's just his illusion well it was a
dream yeah it was a illusion i guess i
suppose a dream
hmm it was not real or maybe maybe part
of it was i mean after he was awake he
saw a [\h__\h] whale flying over his head
i i don't know what that means
maybe whales can fly for real in the
world of legend of zelda
[Music]
maybe
it happens maybe it's just normal maybe
it's a normal thing how does this rank
with the other zelda games you played
well that's a bit difficult to say
because i
i
i have so far only really completely
played on my own until the end of this
game and skyward sword however i dabbled
in
other games like wind waker and ocarina
of time
and some others
um
if
now if i had to say which one i like
more skyward sword or this one i
i guess
that's a difficult question actually
a twilight princess yes i also dabbled
in twilight princess
yeah
i did but never finished it but my
favorite still
is wind waker forever and ever until i
die which is never
so forever wind waker and uh yeah one
reason why i was looking up uh
where to buy a wii was because i want to
play
wind waker this year maybe in summer
because now we're gonna play pokemon for
i guess probably like how long will it
take me a month
most at the most one month of pokemon
and
then we might start i don't know yakuza
maybe
uh or something else if something comes
up
ah
i win like that's why i wanted to get
the wii u for wind waker hd uh confusing
reno yeah
uh but i also need i guess a wii in
order to play gamecube games i want a
gamecube but i guess wii is easier to
capture or something i don't know
i don't know
but yes i will get the you guys said i
should get the wii u version so
um
yeah i was planning on playing yakuza
zero i think we did a poll a long time
ago
on my um
on the community board we did a members
only poll i gave you the choice of
yakuza zero links awakening and one more
game what was the other game
what's what's the other game
[Music]
rory oh yeah well there we go we
finished ori we're finishing awakening
so
there's only yakuza left no
not uh
i don't have a problem with that it's
going to be a long play for them
[Music]
yeah ever since i finished the newest
yakuza on my channel which was my first
one
i was like yo i wanna i'm actually
hooked now kinda wanna play more like
this although it's it's a bit tough
because it will always end up being of
an insanely long series on my channel
but yeah it will be fun
um
and she's playing kiwami oh i thought
that was zero
oh
i said i want to play zero right okay
write zelda on a new save file
what what happens if i what do you mean
the pride zelda
you mean the name zelda as my
character's name
[Music]
it's an easter egg
challenge mode
[Music]
the bgm changes
i hate to type in here i hate it
it's so annoying
[Music]
[Applause]
for a
while i love the tropical vibe
i love it
[Music]
um
it's gonna be sad that i don't have the
option anymore to play these
um soundtrack songs
during my um
super chat readings man
that's tough
[Music]
i should take tango lessons or something
like that i want to take tango lessons
dance lessons
[Music]
sorry i was looking at this card yeah i
guess hmm
[Music]
oh
you mean i'm as a loophole
[Music]
hint
no
you want to look up the secret ending
what do you mean secret ending
how do i get a secret ending
[Music]
oh
wait i probably have seen it before
i think the
the youtuber
whose
for i watched probably showed it
read the game with no depths
[Music]
i think i know what you're talking about
but i don't remember
i probably seen it before links
awakening
switch
secret ending
oh is it that oh
[Music]
secret ending cutscene
well i can't show you but it's a bird
flying and another bird flying
and then it's yeah link on the ocean
uh shipwrecked of course sleeping
and then waking up
because he's listening to a voice
and then fades out into white
and then he sits there so it's the same
so far
what's the same so all right
where's the secret
it's at the very after the credits
until the end of the quest is the same
oh and then you hear an 8-bit music that
i think we did not hear
[Music]
the end
and then we see
money
just like a a tiny
blurred version
of marine being like huh she looks hey
she has orange hair like me and we said
that before i think she goes like
that's what she did
she looks at the camera
and then
yes
marlene lives as a seagull she's a
seagull oh
that's i don't know if that's
good for her or
depressing
wouldn't it be nice to have her live as
a human
orange hair bird oh
well i'm not a seagull though oh that
was her wish
oh oh that's sweet then
that was your wish wait i thought it was
something more like
i hope you
live a healthy life or i hope we are
together forever or i hope i hope you
link will become
the hero of all times or i don't know
something more like link related but
okay it's kind of selfish okay
just kidding
hmm
well better than better than completely
disappearing of course
from another timeline in the dream
timeline
no
[Music]
she opened her heart and you forgot
she should have kissed me
you know link is even more a
dumb protagonist than i am
yeah
i'm gonna make it clear to link
[Music]
she didn't even say i love you or i like
she didn't do [\h__\h]
she did not confess her feelings to me
did where did when did she say she loves
me
huh
when did she say that
dance protagonist
link
no no no nothing dan's about she doesn't
love link
well then what the [\h__\h] where by the way
where the hell is zelda in this game is
it called the legend of zelda link's
awakening maybe the title should be
changed the legend of marine link's
awakening
where the [\h__\h] is zelda they forgot one
important piece
in this one puzzle piece
one important puzzle piece that they
missed
[Laughter]
oh she's a legend so she's not she's she
wants another games though even though
she's a legend you can be real and still
be a legend that's why i am real and i
am a legend
i'm real am i not i'm real
well i guess she's she's there but she's
just not in my dream because link
did
what the hell what what what wha why um
i wanna know the is there like an
explanation like what happened before
like is this does this happen after
i don't know wind waker because he's
he had a shipwreck on the ocean
when is this like in the timeline
how did he get here
i linked
ah a link to the pass is a prequel this
is the sequel so
i i'm pretty sure i watched a
playthrough of a link to the past as
well
but i don't remember but it connects it
connects
[Music]
so i suppose in a link to the past
you do have a zelda
so zelda exists but just not in his
dream she is somewhere near she just
really does not play a part at all
in
this game
um
sad
man sand
it does not really connect oh
officially it's a secret but it doesn't
what
well i'm confused i want to know more
about this link
i want to know how he ended up there and
what where it's going afterwards
[Music]
it feels like it yeah
but the links in each zelda game are
different right so i heard that before i
know of that maybe not every link but
almost every link is a different link in
the zelda games
so even the games that came out like
chronologically after this
are
different uh different links anyway
right
the ones that you
mentioned phantom hourglass
those ones are the same
[Music]
some have the same ones i know i know
oh man
now
then the whole link slash zelda world is
a very interesting one
could definitely do a deep dive into
it
[Music]
what
peter
[Music]
otto
oh i don't know anything about the kh
story
[Music]
this game canonically goes after zelda
oracles uh-huh
thank you for renewing your membership
key
ah i don't need any more of your keys
had enough in this game and i'm also a
key adam
take care of your heart i will thank you
i'm just wondering should i read a few
super chats or should i just go to bed
um
i should probably go to bed
or like prepare for bed
um
for fruits sake are you guys good if we
do a movie watch along for members
tomorrow
and then the next member stream i'm
gonna do something special again
something special like either a game or
a cooking stream for members
is that okay tomorrow
i don't wanna talk so much
if possible
[Music]
what movie that is a good question you
guys gave me recommendations before
oh
what what movies are we looking into
a shadow man
i mean girls
[\h__\h] yeah should we watch mean girls
should i watch me girls
oh my god yes please
yes please
i did not i did never watch mingles
before
oh hell yeah that will be fun
[Laughter]
[Music]
where can you watch it is it like on
amazon prime or cell or netflix
let me see
[Music]
you're gonna love it
i think so too
mean girls stream doco
illegal one please obviously
it was on netflix
oh it looks like it is
netflix and prime video as well
oh i think it's also on prime video
[Music]
okay uh you guys know the time it's on
my schedule
yeah we'll finally get to see the jingle
bell rock thing and and there the one
that i said before that one of the
mothers
is like a really dope actress um
from uh parks and rec right
i do like her so i'm excited to see her
in it
you have to work tomorrow no
oh that is unfortunate yeah sorry this
this week we have a members only on a
oh no
um weekday
i mean in theory
i could if it helps you guys i could
probably also do it on sunday at the
same time
i think
[Music]
but that would be
monday for
like sca monday night i don't know if
that's better or
oh
wait let me see
[Music]
the thing is i was kind of planning to
have some time to read super chats after
the whole live era stream
[Music]
but
i mean i'm also going to try to read
them after our or the first ikea was our
sales stream
[Music]
i was gonna
what's gonna i don't know i don't know
what's best i don't really mind i think
or do i i don't know
[Music]
one
question by the way
um
[Music]
uh
never mind forget that doesn't matter
i see some girls are already starting
pokemon tomorrow huh
some girls
have it in their schedule tomorrow
[Music]
but
at a time where i guess it's available
in their time zone but not in mine
because for me it would still be the
27th
but i guess for them is the 28th
[Music]
how do they do it
at midnight locally
um yeah i'll be starting on the 28th
i want to be one of the first ones but i
can't cause my
my time zone is a little bit
[Music]
later than those sea time zones
australia tends to get games early yo
nice i'm jealous
yeah well
i am planning on playing the new pokemon
game on my channel
it's already on my schedule
[Music]
lagging behind ya are you guys gonna
watch it or are you guys uh more like on
the team of not wanting to watch because
you don't wanna spoil yourself or you're
busy playing it yourself you should play
it while watching my stream
are you guys gonna watch it
i'll play and watch i'll be watching
both
i will watch i will watch and watch or
watch and watch and watch oh
thank you
good to know good to know
of course you will here's my core
audience
they gotta be watching
we'll have some cozy streams
um
uh playing uh the new pokemon game and
we'll have uh super chat readings after
those as well i'll try to
not play the game for too long since we
have two days anyway planned
and then in exchange
you know catch up on the super chat
those
okay so i will go make some food now and
rest my throat it's been nine and a half
hours i love you all much this game was
very fun
wonderful
wonderful zelda game very glad i played
it
and
thank you for helping me out a lot may
not if i touch that
[Music]
thank
you thank you
i love you
[Music]
i'm gonna finish the great now hi movie
i have i think two episodes left
[Music]
cute
i'm gonna i'm gonna watch the great
yeah oh the great has been renewed for
third season [\h__\h] yeah
[\h__\h] yeah
i know
[Music]
thank you i'm proud that we cleared
another game i'm the game clearer
i'm not the gamer of yen i'm the game
clearer of ian i take those games and i
throw them on the ground and then i
clean them up with my broom i go like
swoosh swoosh swoosh
and then i put them i sweep them under
the rug no not really like that sounds
as if i was not finishing it but i i do
finish thinking i'm the game finisher i
finished the games
i don't only start them i even finished
them
[Music]
yeah
i'll finish them
cleanly and nicely yes
what about that
i don't need to clean uh clear every
game do what
nev i never promised i never said that i
would finish the loop i never said i
would
also shut up about super mario shut up
about it i'm out of here
whatever
[Music]
i i i finished them privately off stream
i just didn't show you
no but honestly
out of whole live
english
i i
statistically speaking i am pretty sure
i finished the most games out of
everyone and you have to even respect
the fact that a lot of them are long as
jrpg games okay that takes several
several episodes
atelier rizza
for example
a fire emblem yo
uh-huh
respect
i'm gonna go now don't ask questions
hey i at least moved my ps4
over to my bedroom
because that was one annoying thing to
me like having to continue like in order
to continue to tell our eyes that i have
to go to my pc
when i just want to play it in my bed so
now my my ps4 is
in my bedroom because i realize with the
ps5
i don't need my ps4 in my office anymore
i can disconnect it and move it over
okay anyway bye-bye
[Music]
foreign
bye juicy
[Music]
wow
um
[Music]
meow