[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
n
hi Darlings hello Darlings hello
Darlings hello
Darlings shall we introduce ourselves so
people know everyone in the herum of
that is Nissa
my oh sorry sry I mean our holy
Christian Club of course yeah yeah yeah
yeah that
I never agreed to being a
harm I didn't know it just
happens it just
happens sister Val here at your service
H lives holy sister followed
by oh who whom you followed by me okay
when shooty you're you're still you're
still nunning it up I it's I will I will
be the nun until no nut November end
no
November okay okay good to
know I am Tak I don't have a stream open
so now I have free chats open I have all
of y'all's chats open I'm watching
Everybody my first time playing the game
let's go
wo yay first time power watching you
made me buy the game girls hell
yes nice sorry well H hia darling this
is hello live English Advent devilish
Diva the one and only narissa Raven coft
Dio welcome as weet power wash she is
the harm owner
yes roses are red the fire of my heart
is blue also known as The Scarlet Queen
the harbinger of order leader of Justice
I am Elizabeth Rose blood flame lovely
to see you to see you lovely
do you have a short version of your
introduction too or do you always do the
long one no complaints but that one you
always do that one dang I know that's
her intro there's no shortening it well
the ran will be Mighty sad if I didn't
yeah they'll
cry they'll they'll give a big war cry
if not do you think maybe after like 3 4
years or so of doing this you you'll
maybe shorten it cuz you'll get too
tired of it cuz recently I even get
tired or like embarrassed about saying
Kik Kitty ke how could you get tired of
saying kitty it's I
I I feel like an impostor these days oh
my God are you okay
why yeah I'm fine I just I don't know
the kitty key ain't Kitty keying anymore
a but you're a chicken maybe c what does
that have to do with anything you have
to K Kitty key it's in your
blood uh well try I'll continue trying
what if you do like a k oh actually how
do you say it I struggle with that KY k
k it's more like a
k
k that is like a one of those trickster
Rhymes
oh k
k
oh how is it
rhyming not not a rhyme but like those
uh tongue twisters me I
[Music]
struggle that is so we're cleaning now
right it's okay to clean yeah yeah yeah
just chill you have to be like do you
have to save water no no okay screw the
screw the ecosystem here oh yeah no
don't worry about just have fun yeah the
the main purpose of this game is to have
a good time yes okay I hope
bodies I want to clean them up what but
it's hallowen that's different kind of
game Shi yeah I'll have to find that
game then that will be my comfort game
what's the one Mory assistant for
example oh I I like that game I just
don't like being
timed yeah that one's really
stressful oh I see I see like I would
play um that game without having to do
things within a certain time
mhm well Shion it's time to make your
own game how about that about cleaning
corpses visc Clean o we'll have to play
game developer
shiing we could play that game too the
viseral cleanup thing I only play
Santa's map I think it's a oh is that
about cleaning corpses yeah yeah
actually oh my
God ask literally clean them literally
you have to burn them you have to burn
the bodies
is that it do you have to find them the
flow you have to go through room you
have to find them you have to clean up
all the blood you have to clean up all
the bullet holes you have to clean up
all the all the monsters oh everything
so you clean up the crime scene yeah
there's a game of that coming
out how do you know if something's like
completely clean does it have 100% here
press stop and make a sound and go
Bing okay with tab stop pay ATT
um also when you hover over it and when
if you look up in the upper left corner
it says how much of the map is finished
but if you hover over something and it
doesn't have a like a bar like a white
bar that means it's clean
so for whatever reason I'm not getting
any pings I don't know why I got ping I
got like four ping so far I know I hear
you guys getting pings and it's making
me jealous so I'm going to go do
something else I can p you on Discord if
you want no it's
okay don't you already P her in Discord
often enough oh my gosh the jealousy the
drama I rarely get pinked by Nissa these
days I don't ping anybody on Discord so
you're
not don't have to I guess most I sent
you har pinging
you please
respond you got to see him pretty much
first as soon as it was confirmed you
were the first person I sent the video
to if you don't continue sending me
weekly updates I will divorce you once I
get him it's going to be so
over how are you holding up herb while
they
flirt I'm fine I'm just jumping on uh
cleaning uh kot Empire's
head I'm not feeling anything you're so
strong yeah oh she's light my pain
tolerance is very
high I don't feel anything
Bing um so for I guess Fire and Fire
doesn't hurt each other for first time
players uh if you hit the the tab Button
as Kiara mentioned it'll light up all
the dirt so if you're like missing dirt
you haven't gotten a ping but also if
you hit Escape you can go through and
see all the different things that need
to be cleaned if you select one of those
things it'll make it light up on the map
like it'll start kind of like glowing in
and out white so you can actually then
find if you're like oh what's missing I
have like 1% left on this thing but I
don't know where it is that's how you
can find
it nice while you're talking you're
glitching throughout my entire screen
which I find
hilarious that's
so I wonder if anything I'm thinking is
actually like cleaning
then it's okay we just yapping she's a
ghing
ghosted you're not here to clean you're
here to Yap we were hired to Yap exactly
yeah y life oh this is pretty light I
like this did you guys do anything for
Halloween actually by
storm uh what if we did anything yeah
yeah you dress up or anything well I did
the
stream Ghost we dragged you guys to a a
a haunted mansion oh yeah oh that's
right and everything worked perfect
perfectly so I heard it was so nice well
you know there's a first time for
everything and you got to like you know
slowly ease into the VR World shenanigan
yeah no way at
all you know what the the Ian uh fandom
is very used to having to wait uh an
extended time for the streams to start
if it's a VR
stream they know there'll be more
waiting time than like if the official
start starting time is like whatever
8:00 p.m. they know it will not start
until 10:00 p.m. usually oh my you hear
that guys for future future reference we
don't don't don't listen just in case we
start on
time you got to be ready at all
times yeah just make sure you have like
a snack an extra snack or something else
to do just in case 10 cups of coffee so
you can stay up yeah
exactly get that Red Bull mhm I haven't
tried Red Bull before actually what yeah
Sid
monster oh my God I think that's good
because they're really bad for your
health and they don't oh you should
drink them all the time but no no no no
what are you saying Red Bull every now
and
again Shori I'm going to leave can you
invite me back okay
bye everywhere do you are you ready to
be invited I think I can join I'm
joining okay I send one yeah something's
happening I need a young priest and old
PR right
now
Satan Satan no power of the Gods compar
you you know what I feel like right now
really evil need a r you feel evil don't
yeah cuz I'm I'm um power washing the uh
tombstones and it's reminding of that
girl who is like cleaning Graves from
people that one yeah and she's doing it
with like not the right products
yeah like kind of like like it can be
respectful there's people who do it
respectfully but that girl I don't know
she's just selling her product I think
so I feel like her right now no it's
okay these are just Halloween
decorations okay I mean in Japan a day
go down to the gravestones and clean
them up M everything's got to be clean
in
Japan clean and
beautiful I think that's really nice
back to see the the graveyard in Japan I
wanted you wanted to see a graveyard in
Japan yeah cuz they look a lot different
cuz your your headstones are like more
rectangular than ours ah there was like
a temple there I could have seen a monk
and be like what's up monk but in true I
guess they are pretty different yeah
Shori it won't let me back in oh
no she's trying to steal your Harum yeah
she's stealing my Harum successfully
she's claiming it for herself I just I'm
just so risible I
guess here let me let me try again it's
it's not the rer I don't know if maybe
we need to restart it and it's just
glitched out we can resume yeah let me
go back to the thing sorry everyone
restarting no I've been cleaning so much
no it it just resume job yeah it should
save all the progress really how do I
like get to the menu though is my my
question a good question I have no
answer here probably just have to
quit
dang
yeah this feels good let me oh there's a
save button too okay is still like
zooming everywhere for me I'm not even
I'm not even I had to close game that's
crazy okay I I invited you again just to
try it one more time and then after this
let's see if I can like uh go
back I can't monitor you if you're like
Zip zapping everywhere it won't load you
don't understand oh man okay let me let
me see career let me just go to a random
mode and leave you guys trying trying to
join you is crashing the game for me
what is the online mode not so stable in
this game it usually is this has
happened before but a long time
ago sometimes the game's just
crazy I don't know the best way to leave
this thing cuz the menu is actually like
a tablet yeah everyone everyone
completely leave maybe close the game
completely and then reopen it okay all
get the heck out
everyone wonderful
though oh oh I got kicked out nice yeah
yeah I'm following her
rules wait are we completely shutting
the game down yeah you I
did all right yes
ma'am okay I mean I'm not doing what you
say advin I'm just you know going with
the floor why would you do what we say
you know no I'm doing what I want I want
to close
it
okay me too I'm resuming the Halloween
Town okay and then you can just send out
invites again
it's a magical day don't start until you
send out invites as soon as you said
Halloween Town like a certain song came
to mind that I cannot sing out
loud you can say it out loud you can no
I can't I can't sing it out loud oh you
can't s okay yeah you can you guys
again it's night all right I hope it
worked oh
yeah is it not working oh it's it's
connecting slowly it's loading it's
downloading
dirt wait
dirt I'm going to I'm going to go clean
don't start until we're in don't start
until we're in okay sorry okay okay okay
that's the issue is because the dirt is
constantly changing it has a hard time
loading you
in okay now we just wait for herb and
hopefully the game won't glitch
yeah I'm I'm I'm slowly getting in there
she's getting in her F she G to come out
is theb the herb is the
word yeah herb is the welcome back
welcome back okay
wow we're not going to have to
restart yeah I red our game
[Music]
wow so
beautiful wow I have this hanging body
in my place it's like one of those fake
Halloween decorations first off okay
that that's okay I nearly took out my
like notebook and I was like uh-huh
yeah and the in the hanging body like I
got it for like $5 it's supposed to
shake if you have batteries inside it
but it's kind of like it's not realistic
which makes sense it was cheap yeah you
bu because of Halloween or just because
of for your own
Aesthetics
yes well I think it was on sale cuz it
was after Halloween by
then I was going to throw it away and I
left it on the floor and my pile of
throw away or like a maybe donate but
then my cat managed to go inside it and
and then it was so cute it's like oh
they're hiding in the little body bag
and the just like a butterfly so I'm
hoping that they do it again so I have a
reason to keep it around
a well you got to keep it if if it
became the cat toy yeah I know I want
them to sleep in there
[Music]
more you so cute and unhinged
shy it's not even unhinged I just think
it's funny it's a little unhinged
really just a little and your defition
of unhinged is weird well you know we
some people have their Christmas
decorations out for another five months
she Halloween decorations
out that's that's fine my parents
Christmas lights before they kept it for
a year cuz they didn't want to take it
down that's
valid coron style are your parents coron
no she has her Christmas things up all
the time at least on her
stream oh and plays Christmas music all
the time it's spring the joy of giving
yeah
yes my pumpkin my
pumpkin
hello wait I was going to say Red Bull
did you know it's from Austria really oh
like the headquarters are also in
Austria it's like one of the few famous
things we have I guess it seems so
American maybe you should do like a tour
at the factory there yeah yeah you can
and like they sponsor a lot of like
Austrian um like sports people and all
that like I don't know why they don't
sponsor me though just say that you want
to like get drunk off your
thing get drunk off the Red Bull you
mean yeah you want to drink it up guzzle
it up you know you have aab
bom oh the thing is normally I try to
avoid Red Bull it's like my emergency
solution if I'm really tired cuz I don't
drink
coffee only an emergencies Red Bull
tomorrow be an emergency I just feel the
pain of tiredness you already have wings
you don't need it me oh thank you oh no
I me
about oh I'm wingless yeah you can't
F oh yeah it's Red Bull for light flu
girl in
[Music]
yeah who the heck is not listening to
her
who oh the messages T so that's that
that's the person who has paid you to do
this so you can read the backstory in
which they'll tell you the lore of why
it got dirty like this or just random
lore of the game I bet the lore was that
she was too lazy to
clean probably
huh do you see on the
pumpkin I see you on there oh yeah okay
I you see baby your wings I'm toing do
you guys watch those hoarder channels
and then they clean up the hoarder stuff
I kind of like those I do too it brings
me
joy yeah are you a hoarder is anybody a
hoarder no uh I can't be the queen
mother doesn't like
it I
cannot I also try to control myself
I've I've stressed things in the past a
little bit but not like sickly yeah yeah
yeah oh they just like collecting a
bunch
yeah like things from Japan don't
usually and now I'm hoarding like fan
letters like after four years there's so
so many I don't want to like get rid of
them so they'll just get more and more
and more buy a buy a storage unit then
buy a a storage unit for just or you
know it might not be worth a storage
unit yet but we can work on that
right yeah more more letters more
letters I used get different size ones
usually when it comes to storage units
baby storage units yeah you can you can
get like one that's like a
locker okay in great Exodia you
[Music]
can I heard like homework from like
previous years thinking maybe I'm going
to need this for my next class the next
semester and then once everything was
done I like see you I'm out I think
that's kind of smart keeping materials
from previous years
that's I'd keep them because I'd sketch
in them and I'd be like that's a cute
picture I drew so then I keep
it yeah me
too I remember at the ending M people
would clean out their lockers mine was
pretty clean everyone would just have
tons of homework on in theirs and they
had to get like a giant trash
can and there'd be like a maybe a
rotting sandwich for some of their
lo I
think we should power wash a school it
seems there's potential there
potential more
money from a power business
okay pumpkin are you finished
finally looks pretty
good little bit here so relaxing and
maybe a little dizzying actually hit the
C
button oh I see yeah that feels weird
you can hit it and unhit it so it'll
lock um your screen a bit so that way
you can instead of you know having your
head move with the power washer it's
just
Frozen Yeah it helps with the motion
sickness
yeah n has so much experience with this
game I love this
game wow it's one of my
favorites you're also one of my favorit
well well
Shi I
see you too Queen hey hey hey hey ma'am
huh what's up you ever heard of a poonal
bubble personal bubble I'm on top of the
W for
me uh where am I in your
screen
uh yes spicy sure something
happening oh my nut's fun your nette
sucks maybe you're in sux you're the one
who's like glitching around you're on
top of the well I was I'm I'm off now oh
now I'm on top of the well I didn't even
know you clim yeah yeah you are
yeah what's your favorite Noz girls are
you lighting my gas uh which one's good
I like to the yellow one the yellow or
the red
[Music]
one what was the question what's your
favorite nozzle am I still glitching on
your screen herb
a I think she hallucinating I think this
map is just haunted probably I see Shi
everywhere that how should be just
Shori I mean I'm on it to you so it
makes
sense you're like a
stalker are you cheating on me herb I
thought you were monitoring
me excuse me dating her
herb what's going on there
I don't know I
think it didn't say monitor just
narissa yeah but I'm your favorite what
if for monitoring your back I mean I
monitor you probably the most but that's
besides the
point you need like extra watching this
way okay I guess I can share you a
shory you know what they say happy wife
happy life what you mean allow me to sh
what what
the myob me what to do the most awkward
attempt I've
from all of my flirtation attempts are
awkward what are you talking
about well I didn't want to say that but
okay did you see my my stream title for
this by I did I
did yeah I saw people tweeting about it
I just like it was a funny title
fire
cool yeah what is it again don't worry
about it my my title yeah yes worry
about it oh I I'll let your chat tell
you I I I'll let them
surprise copy paste it's my
Halloween happy
Halloween man I love
Halloween me too I'm a Christmas girl
it's all right I like Christmas too I
like Dr yes yeah you never sent me that
picture of you in your costume oh I
ended up feeling sick so I ended up not
changing and dressing up after all it
was really depressing for me I know
I I wanted to die so B then dress up
like today tomorrow you can still dress
up yeah you can always dress up but now
I'm looking for like I want to find a
cute dress to wear for
Christmas cuz I don't have
one you don't have one I'm sure you have
one
naked no you can't go naked it's
Christmas yeah it'll be like a Christmas
present
no like Merry Christmas put put a ribbon
around your body that's like some fancy
La yeah you guys are
sick wait what you're sick
no well yeah I am sick actually
yeah what about
[Laughter]
it it's getting sick season again
everybody be careful I'm healing though
thankfully thank goodness I don't want
to travel sick
yeah I don't want you to travel sick
either
yeah I think I need a lot up there well
luckily there's tons around the map
where's all the water coming from uh
your heart does this not have Collision
I'm sorry what oh I guess only you guys
could pass
through I I cannot seem to climb the
ladder I will I will go save just in
case skill issue yeah skill issue gu so
maybe I was the ghost all
along I like like that that plat
TST
yeah I would like to go back to the old
house is that a a musical song or no I
thought it was another house in this
game
no it's the
Smiths ah that band that only I
like The Smiths don't they have some
like famous songs I'm sure I like one
song at least yeah how soon is now from
Charmed is the Smith song ah there you
go there you go narissa proving yourself
wrong
already Charmed let's freaking
go it's it's funny cuz I heard it first
from Charmed and I was like this is the
best song I've ever heard and I never
knew that that wasn't like the official
version and then I found it later by
tattoo that one that one band what they
also cover covered it yeah and I was
like oh my God this is amazing it's the
song from Charmed and then I found when
I got really into this smiss I found
that and I was like are you kidding
me this is where that song is
from need to research more yeah oh yes I
only know my my Vocaloid songs My we
stuff
you're my little
weeb oh I thank you you're my little
pony you'll always be in my
heart
wow okay there
Tarzan my little you're my little
chicken cheek nandos that's what you are
you're my little cheeky Nando cheeky
Nando what what you say to me chicken
Nando
me have you never heard of nandos before
no that like a chicken
nuggets it's a it's a restaurant where
they they mostly spicy chicken with
Perry Perry the best it's very yummy
sounds
yummy not as good as
KF uh no but I'm aware of it oh I'll
treat you one day okay okay interesting
I got to study my rivals in the business
I'm in yeah true I'm coming
over yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah I will steal herb from narissa
because I am geographically closer to
her anyway wow this is some NTR
happening on me who said she owns me
what the FR yeah I I don't I don't own
herb own woman yeah she just monitors me
don't you
know what if if we collect her like a
like a Pokemon we just throw a ball at
herb see who gets her first will that
work herb I don't think can you get my
ball if I ask nicely please oh anything
for you sweetheart I'll jump into the
ball for you what the [\h__\h] let me just
squeeze on
in one foot then the other let's go I'm
going to write my twit longer right
now o your Google Document let's go
because I experience
with oh my good is your account not um
verified don't you can't you write write
long tweets on your own about TW longer
but I feel like the twit longer is more
dramatic oh yeah de is and then like a
white background reading like my story
and then a link to twit longer is like
so much better than like you know
opening up a tweet and seeing that it's
like a novel and then you're like I
didn't sign up for this honestly
whenever I see those I just don't click
I'm just too tired same I can't on time
a good in between is um posting a
picture of your
notes bad handwriting no no no no
written on your iPhone or whatever like
your notes
app that's how you do it the evidence
where's the
screenshots where's the
Discord they just Got to Believe
it or or in the
replies proof in
replies yeah proof in the
pudding look it's well isn't done well
well well well well well well well well
this well is not complete oh can I climb
these stairs oh thank God I
couldn't the game is Just i ph through
it
me too
actually what hey didn't you climbed up
on the roof no oh for the well one oh no
no I I faed through the the the steps
over here I faced through the ladder but
I can climb up these stairs near the
house like I said I'm just a
ghost ghost with the most easy mode
everything is easy mode for sh can you
rotate the no yeah use your um the R
button
oo it's true Shri is a force to be
reckoned with yeah she's scary she
scares me man I SC we have two children
together and I'm still terrified of her
I don't even remember how the heck that
happened I just woke up with
it CH like are you sure oh she and
narissa I bought Urban Nissa I was going
to be worried she's probably going to
have children with her soon yeah we're
just waiting done and it was cute I mean
we actually did have a child together
Kar remember you killed you killed them
no no no no no no that's a different
dimension that we're talking about one
that's a whole different universe and
two even then it wasn't real it was
just's child are you going to be mad mad
at me in like Ian REO season 2 as well
about that still or you going to forget
about it we already it's already water
under the bridge right I think so too
well it depends would would the Nissa of
that that realm
remember
yeah hope remember anything that
happened oh I have a bad memory
so well got to rewatch before before we
get back into that that Universe yeah so
dis iated
summary yeah there's still a lot of time
we'll we'll be forgetting even more cuz
it's going to be in spring right oh
that's too far for me I want to Happ now
I remember I had so much I remember I
got left with a child H who left you
with a
child it was it was that one girl and
then he stepped up one girl oh I will
have to pay forge
tuition yeah yeah yeah now I remember
it's okay cuz I know thatl I gave you
money remember that's
true I can't wait for the college
tuition
Arc oh
frig wait you had a shiori of inreco had
a child yeah yeah technically if you
could call it
that oh I don't remember what name I
gave it though to be honest
I but that's our baby now because I I
wasn't the father chaos I remember yeah
K hell yeah I want the K to be in
Reverse so it's like someone who who
didn't know how to spelled
it why are you not mentioning who the
the other girl was maybe maybe she won't
remember we'll have to see m h it wasn't
me
right I I I don't know we'll have to see
Kar I don't think it was remember a fun
night in town with me W no I don't think
I was involved with that many people
anyway my wives are going
crazy
spicy I want to live in this house was
uh in Reco sh
wife yeah wasn't it she we combined seed
and the Egg yeah she loves you I'm I
didn't want to put pressure on her you
know even though I am totally
betrayed it's okay because now you have
a rich a rich Gambler wife
husband gambles away to college tuition
no I only get rich don't
worry it's my it's my it's my lore story
now oh do you have a
strategy
yeah is it a blackjack
no it's I make I make money through
honest means in
andreco
througho Elizabeth was poor because she
was night you say
gambling honest I don't gamble I gamble
for fun I make my money through honest
means and then I gamble for
fun
mhm I don't know if I can trust the
gambl though what are the honest means
then a potato salad probing that one
Quest
yeah ah yeah potato salad let's go I'd
love some potato salad I know right do
you prefer potato salad like uh in the
version that is like mayoni or do you
prefer the one that is like
oily vinegary prob
Mayon I don't know what oily potato
salad is let me through
shiori huh I don't even know where where
you are behind
you you're over there you can come
you're different on my screen what the
heck I'm literally right behind you
cleaning the
door oh I'm not near the door I'm on a
tower remember I'm a ghost
wo get wet get wet what's
happening water plant if you see me just
assume I'm I'm not actually there I've
moved on it wouldn't let me move past
you it was crazy oh I'm sorry about that
I can't help my ghosty
butt
phenomenon
phenomenon Ohan the tower is
difficult yeah but you're doing great
I'm proud of you I'm pretty sure you can
buy a ladder can't you there's already
ladders on around the map you just need
to find them and then place them up a oh
you actually have to move them I see
is there ladders that go that
high uh
yes there's if you come to the back of
the building there's a really really big
like it's not a ladder but it's like
um it's a w Wait I I can't yeah it's
like scaffolding and you can move it I
only know this word thanks to Minecraft
same I'm already up here so I'm going to
just try to brute force it while I'm
here you know I can't break leg anyway
scaffolding yeah oh scold oh there's
ladders too actually there's
ladders
oh what's your Minecraft experience
herb my Minecraft experience
uh uh I enjoy it after a while I get
motion sick but I enjoy it are you
motion sick
playing third
person yeah I I did that at smidge when
we when did in Reco but it was I mean
you were with me actually K when we when
I when we were uh going through one of
the dungeons we had to jump around a lot
they got to a point where I was just
like after this man you're debuffed you
have to live with this debuff but that
shows even more skill
I mean I didn't get thank you for
telling us oh yeah you don't you were
just you just messing with
us joke I'm still very powerful so it
doesn't really it doesn't really not
really much of a you know I'll just
truck on through it I'll walk it off you
know yeah walk it off yeah so what
you're saying is uh you want to go to a
fair together and go on one of the
really really spinny rides and spin
really really fast I can do it yeah you
can do it no you could just do them back
to back to back to back leave her alone
no don't let her suffer through it no
she's it yeah are you call liar
go yeah we go we're going on the teacups
or the spinning Dragon you can just do
the Minion ride with me I promise it's
it's
lighter the Minion ride is
great A I do like minions I think
they're cute yay nice got want like
B bana
yeah in the in the realm of the 40
shades of green green uh which is very
similar to Ireland there was there's a a
game called dizzy dragons where you just
spin yeah I I know
that cute I love the Dizzy
dragons I don't know if I want my
dragons to be
dizzy dizy dragons where I played the
game in my youth
yeah
Y and you didn't
die no she still alive as you can see
I'm a ghost now just like sh
ghost ghost all haunting you yeah please
don't haunt me I'm scared of the
dark what a Twist huh it's like am I the
Scrooge am I Scrooge make duck and this
is the you know the what is that movie
called
uh the you mean the Christmas talking
yeah I love the way you associate uh the
Christmas carol first with Scrooge Meck
there's a load of versions oh it's the
most popular one technically yeah it's
very popular for like
kids there's no Barbie Barbie with the
Scrooge you know is that not no
unfortunately she has so many movies I'm
surprised I know no they didn't want to
make her a
[\h__\h] that's probably true actually
yeah has to be nice yeah I liked her in
the
Nutcracker yeah I don't remember the
Nutcracker One I Love The Nutcracker
ballet man I used to play with Barbies
and I just made them all gay for each
other I
see it was usually the Disney Barbie
dolls too like I ship them with the most
random ships like I I paired someone
with Ursula I don't know who though oh
wow yeah it's like enemies to lovers
let's
go that's
Vibe how we going to get up to the top
of that uh Tower you got
[Music]
legs wings would help
more I can't activate them in this game
can't you see me on the top of the tower
that you're talking about well yeah now
I see you going up there I've been up
here I tried jumping
but that's a skill issue yeah oh okay
now I'm on there there you go you got
skills
[Music]
yay oops
you good yeah I'm fine don't worry what
happened nothing I'm being a
professional okay yeah don't worry about
it okay she's so professional yeah I'm
leader Justice I am professional yeah
very
professional you're officially the the
leader yeah she's been the leader didn't
realize now she's the henchman
now yeah sh's the leader of
AD yeah I'm I'm just the
babysitter hey I don't need to be
babysat same that's true well
technically you have two babysitters
Nissa what
oh you're shy and then you have me
that's true why do I have so many
babysitters well you want to be looked
after though you want to be like a a
baby yeah you're a baby right Gaga
Google gaga take care of me Google gaga
w w
the baby ey Envision but reminds me of
an ASMR I
watched oh is it the the hatan yeah I
tuned in I didn't know what it was about
I was just like ah nice Whispers And
then she translated it for me and I was
like oh
no that moment when the ASMR artist like
knows how to speak English too and
notices you in chat and translates and
I'm like a
no she's like lie you want milk my milk
and I'm
like did you say yes what was your
answer we need a
know uh no comment
oh I I always treat myself to like a
pint of milk when I'm not recording or
singing and stuff I love milk oh wow
that's my treat I hate milk on its
own on its own I like
it that's cuz you're built
different I guess so I just like ice
cream and
cheese yumy but when I was out it with
Justice in the Far East I I like when
we'd be at a cafe I'd buy milk damn Dr
just
milk yeah just milk wow
huh it's cuz I saw it and I was like oh
my God I can get this milk wow man I
always just got water when we went to
the to the east
mhm I remember like do you guys want the
full-on drinks the drink bar I'm like
I'll just get water I liked getting the
drink bar in Japan because they always
had matcha lat oh yeah it's good it's
good and I was like what do you mean I
can just have Macha latte whenever I
want I missed the drink bar so I wish
they were more Comon here along with
like the
iPads the iPads for service I love not
having to talk to people
yeah that's why I love going to family
restaurants in Japan and I could be I
could be weirder because they can't
understand me they'll be like a oh silly
guy G
no I love I love that I just love I love
not talking to
people not
either oh my God that was so funny I saw
the clip of you and uh Rica
and you forgot she speaks English oh my
God you're commenting on her her
her view yeah
yeah it's like I don't know English nor
Japanese let's
go oh my gosh how do you pick up this
scaffolding things if you get close to
it you should be able to it should pop
up f uh you can't move it on the
roof I just want to like go around the
building but it doesn't show up with f
yeah I don't know it wasn't showing up
for me either and I'm concerned about it
because we kind of need
that we can fly we're at
96% we're actually getting through it
pretty fast 96 my only says 90 what do
you mean oh
sorry I'm I'm adding another 6%
weird but say 90 for me too do you want
to host the next map maybe maybe it'll
be better
maybe maybe it won't be
better no I'm sure it will be what if
it's
wora it's it's going to be your birth
week after all it has to be better your
true it is my birth
week yeah the day yay birth week I can't
wait to have everyone at my
[Music]
birthday everyone except
shiori thank you wait hey we're
technically celebrating early Zen I'm
celebrating the 21 which day 21st oh oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah why do excited no
cuz I'm gone on that day
oh on your oh H why is my screen like
having an earthquake now oh it stopped I
guess it
did oh it's because you're shooting me
oh I
see I was like why is there an
earthquake here I don't know what you're
talking
about you just cuz you you know you've
been cleaning so much you got a bit on
your V on my on my we my wear exactly
my my mask your head piece I don't
know I remember when I was uh at the
starting screen I just aim for your
crotch right there it's like I'm going
to stay here and aim at it until she
comes back how dare you I was cleaning
it I'm making sure you're all well
cleaned thank you I appreciate it you
know you're you're welcome I know isn't
she so
considerate that is very consider I
don't want to start the stream being
like uh oh stinky and stuff you know
yeah I'm washing you washing Away The
Sins oh nice thank you sister you guys
should play cookie on me to see how
considerate you really are apparently
there's a new one out oh
yeah there's a fourth one I saw it in
the game perms updates it said cookie
yomi 4 I was like
Hey free go go you have so much to catch
up they're I think they're in English
too yeah they're pretty pretty short but
they're fun they're really good oneoff
games and there's an online one oh an
online like a no wait I I think it's
online it's a like multiplayer but you
have to be off collabing I think I think
not sure maybe you have to be
considerate to each other in real life
no no it's like a battle of to see who
is most considerate I see you're not
considerate to each other no no no that
would be crazy yeah screw you guys I
love you
it's like I'm getting mixed messages
y want to get up on the
hat you jump on the one of the boards
the Bild boards yeah jump on this rock
the I'm up
yay maybe
not try to
billboard oh that works maybe bro what's
going on
we're cleaning cooked we're so
cooked what does that mean
95% uh look like you're
[\h__\h]
oh but like you know without the curs
thing
oh we're almost
done so at this point if you can't find
what to clean well you can uh click Tab
and then it'll show you what's not done
yet and you can go go clean
it I think there's one side of the tower
that just really hard to reach if we
can't move the
scaffolding yeah it is that's a skill
issue but things also just are like not
pinging like it said the well was dirty
so I came and cleaned it but it still
says it's
dirty oh
[Music]
I blame Shi this is all her
fault yeah it was me the whole time I
was the one who did it she she glitched
it I would have gone away with it too if
it wasn't for
my the the cooky kids so
cookie I'm at
99% I'm at
96 me too getting there why are you
ahead of
us she's just that good it's cuz I'm
locked
in it's cuz hers since she's running the
game I think there's no lag on her side
technically so that's why like I don't
know I saw you
zipping well you you can host the next
one so you can get like uh your thingi
can you try going to the scaffolding and
see if you can move it does it say F
when when you get you mean this tiny
ladder or the big one no the the
biging oh I I passed right through it
let me
try am I supposed to press F yeah it
should it should pop up a thing that
says like press F to move or whatever no
I see nothing for this one damn that's
rough H um you can get an extender if
you hit e you can change the thing for
your power
wash and at the very least you can get
an extender you can reach
higher I'm just not oh I know where to
hit I climbed there before I can do it
again oh the Apothecary
Hut yay seems pretty
clean what else is there find out how to
get
there
stairs I'm so sad if some body in here
oh my
God what about our bodies are we not
good enough no no they have to be
dead she I can be dead and then revive
if you want if somebody kills me dang
are you okay there's no there's no dying
in this
game no I mean you know IRL like Phoenix
you know oh
okay I could help you out with that
tired of dying though you
know uh well I i' prefer to stay alive
because when I revive I I just I forget
who I am for a little while it comes
back to me but it's just not really
convenient yeah yeah you know just Fenix
thingss it's just how it is sometimes no
issue I can't reach
impossible oh somebody missed a spot
nice nice nice got
that you guys want to know something
random what what I had an audible
subscription for
like over a year probably two years or
so oh [\h__\h] I and I opened the app for
the first time in a long time today and
I saw I have like a lot of credits so I
bought all of the Game of Thrones book
readings oh hell yeah and all the Lord
of the Rings including the sil marilan
and stuff like that oh yeah nice which
you reading that
on no not Kindle it's audible oh audible
right yeah yeah # Monsters uh now I have
like
probably o over 300 hours of stuff to
listen to
that's
good yeah but I don't even like like
listening to somebody reading to me that
much but I got I'm going to force myself
cuz I don't like uh reading either so
it's got to be one of them reading or
being red too say you go pick one yeah
I'm going to be picking being red too I
guess I mean some of some uh what is it
some uh audio books have like
celebrities reading them and stuff so
like stepen fry you know this a
celebrity I didn't know that St fry he
he's a National Treasure I like Media
stuff though isn't he the dude from like
Sherlock Holmes based on what he
reads was
he well well whenever I see audible it's
like this is Red by stepen fry oh famous
in the UK oh pretty sure he's like red
like a bunch of stuff on Audible
probably okay Shi it's up to
you your game is loaded the most you
need to hit escape and clean everything
that's at not at
100% I'm trying you escape I'm just it's
the house dmer
roof it's still not getting
there how's your game though are you at
99% what what if it just do that 1% to
haunt us
forever um you have to finish
it is this like your OCD stuff no you
have to finish
it I'm not being cute my favorite so St
fry is also on a a uh like a funny talk
show and U one of my favorite jokes of
his is like he goes uh what is it I'm
little teapot short and stout here is my
handle he puts his arm out and he puts
his other arm out he went oh no I'm a
sugar ball
that's my favorite Sugar Bowl yeah a
yeah it's hilarious you know it's better
once you know you physically look at
someone doing a yeah of course of course
of course it's
hilarious well there's another one to do
with happiness but like I don't know
about saying no
one why is it embarrassing no I mean
it's it's mostly an accent joke do it oh
just about a lady who's like I wish for
happiness
[Music]
oh I
see
happiness it's nice happiness happiness
mhm
happy see I get it now got to say it
slowly oh oh you didn't say it sh don't
do it in your brain bra say it out loud
no we don't say I'm good I've said it
once oh man you know jokes aren't as
funny if you say them all times but then
who nobody hears
them that's
fine I need to hear I need to
witness oh another one of my favorite
jokes not by Stephen frer it's uh what
is it um a German Shepherd jumped over
my fence and pooped in my garden and he
had a dog
what what you need a
dog because what that was that the last
sentence a German Shepherd jumped over
my fence and pooped in my garden and he
a
dog and ah ah ah okay okay okay okay
took me a moment no I mean that was very
good you picked up very quickly
especially since I'm always like really
like uh um wowed by people who's not
that their first language is in English
and they understand a joke so fast
especially one like that one where it's
to do with like the wording and things
you're so
nice just just stay in the
treef I'm going to jump I'm going to
jump sure he put us out of our
misery what's how do you check like the
last one I need you need hit the escape
button and then you will have a clean
the Halloween house you can go through
the list and then scroll through all of
them and it'll say what are not at 100
yet Apothecary lanterns then and the
Pumpkin shed chimney and red Tower
walls like one of these lanterns
Apothecary
Lantern if if you click it it'll make it
light up so you can see exactly you want
to start cheating then that's not
cheating
what I'll do the this one then let me up
does it show for you guys or this one no
it'll it'll only show on your side but
I see are you at 99% as well
yeah same these
lanterns
parkour uh
parkour parkour
parkour another
Lantern okay so that's done oh you've
got it there's an around the other side
herb house base
well I'mma die thank you forever oh no
fall damage no fall damage I'm die thank
[Music]
you I'm a die thank you oh I can get
this one yay nice Halloween sign where
be
that maybe in the somewhere in the
beginning in the front it's the graves
actually yeah those are Halloween signs
signs
apparently no
oh this one's
going what map do you want to do next by
the way a good question there's a
Christmas one for free well I don't know
what you
downloaded we can let do whatever ship
and the Halloween one cruise ship h no
please let's show me the last one what a
piece of
ship herb
language no oh my sdiy are my treasures
I would never how could
you yeah herb what the [\h__\h] oh my
gosh right a tweet longer last
longer house jeez jeez it's okay you're
Louise so if you wanted to swear you can
get away
with Lou Stormer house
Stormer I think more fun coming up with
other words yeah yep I'm not so
creative ah I see one spot but it's at
the tower like kind of
unreachable you yeah use the extender if
you can maybe that could
help oh yeah you can ex if you if you
hit e the extension you can put on a
super long
one oh
long oh okay
a
[Music]
[Laughter]
window the roof something at the
roof there's this game I want a perms
for it's like uh you clean the house but
it's haunted and that's pretty much it I
see like it seems kind of relaxing I
want to play it see some
ghosties does it have to 100% in order
to like get out of the MCH it's re's
preference no it's not my preference you
do not win the game it is not optional
you have to complete it 100% you can win
the game sound torture the game has an
end oh it does just like uh you did it
you cleaned everything
yeah oh do you know why I'm on the
roof no cuz the drinks are on the house
oh I'm sending you to jail I'm sending
you to jail hey is this bad humor she is
she's becoming a
dad no I'm an uncle
congratulations yeah's Dad
Uncle come on shiori it's all up to
you I'm I'm working on
it working I
believe where is the Lo happing you hit
the escape button and you can look
through herb but ours aren't updating
for some reason very well uh Apothecary
lanterns but I think Shori already clean
I can send you guys to do things at
least you already the lantern yeah maybe
for me it's not done I see the dirty
still I can't see the dirt yeah yeah
this is still
dirty what's wrong with it I don't know
it's getting better we're getting there
it has to be this like this one
shingle mhm I'm spamming my
[Music]
tab maybe we just need a wait for it to
catch up I am losing it she's it's never
going to catch
up we got to wait a year we're so
cooked oh oh let me just skip this one
for now does it oh wait but you have to
do like 100% for each thing right yeah
everything has to be clear it's not
going to round up that's so weird cuz
sometimes it rounds up the
dirt yeah it it it it does if you get to
like a certain point even if there's
still like a little bit left it'll 100%
clear it come on it's 99% where are you
dirt so strict I
know no it's just it's being bad right
now because everything's glitching out
but usually it's not like
this okay now the window
what window though I need the house
Dormer window along with the eaves
whatever that
is
MHM I think I found the
eaves showing
me it looks clean to me now what's wrong
with it button U maybe it's the I'm I'm
spinning
tab everything looks clean
there's some tiny dirt on the
Windows Eve where are
you Eve what is an eve uh the area
between the roof and the house
wall so basically any Gap I assume it's
not a gap it's like a wood
framing yeah underneath
but where's the dirty Eve that's the
question it should light it up for
you I'm I'm spamming I'm trying to find
it as a thing oh if you click on it
it'll just make it light up for you so
you'll be able to see what specific Eve
it is oh no I i' I've clicked on it I
just don't know where it is where I I
see it it's here but I cleaned
it oh maybe it's Eve that's a all right
Eve's done now I need Rand window
yippe yippe yippe window which oh this
one a house small
trim how small trim where are
[Laughter]
you this is really cursed it's so
Halloweeny in every sense of the of the
way yes
okay sign a
trim I got the Apothecary uh house
entrance
Eve house entrance I can't find a window
oh wait what am I looking for
window to the
[Music]
wall chat do you see the small trim
wherever that
is oh I'm spamming our suffering
go go go the front door you
think that looks like a big trim oh hey
there's ladder icons for some reason
now oh
God not that oh wait can I climb the
ladder my God
invisible uh around the door by the
stairs oh my
God Rea needs it to be perfect I don't
need it to be perfect that's how the
game works
works but how often am I going to play
this no it's just how the game works I'm
not making up rules that's just how it
works no no okay okay okay there there
there
there bre breathe how about we all leave
and leave shiori and then see if
anything
fixes all right because I feel like the
map is clean we've all I still find tiny
tiny tiny things saying is some of the
things that we're cleaning are things
that another person has already fully
cleaned but it just hasn't pinged on
your
map mhm good so so go ahead and manually
leave then and maybe you can come back
safely all right okay I look for a
gargoyle leave C game goodbye
goodbye So Long Farewell har say I'll
see you again goodbye night oh hey I can
finally climb the stairs now that you're
gone wow just no offense no offense can
you also pick it up now c c can we
rejoin now did everyone yeah go ahead
okay I able to do you need another
invite no it might be broken you just
have to finish it you you have to finish
the shy oh man that's a lot of you're
putting a lot of stress on here for a
power wash
game good good luck finish it I didn't
expect this on my my last day guys
where's the
gargoyle I thought we were G to do
another map is it we we're going to do
another map but you need to finish this
map
why it's power off
simulator quick chat where's gargoyle
what looks like a guard to your go is it
the cats at the entrance they at
the I don't know okay let me get
anything on the roof first before I go
to theim guard world yeah red Tower wall
all of this looks like a giant red Tower
wall to
me you can do it I
believe see that's me what do you want
me to do you want me to dance for you
I'm dancing to rest time dance I can't
see what else you want me to do huh I
want you to dance for me dance I'm Dan
what am I my anxiety is school now too
yeah you've got to clean everything
thing cat on if what if I just say like
o 100% let me Photoshop it really
quick here I only have like a few things
I just need to freaking get the gargoyle
these things I guess you must you must
clean it all for Justus you got to clean
it all for justice I don't believe in
Justice what is this a good World clean
it all for our
Rebellion I don't know about that that's
telling me what to
do ignite our beating hearts with the
the power wash dance dance
dance dance dance dance come on cat Okay
gargo clean pathway post decoration what
the heck do oh I
seea has invited you to
play I guess oh I've been
invited yay wait is this the same map
what is this just leave just leave I can
leave she's finally you guys
oh we're free finally wow 100% we did it
we did it yeah now we're in Santa's
Workshop everything's all
green what is it orange this place is
very orange oh that's Christmas Eve Eve
a night we look forward to for one
special reason this is French Bob by the
way it's the last night that our
inventor Ivor Nidia pitches the last
year's star toy to Santa or next year's
star toy it's the lore what why is
everything covered in dirt we're going
to find out from the L what the freak
happened however this year e carry them
through to Santa's office in a big box
to stop anyone from
peeking maybe they filmed a spicy movie
in
here they exploded the nightm Before
Christmas we knew that had to be really
good the movie man no I'm I'm reading
I'm reading the lore oh the
L you see how you see what they do to me
chat they don't care about the
lore yeah I don't know about if I care
much about the power wash lore I know
I'm just clean find out got like
oh don't you want to know wait so what's
the tldr I don't know yet every time we
clear a certain percent it'll give us
more of the
story was going to show they were going
to show Santa a new a new star design
and they were bringing in a box and
everyone was really excited and then dot
dot dot now we're waiting for the rest
yeah
probably he's probably like a goo star
I think they're releasing a Dracula
movie for Christmas I want to watch it
draa for
Christmas I know I was Bamboozled I am
excited maybe they wanted to release it
for Halloween but it got delayed maybe
was probably too competitive have you
seen the van housing movie I I don't
know I might have but I forgot I haven't
I want to rewatch that at some point oh
yeah you haven't haven't yeah there's a
fair few vampire movies and stuff you
haven't seen yeah I watch Dracula do
musical Das musical right I love how you
you you you make the Das sound so
important
do ah yes German
articles
yes this looks like Jinx was in here a
little bit
is anyone watching like neon graffiti
yes but I didn't watch the most recent
like new ones the first three I watched
from the second season mhm I haven't
seen any of
them what about season one I haven't
seen any of them oh not even season one
no I'm waiting till it's like done done
and then I'm going to watch it oh oh
that was what I was thinking for o noo I
very recently started watching in Arcane
and it's so good it makes me want to
play
league you should play league it's fun
no my chat tells me I shouldn't they're
lying to
you but like as long as it's with
friends they say it's okay league is fun
even when you play with random people
they're so protective they're like don't
don't talk to strangers cuz they're
evil I got kidnapped eating the tal so
yeah
yeah that's an Eden Eternal how evil are
they going to be in League of Legends
they're going to yeah they can't be that
bad they're going to Flame you they're
going to be toxic they're going to tell
their mommies on you wow not the
mommies yeah anything but the
MERS hey what percentage isite that's my
favorite character I'm at 8% eight oh
God it's fine what are you oh 12
it's fine there's no problem with that
we'll just be C you you just have to
reach 100% reset it's okay yeah I will
you love reaching 100% yeah you got to
prove yourself to everyone it's not
about proving it's how the game works
Shori
Noella yeah but how often am I going to
play this game no it it doesn't have
anything to do with
that I love how she Y is making Nissa
rage love it do more please leave me
alone I don't deserve
this I'm just telling you it's just 100%
you know I don't care about reaching
100% but that's how you don't know about
that you seem you seem to really care
about finish you seem to care a
lot
yeah it seemed really important to you
indeed we're just chilling
I'm like you don't have to finish the
map I in fact do not understand we're
just cleaning ARA we're just here play
power wash with you guys again except
for Liz she understands me when we
played Shrek together Liz I will invite
you for
power thanks Anda could just watch in
the corner I'll Justa is try Harding I
know she's mid maxing in this game been
maxing
power I mean she is a pro at this so
yeah that's cuz it's a good game she's
going to go into the uh power wash
Esports I know you guys you guys are
never going to get to Atlantis and that
just makes me
sad Atlantis is where the is that where
the Championships are being held no it's
one of the maps
ah I thought you ground in the water
don't worry never getting to Atlantis is
kind of a thing and myth I've
[Laughter]
noticed so I need to continue the
tradition I
see and now we went from Halloween to
Christmas y Christmas being in s like sh
speed running 2024 be like
hell yeah
H the entrance Academy still has
dirt
lies don't believe
it
no believe
it believe
it let's go Naruto oh yeah let's go shy
oh we're going to save Sasuke I think I
sang that song in German before became a
thing what song the The Believer Naruto
song that's not
German he's really cool Sakura the Bea
fool right it wasn't German but I did
sing it in Koka before yeah it's it's
funny what else did they say Sakura was
cool yeah no they say SAS he's really
cool
the Beautiful the
beautiful yo yo do we have ladders time
that we can use there should be some
somewhere I'm not sure you can also use
an
extender no it's more like I need to
like get a different like from above POV
so the exender won't help there there
should be one somewhere Sasuke he's
really
cool takura the Beautiful the beautiful
oh my God there's a window you can see
outside it's so
pretty let's break it
open are we
stuck no entrance what else have I got
to clean here why do you think we're
stuck because she wants to break it open
to see the outside everyone has hard at
work said French bom Workshop is a mess
oh there's like an elf thing here like a
shadow that's cute I leave that for now
now bangs was testing the durability of
their rocket ships on the ceiling whilst
mullet was fine-tuning the high notes of
the
xylophones I I still don't see how that
leads to this sort of mess across way
high top fade had made some planes with
Precision Engineering whilst pomodora
had made some dolls that probably needed
more work really ah he's kind of mean to
his fellow else French bomb you
[\h__\h]
scandalous I'm cleaning my
hardest BB are you raising your chat up
secretly oh I I would never mute and
talk to chat I'm I see your chat
reacting very fondly what did you say to
them that you cannot share with the
classet said to them they were uh oh
stinky and they need to go back in the
mines you told them they're
stinky well I mean I was saying there
there was they were like stinky
socks wow they seem to think they're
presents
oh something sweet is going on she's
flirting with them cute
unbelievable even though we're right
here you're um how dare you yeah how can
you get distracted when these ladies are
around you yeah you know uh you know
Takashi Ki you should be part of Justice
you're really good at
monitoring you know I should tell the
higher ups they like hi are
you all right okay I can have a side job
yeah I'll take it I'll help you guys out
you know help me monitor
Advent you know Geographic I think there
there will be some good Synergy too I'm
close to Exodia was
it
Exodia that's the Yu-Gi-Oh
card I know shaking all the time wait
why is why is it laugh why are they
laughing cuz you
said Exodia which is a Yu-Gi-Oh card
[\h__\h] it's just because they're super
strong you know no wait what is it
called it's
Exodia Exodia how do you spell it right
Exodia can you spell it e ex a r d i a e
ex a r ah damn it close enough okay it's
close yeah yeah I'm sure the Yu-Gi-Oh
people would be very flattered you
thought that it was
Exodia yeah there seem to be a lot of
Yu-Gi-Oh people in all of your chats
that's how exia was made by the gods one
gave their arm another gave their other
arm and another gave their torso and leg
leg and so on and so forth and has how
great exia was made wow oh
great that's why I say bye the
gods have you girls played Yu-Gi-Oh
before I used to be an color of the
cards when I was younger oh wow I it for
the pretty boys I had a frog deck frog
deck I only played Magic the
Gathering that's
okay I never got into that one though I
have friends who are very into it the
cards look really nice mhm they're very
pretty yes I want a it's more mature
Gathering
collaboration girl do you don't know how
many times I tried to get perms for the
online magic the
Gathering they they ignore me how could
they do that you're so cute I don't know
they don't give perms to anybody I guess
gatekeeping Magic the Gathering
why let me play please let me play your
game we're trying to do things the right
way
mhm give us the
perms
please just want to play games hm
rip guess we got to make our own card
game we have one yeah exactly that's
what I'm
saying hint hint yeah play the hollow
life card game
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah
oh
oh I'm getting pings pings
pings
wow it's hard to reach
there there are some ladders over by the
entrance if you're still looking for
them no now I'm trying to like get
really
low low low low lowow
lowow [\h__\h] sweatpants and the reox with
the straps with the straps no
no I sang that truck simulator before
that was fun
oh I'm pretty multiplayer for that game
what for Euro Truck there's a
multiplayer
but technically I don't know if you have
perms for it honestly huh uh I'm pretty
sure the ID girls have played the
multiplayer version hey
y multiplayer no you just drive
together but not in the same vehicle
right no yeah I don't think you're just
exist as fellow truck drivers
oh but that's it
fun well if you don't Ram into each
other then you don't even need the
multiplayer mode you can just play the
single player mode at the same time yeah
you can Ram into each other you just
can't share the same vehicle I think oh
so you are on the same map then you're
saying yeah but you like I don't think
you can do much besides
drive while we can race each other
yeah racing with
tracks might as well just play Mario
Kart no different physics no parking but
Mario Kart has blue shells and you can
hit each other with it [\h__\h] the blue
shells you sound traumatized sh
Mario I always get [\h__\h] over in Mario
Kart that's why you try not to be first
you have to be second and maybe you can
get there I gave up on trying to get
good you know what my favorite racing
game
is Wacky Races on the PlayStation one
ooh sounds Wacky Sounds very wack never
heard of it you never Watch the cartoon
Wacky Races no maybe that's like a exia
thing
no I think it is no it's not it has
Dastardly and mly in it and stuff who
and has Penelope pitched
up o I love
Penelope you remember it so well
yeah she's got a good memory our
damn have you muted yourself again herb
yeah she's talking
[\h__\h] stop talking [\h__\h]
herb I just keep muting and going poop
poop po po
po how immature that like a mating
call
yeah stop doxing
me
stop yeah it's a CL it's a classic
cartoon but they made a a game as well
of it and it was very much like Mario
Kart but with the wacky characters nice
yeah I read a comment the other day when
in some collab stream I mentioned uh I
think it was an Eden Eternal I mentioned
Toontown oh and everybody agreed that we
like we didn't really understand we only
played it a little bit uh but it's
somewhere in our memories and I I read a
comment that made me realize that and
remember that the problem with Toontown
was that especially if you're young I
guess um the the beginning area that's
free to play is free to play and if you
want to get anywhere else in that game
you have to pay that's why I like only
was in that beginning area and I didn't
understand like where is the party going
on like where is everybody yeah turns
out it's not free to play what the heck
it's a freaking ch's game I heard about
that game never play credit
card yeah it kind of makes sense in a
way I guess even RuneScape like there's
a free portion of the game that you can
explore and like 20 or some free Quest
but then like a lot of the game is like
you have to actually become a
member oh Nissa taking all our money
what do you click to like stand still
and just move around your see thank you
yeah no
problem anything for you my angel of
music I tried avoiding like spending
money back then like my first game was
probably Terraria and only because I won
it in a giveaway your first game was
nice
what what about like Pokemon and stuff
like that oh no for steam stuff like I
would have my parents pay for it but I
try not to bother my parents
MH like I'll get this for Christmas
Christmas Christmas is coming the G are
getting fat please put the penny in the
old man's hat what that's cute if you
haven't got a penny I have it would do
if you haven't got a h pen God bless
you you're just making things up now
yep if that is making up on the spot
then you should be a freestyle rapper
onestly okay a to the B to the C to the
D
I love
kfp wow we've got a
[Applause]
winner a rap
god look out Callie Callie's been real
quiet since you dropped those
lines Miss C more you're going to need
to come here and defend yourself hurry
up no no I love how every time any H
member is like trying to rap like a you
know like a newbie everybody in the chat
is always like Callie has been real
quiet since you oh [\h__\h] as if cie had
any kind of
competition well regardless she's like
so unique as well with her rap so I I
don't think anybody could even like be
like her in general so unique special
true
go Callie go cie go
cie I'm going to be right back and get
some
water really really are you sure are you
sure that's what you're going to do yeah
no I am are you not muting and talking
to your chat secretly no let her mute
and talk to her chat that is her right
as a streamer Takashi well she gave me
the job now to observe so now I'm
observing
that's true or monitoring okay he's
going to regret it now I'm on a mission
now we're at 50%
completed
wow wow me and my
40% this is fine this game makes me
sweepy it's relaxing right I know it's
also going to give me
arthritis don't get
arthritis well you can't tell my R to do
that it has a mind of its own make them
stop okay you do the rest of the work
then just get good you'll be fine dang
you can do the rest of the work get your
100% you earned
it that's not how it works we have to do
it together because this is
multiplayer dang
I love how all of us are avoiding the
ceiling we're like [\h__\h] that no I'll get
ceil oh yeah I'll get there yeah I have
my own ceiling
here your own little
area mhm this is my corner it was made
for
me just like it is your hole that was
made for
you this is my hole get out of my hole
this is where I live
and I bought more tech gadgets I love
having more Tech like what yeah what'
you get it's um like another gimbal but
it's like tinier and more compact than
the one I have gambles let's go
yeah what is what are you going to do
with it well hopefully I would like to
Vlog but it depends on the area and the
people who don't get the [\h__\h] out of my
way
like get out of here I'm trying to Vlog
and then just spend your relatives
around so have to be like get out of
here get out my Vlog get out of my Vlog
Mommy it's my turn on the
Xbox only the best Vlogs for Shi mhm
we'll see about
that it's a lot people around also um
did you also get like a extra like
microphone for your vlogging oh no I do
mind silent because I don't want to talk
then you do voice over yeah yeah I also
would be like very embarrassed like last
time when I was in Japan I did a little
Vlog for uh I think I announced my 2.0
for my life to D oh yeah at the end of
it I think um but yeah I I did like a
vlog in Shinjuku uh gave myself some
missions to achieve and and all that and
I was like well I don't want to do a
voiceover I want to like you know talk
that to the camera basically but I'm
like really shy and also awkward about
it too so I just brought my manager with
me so that it seems like I'm talking to
my manager while I'm filming things and
that works that helped a lot see see
that's cute yeah so I told her to always
like walk right next to me so that I
don't look like a freaking weirdo
talking to
myself yeah I can't do that I don't want
my relatives like knowing the channel or
anything I keep as hushed as I can about
it cuz like I'm just I'm just don't mind
me just a video
editor yeah that's all they
know what if something's like way too
close but I have no other way to reach
it either like when you're so close that
you can't like clean it you know what I
mean it's it's hard sometimes it's rough
like that man what cracker I love
crackers I think I got I hate their
facial hair though why it's so soft and
fuzzy no come on I'mma yank
it okay Queen you live your truth yank
yank no facial hair in my world but no
if you got facial hair you're okay it's
like okay no no she said what she said
novaline she won't accept you she's
going to yank out your hair one by one
like facial hair yeah but I'm not going
to hate you for
it no it's okay keep your facial hair
some you guys probably like
it yeah don't make them feel bad for
facial hair cuz look do whatever I want
just look better with facial hair let's
be real oh yeah yeah I think so
too but but not fictional characters for
me sorry you guys have to yank it off
yeah fictional characters meet you with
facial hair no way get out maybe nothing
although he would look less like a
little baby if he had facial hair I like
being baby I like nice
Demitri like nice baby boy
Dmitri that's not what he grows up into
I hate to tell you I I didn't like that
Arc I was going to punch the crap out of
it
do you ever make character AI feel bad
for what he turns into there are
definitely good-looking characters that
have facial hair
definitely name name a few name a few I
don't know does Sid have facial hair and
Final
Fantasy I think he has like a little bit
Sid right blond dude there's so many
different SIDS what Sid oh [\h__\h] right I
forgot
sh s has some yeah okay depends on which
Sid but Sid has
some I guess I guess Leon from Final
Fantasy could be okay with sh sh you
like cursed things now let me give you a
good example you can't tell me that
Santa Claus doesn't look good with his
facial hair but to be fair Santa Claus
is a married Granda excuse
me well he's rocking it I I don't want
to say he's like
like how dare you dismiss SCH T
Nissa thank you for the backup I'm
saying he's my grandfather I'm not going
to look at him in that way he's your
grandfather's your grand well that's
going to be awkward
now
what Santa Claus is a demon you going me
Mr Santa Claus I mean pretty much
everything you see that is like a weird
creature is probably like a demon let's
be honest imagine going around the whole
entire world in one night and delivering
presents you you think anyone could do
that some magic man humans like me
you're different M you're built
different Santa Claus could be human
he's my idol I'm sorry bad news you got
to make him dance I want to hear a song
covers Santa Claus covers Idol
by it's gonna crack some bones poor old
guy no he's very
Nimble I like some uh I think there's
book called cringle which is before
Santa became Santa and when I read that
I just imagine him as an anime character
is Santa Claus real yeah yeah okay good
that we have established that that was
important why why wouldn't he be
I've never seen him PR yet he on the
naughty
list yeah he doesn't want to get docked
yeah yeah he's an idol mhm
yeah not very believable but
okay what if Santa is just like anyone
with a good heart yeah I like that
theory yeah I think he's the guy that
goes what oh uh Tim Allen yeah oh yeah
yeah yeah oh my God taggy from scoobydoo
or
Scooby I do that a lot I had
a I had a phase uh I think last year
where I watched from beginning to end
all of the seasons of that show what
Home Improvement yeah it's so good now
that I watch as an
adult I think I just watched episodes
like randomly in random order when I was
a child but like now as an adult it's it
gives you a whole new POV and you really
end up liking the mom cuz I think as a
child I didn't care about the mom
character but now she's really I like
her she's cool she's chill what exactly
is a show about is it just like this
dude who owns like a construction stuff
and he does f a TV show doesn't he yeah
he has a TV show and he likes you know
doing stuff in the house and car and he
messes up his own house the whole time
too but they have kids they have free
boys and in the beginning of the show
you can really see the actors are really
young and so they grow up like a lot
over the course of the show they become
adults and yeah they go through live and
and puberty and the mom is like always
frustrated with her husband but it's
funny it's like really
funny you
know I heard that was a show turn his
life around cuz he he had like a
criminal record before I don't know what
from but then he got his together and
then he started like acting and then he
became like a good role model he had a
criminal recordal it's probably just
like a DUI I don't
know you have to Google it nah no way
not him
oh what he was a dealer he turned his
life around yeah what oh my God he's
like walon Breaking Bad
there you go but he's learned he got his
life together he became an actor
wow the heck
lore the
archives can't stop
grunting let's do a grunt Scooby-Doo
goes I like Shaggy and Scooby who
doesn't they're
cute yeah I like them in the live action
movie too yeah oh my God the live action
is way too good like way better than it
has any right
being that's one of the really good like
uh was it cartoon to IRL
um
uh uh adaptations it really is because
literally the Shaggy actor in that went
on to play Shaggy for like a really long
time as like his voice
like in the
animation
yeah they were on point with the costing
yeah they
were and I think um and Adam's family is
another really good
costume live action
movies always it's
crazy yeah I think it's interesting
because Daphne's actress and Fred's act
actor are married in real
life yeah
it's Buffy yeah Buffy mm I love Buffy
it's interesting cuz that they just kind
of [\h__\h] around in the cartoon yeah
depending on the version of it yeah
spicy haven't watched it can't judge
you've never seen
Scooby-Doo not
really there's like a different seasons
of it some are better than others yeah
the show definely went through a lot lot
of like change changes yeah like
different writers
voices no around for a long time it's
true a
classic classic
H I should buy like a a big giant
Nutcracker I was tempted before yeah no
raisin I just like them go ahead you
should do a nut cracking
stream nut cracking hand supposed to
crack nuts what why not yeah I don't
know it's because they're not really
like meant for it they're well how how
can you get
in but why are they called nutcrackers
if they're not supposed to crack nuts
maybe people crack their nuts Oh Oh I
thought you meant you're not supposed to
crack nuts in
general well with them like you know
their mouth I don't think you're
actually supposed to put uh nuts in
there it's more just like cute
okay I say they used to actually be able
to like take it yeah but
now I can crack them with my thighs I
don't need a n cracker hell
yeah always always done
that it's just how I do it is the Ste
man do me do me K do me come on me my
presence for sister
sh of
the
Pres
wow oh this
chairman can't get this sigh to
Ping but I'm like I'm pretty sure it's
clean so I'm like
hello
H
well we're having a fun time you got to
get it 100 game that I'm thinking about
it wait I see like an actual good
Scooby-Doo game I'm sure there's one
somewhere I need to get um some pointand
click Adventures of it I feel like
getting it mhm they so endearing I love
pointand click Adventures have you guys
played the wait no I think that's is
that German only Angela Ao no I've never
you know it I know what you're on about
yeah they you know the absolutely cursed
game uh no but I but I do remember it
cuz they had a Angela and a condo before
the Digimon
movie maybe maybe it was only popular in
like
Europe I think it was made in Australia
wasn't it oh it felt so cursed as a
child a terrible show yeah and they had
this point and click game that was so
cursed everything was cursed
cursed actually style of animations so
like yeah was very original very
unique
[Music]
mind I'm so hungry weird you're hungry a
yeah did you not eat anything today M
well I did but it's like uh almost night
now so the last time I ate is a while
ago I need to eat
dinner and then I hopefully I need to
sleep early but I took a nap today again
I'm such a freaking idiot why do I keep
on taking naps but I was really tired
and I I did some stuff that that tired
out my arms too my noodle arms are like
so weak because I I carried stuff from
the from the post
office I cared plates some some
melatonin yeah it doesn't really work
that well on me but um makes sense it's
kind of like iffy I'll still take it
hoping that it will work yeah maybe you
can get those uh heated eye mask maybe
that can help you ah I think I still
have them but uh I don't know they're
they're not like the
most amazing thing for
me try it try it maybe it'll help with
I'll try it before
but combine them for extra efficiency
all right all
right I'll do my
best I'm going to try clearing my
backlog while I am away for my trip yeah
what backlog games homework I want to
play my time at Sandro we don't have
perms for it
oh what is it mean a game back look it's
like a it's like a farming game except
it's not really farming it's more like
engineer I think yeah yeah yeah the only
crappy thing is I don't like the the
environment you're in a desert and I
think you're supposed to make you're in
a desert grass yeah you're in a desert
with your engineering skills you might
be able to give it
grass and you can marry people hell
yeah great
yeah well but why would you want to
marry anybody but Dimitri
because you can't marry the meichi more
than once in a game and that's it well
you want aren't you happy with that is
that not satisfactory to you no I need
more content I got to I got to go with
the flow
yeah I need to get my adrenaline and my
dopamine my
serotonin right serotonin is what like
the Happy thing right yeah yeah yeah
don't in then serotonin both
there they're
[Music]
related man Santa needs to hire a
made that's not
us we are the the higher out yeah we're
getting paid for
this I don't know I feel like we should
demand a raise or maybe more Christmas
presents yeah it's Santa so we he at
least has to for sure bring us a
present I know I better be in a good
list bring Santa a Pikachu this
Christmas you know Pokemon released the
dub released like some original
Christmas songs back in the day no what
I didn't know that until a few years
back when I was just randomly on Spotify
looking up Pokmon songs and it came up
with the Christmas like tunes and I was
like a
oh my God I didn't know that it's kind
of
amazing I need to watch a new Pokemon
they secur the villain in
there he has black and white hair
too I hope he's competent but I doubt
itain yeah in in Pokemon it's you
know yeah
yeah rocket
maybe what's his name is it Larry who's
Larry Gary
oh my God no it's a Pokemon like human
not not an actual poon but if his name
Larry because
Gary oh you thinking of that would be
great no all I know is he's a villain
and then the new Pokemon has two
protagonists like some girl and some
boy
yeah I don't know is he not a villain a
a mytho let me check I missed Ash
already they're probably tired of voice
acting yeah it's a mytho then Ash is at
least English voice actress is still
going
strong yeah who else are they voicing um
there's that one anime that came out I
don't remember what it's called but it's
like got that Russian
girl and uh the English voice for ash
she she also speaks Russian fluently so
she got that role because that's a whole
like that's cool that's one of the big
things about about it uh is like she
speaks Russian but like and doesn't
realize the main character can speak it
so she acts like she's saying mean
things to him really sheim thing yeah
yeah yeah I see I see yeah oh yeah oh
yeah I know what you're talking about
yeah not going to watch it but I know
that's Ash's voice actress it's
crazy Ash went the a long way to
becoming a Pokemon Master to becoming
like a Russian girl now
I didn't realize those was Gunk on the
ceiling yeah you didn't realize until
now oh no I had a Daddy Daycare moment
of you know when the kid goes I miss and
then he he walks in and he's like oh
looks around and he looks up and he's
like oh God
[Music]
he anyone else go like like
randomly that
noise but cie doeses a
good close enough I also do like random
sounds like
uh out of nowhere not no I don't mean to
it's just one of my
things yeah I mean you could do ASMR
then cuz that's most of the mouth noise
is mouth pops mhm oh your destiny shine
ASMR to be cursed with
ASMR
yeah just talk about your day I mean
that's a ASMR too just whisper about
your day yeah oh I have a dead body it's
not a real dead body my cats live in it
it's just you know I got it for
Halloween but it's not Halloween it's
for Christmas too you know
so you could do that
I'm your ASMR manager yeah she's going
to write all your scripts for you and
then you just have to record them do you
like writing
scripts I don't mind if if I have
time yeah that's a thing yeah time yeah
so many
projects yeah yeah time is a precious
resource these days I
know I just want time to slack off
it might be looking for a script
writer maybe what kind of script fider
for like
uh oh no no
uh uh personal uh spicy movie you know
oh a
movie wow she green
movie uh secret secret
NDA oh okay okay
well I I wish you luck I wish you luck
anyone who wants to apply maybe she'll
have a a listing for you yes yes I'll be
sting it out via DM yeah
mhm and I love doing random projects
though yeah it's like I want to do this
I want to do
that but why I just feel like it hey
that's valid a reason as
ever yeah it's the only reason you need
to do
anything so I want to yep
mhm well you should I mean you should be
passionate about you know what you up to
to makes the project even
better there's no purpose but it's fun
oo wow that side is pretty clean nice
nice yeah we doing pretty good oh gosh
it's 2
hours 75% need to
go
uh kind of uh if you have to go get
gone just power was get out of here it's
just power wash we won't keep you wow no
I didn't mean that in a mean way
Wows mys and then she just tells me to
go away
I don't want you to leave how will I
ever live without you back to she Raven
wow she she used that same line on me
how am I going to live out you and I
said you have Liz it's
okay me you find yourself in a pickle
narissa how about how about Liz and I
make the ship then come on Liz let's go
go ahead I don't care
D Mi messages here she says she doesn't
care but I I think she cares I know she
cares about that 100%
too I do I'll have to
get yeah we'll go we'll go out and look
for a cute Christmas dress for
you I like shopping shopping is fine me
too I think we all like
shne they don't even like window
shopping yeah I don't like shopping that
much anymore
it doesn't bring joy great happiness now
it's stressful and I don't know it's
like hard to choose
and yeah I love window shopping I like
getting more to clothes I love looking
around may or may not fit my teeths also
you get your steps and walking around
mall and stuff yeah that's true then you
think that online shopping will maybe
take the stress away but no online
shopping has its own problems like you
don't know what you're getting you w if
it's
SP too lazy to send it back wasting my
money rather look in person
yeah but then there's some shops that I
really like there's one shop in
particular that I really really like um
but for me they only have an online shop
because like their real IRL shop is in
the country far away from me mhm but I
really want to go there and and try out
all the dresses you have to go then come
with me
[Music]
okay okay that was easy I wonder what
easy I mean the clothes are cute it's
benefits both of us we can both try it
out right hell yeah mhm I think you saw
me wearing one of their dresses before
ooh if it's what I think then yes I want
to try on their stuff so
bad oh I might not I'm not sure which
wrong what's your typical fashion for
stuff I remember you saw me and my weird
dress
is oh sorry well um H my typical fashion
I used to one that you're willing to
share yeah no it's fine I used to dress
kind of like how bibo dresses now but
that's like when I was younger nowadays
it's like a very toned down version of
it mhm maybe M I like to dress kind of
elegant now yeah a but have still like
cute Vibes and like Frills and stuff
here and there but not too much and less
patterns just simple
M we're still cute
cute but I've also become so lazy that I
just go in my pajamas everywhere
nowadays that's how you know you've
grown
up I don't give any [\h__\h] anymore
yeah I mean especially if you're just
going out of the grocery store who
cares yeah I mean I still wear dresses
but that's cuz I don't like pants
yeah dresses a
lot but in the winter
time more difficult yeah I like winter
fashion like bundling up that yeah scar
still wear my dress pants I I double up
on the tights usually if I'm wearing
them
yeah have you consider getting
ins uh I mean sometimes I wear those
too
yeah I like those ones a lot but I
always feel like the the ankle area
looks ugly for some
reason yeah sometimes I want the patn
like so that that's why I double on the
thick patent ones cute
yeah I need to eat after this I just had
jagaro as my food
jagaro you still have Jag did you did
you bring it from Japan no no no there's
a there's some Asian stores around oh or
like International Foods or whatever I
guess do you usually go for the snacks
and do shops like they're important it's
a very very small selection so if I pass
by the story like I I'll get it
mhm
not yeah it's like oh they got this
wow one of the things I like to get from
Asian shops is a lamun
[Music]
fizzly I'm I'm not familiar I I know I
know to drink
though was it was it fizzly yeah is it
carbonated yeah is fizzy yeah but not
too crazy not too
much not like a fresh Coca-Cola I
thought was fun T I wouldn't drink it
then but I like the look of it just open
it up and let it stand for a while
oh car actually they like when
carbonated things have uncarbonated
themselves oh like the I don't mind it
huh I know some people are like oh my
God sometimes I feel is insane I like
when they're uncarbonated too but
sometimes I feel like the flavor is just
weird and that they rely on the
carbonation to make it taste quote
unquote
good I like I love water lemonade
uncarbonated yeah wait I've never had up
that
sorry I I correct myself because over in
great Exodia lemonade is usually
considered like Sprite and seven up and
all that oh uh and then the the uh
American lemonade is cloudy lemonade
over here cloudy lemonade you're going
to have to do like a lessons in exia
language it's funny because it's or at
least in in my area it was it's
considered like Posh to have like cloudy
lemonade so when I visited like like
Fria and then it like the go-to was like
cloudy lemonade I be like w
fancy cloudy lemonade I love
lemonade me too it's my favor especially
like it's still go for water though I
feel bad for calories yeah same got to
be mindful of the figure you know mhm
yeah he
dies oh and then and then
also in great Exodia SL what you say
shades of Greenland uh uh what what is
it call when you have a uh shades of
that's my code name for it at the moment
until I reveal more of the great exorian
map uh uh uh what is it so usually if
you have like a bit of a an upset tummy
you like given a flat uh a flat
Sprite really
yeah that's so interesting
yeah yeah that's that's right over where
you are it's a ginger ale right yeah
that's to go to fizzy and
all oh fizzy
ah no she she's saying that uh they they
do uh
give uh un fizzy Sprite for it oh as
we're like here we do ginger
ale I just suffer no
I don't really like what the heck really
I don't really like most pops but I
really like ginger ale I still won't go
out of my way to drink it but like if
it's presented to me I won't say
no I don't like ginger wellow I'm
alone I think what it tastes like I
barely have it I think I'm partially
going to hop because I'm getting a
little bit motion Sicky so okay thanks
for playing with us thanks for having me
fun thank you thanks for thinking of me
don't forget I'm watching you now oh
God abandoned by our Queen
no our Scarlet Queen well I hope we
finish this soon cuz I don't want to
leave you behind but I also got to dip
soon in I I'll help her get a 100
99% oh you are what else do you need
that
at 99 I'm apparently at I'm at 85 how is
this 99 like a lot of the ceiling is
still dark a lot of the CE theost on
mine I think the host gets most of it
I'm I think the whole ceiling just about
is done except for this middle
panel I'll go through and I'll start
checking but we we still says 85 I feel
like it has barely G up it's just broken
let take her percentage Yeah that's her
test score that we're stealing yeah
uh I need to get up higher how do I get
up
higher use your wings I why do I suck at
jumping I've never been so bad at
jumping as when I've been playing this
with you
guys oh is it our fault now
yeah dang what did we do okay uh let me
start okay what's not clean look so like
we have buned what the hell is a
bunting I've heard that word before
bunting isn't it like punching
someone I I don't know
not B bunting
hello oh that's punting oh sorry them I
see it I see it it's the thing on the
top up here and then you guys are
cleaning things
too yeah yeah trying Me Try Me Try oaba
OAB boonga clean clean clean okay cheer
Checker base Che
chest okay speed running running we're
speed we're speed running don't
worry we're almost there very
close shy what made you want to play
this
game oh I just thought it' be funny to
invite like all these ships she to have
oh really that was the concept yeah I
didn't realize I didn't realize that was
the concept either no there was a real
concept it's just why I can't be there
for your birthday so I figured like oh
she play P oh that's sweet of you how
thoughtful yeah so I got all your
favorite
ships here's my present thank you giv me
is it accurate narissa do you think she
got it right very
oh I love all the ladies in this
cam okay I hope you have a great
birthday though oh I'm sure I
will there's there's going to be lots of
fun and it's only two days
away oh my God I know can't wait for you
to Expresso your happiness and joy
espresso stream espresso on stream
streaming services now
yay I've been seeing so much uh Sabrina
Carpenter on my Twitter
algorithm it's always like tweets that
say like oh my God I can't believe she's
doing these moves in her concerts in
front of
children I saw that to too actually and
I to be honest I didn't even know who
the heck Sabrina Carpenter was a Disney
girl she was a Disney girl but like that
was like 10 years ago Decor dang what
did she star in who is she I don't even
know that's the crazy
thing
oh like everyone's freaking out and I'm
like bro it's fine let her let her be
sexy Decor decoration machine
papers oh she was in boy meet's world
the hell is that who is she the girl
Girl Meets World
was she the main
character I guess it's a woman Meets
World now
yeah she is a woman in the
world
mhm I think I need she's the bestie okay
I don't know who that is
yeah did you ever you ever watch that
one sh I watched a boy meets real dude
but all I remember is that there's a
blonde girl and there's this like brown
curly haired dude and they liked each
other I'm pretty sure it's that's that's
cly it yeah I don't remember anything I
don't think I ever watched
it that's all I know I don't know who
these people are I don't know who you
are I don't know what you
want but you move sexy so Twitter
[Laughter]
mad bro why won't this get clean it
doesn't even look dirty get clean get
cleaned I'm I'm literally I'm trying so
hard I do not see any dirt on it in a
place that is easily
accessible and it will just not you you
can do it I'm trying my
hardest I believe in you I'm trying my
hardest I won't yell in your ears like
you do with me earlier I wasn't yelling
in your ears no I don't know
but it's cuz we're like an old married
couple
man dang so you're just interpret my me
as
nagging cute birds what do you you think
is she
Naggy is she cooking I'm always
cooking please be true she always Cooks
the wall is also not clean over
here I'm not sure where it's still dir
feel from me is like not
clean
yeah
please oh hello the
exorian you have been raided
congratulations H time to
defend defend against what invasion of
course exorian Very members remember I
supp just because we're
friendly on the outside doesn't mean
that we shouldn't be prepared on the
inside always be ready always be guarded
yeah M there we go okay but welcome to
my
domain welcome to sh
stream where everything yo did you know
that there's an Allison Wonderland DLC
in here no what what cool yeah but we
don't have perms for it what we need
perms for each
DLC well I think we only have perms for
like Tomb Raider some Final Fantasy
stuff and like whatever
crap there's a Tomb Raider DLC in this
game you mean yeah yeah what yeah Tomb
Raider that's something that would make
you happy yeah you ready to clean some
tombs maybe there's finally a dead body
in them you ready to some Tomb
Raider should have gone with that huh I
didn't know you were a big tomb raer fan
I don't know I'm not I'm not I'm not I'm
just
surprised okay sorry
misunderstood misunderstanding cor hates
them I can't believe she hates Laura
cross
yeah because her boobies are too
triangular let her boobs triangle
okay I'll just move on to something else
I'll come back here what if you're like
a different shape
then like a star shape yeah I I was just
thinking of that too that would be
impressive uhuh and she like shapes the
matte will into Like a Knife oh my God
and then she shoot Mak sense for the
movie She's
in genre yeah like she doesn't need
weapons anymore she's got like massive
bazon gongs yeah yeah yeah she
doesn't that's all you need that's all
you need to do whatever it is lur coft
is doing she just needs to
be okay fireplace
cover hey I'm at 95 can't finally %
yeah and only 96%
this okay it's okay I'm I'm going
through fireplace gonk what the hell is
a
gonk a song called gong it's a gnome why
do they call him a
gonk he's going to Gunk it
out fireplace
presents cleaning these presents pres
was the worst part of this
map what what has been your least
favorite part of the
map
everything I guess maybe the tables cuz
you have to like Crouch every yeah every
angle you got to get every angle you do
you got to get every angle otherwise I
hated the roof in the last map yeah oh
trust me if you ever played story mode
there's one where the roof is really
really absurdly high up GI
bobbles oh God at least this is more
reachable like the ceiling is more
reachable yeah that's true plus it's all
interior so you don't have to climb much
yeah there there are on that are really
ungodly I won't
lie there's like a subway station lie
you would never no it is out of my
character lying hard that's why I just M
what one more giant Bobble yet to be
clean a holy sister would never lie
unless
necessary what are you lying do you have
any papers to prove that you're really a
nun starting to doubt it after all I've
heard from you
H actually a true nun would not need
papers because we would not use such
things for we are poor poor I guess what
you're poor you don't have to go to nun
College who the heck even like said such
a
thing nun College oh going to yeah you
think nuns can afford textbooks in nun
College none of that in here oh my
goodness
Shori I think she actually when I was
growing up I debated on joining like a
nunnery or some [\h__\h] I did too
actually yeah let's go nun
face what
yeah I I was really into Hamlet and he
says take thee to a NY another which is
basically just him calling the girl a
[\h__\h] no it was because he loved her and
he couldn't stand the idea of her with
anyone else but he he was also breaking
up with her gr
oh in in my interpretation he was
basically calling her kind of like you
should go to a nunnery cuz you're dirty
and sinful Bas on my class anyway I
don't actually remember 100% but I'm
pretty sure it's because I mean it's
probably interpreted in multiple
ways yeah he's he's just rude he was a
rude guy I like the ailia scene though
the one where she dies I kind of liked
it I mean it's poetic so yeah it's
pretty it's sad but it's pretty
beautiful mhm plus it spawns to artwork
which is like
neat what artwork are you referring to
there's a painting of her like it's
called ailia yes I know exactly yeah I
love
that it's
pretty I don't know what you guys are
talking about sadly wait you you don't
you don't read
Shakespeare oh basically there's this
girl named ailia he calls her like a
harlot that was his like childhood love
or girlfriend and then she dies cuz I
think camlet kills her father and other
people ESS yeah she she
Shea ks's herself it's not that I can't
read okay no I know you can read
okay this is like a questioning if you
can read or not we all know that you can
read not you
girls she can she's a business woman KF
she has a KF yeah she's
business but spelled
wrong how is it spelled
b u ZZ you know b u z z with Z's instead
of s's and maybe like when Z is uh in
Reverse yeah sounds about right can one
of you come over and tell me does this
wall over here say it's dirty for you
bro there's so much dirty stuff in here
I'm at 99% and there's still so much
things to clean I'll help I'll help I'll
lead us because m is the correct one if
someone can clean this wall here and get
it to say that it's clean what wall the
one that I'm wall yeah The Grotto wall
over by the
me there's a lot of different Grotto
walls the one over over by the present
machine dir for
me
yeah there's one I will clean what I can
okay I wonder why it's glitching so bad
maybe it's cuz uh we're so far apart in
terms of
Worlds that might we got two people in
like near ardia two people near like
whatever calers Culver thing you're
at where do you live uh near Culver uh I
near the
Culver which
one ex the good one
obviously where the hell
I hate when they make things Orange in
this game because when you hit the tab
button it doesn't help you very much
yeah it's hard to
see at least we're bonding while Kiara
starves it's okay starving is just a
small problem I have right now there's
there there's there I still need to
learn Korean on uh in the next
what you trying to learn I don't know
useful words I need to I need to become
fluent in the next 12 hours that's
that's not going to happen even if you
20 billion
hours you 20 billion hours but in even
if you had like 20
days yeah well it's okay I know I know
some
things you're going to be okay I can say
left and
right I can say like I can say
uh
but I can say
cat hopefully it will be
enough I mean can they not speak
English
um a little bit probably her English is
probably better than my Korean probably
better than
mine but still I want to like be a
little bit helpful yeah yeah
understandable I'm Google translate just
in case no it's okay it's going to work
out yeah yeah if only I would have kept
up my my reps my Korean reps ever since
I started them cuz I even had a private
teacher come to my home and do
one-on-one lessons with me cuz I was so
serious about it and we did that for
like half a
year and then I stopped and I thought
okay I'll just try my best to keep it in
my memory for now now and you know cuz I
was just too busy to keep up the lessons
so I thought maybe another time I'll get
back to it but now I need a break and
then that that break continued so long
now I don't remember anything yeah it
kind of sucks when you want to learn so
much but you don't have like the time
yeah sometimes also I think it's not
just a time anymore like I used to pick
up Japanese so
easily but that was cuz I was
young and now my brain doesn't work the
same way anymore yeah that happens as
you get older picking up stuff like
languages really recommend learning
languages uh as long as you're still
young if you
can the younger the better for learning
languages I wish I knew more Japanese so
I can read my AI
games that's your biggest issue
right Lang being able to understand ome
games
like even if you can read hiana and
Katakana you're not going to know the
vocabulary it's like I don't know what
this is yeah that's learning the the
writing is just the first step I know I
don't even know Kani kani's so much yeah
kani's a lot to try and absorb into your
brain s
Skys okay I can't find like visually if
I just look at things everything looks
clean I'm spamming Tab and I still don't
know where like the dirt is on the
object
sometimes it's they they like to make a
lot of like really difficult angles
M honestly it's like how was I ever
supposed to find like how am I supposed
to get the dirt
here cuz that's where I'm at I'm like I
don't even see dirt I know it's still
dirty because I've selected it and I
found
it and apparently it's pretty decent
dirty but I can't clean
it despite my best
efforts
M yeah
slay well I'll just let reisa get the
100% I'll clean but we're not going to
get 100% but Risa can I believe in her
she's a 100% go-getter yeah
sorry we're just better sorry we're
go-getters am I right gotta go get
them I see nothing it's crazy I'm
locking in but so many things are like
at 99% and I'm going in and I'm like
please
game yeah click I'm just going to go B
per which one Santa's list dirty it's
which
list that's this
one I don't know it looks pretty clean
on
me okay
slay get it% no no no so we have
only technically eight things left which
is groto skirting groto wall panelings
and
lanterns so where's the gro
it's the wall
stuff what all the walls no no no it's
just one one so there's uh if you hit
Escape you can see everything so if you
go to groto skirting nine out of 10 are
finished and the one that isn't finished
is at
99 then there's gr wall paneling which
is at 98 and one is left I he's clean
Sant and then there's six lanterns so if
you
we have ladders actually the next found
a dirty Lantern there's ladders over
here um oh I
see R to wall skirting r a wall paneling
what does that
mean wall paneling my nozzle's too
long stubby gun let's go I love the
stubby
gun it's just so cute
such a
Vibe how do I pick stuff up I'm pressing
F and it's like not doing
much maybe I can't um you can but it's
being a
dick yeah I can't get my nozzle back as
well what do you mean oh no break my G I
guess so I have pickup Place equipment
but no nozzle okay wait oh God it's okay
we're getting cooked 99% if you put a
one in front of that I have
199% we're we're so close that's enough
yeah
yeah all right uh well I can't clean
anymore so I'm just going to CH yeah I'm
I can't even jump anymore I know it's
cuz you're holding the
ladder oh really I'm not holding
anything in my screen I know it's that's
what happened to me when we when we
ended before on the previous one because
I picked up the ladder and quite
literally I was unable to then do
anything
else I see game why I'm
cooked I'm just going to stand here
we're all cooked get to
cleaning I think we're we're finished
100% you call this clean not until you
get my
anxiety here track record no okay all
the lanterns are clean so now there's I
don't understand huh how can you ever
100% anything in this game it's not it's
not this hard it's not hard at all I
don't know single player
mode where is this groto wall paneling
in this groto
skirting I'm going to km I'll give you
I'll give you minutes okay wait I found
I found one of them I found one of them
100% re 100% I'm trying I'm going for it
I'm going for
it
I I'm trying my hardest you're doing
great you're doing great okay we just
have food one single thing left and it's
the groto wall paneling if you guys
notori you go through and you find that
and select it do you see anything
lighting
up GR Gro Gro a b c d e f g Groo Groo
what Groo
skirting walls oh I found it or rather
chat found it
then I I'm let's see if it will pop
clean I'm doing my best cuz I I feel
like if I get a 100 it should give all
of us a 100 right like even even if it's
behind right now who knows I'm just
going to copy your homework go ahead
copy away okay yeah people used to copy
off of me and they would admit it to me
job complete doesn't doesn't show up for
me what really yeah job complete me but
we good
job
unbelievable well we got 100 emphasis on
we we yay we well okay close just close
the game just close it it's cursed
y all right well that was a
good simulator session yeah does anyone
have anything to
announce I'm gone see you bye Queen what
about you
miss well if anybody's awake for my
special collab damn it I still need to
make the
thumbnail you got you got it need to
need to eat need to make thumbnail
learn Korean you got this um Yos please
watch if you
awake but yeah uh I want to announce
that nissa's birthday is coming up hello
yes on the 21st it is my birthday I'm
having a big birthday bash please come
by it'll be lots of fun for everyone so
you won't want to miss it also stream
espresso on
Spotify I'll there and spare it yes as a
ghost as a ghost
I'll also be there as a ghost I think
yes lots of ghost ghosting for playing
with me it was fun getting thanks for
inviting thank you for inviting me you
have no idea how I was so so surprised
about the
invitation oh yeah but it all makes
sense now
social no we'll go little more stuff
when I get back we play more Eden oh my
gosh yay Eden Eden Eden
but maybe again someday yeah maybe let
not not be no because of the
connection oh it's hard connection for
RuneScape oh
no RuneScape no because the fans are
crazy oh you got from some RuneScape
OG's I guess they they're amazing but
they also crowned and it's hard for me
to find you my noelites are well behaved
good sheep good
wow except for that one that kidnapped
me but they were a fake novite they were
a novite but
anyway I'll see you guys
whenever darling y thank you for
watching everybody
[Music]