[Music]
oh I'm glad so many people got to watch
The Palace cat
[Music]
video
[Applause]
[Music]
KY
k k k
you know what you know what you know
what uh uh this game is perfect because
we're going to rush you know in this
game you got to rush and the good thing
is or the bad thing is I don't know um
the neutral thing is that we have to
rush indeed because um I can only due to
circumstances uh stream for two hours
now it's already 5 minutes less than 2
hours I wanted to stream longer and
normally I I hate streaming so short
L uh but it it's got to be like that and
that's okay but uh what was I going to
say hopefully we can make some
progress we're just getting into the
game yeah I thought you know two hours
better than nothing right I already like
because of you know delay and this and
that I already asked for the absolute
maximum that they would allow
me um probably normally
the the most ideal would be not
streaming at all um but I I don't want
to I want you know I already canceled
yesterday's stream and I feel bad so um
we're doing the absolute absolute
tolerated
maximum there is no character
customization I
think so um it is what it is guys we
have to accept it okay uh for people who
are watching the archive let me just
explain normally the stream would have
been like 4 hours
long uh but then you know the concert
was delayed first it was delayed by an
hour and then it was delayed until
further notice so that's what's been
going
on uh two hours is not enough for Hala
Miami to be to well I mean I'm not
playing the whole game of course I also
thought it's not so ideal but better
than nothing
right um
uh right or should I end the stream
now uh any news on to please um wait for
management uh
notifications they are working hard on
making everything work out and getting
together uh you know details and so on
[Music]
um what's happening in 2 hours in 2
hours kiaha has to go to too
bad okay let's play this game if I can
ah freaking hell can I play it in Window
mode
please I want to play in Window
[Music]
mode better than playing Final Fantasy
for 2 hours yeah I was like lowkey
thinking about maybe changing the
content again into something that fits 2
hours better oh my God that's loud you
don't hear it yet wait but but I thought
well I already like oh it's
German uh I already you know made
changes so I didn't want to change
things again
uh this in it says in German this game
contains scenes that uh hint
to
sex well things should these scenes be
skipped yes or no
[Music]
uh not not just
seex apparently um danger danger oh here
it is in German I don't know why yeah n
y n we hopefully it can change your
language in game don't
skip should be fine right uh so nine and
we we do have a nine emote let's
go
nine nine
nine yeah no
nine oo what's midnight
animal oh wait you still don't hear it
I'm vibing and you don't hear it oh my
God I'm so selfish I'm such a selfish
[\h__\h] wait a second I tapped
out
oh my God wait wait can I whoa uh config
why why is
it it's like partially English and
partially German this menu
is English but on the bottom you see WD
Gan is
German here it's also
English I'm guessing that
the uh
that the text dialogues would be
uh probably let me see yeah that's
definitely German
uh wa
why why why why why why why they got
lazy half translation I didn't know
people would just half translate a
[Music]
game oh what the [\h__\h] is this sound
is this Hotline
Miami repeating its
sound do you hear
this yeah I closed it the sound only
started when I open the
[Music]
game
uh I'm I'm going to try to how do
[Music]
you uh if there's no language setting in
the game keep the German [\h__\h] it
we but if there's no language setting in
the game how do you do it again uh
outside of the game properties is there
like a setting
there probably in
[Music]
Steam game the sub go in German no no no
no it's okay it's okay it's okay
no no no no I want
English right click the game and I'm I'm
I'm um um um I'm I right click and then
there's properties but then nothing
looks like language
[Music]
setting seam properties General yeah
enable Steam in game overlay there's
nothing about languages
[Music]
here let's move it to to the German
Channel no no no no no
no I don't understand
German just no somebody just got to tell
me we had to do this and then we're done
this but I feel like I did this before
and it
quickly are on the main menu so you have
to run for the in first mod I hate it
when games do this that that you can't
access the proper
settings before going for some
intro oh okay I'm reopening the
game abstracting yes uh distract us not
abstract us distract us please from the
chaos this wasn't here before did I skip
the intro I didn't want to skip the
intro also this looks very English
again this is not German it's only half
German how do I
switch ah Spanish Polish Russian
Brazilian English
French English let's go with
English yes
uh yes the rest is fine I think I'll
just play full screen today I'm fine
with that
wow the music is
Chill wow wow I really like this track
new
game
Brazilian first Exposition for people
who don't know I played hola Miami 1 on
my channel there uh there's a
playlist check it out check it out Miami
Florida
Miami man this party stinks I [\h__\h]
hate these people how do you play this
game again I'm using keyboard right now
who invited all these who invited all
these
for wait that was not a duck rat that
was a swan I
think what do you guys think about
tonight we you going to do it I don't
see why not I'm sick of this
[\h__\h] let sure
super the we are in the car
right soia actually don't
us yeah let's do it Tom okay
okay wait who the hell where are they
who Am I who where are these people that
were just talking these
peeps I yeah these there's duck there's
bear there's whatever the rest
is what the [\h__\h] is going on how does
this work again WD and then something
with the mouse oh what is this
wa but they said something about car
right my my
brain
what you should really go back and redo
the midnight animal
intro no we got no time for
that I I I it should be the same as H
Miami one right I'll get into
it I'll get back into
it oh yes masks wait so
I only have one mask right what is this
roll
Dodge I didn't seem to be able to
choose okay I think I
remember right now I only have punch
[Laughter]
[Music]
right [\h__\h]
hell I'm already like okay okay okay
okay I used to be wait this is too loud
I used to be in the end pretty good at
this game okay but it took me a while to
get pretty good at it so
um it will it will be a moment where are
these people there there okay okay okay
okay
yeah yeah how did I pick it up how did I
pick it up how I how do I pick it up how
do I pick it up how do I how do I I
can't get out I can't get
out I can't get out I can't get out
why my right click right click stop
working [\h__\h] you I can't get out of it
why the door is
there was it spent oh my God look at
this
wa I got some kind of like rolling Dodge
is that what they talked
about my scouter what what's your what
that mean you
scooter
man it's starting off great oh man this
is too funny to
me come here come here come here come
here let me let me bunk you with the
door again both of you at the same time
please or at least the gun guy uh hi uh
uh wait wait
uh
ah uh okay [\h__\h] now the door won't open
well I guess he stays outside oh [\h__\h] h
ah
[\h__\h] uh this room only has one person I
think
so wait what was this oh God oh God oh
God yeah they hear it when I shoot in
the other room I remember I remember and
I could I could could silently throw the
gun I guess
a well nobody heard me now it seems
ah okay um maybe for now I take the bat
cuz it's
quiet yeah is this stronger than a bat
what do you think generally I think
they're both pretty pretty close in
terms of violence to hour limit sounds
good should be enough to clear the
tutorial what's tutorial are you telling
me this is not the real deal I have no
time for a
tutorial uh doesn't look like there's a
gun guy up there let me check out this
room first oh nobody in here
interesting music as freaking amazing as
ever how do I how do I wasn't there when
they're on the ground wasn't there a way
to uh like sit on them and then what
what the [\h__\h] are these
things uh and then like bum space okay
okay yeah sounds
familiar okay can I try to throw it at
him again or or he comes close enough
anyway I I cut his [\h__\h] throat
let's go
oh
hey I broke that
TV
okay nice nice nice I like this
beautiful tomato
color oh the last one has a gun at least
the last one on this
room build the
floor floor cleared sorry I saw the FL
and then my mind went to
beautiful go go go there's someone here
he's
smoking
oh we restart from this room thank God
okay BL
blti
V can
I silently
silently maybe small gun better
huh what the
door I thought there was a door or
something there Hol Tony 1 million let's
go
really thank you guys why did that song
grow so fast
damn okay okay apparently there's
someone down there and I can't see it
from here it's kind of rough cuz
sometimes it changes sometimes their
patterns change at least in hotland
Miami so hotland Miami one so who knows
maybe now oh okay now there's definitely
two
people catchy and loopable thank you I'm
glad you guys liked it all that much
this is rough I I I don't know man I
will just rush into a room I guess
oh he shot first he must have been Han
Solo Han Solo he's Han Solo Han Solo Han
soloo K I shift oh well that's not much
for I don't yeah yeah yeah okay okay
thank you thank you now now I've got all
the controls back in my brain thank you
guns guns
guns actually the right side room might
be the
best but these people going to see and
hear me
uh-oh
uh this is
difficult middle click to lock on lock
on to
what L on to what a to T yeah right
thank
you wait like this oh yeah okay I forgot
about that one too
nice oh now he has a big gun oh okay
okay so shift
oh what's with my
aim
okay uh oh small gun smaller smaller
gun okay I will shoot shoot
him I did
it
okay don't don't don't don't think
there's anything suspicious about all
these dead bodies dude everything's
cool
oh no um maybe a gun thank you
okay okay we just got to wait for him to
be in the right position and then I'll
shoot him out of the way too
and I think no that where did that even
I guess I guess okay I can't shoot like
this can
I I
love that's what the EMP I saw the empty
but I was wondering like what do you
mean empty what's empty the room is
empty what do you mean
ah okay now you know just I I just got
to I just got
to one after never uh get back into
this
okay who are we going to shoot who are
we going to shoot
Nice
Shot nice
shot I'm Tred so hard and come so far
but in the end it doesn't even matter
it's okay this is this is how it works
with hotland Miami you
repeat again and again you learn you
know you you become smarter
better God
ah so funny though Bam Bam Bam okay I
like this gun is this a SMG guys I know
what this is
now this is the proper way to shoot a
gun that goes you go
like riet
goes
yep yeah learn from GTA GTA oh oh oh
oh
hi today pure panic no calm yes Panic
yes you need gun's voice to over
by uh oh yeah let's just change this got
six shots but this one kind of spreads
out right
like
nice okay okay this one just didn't give
a [\h__\h] until
now we are going to teach him a
lesson nice oh he had a gun I thought
that was something else well I'm lucky
for
surviving oh wait I want this one 15 15
shots okay that's enough now we got some
dudes
here
uh but this the hallway should be
empty okay and door door door
strats ah he's walking
away music too oh there it
is should I wait for him to come to the
door
[Music]
or give give him a
minute I panicked I panicked but I
survived
I panicked but I
survived okay okay okay
okay
Yahoo nice okay okay
okay now one last room one last
room wait one oh one's in the bush Okay
two people two
people
uh and there's no door there okay I
could go from the side that has a
[Music]
door I know some people play this game a
lot faster they just run through and
through and through and through I I take
it a little bit
slower you know got to be
careful those
you a
[Music]
let's
go a lot of those sections were first
try okay only the hallway I had to try a
few times to get into the
groove yay go to car yes
okay car doco there it is my car is like
looks like
a like a like
a how to say graffiti
fied uh what what what do you call the
people that heal the people I asked this
just a little bit ago ambulance a
ambulance
van in in synth wave
[Laughter]
Vibes ambulance yes yes yes yes cuz it
has a ladder on
top mhm healing
people kills combo flexibility look at
look at all that what do I get don't I
get
say I used to get better scores I think
but okay ooh the Tony mask oh didn't we
have a Tony mask in the first game what
did it do does it do the same stuff now
hi
hello oh he looks exactly like the guy
before from haai Miami one I feel like
or is it's just the art style Maybe
Tony the one punchman he carried my
previous playr right but it got nerfed
he can't use
weapons
nah no I have to find a new favorite
mask no so
sad happy Halloween sir you ordered
three pizzas right that will be 1450 sir
your pizzas are on the counter to your
left enjoy your meal and watch out for
goost tonight okay
bye H does it have the pineapple and the
tuna thank you thank you thank you yeah
guess I'm the only one ordering that
combo combo that is cheap for oh my God
in Japan you pay like 20 bucks for one
pizza that's not even like American
size ooh Diner American Diner cute
oh that's eggs you guys are being
grilled and you're moving I like
[Music]
it living already you don't look too
good are you
okay but a stressful day you wouldn't
believe what they have me doing I should
probably go home and get some sleep all
right you have a good nice night yeah
you too sweetheart why am I here what is
this car doing here is this your car why
did I can't come here I just listened in
a little bit on their conversation
that's it go to car this car that's not
my car I don't think I should go into
strangers cars different oh is this a
different person than who I just
played he plays a bunch of characters
oh second scene what does what did that
just say homicide or
what what what what what is this
Supermarket oh the
music Let Me inspect that looks like a
supermarket I think yeah there oranges
hey
hey oh oh it's so
open
wait do they even attack me when I go in
hi oh
yes I I survived for quite a while
though
man let's go to the
left check your
car oh
oh
okay uh wait yeah bye yo yeah bye I have
to like
already check him
out or I hope for them to come over to
me one by
one well somebody heard that no no all
right
can I throw it over
those
quick
okay he's
circling he's pretty far
tooi maybe I'll
[Laughter]
go maybe I just go into the middle room
first
[Music]
man how did he see
me okay I think with that one we can
just uh kill him quietly honestly
but ah [\h__\h] Miss uh wasted one
shot
the guy from the right is not coming
this
time okay I'll go probably
inside
but now I would have to get my gun back
where did my gun go ah
here okay just got to just got to play
it smart you
know will he see
me ah
[Laughter]
oh my God this game makes me scream so
much it's so frilling I love it it was
so
frilling uh
I'm very very Ganky
today
okay okay
okay
maybe you want to yeah thank
you maybe I'll throw this knife at him
that should be a quick
kill but when cuz I'm not sure if it
goes for the close or like over
it did you see that
man I will try to shoot him when that
one guy is on the left side maybe but
m n maybe
oopsie Maybe not maybe this one
first bathrooms first H this is a
bathroom oh I didn't
realize guys I had the shittiest dream
which maybe I I was the reason why the
concert got
delayed I dreamt that I was about to
perform
somewhere um but like it was like not
really really well prepared like I
didn't have much info on like when I was
performing and like when it would start
and what how it's going to work there
was no rehearsal
whatsoever and I was like so clueless
yeah
and then I am like around the stage so
suddenly somebody comes up to me and
it's like girl you're performing now
you're performing now you have to
perform now and I'm like what the [\h__\h]
what what but but let me ask some
questions like first of all is there
like a like a backing track is there
backup vocals can I lip sync or so but
like they weren't hearing me and they
were leading me up to the
stage and they weren't answering my
questions because they were like what I
can't hear you what
and I'm I'm I'm like well [\h__\h] I can't
ask louder because I think my mic is
already on and the people are already
hearing
me uh and then he they just they just
don't answer me so I'm like I I just say
it
louder I'm like PR like pretty loud I'm
like uh can I lip syn though cuz I'm not
prepared and the whole audience heard
that right before my performance so you
can imagine that was very embarrassing
but I expected that to
happen so everybody hears that so
obviously it's not going to start really
well
because well that's not a good
impression to start off with and my
problem was also like I I needed the
lyrics uh and and and because I didn't
know my my songs by
heart this one's difficult yo um which
way does this door open
[Music]
open but then there were there were
monitors on the stage but not not in the
middle only on the left side and right
side so I was like very obviously
looking at the lyrics on the monitors on
the side that were also really
positioned very low so it was so obvious
that I was like
looking at the lyrics
there and then and then I also forgot my
dance coros as
well I was forgetting everything and
then that's not the that's more like my
problem okay but then they [\h__\h] it up
because the whole stage there were like
clothing hampers two big ass clothing
hampers in the middle of the stage and
then a couple of like office and other
random chairs were like uh like just
everywhere around the stage and and
other [\h__\h] other crap yeah and I'm like
what the [\h__\h] am I supposed to do am I
supposed to move this is nobody going to
move this [\h__\h] and I start moving it
while performing and then people start
passing through too like through my
stage like some random staff or whatever
or really random people just walk
through my stage while I'm performing
like they don't even bother with like
they don't they don't know what's going
on you know they don't they ignore the
fact that I'm
streaming oh my God I can't believe that
worked
uh let's
go
okay um yeah so it's like going really
badly already and I'm feeling like
really uh embarrassed and then suddenly
after like I roughly sculy performed two
songs they play some random rap song
from some artists I've never heard of
before and I'm like excuse me this is
not my song can you please play my
song and and nobody reacts they just
keep on playing the song and it's really
[\h__\h] awkward the audience is also
like man I feel bad for this girl cuz
like you know she's she's trying her
best and because because of that they
were like somewhat cheering for me you
know cuz they realized okay she's doing
her
best
yeah but it was going so badly and also
they were like really surprised when
finally I came out to perform in the
first place because apparently before I
even showed up on stage they were they
were like where waiting the audience
which was like several hundreds people
were
waiting uh for 3 hours already to have
somebody show up on the stage and
perform and then after the song the
wrong song was being played I was uh
eventually I gave up I'm like okay I'm
coming back later if you play my songs
again but not like this and clean the
[\h__\h] stage
man yeah
yeah yeah yeah and then even like one or
two hours later they still get didn't
get it together like what what was the
stream yeah every possible thing was
going
wrong yeah that was my dream that was my
dream last night ironically
funnily Nice kill nice clean and quiet
kill now let's take this
one
oh baby a
triple that was panicky I can't believe
I survived
[Laughter]
this let's get this
one ah I want to first
um Bonk this one
I didn't expect there was another one
down there but oh my God okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay my aim my
aim okay okay okay there's still two
more people down there and over here
nothing ah okay three people in
here
um
all right
then doorway deps y best strategy monkey
to I am monkey and monkey monkey monkey
monkey a well we should go left first
because the door on the right is still
closed but this one's open for some
reason um I'm just going to start
blasting any moment now
okay
spray and pay prey
yeah Mama
Mia okay okay and bnk and bonk oh okay
okay okay could have just smacked him
with the gun but no no no no
no okay how we doing
ooh they both come by the door wasn't
there another guy
though I don't want to get
[Laughter]
surprise that was marvelous that was
marvelous that was just marvelous go to
car okay not my car huh that was did you
see that oh my
god did you see how the how the door
went like and it helped me get the
second one too what even happened a
genius moment happened
okay [\h__\h]
satisfying oh
[\h__\h]
no drop your weapon and get down on the
ground now get
down don't shoot I'm a detective oh
that's me here's my
badge I'm sorry s l your weapons boys
here what's the situation in there we
heard
gunfire yeah you go look for yourselves
there's a blood bath in there man
sometimes I hate this city wait are we
corrupt are they corrupt are we corrupt
are we all corrupt uh am I am I a
corrupt cop H I'm not the wrong
door change voice AC say I don't know
what I'm doing hey I I got the second
floor first try didn't
I H you little [\h__\h] I don't believe a
thing that those people who grade
me yay first try I should get extra
points for
that it's so hard to get through the
doors what the [\h__\h]
Jazzy see for
cool why do I have to walk up so many
floors man I need an elevator oh is this
my my crib what happened here another a
murder case
huh yeah looks like you've got a serial
kill on your hands poo what same m o as
the guy we F last weak Mr you know I'm
innocent they forced me to do it yeah
right we haven't as if we haven't heard
that one
before the guy must be some kind of
psycho huh creeps me out I'm guess it
will make what was that it will make the
Press happy though goddamn
Walters with all the murderers in the
city I adopt the even K seems they need
Buckets of Blood before they even raise
an eyebrow this just seems a bit too
standard no go
details what this is standard I
guess God this city sure makes your skin
thick I was bored with fake skin you
want to see
it uh anyway have you guys found any
clues not really he got his throat slit
haven't found the murder weapon yet no
fingerprints no Witnesses nothing I'll
let you know if anything turns up
you do that I'll head down to the
station and get started on the
paperwork he said the thing what did he
say my bro voice is good thank
you oh I was born with fake skin what's
so special about that
phrase all right have a nice night
Sir we'll see about
that ah
right hello you Watson how's it going
welcome to the stream where I
scream very very incorrect yeah we'll
see about
that ooh the the bathtub is bloody too
unless it's something else I don't know
it's kind of purple hello can I talk
with you
no
M oh do you even lift I want to lift let
me lift I need to get stronger
okay I guess I'm
leaving is this no one more
floor I stream I scream I stream in
order to scream where's wait wait wait
here here here here okay okay my car my
car is cool am I like why do they have
police cars and I have like this fancy
car am I like from the FBI or
something or it must be like some very
special High ranked
officer
1989 a April 25th oh I'm I'm a different
person again did I just wash my hair in
the sink it looks very [\h__\h] dirty and
I look very thick what's that green
thing is that like a a ribbon on my
pants phone
[Music]
time oh I shaved
oh good day this is Eric from Miami Auto
Repairs I'm I'm calling to tell you that
we have finished
service hello who is this let me talk to
your boss
okay swing on by Northwest 12 a place
and pick hey I'm talking here we
guarantee you the best service in toally
Click don't you hang up on me damn it
show some goddamn
respect
uh did you guys write down the
address you know that's your job right
that's what you here for I can't
remember
that oh we have a cute car
too green get
in why is it so difficult in this game
to get into doors third scene hard
news oh lethal froze that's not bad
bad so whatever I throw is always a kill
aren't they like pretty much almost
always kill
anyway Jake The Snake that I don't see
any downside to that that sounds good I
like throwing sometimes hello what
SM
empty not all right that's
sus AO oh here we go this is where the
action is
happening oh oh
oh oh oh oh oh
Windows
um where is even I can't even enter from
there I thought that was a door but
no uh
okay
how I heard the door how good can how
far can they see did they see that
no
[Music]
okay ah n he saw me but only him I can
take
wait I couldn't go over there because of
the window but okay this is good I got
got it I got it I got
it okay okay okay okay no window here we
can bunk that one the other one has a
throwing uh possible throwing we do they
throw I don't remember if they
throw okay okay okay room clear uh be
careful there's a window there too
woohoo oh [\h__\h] I broke it can I walk
through it now
a I can't see that
far I can't see that wait when he walks
by wait now
he maybe
now okay oh it's a pretty big
room
ah
woohoo sick froze W absolutely sick
thickening oh I still have the knife
even I can't pick this up why
not oh
wait is the the lethal froze does it
make me not being able to have shooty
guns and uh or something like
that it didn't say so but that's what I
feel like is
happening I I'm pressing like right
click but oh oh oh oh oh okay okay okay
someone's
cominging all the way from
where I thought somehow he was coming
from the right side
[Laughter]
no oh
man he was like going to the left but I
guess yeah there was no
way n he could have maybe gone through
here and then for here and then for here
but oh
well okay okay I was ready for him but
not
quite okay should we make this one
actually see me because that was helpful
last
time
hi did he no he didn't really see me
okay now I'll do it without
you or maybe no
no let me try again I
need I think I need you or anyone really
actually they have to go for the door so
I could wait for them at the
door okay anyone
hi I didn't see I was looking at the
chat oh my God he just decided now is
the time to go for the
door oh my
God you know what I'll do I'll throw
this
knife at the right
moment hey now I can carry this gun
maybe the other gun was
bugged why you read us in the worst part
e no I was fine fine I survived I
survived I
survived I I found a good balance you
know actually I'm going to throw one
more normal weapon I think at him does
he come by my window my broken
[Music]
window okay I somehow wasn't able to
throw it uh I'll shoot him I'll shoot
him sorry long wait but then we don't
have to then we don't have to worry
about this one
anymore let's
go uh this room also already
empty and there's someone passing
[Music]
by
no
oh nice the right person came
by oh the gun guy didn't see me he
didn't see me he didn't see me he didn't
see me didn't see
me
uh window y kill him ah okay I have to
for this one I have to press the left
Mouse button I think with only fist you
can just press space space space space
space and that kills
him okay
ah this music is a
banger nice oh I can get it back through
the
window
nice
what I heard the doors I heard someone
coming through but and I tried shooting
but
man okay whoever wants to come see me
come see me I'm I'm waiting for you now
nobody saw me okay
sad
oh yeah yeah yeah it's okay it's okay
come over
bring it on
baby try
me why why did that happen what happened
I don't understand all your skills are
coming back yeah I think so I think it's
going very
well
taking him
out oh [\h__\h] I like how he doesn't care
enough to actually come over to where I
am
though I'll try from
here okay I think it has to
be why does it go for sometimes and
sometimes not maybe I'm unlucky with
like the angle or so
oh
hi
yeah
y that room up there scares me cuz they
have a window
too you know what I'll take this shotgun
M I can't can't Panic shoot with
that oh oh okay okay just just got to
make that one shot count all right all
right all
right yeah nice
okay
uhuh I AB be but they if
I if I do that they they will 100% come
from that room unless if they're as far
back as now but can I shoot over the
tables
M okay nobody noticed
wonderful one even left the
[Applause]
room now do I wait for him can I shoot
over the I wonder yeah fruit tables okay
oh they have a m tough cocktail over
there oh he left the room too okay well
then ooh ooh
okay now I got a rifle I got your rifle
I got your rifle and then I'm getting
your Wu later at
night I'll take everything that belongs
to
you m we want to kill the one with the
gun first and the rest I feel like I can
deal with quite
easily
nice nice m
[Music]
M hi see me see me see me perceive me
no
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay oh
now two guys
left maybe with gun cuz they got big
guns they got the big
guns
homie failed his perception
roll he
[Music]
did right at the
end
I'm sorry I'm
sorry okay it's okay it's okay it's okay
I can do this relatively fast I
think good Runo very good very
smooth have a feeling is not going to
come over
here
so
oh n then now we're talking that's what
I want to
see I'll wait for him I'll wait for him
here I swear I pressed I pressed right
click the moment he shot
me
a he had a gun I had no gun now I have
his
[Music]
gun
quick wow wow wow wow wow wow wow wow
wow w wow wow w w w w w w w w w w wow w
wow wow wow okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay I
think I'm okay okay okay girl not a la
la la la la girl I think I'm pretty sure
at this point I can report back to
go okay shot shotgun I'll take my
shot Okay Okay Okay
girl okay okay okay girl
superiority okay do I remember how to
shoot yes
24 okay ni
right M this room has so many
windows I could try to shoot some by
peeking through the
door maybe I
could
o
a
okay okay this is fine this is fine door
oh I did C somebody look at
that somebody's dead over
there you
you this is all safe right I
hope yeah pretty
empty see
me
nice oh oh one person left before it was
two people in there so I should be able
to take
this
[Music]
and go
yay
woohoo where is
up was it
here I guess I got to take the same
elevator
again
probably
yeah all right all right
uh yeah bye nobody no nobody hear me
okay e is that
what what are these
parts I don't really want to know do
I they must have extremely giblets what
they must have extremely soundproof
walls here damn it's not hear any of
this is this that room has no door
[Music]
huh
spanking thank
you bad dream was very B I was so pissed
off like I woke up and I was like so
pissed off even like 10 minutes later
after waking up even though I knew it
wasn't the reality but I was like so mad
like how can you have this happen man
these people in my dreams are so
unprofessional ah
Gamers have proven to have better
reflectors than non- Gamers
what am a
gamer so what went wrong what went wrong
just
now oh oh
oh I had no shots did I I had no shots
left I fake because I
pressed that's that's fine I enjoyed
that anyway we're going to recreate that
moment oh my God oh my God it's like
it's it's Yeah by because I'm like um
still focused on someone else so I can't
like uh those moments are usually
usually my downfall oh oh oh yeah no
ammo [\h__\h] no
ammo no
problem no ammo no problem I'll fix this
situation I'll fix it yeah
by yeah I saw I saw someone was coming
that's okay hey hey we're getting those
combos we're getting those combos
mhm I broke some glass there
apparently
yeah
no no that's
impossible that there was no
way
[Music]
now
okay rifle time and now we should be
pretty pretty
safe let me ex ex
inspect 50 more minutes guys and then
waa has to go to bed wow I
sleep 15 more minutes by the way
tomorrow tomorrow I'll probably stream
uh at the same starting time minus 1
hour I think probably and then we should
have no limit in length
Okay why am I so
crazy why am I so
crazy he was stuck my shots wouldn't go
through we were both
stuck
rigged absolutely
rigged what a
scam
I two more shots
mm who will I give them
[Music]
to
you
yeah
Fu how did so many people hear it
suddenly but thank God I switched uh I
switched G did you see I switched gun in
the last last last possible millisecond
holy
moly okay that was scary that was so
scary was it a killing did I throw it
away and then quickly yeah the the throw
must have caused some damage too okay
we're going to
go over
here and shoot
through
uh-oh he's
coming
yes yes
yes I think safe room safe oh window
still window there okay let's stand here
oh
oh okay empty and here
one uh and somebody there oh there's
like a Mafia Boss there uh they they
can't see me though cuz there's also
wall
okay anybody passing by the door maybe
would help
me
oh I don't want to risk
[Music]
it
oh okay
why is the gun sticking out of the wall
H
weird okay how do we do this here in
that room do we have to kill both or is
this a situation where like I only kill
the the guy on the
side not
sure just a white suit guy okay well
I'll try oh yeah it looks like he he's
holding him at
gunpoint cuz the gun he has a gun that's
like aimed at the at his face so maybe
the other guy is my
friend yay yay you're welcome you're
welcome I don't know who the [\h__\h] you
are but you're welcome you better repay
me I can't even get over to him and talk
talk to me
no that was
fun she says while walking by all the
dead bodies that are drenching the floor
in in crimson red that was fun wasn't
that
fun that was
lovely that was a walk in the
part see we're back to se guys mask
unlocked Irvin that's not the one we
just had right we had a snake but not
like
that e e what's this is he tattooing him
or what looked
weird hello what is this
place hi there welcome we can I help you
with I'd like to get it to too right you
got anything particular in mind I want
old Dix see right here on my shoulder
okay sure let me see here right how does
next's Friday sound he's he's got orange
hair and purple eyes doesn't that remind
you is that my is that
daddy is that
you Friday what do you mean you can't do
it now it has to be today today's a
special occasion I'm
celebrating Sorry boss can't help you we
all booked for
days oh is that so what kind of business
are you running here you just lost
yourself a customer you Russian [\h__\h]
whatever you say uh
boss
[Music]
uh no tattoo for me today fine I'll I'll
paint on myself with addings okay edings
that's that's the edgier way to do it
anyway
oh oh my God I love this
music let's [\h__\h]
go this is a b
[Music]
oh my God
yeah I can't stop
by okay okay
okay hey hey what let's go we're on the
time limit yeah but we also have to
enjoy the music
I didn't drink Red Bull but I feel very
much
so at least you know knowing that I only
have two hours I can completely Focus
all my energy that I would have for 8
hours into these little two hours you
know I'm going 400% right
now uh uh I'd like to welcome our next
guest on the show famous wait is this
Ellen The The J the J the
generous is that her name the gener the
generous I I don't know how her voice
was uh just really normal I think the
gener r okay okay I don't know that just
sounded wrong to me when I was about to
say
it she's also quite generous
no famous from critically acclaimed
movies such as blue ocean the calm and
land of trees here's Martin Brown hi
Martin how are
you I'm good now your latest film is a
bit of a step in a new direction for you
A lot of people are surprised by this
some are even calling you a sellout oh
wow don't say it like
that what is your response to that
s what do you mean well some are saying
that midnight animal is just another
slasher flick uh that's not how I say it
no don't add the music no no I jammed
for too long I've wanted to do this for
a long time U kill kids Str oh God you
mean in a movie you wanted to do this in
a movie for a long time right right
right right strangle them beat people's
heads in rip their eyes out then you
just listen to them scream see them die
in agony I finally get to do that now um
um um um
okay don't look at me like that oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] what I see this is a dream
right what do you me oh oh she's well
functioning Ellen is a robot or an alien
or something like that this all of this
it's just a dream
right I'm not sure I follow okay pause
kfp has arrived to the
scene you think this is a dream but then
maybe it's time to wake
up who are
you who am I I'm not the one being
interviewed here am I I think I should
be the one asking the
questions oh he turned into the pig
this movie you making you know how it
ends I believe there's a pretty big
twist at the end I doubt you will like
it in fact I don't think anyone will
maybe you to get
out before it's too
late I don't think so you're really
enjoying everything other people don't
you it's just a f
just a
film that's one way to look at
[Laughter]
it is that a sleeping thingy in the
bathtub oh this is the old apartment
who's the
lady she's got some badona dongs the guy
though that's not the guy we played in
hot miami1 I think pretty
sure
BL blah blah blah blah
H wait am I the pig now [\h__\h] no oh no oh
is that the phone but there's people at
my door what happens if I open for them
first
hi he's sweating he's scared hold it
right there sir oink yeah I'm here to
arrest you you need to come with us
we'll take you down the
station do you understand understand
what I'm
saying oink
wait wait should I
have oh no it Final Cut seems fine that
I didn't take the call but it's still
ringing it's still ringing in my
head it's still ringing in a different
room it's still
ringing it's following me I guess oh
wait is that a cell phone phone is that
a mobile phone that that would make more
sense but no no no no you're not hear it
what do you mean you don't hear it no of
course what the
[\h__\h] not bugged
okay ah maybe it's a dream we know what
you've been up to and you're going to
fry for it ah his mustache you the girls
upstairs giving us her full statement
right now soon they will be on their way
down for you until then you step of me
oh he's back to not
Pig I'd like to ask why you did that
what you did but you don't even know
yourself do you look at you you're
[\h__\h] completely [\h__\h] in the head
aren't you why else would anyone be
killing kids in the pig's mask huh it's
uh the phone in my head you should
answer it I'll say it again there is no
f a help me I don't see no phone and I
don't hear no phone okay it's just a
figment of your imagination you hear me
you're insane a maniac and soon enough
you will pay for your for your
crimes the t
phone you're not going to answer the
[\h__\h]
phone just act just act
please there's just no point talking to
you is
there
ah but isn't there a pink phone on the
table yeah look look it's
real you know what needs to be done he's
not even looking it's like he wants you
to kill him
click yeah I
understand my Thro hurts from screaming
a let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go all these cells are pretty
empty it says full cleared but can I go
in here no
[Music]
okay
I what is this red
thing I'm trying to understand these are
the feet these are the arms this is his
head right but he's on the
toilet oh no he's praying oh I looked at
it I thought he was looking that way
he's looking that way Ah that's is okay
I I was hoping that it wouldn't be
anything um
weird good good good good okay we have a
room here but there's no one there I
have to go through it
though oh
hello oh
[Music]
uhoh wait so we're wearing a mask now
the pig mask what does it even do for
[Music]
us I thought it was a shooty gun what
the [\h__\h] ah it's one of those
sticks nothing nothing oh okay he just
he just likes to wear his stupid Pig
mask
okay yeah okay of course it's going to
happen so sorry sorry sorry
sorry uh I
will if they come again yeah I will
Bonk I have no idea what just
[Applause]
happened I have no idea oh my God this
is scary because I can't see so far ah
ah
ah I want the deadly froze again please
that would be
nice uh no no gun no gun yes gun yes gun
okay let me hide here I'm scared there
was somebody coming right after there
you go oh they're in in a team
again
okay okay and okay
okay let's [\h__\h] go wo
[Music]
wo oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh oh that
sus let me let me stay in one room for
now and let me see
n this place is
Big this place is Big
[Music]
ooh
a nine shots nine shots is there someone
down
[Music]
here no
okay I think in this room possibly only
those two
left 15
okay n somebody's like over there
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
W gaming let's go okay this one's also
out side uh I I think I
prefer the smaller guns right now
[Music]
but all right all
right all right let's stay careful
though one
[Music]
person yay that was the clear let's go
woohoo oh SWAT
team oh I'm running out of male voices
guys stay in here and you'll be safe I'm
going to see what's going on don't open
the door until I get back no matter what
who am I where am I there I am
okay oh why is he so fast what the
[\h__\h]
I accidentally
shot what the [\h__\h] wasn't I able to do
that too or was it a specific mask I
already forgot how I did that I can't
even focus on him cuz yeah I really
can't even when he stands
still I have to use my actual skill
aim
uh-oh
uh-oh okay okay okay okay okay
okay
[Music]
um I'll take this one 15 shots is pretty
good oh he's coming he's oh maybe we can
but this is probably one of those
enemies that take more than one shot
though cuzz we had it in Hotline Miami
too they don't die with just one
hit
[Music]
a he also takes one shot to kill oh
really I need a
shotgun wait wait let's not attempt it
just
yet let's let's get
um these guys first if I
[Music]
can Ash at what time am I missing thing
okay somebody said shotgun against that
guy I'll try
it oh he's alive
though yeah okay okay okay I have to
once he falls down I'm forced to do that
so the other guy is in the way I have to
limit them I eliminate them
first
why are you so
stupid Oh my God there's a lot of them
coming yep and Bam all right okay okay
okay okay okay okay let's
go
I okay I'll do the thing that I said I
would be
[Music]
doing nice one left just need him to go
up if if he may ah
[\h__\h] ah [\h__\h] okay
careful let's
go okay now I can focus on the swats guy
this is this should be easy
then yeah if the big guy sees it when
I'm shooting or hears it then he comes
over
yeah so so strategical of course of
course no I just need him to come back
quickly please oh my lady is
here he out yeah he just he just dodged
it I respect
that wow he is very trigger
happy he is
[Music]
quick all right all right all right all
right he doesn't seem to notice as early
as uh his smaller fries that somebody's
shooting
takes him a
while oh wow that was that was close
close close close close
[Music]
close okay we'll try it again it was it
was good uh this the plan was really
good I just need to shoot earlier I he's
listening to music me too me too me too
after all understandable no why
what stop shooting man what I shot too
you saw him go down but
man hey hey where you going where you
going why is he going there
[Music]
now mhm come over here I'm waiting I'm
waiting oh hey that actually cleared out
the middle room quite
nicely ooh the door is in the but wait
we can totally use that door to our
advantage does he get bmed by doors too
because I can wait behind it he wouldn't
see
me oh my
God I might have just found the the most
golden
Strat
okay that never mind never mind never
mind never mind never mind never mind
how can I be faster than him man that's
shooting I have to anticipate him
maybe a [\h__\h] oh
uh
okay I ripped out his head let's
go oh can I take his guns no man that's
that's lame that's just
[Music]
lame 15 there you go this is what I
want y y y y
y Mommy Mommy Mommy Mommy Mommy Mommy
Mommy Mommy Mommy Mommy Mommy Mommy
Mommy Mommy Mommy sorry Mommy sorry
Mommy sorry Mommy is there someone in
here yeah bye by by by oh
[Music]
oh around the corner
Strat oh Mommy Mommy Mommy Mommy Mommy
hotline me at Miami mommy hold mummy
Mommy
Mommy oh yeah
byby nobody's there right by
byby okay okay what's with this who do I
kill wait there's still people up there
uh can I just walk into that
room I'll take care of
[Music]
them but they might hear it when I shoot
here
uhoh
uhoh ah no
y yeah [\h__\h]
n yeah it's okay it's okay it's okay
it's it's learning by doing yeah
[Music]
bye M Mia
hi and three and four and and five and
six and seven 1 2 3 4 5 6 7even you make
me feel like 11 oh I got a I got a five
times combo achievement let's
go
ah you're
lucky it's your lucky
day ah [\h__\h]
oh he's
coming let him let him through let him
[Music]
through oh got
him
okay away with this gun and we
take shotgun let's kill the big guy
again
[Laughter]
ah
[Applause]
o one and two and three and four five we
need the maximum Potential from this oh
he even came from the room below I think
nice six what about the seventh guy
huh there it
is y let's go
[Music]
oh I was too scared to do that right now
right there let me get rid of the door
here great combo
combo guess shotgun is one hit and not
for him I still have to rip off his
head go go go go go go go go go go go
go yeah all right all right right all
right all right wait let me get the 15
shotgun there it is I remember I
remember my inventory keeping
inventory which which where do we
go okay all empty and okay how did I do
this oh
yes
it came from
above what I thought it was
safe
what
oh nice shots nice
shots I guess they heard it me and m i I
thought it was empty all right all right
okay I think it's already good enough
to go for the big guy what the
[\h__\h] it's pretty empty
here man the weather is
[\h__\h] the shotgun dude in the room down
there go go go go ah
get he came it at the worst possible
moment are you kidding
me you're pissing me off big
mistake why why why why why why why why
why why why why why
[Music]
[Applause]
why
my shots
are not so good okay there we
go it's okay it's
[Music]
okay nobody come now don't don't don't
don't disturb me I'm doing something
important right now
okay uh uh
okay
who where did whatever was it this guy
maybe that came out of nowhere when I
was doing my
business pro
possibly
oh God Dam
it this level is difficult because you
have to a take care of so many things
why are you guys not checking for your
dude
man oh nice
shot
oh come around the corner he he more
more more yeah yeah yeah yeah keep it
coming keep it coming I want my
combos ma
[Music]
combo
nice smooth though right welcome welcome
to the party
Raiders okay am I ready for no not yet
actually [\h__\h] I missed
it come back come back come back come
back oh not now
wait wait wait wait big guy big
guy right sometimes you just got to go
to them where is this I don't see the
shotgun is
it
ah no shotgun ah in here ah cuz he died
inside
oh
okay okay I just got to I just got to
shoot early the the the key to win is
for me to camp and wait for him already
around the
corner and get that get that finger
ready on the
trigger seven do this one have more 14
yeah okay
um
n he doesn't want to walk over here yet
I'll
try
ah I don't like it I don't like it I
don't like it at
all I want to kill this one first before
I go
[Music]
down ow where are
they
no no no no no no I shouldn't do that I
shouldn't do that because then I'm too
slow to turn around
oh
yeah yeah
bye oh that was two in
one
come on come on come
on no don't don't stay in that room what
are you doing come down here don't you
hear the
commotion it's a lock
commotion welcome to the lock commotion
it's a love
commotion n
[Music]
oh
nice
ah how how did that guy he was 1 M away
how how did he ignore his friend's
death
I don't see it I don't know it I don't
know I don't know what's going on is his
attitude
[Music]
I come on waiting for
you he went behind me
how I need a partner in crime to cover
my back
[Music]
man okay okay no more right no
more a
close
ah isn't that what we're here for yeah
but I shouldn't be looking at chat all
the time to see your warning I
can't there is one character where you
have an AI Ally
really I got to find that mask then I'm
guessing it's no oh is it a character
then not a mask okay okay
okay
the swans
oh oh
no maybe I should take that head home
and serve it as
meatballs all right today's pasta of the
day is ooh
[Music]
nice
Bon I I'm really grateful that he came
out of that
[Music]
room okay safe safe safe safe safe okay
okay we're back to this point
now what do I do do I need to clear the
rest of the upper area because I see
like you know this room already this one
where the where the interesting stuff is
going
[Music]
on yeah
okay I wonder what will
happen n
nice
ah he
okay at least they don't hear it I
thought they would hear it that's why I
kind of chickened out
before and now and now and
now like there's still people oh wait
that guy is still alive
too do I kill these guys and also the
chunky one does he also take more than
one
hit I don't know should I go into this
room first what's that I don't know I
don't want to mess up again
[Music]
uh more than one use a shotgun o uh
there's there was was there another oh
yeah is this the one from before five
shots ah there's another one over there
with more shots but now uhoh this is
unexpected I didn't think this guy would
come out of that
room and shotguns don't seem to have a
big reach do
they I just need this one shot
[Music]
maybe they can't they just spread they
don't they do in this game okay okay
come over
[Music]
please but when I have him then the
other guy is alone in the room so that's
that's pretty good
um
[Music]
uh-oh uh-oh uh-oh uh-oh
uh-oh I lured him
out don't know where he is uh-oh okay
okay this is
[Music]
good he did die I was like oh I didn't
get him I guess oh get keys
oh and then I I walk into that room
without a weapon or
what wait oh no I
here get
her wait can I take a proper weapon
though what is
this what is this is this the
[Music]
key I'm guessing I have the keys now but
okay cuz it's it says get
her you're good to walk in
okay what do I
shoot oh I
can't I can't focus on
them hey B what if I [\h__\h]
oh oh that was
scripted okay okay
okay I'm not your [\h__\h] go
friend wow chill the [\h__\h]
[Music]
out arer read it's scripted right it's
scripted right this was supposed to
happen don't give me that R2 restart
[\h__\h] make me think I [\h__\h] up I
didn't cut oh no need for a retake that
was
perfect good job guys it's so believable
I could almost think that guy really
died looks like looks like he sustained
some
serious emotional damage and physically
only got a few more shots to shoot
before we can move on to the editing
also kind of ironic to say that with all
those guns being shot damn I'm so funny
why don't you go grab something to eat
oh yeah I am hungry while we put up uh
the new set Pieces Just make sure you're
back in 30 minutes okay time's money
money's time
you heard him Mar time to get
up mar mar oh my God stop messing around
please oh my God you're such a you're so
exaggerating every time you're sick just
like
always it's just a [\h__\h] cold
okay you just have the sniffles don't
act like you're
dying this is why I wanted to kill you
anyway so thank God you're dead now you
just so
annoying second act Rising
oh Rising
Phoenix
uh oh is this like a oh
courtroom now the defendant claims that
he was order to commit those murders
free messages left on his answering
machine did you inv Sate these
claims yes we did and what did you find
well the defendant's answering machine
was empty the tape had been removed did
you find anything supporting these
claims of threatening phone calls no sir
we did
not you see no further
questions you saw you found no physical
evidence supporting my client's clamps
then what about the phone records surely
the police would have no difficulty
accessing such
information indeed we did investigate
the defendant phone
records and did you find any calls on
the record that uh should could support
my client's
clamps we did Sir the defendant seems to
have received phone calls that match the
time frame which He suggests but did you
manage to dress this calls if so where
did they come
from
which oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
[\h__\h] we Trace their calls to a nightclub
called the golden truck stop yes now my
client clamps that he was qued by the
Russian mafia to commit the crimes for
she is now being prosecuted do the
police have any knowledge of ties
between the golden truck stop and the
Russian mafia that could support my
client's
[Laughter]
clamps it's supposed to be kind of
German yeah but [\h__\h]
around the venue that has been linked to
several mob related crimes in the past
yes
however oh the music
M that would be all thank you D no
further questions oh who is
this I can't even hear what he's saying
because there's so much hair in his
mouth
cute the witness way may step down the
court will now Beed proceeding will
continue tomorrow at 11:00 a.m.
meanwhile the defendant will remain in
police C
cust who is this next character I'm
orange I like
it I like it oh is this oh my God the
phone is it
[Music]
real you have reached the Miami Police
Department how may I help
you uh uh uh
uh uh voice uh
uh I don't know man uh I would like to
talk to the detective Paro tell him it's
from
Evan one moment please
cck what do you want Evan I'm in the
middle of something here how many I'm at
the courthouse doing research do I sound
uh how is on that mask
Maniac man
maniac maniac was more British Maybe
Australia n there's no
way not even
close I think there's a a
a hunch a hinch a pinch a a little bit
of uh of a howdy there
yeah uh uh uh what's that got to do with
me well they mentioned the golden truck
St something about M now you made me
very insecure guys
something about more connections I don't
even know man so I was wondering if you
know anyone there that I can talk to
that's privileged information you know I
can't talk about things like that look
I'm really busy here don't be like that
now you owe me won
remember fine go to the Northwest 37
Aven you ask for a r pet TR and tell him
I sent you can't promise he'll talk but
it's the only name I God don't call me
at work again okay no more famous
a why not why not why not I guess I got
to watch more um young Sheldon to pick
up the the
beautiful
Texas
feeling where did I go I couldn't fit
through ah ah oh oh there what there
wasn't even a door how was I supposed to
know hello
are you guys going to kill me
no oo oh child oh can I join this circle
I want to be part of something too man
hello oh
protesting he looks like a dead beat
let's get into my yellow car I have to
end streaming in 2 minutes I can't get
in there we
go is it saving 15th scene first trial
hey I got pretty
far in 2
hours pretty good pretty good it was
fun it was lots of fun but now now wa
has to go sorry I would have liked to
stream longer but wa has to
go
no two minutes Speed Run attemp no no no
no don't go um
uh
uh yeah I'll see you
guys was there anything on Twitter yet
like I I've been I've been streaming so
I don't know if there was any recent
updates let me
Che Hol life production nothing yet
okay okay I think they're still working
on it you know it's it's quite late in
Japan right now but they're still
working on it you know they're working
for the
night noisa hi did you get a nap
huh did you get that
nap I hope you got a little
nap but yeah now in Japan it's like
uh 300 a.m. I think they're still
working on it so please give them a
little bit more time I guess to I mean
for you guys for like na and European
people we're still you know uh in the
middle of our day so we can stay up
longer for the
information
please please sleep if you go to sleep
and I'm going to go so that I don't get
bonked okie dokie let's wish let's hope
for the best for
tomorrow
uh I hope I hope the servers will be
stronger
tomorrow maybe got to download more RAM
or something and then German we myselfie
does in tomorrow I will stream at the
same time but 1 hour earlier if that
helps you in terms of time zones cuz I
don't want to tell you my time time
thing is not going to help
probably uh and then and then we should
have no time limit I don't know what
we'll stream but we'll see that tomorrow
okay we de spontaneously and in
byebye maybe how long I Ami too again
maybe maybe yeah it's good that it was a
short time anyway because I scream and
the thr H okay bye-bye thank you for
watching
[Music]
me I have to go have to go
got to
[Music]
go
thanks guys love you cho cho
cho cheer for
me tomorrow maybe
bye-bye