[Music]
me
okay i'm moving over
and
howdy hello
by the way no i did not sleep in no one
slept in today
no no nine pm it's excuse me it's not
always
it's not always people sleeping in guys
not always
not always welcome back
it takes two it takes two it takes to
attack
we finish this yes we should be able to
finish it today
yeah and we've gotta be expert expert
cooperators
yes today we're starting out with uh
these new weapons i have a sickle
shouldn't you be the one with the sickle
can i cut that whatever you have here
oh nasty oh
what is this fruit is this a dragon
print
kind of looks like it huh oh wow
nice
yeah so supposedly today is the last
episode of our it takes two
collaboration guys
i hope i hope it will be uh
successful right what is this
hopefully it ends well with a happy
ending or something i can't shoot
something
is that a water pistol that's a
waterproof
oh i have two weapons do you also have
two weapons
um i don't think so with l2 with the
left one
i have one episode maybe you have
something else too
l2 like okay for me it's l2 i can
i can aim the i mean all i can do is aim
oh because i aim too but i have i have
something to shoot with
neither hold on i think you can hit this
thing with a sickle
yes yes wow wobble wobble oh my god you
wow
[Music]
let's make it wet there we go oh flowers
that was really nice need more water
no not brown cute so
so we have a lot of collabs this week
callie i sure do three collabs yeah
yeah there's a lot going on huh what are
we doing here
well yeah um i thought maybe i'd grab
this but it seems like i can't
ah hey oh yeah there's something up here
uh how do we do this again i forgot
i did i didn't die thank god
what do you mean no game audio it's just
too quiet i think wait let me let me it
just
it is there but it's just too quiet uh
game audio oh nice
spinner well now you guys should hear it
this is amazing what did you just lose
weight in the game
he said he's yeah we can so if you go to
that plant that you just planted you put
water on it and you ground pound it
i can't magically transform into oh you
can't oh well just kidding
hmm i realized last minute i couldn't do
it that way
still a little bit too low oh man
one second fine adjustments
and here here here okay
here okay
a little bit in the red for me so like
that okay
okay okay muffled why would i be muffled
um you don't sound that different to me
than usually mike muffled eh that's just
discord being stupid
maybe sorry just sorry i shouldn't say
that this card is always nice to us and
always watching your streams hello this
is god we love you a way i can fix
it hold on i might know a way to do it
but i'm still holding this for you so go
ahead and grab it
that was the one hey thank you you did
something there for me thank you
no problem here let me see if i can do
something real quick
no problem
i have to pause yeah hold on nope
we love you this is good
can you hear me oh my god uh yeah you
made a voice
what oh yeah that's much worse
hello hello hello hello robot
kelly howdy robo murray
am i really a robot yeah quite the robot
robotic i don't understand because deep
in your heart you've always been a robot
yeah that's my secret oh my gosh
here let me see here i bet i can hear it
yeah for whatever reason discord doesn't
like it when i use my
usual oh yeah
maybe if you rejoin the channel maybe
it's better i don't know
here all right one sec beautiful
i don't think it'll sound better to chat
though because this is where i was
before
hmm that sounds good to me now though
it's just luxury problems
hello hello yes hello they say it's
better now
much better really that's weird no the
thing that they were complaining about i
heard it just now is
again but yeah it's not that bad
oh my god holy moly
it's all good i don't think there's an
issue
with yours yeah i think there's there's
also maybe
like 10 people in chat that are trolling
uh so
we gotta take it with a grain of salt
jay chad said that she thinks he sounds
good
i hate this character
that's why we're here now and i'm
helping you with your garden
yeah that's a crazy garden yeah
oh this is tightening up my garden huh
yeah oh pumpkins
here if you if you water this then
i think i can turn into this cacti
[Music]
look at your face that's cute
you look cute oh that hurts me oh that
is pretty
cool uh-oh time to kill him
down you go away with you i'm gonna
fight them
oh how many is this endless
no i think there's several things oh no
no
it's kind of endless really
maybe only maybe they stop when you stop
being a cactus
hmm yeah cactus kind of fits you no
longer exactly
yeah kind of prickly huh i get where
you're at what you're saying when you
say that
[Music]
really cute but gotta be careful when
you touch them
i can read between the lines kiara turn
up the audio
even more okay oh yeah
uh can i do it here
like in the game master volume all the
way up
wait did that really did i apply it
ah okay where is you
this is maximum can you guys hear it
it's gonna be a pretty flower
it's good they say good better yes yes
move the chat okay how about your hair
is better right okay
nice okay have we do we have everything
down now
whatever you do it should be okay you
could water it i want to do a flower
i want to be a pretty flower
[Music]
it feels good to let them explode with
all that juice coming out of it
wow look so juicy
hang on i need you sorry i'm gonna pause
you really quick
okay phantom power on
yeah it's on it should be okay all right
whatever i don't care this is how it has
to be for now
yes you sound normal to me really now
i'm normal to you it's gotta be
something weird with obs or something it
doesn't matter we gotta try and beat
this game today i'm gonna make this into
a flower
really really would like to be able to
beat this game i think you can become a
flower now
i can alright i'm gonna be a flower
oh can you do something with uh
that this thing here the phones
i'll give it a shot oh or do i no wait i
have to hang on to you maybe
you're a beautiful special flower no i
cannot hang on to you
eat the foreign eat them it looks like i
can't
sadly hmm um if i
put leaves here is there a way you could
get rid of the thorns i wonder
what leaves nope
how do i
one second trying to remember how to put
out leaves
okay extend turn grow leaves is triangle
and face oh
i don't think we can do anything here
sadly let's see i can ride this one but
then
yeah i can't go past it
yeah it's too bad but i think we just
need to head the other way
cauliflower cauliflower
oh wait i can just walk on your leaves
oh yeah
oh i can't anymore okay no problem no
problem
i'm gonna walk on your leaves beautiful
leaves they're so
beautiful they're right
cute cute cute you're so you're so
you're so you're so thank you kelly i'm
gonna get
over here somehow oh thank you that
looks thirsty
yeah you're first thing yeah it looks
fine
drink all the water you oh
as a flower here
oh i can't really go anywhere
oh oh you can go so far now
can you come over to me actually i think
you need to give me a lift
i'll give you a lift gotcha right on
your right side
okay hello are you so cute look at your
face
okay yeah and now we can go over to the
left side and i'll get you over here
somehow
oh no can you just land where your face
is or you land where you were planted
i have to land where i'm planted all
right well then
uh yeah to the left please taxi
okay to the left
oh bring it
[Music]
back detoxing there you go
the california oh [\h__\h] the cauliflower
taxi
oh man all natural
mm-hmm
okay i'm gonna wait here and on your
last leaf over here before you turn
around
okay can you now make a curve to the
left
yeah oh uh is that your maximum
likelihood
yeah gotta make a smoother curve than
that huh
okay here we go uh
yeah i guess a bit more to the back is
fine
okay a bit more to the back more more
kitty kitty
i'll try is there something to hang onto
now
maybe that one okay
oh no but that distance
you know what you can already make that
curve like
nicely so you uh reach the other side
and i'll try to jump on you
while in the air with this thing okay
maybe that way
yeah you don't okay
okay yeah when you're
when you're growing those leaves yeah
okay let's see if i can jump on one of
those
should be possible
okay wobble wobble wobble
excellent now become a flower again no
flower
it's cauliflower wait wait wait no wait
wait wait don't move don't move i want
you to look at your face look at that
really it's everywhere how could i laugh
oh dad's so cute
i was too focused on your beautiful face
we just have to chop it all up right
well i hope it's that simple
yourself those leaves are always like
kind of going back
i have arrived so let's see what can i
do for you here mrs califlower
i see something go away i see something
wow did something change yeah the the
phones are gone nice that reminds me of
a breath of the wild with like the
uh the the evil stuff mm-hmm
yeah a little bit huh oh oh
the water open its mouth and i fill it
up with water
open your leaves please open up
teamwork oh yeah
did you hear that yes huh
did you see that yes a friend i don't
know
it's a friend that looks pretty
time to howdy some weeds cody what's up
wins
code yeah
yes so i'm holding on to the enemy okay
so you can beat it up
okay okay
i'll be right back i got attacked too
much
are you okay i'm dead uh-oh
okay i'm holding them i'm beating him
yeah
get him
okay bye-bye yeah the cute little flower
snake
how adorable oh cute yeah definitely
please don't die
yeah they really really kind of got me i
need to dash a little more no
why is the book also the loading screen
all right we got it this time
all right yeah
[Music]
it's on a hunt
all right i'm getting them
ugh
[Music]
they are really harming fart things nice
you did it
we whipped them into shape didn't we
yeah
good one yeah oh okay
small trees oh the floors are opening
next up greenhouse spa there's a spa
onsen
onsen episode
oh i thought that was corn but it's more
disgusting than that
yes um we can indeed get a massage
i'm not too sure about this one
i love the relaxation that is pretty
weird but i do like caterpillars they're
pretty adorable
you don't need massage already what do
we have here
yeah i want another massage a little
higher a little higher
they are really good at massages yeah i
feel it everywhere what
oh just to let you know i'm amazing this
is
weird really close to being in a horror
movie actually
um time to stop
okay this is interesting that's adorable
cali enjoying it a bit what are you
talking about
they're eating your foot nails
yeah all the dead skin off the bottom
that's awesome
ah how elegant how beautiful now we
chill
and out this is nice reminds me of
hokkaido
i wouldn't want to come back me too
i've been thinking about it recently we
should have done this first we did the
wrong order
here we go dad's nice and clean
your turn this was about time
yeah off of me nice
nice worked really hard until now
oh gosh all right he's cleaning between
all my nooks and crannies
indeed indeed that was nice cute i
wonder though
uh it's just it's for small bugs
who built that uh maybe dad
you built an onsen for small buckerino
that's so cute
i mean it would appear so ah i can hit
this
oh i'm coming and you can beat the
awkward out of this
all right
slash
there we go nice very nice and the path
opens once again
[Music]
oh the vines are still kind of running
crazy around here greenhouse is infected
it looks like it spread from over there
oh can you get your freaking filthy paws
off of me no
no i didn't plant that are you sure
what about the first flower you planted
in the greenhouse
you mean joy
it turned into a monster joy i didn't
know you named yourself oh no
well just that first one um
you know i i just wanted to make sure
that joy would always be part of our
own oh dad
code sweet it's sweet it's it's also a
little embarrassing but it's very sweet
at the same time it's it's more sweet
than anything i would say still
time cody kill the infection and make
your garden
bloom again okay book you're right come
on
we have to stop this come on man that's
cute
they're both cute i really hope things
work out for the best for them
i think it's gotta go to the floor happy
end is coming
thank you for helping me out ladybug
that's why everything's overgrown and
kind of like there's like dead fruits
everywhere
yeah dad why you forgot your garden
very sad oh there's a mini game should
we do it
did you see it i didn't see it uh
i didn't see anything
oh well we are trying to get this done
today
so we gotta get it done tonight yeah
we're not
spending too much time on minigames
today
drink drink drink nine yeah get your
drink on
beautiful spa relaxing music right now
in the game
huh wow i
guess oyster whoa
mario mario
way
all right open sesame
i
a lot of his friends keep
oh there's more of them
[Music]
come back to me i'm back
all right there's more trouble look at
the shield hey
oh no that's a big army oh my god
[Music]
the game on the playstation before it
does that sometimes no
how do you like this weed whacking god
[Music]
hang on hang on hang on i got i got it i
got it i got it i got it
oysha not over yet all right i'm holding
it okay
and he did does he have another friend
or not
please no more friends please just
just more beating up there we go okay
i think i'm gonna go turn up [\h__\h] tv
okay looks like a dead end
it is
where are you hey i know
ah it's got a little bit too many times
i don't really like spice it kind of
looks cute but also not
cody what are you doing that's adorable
beat up the ghost
dad maybe next time i'll let him get
away with it this time
can we hit you can we ride the spider
get over there
a ride to the other side
cute and creepy yeah i love it
okay oh
it's for you me oh thanks
for me that's so sweet what about you
uh we'll find another one oh look
dad's dad cares about mom
i'm on the spot
[Music]
what comes out of that oh
i wonder what i gotta do what is that
is that me catching like can i catch up
on
okay i can fill up something here again
oh i see
those things okay okay
you really see the progress in maine
cody's relationship you know you know
right you a beautiful thing to see
freaking adorable i miss going hiking in
the forest
hey
right the last time i went driving in a
forest is like
a spider get it out of there about 123
years ago
wow that's a long time ago
hiking in the forest i prefer hiking in
mountains though
oh you got a spider now tell come on
[Music]
they're friends looks like they know
each other
oh thanks that worked out
very convenient
you know i never thought i'd ride a
spider through our own garden
remember we talked about going on a
jungle yeah
i guess this is the closest we're gonna
get oh it's even better
we've got spiders we do
a little bit dizzy though
aimweb r2 this book this is r2 my whip
is r2
[Music]
are you oh naruho i see i
i'm getting dizzy
are we going the right way i think so i
landed somewhere
yeah it's kind of ooh oh oh oh oh oh i
think i'm starting to feel sick again
we good yeah
huh now we're wrong
i've never had a pet spider you're just
so
cuddly i had good identity one of the
pets by them
i can see that but i i i
i i told her she should get something
more like like a dog
or a cat everyone's got their taste i
suppose
i like komodo dragons as pets oh
nice yeah they basically look they're as
close as you can get to dinosaurs
as you can these this day and age
[Music]
yep they also are able to eat um
even larger mammals like deer yeah
rose was here to see this that must be
huge komodo dragons then
yeah they are very big very much like
dinosaurs is i wish there was a komodo
dragon v tuber
oh my god this is oh my god there
brother he already is
still here
i would like to i would like to meet
them
there we go
oh
[Music]
a little different speaking um
you had that collab how was it
were you nervous i was nervous at first
and all the way until the end but
now i feel like we're going to be able
to play a game again like and i won't it
won't be as
it won't be as nerve-wracking that's
good yeah you talked a little bit
afterwards too and it
wasn't so bad i don't know why i thought
senpai would be scary but
yeah it was one of the nicest one of the
freaking nicest senpai
i've ever met despite you know
fulfilling me a little bit in in
fairness i kind of asked for it let's be
ready
something crazy is going on here right
now yeah yeah yeah
you've got to fill it with water get to
know
the first collab is always very
nerve-wracking indeed
that's how it be why i would simply be
scared oh because dragons my dog
but i didn't realize that i had i guess
this bias
i remember my first collaboration with
peculiar senpai
i was so nervous i also i i like
cried a little bit as well
yeah you got to wash off this purple gun
if you could splash some water on it i
bet it might work
where did some good memes go or is it
only
i mean [\h__\h] ready
depends on your definition of good there
were some that had some clever
undertones some clever ideas
i see you you know how i am not much of
a maymay person
in the first place not really my not
really my brand
um of humor but but i can understand why
others like
you know i hope you guys continue to
have fun
i think you just got to spray water
maybe really well
yeah i was like there was nothing left
there
did i wait let me see maybe
somewhere here yeah maybe on that bridge
if you could
oh it clears it up yeah but only for a
little bit so you got to create a
password
right here on this side okay okay
thank you i'll make a little path for
you
the most active person out of her life
english on reddit
oh yeah probably i've been seeing some
good memes every once in a while i'm
stuck over here
yeah that's good i just i guess
i don't look at the memes too often
i think that's okay i'll take care of it
i'll share the good memes with y'all
sure oh i can't shoot that far uh
i think you missed something before that
can you pull that wheel i think it's a
wheel
i bet i can here
let's see what i can do yeah from up
there maybe
someone
it looks like it because there's like a
like a like a green dot
on the wheel looks like it's for you
oh oh that's that's me that is like
that's that's
up here but then here on the wheel there
is a dot
you are also a green dot but this is
also also has a green dot
yeah somehow you must reach it
maybe i'm not on the wrong maybe i'm not
on the right this should be it
can i grab you you're so close oh maybe
right rabbit
sorry um
from the ground from the closest
platform
[Music]
let's see yeah from there there we go
i still feel like i should have been
here
i know should i not go up here what
what what what ah there we go okay here
we go
i think now i can come over here to the
right again spider
oh all right
water them up
pretty adorable adults adoptable
yeah this is a very cute part of the
game
oh no oh squirrels
something what do you want me to do the
squirrels are coming back
mama come on quick mate get up no we're
friends
mama tell tell your mom that we like
helped out and whatever so that your mom
won't kill us
she's their mom what a cute oh
it depends how you define cute in this
species the wife
kills the husband
do you heard that kelly yeah
i like that yeah i like that idea
sounds interesting let's go yeah instead
of you killing me
this is funny funny
indeed yeah let's see
i wonder where we can go from here
oh no buddy you could have won me
yeah same destiny yeah
it's fine okay well fine stuff
whatever they are we need to take them
out okay
here comes us all right down to the
ground
okay it's like that kind of thing
it looks a little bit i'll try and drag
them
because they got some tentacles going on
yeah
yeah you right i got too much fantasy
maybe
enough here i'll cut you all down
okay yeah there we go almost almost
again
[Music]
bring him down bring him down
another one here we go
the small ones were in the way it's okay
one's down no too fast
why you leave the vans come down oh
there we go
okay here we go
what that is really this whipping sound
yeah snap snap
oh thank you and this one is dead yep
there goes one
[Music]
to the ocean it took your soul along
with it
you're good it's fine back to life now
you finally got one good job oh no
oh no hate that sea creatures got to get
out of here
ah i know the plants are way out oh i
could turn into a cactus well i
should do that oh here we go now i can
i'll hold them up crazy critters the
cactus man
has a rock oh god cody oh thank you
out i i i see while you're shooting them
i have
i got you no worries
almost done here
[Music]
very good
yeah you can stop being a cactus
although you look really cute as a
cactus
i was i was going to say that is very
adorable as a cactus
here we go the cactus man oh bubble wow
oh dad cactus man from now on
[Music]
audit what what's wrong with you stupid
plan
now there we go
i'm sensing another boss fight coming up
soon
oh where are we going
oh yeah are you sliding again right
now
[Music]
that was pretty fun
you have so many tiny bugs moldy
yeah yeah you made doubt oh is that
kelly
did you see that i saw something what
what was it i couldn't tell have you
ever seen a ball in real life
i don't know about the friendliness
though if the squirrels are as crazy as
they are in this game i don't have high
hopes for them
just saying yeah i'll be but pretty by
the blood starting not to like this
do we really have to go in i don't see
another way out here oh
nice oh please don't eat me
i think you got it
kind of cool though i like it oh i
should do something here okay
push push
yeah i told you they ruined my garden
it's sleeping i got rid of them
clearly slice him up
sashimi oh no
please i don't think that would taste
very good that's definitely not edible
move carefully sorry to break my neck
there we go broke it all right oh it's
looking so cute so peaceful
too there's a bunch of them wake up
oh my god oh they should sound sound
ometer
oh no the shells though
right i have not to walk on those
there's some grass over there
they're actually quite cute yeah you see
those teeth and claws
i would say that's cuter than the spider
tail
big sleepy monsters oh
is this how british people stay at
purpose
that's not really oh man
yeah you're close you know what close
enough
we made it i think
i really like british accents you know i
can't make you myself
[Music]
hey cody i'm glad you want to take care
of the garden again
i really want to get rid of all these
pests and infections mm-hmm
don't belong here let's keep going then
yeah no problems ooh what's this
can i turn into a big shrub oh
let me try
[Music]
very
you're the one who isn't a sneaky bush
where are you am i able to go under them
oh i guess i can't i'm sure they like
that as much softer than those stupid
shells
yeah i bet they like it
wait a bit oh yeah go right here for a
minute
oh it just flipped over nice so many
what that you
just sneezed on me disgusting deal with
it and
carefully mate okay carefully
yep what what if i start the moles
i don't know what would happen i kind of
wanted to try it out
oh no oh god kuznetsov eh
you don't want to try it out i don't
want to wake them up
hey what if they're really nice
oh wait don't go so fast okay okay i've
got a cute nose look at the cute nose
and those waist guys
oh there's a little envelope all of them
they're ruining my garden with their
save it for tunnels i mean now the
tunnels are pretty useful i would say so
thank you oh okay filling it up
wait there's so many oh i almost shot
one with water there's so many down
there
okay a lot of them okay
you dash i wonder oh
okay i hope the jumping sound
doesn't wake them up okay i gotta gonna
land
nicely on the grass oh
you got this nice
you're good at being grass well you're
good at walking in the grass
yeah there you go that's just natural
very very well done you're you leave me
i'm taking you down too
i won't leave you
thank you i can't leave you on grasp
get it instead of leaves oh there's some
girls there's like
[Music]
okay mouth is kind of
reminds me of a little kitty mouth
[Music]
meow meow meow meow
have you thought more about getting a
kitty cat
yeah but i need to have a house first oh
amazing smartsmart maybe some moles at
last
oh look there all right there's another
purple plant
time to do what we do best you know
actually um
i i don't know what you would name your
kitty cat but
there was someone who like in my someone
in my audience who
told me they're getting a a dogo a puppy
that person was a fan of takamoni
especially
and they asked me for like a name i said
i should give them a name
and i told them to name it money and
they actually did
oh really that's so cute actually i
think it really suits the puppy
oh i was supposed to run i didn't
realize
i wonder if they posted a picture
because i feel like i saw something
yeah someone's dog named very cute
oh did not see that hole in the ground
you see
[Music]
all right let's keep a lookout for holes
in the ground because apparently they
exist
yes
[Music]
uh-oh be careful of that else oh that's
it i think i know you're not very long
oh it will break through
it all right got it go fast
gotta go fast gotta go
okay okay okay this is fun this is of a
cracked vanity
girl but it's not as cool really bad
you look yummy now
i would take a bite from you i know
what's that
[Music]
oh we did it i think oh thank god
it's over i thought he was gonna get it
are you okay yeah we did it let's get
out of here while we're alive
when we need more people i'm here
[Music]
yeah yeah oh we need to ground
it yep
all right welcome back oh cute snail
oh
there you go
thanks i know oh
that is a big treasure
[Music]
we can do that jump wait a minute
uh-oh definitely not very friendly
there's some tarzan
that was very cinematic yeah hey
[Music]
did we learned to speak frugal when they
speak our language
exactly what the heck
they eat is that a french accent
maybe ah okay
yummy hey hold it big boy my back is
killing me today
you take the fat one hey i'm right here
yoga like me double frog
show
oh he will carry me but not you
sorry uh namaste
oh it's so cute
i love frogs i love that taxi stand that
is adorable
that is such a cute idea like if you
were to actually have a garden
and you have some animals there roman in
your garden making like a little
home for them so cute
what those jumps holy
okay i promise you just gotta help me
get out of here
the source and clean it up
oh yeah you are very good
coming wherever you are can i dash
yeah dash is square it's the same button
that you usually use to dash
oh off okay
oh it's sinking
rocks as friendly creatures
i mean in this game at least no i think
have you made
evil frogs actually now that you say
that no
no i have met an evil friend oh it's
like frogger this is very cute
really oh that's nostalgic very
nostalgic i like that
hold it oh game just keeps getting more
and more cute
it's a bit bumpy but uh thanks for the
ride wow it's really fun dude thanks
how you doing back there good thank you
it's more comfortable than i imagined
yeah he's right in this garden
i used to play that uh
hey i need you and your frog for this
yummy
uh oh come on frog you can take a little
water and come on
come on no gumbo
as we can see i was not good at frogger
it's like a remaster of
froggies from the old days oh you can
land here nice
it works
sorry for keeping me waiting what is
this beautiful thing here
is this i should not jump into the pink
stuff right
no try and avoid that let's see maybe
the new ones will come up now
nice okay this is this one and then
it'll put the next one up for you
oh
[Music]
yeah well done that was close that was
really cool
yeah that was really cool that was
yep big steps
i don't like it
all right there's something here for you
purple
[Music]
too bad i really liked using those
freckles
you're very cute
all right i still feel
insulted by that purple finger because
purple is one of my favorite colors
so enjoy the color purple this color
purple is pretty common in the
underworld but not necessarily my
favorite
uh i think this is a i raised that
platform for you so you can
ah you can't jump on it wait ah the
purple stuff
oh wait ah that one first huh okay
ah there we go ah you still need the
frog maybe
because that jump is too far yeah
yeah you're right here we go
okay and then that one and then
that one
and then this one
purple is a nice color yeah purple yeah
and it suits you so well
i just salt you know the taco dashies
mm-hmm all right here we go
did you see the the the time square
thing for inna
yeah that was amazing i went wrong one
that was
crazy i didn't wear you got to
i was going to say though um inna's
color purple is a little more like calm
yeah it's like you know grayish hmm
yeah it's very calm purple all right
here we go
there's the next one
[Applause]
okay oh that was
please y'all okay okay
and almost one
and
this one you
where all the way at the top now i'm
gonna get you up here
oh i should have been on that thing huh
uh it comes down again
yeah thank you frog oh
yeah should remember that for minecraft
because i need to learn how to make
water elevators
yeah that would be so cool how did you
see my gift that i left uh for you on
minecraft
yeah i was waiting to say thank you very
much i appreciate the gift but you don't
really know what it does right
the end for pearl no i don't but i put
it in a safe place
i gave you one enchantment that's uh
called mending it's really useful
if you get like um like a
diamond tool that you don't want to
break
you put the method on it and then it
will
uh not break if you
you can heal it by getting like exp
so by killing that's enemies or by
fishing or
stuff like that that sounds awesome
that way you can keep your best weapons
or best
tools alive forever nice
wow that's amazing it's quite popular i
can get like
uh for the for the city that i made the
village that i made in in minecraft
the phoenixton village for that i can
get like all of those things like
endless
amounts which means now kelly we're like
pretty close to
being ready to fight the the ender
dragon
snail that's awesome kill you're
actually gonna race
let's do this one oh first to finish the
line wins
aim squeeze x
okay what do you mean squeeze
[Music]
oh my god it's it wait how do you move
so hold square ah jumping
ah
[Music]
go right
i'm coming for you come on let me get
some beat me in her loser snail
oh that was a rude thing to say cody you
deserve that
yeah cody you deserve that that was rude
that you called you called me that and
heard enter snail especially it was very
rude come on
they're rude cody who's the fastest team
so close
oh hi
[Applause]
there that was like
that was fun that's cute that was a cute
game
that's the finish line huh where did we
come from
i'm not sure probably back around there
somewhere but i wonder if there's
something we can do around here
next what can we do next
[Music]
what's going on here i know we use those
to get here this is where we came from
just kidding um
my german language came out there for a
moment
let's see there's a stuff
that's the house wait let's go up in
steps
i lost my sense of direction completely
it's fine just look for the the green
the green
house and just to get up to that window
i can turn into a mushroom
oh i don't like mushrooms
they're delicious very good for you
that looks like a i actually i like how
that looks like
sweet like a muffin that one looks the
same yeah
especially before making it wet
okay so you're gonna throw me where all
right
where where am i going where am i going
with that though
ah i see i'm doing something here for
you i don't know what i
have to start from the left side i guess
so jump on down
is an extremely picky eater yeah that is
kind of true
i noticed that when we went to hokkaido
yellow again ah okay
yeah um okay um
it's gonna be rough uh okay yellow again
yeah and then
and then the right one and then the left
the middle one again and i guess the
right one
keep it going got it great as well
oh wait i can probably walk wall jump
and there we go
now we have to pull something right you
made it nice jumping
hmm okay open up the window
what's inside
thanks for that oh no
it really is everywhere but we're so
close now
yeah hang on joy
we're almost there i think we're gonna
have to fight that flower
all right oh don't get don't get hurt
that's not gonna no way of opening it up
hey me you got some more purple gunk
here
well so what do you want me to do with
it oh
oh you're a different flower now magical
watching you make all that great let me
look in your face
that's why i love gardening i see i
understand completely
making it all into flowers huh together
to wash the garden make it something new
and beautiful
is sweet dance you call those flowers in
in german games of bloomberg by the way
though
not all of them there is different types
i guess but look how big
i'm ready
maybe sometimes it sounds really cute
when you say something in german
i tried really hard with duolingo but i
just feel like you'd be a better teacher
oh yeah i think it's sad yeah thank you
yes that is true
i find that's usually how it goes anyway
especially like for jeff with japanese
for example i learned way more with an
actual teacher than duolingo yeah
yeah it's good to like mix it in as a
secondary
way uh secondary method of learning
exactly but to have it be the only thing
you use
you won't learn very fast i don't think
must be so cute thanks i'll try my best
gotta prepare you so that you can visit
me here in
in australia wink uh in australia
and i want to know what to be able to
get around i mean everyone here speaks
german anyway to be honest uh english
english
oh okay wow pretty much anyone
we are
oh
do something here with ground pound
yeah over here we can do the thing again
with that
oh i made the light go on so now
we can do the same thing back over there
let's see what that does
okay almost right into it there we go
what do you become today a flower and
get a pink flower
hey the picture lied to me you should be
a pink flower
not close enough
[Music]
i actually in my current department that
i just moved into
i want to get a lot of plants i hope i
can keep them alive
i kind of doubt it but oh i can shoot
like this continuously
i didn't realize another wave of them
yeah anyway
having some plants in my apartment would
be very nice when i visited you
you didn't have any plans did you no but
i don't have enough time right now i
feel like once i get a house
as well it might be a lot easier for me
it's kind of like
healthy it seems and there's sometimes
that you don't really have to water
much at all really i guess that's true
i guess there is a place outside i could
use so
down down i think there's a bunch of
plants that you only have to
uh water like once every two weeks even
oh that's nice and you guys want to make
sure that it's really good for the what
do you call it oh [\h__\h] no
put a climate in the room yeah
that's cool yeah yeah you can get cactus
cacti but i'm not sure how that helps
the
climate in the room not sure if that
really helps with cactus
that's a thing we got to start over
again
do you guys know in the chat if they
have any positive effect on
on that i don't think so right but
at least they bring some color into your
apartment i think so
cacti cacti
yeah this remember reminds me of my
childhood um when me and my
family we were i think and i think it
was in italy
and we were um driving around and there
was some
some cat dad
and uh i was so young i didn't know
in german in germany they called cactus
in singular
and pactein in where is it
ah cocktail
and i didn't know because i was too
young and i said
and my mom thought that was so funny
because um
is a kind of a insult in german language
too
oh no say about like it's kind of like
saying [\h__\h]
oh yeah so i said i said
that's for the plural my mom could not
enjoy herself more my german viewers
understand that joke i guess
why i didn't where is the big boy did we
kill it out there
one more one more come down here
when kelly wipes you you're supposed to
listen to him
yes
and whatever something like that oh
yes i want some of this all right
kind of let's get rid of the infection
now it should be open
very nice look at all those flowers girl
[Applause]
oh and these these ones here are really
easy to take care of these little boys
they
they feel like plastic
wow most of the flowers okay most of the
flowers
in my home are dead i like dead flowers
ah that's for you that's the perfect
form of them huh not alive but
try something new always happy to try
something new
they have way more effect on y'all if
they're alive yes
maybe if you live in the overworld
especially
[Music]
really so
there's a little nasty spot here do you
have any allergies by the way
uh nope oh okay because flowers could
help in the room
with uh filtering out allergy stuff and
um you know which is i guess ironic
because flowers are the ones who cause
[Music]
no i'm not anymore
sorry sorry to have you deal with that
by yourself i'm on my way oh no problem
oh my goodness
all right are you jerking is there no
big boy this time
oh it's not oh
now for the infection
very nice
it's so beautiful
i want some of those hanging plants
hanging planters they they
look really cool would i get a house i
want a greenhouse my own greenhouse oh
greenhouse and
in japan seems difficult
to get a greenhouse but just a place
with a lot of where i can put a lot of
plants
you know a little garden is maybe
possible maybe
maybe on the countryside maybe
no no joy joy does not seem very joyful
cozy be careful
you're alive it's okay we're here to
help it has a podium
you remember me oh cody forgot about you
[Music]
maybe you should have cold maybe should
have not told the plant you were
[Music]
can i slice you up let me slice you up
come here come here come here
come here oh we should be fighting that
thing huh
it doesn't even work on you i got i got
a
anti-virus no wait wait
yeah you're right it's in the middle of
my screen i think i can do it anyway
this is dub
this isn't an easy easy handicap
so should i just clean everything up do
i i don't have to hit anything
yeah yeah i'll take care of this as a
tomato
uh no but only if the poison hits me
then i'm i'm not i mean i am
technically but if the poison hits me
then i'm in big trouble okay
oh yeah yeah we did
[Music]
give me that give me your hand break
down the infected part
here so you can remove it now i want to
try
[Music]
i got it
nice nice
oh what now
gabi what is going on oh oh the arena is
growing bigger
good job guys it looks like i can't rest
yet there's something wrong
i see that uh-oh good we've come to save
you
please stop enjoy for a moment william
baby
uh-oh it's not funny
love the blabbing the boss music
[Music]
i don't
okay
very busy here yeah
okay no worries looks like it's over
no what now
i'm going to be a potato
time to become a potato
yeah oh boys and poison
let's see thank you
all right who's next yeah i'll take care
of attacking the creatures
okay
[Music]
oh my god there's a lot of poison oh my
god
all right now this one potato char
potato charge thanks
thank you thank you very much for the
water that's how we did it oh okay
all right let's go get that other
infection out
i'm going back in for joy i think i'm
getting through to her
just talk to her talk to your plans
callie talk to your plants i mean it's
helpful if you talk to your plants
sometimes they see it it makes them grow
more delicious
yup then we just need to get the one on
the head after that we'll be done
nice
where are you oh there you are right
here we're doing this again
maybe something happens raise us up joy
oh we chose the right ones no they're
all right okay
they're gonna crash
oh man it's like this right my skills
with crash bandicoot will help me here
and some of them are cracking
you're doing quite well today oh man
too bad not the worst could be worse
amelia calm down yep you're chilling
it's scaring me today no really it's all
fun and games but
right feel what happened did your
viewers
make you salty again
oh my god i felt i felt oh man am i
supposed to jump off
i don't know if i'm supposed to
obviously no dog
and lime uh-huh oh very specific
look at that nose i do like lines the
power of citrus prevails overall
tackle those things all right here we go
middle first middle first okay
all right what a pretty limey one over
here
yeah that's a lot of a lot of purple
stuff
now next we're going over there thank
you for clearing the path
it's so much
you still okay yeah oh man all right
middle first
thank you oh i'm about to die
i pulled it back a little bit all right
now we got this one over here
thank you
what's up okay i always panic when you
die at the end but that's just how it's
supposed to be huh
yeah this is it i can
feel it's breaking through okay
wait
so become one with joy again
this is weird hearing your voice come
from that flower
before i was just hearing watson screams
and we're gonna get rid of it once and
for all
okay so what happened to the crocodile
plants you're a nice beautiful
nice well done oh
did she snap out of it yeah
but she died she died for all the other
flowers
that's so sad
but she gave life to so many others and
then she literally leaves your soil
i should have taken care of you yeah you
should have cody
i'm sorry no no
i'm sorry oh i didn't understand how
important it was for cody
i do now oh that's good
but it's not your fault cody gave up on
being a partner
but aren't partners supposed to
encourage each other
how was i supposed to keep going
if she didn't believe in me why are you
starting that now
no one can take your dream from you
unless you give it up
that's a good point it's all up to you
[Music]
will you give it up again
oh man oh man are we getting more pages
it's pretty pretty deep stuff
yeah that was pretty deep what are you
doing again
[Music]
i have she's playing with my clothes
cute
chunker says hello kelly hello shonkers
i love cats hi there
mom and dad doing our best can we can
you make us humans now
please i think there's probably one more
chapter maybe
yeah we're really close
[Music]
one more piece okay one more page find
your purpose in life
it's time to find mom's passion i don't
have one
everyone has hmm passion for something
she does yeah i mean
you can have a passion for doing nothing
as well
that's fine too nothing wrong with that
it's nice i don't know why you don't do
it anymore
i grew up you can't pay the bills with
singing
[Music]
it's time for you to find it again
get ready to find the last piece of the
letter
here we go last piece is it about music
now
music chapter
maybe i like i like
what a mess yeah we really need to clean
up our attic
oh old old music you recognize these
suitcase huh no oh i don't like where
this is going
oh
welcome to the concert hall hey it's
time to sing
away let's go
that's not a stage it's my old record
player
you're right but you two will turn it
into a proper stage
we need lights speakers microphones look
i'm not going to sing a single note
yes you will yeah
[Music]
oh mom you're good great she sure does
cody and you will help her find her
voice again
let's get this concert started
all day that's adorable
okay let's prep the stage
[Music]
so my skill is singing now
looks like it'll be fine me
you have a great voice not anymore i
won't sing and make a fool of myself
relax you're not making a fool of
yourself it's beautiful
let it all out let it go let's go
yeah whoo
do we have here ooh oh
very different very different from all
the other uh levels yeah
rocking and rolling i like it
it is moody oh this symbol is like a
shield
superhero i can shoot shouts you got the
greatest weapon of all
that's awesome what the heck trade
anytime
no you wouldn't powerful me never forget
that
come back
and then you can use your voice to push
it down and
scream nice nice very cool
screen nice one beautiful vocals
it's broken oh and here i just sing
normally
okay wow
beautiful
[Music]
cool cool stuff okay here i sing again
oh cool hey this is kind of cool they
they did some interesting stuff here ah
sorry i died
so you die with me
i know it has to be all the way up
mm-hmm
[Music]
quick quick
me is the bee singer of whole live
english
that's pretty good first guys yup
yup you heard it here first please
welcome her with a round of applause
and finally finally that means we have
our first real
real british girl in the team yes
i'm gonna yell at that thing real loud
look at that bad boy
what does that say makes me jump
nice
give us another boost
your singing is amazing yep
may appreciate you guys encouraging her
thank you
it should come now yeah there it is
what's up same
ah you can't do it without me [\h__\h] i
need to go back need to go back need to
go back need to go back
back
can't press the button okay you first
go okay then you
right immediately after let's start
sliding
so immediately after you scream into it
once scream into it again for you
and then follow me right away well i
guess i could go with you perhaps
yeah yeah yeah yeah i can go with you
okay
don't have to wait for you and now
wow the button you actually said
something with the button
there we go got it yes
very nice grandpa's jukebox yeah
i forgot we stored it in our attic do
you think it still works
i would put it in
[Music]
other side we're gonna push it together
cool i wish my grandpa could see us
he'd love it i hate it
he always told me to be careful
rings of temptation sweetest couple
[Music]
i'm feeling funky too ready to get down
i love his music let's dance cali
yeah put on a nice dress me too
put it on those nice shoes
[Music]
ah here let me try ah is it is it not so
loud
guys in the audience i feel like it's a
bit loud maybe
oh yeah
[Music]
it's me it's okay okay this speaker has
an antenna on it
i bet it's connected to your microphone
what did that do
i can't remember is it okay to break all
of that kelly
are we fine gotta get through here
anyway
[Music]
oh no i thought we're gonna repair it or
something
destroying it yeah
[Music]
there we go give me some more babe
honey after this
keep those going huh
[Music]
i think this dripbox is never going to
be repaired anymore
no chance
oh i need to go to united probably check
out the size of that
ears cody oh fine
let's fire this baby okay do it
huh wait how often
wait here i fell down i'm stuck
now i'm gonna have to come to you
how do put down
i can't i can't come kid i'm stuck
no oh come on man
can you fall down there somewhere okay
you use all the buttons use all the
buttons
please i don't want to start over
put down ah you can put it down once if
you stop walking
if i jump uh it says put down maybe then
you're
less less stuck
so you can't put it down at all
nah even though it says put down the
button when i press it nothing happens
it can can you
put put it in that corner maybe there's
more space there
how do we have to restart the level
how do i do that
i think since you're the you're the uh
one hosting the the game right now you
probably have to do it
from checkpoint it's okay we can at
least restart from the checkpoint okay
where
is that let's find out
ah okay
oh okay we just have to destroy
everything again i guess
no what dead
dead is that normal
i don't think so that is not normal
send it to ea games tell them to fix it
yeah let them let ea games know what's
up we got the proof guys
sent the clip open that was funny
that was pretty funny but i do want to
say it's an
amazingly great game and there might
have been like one or two bugs here and
there but
i love this game overall yeah it's very
fun
okay so here's what we gotta do you
gotta scream right into here oh i do it
like this it's like this
ah let's go more
oh it's moving and now
go down ah oh my god
here we go again ah you have to leave it
there
it's there i'm going to put it down
right here
there and now i push this but
it makes even louder
here all right
[Music]
now get ready volume to the max
let's go everyone turn off your ears
good work both of you you learn the
speakers
figures yay great now you can let us out
of here
not yet keep on going we need more stuff
for the concert
later that's not fair you can do that
mission impossible
you're too kind
i trust you you got to go first you have
that shield
oh okay i was looking at the wrong
camera yeah thank you i got fruit
okay
oh we got a lot of microphones again do
i start with that one
what do they do what does it do oh
there's
b a b a b c d
wow i'm starting to like this place i
think d
is the pink one a is the red one b is
the yellow yeah there the letters are
here as well yeah so do i start with a
and then go bcd
because if you use b then i go forward
right ah
okay ah okay okay when b was
here
[Music]
oh i know d ah because it's it's like um
the air coming out of it that pushes you
so d
should move and where do we want to go
um i think
any either way is fine okay maybe to the
right
okay to the right so i go to a
but don't you dine i know if you shoot
yes
uh okay there it is try it again
maybe i need to hold it like this i
should run one
d
[Music]
and then we want to go to the right
again so
a and um
one more and be careful yeah and one
more i guess
no okay now
[Music]
i don't worry
see
i see ice
can you move the camera a little bit
yeah nice
thank you and up ah
duh you arrived you did it very good
let's see thank you
[Music]
let's pull that lever it's like all the
levels
until now we're kind of like um
not exactly childish but but i'm not
sure what the word would be and this is
so
very organic like yeah i guess you're
saying like very whimsical
bright and colorful and this is still
colorful but in a different way yeah
i'm like a composer now
[Music]
instruments really i just i feel like
i've seen i've seen that word i've ever
heard of it too
but you died hello kitties
oh she wants me to rub her belly but
mama cannot right now i'm sorry baby
i'm sorry okay where are you what are we
doing
where am
uh-huh
do we do something with that no probably
not
just decorate oh hey check it out
keyboard
keyboard ah yeah there's a portal up
here
[Music]
[Applause]
nice demo tapes no don't listen to that
new top secret
no not my name we must we must
we must it nothing happens
wait i have to press here get back on it
oh one screen now okay
okay what's happening yeah
hey
[Music]
kind of the dj activities really that's
pretty cool yeah i learned that in the
last hello talk that i did with her
wow did you know did you know that song
from local senpai azamina
the uh the really like whispery one
oh yeah that one the lyrics were written
by ayton
whoa what i can flex all my knowledge
i have so much super dope knowledge this
trip i see you on a monitor keep your
eyes on those knobs
oh this is like a game i mean all of
this is the game but
oh dang it so yeah aids actually has a
talent for
writing lyrics as well isn't that
surprising that surprised me a lot
wow i mean i had never heard of it
before so i wasn't
oh wow it's okay all right there we go i
can't get up there though you gotta
lower it again i guess
yeah yeah on to the right
oh yeah in the whole time you really
learned a lot did you know that my next
hold up is with ajan
oh yeah i saw that yeah exciting
i think i think people can learn a lot
about the the company
in this hotel because i'm not not really
going to be asking
much about athens i think it's probably
more about
oh no come on dang it i was up too high
it's probably more about um that was
close
probably more about the company
yeah it's still the 10th episode's gonna
be really special
oh dang it okay be careful to not jump
at that point i guess
okay okay okay okay
okay okay uh that's a bit too high can't
can't jump that high it seems
okay now now to the red one can you get
that down a bit thank you
okay wait and
aloha
yeah yeah yeah we're almost there
okay yeah
it's like steps nice
well done wow awesome
[Music]
yay all right now i got to get up there
oh
[Music]
what is that is that an instrument or
just something
side thing i want to raise that again a
wind chime oh yeah
yep made it nice
wow level design very interesting
oh wait we're very good let's record our
first takabuni original song
now recording what's that
is it a microphone i think so
uh that looks like it's gonna be alive
in a moment
yeah that's not that's not the mic we're
going to use i guess
and that's how you uh explode that's how
you get rid of the
microphones i see you explode them ah
it's alive after all ah you want me to
sing oh
shut your mouth i'm singing
i was gonna say it sounded like um the
the love book or whatever wanted us to
um
get mics more than one mic oh yeah
because we have these speakers
but we don't have the mic shut up you
said mike
might speak the most
why did i do that i fell down
oh
[Music]
that was a big fan again
explosion
what oh dang it that makes it
it's probably really heavy for me you
need help what
can i do no problem i'm good
there we go okay let's go
how do you say that word actually kelly
help me out
they won't work hypnose
[Music]
oh
we should both be on it i camped down
okay okay
don't even think about it microphones
[Music]
go
oh you just went through oh i guess i
could have done
i thought we had to kill them
[Music]
i think you need to go before me
that you can hit this out you have to
sing while we go
well i just had to distract them by
letting myself get eaten but no that's
not delay
okay let's see if i can ride and sing go
nice you're listening good audience
i can't without you
[Music]
um where uh where are you right now oh
there okay right here
[Music]
okay i'm going
where are you going back that's back the
way we came
oh really
oh i got confused that's okay
oh no
[Music]
you little [\h__\h] you [\h__\h]
now
ow the symbol is open
[Music]
what did we do same real good
colors oh [\h__\h] not again coffee
you you're uh carrying us right now oh
eh
oh yeah
this is a ride of death queen superhero
you would know about that
[Music]
okay not dying this time
that's right i'm coming back
here
oh what i guess i went in the wrong
direction
it's okay i thought it was that way too
my friend alive
he's getting
who kill those closer
feeling the music feeling the vibes
feeling the beat
inside my heart lyrics for my next song
hey sounds good sounds like a banger
already
thank you oh
the gate please i don't want to become
pushing or
can we do it
i didn't know if it was like pushing
several times or uh pushing like
constantly like not letting go yeah you
gotta push it a bunch of times
[Music]
rapid pushing okay
that was a little too close for comfort
that was a humongous snake that almost
killed us
well you're still breathing and you
earned
the [\h__\h]
book of love you already have these
things can you just give them to us
keep on going what's next
after the microphone it waits
when the lights are left like oh hey i
played with these a bit when i was
younger
yeah show them your skills then don't
try to
form to make music together all right
let's make a hit yo
how how
ah we need that we need to make them all
reach there
uh i think we did it cool i did i don't
know what
i was doing there but with wicked
[Music]
making myself but it's music
all right
hey look that spotlight must be for you
no thanks come on man you deserve to be
in the spotlight
give us your best wrap bars dad oh it's
a cat look hey hey
oh yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
we're making progress
collaboration
[Music]
oh can you ride on that
oh there we go oh damn it okay well
now we know now we know
we got to make this shine do you have to
shine it on that
okay okay um bit more
i don't want to hurt you i'm hurting you
it's not fair it needs to it needs to
happen
yeah totally i can do a little stick
yeah
this is my specialty all right go ahead
and get that next one popping off
nice
i thought i could let go already all
right all right all right
all right red stays here
let's go green oh come on
i can't hey he's in the spotlight what
do you want
mostly
oh what is that something spooky now i
can move it
right all right
[Music]
okay wait uh i go ah
i can only move the green one over there
okay
now i do hold oh oh no not the right
stick i don't want to move the
rhinestone
oh yeah oh wait there's
there's light here anyway can you stay
in that light
no green put the green on me
you could put the green one on me okay
it's fine oh
fell down
hey i see a light switch okay
why does that hurt him
maybe because it's not perfectly on him
well come on it doesn't matter
my amazing coaching has made you into a
strong tough job to be a live person
[Music]
that was quick yep
no it was just a silly hobby oh no it
wasn't just a silly heart even if
people kind of need hobbies to you know
with musicians
if you don't do it professionally if it
makes you happy you do it
that's what's me seeing musicians now
a band go and find an orchestra
god damn it i hate this book so much
she keeps singing acapella too come on
yeah yes an orchestra where the hell let
me find another
chest this is my very jelly there's a
minigame
i'll call amelia to play that with me
then
i i think amelia will not sure
it's not anymore
[Music]
brings back some good memories
hey is that your old piano yeah
looks still in tune oh pretty
i like the i like the color of it it's
like the color
of my inner hair although with this yeah
i dyed my hair a little bit this is the
best instrument in the world there's a
flute over here
[Music]
you mean a recorder it's a dude machine
sure that's fine too i suppose it
doesn't it's not
where are you here
no
how the hell did fire kill me i'm a
phoenix what the hell
all right i'm playing a
i game where it's supposed to go
[Music]
oh yeah
maybe not up to the piano
if we need to fill the glasses a certain
way
one of my refined tastes appreciates
these bats
it's magic excuse me
she's uh doubting you over fine tastes
hey how long is that lion sitting in
those glasses huh
probably a long time i would not drink
it personally
pray oh wait there's a hole here did we
come from that
yeah we did i wonder where we're
supposed to go then
[Music]
i mean it must be here somewhere oh can
we just go down
oh yeah you were on the float
[Music]
oh oh oh
something with a recorder according to
the chat
you have to play some boots
[Music]
hmm
there we go you can cross now oh yeah
by the way thank you for playing my
songs with the machine you're welcome i
tried my best
it was very fun yours was the only one i
learned most of
it what whoa what's that machine
holy oh yeah it killed me
be careful do i have to sing again
oh let me walk behind you follow me
when i die you can just stay there i
guess hopefully
i was holding why can't i oh huh
what i'm pressing the button i usually
use to hold it
and i can't hold it oh now it
put you into
[Music]
yeah i can't hold it let me try again
it's bugged
[Music]
i'm pressing every button okay i can't
hold it
this is probably a checkpoint maybe just
reload it from here
all right
[Music]
there we go i guess we just can't
uh we just aren't allowed to die again
you're right
oh
nice okay
dramatic piano music
[Music]
piano what's that called in english
accordion sorry
[Music]
oh is that
try again
is that enough time for oh yeah today's
day now it seems like it
okay then i can get over to you get to
the other one
i'm trying right
now are you inside uh-uh
hanging out oh otherwise
wow this is beautiful this is my what
what what what yeah go the other way
okay nice
well done visitor the light
okay oh no
the visual wealth hello
whoa it's heaven
[Music]
gotta go find that orchestra fluffy
clouds
rays of light organs
i guess we must be in heaven yes even an
orchestra
yeah but where's the orchestra gone
hello
they left they're taking a break taking
a little vacation
i knew what i'm saying
let's just cancel the whole thing no no
no you have to bring the orchestra to
your concert
but they have been kidnapped over there
look look
well i wonder who kidnapped them
in heaven oh yeah oh my gosh
exactly but now you have to go and save
the earth
all right okay wow
go go go okay
just
[Music]
okay we're trying to get those notes oh
oh you gotta get all the notes
[Music]
the musical notes are connected to the
doors
okay
what does that even mean i have no idea
can't get that one you i think dad just
really wants to be a rapper
like perform alongside uh may
i'm sure he would do great
and one more
[Music]
i got it and this one and
there we go oh that oh that was some
extra ones huh
now there are two doors oh
oh really i just noticed there's a bunch
of doors yeah mm-hmm
actually let me take that and i'll take
this one
we do both need to open up nice
[Laughter]
i hate the music ah they don't want to
hear my singing
no no wait look
oh oh it's crying hidden in the fog
oh my gosh you will never get the keys
we'll say about that
[Music]
they suck oh yeah wow just laugh it up
crazy devils cause we're about to bring
it
yeah look at dad full of spirit
over here okay keep hitting those clouds
okay hurry clouds we need your tears to
clear the fog
oh did i just make the clock go away i
don't know i don't think that i was
supposed to do that what am i what's my
job here
um great question
i need to try and clear the area somehow
do we want to get rid of the clouds
we don't want to get rid of them i don't
think it's angry
huh cloud of views
can you move them oh i guess i can
so where would i want to move all of
them to the middle
so look at the ground yeah you see how
the clouds look at how the rain is
clearing up
oh sorry boy
[Music]
yeah like that it's gonna take a long
time
we need to clear it all out i guess
the ah
well i saw something here
hmm
oh wow here's one something too yeah
okay let me move those
[Music]
there we go that's what we like to see
did i push it too much
maybe push the cloud over here
[Music]
i'm trying to get them to the other one
first
to the middle come on mom
okay now now yeah
oh there we go we got one
almost cleared up a bit more
[Music]
we let them out is that i don't think
that's a good thing
let's hurt them beat them up
i can make them explode with my voice
nice
mm-hmm i got a key
perfect no
i guess i can walk yeah maybe try and
put it into the cage yep
and then now do the same thing with the
clouds but over here
there's still one more
but why do we have to make them cry i
know
it's just a part of the job yes
there's one cloud enough i wonder
a little bit here and then there
are a bit more
[Music]
ah
you get them to move a little more
it's just really sick of it i think
maybe we can try a different club
that should be it yeah
okay landing coming for the landing
opening and here comes the gremlins
and the keys
wait it's just suits they have no bodies
yeah it's the orchestra we have to open
it together
hey cody come look at the orchestra
brought in the keys
[Applause]
it's ghosts yay there they go
half the orchestra is here oh take it
oh yeah there's one more huh okay
[Music]
more cloud bullying let's get to the
other side good to me
does it feel weird for you to be in
heaven kelly have you ever been here
before
um i'm not obligated to say but
i mean it's nice and whatever i just
think the underworld's way better
but as a shinigami like i would think
you
send people to the
heavens sometimes too or do you only
send them to hell because you like it
better that's kind of based
i mean what happens after we send the
souls to the ferryman is none of our
business pretty much
ah i can imagine i can imagine i don't
know
maybe something dope excuse me
we don't get to know though yeah we're
uh we're gonna need to borrow that
orchestra that you got locked up in
there
we will never let zelda i'm in tune come
on
these dudes okay that's annoying it's
one of those keys
oh [\h__\h] that's a lot of them oh there's
a lot of them beat them up
orchestra that's right
they all look like they're carrying
cheese
[Music]
which one is it oh wait that one sparkly
one
wait wait wait this is like like harry
potter when you're
looking for the snitch yeah a snitch
wait what's it called yeah the golden
snake yeah the golden snitch okay
land
you can get him to land here
okay it went all the way down oh hmm
what oh that was you
oh
[Music]
here we go
so i can sing
oh
[Music]
you're playing the more elegant dude
machine all right i think that's all of
them
let's head back to the stage
kelly be there in one sec hang on no
problem remember how i thought
i had something that i had to do i'm
telling them i'm telling them
wait oh you can you can take 10 minutes
though if you want
it's okay i'm just gonna reschedule this
one no worries
okay okay
are we the maestros i thought the book
is gonna be the most
i bet that's how it will actually be
though
okay here we go party time
it's pretty impressive right i've never
sung with a group as big as people why
did you wait don't worry it'll be fine
it will not say fine
oh you seem pretty good with
a groove coaster oh so i was all right
but thank you
lovely good job we're almost ready
i think you're better with virtual games
than me
you got it book yeah
that's good enough for me oh nice
flamingo sign
oh someone told me this flamingo joke
with them putting the foot down how did
that go again
one of my viewers told me that was fun
oh clap i don't wanna go
oh look at this place
it's jago the bouncer oh my god
hey hey buddy over here what's up
can you let us stop sorry kids no miners
whoa no no no no we're just okay mine is
all in size that's all yeah right
get out of here kiddos we have a child
excuse me we are
adults you have some id oh
uh no we left it at home that's what
they do
yo-yo glow-stick they're with me
team up bro they're with you mama
he's bringing us in nice welcome to the
club
we didn't even have to wait in line it's
pretty nice
nice oh wow it's just kind of mad
that sounds
oh no this is trippy
but it looks dope this is surreal
i'm gonna go ahead and you're gonna go
right right
see ya oh it's beautiful
this place reminds me of something else
oh dad that is something does it remind
him of mario kart
definitely what it was that's the joke
can i drift
can i auto steer
[Music]
what does that remind me of oh
thanks
[Music]
with the me cody
the dragon cart was much easier than
mario kart
oh wait there we go
[Music]
you have the dash jump okay
10 years later
when you enter the club this is how you
enter any club
[Music]
didn't see that one almost
um this is interesting i like the
aesthetics a lot
it was fun oh okay we did it here i am
sorry it took me a while
um
[Music]
i gotta come back to you hold on okay
phone is getting overheated here we go
here i am
i'm back can you move yourself
mom perhaps who's a very
watching myself on youtube oh too big
way too big
small oh no
more to the left okay
more to the left to the left um
up up up up bigger maybe
yeah more bigger yeah yeah more bigger
smaller smaller
yeah yes keep the size get the size keep
the size uh
down down down down okay stop stay there
i can do the rest myself probably
wait
this is just like in in this game right
now teamwork teamwork
all right where is
fixed
well time to wall jump
i see i think
oh i don't even need to go over there
okay
wait for me wait for me wait for me
you got this you got this just hold
remember you can hang onto the wall and
you can wait
[Music]
how did you do that did you hang on to
the left or the right one
yeah um the
the left one oh okay okay
i'll just be surviving it's all good
remember you can hang on to the left
wall uh-huh
now i gotta wait time this is also like
you have to feel the rhythm i guess yeah
a little bit
you got this yeah okay whoa i just need
to
calm down okay there we go
funky funky
the moment i wrapped the platform leaves
oh no
i need to sing at it
gonna wait for the next one yes
one more time maybe one more blast oh
one more oh sorry can i do it from the
side yes
oh thank you wait no
thank
[Music]
do we really have to do that one more
time
[Music]
don't fall into the holes i guess move
it move it yeah i guess now
[Music]
i feel like it is are you guys really
hearing her well
[Music]
yeah oh yeah i i got eaten don't don't
get eaten
bad it's fine
[Music]
i was playing a game the other day where
like it was like a rhythm
dodging game full so i'm in the groove
i'm like my
eyes are already
[Music]
wait the game you talked about is that
friday funky
oh no not friday night funky it's a rpg
rhythm game
[Music]
good job kelly good luck to you too
you were mostly carrying in that one
weirdest experience
it's only because i was i had already
been playing a game dodging things
recently
crazy dangerous nerve-wracking
but fun that's right mom knows what it's
about now
oh you can't hear that crowd mate
yes this is exciting god wants you
hi everyone oh
the dancing glow stick the one in the
middle
dance with me what are you doing where
are you going come on glow sticks you
gotta start singing
jazz music dance
maybe they will if you leave the dance
floor
seriously i think you're scaring them
okay baby i'm killing it
can't you see my hip gyration challenge
challenge
please stop yeah move that booty twerk
it
oh my god my moves are so good look at
this ride
ride to make the audience
dance you need to play the music
get the audience on the floor let's dj
again what what is this the right one
oh we're dj's okay
you're coming back
oh
there we go we're bringing them back
i can't do that because my keys are
mapped like
it doesn't even
[Music]
yes
i don't know where these ones are uh
this is this
this this this this this this
okay roughly
i should i should okay
[Music]
bam
ladies and gentlemen cj cody and fc
may hey
[Music]
yeah me neither all like on the like if
you asked me to do a freestyle i would
not be able to
i got the gist of the keys now even
though mine uh
say different things
this is long what the hell right
they're really jamming now oh my god
[Music]
peace
oh my gosh you can't just kidnap it come
[Music]
on
whatever at this point wait what are we
writing on
music sports music
oh my god
oh
[Music]
don't really think there's a health bar
right now though nice
no hurts
it does pinky
[Music]
you see the whole universe
absolutely incredible
oh
it's beautiful inside the music
wow
[Music]
am i dying am i dead kelly can you check
real quick on your phone if i'm dead
do the shitty dummies nowadays have like
an app device where they handle these
things or do they still do it on paper
i think it seems like it's okay i just
checked my my app and you seem like
you seem to be alive okay good yeah
you're welcome
that was so cute yeah they were
connecting with their music
that was obviously a lot of fun the
music gave me like really happy vibes
[Music]
oh man it's time for the concert
concert time
you hear that mate you hear the
anticipation
i haven't performed in front of an
audience for ages may it'll be fine just
uh just think of them all in there yeah
dad will be with you yes
that would make you relax visa singer
and debut
be like okay like this
here we go i can't do this
yes you can don't do it need to need
dad to be have to be perfect backstage
will face it does
if it's not perfect i'll let them down
no just seeing from your heart
you weren't born to be perfect you were
born
to be you
a bit too relatable
oh
that's really [\h__\h] powerful
will they well will they think of me
will they like me
doesn't matter only want you to like me
from the heart yes sir i'll sing from
the heart
i sing out my feelings
give me your best yes
i'll be supporting you dad i'll be
cheering you
i'm gonna cheer for you
can you stand in the front row
i'll do my best
all right dad do your thing
[Music]
i feel the heartbeat in my control
oh that's so cute
got it mom
i know you got to be nervous but you got
this very nervous
but at least that there's people out
there actually
and not just one person
yeah hi guys
i'll open the curtains it's time do it
peek
they're oh for you
come on me you can do this i believe in
you
come on
um
[Music]
oh
um
i love you mom
[Music]
you can do this me i know you can
hey
[Music]
uh
that was beautiful me thank you
[Music]
oh
trust me
[Music]
okay okay
[Applause]
[Music]
look at them so beautiful
love heals
all audios
oh man and use amigo
i'm still holding triangle i should stop
doing that
endless kissing hey look up
oh yeah you look much better and
than your real food no leaves on my head
world's greatest dad
i forgot they look like this as chad
yeah they look so innocent
[Music]
rose
cody it worked
we're back where's rose
i don't know
rose
[Music]
where'd she go
no no no watch
dear mom and dad i'm sorry that i did
this to you
i know how to make everything good again
all you have to do is stop fighting
i know i'm not a perfect daughter
wait what i'm sorry i don't like to
brush my teeth
i'm sorry i read books after bedtime i'm
sorry i don't put my toys where they
should be
i know it's my fault you want to no
she's blaming herself
she thinks it's her fault
you should be friends no my child what i
love you mom
i love you dad no no p.s
they have my pocket money to buy a bus
ticket
don't worry i packed a sandwich on the
lollipop
oh my gosh child no quick
quick
i mean on that countryside the bus
probably come only comes once per day
oh my god there we go i'm so sorry oh
don't worry just me you can go home no
no
rose honey it's not your fault
that we've been fighting
it it isn't no i like that she picked up
that british accent from her mom
i guess so you know maybe maybe maybe
they're in the uk oh yeah maybe you can
become friends again
honey listen whatever happens your mom
and me we will always be there for you
and we'll always love you
always
okay come here [\h__\h]
[Music]
the book helped us out quite a bit it
did
where did you find this i found it at
school
in a trust me where it belongs no just
kidding i love the book we're beloved
you did sometimes you can find real
treasures in the trash
oh at the end of the day they like the
book
[Music]
okay so rose if your mom had to fight an
aggressive squirrel double
her size who do you think would win
[Music]
you're right you're right you're right i
like the hangout
i used to think you were completely
irrational but i have to say
you make more sense now
[Music]
much better much better than the ending
that we had in a way out
yeah that was just unfortunate that was
so much pain
yeah getting directed joseph
faris good job good job
thank you joseph for the dope game
everyone else
worked on that that was beautiful
you guys killed it gosh what a beautiful
game
all of those levels were so well
designed
it was always like something different
each time we had different weapons to
play around with
and they all like harmonized with one
another
like i completed you you completed me
so dang beautiful and and all when we
went through the environments like we
could like
slide on things that was my favorite
part sliding around stuff
and the rainbow the rainbow place is my
favorite
ah i also i liked the the snow place
maybe the most
it was also very dramatic and but but
beautiful
snow village and then the mountains with
all the
wind and all that and then us like
at the very top of that um tower
yeah it was a really neat idea to
include like where they had their
vacation their ski vacation trip and
i was doing whatever that was a good
idea in the snow glow
and then like picking up at the very end
um oh my god
bit too loud oh my god
at the end where they picked up on
the hobbies of you about that
with the garden and then also um
mommy with her singing and i think
in in the beginning where we were kind
of like ah that maybe fits me better and
and my mom fits you better from the
personality but i think in the end it
was actually
one of the things i felt so super
related
to um yeah mommy yeah
and it was also perfect because the last
episode was on my channel so
of me uh finishing it up with her
concert
that was uh wonderful i was worried that
they were gonna go into like another
thing like oh no but the book is
actually evil and you have one last boss
to fight or something like i feel like
it ended like
perfectly yeah yeah you know all in that
perfect game really mm-hmm yeah it was i
mean there were a few bugs but
i mean
oh wonderful really really great co-op
game
and it was it was a pleasure to play it
together with you kelly thank you
it was it was a pleasure to play it with
you too chris satori what a good
i liked it i liked it maybe a little
better than
a way out and a way out is more like
thematically and like
like with um the atmosphere a way out is
more my kind of game
but i feel like this game was just like
i mean obviously this is a newer game so
like
it just it felt like it had so much soul
in it not that not that a way out didn't
it's just this one
really like brought it home knocked it
out
yeah yeah they like totally outdid
themselves
whoever i guess it's the same team that
worked on it right pretty much mostly
so i think so yeah wow wow
i have a lot of uh snot stuck in my
front
no
did you not get a little bit emotional
at the end
i did a little bit i felt like i felt
tears like kind of welling up yeah
i think i think like if maybe
you know some some parents out there who
are having trouble
maybe they can play this game together
and find their love again
honestly i think if they would give it a
try and be open about it it might
actually work as a fair female
i completely agree yeah because you see
it from a different perspective than
maybe
like um and see how they did it to get
back together by
respecting one another it depends on the
they're going through those some things
are like okay we need to do this a
different way but
you know if you've just been having a
couple fights here and there
you feel like you want to connect
through a game i recommend it
i think they did they touched a lot of
important points of what's
important in a relationship
and uh that in the end
uh you just have to try to understand
one another
and communicate and help out and trust
and passion again important yeah that's
what does the book says
is there for this
black male therapy it's not black no
stuff
um it was really creative too and i
liked i liked all of the like
i don't know the childish innocence in
this game
yeah it was nice
it was still there were still some adult
aspects though like with the cursing
what who am i to say
i try to cut it back but you know it's
not really a game for your five-year-old
maybe you're ten-year-old if you tell
them to not use the curses in the game
it depends it depends on the one thing
was
pretty pretty friendly to children to be
honest
probably children wouldn't even get like
um
like some of those more uh
i mean i mean never barely were were
there any of those jokes
i don't think so they would probably not
even pick up on it though but yeah
well there was some blood though and
like some oh yeah you know the elephant
with the elephant
but that can be fixed i'm sure by now
the elephant is already fixed and
stitched back together yeah no problem
no problem
[Music]
i hope i hope that those creators or
other other creators work on more co-op
games like this because
this is like the perfect like game for
us like
to play in like couples two and uh yeah
one one
and one together need more games like
this
agreed yeah 100 those split screen co-op
games are my favorite for
collaborations
so kelly now that
they found um
that they found there how to get back
i'm controlling this [\h__\h] here hey
come on come on just just uh
just uh peck on the chick
no no none of that we can do a high five
okay wait wait you you're still a bit
too
too far you're kind of cut off there
over here
but you cut out come close that
otherwise you're cut up i can't do
yes yes yes you see it's a perfect
screen we can people can take
screenshots here yeah
okay okay everyone are you ready for a
screenshot
do not do anything
i kiss your shoulder just your shoulders
[Music]
let me help you let me help you come
because i like bugs crawling into my
eyes
that's a bit scary
stop stop
i hope you guys had fun too um
the week has just started it's a really
exciting week tomorrow on cali's channel
we have the ttrpg
right yeah well for me it's technically
i think it's like the day after you want
to say like
what do we do there yeah so everyone's
going to be
officially making their characters we're
going to be assigning uh
stats and creating character sheets for
everyone's characters for
the tabletop rpg game the game we're
playing is world of darkness
specifically uh hunter the vigil and i'm
running
in that is um a little more like
streamlined and easy for beginners not
just for the girls but for you guys too
so that when people jump in it's it's
easier for them to understand what's
going on so i'm playing a very
simplified version of the game
we're mostly going to be focusing on rp
with each other so yeah oh
and it will be a weekly thing right
mostly unless something comes in the way
yeah every other week and and then on
the day after that
we have a collab on vata senpai's
channel you
me yo senpai and vatami senpai
girls playing uh that chicken horse game
what's it called yeah ultimate chicken
horse something yeah ultimate chicken
horse game something like that
indeed indeed on whatever senpai i think
it will be mostly
japanese probably because we all speak
japanese oh
pretty much yeah so three days of
collapse it's not over yet takamori
lives on forever in your hearts
and also just from my side i have on
sunday
and no wait wait oh my god this week is
so crazy for me on saturday is hollow
talk of eighth on 10th episode yes yes
and on sunday is planned to be
my 1 million endurance stream i am
finally ready kelly to
to uh uh uh beat your
record i'm gonna be doing a 12
hour uh marathon
[\h__\h] maybe you can watch some of that on
the 12 hour
i'll drop off yay i'll be doing a lot of
stuff
and i'm i'm planning to do like singing
and gaming and talking maybe a q a
throwing
thrown in there as well all kinds of
stuff 12 hour stream without any breaks
let's [\h__\h] go
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah good luck
hopefully i reach 1 million i mean it
should be
i know you will i mean looking at the
looking like at some calculations it
should totally be possible
so i hope you guys can come to support
me in those crazy twelve hours
yoroshiku got this i know you can do it
thank you
sorry sometimes yeah when you look over
here you got my tail in your mouth
because i hope it's not too hairy
i mean that's fine i'm used to like cat
hair in my mouth just from me too and in
my eyes and everywhere
i can i can like pet you with it it's
very fluffy
no but you like cats don't you
did you did you want to say something at
the end by the way
oh um i have a new schedule up and i'm
doing an unarchived karaoke stream
and then after i do that i've got a
little after party and then i'm gonna
play resident evil again and then i'm
going away
for a four or five days um this is kind
of a wow but
during that time i'm releasing my my
brand new cover song
i just got the mix today um i heard it
heard it
yeah yeah i said i sent it to kusatori
it was awesome and
thank you um i did ask for like a couple
little corrections
um so the the perfect version is
probably going to be here tomorrow
um so yeah i'm very excited i already
sounded so perfect
yay thank you yeah i guess um i don't
know i talked with the mixer a little
bit about it and we both agreed on some
things being changed here and there so
hopefully the final terrific version
will be tomorrow and then the mv is
being made so
hopefully uh no actually i'm
i'm asking uh two other people keeping
it a secret now but they're
probably good because you're so busy
anyway
i'll be able to do all my own art for
mv's but it's kind of hard right now
maybe someday
all right all right sounds exciting we
both have exciting weeks
but i hope you can take a nice break in
those three days
i will i'll try to relax a little bit
yeah so
that's it for today guys that was it
takes two
we've finished it i hope y'all had fun
with it
if you just watched the final one and
missed some episodes for some reason the
last one was on kelly's channel the one
before was on my channel and the first
one was on galley's channel so if you
need to catch up on something there you
go
uh thank you thank you very much it was
it was a pleasure thank you guys for
uh supporting us in this playthrough
yay and in german we say
wiedersehen yes bye bye
see you guys tomorrow
[Music]
peace
you