​​​ ​We're ready to greet the world!​ ​​
​​​ ​We're voyaging forward with courage​ ​​
​​​ ​to run toward a brand-new start​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go live!​ ​​
​​​ ​Bridging the distance​ ​​
​​ ​across the sea endlessly​ ​​
​​​ ​Cheerfully meeting heart to heart!​ ​​
​​​ ​hololive English - Connect the World​ ​​
​​​ ​Lyrics: Stephanie Snyder​ ​​
​​​ ​Cheerfully meeting heart to heart!​ ​​
​​​ ​Composition, Arrangement: Ryota Nakano​ ​​
​​​ ​Vocals: Mori Calliope, Takanashi Kiara,​ ​​
​​ ​Ninomae Ina'nis, Gawr Gura, Watson Amelia​ ​​
​​​ ​Vocals: IRyS, Ceres Fauna, Ouro Kronii,​ ​​
​​ ​Nanashi Mumei, Hakos Baelz​ ​​
​​​ ​Waking from a dream,​ ​​
​​ ​swept up into a stream​ ​​
​​​ ​I make a wish and wait for my cue—​ ​​
​​​ ​How will we connect in this​ ​​
​​​ ​new frontier we're journeying through?​ ​​
​​​ ​Thriving in a scene where no one's ever been​ ​​
​​​ ​With vibrant colors bursting like stars—​ ​​
​​​ ​Radiant and warm; charged with energy​ ​​
​​​ ​that's carried us this far.​ ​​
​​​ ​Each new debut brings a miracle to life​ ​​
​​​ ​Surely​ ​​
​​​ ​We've gotta take that chance​ ​​
​​​ ​We're running nonstop; straight to the top​ ​​
​​​ ​That's right!​ ​​
​​​ ​We're ready to change the game​ ​​
​​​ ​A shimmering showcase​ ​​
​​​ ​Creating a new place where we can shine!​ ​​
​​​ ​Day by day, sparkling stories will intertwine​ ​​
​​​ ​Get ready to cross the waves​ ​​
​​​ ​We're voyaging forward with courage​ ​​
​​​ ​to run toward a brand-new stage​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go live!​ ​​
​​​ ​Bridging the distance​ ​​
​​ ​across the sea endlessly​ ​​
​​​ ​Follow me and we'll turn the page!​ ​​
​​​ ​Breaking through the doubt,​ ​​
​​​ ​we know we'll figure out​ ​​
​​​ ​a way to clear each towering trial​ ​​
​​​ ​Sharing all our hopes,​ ​​
​​​ ​we can conquer any challenge with a smile!​ ​​
​​​ ​We'll link our hearts​ ​​
​​ ​as we search across the globe​ ​​
​​​ ​Knowing​ ​​
​​​ ​No matter where we are,​ ​​
​​ ​no matter how far​ ​​
​​​ ​We can be stars​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go!​ ​​
​​​ ​I wanna chase a wish unwaveringly,​ ​​
​​​ ​playing out a grand story​ ​​
​​​ ​Share the futures that we can see​ ​​
​​​ ​Making them reality!​ ​​
​​​ ​Take my hand and reach for the screen​ ​​
​​​ ​All we need are glittering dreams​ ​​
​​​ ​Our hearts and souls,​ ​​
​​​ ​all fulfilled in the world we build!​ ​​
​​​ ​We're ready to seize the day​ ​​
​​​ ​Traversing the pathways,​ ​​
​​​ ​discovering highways to everywhere!​ ​​
​​​ ​Step by step,​ ​​
​​ ​gathering stories that we can share!​ ​​
​​​ ​Get ready to lead the way​ ​​
​​​ ​With each generation, a shining sensation​ ​​
​​​ ​a dream unfurls—​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's make friends,​ ​​
​​​ ​making a moment of history joyfully!​ ​​
​​​ ​Follow me; we'll connect the world!​ ​​
​​​ ​They'll hear our song ringing out​ ​​
​​ ​over hills and oceans​ ​​
​​​ ​Our legend grows and continues!​ ​​
​​​ ​We'll carry on starting now;​ ​​
​​ ​setting hearts in motion—​ ​​
​​​ ​Connecting all of the world!​ ​​