[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
thank you
assistant
[Music]
[Applause]
this is
[Music]
no no no no no
no no no no no no no no
ah
chicken again
happy New Year oh my God I'm so loud in
my own ear
so loud
[Music]
does it sound very noisy I think it does
I'm kind of quiet no I didn't turn up
your volume
your volume yeah
not me
[Music]
ah oh my God my laptop sounds so noisy
it's not really that noisy but the way
the microphone picks up the
laptop engine do you hear it going
through
oh my God
it's going like full speed right now
does my usual volume though well it's
not my usual setup so of course it's
Gonna Change
yeah
take off yeah it sounds like a airplane
taking off
[Music]
let me turn off this
come on
yeah are you hearing the bgm should I
turn it lower or is it okay
it's
a whole life
ambient bgm
perfect okay
I saw
it's been a while since I used this
background and this setup in general
oh thank you guys for the super chance
thank you
thank you thank you uh if I can I won't
I want to try to get to some
super chats
uh later in the Stream
um I have some plans for the evening
just made some plans
um
with some some girls
so I can't go too long
but yeah
and we're gonna talk about
um my appearing friends from yesterday
did you guys watch it I know it was
sudden so and like when it wasn't sudden
but it wasn't announced beforehand so
and I think some of you guys
uh don't
um yeah so you guys missed it
yeah you waited until now okay that's
actually fine because we're gonna watch
it together and I'm gonna explain and
try to translate a little bit
um
it was live yeah
and I mean it was decided already a long
time ago it's not like I replaced okay
senpai
uh but originally I was supposed to be
like
was there I would have been there for
half an hour or so
Empire got sick unfortunately I was
there since the beginning until the end
yay they changed up some things and then
I was able to participate the whole time
and I want to talk about the experience
because it was kind of a first-time
experience to yeah do some things
um
first time Variety in 3D
and at the studio there
so yeah
yeah so proud of you thank you I
actually
oh I think
what happened is
a while ago when I decided I'm going to
Japan at this time
I just I just said oh by the way I'll be
in Japan at this time if there's any
program that I could participate in and
3D that would be so cool
and it was taken into consideration
[Music]
I actually I was part of the New Year's
program last year and the year before
that too
but
uh that wasn't 2D
if you remember remember
do you remember
[Music]
the 2020 one December and the 2020
December 2.
[Music]
I think uh
one year it was
I think
wait and wasn't it one more couple it
was like three couples I think
and we reviewed
our favorite moments I think
a long time ago
those were the couples
yeah
ah
I play a telephone game with me and
others
it
to die
are you sure that was me was that me
for a New Year's program
did I really do that I don't remember
that
you're 2021
was that two new years
ah you mean the Miko Court in the 24
hour I was talking about a um official
stream you were talking about the Mi
Corona 24 hours one now
yeah that's different
um
anyway how you guys doing
it's 2023 over here and even if I was in
Europe at the time right right now it
would also be 2023 they're already as
well
um
just you guys some of you guys over
there in an a
are not quite ready yet
as far as I know
more than three hours
oh
you still got some time you're living in
the past
lame
also
skill issue
um do I sound sick
I think
um
wait I I I I I I
um I think
um no I'm not not so sleepy and
[Music]
certain in certain ways I got sicker
yeah nasally mm-hmm
um
I remember my last stream in Austria
my nose was pretty clear I didn't have
to blow my nose much at all anymore
[Music]
um but ever since I arrived in Japan
um by my Hannah museum is not
cannot stop it my snot cannot be stopped
[Music]
yeah it's pretty bad
and my flag is
very much
in full bloom still
what the [\h__\h] man I think the hanamizu
it's not it's just because it's cold and
yeah
it just reactivated my nose sensors
um but I've been sleeping
in a very dry room so
that might have also been making it
worse yeah
I still make money of it
sorry to hear you're still sick
I'm not no no I don't know yeah
you know the the worst situations are
when I you know ride a bus or a train
and I noticed that
um it gets much worse
uh it's probably the air I guess but
it's always in a bus or in a train that
my throat suddenly feels like coughing a
lot and I don't want a cop
too much
because
the people in the train and so on they
all they look at me and they're like
um
she have the Rona
[Music]
foreign
every time it happens I've been trying
to drink as much tea as possible
and uh spit the flag into tissue
and then
stick to half wet tissue back into my
tiny bag
so disgusting
[Music]
um
very informative
as always
volume is low huh we'll raise it
I don't believe it
um
does that sound like toilet paper to you
because yes it is toilet paper
um
[Music]
well
but I am just glad that yesterday it
went okay without me having too much of
a throat of a cough attack
like throughout the whole stream
yesterday my throat wasn't feeling that
comfortable I wanted to cough and I was
holding back but
at least I had no like
big attack so
you only called once no no no you can
count it I coughed way more than once
and just try to
not make it too obvious but
[Music]
um
well wow wow wow
oh
yeah I was holding it together
for one hour
um
[Music]
I'm drinking tea right now I'm still
trying
[Music]
to drink lots and lots of pee
no I didn't I didn't spit on anyone
why would I
what
made my ocean be well unhealthy I hope
so too
yeah yeah
you know when I was eating the sofa
and I I you know it was about making
noise and I couldn't
so that was so funny to myself and I was
trying to hold back my life because
otherwise they would notice oh it's it's
her
um so then I guess it sounded a little
bit like I was like throwing up or so
because Mew said it was like is she
throwing up is she okay is she throwing
up no I was just trying to hold back my
love
but the fact that I couldn't slurp was I
guess already too much of a giveaway
um
what's the look he sent by oh man I'm
gonna comment more on this
um when we start watching the Vlog
me who knows this out too well no
apparently not because it wasn't
throwing up
present
no it wasn't spicy food it was just
plain soba
with soy sauce I guess
this soy sauce
Happy New Year
[Music]
yeah I was just trying to
make them doubt themselves but of course
a Japanese person
can slurp
there's no way that the non-sloping one
would be one of the Japanese members no
way
hey
foreign
this is so weird without VOD context
okay don't worry you'll get it
um
[Music]
foreign
when I stopped talking suddenly you know
what it is
I actually had to now I think you
noticed my coughing but I don't think
you noticed me
um I think one time getting rid of some
of like in the middle of the stream
yesterday I was just I just went
somewhere took a tissue and
you know wiped my my tongue with the
tissue
and I really don't I know foreign
Happy New Year
and I want that one
so I was trying to hide it from everyone
the staff and and the members I don't
think they realized what I was doing
I was turning my back on them
[Music]
loud loud noise
thank you guys for the super chance
thank you thank you oh my God happy New
Year guys
ah saw you drinking water yeah I was
drinking water auntie
um
that was so much going on yeah that's
what I love so much about Japanese
members
they're like especially in programs like
these it's very noticeable but also in
their normal collab streams or even solo
streams they talk and scream so much
and everyone screams and laughs
yeah
it's funny
and I have like some stories I don't
know if I should tell them after about
watching or before
um
[Music]
after
okay
[Music]
well then wait I guess we can wait for
that if you wanna are you guys not going
out to see fireworks
the ones who are New Year in shower
manage
I'm so sorry I want this to stop already
hmm
not this year
oh
no watching raining all day so what
I just want to stop you
um
wow so much flag them
oh I I have I still have
hahaha
China bringing me tissues oh and the
moisturizer
oh
jenma finally woke up
Tim I slept so much I was trying not to
wake Jenna up
she woke up one minute before my stream
I wonder how
did she do that
was it a alarm from YouTube
or was it just the feeling that
something's about to start
hmm
beep beep
beep be me
moisturizer is being activated
wait it's not called Lisbon
hydrate
I forgot the word
wait the chat will tell me
I forgot toys
thank you humidifier I mean it's
basically it is a moisturizer it's
moisturizing the room the air
humidifier oh
not happy oh oh now it's working
[Music]
make this room so wet that it's gonna
start molding
by the way guys I am currently in my
dream streaming setup
I mean that mic is not ideal but you
want to know why this is my dream setup
cause I'm
on the floor on a Japanese like floor
chair
on my futon with a little futon table or
like bed table
so I'm in bed I'm in futon
um
foreign
[Music]
my blanket I have my blanket over my
feet
I could even lie down if I want to
hit
um
[Music]
I love this I love this very comfy
more
oh yeah I'm using the kiwama blanket
um
because um uh General had only one
blanket
and I was like this is cool don't you
have another blanket she said no but
then I was like what about the Kiwa
blanket can I use a blanket
so I got to use
the Chihuahua blanket I said
hey at least you get kiwama blanket with
kiwawa scent it's extra special
and I saw so many of you guys received
the merchandise
even outside of like Japan
today
ma'am it's called a blanket
yeah yeah okay blanket
I guess I officially called it Blanca
didn't I
um
it's so big so I'm using two blankets
two blankets
a blanket and a blanket
[Music]
um
my mom like the middens oh I need them
too I wonder if they're gonna arrive at
my place soon too like in Austria
because recently I lost my oven mitten
okay I'm finally have any more perfect
timing for some new ones
recently as in
I think since Christmas because my
sister and her boyfriend were using my
kitchen
and now I don't know where my freaking
oven Mitten is
um inside of mittens are super cute yeah
they have inside lining
they have a pattern inside
attention to detail
s
foreign
[Music]
Japan didn't have fireworks so sad
oh
but
um
you want to know what I did at midnight
what did what did Kiowa do at midnight
hmm I tweeted a few minutes afterwards
but what was I doing at midnight
I was sleeping
um
afterwards
I can't [\h__\h] believe it I can't
[\h__\h] believe it it's so lame to sleep
through New Year's
um
after the
the you know appearance
after the stream
um
you know I changed into my mother
clothes and uh
yeah me and Jenna
I kept my I kept my evening completely
open
but it just stayed empty so me and
gentleman just went to eat some Ramen
um really going around I wanted to eat
ramen anyway so
so
[Music]
um we ate Ramen and then I we got back
pretty early
and yeah I was I was tired
and because my room is so cold I had no
choice but to hide in my huton under my
blankets and being a bit tired in
combination with being on the blankets
kind of makes you tired so I fell asleep
like really fast at 10 pm
at 10 pm but my goal was to still wake
up at midnight at the latest to say
Happy New Year to jenma
but then I slept through it
and I woke up like eight minutes later
and I said Happy New Year
with half open eyes and bad hair
and then I went to I went back to bed
soon after and that's why I was up so
early I guess I mean I still felt like
sleeping even longer
but you know
foreign
[Music]
really fast these past days
but I haven't been sleeping so well
because I wake up so much
um because I
I don't know I I feel like I'm drying
like some dried seaweed
I'm turning into dried seaweed
[Music]
um
yeah the moisturizer
I hope it helps a bit I'm not saying at
10 months Place forever
um switching two different uh Hotel an
actual Hotel
soon
[Music]
yeah
yeah yeah
okay so wait now we can watch it
[Music]
uh we're gonna watch it I am gonna show
it on screen and I'm gonna comment on it
um
just right there
she's so loud at least with my earbuds
in can I hear the feedback
oh I want to get a bit closer without
bum Bumble bulking the table with my
knees
okay
yeah I'm streaming I I wait
it's actually a good time for PST for
once
I never stream at a good time for PST
it might be loud for a second or maybe
not but talking about the testing or
testing
[Music]
there we go
foreign
it won't let me hear it
how come
ah I know why
click click click click click huh
and properties
wait where do I set the audio output it
but I heard the other stuff it's just
OBS okay I know I know I know I've been
streaming for so many years now that I
should I I know how to troubleshoot this
here sound settings oh
sound settings
apps and [\h__\h]
obs
go to my microphone
because I have I guess the audio coming
through the microphone so
nope I don't hear it
what
[Music]
happened
not fair
[Music]
I tried I tried using my my new
Bluetooth wireless
I don't think the pairing really worked
I was trying to pair them but I'm such a
new but Bluetooth pairing I suck at it
[Music]
whatever game music
maybe
I'm setting the output too
[Music]
I'll look back and go back to the
beginning
Happy New Year
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah
let's turn that off
turn the Bluetooth off again
happy New Year Happy New Year
[Music]
what's going on
ah ah
um
it wasn't the fact that the OBS volume
was at the very bottom
s
[Music]
Happy New Year
[Applause]
[Music]
don't listen too much to what's going on
yet
um
why
[Music]
how about I try
what happens if I just play normally on
my windows
if I display it normally in the like
player it works can I capture that
player
let's do it there
um
what capturing sauce would that be
[Music]
Let's test this
no
[Music]
we'll get there guys
how about this
uh-huh that's just that eh
foreign
VLC
do I have a little C on this one I do I
downloaded it before
yeah okay let's try it that instead of
feel safe yeah it's so loud again
oh my God
broke my ears
um okay
[Music]
so
window capture
VLC oh VLC doesn't show up as an option
though
no
are you sure it can be captured because
it doesn't look like it
maybe ah wait there's a there's a
specific one for it is it
well how does this work
no I don't know how that works
uh it should give you the option to add
extra programs
really
um
[Music]
foreign
make sure you captured Source isn't
minimized and problems I only have one
one monitor right now let me see okay
does it work if I have it
open
it does work if it's not minimized
okay
let's
it but I
just seen a black screen
see
I mean I see it in VLC but in OBS it
just shows it's a black screen
interesting
yeah sometimes
you can't capture searching things in
OBS and just shows you a black screen
like this I've had this before
um
mmm
oh no no no no no no no
no no
extra screen necessary now I got no
space
um
it's a copyright protection
some videos you need another player
okay okay what if what if I have this
Windows player windows and open
my dad
uh
no the windows player
the windows player does not show up at
all
okay
I want to just play it in OBS but I
can't hear the audio okay new idea
uh
I'm gonna just
uh plug the earbuds
in out of my microphone
and into
the PC the laptop
hoping that
this way it will not be so [\h__\h]
annoying
now will it work
we will see
now
[Music]
it's just awkward when I don't have
feedback in my ears I don't like that
[Music]
I was gonna give it
um
foreign
[Music]
you can wait well I can't wait I'm
getting pissed off now
[Music]
[\h__\h]
unplug the piece
this time I actually don't have a pizza
I only have a switch no I didn't break
my switch or capture card I don't know
none of that
oh yes monitoring device check my OBS
audio monitoring device
it was the microphone
but that didn't work so let's
fix this
did that come from my PC speakers or did
that come from my headphones I don't
even know anymore
dude
yeah I didn't bring my switch there's PC
games did you know
I have a gaming laptop and there's PC
games and then console games are not the
only thing
rewind the stream before you appear
yes
keep on going back it's an endless loop
microphone
[Music]
what's Windows audio ducking
oh you can change the mode to Windows
10.
automatic bit clip mode
doesn't work for VLC
change the mode
to Windows 10
uh-huh
let me try
where's Dad
uh
ah there it is
there it is there it is
okay okay
wait I'll see
foreign
you sound like you know what you're
talking about so I hope this works now
wait
even though I have
[Music]
even though I have the earbuds plugged
into my laptop the audio is coming from
the speakers right now let me plug it
back into the microphone now
oh yeah get in there okay
and now
wait that's still coming from my
speakers
it's still coming from my speakers
but
can we at least see it now
[Music]
uh
can I at least
oh
[Music]
wait I'm like a new one didn't work
Windows capture
mm-hmm
[Music]
oh okay
yeah the windows
10. thing works
it creates a weird frame for it
but that's okay
what is that weird frame
it's that's actually where the
Blackboard should have been
okay
oh now we just want the one the audio is
going through my speakers
before it was
still going from my earphones
there this should fix it this should be
it
yes
the videos are on the video is on screen
and I hear it from my earbuds finally
yeah
us
finally oh you don't hear okay too much
so much it's okay I can fix that here
okay I know it's quiet
mirrored oh
that's a
that's actually because
I needed I have a mirrored setting on
VLC because I need to learn dances with
it I can fix it oopsie
I can fix that too
I'll fix everything
okay
yeah it makes sense
[Music]
oh
okay
okay yeah
um
okay
uh
how is this
oh my God it's so loud in my ear I know
it's still kind of quiet for you guys
but I have to talk over it anyway so
extremely soft
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] I make it quieter here it was
too loud anyway
and louder here how about this
time
where's the shop tell us okay here we go
[Music]
so fubuki is empty at this time I'm
still hidden in the corner looking at
them being nervous about
being there in a moment
they're so cute
live translation yeah I'm not gonna like
try to solve everything because they
talk way too much
originally
we're supposed to be Gamers
but there's not a gamer right
uh they're all very sad about every time
when it gets mentioned that okay isn't
here they were crying like babies
yeah her ears are moving so much it's so
cute
[Music]
uh smoke
yeah Gamers plus one
honorary gamer
somebody says
yeah yeah
[Music]
I thought it was funny you know how Neil
said by uses Uchi to refer to herself
the
not so common
uh I actually do that too so we were the
Uchi team
team
I think we're then whole life really not
many refer to themselves as Uchi
movie
[Music]
that's the plan streams and here was
still a question mark of people
did not know
who is gonna be there
oh
first program of the day
I was was I always was live
which made me even more nervous
I hinted it yeah but still so many of
you guys didn't get it you get it
afterwards but you didn't get beforehand
but my Silhouette was in the trailer
which was still like for people who
weren't watching it
not really much of a help
and I know she's seen that's what I'm
here for
sure
[Music]
yeah we're not gonna watch the 11 p.m
countdown live because you see a bit not
gonna do that since it's just one kiwama
performance
but
that doesn't need translating either so
you guys can just watch it yourself if
you didn't yet
[Music]
just you know General introductions
Holo quiz New Year's special
the camera
so I was asking
somebody who wants to ask what's special
about Corona interrupted her
what's special
oh The Specialist that there's a special
guest
[Music]
s oh
yes
I ran and gave everyone a high five and
then this is a Japanese
um old comedian joke that pose at the
end
I'm sure you guys don't know it but it's
called kumanechi
community
[Music]
I was so nervous I [\h__\h] up my
introduction but I didn't even know what
to say
I just said I'm first generation Phoenix
and then I said Happy New Years and
they're like it's not New Years yet
here's my announcement of my new butt
yes
I said my blood got fixed
the morning
yeah this is the first time that you
guys got to see the new booty
oh 10K uploads on Reddit nice
okay
a juicy juicy butt is better for bird
meat
thank you
what's going on now they're just
fighting again like little kids
who can help please move on move on
[Laughter]
they're so chaotic
[Music]
two teams
and I noticed this before the others did
I told them hey because you know this is
kind of like the red team and the yellow
team
kind of color coded
my my orange looks kind of red in this
lineup
[Music]
height matched
that's only because of her ears though
people took a screenshot of this and it
looks like the meme from
um
what's it
you guys know what I mean
[Music]
yeah Toy Story
what a coincidence
creating memes
I was hoping for that
[Music]
it's just like me shut up
she doesn't have much confidence she
says we probably won't win but she's
doing her best
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
okay first game
you see Nation quiz
it's oh and then
here
[Music]
I know the meaning of course I just
asked for entertainment value
for real though
and she explains to me it's having like
a
like connection with the other knowing
what they what they mean like a soulmate
[Music]
the first one is
guess which country
is your partner's kanji
at all
and I said if I don't have to ride it by
hand I'm good and I can read them and I
can write it on like a PC or phone but
writing by hand is oof
I don't know
okay here's some backstory
uh before I think after the rehearsal
before the actual stream
um
uh we were asked to write down one kanji
that describes uh our one year 2022 and
I was the first one to think of one and
you know so you already know probably
which one I chose yeah and then
Corona Senpai was like thinking for so
so so so so long she just couldn't think
of a kanji that describes hers uh By the
time
producer came back in and was like did
you decide on your kanjis and I'm like I
did and
the others were like
I couldn't understand if I still didn't
have
a kanji yeah
eventually though
finally she followed one and we will see
now which one that was
I am trying to cheat tell me tell me you
said by which one is yours
is
I was trying to cheat but I'm not even
the one choosing the answers he was
so clearness Empire is trying to get
someone who's kanji right but we all
wrote One
no questions allowed
[Music]
[Laughter]
I made cute poses well I did see it like
a feedback of the camera the whole time
in front of me
so I knew when I was on camera
[Music]
and even when I wasn't on camera I was
trying to do things that maybe gets the
camera to switch to me
it works it works
okay so here we have wait uh here we
have a is new B is uh travel C is
um
that that plot game what's it called
the the pot the guy with the hammer
thing and the pots trying to get on top
of the the mountain
a jar yeah getting over it it's a
reference to that yeah and then D is
nothing
yeah cauldron cauldron
so here one of them is mine but they're
trying to sort all of them to the
correct people I think
so it's like I know chihuahuas
and I'm like do you want to switch teams
so that I would be in a routine
well I think mine's easy though
again
[Music]
what happened what happened in my ears
tonight
and nothing is red as moot if it's just
that single kanji
your mind's tabby
spoiler alert spoiler
[Music]
here okay you know how there's five
members here and only four kanji so I
for entertainment value
asked for example what's your country
because I want to involve her too oh wow
entertain her brain entertain the brain
coconut
height tonight
would love to hear for sure
foreign
[Music]
okay everyone's ready
I'm surprised if I had wrong maybe it
was for entertainment value
so many games and did like watch along
so that seems like a journey
this was just like
even though it's wrong
[Music]
you said by saying since I have wings I
can go wherever I want
and I'm saying yeah yeah I mean I just
traveled here to to Japan so it makes
sense
please
it's just like what is everybody's
listening she's drawing on the board
and there we go
so new is
Journey is for me
uh cauldron is from you Senpai and
nothing is foreign
he's saying mine is very obvious yeah
and then counting where I went
but I forget
[Music]
I had something yeah
if I didn't forget any other country I
mentioned I mentioned Italy Maldives
Korea America
did I forget something
she's explaining that she cleared
getting over it for the first time this
year
him drinking
they're asking me to fight cleared and I
said I've never played it before
I asked her to support me
give me mental support
if I ever play it
seems that you know what Kuru simply
said about her year about Suarez year is
correct
but it fits more to the new kanji
because you tried so many new blue
things
I of course I was trying to make excuses
that her year cannot be told in one
kanji that's why she chose nothing but
as We Know
you couldn't think of anything
[Music]
she just couldn't think of anything
[Laughter]
thank you
so we got a point
we're gonna find
you know I was actually feeling kind of
nervous about being on music by his team
because I you know the others they all
know each other so well and I didn't
want me to standby to feel like
about being with me so I wanted to do
well
and thankfully spoiler alert we won
by a landslide so
I think
she definitely did not regret it at
least
what next is the silver game
which one is your partner
your partner's slippery noises
asking who likes Silva
I don't dislike sober but I just don't
ever eat it
[Music]
no she's asking me well what do we eat
for New Year's then because soba is
quite popular for New Year's here in
Japan
and I said there's nothing particular in
Austria but what we do is uh
big fireworks at midnight and I was
surprised they don't do that in Japan
even though they love Fireworks
and they want to do it now I don't think
Japanese neighborhoods will forget it
oh champagne yeah but that's not food
but I guess yeah
I didn't realize that because I don't
drink alcohol but you're right
so here we are deciding
which one
eats the soba
music is like I want to hear Kyo
[Music]
spoiler alert there was nothing to hear
in the first place
I'm like I forgot I forgot to taste it
so I'm curious I want to eat it again
polite silent eater
oh
they prepared so much soba
so many sub animals I you know you know
obviously we're not gonna eat everything
on the stream right but I felt so sorry
that
there was I think a lot of leftover but
there are also a lot of stuff so
hopefully they just ate
um
the remaining soba you know they made
fresh soba there and there were like so
many plates of soba like small portions
of sopa noodles
um
but it was good the it's just super
noodles with some soy sauce and it's
simple but it tastes good and they're
cold by the way they're cold
actually that was even uh even in the
rehearsal that was a rehearsal so far
foreign
food they often write a little like note
on the screen after this stream after
this uh after this program the staff ate
the remains happily
yeah
[Music]
will be the third one to confuse
so it's not just two options
and she's also gonna be
trying to
survive
oh they were really wearing
um like some
something to hide your eyes
actually
before the uh actual program
we all got to wear different individual
blindfolds and mine was an RGB rainbow
moving animated blindfold I didn't get
to show you guys though because I wasn't
the one being blindfolded oh is somebody
who had a really funny one so for the
stuff I got like I think it was like
some really funny Mimi
small Jago eyes on a blindfold
it was so funny every time the camera in
the rehearsal went to Subaru Senpai it
was just such a funny face yeah
unfortunately you couldn't see those but
yeah the others have some funny
blindfolds too
so what is
foreign
okay hold on this was really cool yeah I
was so animated it can like unfold and
turn around you will see it now
I'm checking checking if they can see
oh
it's like it's like she's a ninja
I think
yeah
it would already be funny if it was just
that but here we go here we go
[Music]
85. it's kind of spelling out uh Yago in
Japanese
[Laughter]
someone's like I'm leaving my team let's
do it together and I know I know I know
I know this is something I do like why
why are they inside of each other
no idea how that happened but we were
like bumping against each other like
clumsy leaves
we were too close a little bit too close
to each other we Fusion
here poke is giving people the order
of who's
first in Salon but then someone who
answered when she was
told she's first
so we had to redo it
oh
[Music]
okay
first slurping by subasho
hey
I feel like it was even louder in real
life
we had like a microphone right in front
of the noodles
and had to slurp into that
I know I was it was so funny
having a microphone on the Slurpee
she's doing so well
you see if I gave a really serious
answer
now she's meaning
it's like I can't really guess who it is
just by hearing one sort of things
oh the corner is like
she's right
how did you know
they must have been out slurping a lot
Ramen or you don't know or whatever
I was louder in real life I was starting
to run around 2007.2 because I was
trying to confuse the two in the back to
make them maybe
you know unsure about who where who is
standing where you know
supported
it did confused oh
so I was surprised too but this was on
purpose fubuki Senpai was slurping
weirdly on purpose
like someone who can't slurp well
they were like is this a bird
sounds like a bird
[Music]
foreign
but only because she hasn't heard the
third one yet
surprised it can get even worse
can daddy with worse
[Music]
you see how I look I turned around for
the camera because I saw on the other
side too that I was on camera
there were screens on both sides on the
room in the room back in front
Mickey Mouse hi
guys
your left hand
left-handed
yep I'm eating you just don't hear it
they're like is she eating
and I'm starting to laugh so hard but
I'm trying to hold inside to not make a
noise
I have to say those sounds really sound
like a maybe I'm throwing up but I
wasn't I was just like
I don't know what it was a little sound
I was trying really hard to make a sound
that wasn't really it
is
[Music]
no yeah
that was too obvious
it was again too obvious
[Music]
um
I tried to go to Corona Senpai sometimes
because I missed her she was so far and
you know until the stream we were like
like a match made in heaven you guys
don't even understand what happened
before the Stream
we were flirting so much and she was we
kept on staring at each other for hours
and then during this dream it suddenly
stopped because she was so far away and
we couldn't look at each other anymore
but I really wanted to go to court on
the same fight
yeah I love her so much oh my God
yeah
yes for hours
the moment oh my God she was like she
was praising me so much but I'll tell
you more about it later but I'll tell
you the love story when we got some more
time later
but once you want you guys to know that
and and really unexpected
love has bloomed
um
[Music]
she's just trying to get closer to the
corners
it was good
I kind of wanted to eat more
but you know you know have to stop
eating
[Music]
well now that I have to guess who was
who
Ops
and even though music plays on the same
team I was still trying to confuse her
are you sure your shirts really like
that
Bubba's so mad at me
is cuter
[Music]
you said that's funny
oh I think um
chicken oh
yes see I can slurp without anything in
my mouth
but once there's noodles involved
I don't know I know it's like how do you
slurp when there's noodles in your mouth
oh happy New Years
too
Mexico
Happy New Year
okay
[Music]
she's like she's doing something
because we're already done writing
yeah yeah making sounds while they're
eating is definitely like rude and Bad
Manners in
in Austria oh [\h__\h] my batteries because
I can't connect my
my charging cable for my phone
because it's too far away
I can't charge
what's dying General if you're listening
to this do you have an extension or
something like that
[Music]
I think she was listening
foreign
so they're saying the absolutely correct
answer
both of them
extension cord
s
[Music]
not at all that's
great
yeah he's just staying on purpose she
was doing it
like
clumsily thank you for the superche guys
thank you
foreign
[Music]
I do have to say though it is a bit
difficult
I practice a lot so it works
but it's quite difficult for me
hey do we can't slip too really
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
for the first time in a long time
I don't even remember when was the last
time I ate them thank you
happy birthday and happy New Year
it's also
Kyle carrot's birthday today
[Music]
oh my God
oh three two let's go
we're in the lid still
I was roasting them because they know
each other
way longer than we do
and yet they're losing
someone's like don't hurt me like that
you're saying it's true but don't hurt
me like that
trying to fix the relationship here
but they're acting like that but they
they love each other
jokes
you can see they get along really well
but for some reason they're not in the
lead
I don't even know what's good what
happened here
[Music]
I don't know I don't know
just being tated
[Music]
so this is again just another attempt of
me trying to get back to Korea
that's that's really just it and in
super Senpai got jealous pushed corn on
the same far away and made me sit on her
[Music]
I miss her already
surprised how people want to be
Sat On By Me
[Music]
the next game will be without points but
uh they're doing it because I'm here
okay
so this is a telephone game
Telephone Game Time
a classic
[Music]
so I started by looking at the prompt
remember it tell it to the next person
and in the end they have to bring it
back to me and we'll see if ah
I praised her
her tail was cute
yeah and then I decided whether or not
it was oh okay enough
or if it's
too bad
happy New Year guys
oh yeah super sample is English
pretty decent
it's gonna do her best and she was like
doubting herself again and I said have
confidence
ah
she says her English isn't good
then I said but you made a famous phrase
you coined a famous phrase
do you remember
and Dad thank you forever
[Music]
but here she's explaining that but yeah
she call the famous English meme phrase
so she shouldn't underestimate her
English skills
[Music]
that's so widespread but I told her to
hear basically
I said the first one should be someone
you can rely on
but they started with music but we're
doing two rounds
[Music]
deciding who goes next you okay
okay
so
cute they're so cute
[Music]
cool
okay okay
I was worried I couldn't remember the
whole sentence when it goes away
through the velocity doesn't help
restaurants
I think the second round was also about
the same
[Music]
weird phrases yeah but they're kind of
related to New Years
they eat rice cakes often
for New Year's
it's on theme on topic
oh first round I was still doing very
very quiet whispering in the second
round I was
a bit louder
still picked up by the microphone
[Laughter]
thank you
I I joined
ice cake
I heard that
I was really worried but that I think
Corner cyber didn't change it much
she didn't [\h__\h] it up much for her
[Music]
live stage
honey Moon
they're trying to translate that back to
Japanese makes no sense
become one with the rice cake
but I guess it changed it from ice cake
back to rice cake
[Music]
I thought that was not good enough
avoid choking on rice cakes
I look so tall in this group don't I
thought so too
much
[Music]
thank you
okay
okay round two
minutes
because everyone is standing like that
but they I guess they don't know the
meme so they were not joining it
it's right did you guys notice
he said until this point I'm not worried
[Music]
Ness being honest
being honest
[Laughter]
the charging is not keeping up with my
[Music]
I think I think it will survive
now this one I don't know I don't I
thought the rice cakes were kind of on
topic but the honey the crabs
toys
[Music]
yeah quiet when eating crabs foreign
how do you it's different from Android
when I when I pull down from the top of
the phone it doesn't give me the
brightness how it doesn't
oh
from the Android how does how do you do
it in the iPhone
top right
ah you're right
okay okay
thank you I'm an iPhone noob
no I heard the elephant it was not so
bad it was pretty much the same
good job somebody
write it
eating
[Music]
[\h__\h]
ing
people
eating crumbs foreign
[Music]
United
eating good
bye
it's like
not bummer
I think I'll think of something that
makes sense
at least you remembered
[Laughter]
because she's happy that she's
remembered and I'm like that was pretty
good
it wasn't United but I thought
tonight it's even better
than the original sentence because
before it was just they were quiet for
being united while eating crabs is just
such a wholesome sentence isn't it
she said something different Corner
Senpai changed it
I guess create that though yeah quiet
could I did she added an R
without the art would have been good
[Music]
but I gave it an okay I gave the final
result and okay
they are quiet when eating crabs
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
would be you remember that that
telephone game
uh I mean yeah there's been a couple of
telephone game streams
but the others I've seen with and so on
were pretty bad
pretty bad
so compared to those
what happened here was pretty good
[Music]
okay next is
charades when I saw charades in the
script that was like
you can charades charades is always like
choice is always part of please 3D like
activities
especially for the debut streams
it's all charades
okay here we decided cool the team is
doing the charade and you know this is
my first time in the variety
program I got the spot again
and here I'm flossing
I think before the stream I taught I
think call of this Empire how to floss I
was like do you know this dance
she didn't know but I explained her it's
um from that shooting game
uh what's it called again I forgot but
call this if I guessed it right
yeah I think yeah Fortnight yeah I think
I taught her I taught someone I think it
was caught on his head butt
okay
it's cute
[Music]
superhero
it's the first one
no I didn't know that at the time
let's see what she does
and I'm like it's going to say
bye
I had no idea what that was
after it was in Minecraft I had no idea
[Music]
here
that one I got I was like superhero I
got it
foreign
she said
first
the villains were fighting and then the
superhero arrived at the scene
um
she said she did that just because doing
only the superhero movement maybe would
have been too obvious right away
which is true because that's how I
understood
yay
foreign
[Music]
next
I got to
go
yeah
and she told me the only movement no
voice of course oh
actually that reminds me
I don't know why but for some reason
before the Stream
well when we were all in the same room
topic came up for some reason
and
I I did my us impression
for them and and super simple
suddenly they were like who was that
just that that was so good that was that
was like it sounds like her and like and
that was me they were all so impressed
with my pecula boys let's go yeah but I
was worried about how to
how to
impersonate pikoda just by moving and
ready
yeah
and I I thought just doing bunny hops
might be
kind of too easy but at the same time
kind of too General
kind of lame but I couldn't think of
anything else
oh
speaking of uh in about three and a half
hours I think
7pm jst
and on the whole live official Channel
there is maybe you've seen it there's
like a Piccola focused uh official
program
and if you look at the participants in
the description
it is me too it's not live and
um it's not like I'm not in the Stream
like from beginning to end I think
actually I don't know I didn't see the
final product but uh you will see some
of me there yeah so if you have some
time later
and check it out I just play a small
part I think but um yeah
yeah I was thinking of uh about like
maybe choreography but I don't remember
any choreography from Piccolo
um
so hmm my choice was
bunny hops
no
my phone died guys
no it died
it couldn't keep up with the charging
oh
Kamina
[Music]
oof
it did
um
no no I wanna be moving
at least I'm frozen in the cute state is
it cute
it's dead oh
oh
stronger
stronger charger
oh
well we will try to revive the phone so
it can maybe come back later
oh it's actually restarting itself right
now or is it no I think it's just
showing me that it's charging
oh
come back to me iPhone I'm waiting for
you
oh that's a
strong power bank
charger with a power bank
are we saying that the power bank is
stronger than the
charger maybe it is it looks like a
strong power bank
all right let's wait a little bit we're
going to continue watching this we have
to focus on this anyway all right I'll
make it bigger now
students
she's giving me a hint but you know I
didn't wanna I didn't want to make it
too much like a normal bunny
oh
all I could think of
um
they're like bunny bird
there we go
[Music]
well she did get it
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
let me take a fruit candy
because I'm out of liquid
okay next is
[Music]
it's sweet how she's choosing me
for when the prompt is
in person it's someone who is part of
the cast today
okay that's just proves
how much we fell in love with each other
on that day
again I wanted to repeat my joke and
said bye
I guess it right
but she continued doing it because there
were no there was no people people
she was confused
and I'm like what what I'm right again
I got really excited there
was my second right guest in a row
I'm just too connected with corn on the
senpai
[Music]
I was throwing hearts at her
Phoenix movement apparently foreign
people try to impersonate me they do a
chicken dance
but that's not okay
[Music]
yay I got two points
two points for our team
[Music]
switch
I got a new tea
[Music]
new tea cup
this is the
good thing about streaming
in an environment where there's someone
else
you know I usually don't have this
luxury
normally you have to get everything
myself
yeah it's like back in the day when I
was streaming in her place for one month
suddenly
in front of the door
there's like food and drinks
[Music]
oh Five Points
such a big lead guys oh
oh yeah
yeah
[Music]
for a team we're Team let's go
yellow team
what happened
she said
she said well we don't hang up much and
I said well we don't either
so I was like hey
I'm really hurt right now
hi
[Laughter]
they're so funny they're so cute
yeah this seems already like the end of
it
so I'm like I always wanted to be part
of something like this
so I'm happy about being here and and
meeting these members for the first time
except for Subaru who I met before
[Music]
but it was a beautiful Midnight's
memories
I don't want to cry
because I was so happy it was so much
fun
[Music]
come here come here
and then I started doing this famous
dance move
and then they joined in
[Music]
he's like it was fine I'll do my best
next year
[Music]
this is the next day I'm gonna be closer
to say bye trying to fix the damage that
has been done
[Music]
yes yes has it really been an hour even
when re-watching it feels less than an
hour
thank you
[Music]
but the actual stream like right there
felt like 10 minutes for me
showing off my butt
hey
[Music]
should I try to revive my phone oh nine
percent charged let's go I'll give it
some more time
a little bit more time okay
a tiny bit more time
ah it was so much fun oh man that was an
hour
how was that an hour
um
yeah I hope I hope I get to do more too
but it's not very realistic
because
you know I'm not normally in Japan
and to do this in 3D
it has to be like organized and
coordinated so that it happens at a time
when I go there but how do I even know
when to go there when you know
when are they doing Church programs
yeah
um but hopefully maybe one time at least
next year
one time would be nice or we just do our
own thing you know
our own 3D stuff but it's nice to to do
stuff like this because it's you know
professional
um nothing can go wrong because
the staff are so good at what they're
doing and then there's so many members
there to have fun with and get to know
with to get to know dot period
yeah
it was a blast and now I'll tell you
some stories some I took some notes
where's my phone
under which blanket is my phone
I'll tell you some some stories if I
find my phone and here it is okay
it's under the blanket
um
[Music]
here we go
oh it's kind of loud
oh well probably not so loud for you
guys right
[Music]
uh
who is it maybe a little a little bit
quieter because actually I've seen my
voice is
quiet too oh sure
[Music]
no
I might oh
let me adjust it somewhere else here
[Music]
YouTube volume
there we go
oh so serving
but now now it's too quiet
oopsie
yeah anyway that was uh
part of the New Year's program there's
like more that came after that when I
wasn't part of so if you're interested
you can watch that too
um
um I was part of the concert though
you guys saw that one right
We performed animals
and uh
some people noticed that I got a lot of
parts
there's a reason for that
um but I got some time to shine ooh
lots of kiwama in that performance
Parts not farts
a lot of screen time
wish it was a different song well to be
honest for me since I already covered
Ali Malu
I Loki was hoping for something else too
but at least that this way I didn't have
to learn a new song and it was a
stressful time in general so
yeah Schrodinger that's basically it
yeah
that's basically what happened
was weird not hearing it in English yeah
yeah we already have an English version
from my song called of Lena
but we performed it in Japanese which
was fine didn't really have to relearn
it it's the same Melody and all that
yeah yeah this was the simplified choreo
and I said we need a simple choreo
as simple as possible
as simple as it gets
not for me but for the others
version better
well that's
that's a individual choice
I like both
has a different vibe
do you guys even hear the bgm
we'd have to make it a bit louder
do you hear it at all
this is like a podcast now
a bit it's Audible
not sponsored
by Audible
you can't hear it okay I made it a tiny
bit more louder now
tiny tiny
now it should be good
also we are uh
um
should I
do you think the power bank can keep up
with charging let's see
foreign
[Music]
let me reposition it
uh
how do I do this
[Music]
Chihuahua's moving again I'm alive
but I can't I don't know how to put it
how did I put it before
oh yeah
[Music]
playing with my tripod right now
come on come on hi I'm here
find me
there it was for a second but I was
holding it wrong there we go okay this
could work maybe
hi hi
[\h__\h] push
okay okay okay finally
[Music]
Chihuahua is moving
she moving
hi finally you know it was so cold out
here that I froze
into an ice cube it seems but I used my
Phoenix powers to melt it
thank you for the Super Chat thank you
[Music]
okay from here on I'll give you some
some details
so uh where do I start first of all I
was
um very much earlier in the studio than
the others had to go there early
um it was the first one I was alone for
a while and
I realized I made a mistake because I
realized I'm gonna be meeting a lot of
them for the first time
so I
wore a really cute dress it made my hair
look nice and all that and did my makeup
really nice new
wanted them to have a good impression of
me right so
I get there and I change into
you know
I don't want to break the fourth wall
too much but you know what I change into
I don't have to say it so that messed up
everything and I I
didn't look so cute anymore
my hair was messed up and uh yeah no
cute dress anymore
yeah
and then
um
I actually in some break time
I it was recording well like I was first
just dancing around because I was having
fun
and I realized oh [\h__\h] I shouldn't be
doing so much dancing because I'm
starting to sweat I want them to think I
smell bad
but I did record by the way something
um really short
uh I had a break time and I was like I'm
gonna record something if it's okay
before the others come
and
within like five to ten minutes I tried
to learn a little dance
you're gonna see which one it is
eventually I'm gonna upload it as a
short
we recorded it really quickly
to upload is a short in 3D later yeah
yeah
so that's coming soon
I think the staff have the data so I
don't know where it is right now but I'm
not in a rush it's okay
um Speed Learning yup yup yup
um
okay let me open my my notes
[Music]
ah
so I think the first one that came in
was I think Mio said bye
Muse Empire was
on time or early I didn't look at the
time
and and and ah it was so nice to hear
her voice I was so excited yeah and I
don't know it was so damaged though and
I realized all the members are starting
to come in now I was like oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] what am I gonna do yeah bye
um
chatting
a little bit and yeah then soon after
I couldn't say bye walked in
and
[Music]
it was like love at first sight
I don't know
well first I was like freaking out
um
but then you know we sat down
and we're just talking you know it's a
quarter
and me I'm gonna start talking
sitting
in our room and you know
I noticed that I'm just looking at both
of them too much but music I was sitting
right next to me on my right side and on
the other side of the table corn on the
Senpai was sitting kind of like
diagonally to me
and so my eyes constantly went
to Corona Senpai because she was I guess
easy to for me to look at her
from like the how she was positioned
um but she was also staring at me the
whole time even though she she said
right across music play so we were both
staring at each other the whole time
while we were talking and and and and
I got so embarrassed by it and I
eventually I was like I'm so sorry I'm
looking so much at you guys
um I'm gonna try to stop and then was
like no don't stop I want to look at you
too look at me look I look at you I want
to stare at each other
and I'm like
hey really
she said I'm also staring at you
and then and then and then like quarter
Senpai would just continuously praise me
she was like
um she was like uh one question she
asked me is like kiwala did you never
want to be an actress you could be an
actress
you're so pretty you could be an actress
I'm like
I guess when I was like nine years old
maybe I wanted to be an actress but no
not really
okay and then later she said oh my God
she knows your nose is so beautiful you
have such a beautiful big nose big big I
wouldn't say it's so big but you know
and then she was like are your eyes real
and then everybody started laughing this
was at the point where I think somebody
said that was already there and
everybody was laughing film except it
was also there she's like Chihuahua are
your eyes real and I'm like yeah and
everybody's laughing did you really
yeah
yeah and she's like ah your eyes are so
beautiful and look at my purple eyes
um
foreign
oh yeah at some point she was like oh I
get it now I get it now
you look like you have a Final Fantasy
games and then the others I think
probably Senpai was standing there and
she was like yeah yeah okay what you
mean yeah I agree
I'm like ah it's not the first time
someone told me I look like I can't come
from a Final Fantasy game
foreign
hmm
[Music]
yeah
so she kept on praising me when I was
also surprising her I said I really like
her looks and
um
we were like constantly looking at each
other and then sometimes when we were
not sitting down at the table she was
like oh no
um further away on the other side of the
room but once our eyes would meet
we would both like grin and smile at
each other and like God
and that would be suddenly so shy and
look away
I don't know what was going on man I did
honestly
Corner sand bite because of the troubles
we've been having to schedule holotalk
I
I thought correspect was the least
likely for me to get along the most you
know what I mean
of course I didn't think we would hate
each other or so but I did not think it
would go so well
foreign
[Music]
I think maybe she needed this little
motivation push
to meet me first and like get to know me
first
somehow because we never collab before
really besides that little bit the tiny
tiny tiny
um
yeah
so maybe maybe she just needed to get to
know me first
maybe she was shy but now she cannot
resist me
so she was very motivated and I think
it's gonna happen beginning of February
we decided I said how about beginning of
February she was looking at her phone
checking and like yeah yeah I can do
that and yeah it looks good now very
positive
and all of that even though I wasn't
wearing my cute dress anymore
laughs
yeah eventually by the way
um so where to standby
showed up
a little bit late
and I was told it turns out
um that Super Sentai
um seems to be late
every once in a while
so we're supposed to have to be a little
bit louder no no no
yeah so she was last
um before that for monkey Senpai came in
I'm pretty sure hmm
hmm
voice I was like oh my God
oh my God holy [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h]
whoa
spooky cell parts real quick Senpai but
I got really nervous especially towards
football I got really nervous I I was
kind of shy towards her
um
So eventually in the waiting room it was
right next to me with Wiki Senpai and
next to kubuki Senpai was mu senpai and
then on the other side was uh coronation
by diagonally to me and then and then
Subaru Senpai right across me
I was really happy to see if somebody
said if I again gave her a big hug but
it's been so long that in the first
moment I didn't I didn't recognize her
but but she's like she looks at me and
she's like she she pointed at herself
and she's like super and I'm like ah
now I have to say I unfortunately forgot
the
um I didn't forget in Austria I forgot
it here and the little thing you know
the iron beat thingy but I'll give it to
her next time we're meeting because we
actually do have plans to meet again
anyway
so don't worry it's the chance is not
lost yet I did however not pack the Lena
one because I had no idea she would be
in Japan
yeah Lena is in Japan right now I knew
nothing of it
if I would have known I would have
brought hers too so I'm a bit sad
and I didn't bring it
um
yeah no one did yeah did she not like
announce it in her own stream huh
she was just suddenly there I didn't see
her yet yeah I was I arrived uh and I
was like Lena
I just saw it you're like with Iris
you're you're in Japan
and she's like oh I didn't tell you I'm
like no
what what
what the [\h__\h]
hmm
no I didn't bring Ian's sock puppets
because they would be squished in my
luggage
yeah almost everyone not everyone but
almost all of the end
is in Japan right now yeah
wow and it's kind of a coincidence
though
like it's not like we all said to each
other okay let's go to Japan at the same
time
but eventually I noticed oh
I was I was thinking of going there
around the same time so oh okay okay
good to know good to know
um
but it wasn't like on purpose from the
get-go
it's kind of happened to be like this
no I would say like it was planned
between council members
but
we didn't like Council and myth didn't
coordinate with each other no
um so okay okay the thing is uh super
simple was like dying
so what would you ever arrived uh and
she was the whole time she was in pain
and we were also worried about her no
like for most of the waiting time uh
music was trying to figure out what what
super assemble I had by Googling it
and then somebody was like oh I'm gonna
die I'm gonna die
hmm
and we were kind of worried that she
maybe couldn't make the stream but she
fought through it
she fought through it she's a fighter
after all
[Music]
she wasn't doing so well
but she should go to the doctor yeah
yeah
actually brought some some self-made
food uh like typical New Year's Japanese
New Year's food
she brought it in like Tupperware and
that it had so much of a self-made
feeling to it
[Music]
and apparently
uh she's like promised Colony Senpai
that she would bring it so Conan said I
got really excited when music pulled out
the self-made food
um
foreign
[Music]
City it's called Uh
and there's different types it was like
some vegetables like carrots and like
peas or whatever and like all kinds of
like typical Japanese vegetables and I
don't even know the name of they look
really funky
and some some meat
and maybe
um
can I find like the ingredients
simmered chicken and root vegetables
simmer chicken and root vegetables there
you go
no no no no no
seems to be something
you eat for
uh New Year's
so I tried as well it was good it was
really good
I I'm quite honored to be able to eat
meals advice self-made cooking yeah
[Music]
foreign
so honored
so lucky yeah
so everyone was kind of like eating from
that and then we also had some really
nice fancy bentos and the other members
were like
wow they spent we have bentos there's no
fencing like you guys don't always get
bentos when you do something like work
at the studio
and I said sometimes
often not just like smaller Stacks but
Bendel and especially a fancy Bender
like this is kind of rare I took a photo
but I'm not sure I have to get I have to
check with jenma if it's okay to show
uh because there was some kind of stamp
branding on part of the food and I'm not
sure if it like gives away anything
um
[Music]
check
and but yeah the potato was good too
which is not expensive it's been so long
since I had a Bento
yeah but you know the last day of 2022
I think a fancy Bento is appropriate
um
actually so yeah I also brought some
food yeah yeah you guys were asking but
I was waiting until everyone was there
and once everyone was uh
together I pulled out the manner web
wafers
the Mana waivers
and then I said and I have some sassy
either because and
how do I translate it's like a souvenir
but uh I guess I guess maybe it's it's
not quite a souvenir
um
and then everyone was like hey we didn't
bring any Sashi there ah it's imposed to
the the waivers yeah yeah yeah
I gave some to staff and I gave some to
the members
I said is it from Austria please try and
everyone liked them I was actually very
very surprised
because I said these are really really
simple actually they might be kind of
boring but I think because they're so
simple
um usually you don't dislike them no one
dislikes them I would say no one
outright hates them so
I thought it was a safe choice and they
loved it
especially football and Corona Senpai
for example I was sitting next to me
eating the whole thing right away
the whole there's quite a big waiver
thingy and the corona Senpai was so
surprised she was like wow this is so
good
why is she so good
my football standpoint was quietly
enjoying the whole thing
a Cornish Empire was going on and on
about how this is so good and I was like
you guys like it so much I gave her
another one she was so happy
everyone so far seemed to like them very
much
um
so I would say it was a good choice
foreign
she was even asking if there's any way
to buy them in in Japan I'm not sure
I don't think they have these in store
anywhere in Japan uh even in the more
International ones but you could maybe
get it off of uh Amazon
foreign
[Music]
we ate the food together
and oh
that was during a little break but you
know we also had like you know set up
and rehearsal and so on and and and one
thing that was really funny to me
um I did my setup earlier than the
others because I was there much earlier
and when doing the setup you know I kind
of had to do some movement according to
a video they showed like a video guide
and it was like a routine you know it
was really fast like maybe like two
minutes of a routine of certain
movements like uh
[Music]
I don't know doing certain hand
movements and doing certain leg
movements and so on
uh can you imagine
like lift your leg turn it around
uh put it down again
put your arms up put the arms to the
front open your palms uh
I don't know turning your wrists
whatever
stuff like that
and it was actually pretty complicated
and super fast so I barely could like
follow it
I was like oh my god look oh yeah arm
yeah left arm right arm
turn around blah blah blah blah
and then I was really curious to maybe
the other members are like already know
it by heart and can do it really easily
so I paid extra close attention to when
the others were doing it and yeah
satsuga they had absolutely no issues
with it they were so used to it and then
when it was caught on the Sapphire's
turn
she asked them
to make it even faster to make it 1.5
speed and I'm standing there and I'm
like are you asking them to do that to
impress me and she says yeah
and then she starts doing it even faster
than it already was it was already super
fast
oh hello Raiders hello hello
um
and she's still absolutely Nails it
she still Nails it and 1.5 speech is
flexing on me yeah but was flexing to
try to impress me
cute
so cute
so I gave everyone a little clap a
little Applause when they were done
um
[Music]
so yeah that is like
most of the pre-stream talk I think we
just most of the time but we're just
chit chatting talking a lot about a lot
of things and
oh one thing you know I told them that
my butt got updated before the stream
already
and
for some reason you know I said I said
well I got a bigger butt but not as big
as the Kardashians and they didn't know
what the Kardashians were who Kim
Kardashian was and I was like hey are
you sure you probably wouldn't know if
you look at them so I pulled up a photo
of the Kardashian family and I showed
them I showed the photo to all of them
and
they had no idea who they were
now guess maybe that's good
yeah maybe that's good and they were
like who are these people and I said
um
how do I explain this and I tried to
explain by saying well
they're kind of just celebrities who are
famous for being rich and well with that
richness they just did like a TV show
and and some do makeup brands and
whatever fashion brands and whatever oh
yeah
I tried to explain it I tried to explain
it yeah
sales people who complain a lot
I thought that at least like even if you
don't watch what they do I thought you
would at least have seen them for some
news and media at least once
huh
no but no one knew
oh
that was surprising
um
said she watches my streams by the way
I know couldn't understand by his name
um comes up a lot but I'm telling you
I'm telling you we were like
on top of each other the whole time
she said she said ah I do watch q1 with
streams and I'm like
what do you mean what what
are you serious she says yeah I watched
him I watched it a lot as like a a
background
like a thing when she's doing something
else
me
as her background noise she said she
likes hearing English
as background music kind of
she says she doesn't understand what I'm
saying but she enjoys the English part
yeah
dog in the hen house
I I don't think dogs keep dogs eat
a live Chicken store don't worry
um
so yeah
all of that happening it was also like
some skinship happening here and there
you know
throwing kisses at each other and giving
each other hard signs and
um
one time in the rehearsal I was standing
right next to her and she kind of I
guess accidentally touched my butt and
she was like oh sorry I'm like
no problem
and then you know since she touched my
butt I sat on top of her and that's why
I kind of repeated it later uh in the
actual stream
by accident Yeah by accident
[Music]
see I really did you guys think that I
would get along so well with Corona
senpai
I didn't
I definitely didn't
she was so sweet
they were all sweet you know I don't
wanna
I wanna make sure you know this but but
I I just had something going on with
code on the same point
and ah I'm gonna I'm gonna fast forward
to after
um the Stream
um because one more thing
I want to say is uh when it was over you
know everyone just really quickly
changed back into their clothes
beat
uh and I was I was I was too shy to go
into the same room so I waited until
they were all done changing
and then I went in and changed really
quickly but I heard they were already
like about to leave so I went really
fast really fast really fast and then I
I left the changing room and then I
stood proudly finally presented myself
in an okay manner
in front of the girls and and they were
like ah wow whoa
whoa Chihuahua
and I'm like this is how I really wanted
you guys to see me for the first time
um and especially Corner simple I was
like
it was like she had a crush on me
oh
no
I mean
um
foreign
I didn't want to invite myself you know
um because I think Japanese people have
a hard time turning down people so
it's fine it's totally okay uh but they
were about to leave so I say goodbye and
and and I I I I gave everyone a hug even
though I am very much aware of how hugs
are not
um so
you know pretty much only like close
family and lovers
hug in Japan
and
but I couldn't help it I was so happy to
meet them and I've been too used to
living overseas again outside of Japan I
couldn't hold back gave everyone a hug
but when it came to coronation by
you know I gave her a hug
and then and then we're like boy really
really sadly and she's like but like
you're not done and I'm like
and then she's like one more hug and she
comes back to me to hug me again and hug
hug hug and then we say bye bye goodbye
corner and she said
let's hang out that's so fun and then
and then and then she says one more one
more and she gives me a third hug from
her yeah and I thought okay that must be
it but then you know we go like bye bye
bye bye again and then and then and then
we look at each other like no p.m p.m
and she gives me a fourth hug
she gives me a poor bug and we're like
and the staff around us are laughing at
us and then and then and then I thought
okay well this must be it because it's
starting to get to get a little bit
awkward
but but we're like
[Music]
I love you love you and I'm like love
you love you and then and then we look
at each other our hearts are breaking
and I and then I say
come on one more make it five one more
hug and give one more hug hug
and then and then and then basically we
had to be torn apart
we had to be torn apart to end it
because it was never ending
stay there
bye-bye
um
no you hang up no you hang up yeah yeah
but in real life yeah
A Moment Like That
I was I was so
shocked
you're so shocked by how that went I
never expected them unlimited hug works
ah
now I'm thinking imagine okay Senpai was
here
do you think this would have happened
hmm
[Music]
would that have really happened
don't think so
or maybe maybe we would have had like a
love triangle situation
but I would have joined in hmm
what do you have even done the quiz well
the script was a little bit different
before we knew that okay somebody wasn't
coming and uh I was not gonna be part of
the whole thing just like a the later
half
yeah so there was some changes being
made
yeah anyway well you know even moments
in the like rehearsal or when we were
just standing there calibrating I was
I was like
you know standing there in line with the
girls
like doing the same thing
I was like feeling so
whoa
oh
yeah and they said oh it's like even
moments like these that are really
special to me right now
I told them
even us just standing here together it's
like really really special to me
well
and they were all so kind to me
all the members were so kind to me so
sweet
um
ah I also saw etan and coyote
audible Facebook
hmm
[Music]
um I gave clearly the Wafers too the
Mana wafers
um I just said hi it was just a quick
it didn't seem uh like much of her she
was like I don't know I don't know what
she was doing she was doing something
else but yeah
[Music]
um
animato
hmm I didn't recognize it's on either
came in the room she was like hi
um
and she's like
[Music]
it's been so long koala well I didn't
see them for over one and a half years
you must understand
yeah
maybe like more like than more like two
years so
next you forget how Gemma looks like I
will never forget how janma looks like
chenma is Unforgettable
no no I haven't met nodokol um
or maybe she was there and I just didn't
recognize her no I don't think she was
here she would have introduced herself
to me
um
it
[Music]
it's hard to forget an Angel
um
she's my
schutzanger in German
schutz angle guardian angel Guardian
Angel
no Yago wasn't there
[Music]
um
did you meet Omega on their birthday it
was omega's birthday no
no
no idea where Omega is
Omega is uh
hibernating hibernating forever
garden guardian angel
ah December 32nd
AKA never
um
[Music]
what else what else
what else what else what else
mmm I don't know I
feel like I pretty much told everything
from behind the scenes pretty much
everything I can remember
ah
[Music]
no I didn't maybe I should I should I
still have other leftovers
I should give jenma a manner while way
before I don't think she had on it I
brought her Austrian chocolate before I
think
but I don't think I ever had her taste
Manor waiver
that the one that you said on the
preacher when you can't think of
attention well [\h__\h] why did I make it so
that's so so how the [\h__\h] am I supposed
to Remember by that
[Music]
yeah I remember telling you guys to
remind me of a tangent
but how the [\h__\h] am I ah cat robot
oh yeah the cash robot service okay okay
there was a little bit more detail
you you uh did leave out that detail
yeah okay camera but that reminds me of
another thing
right first so one more friend well now
when we were like sitting around uh uh
we started talking about cats me fubuki
and Senpai and music
Us free we were really really
passionately discussing cat things
and I told them that I have uh this this
toilet this robot toilet that moves
itself
um and brings the poop down you don't
have to scoop it anymore and poopy
simply was like yeah yeah I know that
I'm planning on getting one too and I'm
like oh I wonder if you're getting the
same one as me
it's a really famous One and and music I
didn't know about it music but still
Scoops Muse Empire is a scooper yeah
um but music I seemed very interested in
the cat toilet robot
it was nice it was nice we had a cat
lady talk yeah
yeah she's a scooper
foreign
[Music]
shocked by how things have been changing
in Japan
and one of the things that changed was
uh thank you for the Super Chat
[Music]
thank you
one thing that changed was I was at
gusto
so remember from the holotalk questions
sizealia or gas tool and my favorite is
gasto so we went to gasto
me and jenma and some others
and
[Music]
I saw they had they now had uh
a cat robot server
like a moving robot like kind of like a
Roomba moving around like a Roomba but
you know taller and with a display that
had a cat face on it
that changed and was animated but not
another like real looking cat face just
like a pixel cat face and it would bring
the dishes to the tables
because there was like a tray inside the
robot and I guess the kitchen would put
the food in there and then the robot
would go to the
um to the tables I am guessing that it
is one uh to help out with lack of Staff
really smart
and two maybe also during the
call peep times
to have less interactions with humans
maybe you know because then
you don't really need waiters and I'm
guessing some people maybe you know lost
their job too I don't know a lot of
people got sick maybe so they needed a
solution
foreign
no I didn't visit the shrine yet
not yet
so Augusto
one step one step closer to Doraemon
so I didn't watch The Diamond so I don't
really get that uh reference
hmm
so who's not in 2023 just yet PST how
much longer half an hour or what
is
40 more minutes for PSD oh let's go
ah
blah blah anyway
yeah the program was a lot of fun it was
it was like a great experience
and really it went so well was
professional had a lot of fun football
did a great job at emceeing and the
others were just cracking me up the
whole time so funny
and I feel like it was really inspiring
too seeing them working like that
seeing how they do it and what they do
and so on it was really inspiring to me
hmm
yeah and I really noticed that they have
a lot of experience with it yeah
um
I'm gonna Read Super chats for 30
minutes because I think I should
not streamed too long
[Music]
but Freeman's better than nothing
um
[Music]
where did I leave off last time you guys
know
how was my flight
[Music]
I didn't talk about my flight yet huh on
my flight was okay I didn't get a window
seat so that pissed me off
uh but I did get premium economy for
myself and it was comfy but
um
I I had to cough a lot and
uh it was kind of uncomfortable I was
drinking liters and leaders and leaders
to try to hydrate myself because you
know how dry it gets
uh
but
yeah it was okay even though I was in
the same road as a baby
and behind me was also a baby
I actually managed to get some sleep but
yeah I I was feeling sorry to the person
next to me for me coughing so much but
in the beginning I did say uh hi nice to
meet you just to warn you that I
um
I mean I don't have to see thing but I
just got over a different thing and
that's why I might be coughing here and
there uh sorry
and yeah it was okay it wasn't too bad
but
um
yeah
[Music]
my throat hurts anyway so
um I should not be reading super Jazz
longer than 40 minutes hope you
understand guys
I don't know man it's not getting much
better recently ever since I arrived in
Japan before that I was like definitely
getting better
soon
popping a cough drop
um
I am planning however to stream tomorrow
guys by the way
in the evening jst evening
was shook it let's open hololizer hold
on
[Music]
what a lighter
do you guys know
where kiwawa has to continue to read
[Music]
did I read the whole talk
uh tomorrow plant solo
just gonna play a game I think
Clubhouse
oh okay okay
24 hours from now oh you guys don't know
when tomorrow is tomorrow
more than 24 hours from now right now
it's for uh half past 4 P.M here
and I was thinking streaming around like
seven or eight pm tomorrow
yeah tomorrow tomorrow
okay
have to be at it but that's
yeah well it's even in Jersey I often
started my streams even in jst in late
evening Thursday in Europe
it's not too different
but yeah I know I know I know and this
is how it will be for a couple weeks
um
oh I said for this stream I won't read
them okay then I have a free pass for
that one was it this one okay okay
nice then then it would be kind of
simple
um
good
good for me works for me
okay
let's see let's see what do we have
[Music]
uh
other words are selling for
[Music]
um
I don't see the setting that where I can
turn off that and now now here it is it
has to load in
uh okay
[Music]
oh you're sure
okay
uh here we go take his monkey thank you
that good thank you for two pinkies
one of them says Gilmore Girls episode
five if smoothie demanded you take her
for walks in a covered wagon would you
uh I I know what you're referencing
maxentino's so thirsty Dean says let me
pay for your groceries Rory you never
catch a champion saying let me pay for
your groceries why not
anyway here's an extra super chat to
help you pay for Kiara's kitchen
groceries looking forward to Hulu talk
and learning more about amane it's weird
that you call her Amanda
unusual to hear that
feels wrong but yeah
um
would I I want I want today's definitely
been times where I've been considering
taking my cats out and I saw other cat
owners using like a baby wagon kind of
thingy
and yeah it's kind of cute I I did want
to kind of do it because I saw others
doing it but
I have yet to attempt anything like that
because well normally my kitakatos are
are in-house cats
I'm not done the only good way to call
her yeah
yeah
I have one of those day work what
you have
like a wagon for your cat
a stroller yeah we're talking about
strollers that's that's the word
what
what motion
motion mentioned
but thank you
[Music]
um
hope you enjoyed the whole toku and
learned lots of things about Canada's
Empire
ooh it was a good episode wasn't it very
good one one of my best
soon
be thank you soon
thank you for the right to the chat I
want to say thanks for everything you've
done this month from the Advent calendar
to holotalk to on the streams even while
sick the sock puppet karaoke was amazing
much love and respect have a wonderful
Christmas season tencho stream
snowflation yeah but now you already
have so many other things to stream as
well the new song coming with crony the
pitani Stein Christmas and so on
so much right
but yeah I I tried to since it's an
important season you know Christmas New
Year's and I'm traveling and so on if
all this wasn't happening if I was sick
like in the middle of
I don't know February January or no not
really but any other time
when I wasn't traveling or so
and when I weren't like special holidays
to celebrate I would have just taken
probably a whole month off to to heal
this [\h__\h] illness this [\h__\h]
sickness
because it was definitely serious enough
to need that much time as you can hear
now from me still being kind of sick
it definitely needed more time
um but you have to understand I was
already holding back when there were
certain things that I had to do
especially when seeing everyone else not
really being streaming not not being
around and feeling like I have to cover
for others and
just generally not wanting to miss out
on certain fun events and yeah
and now I'm in Japan so I want to make
the most of it
no no
I rested as much as I could
oh well oh well thank you Krusty thanks
mate
good luck streaming all those songs
pinkies
[Music]
my message is Dogo oh yeah the first one
had no message what happened I'm glad
your health is getting better please do
not overdo it and take care of your
condition
thank you
uh well at that time yeah I was I was
trying so hard to get healthy in time
for the delayed date for no talk because
I didn't want to delay it again
um it was good enough it was good enough
for it one stream oh no
yeah
uh thank you for worrying about me
I was not perfectly healthy but I'm
hopefully getting there at the moment I
don't know if it's going
upwards or downwards I honestly cannot
tell it feels more downwards at the
moment
but
um
I don't really feel sick
like I don't have a fever or whatever I
don't feel weak or in particular or so I
just it's so much freaking snot
and so much
[\h__\h] in my throat
that's kind of getting worse
[Music]
yeah
your adrenaline might keep it at Bay
while you're in Japan
we don't crash when you go home we'll
see we'll see
my favorite's not too Brooke hope you
get well soon thank you
last bit of sickness is just really
stubborn yeah well you know when people
were telling me Oh had bronchitis too
but it took me a month or even longer to
heal I was like what the [\h__\h]
seems like yeah I I don't know what part
of my sickness because I had so many
different ones is causing this remaining
[\h__\h] right now
but whatever it is it's it's overstaying
it's welcome
right
[Music]
it doesn't always take that long
um
my bronchitis lasted only a little bit
over a weekend seems to be individual
[Music]
hmm
happy New Year indeed yes yes
Happy New Year to everyone it's crazy
it's 20 23 now I don't even
you know Christmas didn't feel like
Christmas to me and New Year's
definitely didn't feel like New Year's
to me because no fireworks um yeah
[Music]
so it's gonna take a while for me to
grasp it
foreign
but I did get to spend it in a very
special way there might have not been
any fireworks and I may have slept over
midnight
but
what
I had a very special day
and nobody can take that away from me
because it happened hey
[Music]
buddy
for two pinkies
you think thank you
Lila Maria thank you
for the pinky best whole talk ever oh
thank you oh this was already when the
stream was longer than an hour
thank you thank you thank you
so if I did get along really well so I
guess that you you definitely feel it in
the quality of the Stream
when the people involved get along
really well right
um
[Music]
first 12. thank you and Jim Tracy thank
you soon
[Music]
I am a chicken I can't beat it for
yourself
I didn't bring my BP thing
Lucy thank you awesome stream tangible I
love the weight I'm glad to hear your
voice sounding much better something
tells me you enjoyed talking with Canada
about Idols
hell yeah
I have no choice
we had no choice
baking soda for L thank you for the big
red Super Chat
you are an inspiration killer thanks for
all your hard work merry Christmas happy
holidays to YouTube
I hope you're spending a lovely time
with your loved ones
even if you're alone
then maybe some quality time with
yourself
no watch watch like your favorite
Netflix shows or whatever
well thank you so much for watching my
streams for a long time
and for your generous big donation I
really appreciate it thank you so much
like a big big Christmas present
wrapped in a red envelope
thank you thank you
thank you Stefan I'll get there one day
YouTube Noob thank you
[Music]
son
thank you soon
and Elias Elias is
[Music]
thanks for this Kiara it's so refreshing
to see you two talking so passionately
together and really lived with my
spirits hope your holidays are wonderful
happy holidays to you too
yeah I am looking forward to meeting
Canada again
very soon I think actually even maybe
this week
what day is today
Monday right it's Monday now
[Music]
I think I'm seeing Canada's Empire this
week
hanging out with her
I couldn't wait any longer
I'm looking forward to that
there might not be a stream on that day
what
what isn't it Sunday yeah this is my
Monday
Sunday
oh oh for the first was a Saturday
oh
oh mistake it's Sunday then I mean next
week
oh okay okay no problem doesn't matter
doesn't matter random collusion thank
you
Happy New Year and merry Christmas
[Music]
wish you all the best
and stay with kfp
and then I'm sure that happiness will
stay with you too
doctor soon
[Music]
best one yet here we go again another
one who says his best one they always
say they always say
thank you Canada and Canada for this
wonderful episode and I hope you both
have a Merry Christmas ahead thank you
thank you
yeah
uh my Christmas was nice
my New Year's was noise too
uh I hope yours was too hope you get to
spend it with your family forgot to
spending with your family it's already
over I hope you got some nice presents
but sometimes you have to treat yourself
so feel free to do that treat yourself
reach yourself
don't forget about yourself always
prioritize yourself
okay not always but it's nice to
prioritize yourself sometime
especially the people who always forget
about it
forget about prioritizing yourself and
always think of the others first and
those people need to learn to think of
themselves
every once in a while at least
[Music]
so I hope you can do that
big kiss from me to you
for the new year
I am a teacher
is
oh wait is it swagburg
was that always supposed to mean like
Swag Like Swagger
but book what does the book mean then
because that's streaming
I know I will never understand your name
you got Swagger
Chase swag book
well thank you for the pinky it's just
random okay yeah it kind of sounds like
a random combination of words
thank you for the pinky this was a
superb episode
went so deep on the idle tangent it was
great uh I was a foolish chicken better
against you messing up the sponsor video
oh yeah a betting
I got it right this time I I was messing
it up so many times in a row I was like
this time
I have to check beforehand if everything
is okay the way it is right now
[Music]
this time I got it right but then I
messed up something in the end as We
Know
as we know but that kind of was an
accident because I was just scrolling
through my
um
for my like scenes
in OBS getting ready to switch to the
ending screen and recently the mouse I
use at home has been like having an
issue where the mouse wheel gets stuck
often and when I was scrolling the mouse
wheel got stuck and it kind of like
selected a different scene and we
switched over to that
I didn't even click on it by accident it
was just me scrolling
you know innocently and then suddenly it
switched and like [\h__\h] [\h__\h] and out of
panic I kept on Switching because I
wanted to I wanted to switch back to the
other one but I I couldn't
yeah
Folk
A new mouse do I need a new mouse I
don't know I've been using that Mouse
for like years
kind of dirty
yeah but we got to see the video twice
this time with a new band in the
background looks so cute
uh Patsy thank you
Tim Tracy thank you for the pinky Merry
Christmas guys you're starting to feel
better this was perhaps the best soul
talk episode yet it was so much fun and
very informative you too really
connected and it led to some fantastic
discussions and moments
oh thank you
thank you thank you very much
um
yeah I was also surprised about the
connection I mean I knew from the
beginning
that
when I first met her you know we have a
Hello project connection but I wasn't
sure how serious she
was into that if she really liked it
a lot or just like like a like a shallow
interest
um
yeah yeah yeah
well she did say that she didn't go to
concerts so that's that I guess in that
case I was a bigger friend
no no need to compare who's the bigger
fan right no need you guys shouldn't be
doing that either
might have been a fake fan nah nah even
if you don't go to concerts
you can still be a real fan yeah yeah
yeah
I mean for her definitely the reason
wasn't the distance
I'm not sure why she wouldn't go because
I think she would enjoy it
um
if she would have gone but yeah yeah I
guess it was kind of like the age
she met them yeah but she didn't like go
to concerts
she just met them randomly in a random
toilet without even trying to meet them
but yeah I think she I remember her
saying something like was kind of an age
thing
yeah yeah
sword isn't it
thank you same Tracy
thank you soon no this one
[Music]
how do I read this Translate
no no no no
here
[Music]
Xiao
that was probably very wrongly
pronounced but thank you thank you
thank you
this is already a while ago you say I'm
glad you're doing much better but look
at me now
thank you though thank you soon soon
foreign
[Music]
yeah I was worse back then yeah yeah
that is true
oh yeah yeah yeah
okay at least I got some super chats
done today
better than nothing
oh
sure
now
um
two minutes
are they doing fireworks over there
is it going like pew pew pew pew
really noisily
um
pew pew pew pew pew I want to see the
fireworks I had my brother send me a
video though of the fireworks because my
brother's taking care
of my place in my kitokatos and record a
record a video for me please
[Music]
looked nice
people were firing guns over here no
joke what that's not a firework
that's not a firework
surprisingly haven't heard me maybe
they're really waiting for the last
moments to start
celebrity celebratory gunfire is a thing
here too
I mean I guess I've maybe seen that
before in movies or so but
I don't really lead I really like that
perfect time to test guns yeah hopefully
try to shoot the sky
and nothing else
but yeah
it seems like a kind of aggressive way
to celebrate but what do I know
I've learned sparklers oh nice
[Music]
don't shoot the sky the bullets could
land anywhere yeah where do they go
they could just like
go up how high did it go I wonder and
when they fall down if they went up
really high then they go down and really
quick speed and they drop on people's
heads
one if that hurts but yeah happy New
Year for PST
is that it is there any like time zone
that's later on PSD
because in my head PST is on the very
edge of the map
is there something left
ah Hawaii
what's the time zone called for Hawaii
Alaska too
are those the last ones
foreign
[Music]
happy New Year guys I'm kind of sorry I
I you know I couldn't do like a proper
countdown exciting streamer so
ideally if I were at home I would do
something like that but you know being
on the road
kind of makes these things difficult and
also being sick as well
but but I would say that me being on
that program made up for it you got to
see it so much Chihuahua moving in 3D at
good quality no no scuff I mean I did
see a little bit of an arm scuff at some
point but that's nothing that's nothing
um got lots of koala movement
in each day
yeah
yeah hey
Jimmy come tonight
cute
[Music]
thank you
really funny seeing how you can't sit
still yeah
I can but the honest weren't sitting
still either I was just trying to
try to you know
get on their level
oh it's
Bob
mama
oh my God
superchat from
Papa
it's your son
what's that
console there must be the time
[Music]
wow
wow what what is
bubbles artists watching my stream hmm
what an honor
maybe they came for hatsumuda at this
Shrine I guess this is had somebody for
everyone who's watching too
imawa
um
[Music]
no I'm not going yet
I'm kind of waiting still on figuring
out a date and so on with I am a senpai
now there's a there's a chance that it
might not happen because it will fail
like scheduling
[Music]
but an attempt was made we'll see I'm
not giving up yet I'm not giving up
[Music]
no I want to go to a shrine
I'm gonna go
but a special one I'm gonna go to a
special one not just any shrine
I want to like travel a little bit oh
yeah oh yeah I heard she has tummy horde
what she has tummy hard
so that might be a problem
at least for a while
but you guys do know that I'll be back
in Japan
eventually so there's always another
time another opportunity
um
okay
um it's 5 p.m now
I think I want to start getting ready
and maybe eat something small
and or maybe even take a little nap
before I go to my next adventure
today yeah yeah that sounds good yeah I
woke up so early and I slept enough but
I'm tired I'm tired since before
starting to stream I got tired
I'm eating some peeps
because I was like hello I'm free today
any anyone who wants to maybe hang
and um got some answers
we're not doing a stream but
gonna hang out
or some girls
perhaps English-speaking girls
oh
you don't know
[Music]
it could be agent I guess
could be eaten
[Music]
clearly hachama
could be hatchimal could be agent
but
um well
I'll tell you afterwards okay
and I think I will stream tomorrow I
want to play a game just a normal stream
to mix a little bit of normal content in
there too
I'll try to get it running
and now I know I want to play this late
the spider maybe give it another go
I started yeah
thank you guys for watching today happy
New Year to everyone and oh yeah
um I guess I didn't really say anything
special about New Year's
um well
as I said in the official stream
was for me in one word a lot of
traveling
and that was nice and I think that will
continue in 2024 as well but you guys
know that I continue to do content with
my travels as well so it shouldn't be
too much of a worry for you guys
um but yeah besides that in 2022 we
finally got to see 3D kiwawa for the
first time
and even though a lot of it was scuffed
and limited hopefully in 2023 there will
be more
and less scarf
and hopefully a lot of fun adventures
together more games for me to finish
play from beginning to end
some nice new RPGs to explore
and I hope to get to know you guys more
and I want to say big big thank you to
you guys for spending so much time with
me always taking your time and your busy
days to
check out what I'm doing even when my
streams are really long or at weird
times
more
foreign
foreign tunic was fantastic hell yeah
Game of the Year tunic
number one
my game of the year
he's an engineering and cyclone
my name is
so easier you must put at least some
value
on what I say about good games
I think it I think it's quite worth
something hmm
no I didn't mention tunic to football
but what am I supposed to say I don't
even know what to say well yeah it was
good yeah yeah it was
what else the the
talk doesn't really get much further
from there I think what what the [\h__\h]
I just noticed
with my laptop how did that happen was
that my unichan
when he was using my laptop well how did
that happen something's broken on the
top right of the monitor
like the plastic or whatever material
that is probably plastic right broke off
on the edge on the corner
whatever it works so whatever I guess
okay I will not
it's a bit mean of me to immediately
think that it was my brother
could have been me while traveling
I guess
sure
uh-huh average specific to do siblings
never change well he has been using he
has been using my laptop a lot
um
yeah
when I was in Italy
you know you know how mysteriously my
title was even more broken than before
when I came back but now it's fixed
now it's fixed
thank you for the memberships
Javier thank you
so yeah
um
I hope you guys will stay with me for a
while longer 2023
I know people move on from things and
lose interest in things and that's
totally normal
but if you guys
want to continue supporting me in 2023 I
would be very grateful for that
[Music]
um
still got some things to do got some
some
achievements and I want to accomplish
yeah
so yoroshiku I'm
worried a bit about 2023
because I feel like in 2022 I've been
um
under a lot of pressure and stress
for some things
um I hope that it will be better next
year
but I'm not sure
a bit anxious
but let's hope for the best
and
make good memories
that will
outweigh
bad ones if there are any
so thank you guys for a lovely year full
with laughs and screams and cries
and golden paths
yeah many many hours together
thank you very much
and in German we say
and who has noise
here I've always known as happy New Year
bye bye bye bye bye
[Music]
bye bye bye
and see you tomorrow probably maybe
probably probably
[Music]
bye-bye
what does the ending look like
uh-huh
it's it's that old one
ending
well why not every once in a while
foreign
it's refreshing
[Music]
foreign