this is a kfb looks normal right that's
what I thought too but then I noticed
something weird about kp's kitchens have
you noticed I mean really taking a look
at their staff they're not what they
seem to be how did we not notice this
before but then I found
these classified documents each one
labeled with a code I'm going to go
visit their Test Kitchen and find out
what's really going on the world
deserves to know what's going on behind
those closed doors at the new kfp Test
Kitchen but I need your help deciding
where to start I'm very indecisive but I
can't be caught I need you to sign up on
the encrypted email list below and every
day I can send you what I find about
these files and little by little we will
unravel this Chimera of mirages that
they've created
[Music]