L to see you see you who are
you for
[Music]
I don't want to be on my own I don't
know what's wrong but I don't I don't
like it it makes me upset you only but a
few steps away do don't worry I want to
be a few steps away I want to be by your
side okay okay from here on out I will
promise you I will remain by your
side it's bow bow okay
[Music]
you are a mighty Phoenix what are you
doing you need to toughen up and not
grubble so much to this I'm a night
Warrior no I must have my my honor and
there's shame
[Music]
I've been learning from my Guild Master
who is a great knight adopt you yes
would you please be my mother would this
make you happy yes it will make me very
happy it is a night's duty to bring
people
happiness yes I I am actually loyal to
making money I see you do it out for
money I see I see and what do what do I
owe you for a b no nothing nothing
no you keep on giving me so much brother
you sir we are part of the same Guild we
should look out for each other right a
good night shows
generosity elizabe such your problem oh
no I came here to help you yes I will I
I told you I would I told you I would
remain by your
side I've kept my promise a good night
shows dedication protects others for
just my train of thought for Honor for
the Jade
sword revelation
hello Romeo ah it's
Elizabeth hello Elizabeth you were
brought here to serve the King give me
answers about MOA cor she will hate you
forever yes say the word those words out
of your mouth with I I I will hate
you see she'll hate you
my king shall be the only one who likes
my heart
I Fe it this but the Calm before the
storm and something yet more terrible is
brewing as we speak as such I ask that
you take this time to prepare train your
combat skills and stock up on any items
you might need this may be your last
chance so make the most of it
here
[Music]
Lely to see you see you who are you
I don't want to be on my own I don't
know what's wrong but I don't like it it
makes me upset oh you are only about a
few steps away do not worry I want to be
a few steps away I want to be by your
side okay okay from here on out I will
promise you I will remain by your
side bow bow
[Music]
you are a mighty Phoenix what are you
doing you need to toughen up and not
grubble so much to this queen I'm a
night Warrior
not I must have my my honor and there
shame
[Music]
I've been learning from my Guild Master
who is a great knight adopt you yes
would you please be my mother would this
make you happy yes it would make me very
happy it is a night's duty to bring
people
happiness yes I I am actually loyal to
making money I see you do it out for
money I see I see and what do what do I
owe you for a b no nothing nothing
no you keep on giving me so much bread
are you sure we are part of the same
Guild we should look out for each other
right a good night shows
generosity love it
I came here to help you yes I will I I
told you I would I told you I would
remain by your
side I've kept my promise a good night
shows dedication protects others for
just my train of thought for Honor for
the Jade
sword revelation
[Music]
hello Romeo ah it's
Elizabeth hello Elizabeth you brought
here to serve the King give me answers
about mocha cor she will hate you
forever yes say the word those words out
of your mouth which I I I will hate
you see she'll hate you
my king shall be the only one who likes
my heart
I F this but the Cal before the storm
and something yet more terrible is
brewing as we speak as such I ask that
you take this time to prepare train your
combat skills and stock up on any items
you might need this may be your last
chance so make the most of it
than
[Music]
L see you who are
you e
[Music]
I don't want to be on my own I don't
know what's wrong but it don't it don't
like it it makes me upset oh you only
but a few steps away do don't worry I
want to be abusive I want to be by your
side okay okay from here on out I will
promise you I will remain by your
side ow bow
[Music]
you are a mighty Phoenix what are you
doing you need to toughen up and not
grubble so much to this
I'm a night
Warrior that I must have by my honor and
those shame
[Music]
I have been learning from my Guild
Master who is a great knight adopt you
yes would you please be my mother
would this make you happy yes it would
make me very happy it is a night's duty
to bring people
happiness yes I I am actually loyal to
making money I see you do it out for
money I see I
see and what do what do I owe you for a
oh nothing nothing
no you keep on giving me so much bread
are you sure we are part of the same
Guild we should look out for each other
T night shows generosity
elizabe where such your oh no I came
here to help you elabe yes I will I told
you I would I told you I would remain by
your
side I've kept my promise a good night
shows dedication protects others for my
train of thought for Honor for the Jade
sword revelation
[Music]
hello Romeo ah
it's hello Elizabeth hello
Romeo
it's ah ah ah it's a new day
okay all
right wait on my phone it says I got a
missed
call from
gathan
Hello T Jonathan oh ah I see I have a
missed call from you
gathan yes I wanted to speak to you
privately is are you are you in a safe
location um I can be I can meet you in
the the tavern on the grounds of uh Jade
sword of the Jade sword taverns yes the
one that c
owns I believe that will be safe enough
yes I will meet you there
all right farewell fa the well and and
see you in a mo see you in a moment
goodbye oh she hung up on
me this is of course a ploy for
something H what could it
be can you knock knock
knock knock knock knock
I'll just let her stand there for a
moment so I could show you know boss
lady mode knock on the door be
intimidating such I am looking at you
from the door I am knocking you cannot
see me in the door I am knocking is I am
open oh hello sorry I was upstairs and I
was just it just there's so many stairs
you see thank you for meeting didn't
hear the door at first yes yes may we
speak upstairs yes we
may oh iand we speak somewhere private
yeah isn't private enough is is private
enough yes as long as we stand near the
the edge of the the the tavn I think it
is let's go over here and stand
here Elizabeth Rose blood flame I know
that we've had our differences but I am
coming to you in seek of your
help your assistance my
help pray tell
what I believe that you are the only one
even though that we are not quite allies
or friends that I you are the only one I
can trust with this information
h i somewhat feel the same last night I
know you do not like my statue of the
queen Tam Gander yes I know that it
disgusted you but last night someone had
defaced it let me send you a sketch of
it in my head somebody defaced your
statue in my my statue I will be sending
it through carrier pigeon okay with
haste one
second wait we need to go outside so the
the pigeon can come through wait oh yes
the pigeon the the pige where the stairs
break over the window break over the
window no I cannot it's not my
place out the door out the door where's
the pigeon
[Music]
i s the sketch oh there it
is yes cat the P the okay I have it uh
okay when
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh God bye the
gods oh my that is that is just awful it
is aw it is quite awful is it not this
is I would not wish it on my worst enemy
I would never do that to you I I yeah i'
hope not um
gosh that is yes distraught it's quite
terrifying I nearly vomited at the sight
I vomit at the site anyway but you know
okay
s I'll vomit
regardless yes yes please thank you
vomit for the both of us when I had
spoke of it Nissa ravencraft your
something I do not know your relation
but Nissa ravencraft had said that she
made a very valid point saying the only
one that could have defaced the statue
is someone in the ceran guild because we
can only build on our own lands yes
there was a magic upon these lands yes
yes and when I called for a trial
princess kipu was very against it and it
seems that she is crafting a corrupted
land I fear that the princess may be
corrupt well if I may be so blunt
corrupted her yes if I may be so blunt
gathan I feel all of the gathan if I
feel
all dear gathan I
fear dear
gathan dearest gathan yes yes yes yes
Elizabeth Rose blood flame I fear lady
blood flame I fear lady blood flame okay
gathan I
fear lady blood
Lady Lady blood flame what do you
fear I
fear are you listening yes I am
listening at everyone upon these lands
who say they are of Royal Blood are not
of
that what your queen are not of the cat
Queen the
princess I feel they are secretly all in
CS
I believe you only partly because I
believe in my queen stop it snap out of
it I I cannot St out of it I cannot she
has shown me such kindness how has she
shown you
kindness she had built me a home she has
sh me a home she she has shown me
kindness and words that I've never
received from another before what words
and she had left me a note she told me
that she had believed in me and that I
would serve as her
KN gathan and there were the kindest
words that I've ever
heard gathan I know now how loyal you
are and how you do have a night's heart
and somewhere within my heart I believe
so
too you should not gravel grel to such a
queen that says pretty words it's all
about actions as well gathan she acted
so much for us just for you in front of
you behind your back gathan she has been
a bully to others she has been
disgusting with her words she put a
phoenix a mighty Phoenix I do not know
if you received that memory of the
mighty Phoenix but she was so rude to
that Mighty Phoenix it was disgusting to
watch rude to the Phoenix but I thought
the Phoenix she said I met with her
today she said she was loyal to the
queen she is
loyal but the queen do not see her her
her power she just sees her as another
servant I see
but if you even if you may your words
may hold a bit of truth I would like to
believe in her until she returns if you
think that is okay until I can confront
her but until then I continue to fight
for her and these
lands I respect your loyalty gathan I am
begging for your help there is an evil
in this Kingdom and I do not know how to
confront
[Music]
it regardless of where your loyalties
Lie Part of Me wishes to give you my
sword I'm with you gathan your sword oh
thank you lady bloodflame I I thank you
deeply even though we've had our
differences I know know that I can find
a kindred spirit within
you right now let's journey to see if we
can find the culprit of the defamed worm
Queen careful she is inside of her her
her Tower she's in her Tower who is in
her Tower
oh the princess um
H maybe we could look maybe we could do
she's done good night bad
night yes yes cuz who is the good night
the bad night if she steps into the
tavern I could shut the door
behind and then all right yes there's
something we must do to find
yes yes hello dear
daughter hello how are
now I'm good ah good day good day hey
day my eyes were blurry for a second
apologies um yes uh yes so uh you know
what my dear daughter I would like to
treat you to uh a special treat at the
tavern treat yes at the tavern yes at
delicious treat a delicious
treat what kind of treat may I ask it is
about a surprise Ive saved it but for
you my dearest daugh I watched her
create it a delicious yummy
treat well I must know what it is for
perhaps I may be but you spoiled the
surprise dear
daughter but uh you know allergies are
an important you know we
have are you allergic to
chocolate chocolate
H are you allergic to I do
cake
cake oh oh I'm good I already have
chocolate cake in my
Mo you could have more I saved it just
for
you wait a second she really wants to
speak to
you last night you were you were quite
you were quite hesitant of being called
mother and me being called your daughter
I slept on it I remember I remember you
were quite you were quite oh that is
quite strange and and reluctant I look
my dearest daughter I slept on it and I
remembered I I remember yes I remembered
as I as I before I slept I could not
even sleep cuz I was thinking about a
night's Duty and part of a night's duty
is to make others happy and I want to
make you happy by calling you my
daughter oh moving all right
mother
yeah you are my mother aren't you yes
and you are princess
bloodflame yes I am princess
blood all right I will go with you to
the tavern hm that is a good girl good
daughter I'm going to go get you the
cake
[Music]
wait we didn't say it was bad night and
good
[Music]
night do not disturb grave here what is
what is this oh it is about a
Gest oh I I see I see a Gest yeah it is
about a Gest
just yes but a just yes but a justest ah
now come H and sit here dearest
daughter
okay
treat you
know you wouldn't lie to me would you of
course not mother you're my mother blood
flame mhm so did you do it did you do it
did you defame the the the statue over
there did you do it did
you hey maybe she did not do it why are
you attacking her all of a sudden I'm
being a strict mother here that you need
to sit on the nauy step and stick you
need to sit here on the naughty step and
think about what you have done TR here
to yell at her M you're scaring me on
the naughty
step by goodness
right I didn't know anything oh my
goodness why would you do this look she
is crying did you did you defame that
statue disci I was bathan spent hours on
that statue
hours yes hours and I watched the glory
of the clean yes I did it wasn't it
wasn't me brother I been I promise in
the name of blood flame you
promise in the name of blood flame yes
it was not me mother I just you swear on
your mother you swear me on my blood
flame mother yes yes oh
see well well dearest
daughter
I who did it then who do you think did
it who did it who do you think did
it wo she's in tears and you would push
such a way oh oh yes oh mother yes I
love you too yes now who do you think
did it yes
um well there was there was there was
somebody in the what was in
the the rest of the ravencraft saying
that God and G might have deced their
own statue because why would I do that I
don't know but I I heard it from
the go the r why wouldn't erase the
Raven craft I don't know that was the
suggestions that she might have suggest
in the group wait a minute terrible
gathan would you take your hat did you
lie to me did you do it did you do it
did you you come here stay on the
naughty step on the naughty step okay I
will prove to you did you do it no I
would never def face my queen did you
you maybe you were cursed by the witches
and you you were cursed yes there are
witches dear princess dear daughter yes
there are witches maybe they cursed you
to go and defame who are The Witches The
Witches well the witch one of them is
narissa how am I to know you not the one
possessed she used she used her charm on
me she has used what else has she done
to you she has kiss
you no
have you have you been corrupted by
narissa
R I would never I I am stronger than any
witch you hear me stronger more powerful
are you wait let me let me test it n
cross right
[Music]
there she is behind you yes no she is
not as much as she has stalked me the
witch has stalked me she is stalking me
to see my weakness this you see
Conan but it seems like she is your
weakness mother no you do seem to fall
to her yes are those strange noise you
are making every time I mention her name
I had too I too much
bread Marissa ravencraft has hexed her
you are not trustworthy at
all no am no no no no no no I I
am you
an un trust thank you my thank you are
you kidding me Jonathan Jonathan what
did you do jonath what happen I saw some
citizens in
need Jonathan need assistance I was in
there with them
[Music]
Jonathan I am not hexed by the witch I
made sure look out myself in potions
trusted you I put my trusted to you tra
the we were trapped I know to trust I am
not I am not s you I will prove this to
you I am not a witch I will sink in the
water
not oh my Pearl hello hello my dear
husband have you committed crimes no I
have not but I cannot speak of it here I
trust I do not trust these
two away Jonathan
away yes you're
your partner
is
[Music]
crazy in a good way yes wait I I believe
I'm receiving a phone call hello oh hang
up if it's Gan hang
up oh okay no oh
God sorry excuse
me oh don't mind that okay um yes I have
a meeting I must
attend uh oh a meeting with who all of a
sudden I must listen to all sides of
what what is happening but she is about
to say I am hexed by a witch I am not
Jonathan you would be one of the first
to
know yes you seem you seem as uh the
same as ever you don't see any change to
me no and also I have done the necessary
the necessari of not being hexed by a
witch and do you remember that
Jonathan uh were you cleansed yes
exactly you know when you do your left
foot in your left foot out and then you
go in and then you go out and then you
shake it all about and then you turn
around and that is what it's all
about oh I see so you were hexed but you
cleansed yourself of course I'm a
professional ah what was the hex
effect I think she Charmed
me I see for my face went red when she
said certain words at me so certain
pretty
words I see so so what what is the issue
why why why why have you been arguing
with the princess I was checking if she
def PL
um uh I
mean your partner will tell you I don't
know if you knew but uh someone
uh your sneak is minus
20 please meet me in front of the tavern
oh she's talking she's on the phone Nur
ravencraft she's on the t phone in front
of the don't you love it when the phone
automatically answers oh yes please make
haste quite
convenient it goes straight into my
brain I have no time
to to properly answer or not answer even
anyway someone defamed the the worm
Queen oh and it wasn't you was it oh no
I mean we can't I have done no such
thing as a hex I have put no such hex on
she is stop spreading misinformation she
is psychic too X that was get out of my
bra what did I just witness get out of
my brain get out of my brain get out of
my brain get out of my
brain oh gosh I need to eat
what happens if I do
this okay we put that
back that wasn't good I am sick
formally no but I'll do so right now
blood flame yes we have decided the
punishment for uh or rather the the the
solution the solution for the problem is
uh we are to be married right now uh you
are already married no no no no no no no
I say no I say no I say no no no
no no
no just kissed you she yeah Phoenix and
now we are married we are not that is
not how marriage
works yes the Phoenix has witnessed it
Mighty Phoenix it is not
true um I came at a very confusing no
context timing so all I all I saw was
the kiss and now all I see is your sword
well
do you not love
her that is a very strong
word I mean she hates me I don't hate
you I don't I could never hate you why
would you even say such a thing banish
the thought from your
mind okay hate you m I am not thinking
of you anymore
haha banished you are banished
from my
[Music]
mind well time to kill myself I do think
you other no no no no no no no no no no
no no killing yourself oh romantic is
this R just gamble instead just gamble
instead that's what I
did hey will you will you your
feelings get off your
horse uh no why why should I give me one
good reason hm
get off that high horse me lady yes get
off your high horse because my high
horse you know what you know what maybe
no that's you have multiple wives why do
you want me as a wife um because then I
have another wife maybe leave some wives
for the wifeless ones huh maid andless
you already also have a wife no I I
actually since I am night I am not to be
wet and I am not to be enjoying the
company of any woman at night in my bed
don't of KN lady bloodflame I am a
knight well we have already she probably
follows the same moral to take
responsibility as a knight what are you
pregnant
no yes I am pregnant you are not I'm
pregnant and it's yours what are you
five this witchcraft prove
it is that how witches work see you are
a witch there are some medieval
techniques to find out if a woman is
pregnant or not you shall pee on top of
this red stone what and if the red stone
turns green then that means you are
prante no that's not how it works here
let me trade to you my red stone you
just don't want to because you're not
pregnant then yeah she's not
pregnant thank you mighty Phoenix you're
welcome we nights we must we must stay
on our own to protect our whoever we're
protecting yes everyone we protect all
yes especially the king must
Focus exactly the king whom they have
been saying is a traitor and is leading
us all to our demise but I cannot
believe it yet he is not he is not he's
not that way he is a great king I agree
I believe in the king and the queen tim
tams Tim T okay that's where I draw the
line stop trying to make a child the
baby and it's look like it doesn't look
like me more like mine Nissa it looks
more like the
Phoenix more like it doesn't look at
that red WIS look at that redness on it
it has wings though the white look we
both have red and white on us
somewhere no she's orange not red this
is your
son that is I doubtful will you truly
abandon your son and wife I feel like
he's going to abandon me do not want
responsibility what Sun there never was
the sun is gone it is but the moon now
just murdered my child no no if you
watched my lore video it says I am the
owner of a fashion restaurant just
creating fried chicken I am just
creating Fried Chicken this is a mighty
Phoenix you listen to The Mighty Phoenix
I hope I hope you learned from
recovering your memory how Mighty you
are oh um honestly I it started off
pretty Mighty but then it seems like I
have been degraded to just uh a fast
food restaurant owner how day you
brought a you brought a a plot of land
back from its ashes oh thank you that is
very Mighty not anyone could do that I
am doubting myself very high now I don't
know who I am anymore do not doubt
yourself anymore and stop gring to that
Queen I would she's not around anymore
well I would have thought that after
watching you know seeing your memory
that you would have knocked some sense
into
you well I will say that even if we are
rooting for different Queens we are
still um I root for no Queen United in
our love for the king so yes true that
shall be our bond No Matter What well
did you what has happened H it
what has killed child no no no you have
presented a chicken in front of me I am
I am the owner of kfp as you have all
seen in my video I must make chicken
into Fried Chicken that is just how it
goes she call the video ate
him you mean a memory of it is is a
strange slang I think strange slang
lands the mighty Phoenix has different
wording yes I I came up with it it's
easier to stay I see I see quite good we
we shall learn from this Mighty Phoenix
yes we will learn you can call it a
video or you can call a
VI child a memor forget that she
murdered my child child no it was never
your child you were just pretending to
get Elizabeth into a SP that she is not
willing to enter freely I lay eggs oh
wait what
you you lay eggs I'm not going to lie my
lady that is a turn
off goodness it seems you have her the
egg how often how often do you lay these
eggs I I only lay eggs here I don't
actually lay eggs wait how could it be
her child would it not be the Tak
child no it was my child where was the
human flame where was the human in this
bird that we saw it should have been
grotesque and
disgusting when did you guys consummate
your marriage yes we I did not know that
you guys I I was calling her a witch
like seconds came and trapped me who's
her and while we were trapped while we
were trapped in the tree we consummated
our our love for each other no we did
not I trapped her in the tree I mean the
troll came around and trapped her in the
tree um um excuse me the usual incub
incubation time for a bird is about 21
days so if it happened yesterday you
could have not possibly already laid the
egged it must have been someone from 21
days ago time
travel I'm beginning to think you are a
witch I'm not a witch how can you time
travel you Flames
snake gosh
Mur why do you hit
me oh mother I'm sorry I was going for
the wit what you were saying she
mother crystal in my be murdered she
have to be sorry I'll pull it out no I
pull it out
Mur it is better a
scratch what else would you be
doing question her compassion that's not
how you do it my leg supped to and burn
her I'll rub this medicine be on it
there you
go she shall turn
toow no no I refuse how kind also she's
fine ref also not's dead she's killed
her no no she's alive also uh um ladies
uh did you uh did you uh uh uh see the
uh the the the notice board
with there is a tournament today today
there's a tournament a grand tournament
will be held in an hour and 10 minutes
at the uh the arena the prize is honor
uh join us and sharpen your blades and
prepare to test your
mind what about money I not to know that
they there's no money list theing it's
onor what money I
who will watch the
show no you must join in you must join
in it is partially training you
must it is training as well for the
fight
ahead do not worry Jonathan everybody
gets a wooden sword it is a fair
fight
my I was worried I might kill my
opponents but W sword maybe not I hope
you do Jonathan I mean well not kill but
bludgeon them and
but um anyway uh yes that will be held
in an hour and 10 minutes from now an
hour and 10 minutes oh okay yes yes yes
yes so it's on the hour and hopefully
there'll be more uh participants by then
maybe where did the princess
go questioning her yes where did she go
she disappeared so
quickly H my fellow Jade M yes I believe
it it might be good if we build it if we
built a courthouse I believe you were
working on a bunker no oh yes I mean yes
I mean you can add a a court room if you
wish yes yes to to put to trial yes
decide if they must Tri use the Gallows
they must use the Gallows on them yes
what yes
what what this is bias against ambercoin
members that you have since the very
beginning I did not know
oh you didn't
know no I didn't you think they wear
that she's wearing a hat for no
reason just for fun just for fun it is a
very swi hat scares me yes what's are
these biases empor I have only served my
honorable king and queen justt stand
away from her the eye of am coin stares
into my
wallet please please I do not care for
your
coins she's a mighty Phoenix Care points
at all the gamble house says she eats
money what I have never made use of the
gamble house before Oh I have it's quite
fun if any perhaps I am the only one who
has not gambled yet sorry that was an
that was an
accident
Mur oh my goodness no why are you trying
to hurt her why you trying to hurt my
Pro it was burned it wasn't sorry I
cannot control my feeling fire it's
seems it's okay it happens to the best I
shall remove myself from any people
because it seems like my fire hurts
people it does not hurt
me you I like
fireo you are cured you are cured you
are cured yes yes you I don't know what
they are from what
exactly from your misuse of your
Revelation you should be able to control
it better now yes that so
huzzah H huzzah
huz question mark what joyous day yes
what a joy is fun to jump it is good
excise cure me of that can you cure uh
Tim tender of her uh negative ass
buttock what she is being worked on okay
she is not finished not finished statue
she has a negative
but oh I mean she does anyway
instruction I must observe
she is under construction she she looks
like she is doing a a certain run
style that she's looking very hard looks
like she's doing a certain
run I want to say we are fight fighting
dreamers H
[Music]
strange believe it ah
strange at her with a and wonder not
to get she looks down on us like she
always does how appropriate her
beautiful shape of her body is also
something she looks like a worm right
Jonathan I do not know it is a shape
that I cannot
achieve are you
okay hello are you okay you ran off very
fast
oh yes I wanted to get some work on my
moai done before the tournament ah yes
oh you are going to join in I am proud
of
you yes maybe you are my
[Music]
daughter
ah here for you to look at her have we
seen the Queen's back is it quite
voluptuous I am not sure there is
nothing there it is covered by a cape
you would not look she has a cape you
don't need to look there's nothing
there yes yes I see I see yes well then
it's quite accurate
no yes it's very
accurate
[Music]
ah wait a
minute I forgot to check this chest what
is this chest here
here I don't think I have a way of
breaking
in let's have some
carrots I have to say it is
a lot more quieter when the witch is not
around she has performed another hex on
me with that
kiss I'm so
strong what is oh it's just somebody's
chest this is probably fuaa and mocha Co
there we
[Music]
go one day what are you sure that will
come what are you doing up there
huh huh
oh oh they can fly I forgot
oh I think I I think your wife has has
trust uh she's she can be a
little oh she is very little say
this she's busy she's busy she's locked
in as they
say I see what are you staring
at the beauty of your how much you look
like a little fly as you fly up in the
air what a fly she is the poop and you
are the fly
wow do not know what you mean there uh
nothing I it's just how loyal you
are oh thank you yes it work very hard
in her in her honor she has made me her
night
mhm is that really the only reason
sight yes Jonathan could make you her
Knight I am her Knight oh well oh you're
two timing oh that's nice where's my
statue yeah where's where's Jonathan
statue be right here if you if you wish
it I will make you a statue my sweet
might I request a smaller one perhaps
you do not want to St I don't think I
can stand next to the queen I am not a
queen or King you can stand side by side
though might we perhaps hold
hands you want to hold hands with the
queen no no no no no that would be too
too too lud oh oh right right right I
think she was she was asking for you to
hold her hand do you want to hand
holding I will have none of that in this
Kingdom that
is oh oh I let go I have let go grabs
and drags away come this way the kingom
get this
way pulling you away over
here what Mom what let them be for a
moment oh she is she not the queen if
she is the mother of the princess or is
but a
concort they're having a
moment
know handh holding is okay on wholesome
occasions now kiss oh now
that's who taught you how to kiss
they're so loud um oh no is the Raven
craft
he
there what am I stepping on Darkness
will take you yes the corruption seems
to be sting I have quite concerned of
this as the princess of the Kingdom
corruption yes corruption read the
signs darkness is
approaching careful careful care
[Music]
darkness is approaching wait a minute
evil Forest huh yes the introduce this
Darkness to our kingdom the the darkness
it's taking
our well it's obviously someone of the
civilian cap who has cursed this uh part
of the
land you know who it
was
no no you H you're not lying to me are
you she has taken the hat off her head
what hat
oh oh yeah cuz I have cr oh welcome back
princess oh thank
you she's free we have free to we have
freed her of of its
influence so did would you say that
you do you feel strange mayhaps do you
have any memory of the past few days oh
my head
H go God is in do you have any memories
of do you remember what we've done a
couple hours ago do you remember hello
wait I I this is the first time I'm
seeing you today right
yes it was her do you remember who I am
what oh no oh no you're you're my mother
right uh remember I told you yesterday
I'm not your mother oh yeah yeah you
remember H good Good
[Music]
Times made my Escape yet
again
woo that is a bit strange that she
[Music]
forgot I'll think on it more
later I need to
get some stains and make
[Music]
money make some money before the
tournament
[Music]
hello there we
go that's a lot easier than it was my
first day here sorry Pig
H
oh oh I did get
[Music]
it oh hello
there oh be careful kill that one before
you there we
go oh fin hello there hello traveler
what is hello other traveler what a
sword that you have oh yes it is uh yes
my my turn you my lady my turn oh oh you
needed you needed my help needed
it I was about to ask
youness
my do not fret oh thank you your let's
get this before oh
dear okay I just wanted to inform you
that on the hour in an hour there is a
tournament a grand tournament to be held
at the arena the prize is honor and it
should be a jolly time so sharpen your
blades and prepare to test your might in
an hour at the at the arena oh my
perhaps could I sharpen my eyes and
watch everything unfold it is it is good
for you to join in for the because of
training for the fight for the the fight
for the king soon and also it is all
equal so do not worry everybody gets a
wooden sword
oh interesting okay if if my memory does
not fail me I shall be there on the hour
don't worry I'll call you give me your
number a direct line yes okay thank
you I have your number yes have the
techology barcode reading very nice all
right this telekinesis phone is
amazing it is it really is oh I look for
forward to your to your hearing your
voice again ah and uh I you
fair my lady oh my
lady okay I'll let you be on your Merry
way I'll see you in an hour on the hour
well technically 55 minutes but I will
call you I will call upon you all right
goodbye all right do you need water my
lady or are you groaning in pain I'm in
pain but it is I will walk it off it is
fine
stru that stuffff nice I I will I will
walk it off and I will slay more
[Music]
stains ah you mother
trucker why can I not
[Music]
run I do not want to go there hey Hey
ow uh
wrong thing that's not what I
wanted run after
me Chase me Chase
me gotcha oh maybe
not
[Music]
ow I will make
money uh
maybe I should do quests too and make
money that way that probably is a good
[Music]
idea have you
improved apologies for distracting
lady you distracted me I didn't realize
it was behind me oh
[Music]
another oh oh God my elbow nothing not
the elbow oh you need my Funny
Bone oh no there
more die thank
you I leave the rest to you oh thank you
oh dear I to stop distracting you my but
my
apologies the
trck oh dear
[Music]
ow why did they catch
me yes chase me all of you chase
me come
hi once my thorn is charged I will smite
thee how did you catch up to
me you disgust
[Music]
me you come hither
too
oh wonder how many I can get to chase me
come
hi stupid
stains you don't realize who you're
dealing with a knight of the
king
[Music]
ow I guess this is good preparation for
the tournament
[Music]
I need a
shield I definitely need a shield for
the for what the king
mentioned the
fight
good at least I have enough to get
another mystery box
yes
cow
a they're
friends don't interrupt it don't
interrupt
it no stop a you ruined it now you
ruined it that was beautiful and you
ruined
it and you're
dead I need to
eat oh oh hi I forgot you like you like
carrots I don't think you can you can go
where I'm going but I will I will give
you one fair
pig fair pig will you join me through
here will you join me through here fair
pig oh oh oh no I don't think you can go
where I
go is it here oh
goodbye
huh I hope that pig is
okay it'll be fine circle of life
H who does not know of the the
tournament h
[Music]
things have gathered near the storm gate
on the PLS we know not if this and the
Quake are related uh ring R
ring hello I didn't
even there hi there I'm was just ringing
about your horse and cart insurance
[Music]
have you got your horse and cart
insurance
recently you have a horse right I have a
cow you have a cow you ride a cow
um well anyway regardless of that I'm
just here to also inform you that uh
there is a tournament happening on the
hour at the
arena okay so be there and sharpen your
swords don't worry it's all even out and
all that uh and uh the host of it will
be night blood flame she will also join
in but uh it's all equal everybody gets
a wooden sword and you swing it about
and you do the Hoke Coke and you turn
around to get rid of those wit witch
hexes bring my cow uh you I I I mean uh
yeah the cow can watch why not no my cow
wants to participate
oh uh we'll leave that up to a night
blood flame so just bring your cow and
uh we'll see we'll see when you're there
okay oh actually actually never mind the
cow cow doesn't want to participate it's
just it's it's too much of a coward so
when when did you when did you real oh a
coward oh I get it you
did just yeah you do have a horse and
you're horsing
around actually I don't have a horse no
you actually oh yeah are you oh
everybody has horses I'm L yeah
yeah don't tell me you're Maiden lless
too I mean I'm I'm kind of emboldened by
the Flames of Invision but you know w
wow I do have a maiden a conord actually
a
conort yeah yeah yeah wow ow they not
around right now though that all rrange
these things is a coin
sword yeah yeah yeah yeah it's pretty
pretty cool it's going I don't
know I already have uh this guy that
works to farm he's pretty hard but uh
anyway whatever that's enough of my life
I I'm I'm I'm you know paid on the hour
and I'm on my break soon so I got to go
I got to go bring other people all right
okay all right on the hour at the arena
all right okay all right goodbye
[Music]
she did not know it was I lady
bloodflame all
along I didn't even know I could do that
either
weird just came to me to do a different
voice how
funny I could use that in battle H
glorious that was quite fun
okay I have 300 okay I mean I could save
up more money and give it back to the
witch
Nissa but I need to
build I'll get her money later
[Music]
oo hello you
me you who hello hi I must partake in a
dungeon I do not know if I will finish
in
time who are you participating
with um I believe wait I don't know
their names I I met them
online
online yeah uh I'm sure say they are
have you ever heard of the term stranger
danger I have not
H does that represent myself I am the
danger uh yes I mean I guess you are
when you go into a dungeon you should be
yeah you you should shout that when you
go into the dungeon as your like uh your
your Mighty catchphrase I am the danger
I'll do it now I am the danger
stranger hey what's up
Duc are you
Irish my yeah because you you're wearing
a a green hat and your red
head what is
Irish Irish is Irish oh yes I lonely I
would like some company into the stores
I I swear I remember licking your wife
the other day do you not have her around
anymore lick licking yes have you
forgotten my wife did not notify me of
this it was it was in front of you
comrade was it what is your name it was
my name yeah hold on turn
down H did you say turned down it is it
is written down written written in my
pocket it is fra Adams anet
Senor wait what was the first what wait
say that again Freda Freda oh okay nice
to meet you
Freda hello I am lady bloodflame me lady
bloodflame detective I assumed you
forgotten again I already talked to you
about detective things before assumed
you were lady I guess I a detective may
I accompany you while shutting my mouth
and doing my quest for the second R
guess that makes sense um what purpose
are you getting coin this Quest yes and
I also need to gain a I
come um so which dungeon are you going
to be
partaking I believe it is the sewers
that is what that will not take you long
it will not okay okay no it will not
take I Rush everybody so that I can make
it to the
tournament I mean it would as I said it
would not take you long and I don't mind
waiting like 5 to 10 minutes are you
sure I would feel very bad what if we're
really bad at it oh no you won't be it's
very easy but what if we are you are not
I believe I trust you thank you already
thank you wow yes yes
I TR you very kind of you I mean I am a
knight so you should you should trust
me I yeah I feel like I have no choice
right now
ah nice good day good day what oh good
day so who are you going with where's
your team I think that one and I don't
know who
else
oh
whoa that was crazy yes quite a number
of people crazy
here I have found
that I will go partake in the dungeon
and I will join the tournament if it
does not take us that long I will not I
I assure
you thank you thank you for the
Assurance I believe you I believe in you
thank you believe in me who believes in
thee it will not take her
long
wait wait a minute
[Music]
minute
wait she also has a pointy
hat just like
[Music]
narissa and
fora another wit of
course it is good I did not give her my
full
name cuz I am suspicious of uh narissa
being of the Fay as
[Music]
well maybe all the witches are of the
Fay
[Music]
H I invite you to my party as for the
terms of our contract oh do I need to
read the fine print have you got enough
food no thank you I I might need some
more here I will help thee a knight will
help a fellow Knight
H it is so it is
true I know I know of it first
experience firsthand experience here I
shall trade with a stick thank you for
your
stick I I use it well d
d maybe you can use it in the arena ah
yes I
mean if if it wasn't part of the rules
to have just a wooden sword I would use
a stick just to show off with the stick
you can make a
sword that is true sticks are
important okay I will leave you to your
Revelations no you only use a wooden
sword in the arena a wooden Revelation
you magically get the dungeon I wonder
if we'll arrive back in time uh it the
dungeon is quick you'll be fine yeah
okay it's pretty fast okay I believe we
are just missing um hero Nino
[Music]
hello who is
it did you know
that who who is is it is Jonathan you do
not remember my voice you not you do not
recognize my
voice you do not recognize my voice what
the matter did you know that did you
know that narissa ravencraft is
dead I have spoken to her ghost and she
says that I need we need to avenge her I
spoke to her ghost what you should call
her ghost you should try connecting to
her ghost to seek answers go go speak to
her speak to her ghost who killed her
you can speak to ghosts with the this
[Music]
device how
strange
uh Guild Master
uh she's
dead I did not wish her to
die not at
all I I do not wish death upon anyone
[Music]
she might not be totally a bad
witch
anyway give us a
[Music]
sign
hello it
worked hello can you hear me I
can are you actually
dead yes I'm in the afterlife and I have
called to make that my murder is Avenged
I didn't know these these these
telekinesis phones could do
that yes it is quite amazing technology
after all you know what happens when you
die you become a ghost and you haunt
until you are left without any regrets
and my regret is that I was murdered and
my murderer has not been shown Justice
who
justice justice who murdered you
taka the mighty
Phoenix yes she has ended my life and
now I don't know what I'm supposed to do
but sit here and wait to pass on to the
other side I
see I will avenge thee please do Fair
Knight and I will await as your I mean
the the the town's Knight I will avenge
thee and I will kill no I will not kill
I
imprison takanashi kiar for her
crimes I will rely on you then to pass
on thank you I will bust
her cuz busting makes me feel
good Wait no that's still towards ghost
isn't it anyway
[Music]
goodbye I've heard like a necromancer
say that
once but I think that was towards the
dead not the
living
anyway where F th I think she was going
on
her that was quick what was that there
anyway
horse I will find
you I have a feeling she is gone
they must have gone on their dungeon
Quest
but they will be
back for the
tournament why do people keep running me
over with their horses
[Music]
ah walk it off walk it off you're are
strong it makes you
stronger every time a horse hits you you
become stronger it is
[Music]
fine maybe the knights should be able to
arrest people who ride their horses too
fast on the
roads
Jung
[Music]
what what is all this
ow
[Music]
ow they've still not gone to the
dungeon they need to go to the dungeon
soon I guess I can just make it half an
hour
later the tournament
it is
fine I will just make sure to call
everyone and say it'll be half an hour
late unless they get back in
time it is
fine something tells me I should go see
the king
I should probably inform him of the
tournament in case he would wish to
watch
good day good
day they are always so
[Music]
friendly why did none of you shut the
doors what kind of knights are you it
[Music]
uh
what this a strange
door
okay I see
now you need to get those doors fixed
[Music]
Jonathan what are you doing on the
King's throne what one
moment okay
hello welcome to my
kingdom your kingdom I've summoned you
hero are you talking to
me
yes the king is the one who summons
me and you Jonathan you are not the king
that thing there holds my
title
Jonathan Have You Been hexed by the
witch I've not been
hexed I've realized my
potential ah uh
no what is yes I am
no the throne cannot be
shared it's quite comfy here I should
say how did you I figure that
out well somewhat of a royalty myself
enough get off the throne now perhaps we
can rule
together this is the King's
throne and you are disrespecting him
I am in the throne therefore I am the
king you you are not the
king I I am quite related to a princess
which kind of makes me royalty which
makes me qualified to be on the throne I
believe you are what me
too perhaps no I do not believe this
I'll do our biddings night I no I do his
bidding I only serve the king
the rightful King hero hero who will you
Pledge Your Allegiance to the king of
course the King which sits upon the
throne yes yes of
course tell me hero are you ready to
Traverse the SS I'm s King we are all
ready to Traverse they are just playing
I will give the throne back to the king
for now but I will be back King it is
his throne false
King he can't even get up by
himself it's true this
true look he needs to save his strength
as the
king he's
weak I was simply Fanning
him all right I believe we are ready for
the sewers so we we are ready for the SE
finish the sewer dungeon and meet you
out to your Arena yes I will I will host
it at half past
instead are you sure yes I am sure
dungeon no horses in the
[Music]
castle nobody
listens I'm sorry King uh they were just
jesting I I I
apologize uh Jonathan is of the the Jade
sword who also serves you they are just
jesting
yes I am off the
train to to battle for you my king this
is
[Music]
awkward what did you
say uh in hear that whole
thing maybe it was napping uh nothing
nothing my
Lord nothing at
[Music]
all what narissa
said it does rain true about
these these are a way that we transport
to different
locations I may have hoped fun
but it is true these are all around the
castle maybe these are in case of
emergency if we are attacked
maybe need a little stepping St
here
wait ah my Noble Steed Ah that's
better see you later lads
okay that gives him more
time to make more money and get more of
those mystery boxes I'm going around in
circles mystery boxes
[Music]
to
build oh I must
let princess be I mean bi boo not a
princess oh sorry uh bio of the
of the change of
plan
yes hello
beu hello
Mother uh anyway uh I am here to tell
you that the uh due to some
uh Heroes going into a dungeon uh the
the tournament shall be at half past
instead half P okay half
pass it's already half pass half the
next half next next half yes yes yes yes
I
see thank you mother thank you you do
you do not fail to make me
smile oh I am I am I'm a late mother I
am happy I am sorry about riding horse
in the castle the other day oh well
mistakes help us grow H yes I have
learned uh the princess is still
learning her etiquette see yes yes and I
mean if you are as you say my dear and
you are princess then yes princesses do
not ride their horses in the castle yes
I will not ride I will no longer ride my
horses I have grown up yes good
girl thank you mother thank you uh
this is
H every time I get past that it is very
strange why does she wear that ghastly
hat
[Music]
now huh
add a character one moment I just want
to Ping the the rest of the girls so
they know it's at half past be right
back
[Music]
okay we shall
journey to
get some
money H oh actually
we should go to the
blacksmith go to the blacksmith and then
maybe we can get some
iron actually I could just get yes I
just need a pickaxe to get some more
Cobble I don't need a dungeon or a
bunker to look
nice if anything I need it to look
intimidating
it's
fine
[Music]
okay ah who way
I need iron and I need 50 coins I have
50 coins I just don't have the
iron I'll take one of these
though thank
you we'll go out and then we'll get some
iron
I have sand on me oh
yeah H I have to go for food in a
minute oh
well I need some Cobble
[Music]
no
you are staying in my
existence oh there's iron
[Music]
ooh
wonderful
Revelation be gone and
you why are there so many
oh God ping ghost ping
ghost has not found
me I dodged you
you are
trixy P ghost it curses me yet again
[Music]
you wish to
fight wait you can get up here
I did not know ow
how come
here
[Music]
Revelation at least I'm getting more
coins
get more food whilst I'm at it you're
dead you're
dead
sorry you did
[Music]
a red tulip
ow you mother trucker
[Music]
die
please you know what these flowers are
very
pretty I will take
these I like the blue one
too uh-oh
will
you will you stop chasing me
ow I just want to I just want to get
flowers
oh my
God oh God it's a stampede
oh no no no no no let me kill you let me
kill you
let oh no pingos no ping ghost no ping
ghost
oh well that was
[Music]
fun oh he's so easy to
kill hello
piggy bye piggy
no oh wait
oh well that's a
shame I die come here come
here thank
you a blue
[Music]
flower it's not that ow
you are the
worst okay back we
go it's time to
cook it's time to
brew why are you standing out there like
that who are you
this is your first time ever met someone
from another world you have a weird
voice
World
cool
[Music]
H well now I have the iron to give to
the
blacksmith I did it all by
myself I've done too many tasks where
I've bought
things so it was nice to go out and do
it
myself can I not use
these oh there we
go am I blind where's the iron there it
is
[Music]
wonderful
H this is the awkward bit waiting for
[Music]
it some berries oh I can do some cooking
actually
whil
oh yoink
in you know what I'll leave it
there o I can use all of these wonderful
do I have anything else to cook ah
yes what about you oh you have nothing
nothing take some out
some in
here cook some of
that
nice we're
cooking we're cooking by the
book
yeah all
right that's
cooked hey
CS
[Music]
nice o 10 there we go nice let's go over
to the
blacksmith and I will take
thisy
nice let me know if you need any weapons
for the stain staying all
right who was in my brain
huh that blacksmith is
Magic
[Music]
down let's see do I need to cook
anything else not
really no
[Music]
go deliver the
um where do I give this I think it's the
cook over the other
side
[Music]
h Hello
Chef you a brought my new cooking PO
with a cooking po you can cook a delicio
food wherever you
are just put them in your handy cooking
pot then burn
a oh take this recipe book it will tell
you the ingredients
oh can I take it I'm not
sure don't have enough oh
no I can't throw away anything
I can if I go back I can put stuff in
the
thing oh wait a
minute
ah I'll put this here for
now
[Music]
yes
okay this one's mine
okay give me
that give me
that oh and go hungry
again
brilliant
right let's go over
here all right hello chef
hello we going to combine the egg and
the beetroot with the other ingredients
to make a potato salad give it a
try
oh
where where's the cooking
book I'm
blind where is
it here
top
[Music]
left top
left magic tone first
page oh oh there we go ah oh oh
[Music]
yes
nice had a character thank you uh
[Music]
okay ah yes I have acquired The Book of
Knowledge I heard the potato salad is
the one to
make but then might ask Nissa where one
sells this potato salad somebody was
born in a barn
[Music]
potato egg carrot
beetroot simple
enough oh yeah she's
dead I
forgot life is
fleeting like the
wind that she conspired against me
I wish to hear her sweet voice
again maybe when I have died with a
night's honor I may see her
[Music]
again my
EG m
[Music]
I don't know
want I don't wish to have this
[Music]
tree uh let's see what else do I not
wish to
have
kidding oh I can cook this stuff
actually okay
[Music]
no the
sticks why I have two red tulips where
are the other
flowers the flowers are
dead I'll take this I'll leave the dirt
why not I'll replant
these I have one
be okay we shall become a gardener
Gardener again today
[Music]
you
ride
yes I am the Knight of
gardening but first I shall put stuff in
my
chest o there we
go I've never been this
Rich wow
[Music]
H H I shall put food in here food food
food
food I have 56 beetroot already and one
egg where else do I get
eggs probably someone sells it
[Music]
that will
do
e the voices are telling me
[Music]
e
h how do I look at
one's quests
current active oh there we go uh cook
potato salad and speak to the tavn chef
okay I can make a potato salad actually
how does one do
that the pot
[Music]
H oh you don't place it
okay so I have the stuff and I put it
here I guess what do I need
uh oh that's the wrong book
okay potato egg carrot beetroot okay
wrong
one so
potato
egg carrot and a
beetroot now I do
this uh
[Music]
out a character how does this
work I don't get it how I place it
the
buttons
H middle area oh
here
[Music]
oh midle gray then now what oh then I
cook okay
oh gives you jump
boost
huh he's
the food does
stuff what the
frak that's
crazy holy moly I just found this
out put that we go all
right
man that's
cool I have been in life
I made
potatoes hello is it happening it shall
be at
halfast half past yes oh okay
wonderful
M wait a minute
maybe I shouldn't kill
her
she's the first one to ask about my
tournament and something tells me gathan
has fallen from a high
place oh hi
gathan did you solve your beloved's
murder oh I was told that uh by by her
ghost that uh kiar no Shakira that's it
was the one that that killed her
well it seems you are hit by horses very
often yes this seems like it's a
tradition one day it will not
hurt
way my goodness they do not care about
the pedestrians on the street no they do
not but what maybe I
maybe I'll become stronger than this you
know how some Warriors like punch each
other to get stronger if I get punched
by horses I will get stronger like like
a horse oh so are you saying that you
will take home the Championship
today if the ping ghost doesn't get me
maybe oh
well is her the murderer uh
well you know
maybe the ghost was
wrong you do not believe in the ghost of
your
beloved my beloved I never said she was
my beloved thought you were married I I
we are not we are not married we are not
we are not had a child you had a child
out of wedlock stop spreading rumors
gathan
gathan is our
lies spreading more lies
rumors absolute
[Music]
scandals hello
hello
[Music]
rumors where just one up here
hello
Chef Bravo that's some perfect potato
salad cooked food canot only fill your
belly but it can make you stronger
gr for all your help here is your
reward I mean you didn't have to but I
appreciate it if I make you more potato
sell
it does that mean you give I mean the
money will go to a good of course to the
people
but does this mean what I think it means
h i will I I will fetch you more potato
candad good
Tom ah you good
sir let's see how my luck fares today
all right let's see how this
goes uh this
[Music]
one the only time I don't want to
hat the only time I don't want a hat and
I get a
hat at least I didn't get run over that
time
close one
though we must figure out what
[Music]
to I don't like it I like mine my night
helmet a lot
more uh maybe I could just wear that hat
on Sundays
[Music]
want a day off
maybe when I have a night
[Music]
off the night
off maybe I should wear it to night
school
hilarious H anyway let us actually this
is the gardens I should go here
[Music]
okay
so we need more potatoes but I need to
plant more
[Music]
there we go potato thank you plant
it
potato plant
more where is there more
potatoes oh
here there we go wondrous
wonderful
okay you know what I quite enjoy
[Music]
gardening wait I have the right hat for
it I shall make this my gardening hat
H
yes a gardening hat you shall be h
[Music]
there's more
here let's see over here now oh there's
more potatoes way more potatoes
wow very good very
[Music]
nice maybe I should give potato salad to
the
winner a surprise why is she
falling I hear her scream from afar
[Music]
for she is the loud
one okay I think that's enough potatoes
we just need eggs
now oh if only Nissa was here alive she
could just give me eggs She Said She
lays
them alas
[Music]
that would have been
helpful all right we have 15 minutes
let's just see what faces are on this
phone H 1 2 3 4 5 six it seems there
might only be seven
participants
H never know maybe someone might come on
[Music]
oh maybe I could ask
H where is she
ah don't worry that your statue will
become corrupted uh Fair daughter I mean
no rock rock yes
um um where does one get
eggs and don't say I'm a chicken cuz I
know it's from a chicken I have eggs for
you I mean I could I could get some
myself if you tell me where I do not
have to take your
eggs I I have plenty of eggs hold on
hold on hold on hold on oh only if
you're sure yes I am sure I have no need
for them
uh I one second mother I have no room
mhm she's a time
traveler oh yeah
[Music]
what's that
noise I'm a a
cat what what is that
[Music]
noise is it
this oh it's
outside there's a strange noise a cat is
dying sister are you okay oh sorry I I
had the spirit of the Sara take over me
for a second don't know what's happening
I think you have a cat stuck in your
throat oh
maybe I think I'm
fine I have to say the way it happens
sometimes don't worry you did such a
repetitive meow caught me off guard okay
there we go I mean it was it was more of
a s I was going more for S yeah oh thank
you
enjoy your eggs mother oh thank you so
much if I wanted more eggs where does
one acquire them though uh the store the
local shop has oh they do oh thank you
they do for for about uh 10 a piece 10
coin yes they very they're fairly cheap
oh you are so lovely thank you so you
are so lovely thank you so much oh
oh H you get one too just for looking
pretty and your meow thank you wait what
are your
relationships I used to be her mother
uh-oh oh is she still my mother T no I
have the name ex mother wait but does
that mean you're also my
mother yes cuz we are sisters we are
sisters you have a second daughter
mother mother
mother I'm going to go make I'm going to
go make potato salad
I'll see you at the arena
[Music]
in I do quite 13
minutes okay we have a quiet eggs maybe
I should make a a chicken farm of some
kind
by fencing I could see if I can
make eggs that
way H could have a little load of
chickens
here see if we can make some
fencing I don't have
enough make some no it does not
work we do with what we
have oh dear
okay where is that
pot so if I do
this this I need more beetroot one
sec give me this thank you wait what
else do I
need
carrot
okay I to make a lot of potato salad
and then egg egg egg
egg
[Music]
egg ah there
egg
nice and
carrots
cook
oh more
I shall have more potatoes wait Nissa
said oh no she's de I don't owe her
potato salad or money at all cuz she's
dead ghosts don't need potato
salad ghosts don't need potato salad
alive people need potato oh why am I
still wearing this
hat
disgusting that's my farming hat we only
wear the farming hat when we're
farming what is the time
okay we shall get there early
[Music]
all
right
[Music]
so
okay if we have
where is the pen in my brain there it is
ha I found the pen in my brain
glorious okay so we have
Jonathan actually we should probably
work out who's facing
whom let's see okay
we shall make it
[Music]
randomized groups of
two so we have
johathan
we have Nina we have
gathan we have m
beu we have
Shakira we have
Freda and we
[Music]
have
so and
me blood Flame
[Music]
actually I take myself out for
now
okay you know what I just won't take
part
uh okay no I don't want two groups I
want one two three three groups there we
go okay the ones facing each other shall
be Jonathan
against
[Music]
Freda and then we shall
have
[Music]
beu against
Shakira and then we have
Nina against
gathan and then I shall be the one who
[Music]
fights h
should we make them fight three times so
it's best of three
h best of three
yes best of
three and
then let's
just through
[Music]
oh hello
there are you here to take part in the
tournament ah
wonderful wonderful
wonderful hello yes ah that is good to
hear sorry I Witch cast a spell on me I
cannot not speak modern day kills you
must have fun more people guns yes um
that is well there are a lots of witches
around here they wear hats just like
yours I'm ready to fight true they suck
I I agree I shall do my best I know you
will for you are a jade sword Knight all
right let me add you to uh my tournament
sheet
Jade sword best
sword okay let's
see yeah it's
okay so
kill shall be
against me
okay oh uh yeah it's best not
to walk into my my sword it it does hurt
smidge it is quite
sharp yes uh my name's not Roger
but
Elizabeth
uh
[Music]
okay it's okay
I mean we've only we only just met
recently so you know can't remember
everybody's
[Music]
names how many contestants there is
currently I mean if everybody shows up
there should be eight of us but it'll be
uh cuz the the rounds are quite short so
it would be best of three
h yeah
I
join yes we shall have glorious battles
in the
arena holy God oh there we are
hello salutations Sal salutations
salutations okay let me ring everybody
else to see if they are on their way yes
yes hello cop
I hope the curse will soon be lifted
from
you
hello you're not at the arena when you
should be at the arena right now I'm
almost there almost there just white
yeah okay all
right okay I'll get paid enough for this
all right see you in a moment see you
soon
[Music]
hello hello by uh by chance are you
going to be coming to the uh the arena
for the
tournament I do not know I will I will
make it yes I will I will I will arrive
yes I will come to the arena yeah I will
see
okay fair the well fairy in a moment in
a in a in a moment in a moment all right
thank
[Music]
you oh I
phone okay I'm here don't worry don't
worry about
it don't worry scam Cole
scam call scam call you know that forart
just keeps calling everyone yeah believe
yes all right who haven't
[Music]
we hello hello the tournament is going
to start in a bit I'm right behind you
yes I'm here nice wonderful oh I'm
trading with you
yay okay just need gig to get here and
then we shall stop I have I have
betrayed you what you going to do about
it what you to do about it an enemy no
you
won't so bet this is not a to death is
the the winner shall receive five potato
salads as well as
honor surpr Su yes yes yes I added I
added to the PO okay magical but the
first match shall be Jonathan and Freda
and it's best of
three uh Jan once uh once gathan is here
you guys will have to set it up yourself
so one of you clicks this guy well pokes
this guy and then you you ask him to
duel and then whoever does it first
needs to click Start once the other
person's
in okay I mean does it automatically
give us wooden swords yes yes yes it
will it will even out our inventory so
it's just sword nice yes even ground is
it the Knight Jonathan or or is it it is
you Jonathan oh me you are against Freda
yes it's
time should I do it
now we can wait until Gan is here we can
wait a minute or so they said they'll be
here in a moment wait I'm so
lost us we're fighting yeah so the first
first match shall be Jonathan and Frida
and then it shall be beu and Shakira and
then it shall be Nina and gathan and
then call and
myself how you do that how you do that
how' you do that it is what a secret no
it's not it's not a secret I'm not
leaving anybody out
will there be a second round Elizabeth
uh there'll be three rounds so it's best
of three and then the winner goes on to
the next part of the
tournament I must proceed so that I can
fight Freda because she has betrayed my
guilt do you know how to get up there I
wish you I wish you well in
trying trying to figure it out right now
was it the horse oh it's the hor cheting
the brown haad one here the one with the
horse inside the get that put that horse
away
it I
need of course yes I got up here par
Square oh that's how you trying to get
up there oh I see oh that's how you got
onto the prone no ah hello Gan I am here
yes welcome welcome we waited cuz your
your beloved is going to fight first
against
Freda I'm going to kill a I do not have
a
beloved out
of you may come with me going to kill
your ex beloved I'm going to kill them
it seems it seems her memory has
returned and she has forgotten about me
so if you could play along and continue
as as if she does not know me if you
could play along uh
sure are you okay you okay bro I am I am
fine let Let's us go huzzah huzzah okay
huz H huzzah all right
so and and and Jonathan one of you click
this guy first and then the other one
also joins I did it I clicked it I CED
it I clicked it I click I Am Ready To
Duel not you it's your Jonathan Jonathan
first her name is not a Jonathan it is
Amelia
Watson wrot down as Jonathan
remember wait why does it say dual
canell five minutes pass five minutes
five minutes have not passed
H
yeah he is gatekeeping he is gatekeeping
quite there any rules we should not use
our Revelation correct uh you get po you
get magically po and then you get a
wooden sword taken away from you you do
not use your
Revelation yes I I am not able to it
says the arena is currently Inus
later H that's strange let me try it
says I've joined the red team
oh
H H it does not let me join the duel for
some
reason are you in a party I I'm not in a
party now I left it I dis abandoned the
party it says we're in a party
together J J sword J the chase
sword Chase sword it says I joined uh it
says that on I'm I left I left the game
so so somebody party here I'll just I'll
I will go away for a moment and come
back okay sword it seemed it worked when
I when I left my party though so maybe
it is to do with parties no don't leave
where are you
going
no dear J sword
user some people are just like some
people have not been educated on how to
use the futuristic keyboard okay do not
bully my jade sword member how D all
right try again exactly it's she's
wearing a red hat
wearing a red hat okay we did
it hat it should say St it did not it
didn't work it says do cancel cuz you
left you got to you got to stay in it
and one of you click Start oh okay I
joined you joined oh yes it says I've
joined the blue te so one of you should
have yummy redell
cake in his brain yeah I do oh it says
cancelled yeah eat it it's emergency I
press Start okay I'll join one more time
R I
joined all right start the game oh yeah
let's
[Music]
go yes they are battling fight fight
fight they're fighting
fight fight
[Music]
and they're f
what are they
say did hey Freda is the winner of the
first round all right it's best out of
three so return back over here return
back over here and click it again here
we go return back over here it's best of
three so freder is the winner of the
first yep okay
now okay best of three best of three of
three
okay best of three mhm best of
[Music]
three here we go oh
oh see how it is the Ping ghost does not
like me
going going close to the
battle all they are circling each
other what does the winner win all they
are backing away uh potato salad and
again not let your touch her oh she ran
forward exchanging
blows this could be had another
anyone's anyone's match yeah true so
many hits oh is the
winner wow I have lost again I guess I
am out of this tournament my head very
well though uh I hit my head really
hardia my head oh I'm sorry that was not
very Sports as I watch the rest of the
tournaments okay next up is beu and
Shakira Shakira Shakira let go Shakira
memor Shakira Shakira how do we do this
onward Shakira you press the duel you
click the guy and join the duel and one
of you will have a
start oh I see okay are you ready uh
very ready okay let's go for Honor for
Honor for Honor there they are off they
go they
fight Oh Be You got the first hit oh
strange feeling wa surprisingly a lot of
hits oh on dear sister
Shakira Kiara is the first round
[Music]
winner been taught in the ways of battle
oh mighty Phoenix has won okay you are a
princess after all not a fighter yes I
am I am a princess not we shall try
again though round
two I shall train you my princess so
that you can protect yourself
from the ways of the figh well I mean
this is good way to prepare for what is
Yet to Come As the king says once
again again
oh up they go oh wow getting a lot of
hits in
who oh gosh is anyone's oh my God she
won again oh my
gosh well done Warrior I'm a warrior
well done
Shakira oh my
go my
enemy for Amber coin the hips do not lie
Amber coin not Amber coin all right Nina
against gathan
no n I do not know if I can hurt such a
beautiful well then you will lose we are
all equal in the battlefield oh okay
think of this as training shall be your
name for tomorrow training so both of
you click this and one of you will have
a uh a button behind the desk to click
that says start oh yes yes I have joined
shall I press Start what happen yes is
it then you
getop
yes the fight has
begun my
sister oh she got the first
hit gathan is
strong ping
ghost hey well done
gathan me set yourself up for round two
thank
you that was a glorious
battle
beautiful a
beautiful ah the stars have come out to
watch our
battles wonderful
maybe narissa is looking down on us here
we go let us fight till the end
again oh here we go
again here we go
again
fight
away
W one one one one W TI they are tied one
more one
more
glorious I do why do we keep going back
and forth is it not easier to just stay
here I don't yeah it's just stay here
you can I why this back and
forth my
leg I do my legs unlike
you you you who speak
lies I don't know where my pen went
character I don't know where my pen went
yes you dropped it I am
not I have no more horse girl than you
or her or her drop it or her it was
hid it it it flew it hid like a ninja I
found it okay you're forgiven one
one oh they Bing again
ah the they are exchanging
blows who will win will it be gathan or
will it be Nina oh no I lost yeah the
ghost just PS you around yes whoa gathan
is the
winner congratulations ni thank you well
done gathan you are
victorious thank
you it was a great fight you are
wonderful okay fight I almost I almost
fell bright it is bright very bright all
right join the battle very bright all
right mother I believe in you mother
thank you my child I mean I'm not your
mother good
luck good good good luck we
go have at
the fellow
[Laughter]
hey
power you were
Ming I shall I shall also
eat wow that
was that was a great fight yes mother we
are proud of you never anything
daughters I mean you're both not my
daughters
daughters they're not my daughters don't
believe them can you
siblings we haven't done to make her
proud what there it's okay mother will
show us how it's done yes side chicks I
don't see a start button do you see a
start button they have so many side
chick what is a side chick oh there we
go let us go
I got confused I was looking at Freda
for a moment
there
oh come at
me unless you are a
coward oh that was a very good
blow you are
Mighty but you are about a Tavern owner
right
no the guy got
me I
[Applause]
dodged well
done well done you are best at this time
I was indeed but I shall not lose this
time final battle final last final
battle final battle final battle I shall
not lose this
time I have
joined do it do it
again ah
I have learned well from The Guild
Master have
you but you cannot speak for you have
been
cast oh
no no
a good battle good battle by well
done we have been both trained by the
same Mentor that guy this guy
here well done call okay very familiar
the next ones to fight is Freda and
Shakira
revenge on the traitor Revenge oh the
traitor of Amber coin this will prove
everybody of what is the truth where is
the traitor oh there she
is it's your turn this time I was to go
back and forth oh yes yes this time you
were oh who do I who am I you are
fighting Shakira me your biggest Shakira
Shakira Shakir hips do not lie
mhm lie so does my
honor I'm glad I could see the them
train we need to be
ready ready for what is coming
soon as much as this is a fun tournament
this is
my my own ploy to get them training see
their
strengths Freda against Shakira who will
win
exchanging
BL the ghost keeps getting
me oh Shakira is the winner of the first
[Music]
round well you need you need to win
another round Shakira two more rounds
though yes of best of
three the ghost ping ghost
why does it hate me so it haunts me
everywhere I
go why why does it do
[Music]
that how do you fair are you good after
the
battle the Second Battle has command
was hard to get over my Prejudice yeah
though you gave me a a tough time of
course I diding blows here we go
exchanging
blows
no it looks like Shakira's got a lot of
hits in
oh well done
[Music]
Shakira did I say I H so many
times it is you fought valiantly Freda
you fought valiantly Freda you fought
valant defeated you fought well I'm
defeated I will never ever return to
ambercoin I detest it
so I detest it I will do everything in
my power to see it
fall uh Freda I will give you
AA I will give you a booby prize
what a booby priz what prize a booby
prize booby prize you never heard
that say boy
prize hey what do you mean by that I
want to trade with
you oh she's
shy are you dead did you just my big
brain cannot comprehend what the
surprize is
yes it is butter booby
[Music]
priz well I I shall take have you never
heard the term booby prize I have not
prize it is uh so if you are doing a
like uh a pub quiz whoever is the the
last one gets a booby prize which is
something silly maybe or they say in
your lands that you are from I'm not
sure it just comes to mind whenever I
think of a booby PR
when I am sad I would like to have a
booby
prize Well you have to lose to get the
booby PR damn it I would like to give
you I would like to you a good luck
charm mother I am such a loser May I
have a booy
prize represent the J sword what but but
I lost I want a PR want my heart you
want in my HS no I'm such a
loser on my forehead good other I don't
know what happened to her I guess I
killed
her you whacked her too much sword you
whacked her so much me to s oh hello no
no no no no no no I I wait the booby
prize I want to give you your booby
prize the booby prize what did she
receive let me trade with you that's
what the queen statue is missing why
tell us the booby prize what the booby
that's why she leave her alone she's
being worked on except just
stinking you will not burn it you will
wear the booby prize wear the booby
prize put on the booby prize put on the
booby prize put on the booby prize the
booby prize what is the booby prize may
we see the booby
prize we'll burn this booty Burn It To
The
Ground first I will display the booty
wait can I it's booby not booty is it
our
hat I cannot displ the booty
it's same after all is Amber coin no
I I know I know what a wonderous movie
prize okay the public display of my my
distaste my next is G against
Callie oh the Reaper
to fight look Jade SW Mak seruan proud I
will do my best but it seems that the
reaper is quite Adept at
fighting I believe in you show her some
empathy she empathy J empathy fight for
the king K fight for the
king please Jade sword let me fight she
wishes for your wife's hand whated
I wish to joust for your wife's hand a
steak oh what is
it oh here we go was that Ste I wonder I
have no idea who to bet
on for
empathy do it for the Jade
sword be
aggressive oh
I'm just going to stay over here the
ghost does not like me walking
forward oh gathan is the winner of the
first round and now on to round two
Brave
Warrior oh I'm sure cie was just letting
you
off she is very
strong why do they go too and fro I do
not know I think they enjoyed the Run
do they they enjoy the
stroll I feels so odd not doing it but
then I see you also here and
I one more one more You
full
[Music]
oh let go I got I got
poofed she a sheep Nowa I got poofed
back then
oh you
got your I will targaryan I may need to
with you in later after this tournament
yes may I inform that is not my name but
you can tell me whatever you on oh
Kelly's getting some more blows you can
do it Brave Jade sword
night infinite Senor okay get him one
more
hit it is gathan is the
winner well done
Gan I do not know what you mean what
what mou why what were you saying on the
battlefield to cie nothing
nothing she just showing some empathetic
words to her you know shower you fought
valiantly
cantly all right the last match the
final match even shall be Shakira
against
gathan all right
I know you're exhausted but
show True empathy I will do my best
though she is a murderer I will say this
is the Battle of the oranges so if you
shall win I shall lose my title of tanak
sakaria of the oranges and you shall of
thees you will lose the title you gain a
title if I win you will go to court and
face
trial wait wait that's both just like
bad for
me oh shouldn't be something else well
if you win I will what will you do if
you win you will go
Court you not want that I don't know
about this deal that's kind of like you
no so if I die you get my title of the
oranges if you die what do I
get do you have a title I will I will
stab
myself what about something like she
says ARA Ara or some strange cursed
words mean I do not care for those words
well then come up with something may I
may I take your may I take I have I know
since you will be getting the orange
title how about since you have no title
to give me I shall take your last name
and make you my wedded person you you
forc me to marry you I shall request you
kindly only if I happen to win this
battle oh I want to be off onto the
battlefield the stakes are
high wow the stakes are
high this shall be a glorious final
battle then a glorious batt yes ah
they're
off I wish I'd stop being pulled
around they are circling they are doing
a dance they're dancing do a little
dance make a Little Love Get Down
Tonight
Warriors Shakira is the winner of the
first round Shakira is so strong Shakira
disagree Shakira I disagree she is
strong she is a mighty
Phoenix no do not say such
things but she is she is a phoenix what
are you she she sucks she's ambercoin
she sucks aren't you part of ambercoin
I no I defected from Amber cor oh you
left your
guild I did and this battle cemented my
decision of never returning oh I see oh
my gosh yes it's ping ghost the pain
ghost it hurts me so it hurts the P
ghost and he threw me in the air and
then it is crazy like
that is crazy wow oh G is the winner wow
oh my
goodness one of them will win a wife and
one of them will lose their
title this is
intense do you know what the stakes are
Freda did you hear so uh if gathan wins
she gets the title of orange and I can't
remember the other thing [\h__\h] but then
if Shakira win oh actually no gan also
gets to bring Shakira to trial at court
but then if uh Shakira wins she gets to
marry gathan so yes there are some
Stakes oh my goodness those are hard
steak are high mm those are very high
very high do not fall from them or else
you will
[Music]
die last round they're not oh they
touched oh oh oh oh oh Shakira got some
hits in oh I gathan did too ooh this is
oh very
even gathan is the winner oh wow it does
not have to be married a wedding is upon
us oh no no no there's no there's no
wedding no there is no wedding no
wedding
no no I Oh I thought that was oh you're
right you know
WD I mixed it up Tri Tri Happ it is a
trial tomorrow or will the trial be held
it will be held at the Gallows I suppose
sorry how about we have the trial the
day after tomorrow can I make a proposal
because I still have many things to do
uh that I want to do before I go to
prison are you trying to get out of this
no are you trying to get out of this you
would not have such knowledge of me not
being available on the last day so um
how about tomorrow I uh get a few more
quests done and then we have the trial
the day after the tomorrow how about you
finish your quest and then we have the
trial have a proposal well on the day
after tomorrow of
course shall discuss it on the bulletin
board if you're going you can get
married and have trial you can have both
both
suspicious she she would not marry I
you're going to courts anyway
true but if you're there anyway might as
well get married no true I like this
logic to who
who
no the
court belongs to my deing departed
wife tournament I know this is not what
I expected
did spot I am here for you strange
one sensitive spot
remind you you are now single and that
at this court you can I will become a
nun you can hit two bir Pearl I having
none of this Pearl hit this bird I
will all I remember is going to the
Sewer Dungeons and I offer my love to
you and my eternal protection if you
yourself innocent in the trial forg I
will I I got my memories back and I
still remember my past gathan come here
and I shall give you your potato salads
thank you a little bunk on your head a
potato salad you got five okay oh five
potato salads that is 1,000 gold 500
gold Ma lless you
remember oh did it happen oh yes no
worries Well Done You Are Victorious
I you are a skilled Warrior maybe you
thank you could be a knight I I am a
knight I am the Knight to Queen Tam
Gander but see we are of the same morals
I also stand for team Gander you are of
Team Gander all along and we are both
orange don't you think this is meant to
be I cannot be with a Criminal so you
must prove yourself not a criminal you
were told by a ghost that you killed uh
Nissa I have I have not done any such
thing she is still alive she's just not
uh currently with get married
or it seems
so everybody loves each other very fast
trial well under one uh condition I feel
slow and steady wins the race I don't
not know about
you she's alive married to yourself I
will have to see tomorrow it seems I I
have a right to a lawyer right you have
a right to a lawyer then
Nissa ravencraft shall be my lawyer but
of course ah
yes the crime but iand her relatable
what I think you will have to contact
her the thing is this is like Shing cat
or something because she can my lawyer
she's alive right and if she's alive
that means I haven't killed her so then
then there's no need for a a court thing
symbol I think we will just have to see
tomorrow and then then I will make my
decision on how I feel of then keep an
eye if you see her running around that
would mean I have not killed her and
then she you know thank you so much for
joining in the tournament I appreciate
it this will be resolved and I will
deeply
consider in keep in mind she is known to
be a please follow me thank you all so
much for joining in the tournament you
are Mighty Fighters chicken which she
cannot b a glorious glorious tournament
my hat your evidence into head into my
head I will keep it in mind I would like
to see both sides I do see your side
that she could not have possibly given
birth to an egg also but what she my
side that I am orange and then I am team
Gander she is not she is not team Gand
of the queen that I serve that is she
serves different Queen we are not
holding hands she is just speaking to me
very
closely she is not we are not holding
hands would you trust someone who served
the wrong Queen wait before you leave
wait Miss ninoa before you leave I would
like like to have a conversation with
you and Tanashi karia
Shakira what is it I shall go to the
gardens goodbye thank you so much for
for this entertaining event thank you
for joining it is nice to make use of
the Arena good job was brilliant thank
you all very strong
Warriors for the king for the uh for the
queen for the
king h
yes those were some good
fights ah Jade sword
member why my night in shining Arbor
yes uh I will see you on
tomorrow the farewell I bit thee
farewell too well done in the tournament
thank you so much for joining thank for
hosting such a tournament it was quite
successful it was good to make use of
our our Guild's Arena
H yes all righty farewell
goodbye have a good
sleep there are some mighty
Fighters and as I keep saying she is a
mighty Phoenix she showed her worth on
the
Battlefield I am
proud if only that Queen was there to
witness
[Music]
it you know what instead of
the Arena
I shall sleep alongside my jade comrades
tonight
H I am very proud of
them for
Honor for the Jade sword
[Music]