[Music]
It's okay, it's
okay, it's
wonderful, the
nightmare and the strongest
[Music]
We're all together
[Music] [
Music] [Music] [Music
]
[Music] [Music]
Back Back
Itadakimasu Good morning everyone Good morning
Mr. Sakamoto I was
recording all day yesterday, but I seriously
missed that breaking point so much that I wrote it down as soon as I got home.I
really don't remember anything from before I went to sleep.
Maybe I don't remember.
Maybe I went to bed right after I won.
Maybe I was really confused, but I
don't remember anything.
Good morning.
You all woke up early. It's amazing that you woke up at this hour.  That's amazing.
Everyone has time to go to school or work.
Maybe some
people stay up all night.
Good morning. Good morning. Today,
Chloe Sakamoto thought to herself when she woke up.  I
thought it was 5 o'clock now, but it's almost 5 o'clock.I wonder
if there are other people who are awake at this hour with different tastes.I
wonder if there's a dog.Perhaps, I'd like to meet this person at this time.I'd
like to know.
Excuse me,
but why are you awake at this time?That
's the normal time to wake up.If you say it in the general world, but if
we say it, it's usually until midnight.
There are a lot of people who are streaming, and I
think there are a lot of people who are working at night and working until morning, so I
thought that the country would be asleep by now, but
if it was 5 o'clock, I thought everyone might be awake.
On the other hand, I
thought that even if there were people who stayed up all night, they probably wouldn't be there until 7 o'clock.Even
so, I'm a little curious.If
there are people who woke up at this time, why are they
awake?What are their plans for today?  Tokasa  I was
curious about a lot of things, so I thought I'd just
wait for Chloe's convex, and then I wondered
how long it's been since I've been waiting for Chloe's convex.And seriously, how
long ago was the last time I did it?It's
been quite a while.Maybe it's not that.  In
that case, it's not my birthday, it's about a year ago, almost a year ago, about 11 months ago. That's right, May 18th is my birthday. Yes, yes, yes, yes, that's the time. But it's convex, it's not waiting, it's reverse convex, so wait for that.  I do
n't think they did that. That was Gyaku-Convex. Sakamoto was waiting for that convex. I do
n't think so. I don't remember, but neither of them did it. I don't
know. It's
extremely rare, but that's it. It's extremely
rare.  I've
never heard
of anyone saying that I should suddenly do something about my feelings on a
morning like this.
If there are any followers who are awake at that time and have some
free time, I'm waiting for someone to show up.I'm wondering if someone will come.However, I have no
appointments at all.This time, I seriously
haven't seen any updates.  I didn't really contact anyone,
and I just
wrote something like, ``Chloe Sakamoto will be here in a moment,'' or something like, ``Please come if you'd like,'' and let's get to know each other.
Because there is only  The
probability is pretty low, and it was
around 5:30 when I sent it.An hour and a half had passed since I sent it, and she said, ``Are you
awake?''It
would
be amazing if you were there, even if you were alone.''
[Music]
Maybe there are
0 people waiting for the convex. If that's the case, it'll
just be a chat slot, and it
feels like it's over
. But it's mostly early in the morning. Sakamoto's prediction: If it
were the other way around, I'd enjoy it, but in the morning.
If you wake up early, you're bound to have something scheduled. I
think there's definitely going to be a meeting in the afternoon, or a meeting after this, or a no-recording session, or something like that. No, I do
n't know, I don't know, I'm super biased, but
that's just...  Well, I guess it's
a bit difficult because of the preparations, and I'm
sure some people are awake, so I'm like, ``If
there's nothing else, I'd rather stay asleep.'' Well,
Sakamoto, that's exactly what I want to ask you.  That's
one of the things I thought about, but
Sakahata
is a complete night owl. Otherwise, she
wouldn't be able to stream at night, so she's a long sleeper. It
depends on the day, but she usually ends her stream in the
middle of the night.  It'll probably end at 2 o'clock, 1
o'clock, 2 o'clock, or
4 o'clock at the latest.It's
over, right? Then,
from there, you'll start replying to that work.  I was
doing all sorts of things like submitting things that I had to return and signing autographs, and
before I knew it, it was already morning. I was there
checking everything for three hours or so, so I was
standing up, so I started writing and then it
was already morning, so it's about
average.  On days
when I go to bed early, I go to bed really early.On
days when I go to bed early, I go to bed at 4 o'clock.On days when I go to bed
from 4 o'clock to 5 o'clock, on
days when I go to bed late, I'm already done.  So I go to
bed around 10 o'clock.On days when I feel like I
really have to do something,
or I just can't sleep, or I
have some insomnia, I
usually go to bed around 10 o'clock.  It
depends
on the day when I go to sleep and wake up.If I have something planned before the broadcast, it might be
early in the day, or it might be from noon, or it
might be today, or it might be yesterday.
Yesterday
was a bit of an exception, except for the one that started in the morning.That's quite an
exception, but if you
look into it, it feels like you'll probably wake up in the evening.So
seriously, I slept like that every day.
I
sleep when I can,
and I haven't eaten, and that's exactly why I
want to sleep to that limit again.
Sleep is more important than anything else, that's why.
Before I head somewhere, for example,
before I go to a recording session, I take dance lessons, before I buy
anything, etc. I have a lot of things to do, like work, etc. There's a
99% chance that I haven't eaten anything by the time I head to work.Sometimes, I
don't know, I might eat something like rain.  If you
eat candy or have a sore throat,
that's the only
thing you can do.  So I
go home and eat, or I go home and sleep. I
don't ask for food before I stream.
If it's a day when I don't stream, I prioritize sleeping,
and then I eat after I sleep. I
seriously don't eat at all. I'm a
wild, skinny guy, but come on.
Sakamoto: I saw you before. It's
strange. It seems like one meal a day makes you fat the most. It seems like the
less you eat, the more you eat
.
Sakamoto: Hey, you eat a lot.
Normally, I can't eat too much at once,
but my digestion is ridiculously fast,
so I'm the type of person who gets a little hungry and
then eats a little bit and ends up feeling full.That
's why I think that's the case.  You'd be surprised to hear that it's the best,
but Sakamoto has always
been about eating one to two meals a day.
But to put it bluntly,
I think there are a lot of people who
eat 45 different colors.Maybe
when I went out to cook, I would be a normal person, maybe a little
less.Mr.
Sakamoto, it was a long time ago,
lol.  When I decided to eat some
food, I brought some sweet bread with me, so I
opened the bag of sweet bread, tore it into pieces, and ate it.  I
ate about 1/4 of it and felt like food,
and when I started to close it up, people asked me why I was eating so carefully.No, no, no, no, I
was always worried that I shouldn't be taking such good care of myself.
After I ate, I put it away and
felt like I was still feeling a bit groggy, but
then we ate together and they
asked me why I was eating so carefully, but I didn't want them to
tell me I was on a diet.  It's
different
because it's easy to open up when you're full.I
can't eat a lot of the same thing,
so I want to eat a little something.How to
eat small fish.I'm a
killer whale, but yes, small fish
are like that.Along
with small fish.  Please don't do this, I'm a killer whale.
But
Chloe Sakamoto from Office Machine is a killer whale who will be holding an aquarium event from now on. Do
you all know that? We're doing our
best to hold an event to commemorate the 1 millionth visit.
There will be an original dolphin performance, an MC, and a lot of other decorations, so it
will be held on the ground.There are only 2 days left.The first day will be held in 2 days,
so I'm really excited about the MC.Yes.  I'm
sure everyone knows a little bit about the beginning of Rolison, but this time there
's also a dolphin performance.It
was made in really amazing quality, and it's
completely original, so it's black again.  We're
going to do a dolphin performance using some original songs and some cover songs just for this occasion, as well as songs from Holo Live.The
choreography is Iruka
's choreography, and it includes all the jumps and things like that.
It's so original! What
surprised me was that it was held at Aqua Park Shinagawa, and it looked
like a messed up live venue. I
don't know why, but it was amazing.  The
acoustics were good and the lighting was good, which
surprised me. It looked like it was a solo concert. It's
still on sale and sold out. There are
more dates, but
if you'd like, I'd be interested.  If it's there, please come and see it. It's the only time
you can see it, and I
want you to call me and
tell me that I went when Chloe Sakahata celebrated her 1 millionth birthday. Thank you very much. I'm going to shake it up a little.
Good morning
[Music] I
'm Kihara-senpai.
[Applause]
Actually, I was watching from the beginning, but I was listening to what you were saying. I was
waiting for a while. I'm sorry. I'm good at small
talk, so it feels awkward to come in right now. I was
talking a lot about advertising, etc. I was just chatting by myself.  It
was like a frame. I'm so
happy. Is it this time?
What about Sakamoto?
Yesterday, I was recording all day, so I fainted and woke up
early in the morning. Thank you for your hard work.
Um, it's Reiji now, it's okay. Is the time
okay? It's
not Japan, so the time is different,
right?
So, it's not like this is really happening.
No, no, I'm
really happy. There were 0 people right now.
Hey, that's right. I'm
really happy.  He's still coming, isn't he?
Hey, I'm glad you want him to come. Can I ask you a question
?
What's the first thing you do when you wake up?
[Music]
Phone  I'm
heading back, but
one of them
eats not only the normal food that I should buy, but also the lukewarm stuff, and as
soon as he noticed that I was awake that morning, he
was so insistent that he started meowing.  It's so
cute, so if I
don't prepare it right away, I'm really into it.
That's why the cat is
so energetic. I've been heating it up since morning. She's
been eating crepes for breakfast
every day. She
loves it so much.  I
love it so much. I found something freshly made
at the supermarket. It's not
freshly made or it's not already made. It's a bit of a pain to make breakfast in the morning. Isn't it stinky
? I don't want to make it.
[Music]
This is delicious, so I eat it every day. Hey
crepes.  Are you a dessert fan?
Can you tell me a little bit about it? It's
definitely a dessert.
Sakamoto is also an overwhelming dessert fan. It
's Harajuku, right? What you're talking about is
[Music]
Cream-filled custard cream.  It's
fruit-based,
but it's
true that it looks a little different, but things like character maids and caramel whipped strawberries. Sakamoto eats so slowly that it looks like a fountain, and I think it's stuffed with ice cream that you can't buy. It gets sticky. You'll definitely need a bath.  I think that kind of problem will come up.Well, there are
various fruits, berries, and Venice,
but ice cream, if it
comes with that vanilla ice cream, I'll be happy,
no, it's delicious.In the end, I can eat both.
Well,
Japanese crepes are
like the ones you often see in Harajuku, but
there's no way to make them that way in Europe, so it's
different.European
crepes are pretty simple.Yeah, I
like both of them, but Japanese ones
come with a lot of different things,
so they're
amazing.  It's amazing. You can taste so many different flavors.
Oh, that's right. I
didn't know they were completely different. I
thought they were the same. Oh yeah. Do you
know what they are? They're pretty good.  I
saw
Chloe's pajamas quite a while ago and it got me super excited.What's this?Actually, I was horrified when I saw Chloe's pajamas.It
's like that, isn't it?The light blue
bunny's.I was surprised to see that they were the same.It
's Japanese.  I bought it when I was living in New York,
and I've been using it ever since.
[Music] It
's a complete coincidence, but I
thought, Wait a minute, we're
going to a pajama party.
Okay, when I come to Japan,
I always wear a short version, a long
version, a
long version, a long version, and a
version with no sleeves.  Let's
have a pajama party together. I'm so
happy. It's a
complete coincidence that we match. It's amazing.
But how long have you had them? Eh,
how
long have you had them? I've had them since before Hololive, not even before.
Because when I bought it, it was before Hololive,
but it was pretty cheap and cute, so I bought it.But it's cheap,
isn't it?
So,
Sakamoto:
Seriously, Sakamoto, I've never bought clothes that expensive.If you
ask me why, I always
did it when I was moving.  It's
like buying clothes when you move.
When you move, you
throw them away and buy new ones, but it's
not like you're throwing everything away. It's like you're
basically decluttering, keeping only your favorite things.
When I add more stuff, my
room
gets dirty and cluttered. I
tend to move around a lot, so I keep it
small. But while I have that tendency, I don't really want to move too many things.  I
had a lot of them, so I thought it was a bit of
a waste, and I
didn't want to buy them because they were so expensive, but
when I got more favorites, I was wondering what to do with them, so I
decided to make them a little cheaper, and
now they're just cheap, cute clothes.
When it
comes to Japanese particles and Japanese girls' pajamas,
there's a certain brand in Japan.I
get it.Gelato
Picking.Oh yeah, that's
right, but isn't it a bit expensive
?
Sometimes they sell it really cheap on places like Amazon. I
bought it and have it here.
Jera Pique has it, I have it, it's fluffy. Hey, it was
only distributed once. I stopped showing it, and
somehow the fans were identified.  I bought it, and
it's fine even though I'm scared of it. I
don't know what I'm using it for. It
might be coming to me right now. If so, then it's
ok. I
might be giving it away.  It's going to
move again. It's going to
move again. It's going to move,
it's going to move, and I'm definitely going to identify it.
[Laughs]
Red Stalker, that bad guy.
So, can I ask you one last question? Do you
prefer an aquarium or a zoo?
That's a difficult question.As I've
been to many different countries, I've
noticed that the
love for animals seems to be the same no matter where you go.  Most of the
things inside are like that,
but the design inside the building is quite
different, and it's quite structured, and it's
frozen.I think it's
interesting, but if I had to choose, I feel
bad for the creatures in the aquarium.  The
fish have quite a bit of space and
seem to be living happily together, so I guess
that's okay.
But ah, the aquarium is more interesting.
Right now, it
's said that the aquarium will open two days after Haihai-chan.  It would
be great if it was an aquarium for an event.
So I put Chiara-senpai's recommendation in the
aquarium.
Thank you very much. It's
on sale. I'll go. I'll go.
No, but I'll go. Hey, see.
Kihara-senpai is also coming.  I told you not to come.
Thank you
very much. That's great. I've always wanted to do this.
very much. I was really happy. If we do it the other way around and
wait, I wonder if you'll come again. Oh, if you have
time, by all means, if you
have time.
Thank you for your hard work. Bye-bye.
Wow, it's really
rare for something to happen. It's
amazing that you know how to advertise when you're waiting for someone to do it. That's amazing. You're really good at
Japanese even though you're from overseas.  I
was surprised, thank you so much.
Masu Cure Senpai,
please make sure to pack your pajamas.
Thank you very much. Tsukamoto is a woman who does what she's told to do. She's a woman who does it when she gets there. Thank you. Thank you.
Seriously, that's amazing. I can understand the advertisement so clearly. That's what I thought. If Sakamoto had said it in English, I would have been shocked. It's like saying something like, ``That could be an aquarium or zoo.'' That's amazing. Thank you very much. I
was caught.  There's
one more thing I have in common with Nademo Kihara-senpai, and I've
been told that Sakamoto might join the Follow Birds,
since he's a bird head, so
what if?  I really
hope we can get along.
Thank you very much. That's amazing. But I
see, it's still late at night for foreigners. Wow, where are you going?
What are you doing? Please calm down. When I got
back, something
terrible happened again.  I'm home
right now,
Mr. Sakamoto.The
reason why I'm not using my usual gaming chair today is because I want to sit around an octopus with someone else and
have a meeting by myself, so I chose this round table, but it's
a little different than usual.  I want to
surround you,
thank you,
thank you.The
other day, there was a book
about showing off all the benefits of membership to the public.I
mean, membership
really does offer some great stuff.That
membership.  If you haven't entered Nena,
please enjoy it if you like. Thank you
. I actually posted a summary
for the community to see the overall effect. I was
wondering what Nena was doing as a human. She's been doing
quite a lot of things and is probably starting to do so now.  Even if you enter  I don't know
how long ago it was, but if it's wallpaper from about 2 months ago, I
can collect it, so please
take care of it. Thank you. No, it's not true. Well,
I'm really
happy to use it. It's a bit strange,
but it might be a little
surprising.  I don't, but I'm kind of shy. I'm scared
to talk to that person,
but I feel sorry for them because they take up so much of my time, so I
have a hard time talking to them, and I can't invite them to collaborate with me at all.
Lately,
you've been inviting me to collaborate with you in such a serious way, shaking my heart. So
every time I write, I write and
erase, and it becomes super long, and I write and divide it into sections. I
don't need long texts like this.  I deleted everything once and said "Hey,"
and in the end I was invited to do a collaboration,
but I've always wanted to get over that, so I've been
thinking about collaborating with Sakamoto for a while.  I do
n't know if it's because I say some cheeky things or not, but seriously, I was really
nervous one more time, like in Kamakura the other day,
and I was really nervous, so I was so
nervous that I had to single-task.  I do
n't know what to say anymore, my hair is so long that I don't know
what to say anymore, but that's about it. He's
incredibly kind, and
when I talk to him, he responds right away.
Even though I'm such a normal person, I get really nervous and I'm surprised. I feel like I can
somehow overcome this problem by taking advantage of this opportunity.It
took me more than a year to take action, but it's
taken me over the past year.  I
want you to take a look around me.
So, if I were to say that there are people I could easily invite right now, I wouldn't invite my classmates,
but I wouldn't invite my classmates either. My classmates are my syncmates, so I
have some idea of their schedules, etc.
None makes me
think you're busy. You
look like you're busy. Just look at it normally.
If there's this here and this and this and that, then I'd probably want to stream it on this
day. If there's nothing, I'll probably take some time off.  I
can't invite her because I'm thinking about things like that, but I guess it's
easier to invite her at a time when we've been together for a while, like the other day,
Nenan, Gartic Phone, etc.
After that, we all went together for a while.  I
want to do a lot of things at that timing, like the scene where we're talking on the phone.We talked a little about
doing something like this, but we
can't talk unless it's at a timing like that.It's like "
Friday," Sakamoto says, "It's
really Friday."
Even if you tell me not to worry and it's okay, I
think I'll get upset, but I
totally understand how you feel, and I
wonder if it's okay.It's amazing.  I
know you're giving me too much perspective, but I'm wondering
if you're forcing yourself to open it or
something like that.It
would be nice if it was someone you had a really close relationship with,
but it would be fine if you were from the same generation.  But if
it was anything else, they might try to make it happen,
but there
are so many things that would be impossible.
But I want to do it. After all, I have to have the courage to do it.  I
think about all sorts of fun possibilities, but I
try not to think about them. That's why I
suddenly
end up waiting for a convection on a morning like this.
People who do it at this hour just because of this are idiots.  I do
n't have any appointments on time, so it's
extreme, isn't it
? I want something in the middle. Anything is extreme, really. If I
decide to do something like this, it'll get really expensive,
so I want something like
this.  You do
n't have to shake it off, you say it's
too much, but we
avoided 0, so that's true.
Thanks to Kihara-senpai, there are no longer 0 people.
Thank you. We can't do an aquarium. I'm
going to stick a needle over there.  I tried to tell everyone that I would probably never end up at this table,
but
they're all just friends.
I heard that you all have friends, so I wanted to know how you make friends, so how do you make friends? No, you guys didn't say anything, I just asked how you make friends.  I'm
already too jealous of people who can say that.
That's definitely not my friend. You're
not my friend.
Because you say things like this, you say things like this. Do
n't you get misunderstood? I'm serious, Sakamoto.
Even when I talk to many of my seniors, I get told that I
thought I was the type of person who could talk at all,
and that I don't look like that even when I actually talk to them.I'm
really, really
nervous.No matter who I'm talking to, I'm
nervous.  I wonder if he's trying to pretend
like he's not doing it and is being
extremely nervous.I'm not shy, but I don't have any communication problems,
so I can talk to him, but I wonder what's wrong with him.  It's difficult to
interact with people who have high hurdles
.
Some people have friends, right? Friends
come naturally rather than thinking about something, right
? It's difficult.
Make it into a sport, what should we do?
Create a Hololive yoga club. Let's all
run together.
Yes, I'll throw up.
Should I make something for yoga? I don't think I'll be able to do it yet if it's yoga or something like that. If I
invite you to do some really intense exercise,
everyone will be streaming but I don't
want to do that. So I'll just
do that moderate thing.  I'm
so happy.
Who is going to do yoga in 3D and what is the demand for it? Watch It's
only the sphinx pose, so the
lying cat pose is really important. It seems like it's
possible. It's likely. Survival game.
Survival game. I want to see Hololive, which is a survival game. But it's
a little
scary. Hit
judgment.
Button-senpai is clearly the stronger one.
But there are a lot of things going on
with Sakamoto.The
problem is that when I ask someone out and they
say it's totally fine, when I
really want to invite them and I think about what to do with them, I just can't think of anything to do with them,
so I
end up not being able to invite them.  Well, that's exactly what I
wanted.At that time, I went
to Mikochi Sakamoto and said, ``
Wouldn't it be okay if I asked you out?''Even
though I was
okay with nicotine, I was like, ``Oh no.''
What should I do? I
was thinking, ``I wonder if I can come up with something interesting?'' and then Kobe-senpai came
up to me and said
let's do a collaboration.
So it's true, maybe. I'm overthinking it. I'm
not serious. I'm not serious at all.
But I don't know if I'm going to think about it. I'm sure I'm going to think about it. But now I have no choice but to
invite you, so I'll invite you.  That
's right,
Mr.
Sakamoto. What I was thinking before was that I wanted to
take out a close-up and have an extremely long experience playing with that deathly holocaust without making an appointment.  I
thought I'd like to make a schedule for that time and have them fight instead of changing, but only have them fight in one type, but that's just the
way Momotaro is.  I
thought, ``Isn't this amazing thing to do when the time schedule is so different?'' I thought, ``I wonder if it's going to be dangerous if I use a lot more,'' and then I thought, ``It's a relay,'' and then I
thought it would be a little difficult.But it
seemed interesting.  Right, that
sounds interesting. That's why Karuta-senpai is
so easy to invite. He's been using LINE a lot lately, and that's today.
Maybe he didn't say that, but it's today.  I
heard that I'm going to do a collaboration stream with Harada-senpai at night, and I'm thinking of doing Minecraft on the stream as well, and I'm thinking of going to an underwater temple, so there's a lot of things going on. It's Karata-senpai, and he's like, ``Let's do this, let's do that.''  I have a plan in place, so please
take care of it.Well, according to the plan, it will probably
be an early night, around 7pm,
but it might be a little off.  I do
n't know, but that's what I think of it.Yes, I
want to go with my girlfriend.Sakamoto:
I want that, Minecraft, that
minecra.It's the
first time I've heard of Minecraft, and I
want a sponge.That thing that drains all the water is convenient.That's why I
want
it.  I'm thinking about it, so I'm going to
do Mine Clara today, so please help me.I
also want to do that.Recently, when I
went to sleep, I finally received an additional Holo
Live wafer.  I
ordered the Hololive wafers with a strong desire to pull myself out of them if I grabbed them, so I could
open about 6
boxes of them.I had made some changes to those roses, so I was
hoping I could open up a lot.  That's why I
want to stream the unboxings.That's why I'm thinking about
Weiss Schwarz, so I'm
wondering if I want to buy more for myself.I'm
opening it now.  I think it's
okay to have another revenge after broadcasting it,
but I'm wondering if it's a good
idea to summarize it all, so I guess I'm just
worried.I
can't digest it all, Sakamoto, that happened.  I
freeze it in a Ziploc bag and
eat it every day.The
size of the wafer is just
right.I eat it in a small size.  I can
understand, there's no gravity to it. I
feel like I want to eat something. I eat it,
chew on it until I'm full, and then put it back in the ziplock bag.
So I'm looking forward to it. I wonder if the news about Rokuhaku is going to be bad, so I'll just put it in a box and
check it out.  Check it out. I think it probably fits in the fridge.
Mr. Sakamoto, you idiot. He
originally had a huge refrigerator. It was
huge because he lived with his grandmother and sister.
But since I brought it as is, I
think it'll probably fit in there.The
freezer is full of refrigerators.On the other hand, there's nothing in the freezer,
so I think it'll fit at all.There's
bonito in there.Isono is in there.  I don't even have bonito at all.I wonder if it's about that one.Yes,
bonito is a bonito.I
like to pound it and eat it, so I keep it.Why
would I be surprised by a bonito like that?I don't have bonito at home.  I
don't normally put it in a fish house.I
put it there with the image of putting saury, mackerel, etc.It can
handle fish, but it's not true.I can handle it, but I
wonder if I have a knife that can handle the size of bonito.
Even the one with the open parts
may be a bit big, but it's definitely a version of the bonito's body that has
been cut to the correct size.  That's
what I buy when I eat.That's how I
eat.When I
eat, I
can't resist the urge, so I feel like if I
don't eat what I want, I'll
feel full.  On the contrary, I have a habit of
stocking up on things I like so that I can eat them
right then and there because I get full quickly or don't feel like eating.  It
used to have broccoli and
mussels and things like that,
but lately I've
been eating all of those things, and I've been so
busy that I've had a lot of luck making them.
It's a mess, but it's actually full of stuff.I've been
busy lately with the stock I kept for cooking for myself, so I didn't
have to go buy it, and it was just
fine.The wafers are coming soon.  It
's instant, but I get it.
Mr. Sakamoto just
wants to shout out his title as Cup Noodles' strongest champion. Everyone, it's Cup
Noodles. So, it's Nessie's Cup Noodles.
What do you like most
? Kamata has already been ranked number one, and he's definitely number one.
This is it.
By the way, I still have it at home.
Absolutely No. 1.
Ah, I know. Curry and seafood are
delicious. Normal and delicious. Chili tomatoes are
also delicious.
Oh, what's salt? The
one from the stand.
Tom yum kung, sorry for the wait. I'm sorry for the tom yum kung. I
heard it once and it has cilantro in it.
That means there's cilantro in it.
Sorry. I'm scared,
so I haven't eaten it. Is there any cilantro in it? No, there's
no cilantro in
it.  No. Are
you
eating the same thing? Something with
coriander for a limited time or something with coriander in it.
Yes, it's in, it's in,
yes. So let's exclude tom yum goong zee for now.
Exclude it. The
number one supporter
is [laughter] Chili tomato.
This is definitely the best. Seriously, this is my favorite, but I've
always been a seafood fan, so I'm going to eat seafood.  I
like seafood the most, but you know,
from the moment I ate chili tomatoes for the first time, I've
loved chili tomatoes. They're really
delicious.
But,
Sakamoto hates tomatoes.  It's
strange, isn't it?
[Music] I
can't even eat chili tomatoes. I can
eat them at all, and I think they're delicious. But I don't
like tomatoes. I
especially don't
like hot tomatoes. I wonder
why. I'm starting to wonder why, even though I'm
talking. I wonder why they use
ketchup.  I can't eat ketchup,
because ketchup isn't tomato. That's
jam-like jam. That's
different. It's
delicious.Jam
[Music]
Tomato sauce, though.
Sakamoto: Well, I think there's something
different about ketchup and tomato sauce, and I do
n't really like tomato sauce. It
depends on the thing, but for example,
tomato sauce with a tomato juice flavor.  It's a bit of a
different story, isn't it? I can
eat Neapolitan, but Napolitan doesn't have
onions. I
can eat Neapolitan, but I don't need it.  I
like minestrone, whether it has pulp or not. I
don't know, maybe I don't like the natural taste of tomatoes,
but I
like the tomato flavor. I
think I like the meat sauce that I was just talking about,
but I don't know where to draw the line.  Maybe there is. I do
n't know, but I
don't know the standard
. It's a mystery. It's
really strange,
but I think it's delicious. I think it
's a cheat. I
think there are many people who have eaten that, but what is it?
Name, oh, my name doesn't come up.
Somehow, it's pretending to be an
affair. The yuzu salt ramen is
delicious. The yuzu salt ramen is really delicious. It
was a small Mr. Squatchcchi.
But it's really like that. He was sitting
next to the water server.  It
's about the size of a cup, but it's about the
size of a cup.It's delicious,
isn't it?It
's very African.
Afuri's Neyuzu salt ramen is super delicious.I
recommend it.If you like yuzu, you'll definitely
want to try it.It's
like a cup next to mackerel.You
can line up about 5 of them.It's
delicious.It's super
delicious.I recommend the color.I
also recommend the seaweed ramen.  It's delicious, right? I
know they served
wakame ramen with fresh wakame soup. I know they served wakame ramen without noodles. I was
curious about that for a long time, and I was looking for it,
but I couldn't find it.  I'm
looking for it, isn't it? It's
delicious. Noodle-
free noodles
are already too new. I
thought Sakamoto wouldn't understand something like Watanuki. Well then, wakame
soup is fine. No, no
. Everyone wants to drink wakame soup for wakame ramen.  I want to
drink the flavor that was in the stupid ramen.It's
a little different from the regular wakame soup.It's thin.
Miso-ha is a standard miso soup for breakfast,
but there is always one in the story that is the best.There
are many kinds of miso, such as white, black, mixed, red, etc.Ah,
but surprisingly there are people like Sakamoto.
Or, you know, red, I'm a fan of red soup.I
think it's surprising, but
red is what red is, uh, Kanto.  I
have the impression that
red miso is delicious.
Seriously, white miso is also delicious, but what I want to
drink most is something strong. I think you can drink whatever you
like, so Sakamoto believes that as long as there is a
flavor, there is one.  It's so good, that's
why I like it.It's
verygood,
but the white soup stock is amazing.For example, the
white soup stock that has a flavor of clam stock is
also delicious.  It's
delicious, but I really like the red one. Hey,
that's what I was talking about earlier about the chili tomato. I like the cheatwort one
because it's a cat's tongue, so I add a little less hot water to cool it down. I
also like the noodles to be firmer, so I
drink it cheaply, but that's it.  I
put ice in it, but I end
up sprinkling salt on it
because I think it tastes bland,
so I sprinkle some salt on it.Well, I don't drink soup, so I'm
reluctant because I think it'll be forgiven.  It's
delicious, the more expensive
it is, the tastier it is, so of course it's
delicious as it is, but it's always better to follow the forecast than it is, but it's always
better to take a step forward.After all, the more harmful it is to your health, the tastier it is.Ah,
Tabasco is so bitter.  I
can't really eat it, but I guess it's
delicious if you add a little bit of it.Yes, it's a
bit salty, but Mr. Sakamoto, this is killer whale, so killer whales are just like salt water.
Isn't it like
drinking salt water? It's okay, it's okay. Physically, I'm drinking that salt water, so I'm fine.
Probably right. It
's delicious.
Also, I guess
that's what I do.  The
cheat tomato comes with cheese, but the cheese
tastes a little bland.Since it's a dairy
product, they started by adding salt.
When I eat something like beef tongue, the lemon dies, and it's really
untidy.I
didn't realize this until someone told me about it, but then my family told me about it, and I realized, ``Are you
eating that lemon in Sakamoto? Or
are you eating beef tongue?''  I don't know, even I
really want to drink lemon.I
want to drink it, but I've drank lemon itself,
but it's Pokka Lemon.It gives me
a lot of stomach pain, so it's
like there's some kind of ingredient that can help relieve it.
That's
why fried chicken is also an accompaniment to lemon.Also, lemon and salmon.Salmon is also eaten with lemon, so it's a
challenge to see how much lemon can soak into the salmon.I
love lemon so much.  That's right, I
love it.
Whether it's salmon or eyeshadow, I've
already decided that salmon is lemon, but my
definition is...
There are people who don't accept that.What do you put on salmon?
I understand if it's foil-grilled, or just regular salt-grilled
salmon, but I like to put lemon on everything.It's
meuniere-like, yeah, yeah, that's right.Some
people don't put soy sauce or anything on it.That's
amazing.  You know, you're eating natural food, you
're taking it in its natural form, but I think
Sakamoto
says that in the end, the best way to eat food is to not cook it much.That's
really something like yakiniku.
Things like sushi and things that I eat naturally, things like shabu-shabu, etc., are the
most delicious. Of course, processed food is delicious, but I feel like that's the
best. In the end,
being the best is like a reward.  What do you mean
when you say eat something?
Yakiniku or sushi? I
guess that's what it's all about.
Sakamoto,
it's hard to say that it's not cooked at all.
Especially when it comes to vegetables, I
feel like the less something is, the tastier it is.In
meat and fish, yes.In
meat and fish,
vegetables are no longer included in fish-eating
foods.They don't exist anymore.
When I looked at it, I looked at it objectively, and now I
can't stop
shaking. I can't stop shaking, but I wonder
when was the last time Tsukamoto ate vegetables.
[Music]
Seriously, when will it be? Seriously,
when will it
be? Hmm, I seriously don't eat it. Broccoli I really like broccoli, but I don't have it in stock lately.  No, it's
just broccoli.
Maybe I'm ingesting broccoli. I
waited and ate it. Sorry everyone, Star. I
made some pickles at McDonald's the other day. I was
eating them.
Oh, good, I'm
taking it. I was so
nervous that I thought I hadn't eaten anything, but
yeah, I ate McDonald's pickles and fries about 2 or 3 days ago. It's
healthy. I thought I'd have a week or so. That's
good
.
But it
's a vegetable, no, no
, everyone, it's a
vegetable, it's frustrating, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, it's vegetables.
As for potatoes, I've cleared the previous one. I just
gave it to you.  It's
not processed at all, so I just sprinkled it with salt. It
's natural.
Pickles too.
Just pickled in vinegar. Look,
natural. There's a lot of
salt in there too. If I
remove the salt, I do
n't think it would be able to survive.
But I'd like something with a lighter flavor.
They say it's bad for your health if you don't have something to eat, but I
want to live a long life, and I'm
aiming for immortality.
I'm sorry, everyone, I'll go first. I'll reach that state of
immortality. I'll eat whatever I want,
live the way I want, and become immortal. If we can
all reach that world line, we'll move
forward together.  I'm going to
continue my activities as a vtuber, so
please support me.No
, I really don't want to know, but it's
definitely going to make me happy, so please support me.I don't care
if I kick that person down, I'll do this.
In the moment, I will block you no matter what you do to the plate.
Thank you very much. I'm
not half-obsessed, so if something happens,
that's the moment.
If I get caught.  I
wonder if that was the moment when I realized that the elixir of immortality had arrived.Thank you very much.If there was a
wise man among us,I wish I could receive the Philosopher's Stone,
so please take care of me.  That
's right. He's an
intelligent person who's lived for many years. He's already been
involved in that clinical trial.
Why are you doing it, please? Thank
you. It's been about an hour already,
but I'm glad
Kiyohara-senpai came.  I'm really
glad I avoided 0 people.
Thank you very much. Now let
's move on to the super challenge.
Thank you everyone for taking the time. Thank you
everyone for getting up so early.
Once again, we are holding an aquarium event right now,
but there are quite a few dates that are sold out,
so please check it out.It
's in the pinned comments and summary section, but there's
also the black original dolphin
performance and the nesting
projection inside the museum.  There's mapping,
but it's completely original to Sakamoto mythology, there
's footage of upside-down creatures swimming, there's announcements in the museum,
panels explaining creatures, and stamps.  There's going to
be a lot of stuff like rallies and stuff like that, so I hope you'll have a good time.And
if you all buy tickets, you'll definitely get this poncho that comes with every ticket.It's a
really
durable poncho.It's amazing.  Seriously, how amazing
is this poncho that's so strong that even if you try to break it, it won't break?
Oh, there's a senpai, now there's a senpai, ah, [ __ ]
ishere.
So, thank you very much. I
think it will not break and can be used repeatedly.
And
for the premium ticket, you
get a glass coaster, which
also has a really nice design. They
have already announced a glass
coaster.  Do you have a picture of it? I wonder if it is
? The quality is really good, too. This is also
something you can't get unless you have a premium ticket, so please
take a look. Please take a look at the overview section.
Good morning Good morning
[Music]
Thank you Good morning
[Laughter]
Because it's quiet Aquarium
versionAqua
French
YesIwikipe Sea animals
OkGoogle
[Laughter] I'm
too happy
Aquarium Aquarium
Oh, I love it
[Laughter]
One-two
says please  Thank you very much for visiting the aquarium that my seniors also want to come to.
Thank you
IwanttotalkuseOK
Study and study
Thank you Bye-
bye  I
'm so happy that even an anonymous senior came. Thank you very much. Hey ramen.
Anonymous senior's
icon is also pronounced. I'm happy.
Foreign students are always awake at this time.
Thank you. Two people
came. Thank you, Hololive.
Thanks to ene.  Good,
thank you. You
saved me, Mumei-senpai also wants to come. I
'm confident that I'll entertain you all. I'm confident that I'll have a lot of fun.
That's why there
's a different MC every time. Sakamoto is real.  I'm
going to do it on time, so I'm
sure everyone would like to be played around with it, so
please take care of it. I'm so
happy that I'm not really a tankaran.
At first, I
completely ignored it.
Thank you for the hardships. I'd like to guide you, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
DoYours Sakamoto
Kuro-chan
said he liked me.
I also like Sakamoto, who seems to like aquariums. I
also like killer whales. This is as expected of my senior.  I
thought there was going to be an event,
but it seems like they're coming.It seems like they want to go, so I'm looking forward to seeing
you.Thank you
very much.Yes, it's quite a lot, but I'm
sure there's a holoforward coming.  I wonder
if Sakamoto doesn't know that it's a killer whale and thinks it's a fish. Killer whales seem to be
smart, so I
don't think that or myself is smart, but...  Feed the cat
to the bird, guide it, and
eat the bird.
Thank
you very much. The quality was really high. I thought they were going to put on such an amazing live performance. The dolphins were having so much fun, too. Please come.  The title of the movie is Sakamoto and the
Aquarium, and it's
going to get so messy that you can't even laugh at it.
Please know this before coming. It's
going to get really messy.  You'll
get soaked, so your smartphone
might get damaged if you take it out. It's really sea water, so I
just want you to be careful.
If something breaks, I won't be held responsible for it, so I
don't think I'll be able to take any responsibility for it.
Thank you.Seating
order I'm sure there isn't a set seating order.I guess
it's somewhere in Shinjuku, I do
n't know.I feel like it was something like that.Just
in case, I heard something like a game or something.  It seems like you
can wave it too. Yes, anything you
want. Please bring a siren if you'd like. I'm
sure I'm checking various regulations right now,
but
the siren is OK, and it's
probably OK to make noises. I'll
probably check that again.
Yes, but there's a chance that the psyllium will break too. I
want everyone to be careful.
[Music] The
penlight looks like it's going to break, so there's a chance that the psyllium will break.  I don't know
what to do with the crystal, but I think the regulations say you can bring something that glows, or you
can bring a glow stick, so
either is fine, but I don't think it will break.I
feel like it could break either way.Yes,
thank you very much.  Please, I'm
serious about reproducing it in a Ziploc bag. It's surreal to be waved through a psyllium ziplock.
By the way, this is a punch, but it's true.  I
want everyone to wear it, so I give them points,
and
this is pretty much the motif of Sakamoto's regular costume,
but I want to see them lined up in this seat, and it's
even
a little
scary. I'm looking forward to it.  I
think that's why everyone is
welcome. There are also disposable reproductions,
but please take your own trash with you. I don't want it to
be thrown away on the spot.  I'm
sorry, but I
hope you enjoy your time with good manners, so please help
me.As long as you protect me, I'll be fine.I wanted to
erase the secret, but that's true.Speaking
of secret societies, it
's all about getting over the Rocks world.  I think so,
but it looks like it's a solo version.
Please look forward to the singing part.
Thank you very much. It seems like I'll do it.
Please.
There are quite a few rare versions.  I
think there will be a song that everyone doesn't expect after it plays.I think there will be a song that Eko sings in Hololive.Thank
you for your support.This can only be a great success.This is
okay, okay, I'm sure.It was okay.  It's a big
success, but I feel like a regular penda
or psyllium would be better,
but there's no special separation between them,
so it's a bit too bright and bothers the people around me.  I
think it's going to get messy, so I just want people watching to pay attention to that part. I'm going to leave it to you,
please. Socks. I'll
do it. The surroundings are predictable,
so it's a little different. This time, it's
not a trash can. Thank you.
No, but I'm really looking forward to it.There
will be panels placed inside the museum
after being arrested.I also wrote messages and signs on the panels inside the museum.  The
panel is so cute,
Sakawatari's handwriting is amazing,
and the noise made me wonder what to do,
but I wrote it properly, so I
hope you take a lot of it.I
think you'll really enjoy the photos, and it's really true.  It's
okay not to get too
worked up about those panels, I thought, wow, I'm so happy that I can get this.
Thank you very much. Yes, by all means.
Hijiki Migochi Migocchi Are you listening?
Migochi, I
said it, right? I thought there were hijiki scattered all over the place. Hahahaha, I'm getting
hijiki, but what I thought was that
when I looked at it upside down, it really was hijiki.  -
Sakamoto was seriously surprised by Hijiki,
but I had a lot of opportunities to draw it in the next month.  If you
look at it from above, of course it's your own handwriting,
but when you give it to someone, it looks like this.If you
change the angle, the angle is hijiki.If it
was someone else's handwriting,
you'd probably have changed it, but you thought it was hijiki.  It
turned out to be true.It
was indeed an elite beach for the elites.It was
known that they put a lot of effort into it, but I was surprised.
Even though it's an aquarium event,
Sakamoto's voice is played a little bit, and
Sakamoto's music is played in some places, so I
thought it would be like the dolphin was doing a prank, but it turned out to be a scene from
that aqua park scene.
There was a place in the middle where water came out from a fountain,
but they were so particular about that. I
thought it was amazing, and then I
said, ``I want to do this if I get arrested,'' and they thought about it.  At
first I
thought it would be difficult to get drenched,
except for having Iruka do it for me, but
even though I may or may not have had it, it
ended up being more difficult than I expected.
Yes, there
may be calls from people other than Iruka-san,
but
thank you very much.
[Music] It's nice to meet you,
so
let's get soaked together.
Thank you very much. I
waited for about an hour, but two people came. So
, seriously, thank you enj. Thank you very much,
Ume-senpai and senpai. I'll
do it again unexpectedly.  There may be some, but
at that time, please everyone try to predict how many people there will be.I
thought the fun of doing it was a little nice, so I'll do this regularly, but it's
another normal waiting game.  I think I would like to
Okay, thank you very much.
Now let's move on to Super Chat Reading.
Thank you
Aquarium
and
Aquarium Events in progress For
details, see the
summary section. For
details, see
comments.
From the pinned comments. It
was fun. I woke up so early. I think I'll be able to talk to everyone.  I
thought everyone was sleeping more, so
even if I was awake, I
thought it would be difficult because I have work, school, and other things to do.
But maybe there are some students on spring break or something like
that, or maybe the entrance ceremony
isn't today.I'm
surprised it's too white.I think I
should go back to sleep or go back to sleep.I
feel sleepy.  Okay, I understand,
and be careful when distributing it. I wonder if I'll listen to it on my way to school or work.
Entrance Ceremony - Do your best! An event that doesn't happen often in life. Entrance
Ceremony - Good luck!
Now,
I would like to read it.
Thank you very much
Mummy Mummy will
start in the morning Mummy or Mummy Kosame-san
Shion-san went bankrupt Toromi-chan Suu-san
Thank you Bubble-san Babub-san Red
Thank you Spa-men I'm
happy to hear Sakamoto's voice in the morning Thank you and Happy
Birthday
Thank you  No, seriously, Sakamoto is already super
rare, and the morning breeze is really rare. Chatting and
waiting is also quite rare,
but when I go to the morning activity, it's like it's already been a year. No, seriously.  I
'm Sakamoto Kuro, who is extremely rare in many ways, but in
the past year or so, I
haven't been waiting for him at all. I haven't been active in the mornings at all. I've been
chatting a lot less. In the early days, I was doing a lot of it,
but lately...  After all, I'm busy
and don't go out anymore, so there's nothing to talk about, so I
just stopped talking about it.
This is pretty rare, super rare, super rare.
Thank you very much for
watching this at such a time.  I
was really happy, thank you.But
recently, I realized
that I really don't have anything to talk about anymore, and
that I need to take some time off.So I
went somewhere and had this kind of experience.Also,
Sakamoto.  I'm really curious
to know what a cat is,
so I went to  to check it out.I
wish I could report on my experience.
Thank you very much. It was really
fun. Today's broadcast
was really exciting. I
was wondering if someone was coming or not. It was
nice to be able to talk to everyone like this for the first time in a while.  I'm
going to sleep
every now and then. No matter how early it is,
if the broadcast starts at 7pm, Sakamoto will get sleepy at all. I
definitely have to go to sleep by noon.
After I was arrested, I went to bed and worked on the work, so I'm going to
sleep again.I have no intention of doing it at all.Thank
you for watching the theater company's broadcast.I'm glad that I was
able to hear everyone's voices in the morning.Now that I
think about it, there are people who do morning activities.  I
think you have a lot of stamina, after all Sakamoto. I
often think that I need stamina. I want a good body even if I don't sleep.
Thank you,
Rain
Kiru-san Cat Can Slayer-san Horen-san Bean Sprout-
san Time Dragon-san Sekki-san
Meru-chan Karikari
Kunrokuto-san
Ponykin Mochipan-san Amochipan
Investigator-san Aromaru-san De Punkamuri-san
Laurenta-san Arisco-san Aki-kunya Bame-
chan  dot com mask stay 3
village turtles 3 turtles 3 islands cats and 3 Chumsuke-
san Thank you Tara Tara-san Day
Thank you  The day before
yesterday I realized that I had taken a quick bath again,
but even I thought I was crazy because I hadn't taken a bath in 26 days. That's a good night's sleep. That's
too much. Are you
okay? You
're sick. You're
in the hospital.
Thank you for the laser. That's outrageous. Isn't there a molester
in the bath?  That's why I'm 26.
Thank you for not telling a lie,
but I can't take a bath for some reason. It
seems like I have a tendency towards depression.
At first, I really stopped taking baths,
and I was a bit mentally
uneasy about it, and it seems like I can't take a bath when it gets too expensive, so I thought maybe I wasn't taking a bath, and I thought it would be really hard to live here,
so I went to the hospital for a while.  I think it's a good idea to go.
Sakamoto: That's what's really going on lately. It
was there yesterday, and I
wonder if it's going to be there today, too. Pollen is annoying.
Also, I've been doing a lot of dancing and
recording lately, so I'm
sweating a lot.I can sleep like this,
but when I wake up, I wonder if my liver will be wet.It's
hard to sweat to begin with, right?When I'm sleeping,
But when I'm sleeping, it's hard to sweat, but
when I go out, I sweat a lot just by walking around,
so I'm
naturally sweaty so I'm thinking of taking a bath there.
Well, I was surprised when I used it.I
looked like I was fine,
but I got soaked.It wasn't my body.The
worst part was, I
thought I might miss the train, so I took a quick dash.I was
really, really soaked.  I'm
sure it was winter at that time of year, too. I
was drenched, and they made fun of me.
When I got there, they told me it was okay,
so I ran. I ran for a while, and then this happened. I
was a little worried about things like that.  I'm
going to go in because I'm in trouble, but
thank you Razer. Do
n't say anything stupid, but if it's true, I
guess I'll be happier if I just go to the hospital, so
let's go to the hospital. Maybe it's because I
don't like taking baths.  I feel like it's more than just not going in
. It was really 26 days,
so I recommend it. Thank you.
3 Koyuki-san, Ain-hwa, Furikake-san,
Ayakani-san, Shiro Akiyama-san, Mon-chan.  Is
it Mr. Hosuirei? Mr. Water Lilies. The legs are also based on Mr. Lily.
Mr. Gen Maou. Mr. Ainfa. Mr. Udonya Donko. Mr.
Blank. Mr. Makopi. Mr. Takahashi.
One day 380 Mr. Evu. Mr. Yusuke. Mr. Hina. Thank you pksk. Good morning. I got excited when I heard your voice before work the other day.  I graduated from Cherry. I
graduated from Sakamoto. One year has passed quickly.
From now on, I will do my best as Kyo Suika.  I
'm going to go to work. I
love Sakamoto.
Thank you.
Have you been arrested or graduated?
Sakamoto's conditions from becoming a cherry
to graduating are those 6 months and 1 year. So, the
timing of 6 months.  So, I graduated from Cherry
one year after I became Cherry,
so I
wouldn't be able to graduate if I didn't have someone who has continued to be a member, so thank
you very much.Thank you NHK.Thank you.It's my
graduation Ame-chan.Thank
you very much.
Thank you very much, Mr. Modbarion, SSS3, Kuzu-chan, who added the mysterious friend y3,
Mr. Mikoto, Mr. Shirona, Mr. Dejio, the president of the company,
and Hot Keiwa New Sun Hotel.
Thank you, Harunyan, and Kasupo Mentaiko. Good morning, Mr.
Tsukamoto. I
haven't seen you lately, so I'll hear your voice in the morning.  I'm so happy.
Yesterday I had to work in the fall, so I
passed the station where I usually get off and went to the last stop.
Wow, that's amazing. It's quite a long journey from the flatlands
to the mountains, then back to the city. It was interesting because it was a city test train.
Today is my day off from work,
Mr. Kamata. I plan to watch it over and over again. Oh, I was
surprised. I wasn't oversleeping.  It's
just that I went there, I was surprised. I'm so
grateful for spring. It's amazing, but it's okay. It's
kind of nice to travel by train.
Getting off at a station I don't know is kind of nice.
Sometimes I don't enjoy it, but I
sometimes do it again, and it's
amazing.It's so much
fun when I go to a station that I don't know anything about.People who are just
having a normal life are like that.But I
like watching people, and I see
people having a normal life.  Actually, when it comes to human resources, it's
definitely different from my own world.Just because I
'm in a different area, I guess the way of life is
different, and each person has their own
family environment and what they're aiming for.  I was
thinking, ``I wonder if all kinds of things are different, and maybe someone is on the move at this time, or someone is on vacation,'' and I thought, ``It's kind of interesting.'' I
thought, ``I saw something amazing.''  I
think it's good to get off at different stations because it's fun.
Yes, Arashi has a sense of adventure. I
think it's fun, but when I feel a little
tired, I try getting off at a different station.
Even just going for a walk from a distance
can make all the difference.It seems like
walking is really good for your mental health.Exercising is
good for your body and mental health,
so just taking a short walk is the usual
way to work.  It seems that just trying to look at a slightly different path is
a little
different, so thank you very much.
Or rather, it's a day off, or rather, it's a nice day. I'm
off work today, so I took a lot of rest.
Thank you, Mr. Sunflower, Mr. Richard, Mr. Human, Mr. Hair, Mr. Kinosaki, Mr. IM, Mr. Ayumu, Mr. Caspon, and thank you for the mentaiko. I'm
so happy, Sakamoto.  Yes, let me go on April 8th. The
first day of the
event is the aquarium event on the 8th. I'm so happy. Bye bye, it
was cute. Sakamoto's stream from there. I
'm happy to see it. Please name it if you like.
If you could do that for me, I'd be worried.Then, Puff-san, Puff-san, Puff-san looked like that.It was
love and M, so I decided to say ``Im''.
Well, I thought, ``I'm the perfect human.''I
thought, ``I've been a perfect human for a long time,'' so
as Buff-san and Parfait-san.  This is Yara-chan.
Please take care of me. Thank you. Thank you for
showing up this morning and also on April 8th.
When I heard that the first day was sold out, I thought it was serious.
That really is an incredible amount
of capacity. This is not the kind of capacity that you would be able to meet alone and do it alone.
Honestly, it's quite big, so I
thought it would be really filling up.
To my surprise, it has sold out for quite some time, so
I'm really happy about it.It really feels
like everyone has bought it, and it's been very well received.It's been highly rated, so it's still on sale, so
please take care of it.
Thank you so much, Parfait. I'm
looking forward to that. Thank you. If
I ever decide to go there,
Sakamoto, I'll make a tag again, so I'll use the tag to wear what I'll wear when I go there. I'll
also bring something like this.  I
thought it would be nice if you could tweet a few things like that.
Please, thank you. Thank
you, maniacs these days.
Thank you, big brother. I do
n't like spam nail polish.
Good morning to me, good morning to my albino yesterday. Good job, I hit my head,
but it's okay.I'm the
kind of person who reverses day and night and stays up until the morning, paying attention to my daily life and living in reverse.  I
stayed up until noon.Here's a
commercial.If you're listening to it right now,
now's the time to go to the Bishonari Aquarium with Sakamoto.It's
sure to be fun.For more details, go to the home page.  I
was so happy to hear Sakamoto's energetic voice on the page this morning. I love you today too. Well then, I said good night,
so I went for a manicure.
Thank you, my head. I was asked if I was okay. I was
really annoyed.
Sakamoto: Unbelievably, everything was
buggy and I had to go to the bathroom, so I
had to go to the bathroom in between recordings, and I
really had to hurry.  I
really have to take a break, and I ca
n't really take a long break, so I'm
going to go really fast. I'm going to do a real sprint. I
don't know why, but I
always give it to Scout with my right hand, because I'm right-handed.  I
opened the door with my left hand and put my head on it.Even
though I
had left, I felt sleepy so I thought it was okay, so I just
peed and went out.
My head was completely fine, but somehow my head
was fine, but my
hairstyle was all messed up.There are a lot of
things going on.It's
hard to tell if you ask me, but there are a lot of things that I
appreciate about hair.  When it's long, it's
tied up a little bit, but it falls apart a little bit, and the
staff members are like, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, I'm sorry.
Can I have you fix this for a second?
But it's a mess. I
woke up the moment I got caught, and
then just before that, I was really bye-bye. I felt like I was going to pass out. I
thought today was going to be really bad, but
thanks to you hitting me.  I woke up a little and the
condition was good.I
guess when I put it on, the screw stuck in the place where it should fit,
so I'm glad I
was able to drive it.I
thought I'd keep doing it.The rice balls are in February.
Thank you very much for your support at the Caught and Bishonari Aquarium.It's our first exclusive
event, so I hope you enjoy it, and I
think it's going to be a great commemorative event.It's so
great that the only people around us are Follow
squirrels.It's also
great.  Right, it's
reserved for you, so please enjoy it.
Thank you.
3 autographs x 3 rice-chan, moon grass, 3
sparkling counters, this fun-loving Nami-san, a
visiting person, and a Kamakko-san.
Mr. Hidekazu,
Mr. Sunsun Luna,
thank you for the pulchika. Please
look forward to it. Good luck at the entrance ceremony.
Traveling is a treasure. Thank you
Geski Ball for the
first spa of your life. I was just throwing it without saying a word.
Thank you. I'm
sorry for the first comment. Sorry for the inconvenience. Thank you.
Thank you very much. It's good for Sakamoto for the first time in my life.
Thank you for such an unexpected grave.
Thank you. From now on, I'll be Yo-chan. I've done my best. I'll be watching a lot of your streams. Thank you for getting to know me.
Dracula Sprint Thank you
Wooden Hoi
Thank you very much It's
difficult in real time when you're busy
Well, you're already busy, so don't overdo it and
prioritize yourself After
all, the
best thing to do is not to get tired.  It's
the end, so seriously, you should push it as a break after all,
so please enjoy it.Thank
you, there is an official push for Shiro Orca.Maybe I
don't really understand it, but it's just me.  I
may not have realized that, but
thank you very much.Thank you very much.Thank you very much.I'm really grateful for the
users, who have gotten along well with me, and who have told me things like, ``
Let's go there next time,'
' and who have been on LINE with me almost every day.  I
feel like I'm kind of embarrassed, but I'm really enjoying talking to you.I
recently said something like, ``I recommend this
movie,'' and I said, ``I recommend this movie,'' and I was
like, ``Well, I'm going to watch it.'' It
was really good.  That's what I was told
Good, we
can have this kind of conversation, of course it's
good. My senior didn't seem to
be having fun, so I'm glad, I'm
glad. I'm so happy. It's not a dream. It's a dream. It's
okay. I'm on my way to that point.
Maybe I
should go to the hospital.
Thank you very much. Don't say anything scary. It's
definitely a home like that. Thank you very much. Thank you, Kuronya-chan, Nanno-san, for
buying the collaboration goods. I see.  It would be amazing
if you could buy goods on the spot, because there would
be long lines and it would be a hassle,
so now you can
buy things in advance and pick them up like a holocart, so you can
use those tickets.
Therefore, the
pick-up time seems to vary depending on whether the regular ticket is a premium ticket or not,
so I think it would be the smoothest if you could buy it a little in advance and
pick it up at that time.
Thank you very much. Yes, by all means, I'm
Yuru-chan.
Thank you for feeling like this.
Thank you.
This is already destiny.
Why are you so scary? Name-
chan Hate Earl-san Moriya Suwako-
san
Sidewinder-san Lortia-san
Kick Boss-san Honwan Seamason Koro-nyan Shirasagi-san
Kontaro-san Tani
Tiramisu Cat-san  Solfa-san,
Libe-tan, Sorofa-san, Solfa-san, I've
been able to become a member from this month.
Thank you for your support, members.
Thank you, this is Yura-chan.
Thank you very much. I'm happy.
Renge-san 6 and 3SSS-san Kamiya Suzune-san
Moyashi-san It's
scary.
Something like Moyashi-san is a bit of a specialty of ours. I'm also a listener.
Seriously, I'm there at any time. I'm definitely real.  I'm
not scared, but I'm scared of being a Type 2 or something.I
said something the other day, I'm
like, there's a lot of people out there.The truth is,
How many people are there and how many people are cooperating with each other? I
don't know if it's a lie or the truth.
This scary person said scary things. It
's not love, it's amazing. No, even if I love you that much, it's
hard to do. Thank you,
Shio Kapi-san,
Pukupuku Fuku-chan.
Advance travelers, Shin from Tachikawa,
Garuru, Hungry Aiken,
Haccha, Randy, Yunyun,
Takenori, Tomorrow's Yaotome.
Mr. Ono is Electronic Shinobu-
chan, thank you very much,
thank you, Fallen Angel Shinobu-chan, thank you, Asakatsu, it was nice. Thank you for coming to see me.
Thank you, Randy, too, for seeing me for the first time.
And everyone said they were going to the aquarium that day.  I'm so
happy.
Thank you for coming so many times. I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you. I just
got off the cruise. I fell in love at first sight. Do you believe me?
So please marry me.  I'll
send the marriage registration in an Amagift. I'm really looking
forward to getting soaked in the aquarium. Isn't that the old Niko student? I feel like I'm getting excited and hitting the water.
Cruise is like that too, isn't it?
What is it?
What is Fruce? There's no
way it exists. It's the one that goes to random people.
Thank you.
Thank you. Send me the coin in Tokyo.
Can you give it to me? Thank you very much.
But if I get angry, it will be a heavy burden for me. I
want the book and this card, so it would
be nice if you could send them to me. Thank you.
But I wo
n't give you the ice. Thank you.
Thank you for the Shizuoka miso coating.  Well, thank you for looking forward to it. Is
there such a thing as subscribing to a channel? I'm smiling, but I don't understand it anymore. It's such an ancient culture. What's the point of subscribing to a channel
?
Yes, no, no, no
, I just took it off and left the iron handle on. Please take it easy. That's why I guess they want to leave the
iron handle on. Please
register in the community or community.
Thank you very much. I'm sorry that I do
n't understand.
Thank you.  If you
make a voice while you're already making it, you'll start to feel
sick to your throat.It's something I've never used before, but it's a bit too
advanced.It's
Kuro-chan, after all.It's a
strange but interesting culture, is
n't it?
Niconico Live, etc. I
knew more about NicoNico Douga than NicoNyan Nico Live,
but it's an interesting
culture. I never
thought YouTube would have such an atmosphere.
Live streaming.  There was clearly something going on.The
first one was just a music video or
something.Thank
you very much.I
was looking forward to seeing you at the aquarium.Well
then, thank you for the Cospa Mentaiko.
Thank you for the first morning in a while.I couldn't watch it because I was at work, so I
'll check the archives later.Yesterday, I
booked all the flights and stops to attend the aquarium next week.Thank
you, I'm just leaving the rest for Iku.I'm really looking forward to my first solo trip to
Japan,
but I'm also
really nervous.  So,
thank you Sony. I'm
sure you'll have a lot of fun. For the first time in my life, when I
come across something that I don't understand, that's
pretty much it. If you translate it on Google and
listen to it, you'll hear someone from Japan.
I don't know if there will be many people who will answer if I call, so I won't do that. Thank you, Sore-chan, I'm looking forward to it.
But you're already
going overseas, but you came all the way. I'm so
happy, thank you for Sakamoto.
Thank you. I'm
so happy. No,
Sakamoto too.  If I were to travel abroad alone, I'd
definitely get nervous.I'd be fine if I were in Japan,
but I have no idea what that would be like.If I
were in America, a vast country, I wouldn't be able to do it
.  I
don't know, I don't know, the system is different, and
there's a tip, so I don't know,
I don't know, so that's how I
feel. I'm sure you'll enjoy it,
but your Japanese is really good, so it
should be fine.What's going on,
Chihina-san?  Bame-chan Eve,
Mr. Chapun-san, thank you for the pin, Hina, I
found the pin list, thank you for the red spam mail, thank you,
Hina-pi, if you don't put it on your head, I'm also
kind of worried.  It's
not swollen, but it hurts when I press on it,
but I'm hitting it with too much force and it
's gone for a while, but I wonder
if it hurts.It's a little bit of pain, but it's just a little bit of pain.It's
okay, thank you.I'm going to sleep properly.
Thank you for making me feel important. Please
sleep a lot.
Thank you. Good night. Thank you. I hope you become smarter. I really feel like I
know Japanese.  Come
and learn the Japanese wabi-sabi, seriously! It was
dangerous. I almost
got angry. The
condition of the cat's head
told me that I hope the injury will get better. That's what
surprised me. This made me
angry.
Thank you very much for this guy.
1 million languages 3
sites, public relations boy HARU,
you,
Sakura Mel, who is hospitalized for Sakura Birsa.
Super cat weather forecast for the first time.
I'm an exchange student in Japan. I'm studying Japanese right now. I
watch Masukura-chan's every broadcast. Not
only can I practice my listening skills, but I
can also learn more interesting things. It's
really helpful. Thank you very much. I'm
glad you're watching it again.  It's real time.
Thank you for watching it in real time.
Sakamoto is serious. He's
not very funny. He speaks
very fast,
so it
might be difficult to understand, but he's practicing his listening skills.
Thank you.
Recruiting Japan. I wonder if it's
fun. I'm enjoying it.
There are lots of fun places and delicious food in Japan, so I
hope you enjoy it a lot and make some good memories. Thank you, thank you.
Thank you,
thank you. The
Sakamoto Good Morning Aquarium event starts the day after tomorrow. To
commemorate this, I was surprised by the first supercha, which
is a real zookeeper, and this event.
More Prairie at Work I'll be there on my first day
too, so maybe that's not it.
Hey,
if my job was longer, I might have met Sakamoto.
Thank you, and thank you for the first super chat.
Thank you very much for the first time. It's more
interesting at work. It's even more interesting at the workplace.
Also, at the Hololive event, at Sakamoto's
event, I
went to my former workplace as a guest. It's interesting and
interesting. It's
quite emotional. I
want to see your tweets.
Thank you.  Thank you so much, that's so funny.
Thank you so much for raising someone who tends to sleep. It's
T3 Macchan 03233
Mai-san Uta No. 1, the northernmost 3 km pinobaka. Edge
pervert, thank you Debirin Sayaka.
Thank you very much for April 9th.
[Music]
Thank you. I'm going to the aquarium on April 15th. Today's
Minecraft broadcast in Kamakura is also
compliant. Minecraft is fine. I'm looking forward to the Minecraft broadcast as
well. I'm going to work.
Thank you Remi Ria. Thank you.  I'm so
happy, don't start
using Minecraft right away. Minecraft has been messed with
, but
all I have to say is this. Everything will be
picked up.
Rascal will still be released, which is helpful.  I've
only been there once and it's
been rubbed quite a bit, so it's already worn out. Thank you very much.
Good luck with your work. Please look forward to today's Golden Black Undersea Temple.
Thank you,
thank you. Thank you, Rino-san.  ANA All Nippon Airways map is really
amazing, but don't push yourself too hard because you feel like
you're
feeling sleepy or you're done with work, but you can
watch it in several parts.  It was
really amazing.
Personally, I thought I wouldn't be able to see it all if I watched it one more time. If I
said it once, I'd want to go twice. It was a really
amazing dolphin performance.
All the prototypes were great, and the inside of the aquarium was also great.
Sakamoto  Since it's a myth, I think it's easy for people to want to go again.I
hope you enjoy it a lot.Thank
you.I'm Yoro-chan, and I look forward to seeing you.Tickets are still on sale.  It's
almost sold out on Saturday,
so it feels like it's Sunday.The rest are pretty much sold out.All
in all,
quite a few are booked up, so it
feels like there's only a little time left.Thank you in advance.
Thank you very much,
Sakamoto. I really had fun today. I'm glad I woke up early. I
want to do the convex waiting again, so let's gather up the
courage.
Thank you again. I'm wondering if I should go to the second floor.
Come on.  I wonder
if they're aiming to sell out everything again.
Thank you for your support.
Please come twice. But I really
think you'll want to see this twice without this one. The
Dolphin performance was of such
high quality that Sakamoto...  I'm
sure people will want to hear the solo version of the song,
and the
bonus is so good that even if I get two of those punches, I'm sure they'll want to hear it.
That's great, I really want to be able to wear that to a concert or something,
but I'm
wondering where it was sold.In the future, it looks like it was
only sold at an aquarium.It
has a rare feel to it.Thank you very much.
Thank you, Tomo. Good morning from the venue. I've been
doing a great job and I'm waiting for Sakamoto's convex broadcast. I'm
sorry I missed it, Orca-chan. I'm
going to the aquarium event on the first and last day. I'm looking forward to the
aquarium event, of course.
Please pre-order the goods. I
'm also excitedly waiting for Tsukamoto's name. I have work so I couldn't watch it until the end. I'm
sorry, thank you, Ruka-chan. It's okay. Good luck with
your work. Meanwhile, I'm
grateful that you're making the monsters come true.  You know, as I
said before on the first day, I'm
really looking forward to it.The goods are
cute and cheap.That
's what I'm surprised about, but it's Papa Jelly's
quality goods.  I
think the price of something like this from Key Vision is quite cheap.I think it's
because Chugai Kogyo is
doing something really well, so it's really cheap, so
definitely take this opportunity to get it.  I
hope you like it.Thank you very much for your help.It's an
online sale.I wonder
how it went this time.If I remember
correctly, since the aquarium event started, there
's been mail order, but it's just that all of them are sold online.  I was
like, ``I don't know if the products will be sold.'' I heard that if you order online, there may be times when the items are not available.I don't know if I can get everything.  Since it's production, I
don't think there's an inventory problem, but I
hope you'll just be careful about that. Yes, I think some of them are
missing.
Thank you.
Thank you for your hard
work. I have a work schedule, so I'm going to clear my schedule and be quiet.  to  I'm thinking
about whether to go to work or not.Which one is better?In the end, I don't know
which one is better.I think both Shizuoka and work are important,
and I think it's important if you're an otaku.But which one is better?
That's fine.
If you think work should be your priority right now, then of course you
should prioritize work, and if you
want to go to an aquarium because it's only open now.  I
think it's okay to come now, it's not too much of a stretch, but I
think it's okay, so I think I should just follow my feelings a little bit.
Yeah, I guess, thank you.
Well, I cleaned it up with a Shirokanedhirudan sponge.
Thank you, Shuntaro Roast.
Santa Claus or your name.  If you don't remember this
, it won't be displayed because it's extremely long.
Thank you for the trouble at Red Spa. Yes,
Sakamoto-
kun.
Thank you. I might not be able to come to the event. It's
really okay.
If I get caught, my other goal is to work hard enough to hold another event like this while I'm involved in this activity.Although I
was able to make my dream come true this time
, I still don't have many dreams.
It's okay,
thank you, laundry. Thank you Mr. Lois. I really want to come too. I'm
happiest that you thought so.
Mr. Relax, Mr. Reese,
Mr. Shoulder, Mr. Roy.
Thank you,
everyone. No, seriously, there are so many of you.
People are trying to come, and I can't go because it's far away, but I'm rooting for them.I'm going to watch the stream.I'm so happy for you, everyone.Thank
you so much for coming so early in the morning.The
most important thing is for everyone to have fun up
to the hill.  That's important, so don't
forget, okay? That's the
most important thing. It's really
important that you don't get tired while pushing, so
please take care of yourself. Thank you very much. It's pretty
amazing that it's been decided.
Thank you so much for that.
So I'll be broadcasting Sakamoto again tonight,
so it's a Minecraft
collaboration, Minecraft collaboration, and it's
fun. Please wait. Thank you,
Mr. Diaper. I just bought the ticket.
Thank you very much. I'm looking forward to it. Thank you. Good luck,
seriously.  Thank you
very much, and I look forward to collaborating with Minecraft.
Thank you for writing, dying, and conquering. Thank you
for the feast, thank you for the feast.
Thank you, wait a minute.  I
didn't miss it, Hypo-san, it's my first supercha.
Thank you. I want you to do a national tour. If you can do it, I'd like to do it. I'm thinking about how difficult it is, but if I can do it, I'll do it someday. If it looks like I can do it, I'd like to do it. Thank
you. Thank you for the
height. I wanted to go to the prototype.  I'm
busy. It
's okay. Thank you very much
. Don't push yourself too hard.
Thank you for enjoying Ornina. Thank you
for the meal.
Thank you for starting, Saitama. See you soon. I'm going
to sleep.
[Music]