[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
a
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
a
[Applause]
[Music]
n n
[Applause]
a
[Music]
k
k oh oh okay okay
[Music]
hello chy
Wy you want to sit on all of my accent
stuff yeah yeah yeah yeah it's your box
and your straps sure she's so cute she
was like making herself really
comfortable in the accents box it's it's
quite a nice box that the straps come in
today uh today huh me reading comment
while
talking uh hello hello
hello uh
[Music]
oh uh today we're starting a little bit
later but I actually went into the game
already uh a little bit ear earlier
today I was just having my breakfast and
I didn't plan to participate in this at
all but uh maybe you saw that Picola
Senai built this big fighting
ring uh where people who previously died
would fight against each other and the
alive people would bet who would win and
I didn't lose any money I used the
diamonds that I got from my missions
originally I thought I couldn't
participate because I didn't have any
diamonds but then I realized ah
wait I I should be getting some from the
mission so I checked and I got 15
diamonds from oh why did I stop
moving I got 15 diamonds there we go
from just uh doing the missions
yesterday it's 15 plus another five
actually for ah and wait there should be
another one um because because because
okay okay okay okay wait so I ended up
betting but I didn't lose any money just
don't worry I I think I gained five
diamonds I should have gained I bet 555
because there were free
fights and I got
back I I mean I didn't get it yet it
should be my box let's
see let's see if the math adds
up and I didn't stream that because I
didn't plan on participating I wanted to
start later today so wait we'll look at
the missions in a moment it seems like
they didn't change much though
except for you get like a [\h__\h] ton of
diamonds if you there we go that makes
sense if
you uh yeah 100 diamonds if you find a
wizard head and I am if I'm up to date
now they only found two so far even
though they've been out there for hours
so
maybe ah this hasn't been separated
yet okay so while I was off
stream only there only found two maybe
the maybe our ID kiata group can find is
anybody in the Wither in the never still
looking for the Wither
heads we can maybe go with with the ID
Girls and find the third one I don't
know I want to get some of those
diamonds too they're still looking
sheesh damn is it so hard it's tough
without looking
free you mean fortune free does Fortune
free work too oh that that's for mining
probably right not all H I feel like we
with my Phoenix luck I could do it
easily but uh if they've been looking
for hours they could find it any any
second now but okay one thing um they
did end up giving a reward for both The
Fortress and the Bastion the one for the
Fortress I already separated of coyote
there's two people who didn't take it
yet though but I took my reward that was
another five diamonds but then this one
is for the
Bastion and I was like okay I'm just
going to wait
until someone else separates it but I
still separated so I
wonder uh who was who was in the Bas
trip how many let's do the map okay and
see how many we'll get H it was Wawa mik
Senai Ana SE anaan and
Ana subu was also in but died so maybe
we can count without her cuz she's not
getting back into the game so uh wait
that's um me m Ana and then alun right
uh who else was in besides superai in oh
my god of course so we split it for
five
maybe Aqua yeah Aqua zai was also
partially there but was she there I
think she was there when we saw the
Bastion was she on the on the picture we
took she was okay so that's six people
that's better to split uh I think 20
through
six uh
help there's a worst split H well
somebody will get an extra one maybe
free okay so it's
like wait 1 two 3 one two three uh one
two
three one one two three two three ah
okay so let's
[Music]
say wait uh did I forgot someone
or is this just still a leftover I
thought there would be only one
leftover left over
this offerings to
subu okay then I'll take another
free nice
to now people might get confused or
maybe they'll even completely forget
about taking these in the first place
[Music]
yeah I think that will be fine and then
I'll put them just here for
safekeeping uh and it seems like we
might go into the nether again let let's
see the
missions didn't look at them properly
yet oh same same same same so I can do
it again and get a reward again same
and this is some kind of I don't know
what this item is in English an
old
something what could this
be and uh this is the head of the Wier
yeah which gets you 100 diamonds ancient
debris
ooh yeah that makes sense ancient de
breath mama mama that's the stuff right
in that you mine in the never was it in
the never and in the ceiling or or was
it at the bottom it's ceiling right
explosions in the ceiling the show Mama
at the bottom okay not in the ceiling
the ceiling sounds kind of difficult the
bottom usually
I might want to try it because we we got
a lot of time
[Music]
and we just do these again I mean these
are if I'm going to go to the nether
then it's going to be easy to do them
again
[Music]
I would like to go but then we got to be
fast because every second
[Music]
counts w we writing a novel I was
I I watched P's news stream and
everything I think I'm ready whatever
um I watch a stream uh the new I'm not
tired I'm fine I watched the news stream
and oh CH W is actually still there on
my accent stuff cute fluffy um and and I
saw I saw her reading my my d
gold
maybe uh how much maybe wait ah just
just for one
equipment is that what it's
[Music]
for have you enough food oh probably
well look let's let's do our own
preparation maybe eight just for two
pairs of shoes okay did I leave gold in
my mining
area did
I there's some gold nuggets here but did
I have more
there yeah in my cave
right how much is
uh 12
iron uh drops that I have how much is
that one
Ingot
approximately do you guys hear the bgm I
feel like it might be too quiet for you
guys I think my cave was behind this
stuff right little quiet this you in
there I thought
so okay
yeah the fight in the arena was fun too
like watching that I I voted or I I bet
it I bet I bet it I bet for in the fight
from n versus Subaru Senai I vot I beted
for Subaru samai which was going well
but then like they had to have free
fights instead of two and then in the
last one what s I did lose uh where the
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] I can't really recognize where
it
[Music]
is might be too loud if I
run uh and then the other one was pora
versus Kori and they were like I met
coyote and she was like questioning why
she she said I saw you voted for B
s notai p and um she's like why what for
me and I'm like well you know and I
mentioned that a long time ago this is
really
dangerous long time ago
I I had a fight in the ring with POA
and well she seemed really strong back
then I didn't even remember if I won or
not but I just had it in my memory that
that she must be strong because we
fought before I don't know I had no idea
if
um if COI would be strong or
not it's been a long time that was like
3 years ago and then she was like oh
okay well you haven't seen me fight so I
guess that makes sense but then pora did
win easily that was pretty cool and then
in the end there was another fight that
was like a mystery fight uh Aqua Senpai
versus mystery
enemy until the the very end they did
not reveal who it would be and then they
revealed that it was just going to be
like anybody any
volunteer and then OKO Senai who started
today I think she volunteered and uh she
won and I was originally I didn't know
who aquaa would go up against but I had
a feeling you know my intuition told me
that
a they got got it damn it they got the
Wither the last
head damn it so what now I guess we can
still go though because of the other
missions uh where where the [\h__\h] am I
now can't find my mining area was it the
other
direction the head the last
one um what am I saying I
whoever it is they will I don't know I I
don't I I thought Aqua Senpai might be
really
good um but I I thought that that peka
would probably troll really hard by like
bringing out some crazy boss monster or
something like that which was not the
case at all but uh when okou
Senai uh stepped up I was not sure how
it was going to go
but yeah
uh it turned out to
be a success for everybody who bed
against AA Senai and well me was I was
one of them me was one of them yes
yes okay is my mining area here at all
or am I totally
wrong was behind yeah yeah I'm in the
wrong direction I guess this is not the
courthouse direction
[Music]
okay let's go back so that's how I got
some extra
diamonds
I did quite well I didn't have more to
bet so I didn't make a big
win but it was probably better that way
I you guys looking for you ah to I'm
looking for the uh gold I hate water
if they're really looking for me
desperately they can write a message
o what the
[\h__\h]
Courthouse
hi hi hi hi I'll be be I'm looking for
the gold
[Music]
still where are you going I'm still
looking for my gold I I I I made a mind
somewhere and I think I left some gold
there oh no it's okay we we got gold
really okay um hi MAA I think sorry for
the long wait oh no worries it's okay
I'm not really waiting I just started
anyway but uh so they just found the
Wither head which was the biggest
mission for today
but I think Mauna it's your first day
right is it yeah so it's my first day we
can do all the missions in the never for
you and I wonder because I most of these
missions are the same as yesterday I
wonder if I do them again if I still get
the diamonds
probably yes probably yeah yeah and you
also didn't do it right saying that
there's a basan quest oh Bastion is
hard really was it Bastion
oh want to take the missions together
actually yeah uh okay we can go if you
don't need the gold
oh don't worry we have gold both of you
weren't there yesterday
so we can do all those missions and
hopefully I'll also get a reward again
second time yi yay was it here no
here uh yeah oh oh oh this ah one guess
okay that's that's pretty easy that's
pretty easy wait how do we get how how
do we Soul Sand yeah Soul Sand easy like
I got all of these like yesterday the
only new ones is this getting the Wither
head uh but this is over now because it
was only for the first free people who
found it and the other new mission is
this one that's not translated it says
we have to get uh what's it called again
uh you know in the never that really
rare material to
build I think it's for never debris yeah
ancient debris so if we can find free
ancient debris together uh then will all
all of us I think will get each 20
diamonds
20 20 why is it so cheap debris yeah
ancient debris is pretty difficult cuz
we need bombs
probably yeah but wait we just need one
ancient debris well for each of us yeah
if if we want 20 diamonds per person
then we need one ancient debris per
person
oh I see maybe we can do it without uh
do you think Kyla is going to join
us she said she'll be here at
uh yeah yeah so like four more hours
she'll be on four more hours oh you you
mean she will be another former hours
online or what yep okay do you think she
wants to go with
us she would love to okay then we get
four ancient debris
yeah but the good thing is joining um
she can give us maybe can give us some
some
bombs yeah we don't we don't need the
bombs yeah but need right beds oh yeah
beds ah right wait what okay I think cuz
I did this like a long time ago and beds
in the never for me just translated to
bombs cuz they BL
up okay okay let's do that together and
all the other smaller things we can do
everything except for the Wither
head mhm mhm looks good sounds good all
right let me screenshot this real quick
I'm going to go get some food farm
yet but there's no wool Farm but yeah
but there's sheep from paa right make B
to make bed easier yeah we have we have
sheeps from PKA Senpai we just have to
share
them yeah don't do it and we need cut
wood mhm if you die in hardore yeah uh
we won't
die we will not die I mean it's it's
mine you haven't died right yeah not yet
haven't died first revive is free is
what I heard right wink wink not free
for survive you have to go to the solo
server and get seven diamonds ah okay
and then second revive does not happen
normally oh oh I see well I mean we can
do this we got this we can we can say
like maybe Kyla you know Kyla is very
very calm in the nether so we just let
her explode
everything and we take everything from
her she must have she has so much
experience I think with uh finding
ancient debris so we just leave it to
her and we'll stay in the safe backside
that's a good idea okay I'm going to go
get some food and when we're all ready
to go maybe we meet in front of the
portal yeah sure okay all right then all
we need is maybe some beds though I I'll
check out POA Farm yeah I'll go to B
sinai's Farm as well
okay let's
[Music]
go torches behind her no I don't think
we need to dig like that much anymore I
think but
yeah okay Let's uh first I'm checking
for food did I have more
food uh no let's pick it up on POA
Senai pora is indeed a senpai to
me it's just uh Hol is not a
senpai oh my
brain my brain cannot sustain this pain
when there is no
gain who is this
[Music]
maybe some
torches and I don't think nowadays that
people need these beds
so I'm going to share I took like like
20 beds already you guys can take the
rest
maybe okay okay
okay I take the beds oh now wait it
would be so good if we had a Ender
Chest how do you make end chest
[Music]
again never never just
plant all right you need
the do any of you guys have
axes what kind of
Axe I I want to cut down some trees oh
here thank you oh I'll just take the oh
oh oh I'll just the iron one thank you
[Music]
okay yeah I guess one of us will we're
both some of us will carry the
beds what what what is she getting and
now I am back in my environment what are
you getting the wood
for to make more beds oh okay I have 1 2
3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 I
have 177 that's in my
inventory hopefully hopefully that' be
enough yeah what do you guys think will
it be
enough oh yeah I think MAA took the
other beds out out of the box so we have
a few more than 17 like maybe
oie and get rid of oh what should I get
rid of I'll get rid of
this and here's another one I'll get rid
of um um um um um um look get rid of
that I'll clean out my inventory really
quick takes a stack of TNT to find a
round usually takes a stack of TNT to
find a round four a
stack do do TNTs and beds explode the
same way
oh yeah
[Music]
food Kyla is not online didn't they say
she will be online for four more hours
or did they mean in four
hours I mean I think I'll still be
[Music]
around thank you
oh not in 4
hours
ah uh well I guess we can start with all
the other smaller things put that right
there yeah I think I misunderstood you
guys you guys were saying she was
joining in 4 hours not for another four
hours yeah okay H maybe we can do all
the small missions before the ancient
debris Mission yeah okay cuz I think we
should wait for Kyla for the ancient
debris I want her to blow up
everything oh okay okay okay
[Music]
okay beds explode
better well in this time we can make
some more beds then too I guess what
does she does doesn't want to I'm sure
she wants
to uh
duh pretty sure she wants
to I'm also pretty sure she's open for
anything really
but she's she's ready for
danger at all times that's how I know
Kyla especially if it's about the never
I don't want to like be like no I don't
want to do it with
[Music]
Ollie actually I don't think I can
play
[Music]
Ollie Ollie but then she'd be
disappointed
Ollie Ollie oh man the range is so small
Ollie oh oh oh hi who do you not want to
go to the never with what what no
what who no no tell me do you not want
to wait for Kyla that's fine we can go
no is it well yeah well I I yeah I don't
want to wait for her because I have
something in the morning and I don't
think I can play for another four hours
and I kind of don't like relying on her
a little bit too much because you know I
kind of want to experience it for my own
oh see you can just say that to me
I heard you like like a bracket of what
you were saying on the bridge because
you passed my house I was like heyo wait
that sounded like she doesn't want to
like she has something to say but she's
not feeling like she can say it because
of because I said something but you
don't really want to wait so long for
Kyla and I was like oh swly stop stop
stop so we can go but uh what do you
think do you still want to try the
ancient debris m
Gathering I mean we we can try the small
ones and then maybe if we have time we
can just blow stuffs up have you done it
before I've done it a few times on my
own me too but it's a long time ago but
yeah MAA probably did it too I
suppose we can figure it out right we'll
try sorry about that no worries if we
don't find enough I'll just go again
later with Kyla
[Music]
okay all right what time is it for you
uh half 5:
p.m. oh okay H so I got time um all
right then let's take a few beds bring
them to the Nether and then go
digging yeah or do you think we should
PRI prioritize the small things first
before the ancient
debris we can prioritize the small
things first I feel like um yeah okay
but then I'm going to uh should we bring
the beds anyway into The Nether and just
put them in a box
somewhere yeah we could do that okay all
right yeah I heard something
[Music]
I give
you
[Applause]
okay oh still
there I'm full can you hold this for
me for
[Laughter]
how yeah you can hold down this as long
as you
want all right I think I'm mostly
ready so when waiting for
by MAA are you
ready all right it's her first time do
you want me to pick you
[Music]
up pick me up mommy I'm
scared all right I don't need sapling
oh oh she might still be at uh PKA by
space I'm going go get her okay I need
to go back to to get a
box
yeah
H wasn't that considerate of me I had a
feeling that she was going to say
something like that and she just didn't
feel like saying it to me because she
loves me I suggested
[Music]
it had a
feeling she should just say
it what are you planning with those beds
blow everything
up yeah until nothing is left no more
just like how I Blew Up The Village and
St you Valley
what did I come here
for ah getting a
box to put it in the nether for the beds
just for the
meantime one of us should be bringing a
lot of building blocks too maybe
although most paths we pretty much like
already made paths if anything we need
to yeah I guess no you can always need
building blocks but
but my
inventory I don't need
this uh yeah don't need this
right
[Music]
um maybe I'll need a shovel I don't know
oh I can put back the Birch plank planks
okay guys you know today I'm being
accompanied by lemon water because I
have digged out dug out out my uh juicer
that I forgot I
had I dug out my juicer and the extra
parts that were buried somewhere else in
my storage
room I have a really cute juicer like it
looks retro and it fits a lot of my
other appliances they're all like mint
colored and the past few days I bought
like oranges and lemons and I've been
like making fresh orange juice but I'm
surprised like how how little orange
juice you get out of a [\h__\h] orange so
at least like two or three oranges for
anything
meaningful and yeah now it's like lemon
water really nice to juice my own juices
yeah okay okay hey yo hey I brought a
few building blocks and I brought
brought a chest so we can put in all the
beds and some fire potions here one for
you
MAA oh I still I have one already okay
now take it though because I also have
two okay and I brought some torches and
weapon and stuff and food okay my
inventory is pretty full do you guys
have like some more mining blocks maybe
we'll need
more I don't know oh I have three threee
stack of planks oh maybe PL maybe planks
are a bit too valuable but
okay oh we we could you know uh what's
it called we could turn the planks into
like those half planks what are they
called again oh well half planks yeah
half planks yeah yeah yeah yeah I if we
need more uh blocks we can always mine
the never rck so we could oh yeah so we
can go I think yes let's go MAA did you
ever do this before with the ancient
debris although we're doing the other
things first but have you ever done the
ancient
debris well not on Hardcore oh
well where's the difference he's
experien at least we need to go to minus
19 kind of thing okay you know that wow
that already bring us by the y or by the
X's
but wait why why why I think it's why
yeah need to get
low
oh ooh
oh there's another blocks in
here oh there's another another bed yeah
three more beds out of here but I guess
they belong to someone
probably okay
um where we go wait what is there's
another Titi in here TI well okay so
we
yesterday we just went through one of
the paths randomly to find all the
mushrooms and the other stuff and the
the gas so we can go anywhere
really oh okay anywhere is fine so what
was it again the Soul Sand one gas sand
kill one gas kill three skeletons them a
potion make a potion we going to make a
potion yeah we can do that later outside
the
potion cuz we have a potion maker where
are we going
M which path did we go yes today was it
this
one was it this
one I need path is fine
though wait hold on is this a good path
maybe let's take this
path
okay we don't want to go to the uh
Fortress because they already took the
head so we don't need the
Fortress don't
worry okay let's go okay let's go yay
uh left or
right you choose any anywhere all okay
left again in the never
okay writing down
coordinates it's not
forbidden but why why would I need to
ride it
down oh God
surprised ol didn't fall down the vines
that we needed to
get the warpy is that it no yeah the
yeah the mushroom that's the mushroom
the green mushroom but it's not here
oh uh we should find stuff like here and
there oh I hear some gas yeah yeah wait
H H how would P know that we defeated a
gas oh we just have to like ride it in
our mission she will believe us
I also just run it down h no nothing
nothing
nothing gas
g write it right on the on the diary
right ah here's the Bastion
ha oh so this is the Bastion but we
don't get points for this anymore Only
Yesterday
unfortunate okay yeah this is the the
path that we took yesterday
[Music]
going to improve some
sections
okay close go very [\h__\h] close go Fu I
was like balancing on there did they go
that way are oh here
oh I almost died I can't see how did you
almost
die I was walking Edge to death don't
worry we only got in uh oh the path
continues here I think over
there
oh can they regrow the the ones we took
yesterday do they
regrow there should be some green
mushrooms somewhere in this biom but be
careful of the
pigs I hear it G but I can't see it yeah
I hear it but I can't see
it somewhere somewhere maybe we should
go further yeah yeah we'll find
everything
[Music]
eventually she coming
okay okay
uh
yeah I'm going to make a little bit more
you know secure
you're so cute oh thank you you
too that pig is also thinking about
dangerous things it's like standing
there on the edge you see
it
oh
okay why it
oh oh God oh my God they're good they're
fine they're strong they're ID shouldn't
be worried about
them it was killing pigs on the mission
list no
[Music]
right cuz I feel like I saw pck Senpai
doing
it MAA Senai
what she you're not dead are you can you
hear me ma z
Hi H I see her she's down
there oh yeah there she
is why would I need the fire resistance
potion when I didn't need it yesterday
what
thing oh Fus you got the green wait
really
where down there just one though maybe
there oh there's another one there
yeah oh yeah I I've already got one oh
there it is behind the lava be
[Music]
careful oh oh no all right I forgot [\h__\h]
have
to sorry I'm trying to hit the pig sorry
sorry sorry sorry okay I I saved
Ollie yay is you okay I saved you Olli
you good okay
[Music]
should we go down yeah maybe there's
more funy
okay but no pigs
please they're
everywhere when a pig is coming at me I
feel like the best way to react which
I'll probably not remember is just
building a quick Tower of blocks
[Music]
maybe oh be careful did you get the your
green come on come on come on oh you
found another one yeah lots of it come
on lots of it
okay yummy yummy mushrooms here oh my
God that's so much ni nice okay one
Mission we take them all oh just one per
person is fine just one right okay okay
nice okay now we got to look for Soul
Sand yeah Soul Sand and gas and whatever
skeletons okay wait are the skeletons
like the upper skeletons or like the
nether skeletons just normal skeletons
are fine the white one M oh okay okay
guess we're going to go back up where is
the best way to get
up maybe here oh it's so nice being able
to walk on top of magmas oh God there's
a lot of pigs around I just want to go
up look I'm burning and I'm not
[Music]
dying okay scared
scared there is a pig over there
over there
oh but doesn't I'm Not Afraid no don't
[Music]
worry wow nice aim but needs one more
hit or so a
nice
nice all right you guess remind me what
are the missions are we forgetting one
the whole the whole
time do we go back back oh just continue
somewhere we'll find Soul Sand all of
these all of this path all of this path
is made by me mikoi and Ana and the rest
of our group by the way we made all of
this path everything you guys paved the
way yeah we
did yo we were so scared the whole
time gas skeleton Soul sound oh that's
it and the ancient debris okay okay
okay yeah let's
[Music]
go oh Gast I hear Gast loud and
clear
yeah come at me yes why is the chicken
here chicken really really weird how is
the chicken the only normal animal you
can find in the nether I don't
understand it's because they are
actually evil around there or because
they're
dinosaurs ooh now where do you guys want
to go oh just
continue this way oh did we stop
building here oh no we just oh God is
this I think this is a path that leads
nowhere we made another
path was it this way
oh yeah this way
okay I'll make it
safer you're so
sweet just for
safety for
safety oh I think I saw this in the clip
somebody died here right uh it could be
anywhere really like everything looks
the same but yeah subai died on our trip
while we were going through here oh ma
ma' Pig coming Pig coming don't worry we
got you
so we got
you oh God oh
God nice there's another one around the
corner all
right see oh god
there they we're
fine sorry sorry sorry it's
okay oh look it
K oh my God oh my God oh my God oh my
God wait wait wait wait wait
yeah
Warrior oh God Ollie are you okay I'm
fine nothing a zombie campaign
oh look the child what all these pants
get the child get the
child they're so many must exterminate
Pig must exterminate
Pig okay okay looks a little bit clearer
now
uh I killed the child good
job
yiy I almost died
yay uh let's
see uh kind of lost track we need to
find Soul
Sand Soul Sand right I mean I mean we
can we can do by going down there is
there a soul sent down
there I think on our this I know that
this path eventually will lead to Soul
Sand because we just got all the items
yesterday while making this path So
eventually we'll get there ah is this
the path we go here yeah I think so or
is this where we came from no this is
the New Path
okay
[Music]
yeah yeah there was a lot of souls sent
somewhere on our
way oh maybe we passed some already that
could
[Music]
be been here before or do I have Deja
vuu
where uh where are we here before did we
go the wrong way no no no yeah I think
it's
new
[Music]
y I got some sound effects now too
Ollie
yeah this one I got the same as you oh
my god let's go
[Music]
and oh no and I got
crickets and
Applause
ooh you have a lot and I got some Chimes
and the rim shot when something's
funny
but I don't have any that's okay we'll
be your soundboard you don't need one
anyway this path uh
where does it where does it go it's dead
end end here oh did we go back there
there's another path over here but I
don't know where this leads oh this
leads back to the portal actually we
eventually realized we were going in a
circle um was quite funny oh oh my God
you're
right oh yeah but I think this way will
lead to another different area a little
bit
different in the end it's all connected
but somewhere there are is some Soul
Sand I'm
sure oh not everywhere Soul Sand is
everywhere Soul Sand
[Music]
everywhere yeah oh are we going we're
going home if we go this way are
we yeah yeah because maybe we should
just take a different path then
[Music]
this is straight to the Fortress this
path oh God I need to
eat
[Music]
H you do not need double
torches yeah don't worry about
it oh you're trying to you want to fix
it
yeah you know if this server lasted for
a month I would probably fabuliz this
whole
place yeah but it's not worth it spice
not worth it where was this
again this way
right this torch is not good only this
one on the not good at all
[Music]
put the bed away from your hot
bar
okay we
G we need
you come on is it is
[Music]
close there it is okay you guys you can
kill it if you want it has to be one gas
per person what Go Get It Go Get
It Go Get you missed go get
it oh it went down it went down it will
come back
right it's over there
back come
back come back want to go down you can
if you want be careful though
careful y
be danger
[Music]
zone where is where is
it I can't find it oh it probably went
below the whole
platform I think it will come
back hopefully it comes back h
oh she oh it's time for me to
eat my medicines wait hold on but I'm
not going to
sleep
a oh is it coming again is it coming up
I feel like it sounds so loud why is it
not in front of us
[Music]
oh it shot it shot it's somewhere in
range I heard it
shooting are you sure yeah
yeah but it would usually
go usually stays above lava
it's not coming back I see the chicken
piglin
though
there
she it's so far where is it so it's
pretty
far pretty
far it's not
rendering how does it see us and we just
cannot see it oh my god oh oh oh that's
not good oh that's not good uh run this
is not good this is not good at all run
carefully ah ah
no
no no no no no no that is really
bad uh is p play around
[\h__\h] no oh
no oh
no what do we do we got to pick up her
things wait I have one
box oh yeah okay let's not take the beds
let's just take the important
ones here we can put her stuff in here I
don't know what's hers I I barely had
space in the first place
um and that's not important the mail
I'm guessing is gone but in theory she
can go to the solo server and do the
seven Diamond thing not it's not the
whole life server it's a solo server
where she has nothing I
think
um get that and
then and maybe staff can revive
her while p is sleeping
still oh the planks are
hers first death on her first
day damn
why that's tough
[Music]
buddy we can't we need we need
her
yeah I need let's cut
it wait where's her other armor a sh uh
[Music]
go to solo server and get seven
diamonds maybe St can revive you if they
are around I'll check in
Discord oh why can I put the diamond you
just need to post a screenshot
of the diamonds in your inventory in the
Discord but it
has we're fine we're fine kill it kill
[Music]
it
oh yeah cuz like I heard Ana explaining
it to Mauna saying that it has to be the
main server but I think that was
wrongly wrongly uh uh communicated it's
not the main server it's a solo server
where you have
nothing as far as I
know no it's seven normal diamonds not
blocks seven normal diamonds in the solo
world yeah I can check what the others
did
too yeah seven normal diamonds in a Solo
World let me add let me check staff is
if anyone
is
around oh that is
[Music]
okay yeah let's see if they'll reply at
this
time oh Pi in by typing oh pi
oh okay
okay okay yeah I don't know if she's
actually going to go to solo server
though is MAA streaming is she doing it
the right
way let me check real
quick that's just unfortunate I wish I
could have saved her but it was yeah
pack yeah but she probably did she hit
the pigling by accident when she was
trying to shoot the the gas oh
man that is really bad when you pull the
argro in a Big Field of piglins like
this
oh I I think she has
it yeah but then she probably did it in
the main server if she already has it
right that's not the
challenge I but solo server right yeah
like where you have nothing you got to
start from
zero
oh be on the solo server with start from
zero what block
just seven
[Music]
diamonds
uh okay I think maybe now I explained it
properly yeah okay she's on it and then
p s still online so once MAA Senai is
done she can uh revive her oh yeah 30
minutes time by the
way forgot to say that she only has 30
minutes yeah time limit yeah but others
all managed to do it
so we can for now gather Soul Sand for
her maybe to save some time
yeah okay um but let's save the
coordinates of this
I I took a screenshot of the
coordinates oh
okay is the gas dead did you kill
it no it's gone I wanted to get it but
what yeah
again okay it ran away it went off to
the unrendered where did we come from up
there we came from up there okay I think
there's another path over there
[Music]
mookies we're fine we're fine yeah only
two uh people but we're less of a Target
then right wait isn't that Soul Sand but
I think there's a better place to get it
oh what was this oh my God it's just
floating here yeah no there's definitely
better
places wait I think h no no no no no
trust me there's better
places okay
H Pig again
man we've been through so many
times wait
wait I don't want to be suddenly
surprised attacked by it there we go
thank God for my eternal
bow oh did she find
something oh Jon by
oh yeah you want to go down
there no no just down
here yeah you want to go there
yeah do you want me to get it for you no
no no no I think we'll find a
Bed Oh you mean there oh I looked at the
island oh be careful be careful don't
worry we're fine 1 2 3 4
there's a there's a guest there is a gas
there's a there's a
gas where then we just need to avoid
where is it where is it okay there it is
it's over
there I can never get it okay I'll try
come
on better oh oh
come on better up so [\h__\h]
far better up better up
better I got it I got
it
okay come
on oh no playing tennis with the cat the
underworld cat
stop oh what the hell almost got
it is here be careful oh yeah is there
help
okay yeah hi
hi you can
[Music]
heal it's gone no don't go did you kill
it oh still there where is it why so
far it's over
there okay but it's super far now come
here come closer it's not
fair
yeah come closer
card that's a
zombie oh a closer
one where's the
[Music]
[Laughter]
F it's aiming for you
right I hit it I hit
it man I'm a bad feeling
here oh oh we got it oh I think
we killed that one did you see if it you
killed it okay then I got the hit you
got to get the other gas yeah let's
clean this up you have any arrows H I
have an eternal
bow oh can I borrow there you go don't
die thank you don't die I
won't Eternal
bow sheesh I got let make this place a
bit
safer how do you use an eternal
I'm sorry you just need one Arrow do do
you not even have one Arrow here no
there you
go she ran out of arrows that's not
good my boots almost done oh
no then I won't be wearing gold oh wait
there's can I do you think I can fix it
while I'm here oh but I shouldn't be
mining that now huh
Oh Oh I thought he was going after
her is
he okay maybe since MAA I did it good
job then you also have the kill uh one
thing though my boots my golden boots
are kind of like about to break so um
since MAA isn't here anyway maybe one
time we should leave again oh yeah yeah
we should definitely leave
okay let's let's regroup with MAA when
she's done with her
Mission uh do you know where we came
from yeah we came from this way
okay
damn uh-huh and we go this way I think
really really are we going just go back
that way yeah
yeah orange juice yummy did you got
carts a I took a screenshot juice oh
yeah uh can I have the bow back oh yeah
here you
go thank you thank you do you want the
arrow I just one is enough just give me
one oh
wait oh [\h__\h] no wait mistake ah wait
wait one two three uh here take this Le
got a few more arrows now he
nothing much appreciated
look look how dangerously she
lives you think she'll survive
today the way she runs and jumps on the
[Music]
edge we got to get back here we got to
remember this place so we can bring MAA
back here wait wait wait one second one
second
Oh Oh I thought there would be one no
run run just run just run just run just
run where uh
here just run just
run he can run he can run he can
run are you okay no die my gold my gold
armor is gone
Ollie Ollie Ollie I'm
scared he broke my he broke my golden he
can take my boots he can take my boots
what about yours I'm fine I can I can
kill people no we just got to get back
safely but I think why did he have aggro
on me because I opened the
chest yeah it's because of the chest oh
[\h__\h] I was just checking if MAA had a
golden piece of armor in there that we
would bring back to her so she can enter
the nether with that
again did you kill him or where did he
go yeah I killed him oh my God Ollie ch
ch Cho ch
ch I was just checking the chest it's
our stuff he thought we were stealing
but it was our things
sensitive little [\h__\h]
yeah we're living way more dangerously
than yesterday today
already yeah
be maybe that's just the ID style of
living yeah we live in the edge you know
uh I like it oh my
god oh we could get some you know gold
from here yeah easy
gold careful though
[Music]
oh I have silk touch that Ah that's why
it's coming out like
that
oh oh don't bury me alive no
[Laughter]
no yeah my chat is saying don't dig down
Ollie digging down is dangerous you're
taking your own
grave ironically
I hope moa's doing okay oh hello sir
hello oh no
no run oh forgot about
that wait
girl you killed him you fine you you
ruthless
murderer oh Shez okay well I guess in a
tunnel we can just kill him yeah
it's not like they'll remember our faces
yeah he and it's not like he will tell
anybody else what happened here this
tunnel a dead man tells no
stories unless he revives like you like
a
zombie right how do you do that how do
you Revival IE a zombie instead of just
dying tell me what's your secret um it's
a it's a I don't know myself it's a
mystery
H Maybe maybe there were certain things
that Destiny wanted you to still do
because you left things
undone maybe is that the door that would
explain it we found our way back
y one good thing so let's remember if we
go through this door we'll find probably
the chest
again okay then I'll just put a dirt
here to remind this then for now we can
go back get another golden item and and
put the Warped fungus away wait did you
put yours into the MAA
chest I oh dear cuz I was wondering why
there were two in there we'll get it I I
I can get it back yeah yeah can I Bard
the boots
oh oh I thought we were leaving once to
get another boots oh oh okay we can do
that too yeah yeah yeah
okay
uh wait wait wait wait wait wait how
much how much gold do you have here's
some gold and here's some
gold yeah
okay these out of these we just get a
gold nugget right oh yeah
yeah
what oh my
how are
you I'm great how are you great we just
lost one of
[Laughter]
[Music]
our thank you okay that's 55 gold Nets
uh let's go let's go make uh out of
these gold nuggets a proper gold right
yeah ingots
[Music]
okay good luck come
back should we go to your
house we can go to my house
okay my house
until my my house until
I'm always chill
Ollie always
chilling not answering to your
[Laughter]
[Music]
flirt Luna Senpai is doing great oh how
do you know I'm watching her stream as
we play okay how many diamonds does she
have none she's looking for a swamp I
think oh
my house is why for a
swamp cuz when you go to a swamp and you
see like a certain um
clay then you just go to the east
side uh three blocks and then you dig
straight down and then you should be at
like a diamond place I think yeah what
oh no she's looking for
iron what
[Music]
do I put this here oh yeah okay I have a
lot of barrels on top too so you can use
that okay but when do you have
coal Coal yeah to burn the
Nugget oh oh we can burn the nuggets
with literally anything I add trees I
guess wait don't don't you you don't
wait s you just need to craft them right
sorry it's been a while with Minecraft
how many do we get out of that we got
six oh I think with six we can make a
golden armor piece right yeah we can
make boots all right fresh sick
boots then I'll give you the boots the
new
ones thank you
yeah all right then we could already go
back in in theory
mhm but what do we do once we're inside
M look for the Soul
Sand oh okay but like we can get the one
for Muna too I don't think she has to
pick it up
herself yeah wait if Soul Sand then I
have it right
here oh I got
four I think the mission at least wants
us to get it like today like mine it not
not like existing so Soul Sand that was
already in your
chest ah or did you get oh wait yeah
never mind you got it from the
ground before MAA died I
forgot yeah oh okay okay okay oh then
that's complete we could find another
gas for you to kill wait you killed one
but I killed oh no then well
then yeah honestly I don't know what we
should do right let's check the missions
again feel like I'm you can make a
potion you can make a potion but then I
think you need um oh oh for breing
station right yeah but also Magma Cream
if there's no no Magma Cream there left
anymore magma what's a Magma Cream you
get those from the magma the bouncy
magma blocks in the nether the ones that
separate into smaller blocks
oh so that would mean we should probably
go to the Fortress there's an easy path
to the Fortress and then there's a lot
of magma creams there
usually oh okay then we can go there
yeah and there'll be some wither
skeletons too which I guess counts as a
skeleton
too okay I killed one today so I just
need to kill two more
skeletons ah let's I want to go to my
house for one one
moment
[Music]
okay small
house okay I would like to ask for your
consent if I were to take down your
house and renovate it when you're not
looking would that be okay yeah but like
is it worth
it well you can come back to like a
really nice house wink
wink yeah I mean if you want to do it
but like it's maybe it's a waste of your
time of course
anything for Oshi is never a waste of
time besides it's the only thing I can
do in Minecraft I can only decorate no
you can do way more than that trust
me uh okay I'm putting away the Warped
fungus let's
go I took some of my own NE wart in
case well actually there's a lot here
anyway we don't really need my never
W okay
let's just check if there's Magma Cream
there maybe there
is wait over
here yeah
uh ah there is there is uh everything we
need basically just uh
yeah what do we got to do to actually
make a potion wait I did it yesterday I
should still remember how it works Works
actually it should be working right now
only once make it with the ingredients
ah wait so it was never W first right
and then Magma
Cream cuz it it doesn't seem to be
working
automatically so we just take it I'm I'm
going to make it for
you
oh then it just counts as you made it oh
actually no here let let's have you make
it you see the the second box from the
top mhm right click it it should be
Magma Cream
inside oh it's uh no check check from up
here from here from here where I am this
the second
one okay I got one yeah take it and put
it into the potion brewing
stand put it in the PO potion brewing
stand oh I think it's doing it yeah
but maybe we did it
wrong
wait after that you have to put red
stone
in to extend the length of it but let's
see if we made it right okay yeah okay
now put Redstone in there just take it
from one of these
boxes okay yeah I'm donating my never
wordss and then you can take the potion
and say you made it
oh so that's how you make potions yeah
I'll beb I'll get some
water
okay
yippee mission complete I guess wait I
guess I should also be making another
but this counts as me making we made it
together because again the potion making
is a uh another mission for today just
like yesterday same
[Music]
we did it
together when moai is back we're going
to get her the remaining small missions
and then we'll start trying the never
Right
Stuff never right ancient debris
yeah maybe we'll get lucky all right OE
we did it I'll quickly make one for my
own uh you know for my own mission
completion M I'm going to go get like my
other stuff that I left at my house and
put it in the um Locker just for you
know
proof maybe there's actually a button oh
wait maybe there is a button let's
try maybe the button actually works
there's a button down here is this the
button
okay it says press the button on once
otherwise it will not operate
properly oh [\h__\h] what that's an accident
but it wasn't happening it's not
happening what about this
one uh this one's already wrong though
[Music]
like oh it's clicking but why Redstone
first this is
wrong it's still not working
let's make it manually it's
wrong so we start with
deward then we take the Magma Cream I've
never ever made potions in the normal
Minecraft playthroughs I've had so far
so this is actually something I've
learned for Hardcore
Minecraft
nice it's p
[Music]
and then
Redstone well these potions will be
useful for both Never End Ender fight so
and also tomorrow apparently is the
Wither
fight so you guys got to get up for my
early stream
again if you want to see that exciting
some people might die again but I'm
feeling like I'm thinking back of our
weather
fight and how it was so antil climatic
because it ended so fast and it was so
like no
[Music]
problem so I don't think it will be a
big deal we're still enough people to
kill it with no
issue all right
uh putting the thing back and I got
threee new
potions so many potions nice
okay threee
potions just evade yeah no I don't want
to shoot a bit with my
bow
zombie oh Ollie hello okay so potion
done defeat one gas done uh soulan
done warped fungus
done okay we we can kill the skeletons
also if we ask everybody to not sleep
next night
sometimes people do that we can just go
for the night and kill them over
here okay then I can ask in the chat
[Music]
okay or we could go to TT yeah true
there's a TTT yeah they finished it like
two days ago or so wait okay how how in
the world
T never mind then we'll go to TI
found uh found Soul Sand oh you're
writing in your diary right now in the
mission
thingy yeah okay okay W mushroom this is
what I wrote down today I did lots of
missions with K
Senpai came but died though
no and I just told
yeah okay okay uh follow me
following we'll go to
T this way right was the portal oh I
love watching you from behind those
cheeks be
clapping I'm sorry are you pressing four
or
what pressing for with every step we
take
Ollie see this is the grave we made made
for Suba
yesterday why is there hay growing
around that wasn't there
before it just goes to show how fertile
her death was fertile I have no idea
what that means yeah I don't know either
Ollie that makes no
sense
[Music]
okay I was the door open did you open it
no I think someone was here it was the
the girls right probably all right uh
this
way it's a pretty short path I hate
watching you leave but I love seeing you
go Ollie you little
[Music]
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] I'm I'm your little [\h__\h]
princess
I'm so sorry Ollie that's not about you
it's about the other
Ollie but but I kind of like the title
right it kind of sounds good yeah it has
a nice ring to it [\h__\h] princess it's
reminds me of [\h__\h]
lasagna lasagna [\h__\h] lasagna [\h__\h]
lasagna you know what's the difference
between me and you and
lasagna m
M all three of
us no me and the difference between us
and lasagna lasagna is
food
no lasagnas are pressed against each
other
you are such a sussy
baka only for you dare this
TT they actually made tit then yeah so
fast oh is my t house wait is my T still
in its t t house SM t house yes yes yes
t the house
okay he's still
there
yay
[Music]
y so wet sorry sorry I checked my turtle
I made a turtle house for the turtle
that was over there you mean a turtle
house yeah not really it's not a real
house also people were calling it a
prison
oh it's not a prison though it's a
smaller smaller t
house when I is gathering coals she's
doing great
really how much time does she have left
feel like only 10 minutes but we're
probably not taking the timer that
seriously
[Music]
I don't think anybody really properly
timed the others
[Music]
either haa took like 1.5
hours oh it did feel like she was gone
for a
while but then kyot did it in 27
minutes um welcome to H life thanks for
the gift thank
you oh Aqua Aqua I died here oh yeah
that was also
so
fun so many people died no she just
slipped when they were building this
thing
oh all right uh
skeletons come
on come
on skeleton dle only I wanted to ask you
the the OE game days of
Ollie uh did you like have
this made as
your oh sorry did did I hit you no no no
no no did you have it made as your 1
million
wish oh no not at all I I uh made that
with my own money W
what how long did it take to make that
since the moment you like say okay let's
start the
project uh 2 years ago with a proposal
yeah it got played quite a lot because I
got busy and then developers got busy it
was very hard to like align our
schedules
oh and also uh I paid them at a pretty
cheap price M yeah yeah yeah so it did
take quite a while not at all well game
wise it's pretty cheap but like wallet
wise honestly it's not the it's not the
cheapest
thing m
but now my 1 million whis is coming this
year oh I wonder what you asked
for you should tell me after the
stream yeah oh what are these wz I can't
say anything
[Music]
else yeah why are there
witches well at least um maybe you'll
get some money back from the sales of
the game right amen amen everybody
please support ol's
game yeah as buggy as it is we're
working on an update every single day
there were yeah there were quite a lot
of English uh grammar
mistakes oops sorry but it was still fun
and the art was so
cute maybe one and only he
us
yeah oh the the name of an artist
oh yeah I
see would you not want to make a game of
your own
Senpai sorry we should say opposite
ends like a game like this I mean sure
why not you you take that one yeah I'll
take the next one thank you do you have
free now free
skeletons I think this is my second one
so I just need oh speak of the devil oh
wait did you hit him or okay now I think
I got two
now can we make TNT with
gunpowder yeah we should maybe make some
in addition to the
beds yeah yeah wait let me look for like
the TNT recipe I keep
forgetting TNT recip is sand and
gunpowder that's easy we can get a lot
of sand down there on the on the shore
oh yeah just a bunch of sand and gun
powder and the TNT can stack unlike the
beds so mm that's going to be
good dite TT it's
[Music]
dite oh you're thinking of a different
song you're thinking of a
song well wait what's what Dynamite were
you singing AC
DC t
it's
dynamite T and watch
me do different brain cells but you know
the song
right I think I've heard of
it come on I think I need one more
skeleton
Poli Poli
[Music]
hello oh generation I don't know AC it
because it was released at my time or I
just know because it's a classic guys I
also know other songs that are before my
time I mean I know moart songs too
so I definitely oh my God Mozart she's a
hag well no I did say I I I've I've
lived during that time M was my bestie
all right you done with skeletons I'm
done with skeletons okay for good
measure here was another one just in
case okay all right there is now proof
in our stream that we did
[Music]
that oh wait what about the gunpowder oh
well how about we just gather the sand
now I do I have my I don't have my
shovel no Ollie Ollie I have shovel oh
can you get like a [\h__\h] ton of sand here
then okay and then bring it
up I'll try to kill some more mobs to
produce even more gunpowder how is that
hi how does that
sound that sounds
good
yeah don't forget flint and steel hey
why oh to oh to light the
[Music]
TNT
oh well we're still waiting for MAA to
we have
time flameo ah flameo I don't have one
do do the other girls have
[Music]
one damn this is a long
path check t for
bows well flint and steel should be no
issue though
[Music]
fire
charge there's so much gunpowder yo we
can make so much
[Music]
te sheesh wait okay for now let me
put my a few of these
[Music]
beds let's go we can we can we can blow
everything
up hey yeah let's
[Music]
go what's
up much much more yeah then maybe we
don't need the beds at all what do you
think can I leave the beds behind no
I'll bring them back to paa farm
though but this looks like a good
amount just don't use the beds just make
TNT yeah yeah cuz the beds don't
stack this way we can
[Music]
stack you do much safer than beds oh cuz
we can go away is that what you mean
with the beds I guess you have to stay
close okay yeah that doesn't sound so
[Music]
smart wish there was a button like in
our Amy PE PE
[Music]
I want to push it it feels nice when you
push it and they all come down at
[Music]
once oh she could get bows arrows for
her bow here some extra RS if she's not
going to put uh the Eternal thingy
Infinity on her
bow glad I'm a never blew up P I would
be so mad at her I would be so angry cuz
I I love I love it I love the existence
of it even if you if people don't use it
anymore except I do even though then it
should still stay because it's a piece
of History
M it's
beautiful this doesn't really spawn much
does it is this normal is this the most
effective itive way to build
[Music]
this is she exaggerating with how much
sand she's going to bring
me a monument to 2022 2021 Yeah man so
many years have passed time and time
again I realize it and it's just
mindblowing go up ladder to
[Music]
FK okay
can't I don't know
how I could put a block here
[Music]
though when only asks where I
am it's closed off hey yo maybe it's not
meant to be visit it up
[Music]
there it's okay we really have enough
gun powder I
think let's see how much we can make I
wonder if the others are not going to go
for it
because they would probably take the gun
powder would would have taken it already
by now I think maybe they're all
thinking ah
that mission is a little
bit too much
work so they're ignoring
it ah it makes them spawn around her
well they should be spawning at wherever
anybody is playing no
[Music]
Anya and V are looking for Debbie right
now oh well at least this one is not
like first come first surf but they're
only digging we're going to blow it up I
guess they were too worried that they
will die in the
[Music]
process it's been a while since I did it
with my mom and mostly like she was
doing
everything
oh hm
[Music]
Anya did get some
already
really maybe they didn't think of it h
wait did it say only one right but like
we're thinking per person I don't know
if they're also thinking the same way or
if they're thinking oh one debris per
group will be
enough I mean the more de Maria right
because we can put it on our armor Maybe
maybe although one one ancient debris
per person with one ancient debris we we
can't really make anything out of it
maybe we'll find even
more maybe we'll find even
[Music]
more yeah it only would make sense cuz
otherwise you could go with 10 people
and find only one hi Ollie I realized
there's a [\h__\h] ton of gunpowder in there
I don't know I already took it can you
give me the the
sand oh yeah yeah it's not that much
because uh I was on the verge of death
oh [\h__\h] oh yeah cuz it was night time we
should have done it during the daytime
sorry it's okay we could have just slept
but okay this way we don't have to bring
the beds so there will be more space in
the inventory as well mhm oh we can
still make even more which is need more
sand okay
gotcha this time it'll be safer
we can make way more oh so oh what's WR
what H oh is it because she's really not
down
there did they really just all spawn
there because she was not down
there you have enough we'll make more
and if we have left over we can leave it
for the
others but it's pretty late in Japan so
I think most Japanese members are not
really going to do much more and logging
out
you were supposed to be doing your
research on your thesis is well how
about
you change the topic of your thesis to
Phoenix then you're currently or
mythical beings then you're doing
research as you're watching
me
yeah they might be getting ready to lock
off yeah I think so when you're on the
ground lots of M spawn in caves below
you
oh yeah makes
sense oh oh there's a lot now
though
wait stop jumping around he knows like
he's doing it on purpose he's teasing me
he's jumping you can't get my toes you
can't get me p
p Isn't it nice guys that Minecraft is
like popular again for just one week
Isn't it
nice feels good to be
back so this oh by the way my hello
fresh box still didn't arrive so I don't
know what the [\h__\h] happened with
[Music]
it it was supposed to arrive yesterday
and after my stream I called the hotline
and you know they can't really see where
it is but it it was delivered but there
are cases where that it's
like it says it's delivered but it's not
and sometimes in that case they said
that maybe the delivery person put it on
delivered but is delivering it like
maybe half an hour or so later they were
just like hurrying and already setting
it as delivered when it wasn't but
they're still coming but they didn't
come it was already too
late and yeah I kept on waiting today
too because they said okay okay call us
again if they still didn't deliver it
until the following day 6:00
p.m. no nobody nobody nobody got
anything I didn't get anything I checked
I also checked if I I don't think they
would do this like you know bring it to
a post office
station cuz no even when I'm not at home
they just deliver it they just put it in
front of my
door you
know but there was no like pickup paper
in
my oh but it's okay I'm going to get a
full refund it's okay but like I was
going to cook something and I was going
to cook food that has you know the
appropriate amount of
calories but yesterday I still I think I
still uh did not consume that much
calories because I only had for
breakfast I had like a banana and like
an egg or so right no three bite three
bites of the the the moole the
cereals the oatmeal chocolate
cereals like three or four bites of that
and one banana and then I streamed and
then after the stream I had one frozen
lasagna because that late at night
that's all I could get well I warmed it
up yeah and a little bit of salad to go
with it like Leaf
salad so I'm pretty
sure uh I did not take that many
calories
so I thought ah then I can eat a little
bit of ice cream so I ate a little bit
of ice cream but I still think that's
like nothing cuz the calories on the
lasagna it was like under 300 or
so I
checked so I
haven't that's less than what I would
have had with the hell of fresh
meal
yeah just was a few scoops of uh not
Scoops but like spoons of ice
[Music]
cream yeah so this
there yeah I was I was surprised too at
how little calories the lasagna had
pretty surprised no no it's said per
portion and and it was one
portion H I was surprised too no no no
the whole thing I checked there was a
100 G and then there was a 320 G which
the 320 G was considered the whole
portion
yeah so like
I if I still don't have anything to cook
today and my stream is ending late that
means I can't buy
groceries so I guess I I don't know I
don't know what I'll be
eating probably not something
necessarily healthy but you know I
didn't consume much much in general
today either
so although no yeah I mean at least I
had like a sandwich before the stream
and I did have a little bit of breakfast
so yeah I'm not hungry just don't know
what to eat for dinner girl dinner time
guess I'll starve yeah call it cheat
day well I I I I actually I don't know
how long we'll go today I
do like if we don't get of Dey before
Kyla comes then I'll stay longer and do
it with Kyla I guess but
possibly honestly after I get the deis
then my missions that I can clear are
clear so then I'll be able to end it
earlier today but tomorrow might be a
long stream again because yeah with
wither
fight and then the missions or the other
way around not
sure you definitely find you think so
unless someone dies do you need Redstone
to make like this like line to activate
it like you make a line and then at the
end of it you go beep with the fire
thingy yeah oh then we need Redstone to
ah
Ollie I'm back no just a lighter you can
do that yeah oh okay okay okay thank you
let's go we'll have more than enough TNT
the left TNT we can give to Kaa or
anybody
else oh you little
shits that so
sexy okay let's see if we can use it all
up
[Music]
TN no okay now actually you brought me
too much sand but that's
fine we have we
have 100 about
TNT oh I I I have more uh gunpowder if
you want hey
yo yo a bit more
then yeah now we have like
10070 almost oh more creepers yeah yeah
creepers here spawn
more yeah let's see it's already too
much I think
oh maybe we can fill up that one stack
still come on
creepers how's MAA doing
creeper do you know how maa's
doing oh wait let me check on
her
um oh she's digging straight down right
now she finally got her iron pickaxe
okay digging straight down the classic
oh by the way you are you not planning
to put uh infinity on your
bow oh yeah I do want that maybe do they
have it no but um you can go to Kyla
place and get it there if you have
emeralds oh I got to grind
then maybe there's a free one L around
though wow oh now you know what let's
leave it at that and then I'll
put um you think they need the sand
here's some
sand let's go let's go Al let's
go Emerald I have a boat right here oh
wait never mind it's only a one person
boat where are you ah actually if you
don't have emerals you can just um take
the iron because there's two iron Farms
now right and yeah then your job until
Mauna comes back is put Infinity on your
bow let's
go let's
go what why are you why are you on the
boat oh I found it there so I need to
return it
oh but obviously if I go too fast and I
wouldn't be walking beside you it's
okay speed
[Music]
dolphins wait Ollie Ollie Ollie come
down here Ollie come down
here down here and look at my turtle
here oh hello
to
yay it's chilling do you know the
[Music]
coron phrase where she says it's quite
famous where she says Ah SM T of the
house at like Mario uh like a Super
Mario
game like she was making fun of uh enemy
you know the the the the shell enemy the
dude the the turtle
dude yeah and she was like you know
making fun of him and she said SM t
house and ever since then I just have it
in my head the whole time I love it so
much the way she says it is so funny
what say that again what say it again no
never mind say it again say it again say
it again I'm shy say it again you're not
shy ol say it
again no say it
again smart smart T the
house smart
smart kute
I am so I want I'm going to show you the
original
later
[Music]
okay are you also pressing space
endlessly
yeah wait I left all the beds at TNT T I
mean oh well no no really needs them
anymore let's go to Kyla Farm oh no iron
farm first for you
boie I guess she knows where it
[Music]
is no that
way
sorry he's so
[Music]
gay yeah nobody needs the free BS
anymore and nobody's thinking about
getting neite I guess but maybe the
neite will be a mission tomorrow too cuz
it will be useful for the Ender Dragon
but n we so Overkill
[Music]
anyway did you
oh oh hi I got raided oh hello friends
oh you got
raided should we sleep oh maybe we
should sleep
yeah but maybe we should kill
him blood blood blood where are they
come
on come down here yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah
[Music]
oh nice I got
one no photo haw
no aim practice for the ender dragon
[Music]
yay will go to
the let's
go it's good that they made a second one
because like yesterday we were running
out of iron everywhere
everybody wanted iron was at the same
place yeah everybody wanted iron to get
emeralds oh that's so funny let's see
how much is in
here oh plenty of iron
W oh I'll be taking yes take it
all there we go I take them by halves
because I'm not a
monster unlike
me I usually take it
all and then I I trade
everything at the trading Hall so that
sub Senai cannot trade anymore and never
gets any I did that um in front of her
eyes in front of her that that is
diabolic
ni careful no it'd be funny if we fell
no it would not be fun okay it's
water all right go to
kaella all right we wanted to go to
kaella oh skeleton Hy W seems like
nobody cares about sleeping anymore oh
be careful though cuz of the creepers
girl don't don't try it don't try
[Music]
it oh but they're in
water can they oh can they not explode
when they're in
water usually when explosions are in
water uh the explosion decreases by a
lot oo I didn't know that
yeah
yeah I only knew after the Summer
Festival two years ago I could have I
made something similar like
is today's bgm less mind breaking for
you guys are you liking
[Music]
it MAA no maa's coming back don't
worry [\h__\h]
[Music]
you thank you for more membership gifts
yay I appreciate
it yay yay yay oh there is
looting oh but if I mine the ancient
debris with my fortune free
pickaxe mhm or do we need silk touch to
mine ancient
debris oh do we need I'm not sure Chad
tell us please I you still just get one
okay even with Fortune free okay but we
don't need s
touch Fortune doesn't work on Ancient
debr
okay okay don't need tou okay we're good
we're
good all right I wanted
Infinity
yeah
Infinity oh it's only 18 it's so cheap
easy if and do you think you can afford
to
oh I wait we could make one for
ma oh Mauna already has Infinity
ah she just only whoes have it yeah and
you you don't have it yet Ollie CU
you're taking care of me before you take
care of
others love love to you
[Music]
oh there we
go I named look look what I named my
[Music]
bow because it's Infinity you know okay
you know what with the other uh emeralds
you should get
Unbreaking then you have the same bow as
mine here Unbreaking Go Get It Go Get It
oh uh I don't have
enough you should have taken more
iron I I already took a lot of iron but
they're not taking anymore they're not
buying
[Music]
oh you want sticks my dude I don't have
sticks H we could exchange some more at
the other villager farm
if you
want
yeah I'd like to announce to
everybody the famous Maple
cat on
Instagram has after many years of
breeding lost his b balls he has been
finally spayed as well as the other cats
in the household which is really sad
news because those were some magnificent
cat
balls he looked like this short squish
Short Hair Cat do you know Maple
cat yeah you know Maple
cat you know the the cat the short
British Short Hair
Cat yeah
so do you wait wait you follow wait do I
know the same one yeah do you follow the
same
account do you follow them I I I I I
don't follow them but I do know it's the
the the the the the the chubby cat with
he looks a of a chubby but he's not
chubby but he's so cute and and his
owner you know she made him breed for a
few years and now she said it's time to
you know end it all so she spayed him
and and the other cats she had and now
his balls fluffy balls they're useless
now the The Fluffy what yeah just talked
about it because this cat looks like
him he got spayed and his fluff his
balls were so fluffy and so round and so
friend shaped they were so good yeah he
does look like him and the the I got to
be honest the Bells around the neck of
the cat to me looked like cat balls so
that's really why i f about
this wait does wait what what yeah don't
you think they look like plump cat
balls they look like cat boobs I guess
so you could take it like that or you
could take it the other
way yeah but yeah anyway that was just
some random no don't shoot it that just
some random information you don't have
to spay this cat oh no no a a it's
drowning all do
something it'll it'll get to sure on its
own okay okay okay if he know how to
swim oh maybe they're ready
again ah he's ready you can
tra
yipp I like it when you say yipp it's so
cute
yipp that's that cannot be good on your
throat
oh uh oh you know I I I just figured out
a talent that I have that maybe not that
Hol life Talent has a frog
noise it's similar it's you know the the
mushroom guy from Mario the
toad wait do it do it do it do
it wait I I can do it too wait I can do
it
uh uh I can do a really good toad
uh I just need something to read
uh left the
game oh that's good I can do it better I
think but the funny thing is that if you
can do a toad impression you can also do
an Amilia Watson
impression wait what does an Amilia
Watson wait same does she sound like
that yeah but like in the best
way what try saying re r e in a toad
voice see that's
am is that actually
that's I didn't know she my I heard that
she was a gremlin but I didn't think she
was actually one I thought I was like
for the memes what she's not a me
uh she's a toad Gremlin or toad is a
gremlin maybe toad is a
gremlin all right is you're getting the
Unbreaking yeah I'm breaking three let's
go then we have the same
bow the same bow y it's like fate wait
can I still put a third thing on my bow
if I wanted to I think so right yeah
mhm I could put fire on it then we can
shoot the TNT from
afar fire fire let's get fired do you
still have some emeralds
now uh oh oh no actually I used all of
them up sorry how much does he need uh
five only five oh sorry girl
sorry uh then let's get some more
iron yeah get the flame MAA is still
busy
[Music]
Uber my
lady that that that that was uh scary
what happened I think I got stuck
between the boat and the
block wow Suffocation That Could Have
Ended like L's death cuz that's kind of
how she died she got stuck somewhere and
drowned oh wait I want to hear like all
of their deaths how did everyone die do
you remember
well okay um H there's so many by
now I died because we were in a group in
the Nether and a pig was attacking us
and you know they pushed really hard so
I think while we were all panicking and
fighting the pig pushed Subaru down into
the
lava and then hatama was in hat was in
our group in our second trip to the
Nether and she was a little bit too
excited too naive and she was just like
excitedly jumping on the ground and then
just randomly fell into the
lava that is oh yeah andun I was about
to close off the area where she fell
into and then she just jumped into it
yeah I could not save
her oh nice
okay and then got it who else
uh well those are the ones that I saw
Pur there's a a lot more
though
[Music]
oh okay oh in by strip mining strip
mining where in in in the solo world
right do did you pick up the fence I
don't have it oh oh yeah
okay there we go strip mining just like
the pro that she
is
sasuga ah pa I yeah right like yes
yesterday I guess it was yesterday we
had a Pillager rate of the highest level
uh to the other villager Hall that we
have um uhhuh yeah you know when the
Pillager raids like sometimes it can be
a simple raid but also sometimes they
come with crazy [\h__\h] like the big pigs
and stuff or whatever that was mhm and
paa died there at the very end when we
were pretty much already finished with
the fight but she died as a
Warrior W
yeah oh n died looking for iron yeah Lia
died to the auto fishing machine that
she built to the auto fishing machine
yeah a lot of building
accidents to up to this
point all right we
need I was scared I was hitting him okay
we're good 12 oh that's fine yay yay yay
yay I'm going to make a burning just
just like the Phoenix I
am wait I need the
[Music]
book
flame but like isn't there also like
flame one two three like stronger Flames
or is it just flame guess it's just
flame is just flame okay cuz if there
was Stronger flame Pro probably Kyla
would not have been satisfied with
flame
zero she would have not accepted it
makes sense okay let's call
[Music]
it Phoenix
flame
yayen and burning I think wait there's
enough for you to also make flame on
your bow here let me give you
theal take
y thank you thank you we both got the
same Bowl let's go yeah it's like my bow
is Spitting Fire just like my
ocean sword a sword has fire aspect that
has one and two levels now hold okay yo
we're so ready to go for some ancient
debris yeah oh we can get a good amount
let's go we got this H all right
then what do we do do we go back oh no
sorry there we go don't worry I won't
kill a cat you're so
nice I don't want to do that in front of
you but when I'm not there you
would oh [\h__\h] um you know I'm a zombie
and maybe maybe those cats would have a
better life as a zombie as well no
no no I don't want no zombie cat in my
household we have 120 160 like 175
TNT holy
[\h__\h] that's a lot that's that's very
much that's a good
amount nice that's an amazing amount Lam
I hope MAA is coming back soon should we
should we just start without
her she's uh she she's still strip
mining uh she has a she has three blocks
of lapis lazuli ah lapis lazuli please
that's not going to help
her five TNT would have been enough but
we want a lot of ancient debris wait how
is five TNTs enough yeah I don't know
maybe for one for finding one ancient
debris maybe it's
enough you only need five to find like
one ancient debris isn't that like so
cheap H oh
well we can find enough to make full NE
oh Ollie we can find enough to make a
full never right armor for all three of
us and everybody will be like yo what
the [\h__\h] you guys are so so cool we're
going to flex Flex so hard we can eat up
the [\h__\h] yeah we'll be the strongest
people on the
server yeah let make some never right I
may have to go in another half an hour
okay then let's get started should we
get started we should get started oh God
is it okay if it's just us I'm
terrified we'll be fine what's the worst
thing that could happen
okay you have your
gold H uh y yep yep yeah okay so now all
we need to do is look for a place to
blow things up
yeah yeah I I don't think these two
places are like the best yeah maybe we
could try going here
yeah okay and then we just dig stairs
down and hope we don't meet
lava what was the level cuz now we're on
68 19 right
okay no they said why level five in chat
oh why level five what we need to do oh
no 8 to
15 oh hey okay did somebody dig down
here already I think they did just a
little bit or oh now we can just dig
down on our own yeah
[Music]
okay are you
oh are
[Music]
you going to be fine if you meet lava do
you think you're the calm
type um with you yeah
really cuz I usually scream and run away
while Kyla she just calmly covers it and
fixes it
immediately oh well uh don't worry we'll
we'll we'll be
fine H how' we get
down just we can go slime oh we can just
go the other way like this way down just
like a
curve oh yeah you're so smart I am in
love but we should make it safer yeah
just this
way oh or that
way oh got to be careful
[Music]
mhm I have ah if you want you do you
still have potion for fire resistance
Ollie we should take this
way just this way oh yeah oh my God like
make swirls why didn't I think of that
why are you how can you be so sexy and
also so smart at the same time I'm not
can you like choose one no I'm not and
also I'm so terrified of digging and my
pickaxe is too powerful man but okay
let's do it
o it's okay I can keep a good distance
from
it sorry Ollie I'm I'm slow because I'm
scared oh it's okay do you want me to
take charge I'll do it for a while until
I freak out
okay Co
[Music]
this looks good for
now yeah we're at 46 45 44 all righty
are you placing torches I don't think we
need to but would look nice I can do
that oh I hear a little
gastrogen no I don't have a
shovel
[Music]
olly do I oh wa I do I actually do
forgot why is there sand here why is it
normal is that
normal why is there normal sand
OMG
H oh it's gravel that's pretty much
sand a gravel
yeah as long as it doesn't drop on me
let me actually get rid of the whole
roll oh did you know you can just put
torches at the very bottom I yeah well I
heard of that years ago but it's been
too long it's been 84 years
Ollie well it's been 84 years can you
put a torch there just in case like over
there I got to B
girl thank you [\h__\h]
princess she call you [\h__\h] this okay
there's lava so what do we do now maybe
we turn into a different
direction oh yeah we could do that we
could go to the
right
okay um let's see oh God
[Music]
wait okay
oh scary
scary scary scary scary scary only you
continue okay come back check courtz we
are at 30
oh oh oh
again yeah okay how about Let's see we
can go straight for a while instead of
digging down just for few met yeah we
could go straight for a while but
careful careful though be
careful I
will use the gravel that's how that
works
huh do you want gravel
wait can I'm fine okay looks like you
stand on the lava Ollie oh there's so
much here oh be
careful there's so much too much lava
careful
it was
overflowing how do you put it there I
can't place anything oh you shift and
then yeah okay so there's the lava if we
open this window let's try opening this
part oh y see ah you're so calm is this
like in an Indonesian trait or
so I'm trying to look cool in front of
you
actually understandable okay I'm going
to try uh opening a little bit near or
left we can also try left
a so everything's lava okay let's try
left okay as long as it's below it can't
flow on us so that's
good ah how's
this I'll just drop until okay not a
hold all
well but there's just more and
more yeah this is difficult if only mama
told he was here let's just then we got
to go straight for a while until we're
out of this lava section right
yeah she's so
cute Ollie tell me a
story a
story this no hold oh if you crouch you
can walk on it if I remember
correctly better to fix
it yeah tell me what You' been up to
recently besides promoting days with
Ollie oh I've have been very sick oh
yeah right what do you in the hospital
in the hospital
yeah what do you
have I had what's called a typhoid fever
what the [\h__\h] is that so it's like a a
virus that would would infect you if you
were to uh to eat it
orally to consume it
orally like it's either you eat like
really uh dirty food or like really
dirty
water you ate really dirty or really
really dirty food or really dirty water
honestly I don't know because I've been
eating the same thing my family has been
eating and they didn't get
sick I think I'm have a different immune
system yeah zombie body weak so could it
be that something like one part of the
food was moldy or
something uh that could be it or I was
just unlucky with my
food oh how's it oh wow where are
we not quite sure let me h
there's too much
lava
yeah
to we still can't dig
down maybe we should have started from
like a lower area but like I mean we got
to get lower
somehow oh oh I think we can get low
[Music]
nice show me only how you get down get
low twerk for me me yeah yeah
yeah damn damn she can
twerk M it's a bacterial infection not a
virus okay but doesn't doesn't matter I
just hope all gets better does it go
away
soon oh yeah I'm feeling better okay but
after I got better I got bombarded by a
lot more other um sicknesses it
sucks yeah
my Ollie doesn't deserve
this I deserve kisses and hugs and maybe
a little Kiara
[Music]
sex what the
[\h__\h] okay maybe that could cure me from
any sickness you know okay
ol I I I I
I yeah you make me speechless we could
talk about cat balls again I don't
know oh we're at level 10 let's go we're
getting thereus 15 is where we want to
go- 8 to 15 oh Min is 8 to 15 got
it
nice you're doing so well Ollie also I
was going to say for you my love some
kind of disease or so maybe it's just
you know how
zombies
live oh yeah are you we just
um is this a Bedrock
oh I guess it can already show up
here yeah um so there's no more minus no
maybe dig around because it doesn't
always go in one line I think yeah yeah
yeah yeah it's just like a little bit
here but then around we should be able
to find some ancient
debris oh no we can like strip mine here
I guess I don't know I forgot how you do
it oh wait it wasn't - 15 sorry it was +
15 oh it was plus 15 oh so we can go up
a little bit uh okay from here here's
eight so from here here
to no wait that's minus8 sorry I'm so
dumb no that was normal Aid never mind
so confused okay till here until here
yeah yeah all right then around here we
can maybe make some paths or is that how
you do it yeah we we could maybe go here
since it's like the middle ground M
sounds good I'm not sure though I never
really go netherite what what's it
called No me neighbor never right
farming yeah and then we place a TNT and
we go back and we shoot it and then
Kaboom yeah nice it's going to be
awesome how far should we go guys how
long should the path
be every four spots drink potion before
[Music]
shooting as long as you want want about
100 six I think we can already place it
there oh oh no wait never mind make it
longer and then each four uh spaces we
put a tnt I think now I understand okay
okay so how many it it will be a big uh
Chain
Reaction it'll be
I think okay let's let's stop there yeah
let's stop
there
oh
okay oh nice let's stop there no let's
stop there ol let's stop test run test
run okay so
one one two three four on the fourth or
on like like this four in between one
two three four this one 1 two three four
like this okay one two three four not
the gold what's going to happen with the
gold it just drops on the ground right
one two three
4 One Two Three 4 one two
three four one two three 4 One Two Three
4 One Two Three 4 oh
that may have been too early one two
three four 5 one two three four five one
two made some space so that we can you
made more the other way nice but wait oh
yeah so we can back shoot this one okay
H I'm so
scared you got this I believe in you I
suppose we die together should we drink
the potion just in
case oh yeah good good car okay
well then we don't need to be afraid of
anything no no come
back I'm a shoot okay are we doing this
right free between up four did I do it
wrong I spaced them out too
much
really should I fix it can I fix it what
if I how do I let go of the
arrow oh you just SC test it anyway
okay y come in come in come in come
in it's working oh it's working
w w yippy yippe look we're doing it what
does it look like again oh it's stop
there it's
like I don't see any right now it's a
brown oh yeah and has stripes I don't
see any
here that's okay oh I see one oh you oh
my God you found it let's go is there
just one it's just one we found one ol
we'll find more let's find more easy oh
yeah
Kaboom oh the lava OE the lava but okay
it's going it's going to fill up the
holes right can we close yeah I I can
just cover it up for
you one cover
[Music]
did you pick it up
uh
no
no that's
okay uh
careful I have the potion I'm
fine don't
underestimate the power of the lava
let's close this
off can can we close it without uh
spreading it oh oh it stopped only
you're the
best yeah I'm somewh of a genius
myself okay but that was the end of the
line and there's no more okay do you
want me to dig more from this side or do
you want that side M let's go the other
side
okay nice how many pieces of um
never right guys of of ancient debris
for making one armor piece never
right question
mark four 16 for four armor M four for
one piece of armor 16 for a full set of
armor not oh look we found one let's
[\h__\h] go
there's another one let's [\h__\h]
go let's [\h__\h] go we found enough for
all three of us to complete the
mission yeah did you bring some wood by
any
chance I I I know what's the wood for we
could have put it in a chest in case we
die
now ow but we w die it's not like we'll
die yeah we won
die you think there's more even though
it's not
connected doesn't look like it we'll
blow it up
anyway we'll blow all of this up
anyway sheesh this is fun this is fun
yeah we're actually
oh
explosion of the
lava okay M just got the diamond oh ma
can join us
again okay she add she tagged P Senpai
so she'll
probably uh revive
her I think we have to put the what's it
called TNT now there's a lava and I
can't get
through
okay 4 1 2 three 4 One 2 three 4 1 2
three four one two three 4 2 three four
one two three 4 One 2 three 4 One 2
three 4 One 2 three oh I the
[Applause]
game let's go one two
three uh one two
three 1 2
4 1 2 three
1 to
threee looking
good nice okay let's blow it up do you
want to do the
honor oh no I would like to see you do
it
okay let's
go w
w w w it's going it's going it's going
W oh oh there's so much
lava that's so much lava well there
might not be any Asian debris here cuz I
feel like we already got the like the
the two debris yeah the the luck in this
area is already out maybe but I'll
[Music]
check just get
you know the what what did I say not the
ratio the the quota has been met
perhaps the
quot the ancient debris quota oh she's
watching us
oh come here we got to bring her over
here maybe oh we got to show her I can
send her the oh she's still spectating
though okay I can send her the
coordinates for where her stuff is this
oh oh oh no Ollie OE OE Ollie Ollie ol
oh no I'm on fire are you
okay I'm fine oh but maybe P already
went to sleep
oh feels like there since she's not
replying P oh no she TR again
okay let's go never mind mind never mind
never mind never
mind never
mind there's too much too much too much
lava no more lava oh what are you doing
here
buddy you are in the wrong neighborhood
should I push you into the orange sh
at I feel
like there there is wouldn't it be funny
if there was ancient debris right
[Music]
here that would be so cool if I'm like I
think there's some right
here right behind here surely
[Music]
God damn
it maybe
behind
this where are we right now eight eight
is maybe already too
low did she find anything over
there how's it going it's very hard yeah
I can imagine also I don't see any
ancient
[Music]
here but I think I can close this one up
oh check the roof too and look backwards
through the tunnel sometimes they're
hiding back what do you mean what check
the roof like oh
okay but first check the floor before
you check the roof right oh and another
one of them oh they're they're on a
family field trip the
tourists checking out the new uh
neighborhood
buildings I don't think I missed
anything but I wonder if it would be
recommendable to like make more
paths like M but probably not that way
probably should make them parallel
right G to c ah F3 and G it
g all together
wait
ah
[Music]
uh are we looking for them
uh uh don't know what this really does
[Music]
uh mine between that
line which line the red
line
between between
here
between the chunks
oh this box that I'm in right now is a
chunk in the middle they're they're
trying to teach me something about the
lines that I'm
seeing I pressed F3 F3 and G at the same
time and then you see like chunk
lines oh but I don't really they're
explaining it but I don't really get it
[Music]
oh
well well I don't know I think we should
just make another parallel line of you
know
explosions where where was the where did
there's a only where did our where was
our path where we went left and right
where oh it's uh don't worry I
remember cuz it all looks the same to me
has has uh MAA been revived the other
one already wait okay
um uh but once you found some you need
to go to the border of the next area oh
okay but I don't know anymore where
exactly the chunk was with the ancient
debris but I'll pay attention next time
oh oh no okay then we right now we're on
10 so we can just make another line we
can continue the line here kind of yeah
one way straight I
guess we could do that yeah we want more
we're hungry hungry for more ancient
debris exactly ex need help need St okay
let me send her the or should we bring
it to her
either is
good okay um uh but she does need
equipment yeah but it's in the never
so uh should we should we should one of
us go
maybe one of us can go I can go okay
should I send you the
quartz yeah okay I'll you just type it
on chat uh okay don't I'll find it you
take care don't die now okay I'll
try I love you come back soon please
like really soon are you we you
[Music]
okay cuz I don't know I I I I'm not good
at fixing the the lava Parts okay um I
think where is
it oh okay I got it
it is um o is coming for you MAA and
brings you to your stuff it's
at
296 uh
43 -
okay no wait I'll drink it when I blow
something up maybe I don't
know okay we just go straight for a
while and then we blow it
up if I see something I should have a
block in my
inventory to react
fast yeah that's how you do it that's
just how you do
it I'm shaking I'm shaking in my boots
but if I keep this distance the junk
thingy makes me think there's lava
coming cuz it's so bright
yellow if I keep a good distance like
this I'll be fine I'll be fine I can
always run away and scream that's what
I'm best
at yeah yeah yeah
yeah you're quick to run away yeah I
don't think I'll get caught in it as
long as I'm not like digging
up
hey
hey just finding it right in front of my
eyes
Y where did it go did it go into my
inventory yes it's four now
wait yo another
double oh baby a
double
five found two more we got five now
let's
go so that was like a chunk so well
whatever I'm still blowing it
up mine around to see if there I mean
wouldn't it be connected I'll blow it up
[Music]
anyway it's going
well new chunk
ah my pickaxe too strong oh my pickaxe
needs to be repaired
soon
a it's been going
[Music]
strong okay maybe that's where I'll stop
digging it's pretty long
right that's a good distance
right mine the quartz to repair ah so
this
indeed I don't want to I don't want to
dig up
upwards I think that's a smart decision
generally
you guys are also smart for coming up
with
that okay I will place
the
TNT she called me crazy but is she aware
that she's the crazy
[Music]
one 1 2 3 4 1 2 3 4 1 2 3 4 1 2 3 4 1 2
four one 2 three
four maybe not four 1 2 three 4 1 2 3 4
1 2 3 4 1 2 3 4 1 2 3 four 1 2 three
four 1 2 three four 1 2 three uh four
one two
three four one 2 three
four one two three hi would be fun if we
could blow them up
together collateral damage all right it
is time for another
E yeah wait
oh oh I just
realized oh do you guys know what I just
realized I I thought I thought we were
doing it parallel
but you have a bad feeling about this
why a little bit further yeah okay don't
worry don't
worry but I just realized I wanted to go
straight and then another line and then
straight and another line you know did
it wrong but oh well oh well
perpendicular is fine too that's what
you call that I never heard that before
[Music]
who
big what are we on eight maybe it's
maybe I went too low again I don't know
oh yeah it's like hitting
Bedrock that's okay a to the Bri my
beloved ancient the
britan I think that's see maybe no not
sure and you up so
high baby girl what you doing up there
what you doing there don't you want to
be with me let me rescue you I can fix
[Music]
you I'm lucky you think so
oh
[Music]
hello what what does she mean this is
normal I think this is
normal getting never right before Kyla
though kind of cracked kind of unreal is
this real is this real
[Music]
life or is it I don't know
fantasy I want to see like also what's
below the lava could there be ancient BR
like under here maybe it's too low but
[Music]
um found the no no I don't think
so let me
check would be so funny if it
did I think we good six is uh I think no
I have more potion but I don't need it
I'm not trying to tickle the lava don't
worry it can be under the
lava and then for this I got to wait for
uh only to fix
it not hold maybe I'll go that
way what if I do it like right here if I
go take a path right here it will be
taking from two chunks
right is that smart
um will be hard to find me
here oh go hi yep cuz we're at six
that's too
low
wait where at it
where is fauna actually what the [\h__\h] is
that is fauna still
joining I was hoping she would join like
yesterday does she have a stream
reservation up or
something it's not too late for
no 15 is better
okay 10 11
just trying to make it look somewhat
nice for now so that it looks like a
path um oh
stop don't like this side I'mma go this
way the forklift Dr what kind of game
was
that follow play some funny interesting
games
I cannot fix the lava it's not my kind
of it's not my kind of challenge you
know
10 oh search protector why why did they
all get that at the same time what is
that what is
that I'm
jealous k
serious okay maybe one more level higher
so we're on
14 now we're on
14 lightning rod click on it and CH oh
but how do I move the mouse when it's
always in the
middle okay uh so I'll just I'll make
I'll make a path here
you
good you satisfied
stop stop there's so much no
no okay at least there's no
[Music]
Lava all right s sampai wants to sleep
if she wants to sleep I should really
sleep because she's a big senpai I
should just put my bed out right now and
sleep out of respect otherwise it would
be not respectful I should be polite to
my Senpai and fulfill their wish to
sleep let me just never mind I don't
have a bed with me too bad too too
bad can I fix it it came out of the hole
Yeah I can fix this one I fixed it yeah
now s
P just this
once I'm getting
better hey yo what the [\h__\h] is
[Music]
happening
hey I don't even have to blow things
up she but there could be one right over
there too
[Music]
oh oh
wait two is maximum maybe could it
be Phoenix lck I'm using
x-ray x-ray cheat we got eight now oh my
god let's go
not a h not a h stop stop
twering my tools are breaking
[Music]
soon do I get the gold exp yeah but um
the other one is nicer
right and now about to blow up another
vein and this will be a long one
[Music]
hopefully we're going to split them
evenly between everybody but I hope I
can find a lot more so that maybe at
least uh everybody can get one piece of
um never right armor just one piece even
can I make it into gold
here
no
sad give me the gold
okay 12 then oh I need 12 in total then
okay we're close to
that would you guys say I should make an
armor piece into neide or should I make
uh a a weapon into never
right probably armor right for
[Music]
protection should probably the chest
piece are they all the same just like
four per
armor was it four yeah
[Music]
four chest gives the most bag for its
buck n
n y I fixed
it w the fixer W the
Builder W The
Miner no mining
accidents in wa's
mine oh Jinx sounds like a jinx doesn't
it
[Music]
thank you just a little bit um maybe
yeah yo I'm still getting like shocked
and but I'm I'm getting like I don't run
away
immediately
H uh wait uh wait this one's a bit more
difficult now maybe I'll stop it here
okay okay okay I think it's been long
enough one 2 three 4 One Two Three 4 One
Two Three 4 one two three four one two
three four one two three four one two
three four one two three
four three
four did only find the armor yet or did
she pick uh MAA up did you guys watch
what she's up to
oh [\h__\h] oh
[Music]
well she's at uh with MAA MAA got new
stuff when I full diamond now what
happens
how but I think it's still good to pick
up her stuff anyway oh
ah this is where I found the never ride
the never ride the never ride this is
where the found the never ride that
makes me
happy ma Got onion K assist shees that's
why they got it all
together
maybe the
[Music]
achievement for only's been 80
years oh okay uh that is the beginning
oh it will be a little bit hard to hit
it but it's
okay oopsie uh well no it will really be
hard to hit
it I can just quickly run away
[Music]
yeah come
on Yoo
my beautiful work of art once
again you guys probably see it before I
do and we still
have
uh so much more
TNT hey yo what's up what's up up kept
you waiting
huh you're another double huh
sexy
[Music]
wow now we have
wow maybe if I'm like if I don't have
anything to do tomorrow I might even go
mining for more
[Music]
actual cheats soon we have one piece of
never right for each of us uh never
never right that's not how you write it
huh never mind uh armor for each of
us never say never says you know but oh
there's more what if you want to say
never right
[Music]
sorry it took me a
while you are not blown up yet what's
wrong with that everything why can I not
shoot did I forget how to shoot
or am I doing something
[Music]
wrong
oh oh the biggest jump scare of the
[Music]
allall time for a refill of lemon water
oh dear sent me back so
far I stopped existing at that
point
why okay okay this is scary this is
really scary because I could suddenly
walk in lava
now I'm scared
[Music]
a I don't like this
um h
ah is it over for me today why is this
happening right
now can't save you from lag yeah but
like they could get me to Safe ground or
take my never right you know I don't
know
[\h__\h] the TNT nah all's lost oh
no I can't seem to move on from this
spot I'll I'll just wait for it to calm
down my Minecraft trial account has
expired what
what ah there we go maybe we're fine
now I'll stay calm and put
k
k k
[Music]
k sexy baby
one
more I can fix
these I
think yeah only one yeah this time just
one we got a lot of doubles
so oh my lag is gone I
think
y
okay any more
I feel like there's more I can smell it
I can smell it it's like Behind These
Walls may I should go that way I I'll
I'll never find my way back this is like
really confusing cuz it's
[Music]
like don't don't touch
me but okay that's where the the laa
came where I didn't want to continue
mining no it's okay maybe no need to fix
it I don't think it will be like below
any of this I don't smell it
there you think it could be I don't
smell it though I only smell
lava where didn't I fix this
now did that help
uh where's it coming
from
oh
[Music]
no I made it worse I don't know how to
put it
there can you pull up your location sure
you want to tell it to ollie or so it's
-
215 -
easy but I'm not lagging
anymore I'm
fine but my tools are breaking anyway my
tools are
breaking soon anyway so I might need to
let you guys do the rest of the m
soon or Ollie is leaving so maybe MAA I
don't know how long she wants to play
but maybe MAA can do some or I'll fix if
they have to leave then I'll give them
the never ride until that
point
[Music]
uh well even if I give her these
coordinates I should give her the
entrance entrance of the mine
coordinates
[Music]
okay yay but I just need like one more
never right until we have full uh one
full set pretty much but we'll split it
between everybody no not one full set
one wasn't that 16 ah but we're fre
people so one piece for everybody the
one piece is real
no one
check one
[Music]
check this is smile never right mine my
baby okay so I went we went not per
parallel but wait oh no yeah this is the
path but I'll go to the beginning oh no
never mind that's not the path that's
where I changed
Direction so maybe I do go this way
should I try to fix that cuz it's a
lot let me attempt really
quickly Oh I thought I saw one but it's
just the other beautiful material
[Music]
but this is eight this is eight there's
not going to be anything
here super slow reveal it's like a h
life outfit reveal
[Music]
that's one way to do
it
[Music]
h
okay bye-bye bye-bye
bye-bye okay a now it's so
dark just a few here and
[Music]
there the others they got some neide
right the Ana V group but did they just
stop after finding
two or so
[Music]
anybody who
knows oh it's about to end her stream
no I'll give her her her uh her de
bre only wait don't leave
yet oh
okay she'll find it tomorrow when she
gets into the game then I'm at the
entrance really where
is a
[Music]
oh
wait
no like this then let's make this also a
little bit more noticeable
[Music]
okay I'm at the entrance of the M
now although I'm scared will I find the
exit the real exit the portal
exit I don't know what kind of path was
it a
[Music]
Peter Griffin love
really follow the Torches did we really
put torches every oh wait oh yeah we
made a curve
here and then I'll go to TT and get exp
to fix my pickaxe really
quickly and then I can continue with MAA
maybe if she wants to no
pressure ah this is where we chose left
or right and we first or was that a
different was that when we were with MAA
it's this way
ah I'm at
portal Ollie Ollie Ollie Ollie oh oh
there you are back yay yay yay yippe so
wait how much did you got I have 11 now
I had to stop because I need to fix my
tools but I can get more because I still
have a lot of
[Music]
PLT you are a Monster yeah I'm going to
get you could have done it all by
yourself look at you yeah but okay let's
see I think uh four I give you four
pieces for now so you can make one piece
of armor four piece that's so much
though no I think I can get one piece of
armor for all of
us MAA you and me you are amazing no no
I did it with you you helped me get the
TNT and you help me build like a lot of
the path so yeah I'll continue
though okay oh so are are are you going
to like uh still are you still going to
stream or hey y wait Oh I thought that
was uh yeah I'm going to continue
streaming oh okay I think I'm going to
end it here okay thank you for the
debris though I'm going to write this in
my diary are you going to be there
tomorrow early on like with the weather
fight cuz that's happening tomorrow
weather fight wait that's
tomorrow wait what
time probably like 8:00 p.m. or
so oh 7 8 p.m.
yeah I think I can go okay I'll be there
too
yeah yay now I'm going to find MAA
again oh she said she'll be signing off
I think she's at the diary section her
too oh oh let me give her the pieces
too
yeah yeah
okay okay okay okay diary section daily
diary daily Diaries
diaries I can't believe I can't believe
the weer is tomorrow yeah and so I think
that means that the Ender Dragon Is The
Day After
Tomorrow wow
MAA hi are you already
ending not yet not yet well I'll give
you four four pieces of never ride so
you can make one piece of never ride
armor and you fulfilled the uh the
mission with this yay oh thank
you thank you so much wait is this
that's all you need for one right guys
one four blocks of ancient debris for
one part one armor right yes one
armor I'll continue mining but yeah um I
don't know what are you planning to do
for the rest of your stream
MAA well I think I'm just be safe
because I just died one
so I don't know if I'm going to the yeah
you really need to be careful just for
the yeah I need to be careful true so
right now maybe I'm just grening uh in
this place maybe to upgrade my my weapon
my armor kind like that now maybe Kyla
can um will go online later and join me
or so I don't know all right I wish you
the best thanks for hanging out today
with
me thank you
K oh and Ma tomorrow probably around 7 8
or 900 p.m. is probably when they're
going to do the Wither fight
J 7 yeah 789 they didn't have a proper
time yet but I think it's just like a
gold golden hour like the usual prime
time for
jst oh
okay so maybe I'll see you guys
there yeah have fun with the ancient
debris you too you too yay
[Music]
so Ollie Ollie
yeah don't think you understood that you
guys say I need also gold don't worry
guys first of all I'm going to get
myself a total of 16 pieces of never
right just for
myself a 16 ancient debris I guess 16
you said right and then we'll take care
of the rest I am motivated now I have it
all figured out I'm fine I just need to
go to TT
first yeah I'm going to show up tomorrow
with a full armor of never right I'm
hungry I'm so hungry for
never I want to flex [\h__\h]
yeah yeah I have a full diamond armor
too so I can put it on top of that right
it has to be
Diamond the base has to be
Diamond don't die yeah I'll try I'll
I'll still be careful you know I'll be
careful
you need
trim I need what do you mean I need
trim what does that mean I forgot what
that
means I don't need trims right I I don't
need to flex [\h__\h]
that a template you need a
template Tri I don't know what you guys
are saying right
now
a well I'll I'll be able to build it
right
whatever in any case I'll be able to
build it I
[Music]
hope make more fire portion
portions I've got two more and I think
generally I didn't really need them I'm
I'm more calm and like used to it now
like I'm in the zone you
[Music]
know oh but before I go back the
existing nether ride that I have before
I go back into the nether I'm going to
put it in my house don't don't let me
forget
that even if it's just free for
now not not to apply never right to
Diamond Armor you need a smithing
template well where do I get
that where do I get
[Music]
that Bastion chest well good that I know
where there is a
Bastion
Sebastian I'm coming for you a certain
type oh could it be the one that we
found oh do you think Kyla already has
it Kyla has does she have it
though I want to find um never right
first
though let's find
it might check if someone else have got
one you can duplicate them Kyla has
it okay okay all right uh zombies please
not zombies uh anything really
[Music]
hello oh but I need um to have it in my
other hand
right
okay get
[Music]
gunpowder yeah I still have enough
TNT I don't think there's really much
gun powder here
now you'll need diamonds to D
them 10 template Ingot and diamond armor
and how many diamonds to dup them tell
me tell
me diamonds that's the one thing I don't
really actually I have like a few from
the missions and I'll get more tomorrow
after completing these missions 6 seven
oh I might have seven I might I might um
I think I think I have seven at
least from betting too oh yeah yeah I
have like more oh yeah I do I do I
do okay seven to duplicate no I wonder
if she got it from that Bastion that we
found did she go in there in her solo
stream crazy
lady is this healing my
pickaxe if yes then very slowly oh no it
is okay I saw it move
now oh it's one template per oh armor
piece oh my God okay so I need 28 what
the [\h__\h] okay I might be fine I feel
like I have maybe 27 or so then we'll
[Music]
see I'll be
fine yeah
first case Kyla can lend me a few
diamonds maybe
[Music]
maybe she has a lot she definitely can
yeah me and Kyla are on good
terms that's that's really important for
a game like
Minecraft got to be good with the right
people the right
[Music]
gang you think neite was too easy to
make that's I guess that's why they
changed it but I don't know if it really
was too easy I don't think so it takes a
while to
get they could have maybe made it a a
little bit more difficult but making so
many different templates man to you have
to will will one Bastion have like one
template then that's crazy then you
should be fine with one template not
four different
ones that kind of
[Music]
sucks it was a controversial
change
[Music]
mhm Bastion super dangerous as well is
it more dangerous than the Fortress cuz
I've been to the Fortress and I don't I
don't think I ever entered a Bastion
before even in non
hardcore way
more have I been do you guys
know very
dangerous piglins all the piglins do
they attack me even though I wear
gold pigling brutes oh she
you can cheat it with platforms oh Lou
died in the Bastion oh that's how she
died in
hardcore they attack you just for being
inside no okay well at least that means
you can put off your golden boots and
replace them with diamond ones
[Music]
might get
um some more iron to fix the shovel too
oh I have some
iron cuz I might still need it as
well it helps to Lava bucket drown the
Basin oh okay but I wouldn't want to do
that
alone now I do wonder where she got the
templates from
so wait I don't think you guys answered
my question do you get one template from
one Bastion and then you have to find a
new Bastion or are they all in one
[Music]
Bastion one template and ah you get one
template oh and it doesn't say like
template for boots template for head or
whatever it's just one
template oh and then you make more no
no hold
on I thought it was like a Schnitzer
[Music]
Y come on I need a few more
just a few more
[Music]
more a little easier like that I think
even if it requires diamonds
no no no it's okay I won't go to the
Bastion because uh I'll just copy what
Kyla has with
Diamonds oh that's how use up all my
diamonds ah have diamonds for one day
lose diamonds immediately on something
but but it will be worth it for the
never ride I just it would just be such
a Pity if I
die but I have really high defense with
the never right right so I'll be more
difficult to take
[Music]
down more gambling I'm not going to go
gambling
[Music]
yeah I'm putting it to
use oh my God come
on yeah I know where my boots are I'm
not looking looking for my boots I know
they're in in one of my chests for
safekeeping wither has with effects with
take a milk oh don't worry I feel like
tomorrow there'll be a lot of milk
prepared Maybe by other members or so
other I can just quickly get it
from the cows at paa's Farm I think she
has
[Music]
cows I should get feather
falling feather falling on my booies
would be nice yeah wait once you put
neite on your armor can you not enchant
it
[Music]
anymore you can oh okay then I'm I'm
going to put fed falling on the
booies for
[Music]
sure she I saw Kyla has F falling she
has all the good stuff
man she knows exactly what is needed and
what's popular she knows it
all the ones that can change appearance
she found it while exploring in the
ne is that never the only place where
you can find
those change appearance so I can copy
those too or is it more expensive to
copy
those oh sass got blacksmith
right boats and jungle yeah I feel like
I heard about that that there's three
different places or so where you can
find different kinds of
trims ah wait trims template ah never
mind that's two different things right
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah we were talking
about different things
[Music]
now you know they change stuff like that
but the one thing I really wish they
would change in Minecraft or upgrade is
that we can have more than one type of
Shield there's only this wooden wooden
iron shield now but why can't we not
make like a diamond Shield it's so
[\h__\h]
lame it's so lame like imagine your
whole armor your swords everything is
diamond and then your freaking one
Shield it just looks so dumb why is
there oh no
[Music]
what
what I'm sorry kfp I want to save you
but I couldn't I was put into a
difficult situation ation there hurts my
heart what have they done to
you
why no zombies shall ride my kfp
chickens breaks my heart I didn't I I I
was trying to free
you the patterns on the Shields and no I
want
diamond
[Music]
diamond I want a shiny Diamond Shield is
that too much to
[Music]
ask Shield kind of useless yeah I don't
even use it much either but hi toad yeah
that was kind of toad is kind of Tosh of
me think I I think that's enough
[Music]
if you could upgrade yeah that's also a
thing you can't even put any
enchantments on the shield either no
diamond shield no enchantments what why
why what are they thinking what why do
they hate Shields so much
the
[Music]
[\h__\h] Shield haters
man foreign oh
yeah or like something like when you hit
the shield it like throws you back what
do you call that kind of throw back I
don't
know what do you call that
effect you know what I mean
[Music]
there's some more gunpowder in there now
but I'm fine thank
you anything else I need from here
maybe oh the beds are
here
um I'm going to take some of them
back H oopsie
[Music]
to where they came
from ah wait I can
[Music]
maybe do this
yeah maybe I'll come back
[Music]
again
Trident Trident never ride and Trident
would be the sickest [\h__\h]
ever empty vials stack
oh oh
[Music]
makes no sense why do they only stack if
they're
empty IRL that would not really work
depending on the shape of them but no no
[Music]
no good stuff what's what's here by the
oh just outside oh
what level is this on
79 don't forget to put yes yes I'll go
to PO house bring back the beds or stop
by my house to put away the netherite
and some other useless
[\h__\h] uh if I have anything and then I'll
maybe put the empty potion thingies back
to the potion
[Music]
maker all right uh where are we H this
way are you guys surprised that I'm
still not dead did you think I would
die early on or so it's only my second
day though but yesterday I could have
totally died because it was kind of
crazy and today also though like I've
been through some
EV We we played it kind of
risky oh wait I was going to go this
way oh but actually
first yesterday was scary m not surpris
at all oh look there's so many free
potions that I could
take yeah MC veteran I really am at this
point I'm more like used to MC I just
had to like get back into it but like
Ana for example is kind of a
noob it was funny yesterday what was it
like she didn't know pretty basic things
cute
cute the gold okay 23 Gold and oh the
other diamonds I think are in the other
chest right mm mhm
let's leave this behind maybe the iron
is
unnecessary the
Flint I
guess the Axe really in the never is
actually also actually useless too so
let's leave it for safekeeping in case I
die I'll at least have the axe to turn
back
to yeah
gun powder no no no no no I have TNT
plenty you've been the most safe all
almost died when she went off on her own
you mean
today after she left
me I swear that girl the Mauna situation
also I feel like that was such a waste
like such a Mauna is a good Minecraft
player and dying like that is yeah
really unfortunate now she has to be
really be careful he they already
restocked with so many beds was that
suicide
simply cuz it was suddenly empty but I
think I think it's
um not so necessary anymore unless
somebody wants to farm never right with
beds I don't think anybody's that crazy
I can't believe we almost did that but
the gunpowder was right at my fingertips
so writing that mission stre come oh
let's see if she's still standing there
I'll ask her if she needs
[Music]
help also ah the chest I wonder if did
all get the chest and give the stuff to
Luna because that's where the mushroom
was
[Music]
you need
help with
writing yeah I'm writing right now you
can write it in English
probably oh I mean Japanese seems
fun I can just learn at the same
time yeah yeah yeah what is
um what is the the
nether you mean the never right that we
got NE right yeah uh just write wait I I
can send it to you in Discord and you
can copy paste it oh yeah please thank
you I don't really know what they call
it in Japanese either but if you if we
just write not ancient debris in
Japanese but just never ride they should
they should know what we're talking
about
NE
yeah yeah just in Katakana
oh okay that's all right it's just done
evolved form of ancient
debris copy the one on the mission I
don't know how to copy it can you like
copy paste
that already done okay you got all the
others too I guess you did you ever end
up uh killing a
ghast no I guess but the potion did you
make the potion ah Ana
Ana the
[Music]
chat wait I I'm writing you sending you
the fixed one in Discord that's that's
how ancient debris is in
nongo what should I write
potion uh wow I feel so cool writing in
kanji even though it just got
P
pull
oh my keyboard
[Music]
po like that potion
po
potion okay potion
[Music]
okay I forgot what just I just
write those threee things or did you do
anything
else oh wait are you writing this into
the diary I thought we have
into the mission
book H we have we have our own book yeah
but uh the diary is just for writing
like General things like what you did
today and then there's the mission book
but you can copy paste what you wrote in
the diary and then put it into the
mission
book oh yeah this is just for you know
today I went out with this person and I
did this and that cuz peka will read it
in the beginning of her stream
[Music]
M okay okay okay so so
basically wait where where M no not here
it's
outside around the
corner in in the right side book first
uh you can see that they write the date
and then they write their name so you go
to the very last page page and then
write the date and the name and
everything you did Ol wrote it in
English
so you can also write it in English
probably okay okay oh in order you know
how to take it you can write it first oh
I'm not done yet for today so oh okay
yeah take the book and then I'm going to
take the book yeah just copy paste what
you wrote in the diary or write it in
English
ah did you get the Soul Sand too copy
from
[Music]
Ollie no
no
no I think you
yeah yeah yeah we got that on our own
kind of so yeah maybe it doesn't count
okay
not yeah are you going to be okay I
canot cop from this from you can't from
my own place oh oh and just copy from
Discord or so
again
yeah always say found anci like
20 yeah I found I found uh a lot a lot
of ancient
[Music]
debris yeah I just wor oh she she wrote
it ancient debris in
English yeah that's fine that's fine I'm
sure it's fine yeah I have 28 diamonds
we have enough
yeah this
good
okay okay going to go back in I think I
cannot see I cannot just MAA just MAA
and when you're done you put it back
onto the table where right click and
then your diary you have to put it back
into the box where it says put book
here oh
okay if you need something you can just
write in the
chat U good
night okay U
bye-bye Bye Mom I got to I got to go get
some never right wait it's this
way it's time it's time for
me to get a full set of neveron mhm
[Music]
mhm a few more of
these just so that you guys are
calm pour one out for shba no I'll drink
it when I'm in there though for sub
compai
yeah full never at time let's freaking
go I'll do my
[Music]
best I'll try not to die I'll try uh
I'll genuinely try where did we
go uh was it the door
no that's
where uh the first trip no was it was it
was it for the
door oh hey this is someone's never ride
Farm
H let let me take a look they made it
right here which of course you can do
too yeah I don't know why I went so
far I want to look
want take a
look who going so
deep Ah that's how you do it wait they
didn't blow it
up that's why it looks so neat because
they didn't blow it up yet is it free to
blow it up or what is
she did did you just make this for
people to blow it up on their
own Oh you mean they actually strip my
wow but this is like a template for me
to use now can I blow up their strip
mind cuz they're done
here oh I totally want to blow this up
but no they're too close together
[Music]
like I kind of want to blow it
up it's such perfectly neat
lines
damn let like to ah yeah right yeah true
cuz they're so close together like they
should have all the dees from the these
trunks at least on this
height yeah cuz there could there could
be below and above
still they're done with it yeah I still
feel like maybe I'm doing something
inappropriate ah they made it so pretty
I wonder how much lava they had to cover
up or if they were lucky and didn't do
didn't have to do
much blow one up to test at the end
there was a few um like uh
unmined
blocks god dude okay I'm leaving I'm
leaving okay okay okay
okay every end is lava is that where
they stopped
always yeah Ana was watching a moment
ago I guess she's not watching
anymore let me go first no no you're in
my
face block like deep slate that's a bit
blast resist oh maybe
what what the myai is not online anymore
I guess she's reading super chats
[Music]
okay uh so is this
where is this where I went though I
don't know where I
[Music]
went do you guys know where I went if I
went for one of
these let's see ah yes okay this way
never mind guys I found my
way found my way
[Music]
oh yeah yeah yeah we went down there cuz
I was like oh did they start no never
mind they didn't start
here and then we went here and yeah
okay G oh I'm sad I thought I could play
a little bit more with
MAA that was not the case
pleas all right my home my Paradise how
we going to continue this in which
direction this was too low
anyway but I guess I'm going to go to
where I put that torch is it this no
this hello you're freaking me out you
scare me
here though I put a torch where I wanted
to continue I think there must be over
here no or
there
no ma ma rated me yay thank
you thank you eat food yeah good
idea very much appreciated Teddy Maki
[Music]
maybe
here uh well it doesn't really matter I
guess but that might be
it o memberships free memberships let's
go eight that's too low again is this
really where I went H or did I like the
torch was somewhere else
[Music]
maybe why did I stop there
why would I stop
here let's let's get higher can we get
much
[Music]
higher why is there a reason why I
stopped
here I don't see
lava yet and we're in the middle of a
chunk
divider there was lava hm H 10
15 so far so
good okay more membership yay you guys
are so generous kfp so
[Music]
generous I kind of want to make the
ceiling a little bit higher so it's also
easier to
escape m
in case of a
[Music]
disaster okay maybe
here all right is this it this is the
end of a chunk right the end the corner
The Edge the yellow
line yeah okay
I wish I had my phone with me right now
then I could I could look for tangents
on my
phone did you guys see the whole life
magical girl
thing it looked so cute I watched the
the whole like animated trailer
thingy I don't really know much about
the project because I'm not
involved but it's so cute maybe one day
I can be involved into something like
that too I don't know really cute
yeah must have gone a lot of budget into
that because animation is really
expensive and it looked really high
quality
[Music]
I feel like M Senai if we compare this
to like uh maduka Maga like M sampai was
like the the blonde curly twin tail girl
because of the sex
appeal also I was a bit confused um they
drew them like like uh one of them or so
was in their default outfit yeah
Mommy sorry mommy for dying uh and some
were some were in like a casual one like
it was really all over the place bada
bada I wonder if that was their
preference their own preference or if
the or if I want to fix that but now how
do I fix it
[Music]
wait I need to get
closer uh I wonder if maybe it was like
an image kind of thing like oh we think
it's would look better cuz we want you
to be the sexy magical girl so we want
you to wear this or that I don't know if
that's how they were
thinking I have an idea
[Music]
maybe and then go here and then
how how does this
work block it closer a then remove your
wait what we remove this okay I'm
here is it is it in front
no you think it's a big one okay maybe
I'll stop
there Lava Lake OH Oh you mean ocean of
lava
oh okay 1 2
[Music]
three wait so out of strip mining that
much how much did they get in the
end I'm really curious how effective
efficient their method was
where are the Insiders two each they
they got four each two two or four each
maybe four in total two
each yeah that doesn't sound very
efficient
shees even I found I think more just by
like making these paths they were kind
of
unlucky but they fulfilled the mission
yeah that's why we blessed yeah that's
right
baby that's right
[Music]
oh only one block
left I don't know if I want to CL blow
blow it up that close to the
entrance let's not
let's go where's it
happening
there no I'm missing all the
fun I don't see anything yet but there
has to be
something oh
let's [\h__\h]
go a
triple I need to
[\h__\h] free baby is that like the maximum
I thought to was the max but I was
proven
wrong oh my mama M momy Mama to are you
watching are you seeing this
hey where is it like this
okay I have four already now I
started ah wait and I have uh two or
three three in my inventory so we have
seven in my chest I mean we have seven
oh you just spawned there or what I'm
going to blow you up to to get of that
TNT stay there my friend stay
there I to try to fix that
maybe looks
[Music]
manageable let's [\h__\h]
go it eight
[Music]
this oh my God is it is it going to blow
him
up oh he took that
oh oh he did realize that came from
me it's okay
[Music]
doing this to collect 5ou why would I
want 5,000 of these who did that
KY
oh oh my
why what for a beacon you need 5,000
what what do you mean
5,000 now
[Music]
there we
go 36 for one block one and
164 what took her half a year just for
Flex she lived in the never that's why
she's so calm now I get it yeah okay no
wonder she was so calm
yesterday no
wonder okay got to look closely it
Blends in so
much maybe make it a bit
[Music]
brighter oh it went way further so and
that does look like a big pool
[Music]
M what have I
uncovered as if it was
sauna
man no I envy her for like finding
things to
do constantly that like make her feel
like she wants to play more like I'm for
me it was
[Music]
over whenever I I found some new biomes
and
whatever
[Music]
okay can I fix
this not really
[Music]
looks difficult U but I want to
check if there's anything
there don't want to miss out on
anything
ah yeah no
that's ah those you oh oh no probably
not oh but I can go a little bit past
it you guys want me to drink the potion
right oh okay
okay for
[Music]
you oh my god what have I done what have
I
[Music]
Unleashed there might be ancient fre
somewhere there well maybe not because
it's all lava I don't
know I don't
know yeah uh let's leave that uh in
peace see nothing happened I'm fine
guys but where do I go next which
direction next or should I go like from
here
Salon are you looking for your family
member that I
killed he's gone he's long
gone follow your never right
Instinct I do have some some feeling
here and there
[Music]
it would help if I had a directional
sense of where like in my mind I wish I
had a map where like cuz I've been like
not doing it parallel so I might meet my
other tunnel if I go in one of these
directions is what I'm
thinking uh what if I go far
enough look I'm
[Music]
I'm I have I'm also scared to not find
the exit
M five blocks plus the four at home nine
oh my God I just need less than half of
it 1 14 let's go
[Music]
here oh why am I doing double
go right by 12 blocks and explode
parallel
oh
oh oh so go like this way
now yeah I already went too far but yes
that would be like almost like strip
mining strip
blowing strip
exploding yeah let's go with strip strip
exploding
oh oh I don't know if that was 12 but
approximately right I mean one 2 three
four five 6
S8
yeah pretty
much you think it will become one big
Hall will it open up is this 12 kind of
the how far the radius of the explosion
should go normally
[Music]
sorry about I don't like
that how do
I oh oh it's not coming to
me I want to put it right there though
let me put it there how do I do it
might be another lava
pool
a maybe I maybe this whole area is a
whole [\h__\h] lava ocean man
not hold door that is very
manageable yeah oh am I am I under the
lava
SE what is it gone is it behind this
block
[Music]
yeah oh
can I fix it I don't think so those the
L though yeah it's
above so should I just blow this Hall up
maybe one
[Music]
maybe I should go a little bit lower
actually not to age but like you
know what did did it spawn in my hall
does that
[Music]
happen no
way okay but it sounded like it saw me
or
so cuz like it sounded like it was about
to
shoot okay a qu
[Music]
dude oh maybe we'll meet it now if I
blow this
up am I going to be
fine this way in case I need to
[Music]
escape you should be
fine lava oh I don't go ah
okay I have to I have to fill that one
up I have
to did I waste a lot of my was it just
all covered in in lava over there no
like several of
my maybe I maybe I want to go somewhere
else this is like bad
area yeah I see it
[Music]
nice just one
though
wait does it burn does it disappear in
lava after it's
mined hopefully
not we are at
6 6 I guess yeah no it floats
okay as it should as it should
[Music]
oh I see several okay one two here one
there okay okay
okay oh my God oh
my oh Jesus loves me even though I am an
atheist thank you
Jesus thank you I appreciate it nine oh
my God I almost have
it I have three at home right so we have
12 now and then that is another one
um could there be like one under here
[Music]
I can try to get rid of
this
yeah we're going to fix it I need to get
a bit higher
maybe
[Music]
nice I
see ah no that's not it
no can I put it
[Music]
there just swim what what do you mean no
is it really dead
safe your armor takes
damage I
don't but can I so would I even be able
to cover it up it's not necessary to
swim in it wait how about we just do
[Music]
uh
there thereare
thereare do it coward KY does it all the
time
what the portion H gr not is good wait
wait
wait I don't know if I feel mentally
capable of
that I just want
to okay let's
see wait how much do I have
now nine okay so I should pick it up and
get up to
10 10 don't Ste don't take this away
from me all right
lava mining right here is kind of crazy
OMG all
[Music]
right give
meit did I get the other one yeah I
think I got them all
yo I'm
fine wait one more and I have a full
armor
you got 15
e yeah yes so one more oh [\h__\h] oh
[\h__\h] got 24 weapon flag I
might I might Now cover the roof okay
wait
[Music]
it just doesn't want to go
away I mean I don't think there's the
chunk you know there's probably no more
there I don't smell
anymore there's probably a hole in the
middle
but I do wonder if my TNT went any
further and if it's just covered up by
this no no I don't think it did no no no
no
no it's my Phoenix
Instinct that's right and my Phoenix
instinct tells
me to
continue
[Music]
um from
around here into that
way I think the Lava is like chilling
there so I feel like you know it should
be like here and we want to try 11 is
fine
maybe or
12 she I can't believe it I can't
believe
it I don't even want to announce it to
everybody that I did it
I just want to show up tomorrow and
surprise everybody with
it
chill no go away
no no I didn't choose a good path it
[Music]
seems I want to blow up bom is
place okay I'll go to like here for now
just small steps is okay
[Music]
too her place just seems so free of
uh was that too
close so free of lava but maybe they
just covered it up
nicely no I swear Kyla cannot do this to
me if KY okay I can see KY showing up
with full never right armor tomorrow as
well although who knows if she'll be
there at the time
but no no no no no no no no
no oh okay just a
small bit chck
[Music]
small
TN that's it
[Music]
no but that's where it ended anyway
right my little small small
TNT
house so I have enough for full full
never right armor I still need to get
the templates from the um from the Lady
of all ladies but I'm going to go how
many more do I need for the
sword two
also one TNT is
left did you count the explosions oh
there it is you you are
genius four okay we'll get four more
easy I have nothing else to do anyway oh
there's more than one there
more than one
left but do we get
any
no no it doesn't look like it I don't
smell it
either but I kind of smell it in that
direction uh nine that's too low
[Music]
yeah no
maybe you think I'm too low you think
what 15 is really the
best okay that just makes me feel like
I'm getting closer to the lava
pools cuz how I'm imagining although I
might be very wrong with
it how I'm imagining it is
that there is
H the lava always will have a certain
amount of blocks under it but what do I
know I don't really
know that that was my impression so
far a guys I'm fine
[Music]
no have you learned nothing
H yeah I mean that was bound to happen
at some point and I'm really confused
where I am and where the exit Let's Get
Closer to the
[Music]
exit is it like no that's uh oh
[\h__\h] m
wait don't
fret we we I see a lot of torches there
that's a good sign cuz I generally
didn't put many torches until now but we
did before yeah this is the exit okay
let's make another one like close to the
exit where oh this is 10 let's make one
close to the
exit check
boots they're fine
maybe this way I don't think we did much
in that direction only that way I
think could be good I know about the
potion I know
[Music]
I want to
live
risky I want to feel the
[Music]
excitement I want to feel the frill and
no cheap frill at that ah ah ah ah wrong
[Music]
wrong I feel like we're so close but I I
don't think this is a good area
never
was I'm going to go to water Senai house
not house but strip
mining uh
mine
oh I'm not going to blow up her nicely
lined up strip mines because they're too
beautiful
but I'm going to go to the end of
it and continue
There got 20 and decided it
sucks yeah no not I mean yeah there's
there's an ancient debris there but
uh only with a lot of pain in the
ass
uh where was it
uh where did she do it here
[Music]
yeah store the debris you already
have yeah okay
[Music]
nobody take
it this is
W only me online anyway hey yo everybody
left this is wow
time wait for Kyla it will be early in
the morning right early early early what
time is it in IND in Indonesia
a should just
started I wonder what's her plan for
today don't don't don't give her too
many good
ideas two oh okay that's not really
morning yet
okay so I wanted to go
here it's 16
even how about
here feels good
I smell
it yeah smells quite
good the fragrance of
success my eyes are starting to feel
funny you don't you're not even going to
move towards
me don't know how to fix it
1 2 three 4 One 2 three 4 One 2 three 4
One 2 three 4 1 2 three 4 One 2 three 4
One 2 3 4 1 2 3 4 1 2 3 4 1 2 3 4 1 2 3
4 1 2 3 4
oh
oopsie I'll fix that oh [\h__\h] I made it
so
ugly sorry sorry
sorry I see
[Music]
one I want to fix that
no the XP
[Music]
burnt
nice I wonder if what Theus Empire is
planning to come back
here then she would be surprised at what
she's
seeing uh ah oh oh
oh hi n Uno uh is this really where I
ended it where I
[Music]
stopped what do you think is there more
behind
[Music]
oh a what a pain in the ass man nah
there can't be I don't think there can
be something spawned and it
despawned double check double
check where did the pig go I saw it or
was it like a fat Morana
where did it go to the
side no where they spawned SP be I'm
going to close it off or maybe leave a
window but it will look a little bit
nicer if I close it off again maybe
[Music]
like this yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
that's good then
yeah no no no I mean yeah I could cover
it up completely but I I do feel like at
least
I you know I don't know I'm not hiding
my crime completely it's not even a
crime I want to blow this up but no a
that's where a chunk ends right
H want to blow these
up
Dino maybe just one maybe just one
[Music]
me just one just one just one
not this lande why not oh is this
like
no not the last one feels like too close
to
Lava
smell wait I disconnected my
headphones another Lane right next to
yeah but they're
what I I want the
space okay I'll go to the last
one oh yeah right no oh never mind yeah
I guess there wouldn't be any Dees in
this line
really I mean there could but the
chances are
low is there lava right
[Applause]
here
yes m
what
what I'm fine but why I I I covered it
up and it still came back out it like
destroyed the block was it lag or
so we just nobody will ever know about
[Music]
this I just want like what threee more
just free more but uh not sure where to
do it okay have an idea have idea I have
idea I have idea
we turned right and then
left so I don't know what if I
could I hear so much lava though [\h__\h]
what if I go like down
here or
[Music]
that works right
okay here
right or or here was it here here I
[Music]
think the wa
path wa DLC to this strip mine
you guys going to buy the
[Music]
DLC DLC cancelled that sounds not good
looks not
good
oh I can't oh maybe I should have stayed
in the wa mine but I feel like I didn't
know anymore where to where to do it I
didn't know
[Music]
anymore just dig down straight down
right
no wait
[Music]
what's that path what about
here this is calling
me
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
[Music]
no go away evil evil must be
purged I see how it
is as long as my golden boots don't
break I'm
happy that was not it
either feel like I'm getting worse at
this now cuz I I just need to go for
it m
[Music]
I don't know how about this way or from
here no not with these holes right and
that biome is right there but probably
not
underneath let's
try I just want to safely get down to
level 15 not minus 15 just
15 not
um not here why
not what's bad about this place tell me
the
meta teach
me that that is U sad to see
but I'm not giving up
[Music]
yet Kyla s and kiaa lck
gone no I would not blame her for that
that's just how things go
[Music]
sometimes remind me guys when I'm done
here I need to fix a date for next week
collab cuz I just uh like remembered it
but I know I will forget it
again I know
me thank you notification service of kfp
I'm getting
hungry or at least I don't know if it's
really hunger it's just my left side of
my
tummy is hurting a little bit I'm
probably a little bit
[Music]
hungry well I hear the lava really
loudly this doesn't feel like a good
sign with these
blocks
maybe in a different
direction should have a snack
yeah the difficulty that I feel with
like healthy snacks like cucumber and oh
my God look at my pickaxe again
again doing so
bad and the difficulty with this
oh what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] the
difficulty with it is that
um
I I I would want to prepare it freshly
if I prepare it at the beginning of the
stream then the cucumbers are just not
going to be so nice anymore if I would
want to do like
cucumbers with some salt I would love to
eat that right now but I'd want to make
it like
freshly or
maybe what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
my previous place was perfect I don't
like it was
perfect
but maybe I'll go straight for a
while that's another
hole and a lot of [\h__\h] lava
H
[\h__\h] I could cross over
but I don't have that much power anymore
in my pickaxe either which way was it
I need to recharge it again no I'm going
to go anyway one more time into the old
mine I guess
yeah damn
it where did I
go oh did we actually go through the
door this way
right yeah
back to the wa
mine it was much safer you think
[Music]
so yeah I don't want to like mine too
much now anyway if I want to keep some
of
the
uh pickaxe power
then it's better
to
continue and just make another small
tunnel small small tunnel even small
small tunnel is good tunnel tunnel
tunnel did this way did that way too
much lava over there and then I think
from there I went back to the right side
again
too where could I go have I gone from
the middle path to the
left like from here to the
[Music]
left not
really let's give it a
[Music]
try and
eat I I have fire potion on me right now
activate it as we speak
[Music]
eight
10 sorry guys I'm kind of boring
today I'm just
chilling ah I feel like I have tangents
but I can't remember them if there's
something you want me to talk about let
me know
[Music]
oh we don't want Tang we want gaming hey
y That's weird for kfp to say normally
you always enjoy my tangents what's
wrong what happened you
sick sick of
me okay I see any new diet Pizza ideas
that pizza that I made was not a diet
Pizza by the way but I do want to make
that pizza that I linked in the pre-
chat
previously
oh what
[Music]
what I was almost
there where I wanted to do it
I don't know if I can fix it
no
no Bruce Jed Le no why do so many of my
viewers go to the
Army is this what happens when you have
a mostly male fan
base they leave you for the
Army why do you love the Army more than
me
no don't
go why do you
go we don't have an
option yeah that [\h__\h]
sucks
man but it's so sad to go say goodbye
and then you're going to be gone for so
long too right oh I see I closed this
off probably for a reason
come on I just need this one more good
tunnel or
so probably close it off because of lava
but might as well blow it
up you served 12
years that's like more than what you
have to do
right so shees thanks for your services
even though I'm not from your country I
[Music]
think wait I was no wait I'm on nine I
didn't realize
ah
H I thought I was high
enough
Kaa CA but hey there was no Lava why did
I stop there
right
oh
really H
well I wish you the best of luck but for
now until Autumn there's still some time
so let's make the best of it and but
then
afterwards once you when you're in can
you still watch sometimes like on the
weekend or
so or is it not possible at all
[Music]
good night thanks for
watching oh yeah last night I logged
in uh to Minecraft late at night I just
to check something because I thought I
forgot writing something into the
mission book and Ena was online and I
was like Ena what are you doing and she
wasn't streaming and she was like oh
yeah I'm just making a fishing house I'm
like oh okay and then I'm just checking
what I wanted to check and a few moments
later Kyla joins and she's also like why
the [\h__\h] are you guys
online same to you lady oh wa I'm too
high we we all just all had the same
reaction to each
other wait so did you
[Music]
answer oh I'm catch some strings but not
as regularly okay that sounds fine that
sounds like at least to
compromise I hope you
can how long do you think you'll be gone
H although I don't know man at this
point if it's like one or two
years oh this is a good one this is a
good one guys
e yeah it's a good
one no Lava no Lava so
[Music]
far training will take some months
probably and deployment no idea yeah
especially in training um I guess not
not really do you have more freedom in
training or is it the other way
around oh God yeah my pickaxe all right
then we better find those how many more
do I want
threee in this one tunnel we better find
them
okay I'm going
to I'm going to do
it mind the quartz oh true but no maybe
this maybe this is the one maybe this is
the one time
of my
[Music]
dreams for me it was less freedom in
training training is the
worst oh man one two
three one two three
four what's your plan for today
[Music]
I'm
curious oh and peace some I'll probably
have more free
time
[Music]
not let's make it peaceful how do you
mind can I just yeah
okay let's be peaceful guys be nice to
each
other don't do anything
stupid like me who cannot count but like
everything looks the same to me and the
colors are blending into one thing in my
brain oh I'm out of TNT oh I oh the
tunnel was way too long
okay maybe if this is not satisfying I
can go get some more TNT and finish this
tunnel I see
one
hey
hey out of
[Music]
tent I I I wonder if the pig has enough
durability even if you do find Asian de
oh right okay let me mine this stuff
[Music]
here all that
helps all that helps a lot oh this is
kind of faster than the farm I
think
y or as Ollie would say yippee
all
[Music]
right preparing stuff to fight the
weather
o like
what if she start streaming now she
might stream all the way until the
Wither fight right cuz like it's might
[Music]
be yeah maybe around something like in
12 or like maybe for 15 16 hours hey
don't push
me that's very
possible not so lucky this time
huh it's probably right behind the
wall
no upgrade oh oh yeah I wanted to ask if
I can copy your template I have the
diamonds what does she
mean
with upgrade
template it's always one block away yeah
[Music]
I haven't search oh she doesn't have the
template
yet oh you don't have it
yet oh maybe there is one in the Bastion
though oh Chad told me you
do we can go to the Bastion
[Music]
did I get one guide I feel like a lot of
people oh we're saying it I just F my
pickaxe
[Music]
broke I know where it is I mean I've
seen it but will I find my way back to
it
h a new one
oh it did did the Japanese members go
inside and loot it
all cuz our group did not go
[Music]
inside damn
why Minecraft why why do you make it so
much more
[Music]
difficult then but if they looted it
maybe they have the template but I
haven't heard anything about templates
by
others so one group went inside at least
yeah true
Okay I uh will go back and get some more
TNT cuz I'm not
satisfied so I guess that's her plan for
today to find the template in the first
[Music]
place this is a sign for
me to continue There
how many more do you need I think
two maybe yeah maybe
two which is really not much but then if
she doesn't have to template yet then I
cannot Maybe not maybe I cannot show up
and never ride tomorrow I don't know
would be so cool
though see she's depressed from
yesterday what why what happened she got
Dragon sickness what
maybe before the
Wither she will already have the
template and I can before the Wither
make my
[Music]
armor I think I will log out in 1 hour
or
so so
maybe before the weather fight I will be
streaming again and then if you have the
template can I copy it with my diamonds
then before the
fight
than she knows how does she
[Music]
know how does she know
maybe she was watching or chat already
told
her you think she was
watching XD
[Music]
X should I go to oh she was
wanting I feel watched and
[Music]
observed why does she not write
something in chat
I've been perceived and
witnessed I don't want to be perceived
and
witnessed wait this path down and then
straight yeah yeah yeah okay okay
okay
lurking but as you can see now I didn't
have so much problem with making another
uh mine within my mind after all so my
mine really was quite good huh should
have trusted in my mind M
abilities my M
[Music]
abilities my mind had the D
extra in German we say that
[Music]
let's bring it home and look at the
beautiful
number together and what
else what
else was what else did I come back for
ah TNT ah in that
[Music]
case ah oh
that's sorry I
M the specific special
[Music]
something you can say that to someone
that you think has talent for example
they have that special something
H I wonder how much more gunpowder I
need there I think there were there was
like 50 or so
[Music]
fedal falling can't come soon enough
[Applause]
[Music]
but that
was why was that so thin why was the the
path so
thin damn
son that was kind of
crazy my boots are
[Music]
fine oh perfect no no no yeah
perfect
damn right it's not going to happen
again don't worry I'm staying away from
it okay okay okay
okay scary
come here come to
Mama you guys know that
guy yatan I think was his
name H
it means I'm really surprised like this
is a guy who certainly is fluent in
Japanese uh lives in Japan but makes
like these like Tik toks and whatever
short videos where he speaks in this
really strong American accent Japanese
did I go the wrong
way let going going down you know wrong
way and it's so funny and he his face
and everything looks really
friendly yeah the funny blonde one
[Music]
yeah a he's Norwegian
oh
well yeah white
guy friend shaped no not friend shaped I
think he's pretty tall and and
thin he's fren he's not fren shaped I
don't remember him being friend
shaped not that there's anything wrong
with being friend shaped but I don't
remember him like that he's skinny yeah
who are you thinking
about kind of want the gold you know
yeah Mr yat yeah yeah
yeah one of those Japanese
creators non [\h__\h] guiding creators in
Japan which PewDiePie is also now one of
them damn I don't watch his videos but
he seems to be doing well he's got a
[\h__\h] baby
now oh yeah right I was going to
TT he's kind of freaking
baby it's so surreal
though like I never was a big PewDiePie
Watcher even in the past there was maybe
like a few videos like I used to watch
him a little bit more than now and now
is like never but I don't I don't
dislike him or anything if anything he's
like way more bearable
and like a cool person than many other
famous creators out there
yeah
um yeah and his content well no it kind
of changed over the years so I don't
know it changed many times I feel like
he started doing so much react content
at some
point I feel like that's when I didn't
care
anymore not that I hate react content it
just depends on the person and what they
react to
like you guys maybe heard me mention
several times now I really like Cody
Co c o d y
KO he is really funny and I do like the
content he reacts to I I avoided some of
his react content because I was like I
don't care about this I think but then I
ended up watching it anyway because I
felt like I need more Cody Co in my
veins I really like his
humor hi guys
[Music]
yeah it's Case by case but PewDiePie
yeah
well he's an interesting dude I
guess but no problem with him he's he's
chill we still got the sand here right
all
it yeah
[Music]
exchange don't we don't need that much I
guess
[Music]
M
12 I could finish that one line but
would that get me two more if I get a
double or even a triple yeah but there's
no guarantee I get anything at
[Music]
all I need to be lucky he's technically
responsible for C me who
[Music]
piepie you barely use your diamond one
yeah I mostly rely on my bow and my
arrow that's true
I mean you know I got so far I thought
might as well
right might as
well yeah all the next me yeah I think I
did hear that from PewDiePie too
yeah my favorite creators from back in
the day shall we name our favorite
creators from back in the day it was um
Community
Channel and Jenna Marbles I think that's
pretty much it I can't think of any any
others I did not watch filthy Frank at
all I did not watch
gron I did not watch
smos yeah Jenna has really missed
greatly your
loss Ryan never watched Ryan never
watched yeah the [\h__\h] I don't even want
to say it so that people don't [\h__\h]
clip it
I don't even want to say it FY Frank no
never watched Mark Player never watched
that
either loved Community Channel for real
she's also so missed both Jenna mes and
Community Chanel and Community Channel
like damn she was like teasing the [\h__\h]
out of us I feel like because like she
would stop being super active but then
she would bring out a video super rarely
and you would think oh is she back is
she back and then she never really was
back
[Music]
Vine sauce
what don't really know them Captain
Sparkles matad
pet all of these names sound a little
bit familiar
[Music]
but but how much do I have now three you
need like four right for one te I'll
make one more
[Music]
TNT Marbles and Kermit updates from
Julian yeah and I do like Julian but I
liked him more in combination with Jenna
like in combination with Jenna he was
great Al Lon is also fun but not not I
need that female charm and her humor
too ah met is the game very guy
[Music]
I don't know the best friends people
what's
[Music]
that it isn't the same out there so true
I started I need to get back into this I
forgot about this I was binge watching
some some of the podcast because the
podcasts were something I never watched
because back in the day I was like what
the [\h__\h] podcast who gives a [\h__\h]
there's nothing happening they're just
talking and yapping I didn't care about
it but now like I mean I still don't
care that much about podcast I don't go
out of my way to listen to podcast
but if it's if I can hear more of GLE
Marvel's I I thought it was good I it
would be good so I started watching some
of their podcast cuz I have so many some
of them are pretty
fun um some of them are more like boring
too but I gave it a try and then I
watched them like while I was cooking
and so on or listen to them
mostly
but then I forgot I just watched
something else and then I forgot that
that was a thing that I was
watching forgot about
[Music]
it totally forgot about
it I'll try it with this whatever oh
she's sleeping
oh does everybody have to sleep now we
just two people so it's just 50%
but
H Phil up the Frankle didn't watch him
either not really I don't really
like him I
[Music]
think professional yapper complains
about
yapping yeah I don't know podcasts are h
they don't quite charm me but I they can
be really good I'm very aware of that
and I did enjoy a bunch of the podcast
but I just don't really think about
going out of my way and looking for
podcast if it's a creator that I already
really like then I'll think about it and
the good thing is about jna Mel's
podcast is they already have they do
come with visuals like there's I I don't
even understand why you would call in a
podcast when there's a video to
it I thought podcast were supposed to
have just the
audio so I'm like how is this a
podcast what is a podcast
anyway cuz the the moment you put a
video on it I feel like I have to be
watching even if you're barely
moving I I feel like I'm missing out if
I'm not watching and I do miss out
sometimes in their podcast they do like
have some visuals that you want to
[Music]
perceive does the name come from iPod
shows oh really
oh you're always a podcast to me while
when I'm at work
yeah sometimes maybe you take a
peek when I scream did you peek when I
screamed when I fell down H tell me you
peaked I know you
did hello to all the viewers who
watching with without
watching say hi in the
chat say
hello
hello I notify you loudly something
happened I have to
[Music]
look hi what's
up all right we're going to go back into
the minds of
Moria which were around
[Music]
here did
I where did I what did I hit
there something here oh I went up there
okay
[Music]
okay you you story your never right yeah
I
did oh so
excited are you guys
excited it has to be good don't
disappoint
me should I put it right here or a
little bit further behind
cuz it has a range right maybe
[Music]
like no a let's go
please oh please be
enough and please bring me the goddess
of luck shall be with me
okay oh I still have three more
[Music]
okay blow him up blow him
up come on come
on it doesn't look good doesn't look
good what the [\h__\h] is this
but and there's so much lava
[Music]
here okay did that work I can't
see did that
work I'm doing it I'm not scared
anymore it's not even doing as much
damage as I thought it would let me
out oh the the the pure red it's kind of
scary it's like I'm
enrage I'm enraged
in
lava can I drown in this like you drown
water no cuz I don't I don't I don't see
any like bubble bubbly
things ah no don't come out from
there I just closed you off
not why the potions
[Music]
working maybe they just didn't program
that at
all the bubbles in in the
lava okay what's happening here
here
yeah okay was that worth it or is there
nothing
there I me let's let's get rid of
[Music]
this
no not necessarily worth it ah please
please please please please please
please please where did it end like here
there's still fresh loot so
Nar
[Music]
nothing but I feel like I I should blow
it up here just with one
TNT I don't
know first bust yeah but it was only a
short one
[Music]
so what what my face one and face two
look like damn you're asking some
creative questions here Mar
[Music]
friend no idea right
now don't put TNT on blacks are not
worth it oh that's why it didn't blow up
much
there cuz it's so more blast
resistant what if what if um where do I
go now I I only have three more TNT
and I need two more I could it could
happen it could
happen and then I could also just out of
desperation strip mine for the rest of
[Music]
it can I go this
way is there anything that speaks
against going this way for a little bit
I mean it's really just a little bit oh
but there's black stone
oh wait oh
interesting oh I blew it up here
too you don't have to
accommodate that much so I'm just going
to go a little bit in that direction new
chunk I told you I smell it I'm just
smelling it
free free never right free [\h__\h] never
right free never
right lucky
[Music]
Phoenix oh
small small
[Music]
explosion
there did you bring your fall leaf
clover I don't have one I don't need one
it's my
[Music]
instinct
no sometimes Phoenix Instinct also can
be wrong that was the perfect
[Music]
example just a tiny bit more space
Black
Stone but here starts a new J
no I'll go through
it one one
TNT and a big dream
[Music]
maybe you know cuz I was Bing
today betting on TNT doesn't work
anymore cuz I already used all my Bing
[Music]
power on Bing for the fighting
event strip mining it is don't don't
worry guys it won't take too
long did that sound
cool hell yeah oh
oh love when that happens well this
is what do I have this strong pickaxe
for m
show me reveal yourself to me
[Music]
should be somewhere it's got to be
somewhere a
don't hide now I'm going to get you I'm
going to get
you I can smell you stinky stinky anent
debris you're so
old you're so old I want to bathe
you and then cover my Fu self in
you come on
St the
co Somewhere Out There
[Music]
no why why is it so weak
I am mildly disappointed
now and I'm lost but that's
okay both situations could possibly be
fixed
maybe my pickaxe was so good what did it
have what do I need to recreate
mending uh Fortune free not
necessarily and what was the other thing
[Music]
efficiency free or
so all right we'll make a new
one pickaxe was also
stinky not just the ancient
[Music]
debris can I smelt the ancient debris
into never right uh patches already or
do you just go from ancient debris with
the
templates how is the
order smelt then mix with gold after
smelting it
alone on its
own sound like goof
[Music]
okay de scraps gold engot
Aha and then in order to make it into
armor for that I need the template okay
so I can make the ingots on my own
then gold ingot four
Ingot okay I'll make that that will look
good in my
[Music]
inventory just the beautiful never ride
pieces and I don't know man it's just
this one p peace I feel like
it's I I I can grasp it it's right there
I'm going to go back and get
it I'm not going to give up
[Music]
now do you think I'm just going to leave
it at this I've already
begun oh oh I was carrying it oops I've
already begun this journey wait 16 a
yeah and then there's the ones in my
home
yeah I'm not a quitter I mean this
moment I must say was a little bit
embarrassing but I'm I'd rather have
that happen than me dying that would be
more embarrassing so this is fine this
is fine
did I put it in my house
probably premeditated mder on my
pickaxe it want you like a minute well I
was in the
zone I needed an alarm or
something where is it
there 19
baby like got some good ingots too uh do
we have a furnace in here
no oh I could oh I didn't know you could
make it with black
stone guess it counts as a
stone did you guys know that I don't
think most people probably don't attempt
to do it that
way oh I want a house made out of never
bricks wouldn't that be
cool wait I can make a bunch more uh of
gold
inets
yeah actually maybe a bit
more
nice 37
now
mhm ah hey I have Fortune free here at
least I don't need to get a new Fortune
free oh but
um only one
[Music]
Diamond how do I get more
diamonds how am I going to get more
diamonds crony will love to sort that
chest well crony better freaking join
the Hardcore Minecraft
then strip
mining oh yeah right I can just buy a
diamond pickaxe yeah yeah yeah yeah did
that's is that what I originally did I
think
so yeah okay okay but emeralds I don't
have EMD so I got to get I got to get
the I got to get the
iron let me throw some of this away
[Music]
no go
away you're not part of my
[Music]
system I'm
hungry I'm probably going to have to eat
something that's not very diet friendly
to today
[Music]
guys oh thank you for the
raids welcome I have looted gotten lucky
with a lot of never uh ancient Dey but I
need one
more I want it to be a bucket man that
would be nice right now not just the
bucket but the chicken
inside let's let's sort a little bit
just a little bit uh
[Music]
no don't worry guys we're getting close
to the end I didn't think I would stream
so long today but I didn't expect that
never right or ancient debris would be
one of the missions
today I did not expect that that is a
little
bit tedious tedious this
now
okay always expect a long stream well I
mean we're still under 6 hours I mean
we're going to go over the 6 hours
probably but that's not so
much not in the waa
World m you can pop the ancient Dey into
the furnace yeah yeah but do I have
coal a little
bit I can put wood there too
though nice do I get an achievement for
making
this or only after
it's yeah okay not for the scraps
you have another early oh you're right
I'll be so I'll be so like when I wake
up I'll be
like every [\h__\h] time when I like do a
stream that's like right after waking
up well my fault I didn't think it would
take so long I didn't plan for such a
long stream I thought maybe 4 hours
maybe oh oh I I I thought I had to
replace it like soon but now I'm just
staring at
[Music]
it what is this doing on my inventory
little bit of
organizing would not be a bad idea look
at those Stone
pickaxes don't need that [\h__\h] not in my
[Music]
household I don't know
I don't know where to put everything but
I'll need
this can stack
yeah I'll put them back oh but actually
I feel like um it would be easier for
them if I already filled with water
[Music]
cuz that's the base right water
bottles for the potion maker let's make
it easier on them thoughtful wow wow wow
thoughtful you're still
going come
on okay
enjoy uh next step is putting the
bottles
away and going to Kyla place no going to
iron farm then go to KY place then make
new pickaxe then go back into the nether
then get a the
last God
damn last never right never well you
know what I
mean irn stop was right over here right
oh no
wa where was
it it's close everything's
close spare gunpow no I'm sure she wants
to do the same stuff so not going to beg
for more from
her I mean I don't know I mean first
she's going to go for the template and
she's doing other stuff too so who knows
if she'll even get to it but I mean if
she's going to stream for 12 hours again
then she could totally get to it where
the hell is the where where is the iron
farm I saw it several times already and
I used it several
times also are you guys annoyed
by the lines that they're still there I
I kind of like
uh I don't even see them anymore ah
[Music]
no
okay F
you where's
[Music]
the ah
ah
please please please thank you thank you
KLA cross the bridge near po Farm oh
really ah near po
Farm I forgot that it was there
burn burn evil
[Music]
beings burn in the Holy
Light of the azour
heavens
[Music]
oh is this ena's fishing house over
there or did she build it somewhere else
I'm not sure where she posted but she
had like a a fishing a place fish for
fishing that she liked and she put
the
her house there her fishing house she
made a fishing house small smaller
fishing
houses okay iron what did you say behind
it
or uh
I'm going the wrong way but this is
portol
Place damn
[Music]
it what the
[\h__\h] let me go p p what the [\h__\h] is that
tree
why does it look so
funny I see it I see
it I did see that building already from
far away before but I didn't realize
that's that's where it was didn't
recognize it what's this
then no no buck
what is
this that's it don't has wood Farm ah
the big
tree
who
she probably don't need that much
especially cuz they're not going to
although I can go to the other not Kyla
place first um
for trading the
iron don't stack them oh what they have
the iron spread out like that so it
doesn't ah hold I didn't know
that
oh how do I like
smoothly like I see Japanese members do
it all the time how do
I how do I smoothly go like H okay I
figured it
out I tried with shift and that was the
way to
go all
[Music]
right okay
go next
to everything's so close together and
I'm still not really aware like I just
like I've been to all these places but I
just can't help
but really remember where where
everything is by heart I have to look
visually this is so confusing for some
reason
yeah the landmarks only like big towers
or
something oh also by the way apparently
while I was not streaming I missed
another raid the Pillager raid I just
like uh I was I've been peeking a lot
into P sire stream just to see what's
happening what am I
missing turns out turns out
missing a lot but uh I missed
the the whole another Pillager raid I
didn't
realize fed fall yeah yeah fedal is at
Kyla's place I guess I can get that
right away too but I wouldn't put it on
these boots right I would put it on
diamond boots and then maybe get a
golden helmet
instead six now
okay going to kylo please uh
which was from here further out right
always get
lost always get lost going to
[Music]
KY this looks
right wait the Torches the path
[Music]
the
Torches Japanese members you know they
put torches like everywhere so I also
just um hide them in my vision I hide
the layer of torches usually I don't see
the Torches normally but if it's just
one line that means it is leading us to
Glory
yeah this seems
right who made these torches I wonder
who put these here was it Kyla or
someone else who thought we need
this I wonder if she's there right
now you like the
bgm hi
[Music]
Kyla I'm so stupid
Kyla hello why I needed one more um
ancient Dey and I ran out of TNT and out
of gunpowder everything so I was like
okay I'm just going to use my pickaxe
and go
like uhhuh and I did that for a while
and then my pickaxe broke so now I need
a new one oh no yeah oh no no
[Music]
wait
first oh fire
protection uh no I'm looking for uh the
exchang is over there right I don't even
I probably don't even need
a ah oh well probably don't even need
this
much okay uh what are we getting we're
getting a
nice pickaxe who had the nice pickax was
it it can't even be these guys right cuz
these are book
people but we want The Mending didn't I
still have no I don't have I don't have
another mending
[Music]
book I think I need this for that do I
no do I I want
this y taking the free book Thank you
thank you you're
welcome 20
[Music]
emeralds you can you can have
oh
um Kyla is so chill eight M I'm breaking
to is that the one I originally
bought efficiency too I probably this
one is what I originally bought and I
think I'm going to buy it
again they don't like me that's kind
like at the same prices right now
yeah I'll take I'll take
that
[Music]
kaas and
then was did I call that pickaxe waa axe
or was that the axe that I called the
waa ax so does my pickaxe no not have
any name at
all wait what about mending what about
mending
what about
[Music]
Ming book with
book wa book with book book with what
book combined books what book not the
FED falling book what book these books
what got a m book
[Music]
combined
mending a mending
book efficiency five efficiency five and
efficiency five and
[Music]
then never did that before
I don't need I don't
need I didn't know you could have two
things in one book like that he yo and
then what which one does it replace
then what I can have four things on
there what I didn't know that I thought
threee was
Max
what I was
there should we put something else on
the diamond
sword we have looting porns protection
touch flame sharpness feather fall
Unbreaking
efficiency un Fortune fire
protection Max it sharpness five ahuh
sharp
sharpness but then should I just get
this one
then I don't have any
[Music]
wait don't need sharpness yeah I have
this I have the feather
[Music]
volum yeah
look at
this what would you put on
it sharpness sweeping age you need
Unbreaking
um I don't use it that much though so I
never Unbreaking and mending at least
Unbreaking and mending if you don't
really use it
okay but I want more power and you can
have looting tree if you want so that uh
you can get
more drops from the
monsters if it's really important for
you but if not then I want more power
okay well okay looting Unbreaking Min
okay maybe not now but maybe later M and
if you want to increase the power you
can get the sharpness that's sharpness
but sharpness to right sharpness is
actually sharpness five you can have the
sharpness
five
somewhere yeah actually I think
I uh yeah no more emeralds it's okay
I'll be back eventually you you actually
I have the bamboo Bamboo deer and then
the what's that the bamboo and uh sugar
cane oh you can just chop it off and
then trade that with some emeralds uhhuh
okay I don't know if that's enough okay
because my I have still iron but they
their prices are crazy right now like
eight eight uh iron for no yeah Emerald
how much how much you need like how much
four more emeralds if I want to buy
sharpness this one just take it thank
[Music]
you power power is is
power sex nice okay we even stronger
than before
nice
okay and then I'll just go home get the
diamond boots and put fed falling on
them although that's not really a
priority right now anyway yum let's use
it right away
[Music]
we can accidentally kill people faster
let's go accidental kills but I didn't
do anything like that until
now if anything I would accidentally hit
people with my bow more often than with
the sword because I don't know how to
release it without firing the
arrow okay my diamond pickaxe even
better done before yo maybe it was meant
to
be just it and it cost me really nothing
because the iron is free therefore the
emeralds are free therefore the upgrade
is free therefore the pickaxe is free
it's free what a
deal go to scroll oh right okay thank
you that's all I needed to
know so much for Minecraft veteran but
but I feel like I knew this in the past
but you know it's
just spaghetti
memory memory is
pasta melted cheese
[Music]
fondue
hungry OU [\h__\h]
you okay and now that we did that we go
home one more time leave the F falling
there leave the iron
there
uh
oh should I try to get more gunpowder or
should I strip mine I mean it's just one
you saw how often I was able to get
lucky but once we rely on it that's
probably when I stop being
lucky maybe a little
[Music]
bit you might find one at the
Bastion what just lying there you mean
like already as a scrap or so or n I'm
not I don't I'm too scared to go there
are you crazy are you
crazy
wait you
crazy a bed bomb ah can I shoot the bed
or do I really have to touch it I guess
if I have one of the potions on then
blowing up won't be so
bad m
[Music]
ah my boots are
elsewhere that's to risky of
lag very
dangerous oh wait I wanted to
[Music]
switch going to switch get the
shoes you need blast
protection potion oh there's a potion
for
that well I don't know I I think I'll
just try strip mining a little bit we
just need
one maybe we get lucky we've been so
lucky before
[Music]
but I'm more more Decked Out decked out
like a Christmas tree deck deck the
halls with what Deck the Halls How does
it
go the
amaz than D
[Music]
the the
with balls of Hol
La the
the the W with chunks of no with ancient
de wrong
[Music]
direction W with ancient every la la la
la la la la
la I will just go strip
mining Phoenix luck will gu me
[Music]
there I will be the first
noide La hey
[Music]
let's
[Applause]
go should I so to say strip mine or
chaotic mine as I like to call
it uh in my own mine my previous
one that's not there
chaotic mining neutral evil neutral
chaotic NE neutral good I am
chaotic the way I
mine no fed fall no not for now it's
okay that was just like for now
preparation let's get the boots at least
in
order chaotic evil yeah that's that's
how I M
Ka lawful mining no chaotic mining V
Miss empa and Ana were doing lawful
lawfully good
mining I'm doing the chaotic evil mining
which breaks my [\h__\h] pickaxe I'll be
more careful
now but I think I still might want to do
it that
way is it not like more guaranteed to
find me something
what do you
think I feel like it
is where was where did I do that where
did I do
that where did I do
it oh whatever I'll just go
here 2 two is best no no no I'm going to
introduce the new meta to you trust me
bro
okay I'll go a little bit straight for a
while ah [\h__\h]
[Music]
Blackstone
watering water water ring water ring
wasn't water ring that artist
it's been a while I heard from
you are you working on something new
or I'm looking forward to it if yes
thank you for the red super
[Music]
chat thank you
sh I am at the end of my stream
but I cannot end before I get one
more ancient dead
bre seems like there's a lot of lava
here last time I was like more lucky
with uh just not being
[Music]
disturbed if only I had TNT
I really don't like the word ancient de
is a it's probably Dey
right you don't say the S right I don't
like it it's like
confusing don't worry guys I have an eye
on it it's still very full
the S is
[Music]
silent what what is it Shy like Aqua
sire Come on talk to me don't be so
silent why do I have to do all the work
in this conversation you and me ancient
Dey talk to me so I can hear you and
find you easier why are you so
shy where am I even
having a hard
time don't go away Gast you're not
welcome
[Music]
here man I I I was watching a lot of P
stream today and it's really funny how
like the whole you really got to know
Japanese man or hope for some good Clips
but the whole
[Music]
the whole
ah I'm done yet I'm done here
anyway I'm
done the whole
Aqua serving picol Arc is very
[Music]
entertaining don't worry guys I may seem
panicked but I'm less panicked than I
may seem
like I am an container
[Music]
Apple you know the arc you have clippers
been documenting it quite well
it's quite
[Music]
funny she gets so intimidated by P I
don't know if it's really just because
of their Dynamic right now within
Minecraft what if it's always like that
cuz right now like pic sfai has has her
on a
leash like quite
literally but D
hello uh uh uh uh uh
Mercy B for the red super
chat oh my God where is my ancient
debris you really only find it this way
if you don't want to find it
[Music]
now hold
up that's also something to look out
for should I go
higher just mine in straight line you
don't like my style oh no
TI what's going on guys what's happening
why is everybody bringing out the big
money right
now all I want is ancient Z not friend
Super Chat thank you
Z what the hell
guys thank
you I just want to show you guys how
it's done
man what a [\h__\h] mess where they I
come from from
[Music]
here here
ah the
akaser what the [\h__\h] another red Super
Chat oh you are ah what the [\h__\h] guys
thank you random collusion thank you B
and dougle
Jones now now with I I I smell it am I
smelling red super chats or am I
smelling ancient the we will see or is
it
lava find out soon and strip strip
mining also recommended at
15 SE bass what the [\h__\h]
guys thank you for the red super
[Music]
chat ah what the [\h__\h] J swag
B what the [\h__\h] thank you for the red
super
chat what is
happening What's happen
happening what's what the [\h__\h] P I'm not
giving up Polaroids are you guys
aware thank you
Rana there's no Polaroids guys keep your
money wait wouldn't it be smart if I did
this so much smarter finally realiz
something
[Laughter]
here did I just sound insane well that's
because I
[Music]
am it' be smart if to sell Polaroids
right now no obviously not because it's
working
without thank you guys you crazy Lads
what the [\h__\h] cimo paint pickle that
does does not look red to me taimo thank
you for the red super
[Music]
chat thank you pons for the red super
chat this is too low why did I blow up
anything this low H mix
mistake that was scary I'll slow down a
little bit okay for everybody's
heart Bo thank you for the right it's
payday what today middle of the month I
guess some jobs are being paid like in
the middle of the month thank you m mwah
wait thank you Mar P mwah thank you Jim
Tracy
a [\h__\h] no what's happening I'm not I'm
I'm baffled this is not uh like I'm not
doing anything that deserves super jets
right
now thank
you that might lead into the same hole
would it is this the same
direction or it might lead to ancient
debris could lead to a hole or to
ancient debris
deis de debris
debor thank you
soing I love you
too oh thank you slime for reborning
your ah there it is reborning yourself
yep and Jimmy col the red
of I'm going to give one as a gift to um
Kyla
give
[Music]
me what how does she say it she's been
this is also like kind of
a like thing that's the people are
laughing about on the Japanese side F
school thank you for the
red thank you for the
red thank you do 8 hour drive oh you're
welcome happy thank you f up yay yeah
like no I think she
said yeah yeah there was something there
um I father was really funny cuz like
she would say like that sounds so polite
but in actuality like the way she uses
it in the best moments when people die
or
so is is just the sound of it is really
funny it's really comedic timing at its
best
Hulu
come resine what the [\h__\h] let's go
indeed thank you resine you guys can
stop now I found
it oh did I walk past the accient oh
where are
we uh
do
oh where am
I where where am
I where am
I I don't need to smell the ancient Dey
anymore I need to smell the exit the
fresh air
maybe there there's one torch there
that's a sign right they're fan going
above the phras oh
[Music]
really that looks like Ollie put it
there cuz I didn't bring those blocks
that means it's more recent and then I
see my
tower should have made more like signs
but then I built already so many paths
then there would be a sign everywhere
you
[Music]
know thank
you thank you thank you soon Zuma thank
you soon and space wonderful thank you
soon I'm probably not going to read
super chats again so sorry so sorry so
sorry we'll catch up again we'll catch
up no
worries and I'm doing a shorter stream
again probably next week we'll do
shorter streams
right oh my God that sounded like
her Ami should I do an Ami
Video regular short or laa
short somewhere in between
a I wish I had a name that works well
with the lean lean at the end cuz I feel
like that's a really cute ending for
Japanese
nicknames nine why
nine is Kyla in her house right now
question
mark is she in her home
home she's in
T is she trying for
gunpowder is she trying to farm
[Music]
gunpowder I hope not because I feel
bad well you know first come first serve
and she's probably going to be stringing
for a while repairs not a the
but I didn't only use the gun powder for
myself we used a lot of it for the sake
of Ollie and MAA as
well M and I continued mining for a
while and still shared those things also
with
them yeah I can turn up the lines now
was it F3 or F4 and G I know the G
[Music]
but yeah gifting one to a
under my
[Music]
car than it up yeah I'm sorry next time
I'm going to bring my freaking
phone I'm so lost
man my brain is just so empty when I
don't have my tangents written down and
I also I feel like I've been like
skipping out on writing everything
down and I'm just hoping that I'll
remember it but as you can see I don't I
don't spaghetti
[Music]
brain this looks like the
Matrix Ella
Kaa Kaa
[Music]
wait was it sorry sorry what was it
every this just happens too often
doesn't it TI you crazy no
don't I'm sure you spent enough money
these past weeks thank you for the red
super
chat
man I I watched some video on Twitter I
think today that was questioning
Australians because everybody was
freaking Barefoot on the street walking
around and they were like Australia what
the [\h__\h] is that really so common oh hi
hello
hi I have one present for you not this
not that I just had okay wait
here here hold on ah thank you you're
welcome for your help so far I'm looking
forward to the um template please yeah
the template I I I don't know if if I
going to get it but I'll try once you
have it let me know cuz I have diamonds
that I will I will use it to copy okay
than you can also write me a Discord
message or so I mean I won't be up right
away but just good to
know okay thank you uh what what what
time you'll be like
going back online or whatever uh is it 7
hours or 8 hours right now I think
8 time it's okay I think just uh just
just uh what's that uh just tell me your
time it's okay I can count it by myself
11 11 a.m. Austria time but I was going
to say okay it's GMT plus two right yeah
okay okay okay got it that's when I'm
going to start the stream again oh
uh what time again sorry my brain is not
raining same 11 a.m. uh 11 a.m. okay
yeah okay got it see you you're going to
be there right today he are you going to
stream from now until the weather or are
you going to take a break sometime no I
think I'm going to stop like around
lunch time
probably oh my time lunch time my time
yeah your time not hold okay okay come
back
thank you
byebye
[Music]
byee oh my chat died the moment I
entered the water don't
[Music]
die it's been 6 and 1 half hours for me
now so that's pretty good pretty good
pretty good you guys are eating well and
now I hope I will be eating well what
will I be eating though it's not quite
midnight yet I
could probably try to order some
[Music]
food uh uh God I'm like where the [\h__\h]
why am I in the never
again so
confusing it better not wait too long
yeah I uh order something good well this
time most good restaurants are already
closed but
maybe I'll find something
anyway chicken burger you mean crispy
chicken I don't know if I don't think
it's open anymore
either it's okay
though my beloved crispy chicken I
haven't eaten a crispy chicken in a
while was kind of even considering it
yesterday but then I was like you know
what I'll just have a
lasaga with the little amount of
calories that I had at that point
yesterday I could have totally eaten a
crispy chicken I think totally but I
actually wasn't even craving it but now
I'm craving
it yeah I'll take a look right away
what's there to order ah [\h__\h] I still
need to ah let can I order now let me go
get my phone and then I write the diary
[Music]
my mommy wrote to
me my mommy says really funny with the
Minecraft stream yesterday oh she wrote
this before today's
stream uh it's quite the difference when
you play uh with a lot of people rather
than also alone pretty
much oh
yeah oh and mommy was saying at some
point I have to go higher and then she
can we get much higher and then she said
I'm so proud of you she's probably not
watching anymore but I got them
all I got them
all more than I was hoping for okay
let's order something and then and then
we can write in in
[Music]
calmness
oh did I I didn't tell you guys remember
that one time when I ordered something
and I got a completely different order
and it was way too much food I had to
throw away so much I feel so
bad but a lot of it was disgusting too
but it was actually a McDonald's order
that I got and I got um two glasses
originally I would have gotten only one
glass but I got two glasses because the
order was so [\h__\h] big so that's a big
win disgusting yeah cuz like everything
got like also because it was like for
free people and I was eating as fast as
I could but everything got cold and then
it got really disgusting and uh the
burger that came with it was [\h__\h] and
most of it was not like it was just like
a million chicken nuggets for some
reason and I love chicken nuggets but
I'm not going to eat a million of them
and then the sauces they had like a
million different sauces and some were
like really spicy and disgusting I just
want my sweet and sour oh s and sour
sauce wait wait wait my
mommy oh she was still
watching she said I was very amusing
today
really
really I need to order food I 5 fre a
day that was probably really 50
free m
can I order this can I order is this
still
open
yes oh
Nar n okay but is there also
[Music]
I'm
F I'm ordering
food okay nice oh that's
[Music]
not okay
I like this music it's
[Music]
cute
uhoh wait so
wait
mommy mommy mommy mommy do you know that
I streamed stard you Valley as a members
only the other day and then I decided to
never play it again cuz I just can't
really I'm not vibing with it I'm so
[Music]
sorry cuz she just wrote to me that
she's still mad at me for not playing
Studio Valley with her
yeah I don't know I don't know what what
it is like it's
just so difficult to
like
Terraria Terraria
honestly like visually Stu Valley is
even more appealing to me than
Terraria and I don't
know I tried Terraria once and I to to
be honest it wasn't even like me I would
have played longer but then Martin
Senpai who who wanted to start the
project never felt like doing it for
real for real is this okay am I is kind
of
okay there's more yeah probably Terraria
I can see how it would probably probably
um be more engaging for
me than stardo
Valley also I assume there's no stupid
time limits where I have to go back and
sleep right
away n no take ah it's n's remaining
things cuz she dead for real for real oh
that door is cute maybe take it
maybe ah this is
take this is p stuff but it says not
wait if you if you like Ka or so you
might misunder understand because in in
English it says take
free that's the only thing that it says
in English uh oh but it's just signs
what wait
what
what do you ah maybe she's still putting
stuff in
there H anyway I ordered my food Alice
is good so what do we do I did the
skeletons I made a potion I got another
warp fungus I got uh the gas I got the
Soul Sand again I did the ancient Dey
the only thing I didn't do is this one
because of a Time issue if I would have
streamed earlier I would have gotten
this one too I swear I would have at
least been in one of the groups that
would have gotten
it so okay we have to ride all of
this oh oh okay
okay it's it's 17 yeah
[Music]
17 I I think she wrote it correctly
nice I should just like copy paste it
from someone
else although not necessary
[Music]
makes it
easier
ah ah I ride from here I was like how do
I do this
[Music]
again missing all the
keys thank you for the Super Chat
[Music]
y
okay and
[Music]
Uganda Uganda
Uganda Uganda not Uganda ug are you are
you guys just making jokes you guys are
just making
jokes okay
die
and S sandle maybe is not there yet I
think
s that's six missions is that
it one two three four ah uh yeah one one
2 3 4 yeah six yeah
oh oh that was
yesterday
damn no this also yesterday I was like
damn she got it all is there anybody who
got it
all
no
oh oh oh they have wither heads the
first one I was watching akua and P were
mostly moving together and uh they got
two of them and the last one was Ki who
was I'm not sure if she was alone or in
a
group damn unnown thank you for the red
super chat it was crashing the whole
time damn thank you so much I did
amazing well I feel like yesterday was
way more eventful but today I also did
all the missions I yesterday I didn't
manage to do all oh wait never mind I
mean the Wither head obviously I just
couldn't do it wasn't even possible for
me so I did all the missions that were
still available to me at the
time but yeah I don't think anybody did
everything huh they
got the one thing that they do is get
the ancient Dey that's like really
difficult what what Senai and
uh the only things they do is getting
the ancient de
is it because the other things don't
count even if I do it twice but
Anya
Ona it doesn't say anything about you
can't do it twice and it doesn't count
she did gasto also twice for
example it should be
fine should be
fine h
huh I'm adding today as well I killed
free not so that just so that there's no
misunderstandings that I'm just copying
that I'm just assuming because I did it
lot yesterday no no no today as
well uh today as well and today as well
[Music]
and okay so this way I think it looks
nicer
okay now now we write the stupid
diary stupid because I feel awkward
writing
it also I got to write it in Japanese
it's so difficult to write in Japan wait
it's in my thingy oh I it's in
my such a poet I'll was trying to keep
it short actually today I think I'll be
able to keep it short easily what did I
even do not much
[Music]
um
keyboard okay so we started with just um
ah m
I guess I got to mention that I was
betting
[Music]
um that's there's so many can CES for
that
[Music]
okay I kept it short that's it
don't touch me horsey don't breathe into
my ear your breathing into my ear is a
quite a bit stronger than a human
breathing into my ear and a bit more
disgusting please don't okay so I'm
writing we had a date in the nether with
OE and
Mauna and
Panic uh imagine Panic GIF or whatever
image there's so many actually but I
mean the one holding your
head um
[Music]
Mission what's it called
again H got it
for
[Music]
NE
how much did I get in total for myself
how much is it again to get enough for a
full was it 18 or 20 20 to get enough
for sword and okay oh
[Music]
I wonder if they call it template again
as well in Japanese because I want to
say from here on out I'm uh leaving it
to Kyla to get a template you you okay
okay
[Music]
I want to finish it on this page wait
wait I can do it
[Music]
okay okay I kept it with two two two
pages nice nice nice nice nice so I
wrote uh today I bet all my diamonds in
the event it went from 15 to 20 diamonds
let's go let's go after that I went on a
never date with Ollie and MAA but Mauna
died really early Panic uh then me and
Ollie uh after we gathered a lot of
things we decided to get ancient debris
as
well even though we only needed one uh I
uh got uh for both of them one enough NE
Nez neide or ancient debris for uh to be
able to make one piece of uh armor for
each of them after that they both logged
out so I decided to get 20
more and got them uh so that I would be
able to make my sword and my full armor
into never right I'm flexing real hard
on P she's going to be like when she
reads
[Music]
this and and then I wrote uh uh as a
little present and souvenir I gave Kyla
also one ancient Dey and hoping uh or I
actually wrote it more in this Nuance
you better give me you you better let me
copy your template all right and then
vaa like let me copy your homework
please but it it's not free I need my
own diamonds for that too so yeah yeah
yeah yeah NE to you
know
yeah where's my present B let me copy
that done all
right will be very thankful for uh
keeping it short oopsy
[Music]
um yeah maybe I think tomorrow I'll try
to interact with everybody a little bit
more again but it was really just
because today I started so late but I
think that's fine too like because
yesterday it was so full of emotions and
stuff it's good to have one day that's a
little bit more chill in between cuz I
think tomorrow and the day after
tomorrow will be a lot of
exciting
[Music]
activities so is now we got so much of
this sheesh oh my God all that
disgusting neack let me throw it
out where the F tomorrow yeah but
honestly I really think it will be over
in an
instant I got to be careful though so I
can't let my guard
down I need to uh figure out how she
talks like what's the voice not really
raspy at all it's more like soft
actually imagine me throwing away my
freaking ancient debris where's the
rest a in here why one more one more we
want to see it right we want to see it
cooking let's
cook a little bit whispery yeah
not that good with
Impressions I kind of want to make one
block at least uh how does it work in in
uh here
[Music]
ah just
five oh I need just one Ingot for one
armor piece that's four armor pieces and
then one
sword me
there wow it looks like a candy liquor
licorice so it's disgusting you wouldn't
want to eat it oh okay just one piece
okay okay for a moment I was
[Music]
like thanky must
yay does do the others have never right
ingots
yet sorry I'm feeling so proud so flexy
let me Flex please let me
Flex let me Flex I'm rarely in the
position to
flex I need to enjoy this while I
can licorice armor coming soon
[Music]
going to eat soon and then sleep soon
and then be up
at did they write what time it actually
is happening ah oh wait maybe I don't
have to start at
11 uh
[Music]
you guys would be happy about that too
right oh my God they don't start the
Wither until 3 p.m. my
[Music]
time 1000 p.m. jst like um okay
originally on the schedule I said 12 but
I could start 3 hours later
approximately but I don't know like I'm
so prepared like what else would I need
to do although who knows maybe they're
doing some exciting stuff and I don't
want to miss out on what if I start just
on at 12
then that's better for
me but I yeah I just I just like what if
they're doing another small event but I
don't think I get I guess river is the
event for
[Music]
tomorrow 12 will definitely be early
enough
and more interactions with J JP JP if
I have nothing to do I just do the
missions there are surely other missions
I'll do them until the
weather and
yeah yeah I'll start at 12 yeah
do you need all the diamonds to copy the
templates H I think we already
calculated how many I'll
need uh oh they're in the other box but
I think I have
enough let's bring it into my
house
end it really seems like Sunday is the
last day I thought maybe the uh Monday
might be the last day but yeah Sunday is
probably more hype
for many people can watch it
[Music]
so have 28 I think
it's you have 25 you uh 28 and we'll get
20 for the I'll get more I I have enough
cuz yeah by the time I log in again I'll
have uh
again a lot more
a lot more I need 35 okay I'll have
enough I just need the template from KY
so I'm counting on her for real for
real better close the
door yeah 29 29
[Music]
strong wava
strong so strong look at this
waa look at that ugly
Shield okay
um I'm going now good night and I'm
counting on you
good
luck uh starting my stream at 12 noon
GMT plus 2 after
all h e stay strong oh thank
you e literally just me
though way just you don't have to say h
you just say Ki
same
thing moving to
[Music]
e you work on all time zones
all
righty good luck don't
[Music]
die girl love me I know and I love them
even
more I'm looking forward to my
food what did it say oh sunm says
would you believe
it thank you guys for the crazy super
chats thank you for watching throughout
the
stream
uh we are so powerful now we've got the
power all of the
Power Super Chat time sometimes soon who
knows maybe one of the days one of the
weekend days will actually surprisingly
and
early you never
know have a nice meal thank you you too
guys
hopefully if you guys stay in the Stream
I'll uh redirect you to
KY with your support surely she will
find the temp the template that
everybody will copy from I don't know I
don't know I feel like actually maybe
not so many people will really go that
far to get never never right armor
because it's Overkill like we also
didn't get never right armor for our
myth Ender Dragon and we don't even we
didn't even play hardcore like it's
really not necessary right but it's for
the flex it's for the
flex
uh let me find her
stream ID redirect to me and I redirect
back to c e but she doesn't show
up
[Music]
wait I don't have perms to redirect to
her manual redirect
guys I I'm surprised it doesn't let me
it's gray out look
guys yeah manual let's do it manually
[Music]
uh I'll give you the link if you
want R perms
do I will manually rate you because no
perms to raid
you all right this St is for the
S okay and in German say to maximize
[Music]
my I'll manually rate you because no
perm to radio you still have no worms
yeah I don't know
why thank you so five by