[Music]
he
n
[Music]
he
hello Heroes and training of the mini
chat box yes this is why you watch my
stream is it not to learn from the Great
Hero Jonathan
Watson hello hello
okay we're
back seems some heroes are here in libba
sty probably celebrating their Victory
after the
dungeon I have a little Quirk to tell
you of little chat
box I wish to Traverse the dungeon alone
or
brother with Heroes who have not yet
experienced the
dungeon I am the same when I watch those
uh moving pictures uh you may
say I do not enjoy to watch
them with people who have already seen
the moving picture does that make
sense I like to experience it
fresh you wait let me let me test it
ohing R cross right
[Music]
there she is behind you yes I can no she
is not as much as she has stalked me the
witch has stalked me she is stalking me
to see my weaknesses you see
gathan but it seems like she is your
weakness
mother mother to fall to her what is
happening noise you are making every
time I mention her name
no I had too I too much bread oh I have
also experienced that too much bread
all am no no no no no no I am me out of
here I will not be with an un trust
thank you
my are you kidding me Jonathan Jonathan
what did you do Jonathan I saw some
citizens in need
Jonathan yes I was in there with them
Jonathan
oh I am not hexed by the witch I made
sure myself in
potion wasn't my trusted to you trapped
Us in the Trav we were
trapped I am not thank you I
willome I am not a witch I will s
I see oh my Pearl hello hello my dear
husband have you committed crimes no I
have not but I cannot speak of it here I
trust I not trust these
two away away Jonathan
yes
your your partner
is
crazy in a good way yes wait I I believe
I'm receiving a phone call hello oh my
pear you are the only one I can trust
please meet with me behind the Gan hang
up I cannot be in their vicinity I I I
used no oh
God sorry excuse
me oh don't mind that okay um yes I have
a meeting I must
attend well oh a meeting with who well
all of a sudden I must listen to all
sides of what what is happening
but she was about to say I am hexed by a
witch I am not Jonathan you would be one
of the first to know yes you seem you
seem as uh the same as ever you don't
seem any change to me yes no and also I
have done the necessary the necessari of
not being hexed by a witch and you
remember that
Jonathan uh were you
cleansed yes exactly you know when you
do your left foot in your left foot out
and then you go in and then you go out
and then you shake it all about and then
you turn around and that is what it's
all about oh I see so you were hexed but
you cleansed
yourself of course I a
professional ah what was the hex
effect I think she Charmed me I see for
my face went red when she she said
certain words at me so certain pretty
words I see so so what what is the issue
why why why why have you been arguing
with the
princess oh I was checking if she def
just plopped um uh I
mean your partner will tell you I don't
know if you knew but uh someone uh
your sneak is minus
20 Ro is up Ren craftt please meet me in
front of the tavern oh she's talking
she's on the phone
Ren on the
teles don't you love it when the phone
automatically please makee quite
convenient it goes straight into my
brain I have no time
to to properly answer or not answer even
anyway someone defamed the the worm
Queen oh and it wasn't you was it oh no
I mean we can't I have done no such
thing as a hex I have put no such hex on
you stop spreading misinformation she is
psychic too that was a hex right now
what did I just witness that was get out
my brain get out of my brain get out of
my brain get out of my brain get
like honey get out of my brain get out
of my brain get out of mine
unintentionally hexing those and
seducing them honey I I it's
unintentional for sure Jonathan and
Jonathan a consequence nonetheless must
take responsibility for H's
witch you must speak it out with lady
bloodflame I guess I guess lady
bloodflame then shall be my wife from
hence forth oh yes well have you
proposed for that
no but I'll do so right now lady
bloodflame we have decided the
punishment for uh or rather the the the
solution the solution for the problem is
uh we are to be married right now uh
already no W I came at the right time I
say I say I
say she yeah we we kissed and now we are
married soe you're already married marri
Works yes the Phoenix has witnessed it
so therefore it is true Mighty Phoenix
it is not true um I came at a very
confusing no context timing so all I all
I saw was the kiss and now all I see is
your sword well do you not love
her that is a very strong
word I mean she hates me I don't don't
hate
you I don't I could never hate you why
would you even say such a thing banish
the thought from your
mind I don't hate you m I am not
thinking of you anymore haha e banished
you are banished see from my
mind well time to kill myself I do think
you each
other do we follow I must speak with you
in private Myro it might be should we
follow might be a matter between two uh
Quite A Private Matter maybe may may I
speak to you in private now that they
are gone yes shall we go to the gardens
as planned yes yes let us go to the
gardens onwards
I think they will not hear us here no
it's a quite empty yes there is some
treachery of what treachery I sent some
evil in these lands yes and I I do not
know I tried going to Lady blood flame
because I saw her to be reasonable yes
but she she is not she's little headed
though no I tempted I attempted to
appeal to her to her heart and her
kindness but she turned on me so easily
because of the the Scarlet Witch that
she calls Marissa she's being influenced
by the Scarlet wand yes I see yes she's
being influenced by them well I I
believe that lady bloodflame did apprise
you of some things that have happened it
was that
my statue of Queen oh that's your statue
I see yes it is it is for her honor I I
had built it last night and someone had
defaced it in such a terrible and awful
way well it must have been a member of
seruan no it it must have been so I have
been trying to call Princess koseki
bishu and the hot pink one to trial but
princess kosaki Vu is very very against
being put on trial and she's acting
quite strangely suspicious you notice
that the stain on her head is not a
plush and I think the stain on her head
is actually a real stain do you think it
could controlling her thoughts yes yes
that is exactly what I am thinking and
every time I ask her to show me her
crown underneath the stain she sidesteps
it and
refuses uh we must get someone with more
authority to demand the princess prove
her bloodline yes yes she should prove
her innocence I believe believe that is
true what do you propose we should do uh
I I I I may attempt to question her
perhaps I think I cannot be there for I
have been there too often that she may
grow suspicious okay okay I will I will
make it I can be in the yes yes you can
trail behind me hide behind I will try
hiding as best as I
[Music]
can oh what a beautiful
statue oh stay there I will show you
something oh the princess is that you
yeah wait have you done your own dungeon
yet I mean I mean the dungeon of the
sewers I have yet to attempt the dungeon
but I was thinking of waiting for the
heroes help Tak shakar just murdered my
child what I had a child with with Lady
blood flame and Tak shikiar used her
Revelation on it and it is dead yes my
son has died
your son my
son I'm so
sorry I'm I'm so sorry we must we must
have trial for for this Heathen who has
decided to kill my child my child how
could she where is she wait wa we must
get her to the the gall wait wait when
did you have a child with follow me H uh
just recently follow me I will take you
I will take you to them follow Takashi
Takashi has killed my child oh no what
in what so one thing after the
other what has
happened
what has killed my child no no no you
have presented a chicken in front of me
I am child I am the owner of kfp as you
have all seen in my video I must make
chicken into Fried Chicken that is just
how it goes she killed my child and ate
him even
worse video it is a strange slang I
think strange SL her
lands the mighty Phoenix has different
wording yes I I came up with it it's
easier to say I see I see we we shall
learn from this Mighty F yes yes we will
learn you can call it a
video call it a video child child
can we not forget that she murdered my
child no it was never your child you
were just pretending to get elizabth
into a SP that she is not willing to
enter freely course I lay
eggs what oh that's wait
what I'm not going to lie my lady that
is a turn
off oh my goodness it seem you have
given her the
egg I only l i i i only lay egg I only
lay eggs here I don't actually lay wa
how could it be her child would it not
be the Takashi child that's what I no it
was my child with Lady blood where is
the human in this bird that we saw it
should have been grotesque and
disgusting when did you guys consumate
your marriage yes I did know that you
guys yesterday I was caught in the tree
an herb came and trapped me and while we
were trapped while we were trapped in
the tree we consummated our our love for
each other no we did not I trapped her
in the tree I mean the troll came around
and trapped her in the tree um um excuse
me the usual incub incubation time for a
bird is about 21 days so if it happened
yesterday you could have not possibly
already laid the I time traveled I time
traveled I time traveled it must have
been someone 21 days ago time travel I
I'm beginning to think you are a witch
I'm not a witch how can you lady blood
flame wife I'm not a
witch attempted murder attempted murder
murder
murder what you were saying she M
because she a she deserves to be
murdered she deserves to be a witch no
no not murdered burn believe we should
be put to The Gallows scratch must be
put to trial to trial you must be put to
tr what else would you be doing with a
witch we question her and we show her
compassion that's not how you do it in
my land you're supposed to put her on a
shake and burn her that sounds
barbaric
become she shall turn Tois to the No No
I refuse how kind also she's fine she's
she's not she's dead she dead you have
killed her no no she's alive she also uh
um ladies uh did you uh did you uh uh uh
see the uh the the the notice board with
uh there is a tournament today today
tournament a grand tournament will be
held in an hour and 10 minutes at the uh
the arena the prize is honor uh join us
and Sh your blades and prepare to test
your mind I did not know that they had
there is no money this in the Kingdom
it's honor what money I love honor Mone
we will watch a show of
blooded no you must join in you must
join in is partially training you
must it is training as well for the
fight ahead
do not worry Jonathan everybody gets a
wooden sword it is a fair fight ah my
daily training I was worried I might
kill my opponent but if I have a wood
sword may
not I hope you do Jonathan I mean well
not kill but uh blooding them and win
but um anyway uh yes that will be held
in an hour and 10 minutes from now an
hour and 10 minutes oh okay uh yes yes
yes yes okay so it's on the hour and
hopefully there'll be more participants
by then maybe yes I the princess
go I was questioning her yes where did
she go she disappeared so
quickly uh my fellow Jade member huh I
believe it it might be good if we build
it if we built a courthouse I believe
you were working on a bunker
no oh yes I mean yes I mean you can add
a courtroom if you wish yes to to to put
to trial and decide if they must to
trial use the Gallows we must use the
Gallows on them yes what yes
what what is this bias against ambercoin
members that you have I since the very
beginning know I did not know you were
of ambercoin I believe they eat
money is this true yes you didn't know
oh I didn't look at my hat they wear
that she's wearing a hat for reason just
for fun all seeing I have
ever what's at these Jes EMP I have only
served my honorable king and queen EXT
stand away from her the eye of embercoin
stares into my
wallet please please not care for your
coins you will have to here for you coin
the gamble house says differently she
eats money what I have never made use of
the gamble house before Oh I have it's
quite fun and perhaps I am the only one
who has not gambled yet
that was an accident Mur Mur
my no why why it hurt her why you trying
to my p i was burned it wasn't are you
okay sorry I can't control my Phoenix
fire it seems okay I shall I shall
remove myself from any people because it
seems like my fire hurts people one I
will hurt me you
should I like fire
huz you are cured you are cured cured
you are cured yes yes you are cured I
don't know from what exactly from your
misuse of your Revelation you should be
able to control it better now yes oh
that is so nice with you yes huzzah
huz question what Jo day yes what a
joyous occasion wonderful it is fun to
cure me of that can you cure uh Tim
tender of her uh negative ass buttock
what she's being worked on okay she is
not a finished not finished statue she
has a netive looking she's she's under
construction must inspect she
construction does it abide by the code
she is under construction she is being
worked on she is doing a a certain run
style what is that leave her alone she
is working very hard uh
oh I
see can you wait but um are you if
you're adding the but are
you um what's a medieval word to say
[Music]
boes
bz bz the buzzom awesome she was not
made for objectification you look at her
and you look at her with awe and wonder
not
to get to
her beautiful shape of her body is also
something to be honest looks like a worm
right know it is a shape that I cannot
in any worlds that I live in a little if
she's she's almost she's getting arms
soon it's nothing to be ashamed of she's
going to get arms that's okay I must
honor her shape I see you adding some
more Dimension here yes she is getting
some she will soon be breaking
Dimensions what does that what exactly
is why is her front more
threedimensional than her back she is
not finished okay it's just here for you
to look at her have we seen the Queen's
back is it quite voluptuous I am not
aware of color is there is nothing there
it is covered by a cape you will not
look she has a cape on you don't need to
look there's nothing there yes yes see I
see yes then quite accurate
no yes it is very accurate leesta wasn't
built in a day so she shall also not
buil be built in a day she she's not
built in a day she will be built over
two days mayhaps okay I shall observe
her tomorrow again her beauty I hope to
be impressed by her beauty yes when you
observe her tomorrow she may have a
backside look forward to this
yes
side I love her body
I love her for princess what a beautiful
hat you have oh thank you it is my
friend uh his name is do he has a
name yes he does not control your
thoughts does he no no no no he is just
my companion then if he is your
companion are you able to remove him for
but a moment I would like to admire oh
yes yes yes see I can yeah see I oh what
a beautiful crown you have upon your
head a thank you yes yes it is my
indication that I am a
prin I
see yes yes yes well thank you for
showing me your crown I have verified
your
princessness thank you it's quite
wonderful you are you are a wonderful
Pearl I can see what gathan sees in you
yes so kind the tri princess thank you I
look forward to your
rule ah yes one day I cannot wait to
take over this beautiful kingdom one day
Beauty I'm sure that will come what are
you doing up there oh
huh oh they can fly I
forgot I think I I think your wife has
has trust in
ah uh she's she can be a
little how do I oh she is very
little she's busy she's busy she's
locked in as they say
I see what are you staring at uh the
beauty of your statue you how much you
look like a little fly as you fly up in
the air a
fly she is the poop and you are the
fly oh do not know what you mean there
uh nothing I this just how loyal you are
oh thank you I worked very hard in her
in her honor as she has made me her
night
mhm is that really the only
reason yes Jonathan could make you Hern
night I am her Knight oh well oh you're
two timing my stat
no statue it'll be right here if you if
you wish it I will make you a statue my
sweet my my dad requested a smaller one
perhaps you do not want to Statue this L
I don't think I can stand next to the
queen I am not a queen or King
you can stand side by side though might
we perhaps hold
hands you you want to hold hands with
the
queen no no no no no that would be too
too too ludd oh oh oh right right now I
think she was she was asking for you to
hold her hand do you want to hand
holding I in this Kingdom that is
Princess hand now oh oh oh oh I I Let Go
I have let go grabs and drags away come
this way come this way get this
way pulling you away over here what Mom
what what let them be for a moment she
is she not the queen if she is the
mother of the princess or is she but a
concort they having a moment I do not
know it seems that holding is okay on
Pome
occasions now kiss
oh now
that's who taught you how to kiss they
are so loud um and don't Focus where is
the ren the person in front of me with
with all these whisperings in my ear
yes oh she has run off she is in the
haunted
forest oh that is a haunted forest to
yes if you go closer there are signs
that says that the darkness will take
you yeah that's the the corruption seems
to be sweating I have quite concerned of
this as the princess of the Kingdom
corruption yes corruption read the signs
oh darkness is
approaching careful careful
you isoing evil Forest huh yes introduce
this Darkness to our kingdom the the
darkness it it's sticking over I
head well it's obviously someone of the
civilian C who has cursed this uh part
of the
land you know who it
was no no de husband you're not lying to
me are
you she has taken the hat off her head
what
hat oh princess I have a crown a welcome
back princess oh thank you
she's free we have freed we have freed
her of of its
influence so did would you say that
you do you feel strange mayhaps do you
have any memory of the past few days oh
my
head got is in do you have any memories
of do you remember what we've done a
couple hours ago you remember hello wait
I I this is the first time I'm seeing
you today right
it was her do you remember who I am oh
no oh no you're you're my mother right
uh remember I told you yesterday I'm not
your mother oh yeah yeah oh yeah
remember what a confus it's the first
time I've seen you today right really
Jonathan and pearl yes yeah what what is
the last memory you
have
um going to going to sleep last night
and then waking up right now just now
right now you just woken right now yes
oh oh so you do not know of
this
wao what is this it seems that Darkness
has taken over the
land was the darkness that influenced
her oh no I don't
know something is a foot I believe so we
Whispering nothing yeah I just I just
nothing you stay away from the darkness
the forest it's spreading will you I
going to create a perimeter yes let make
let me make some stuff we will contain
it yes contain
it it's quite an amusing ride you have
placed here
yes is this fun it's coming out of the
mouth it's like a
little ah it's not coming out of the
nose right oh wait look I can do this
too hold on hold on hold on I can do
this one
second uh uh uh uh I don't want to do
hers yet
uh wait where did
my was something magical happen yes M
something magical will happen
once it is it's a giant
speaker yes
beautiful you have made this
[Music]
song an ingenious design
princess right
it's not done
yet I'm still working on it it's a
working press looks good looks
good V language comes out
[Music]
of why are you hitting the
it is dangerous princess must stay back
yes stay back from the fence it is very
[Music]
dangerous think
that I would like to visit you know no
the do there's darkness in there as you
can see it's already spreading to the
Amber
coin we must loock it off where we
can to protect you princess this is to
protect you you must stay away from it
looks so F no no no it is protect
you a man
[Music]
fuing
danger let chat box please tell me
the the news of today's happening in the
LI
town you know
what are your thoughts my Pearl now that
you have spoken to
her she she she was able to take the hat
off take take the uh creature off her
head which was influencing her actions
so believe she might be safe for now but
we should keep a close eye yes we will
keep a close eye on her in case that
it's Darkness has spread root maybe she
doesn't even need a hat anymore I don't
know maybe I did I did witness her crown
on her
head she is Princess a small thing she
is Princess but she just has a stain on
her head well I hope that this is the
end of it for now I have blocked out the
evil though I cannot block it out in the
others it draws her it influences her it
does can't believe she was so influenced
to break this to
enter I do have to say dear husband have
you visited the new Library which has
been
constructed I have taken a look upon it
it is beautiful and wonderful ah then I
shall go take a look I'm curious about
this new edition
toist do take a look farewell
fwell well wait uh yes yes is it is it
is is have I um my my allowance is oh oh
yes yes here I I have
my allowance what kind of relationship
is this no it's to support the family
business this is between two of us
princess mhm ah okay I will I will it is
matters between husband and wife yes she
does not understand she's too young yes
she does not understand really well for
now thank you dear husband tomorrow I
will definitely not be going to the
Ember coin what
what ah so this this is the library is
this it Scarlet one Library brought to
you by funmart
ooh work in progress do not
enter can't
I it looks so
fun oh it's the shape of the Hat it is
the shape of the Scarlet wand
hat I see they're going to make it even
more pointy
it's quite
relaxing stained glass lanterns
[Music]
chain floor plan is the Scarlet wand
symbol what is the
symbol I
[Music]
see what ingenious
architecture very nice
now do excuse me little chat box I have
an appointment at the ambercoin gambling
house but one bet I will
make just a
one I'm a little turned
around is it this way
just one bet I will
make I would like to
[Music]
repay my dear Jonathan with a
G or for their generous allowance
perhaps I may make profits at the
gambling house
and with this I will make
profit just you
wait no yellow not this time I don't
believe yellow has what it
takes all right bookie yesterday we had
a a really good run pie let's keep it up
huh I left the gambling house
yesterday with my pockets
filled new
coin today I'm feeling confident that
yellow oh sorry green or blue will
prevail
oh bookie bookie remove the yellow
please you heard
me no no bookie yellow look this is the
yellow color you must remove that
one bie there is a disgusting red stain
in the middle of the board please remove
it
bookie bookie this is no time to justest
bookie ah
yes aha I have made extra coin
and you little chip box doubted
me how Dost thou feel now like a fool no
let's chat box are you aware of any
Heroes who have also not traversed the
sewers
[Music]
let's chat box am I spelling this
right how do I say this
[Music]
first timers yes we
will we will defeat this is the final
dungeon I believe shall defeat it
seems we will be traveling with the
heroes Nino Ina and Nana
M I have yet to make this M's
acquaintance I
believe but until then I will
inspect the bath house and make sure
everything is running
smoothly I believe there was something I
wanted to add a
banner as I have coin now I will attempt
to get more construction materials
and I do hope I will not be given
another wretched hat yeah no I get it
heard the term
Strang ah I bought a lantern by accident
but that's fine I did I was in need of a
lantern I am the strer
stranger who has a flashlight oh yes I
have a lantern oh my gosh incredible
Hello Hero nice to make your
acquaintance Hello Hero acquaintance is
nice of yours too I see you are looking
for someone to assist you with the
dungeon what is Irish I am are you
looking for the
same yes I am quite lonely I would like
some company into the sores yes I I
swear I remember licking your wife the
other day do you not have her around
anymore
licking yes my have you forgotten my
wife did not notify me of this it was in
it was in front of you was it what is
your
name my name yeah hold on WR
down H did you say turned down it is it
is written down written in Myck it is
fra Adams anet
Senor wait what was the first one wait
say that again fra Freda Freda nice to
meet you Freda nice name detective I am
lady bloodflame lady bloodflame I'm a
detective yes I assumed you forgot again
I already talked to you about detective
things before assumed you were a lady I
guess I a detective may I accompany you
while shutting my mouth and doing my
quest for the second run I guess that
makes sense or what purpose are you
getting coin for this Quest come here
yes and I also need to gain age levels
and will I be receiving a percentage of
the coin you received from this
Quest are you asking coin from the
others who are accompanying you well it
is their first time the experience with
them is uh priceless
how much coin do you want well how much
coin will you be receiving from the
quest uh let me
check I must find a way to repay my dear
husband back such allowance that I've
been
afforded I have no choice right now
ah nice good what oh
[Music]
day good day hero
say it doesn't say how much coin I will
receive well then I will require a
fee how much I believe five coins will
suffice five
coins fine I will give you 50 oh showing
off what a
deal yes all right I will accept your
offer y
55 up fine I'll give you 500 oh for free
not to flex or anything uh I give you
500 for the return
of uh
445 what
which I think comes down to 55 then
right
math I demand 55
coin I shall give you
56 wonderful
wonderful can you break a
200 yes I I I do have change oh wait you
want it up front yes I requireed up
front uh let me see I've never done this
before uh
pardon me I must go behind this tree for
two minutes you are not taking a leak in
a public area are
you okay I think I did
[Music]
it
meat ah thank you thank you I wow that
is a fair exchange yes very high quality
meat I required that anyway I appreciate
it I inv you to my party as per the
terms of our
contract oh do I need to read theine
print we got enough food thank you I I
might need some
more yeah I will help thee a knight will
help an a fellow
KN it is so it is
true I know I know of it first
experience firsthand experience here I
shall trade with a
stick thanks you for your
stick I I use it well d
d maybe you can use it in the arena ah
yes I
mean if if it wasn't part of the rules
to have just a wooden sword I would use
a stick just to show off with the stick
you can make a
sword that is true sticks are important
oh will we not be using our
rations no only uh no you only use a
wood sword in the arena Revelation
perhaps you magic get a wooden sword I
wonder if we will arve back in
time uh the dungeon is quick fine it's
pretty fast okay I believe we are just
missing um hero Nino Ina wherever she
may be but first I will look for this
mad person who I believe is you could
call her defecating on the public
property oh she's still oh my God yeah
wish I'll leave her for now my eyes did
I look we do not need to witness such
things my eyes I need to wash
them I need to know where with SE water
where the hero n in a
frequence I am uncertain you made you
might want to give her a
call would you perhaps make the phone
call for me I shall do okay are you
shy oh no yes you
are
mhh I have been requested to uh call you
um to inquire where you might be uh to
soon depart for our quest to the
dungeon
oh okay so you are more or less ready
for it okay uh
[Music]
I mean I mean at least
lightly I was in in the vicinity of you
I have sanitized you after your public
defecation you have forgotten that was
harsh
punishment bad memory oh it seems the
party is here well yeah party let me get
out of this call hello party let's do a
party
callot wot hello
free the
roof you must accept our our invitation
who's Freeda oh thank
okay oh it has been accepted do I oh and
then I
be party co yes we are here okay I will
indeed shut my mouth so you guys will
have to find the dungeon your it's not
like I remember I I do not I really do
not remember how to get there oh I do
well they said the king said it was the
uh oh shoot you guys visited the king
already
uhoh me go to the king he has very
strong Scott I don't know what Scottish
action means but Scottish action
according to the voices in my head is it
Scotland SC Scottish from
Scotland yeah if you if you could change
your fate would you my connection is
weak I do apologize for the
interruption yeah yeah yeah yeah case
yese
Mye he rose
Mye I can't believe Scottish is
real what foreign lands do you speak of
Irish is real
too lands I've read in a book not heard
of
oh I'm reading the things he says oh yes
oh yes I see uh-huh uh-huh King
reached yep a witch has
returned oh dear an omen oh
not are you Skipper
Skipper I know I I have incredible
reading
I had forgotten how to read and then
when it all came back it came back even
better than before
o I wonder why you have this
ability I think I'm special quite rare
in these times in these trying times
here want to hear how fast I can read
yeah
oh
impressive she's absor in the text go to
the castle and speak to King Li oh I did
that speak to the Jade to Guild Master
is that what you all have to got make
the rounds the green one you haven't
done this yet oh no you have done this
wait you've all done this oh no oh no
just finished I
will
onwards apologies if you can hear me
muning on the minest of wheat oh the
minest of
wheat is it the one with the magical
white sauce on
it what are youing yes something
something like that yeah mini miniest of
Wheats the
wheat I think it is called icing
Icing sugar o icing I am very aware of
sug sug
I might be going here icing is something
I have previously feasted on on top of a
cinnamon
tornado the cinnamon tornado yes it's
real it is so I've seen them I thought
it was just the food of the
Legends it is realer than anything I
have
evered right here oh
okay yes the the green ones like to hide
in the
in a little cave
cards let's
see I gave very oh shoot
okay
[Music]
oh I am the king now I sit upon the
throne I have shared the news with the
notice board of which Super speedy again
Heroes can AC see the news fascinating
you see the way
SK you see
it Scarlet wand Master okay all
right with Scarlet again
um might be the other way I'm not sure
oh you're right I think it is the other
wayy doopy the king is but a servant for
me who holds my title let know when you
girls are ready to go I will go slay
some things I am ready I am waiting in
the king's chair for a
apologies oh no worries did not realize
you acknowledge my kingdom are they this
way ah they're right here oh oh that is
a my GPS they have the same hat as you
you should you should know I will await
Hero's Return before she must return to
the king to gain access to the sewers I
believe no no matter what I click on
oh my gosh I have to speak to everybody
okay too much socialization for one day
social batteries oh my
goodness social to be drained social
batteries what are
batteries I'll show you she has finally
done
it I she B we talked about it the first
day we were here how's she doing
I didn't get up there what is it I have
accomplished the feat which now names me
as the new king wait potato salad
perhaps potato salad is that the trick
salad no potato salad was not involved
in my coming to
King any other food that has boosted
your abilities what are you doing on the
King's throne one unnatural
way okay hello
Welcome to My
Kingdom your kingdom I've summoned you
hero are you talking to me
yes the king is the one who summons me I
am the king and you Jonathan you are not
the king that thing there holds my
title Jonathan
Have You Been hexed by the witch I've
not been
hexed I've realized my
potential ah
no what yes I am
no the throne cannot be
shared it's quite comfy here I should
say how did you how did you that out
inde well someone of a royalty myself
enough get off the throne we can rule
together this is the King's
throne you are disrespecting him I am in
the throne therefore I am the king you
you are not the
king I I am quite related to a princess
which kind of makes me royalty which
makes me qualifi to be on the throne I
believe me me too you
what
perhaps I do not believe this now do our
biddings
Knight I no I do his
bidding I only serve the king the
rightful King hero who will you Pledge
Your Allegiance
to the king of course the King which
sits upon the throne yes yes of course
tell me hero are you ready to Traverse
the sewers I am ready this King we are
all ready to Traverse all right I will
give the throne back to the king for now
but I will be back
King it is his
throne he can't even get up by it's true
it's
true look he needs to save his strength
as the
king he's
weak oh I was simply Banning
him I believe we are ready for the
sewers so we will we are ready for sewer
dungeon and meet you at to your
Arena oh yes I will I will host it at
half past instead okay the sewer dungeon
yes I'm sure to the
SE to the to the sewers huz
huz oh it's
foggy wait a minute these
these lanterns look very familiar just
like the ones in the
dungeons huh the one
Castle no I don't think this is the
entrance I think the entrance is uh the
purple marker on the magical map yes
that was given to us by the higher power
on my
way I must find the bridge here we go
oh you must join our party call
you mock me that was so beautiful no it
sounds so medieval I like it hi I I no I
just lost oh I found
it
oh oh I
see are you in front of the sewers turn
your bre lights on lady my goodness I
put my turn signal on
I did not see
that sounds like a you
issue I don't believe so I think you
have an issue with
lying Lu I have a dashed
him in my in my
brain yes I know you are crazy the
public defat vlogging sometimes it I
didn't know such a thing oh yeah right
sorry you don't as that is not a
technology that is available to us yet
right oh I yes I I've done absolutely
nothing anything you name it it was not
me wait I should have made oh you know
what I'll be right back it is it this is
it this is it interesting I do not hear
sound of this
world I shall receive a diamond
sword wait is this the right
way I do not know huh I'm following
you
um
I the marker doesn't it doesn't look I'm
going back I don't think I don't think
that's right away yeah everything else
is working so I am
unsure are you girls lost no okay that
works I I see I see this what was your
name your name your name your name oh I
am John Watson with a
Y John Watson with the Y yes John Watson
with the Y yeah
oh look at us we all wear different
hats are we one from every single the
front Guild oh the Power Rangers yes
because uh Freda has been trade to
amorin Guild oh yes I see yes we are not
getting along you and I we hate each
other yes what trouble but we will get
along for the purpose of the of
succeeding in the dungeon how I lo you
so this can say is I hate you so more oh
oh oh no fighting yet but the moment I
enter this dungeon my feelings for you
shall poof into th air perhaps they will
flourish something
beautiful I will become NE and we'll see
where it goes from
there oh suddenly I feel this love for
this bird Freda graffiti upon the sewer
I still feel neutral graffiti oh then I
shall feel neutral too oh but perhaps if
I feel enough love I will return
it I must prepare I will work hard for
the memory Shard one
moment Oh I thought we received those
after we clear ha oh yes yes I'm
preparing mentally one moment okay I see
I
see
meditating she's meditating wow nice
enchanted diamond sword you have wowk I
a pickax for this
dungeon it's all right I shall protect
you all I am a hero from another world
if you if you didn't know thank you for
your protection there it is all right
I'm ready are we ready God ready Freddy
The Gift of the Night o ready I am ready
more than I ever
was oh we go
wa I oh my what is this place I've never
seen it before it's so dark and so deep
we find ourselves in the white empty
space it's so vast that the very concept
of distance distance seem to lose
meaning
in the midst of that space we see an
antique desk in a leather chair and on
that chair sits a girl sipping tea tick
tock tick tock tick to we hear a clock
but from where tick tock tick tock as
more and more clocks join the chorus the
girl closes her
eyes oh I finished reading that way
before you she's too fast for us letting
you know I tell to fast but also humble
wow seers we're going to see some SE
rats maybe some type of creatures so
prepared some Mutant Turtles of teenage
age a perhaps a type of lizard that
lives on the coast oh oh there's letters
wa did you obtain a lantern if I may ask
shopkeep yes the shopkeep Sals then I
did not which source of energy did us
offbeat Reaper discover people's strong
emotions consuming people's soul soul I
know which one it is I believe it is
this way wa eating lots of sushi wait
wait oh there's another oh what's Sushi
sounds reasonable
Sushi I've not heard of such things sure
she loves Sushi should we also eating
lots and lots of sus I think that's
pretty sus maybe we should someone
should try for science select the the
wrong one okay is the wrong one
consuming people's Souls I believe so or
perhaps sushi that sense we all have to
if I die do I lose all of my XP no oh
are you telling the truth would you die
she is she is you will not become
younger unfortunately oh dear it's
attached my name to my selection I don't
know if I feel comfortable about that oh
it's it's a majority vote
oh I spit the VA Vault into the third
party let's go and what will happen if
we I think almost all V I guess everyone
has to vot the same oh I see I'm curious
what happens if we pick the wrong
answer oh oh oh oh must we battle we
battle that's good I need to grow older
ow I appreciate this challenge I don't
have a shield
we made it that was fast ah we went
back oh it's it's the beginning it
did now let's answer it correctly shall
we okay I guess we must that's a pretty
good place to farm the stains yeah that
be good power does not they don't have
to run so
far right so this is some type of exam
huh MH everyone taking
notes back to the school that I have not
been to a
library a book here souls are not a zero
sum game that's what the reaper realized
for if she could stir the hearts of her
audience the power of their emotion were
energy enough yond the Crimson bows a
treasure lies in wait the Gaze of Orphus
will point you straet the Gaze of orus
oh oh what oh is this a puzzle perhaps
is there a secret do this bookcase move
or something perhaps G of orus I think
it's just through here ah orus what if
there's a secret orus oh secret a secret
you
say oh secret I don't know it could
possibly be there has been secrets in
the other
one but I guess we
go ahead shall move on we can always
come back yes
good let them
cook they're cooking why does orus sound
so
familiar
orus orus think are you thinking of what
the morus movie Morpheus
orus that why it's familiar a movie I
mean tail tail
the great the mor
morbius
morbius that's the name okay which of
these
guard the force field around Atlantis
Stark shark statues electric jellyfish
do you signified man with a
beard oh do you remember it I remember
dolphin statues dignified man with the
beard is it not Santa
Claus no no no not Santa Claus it's like
the fish version of Santa Claus oh so a
shark
then
perhaps mayhaps sounds
reasonable oh okay
oh
marvelous Divine we are but genius
another
book in the depth the kingdom of
Atlantis sits safe within its force
field Mighty Stone shark stand guard to
defend it and yet rumor has it that one
girl slipped through those
defenses the ancient doll meanders and
its maze reward awaits who out boundary
Strays so we H doesn't that
sound like how One achieves The Treasure
of the second dungeon because the
ancient doll sounds like the zombie or
whatever that was the thing with the
tried it if you
if you did it did you do it did you get
the secret treasures yes I did it I
did
yeah so I did it I guess this is
probably for those people who didn't do
it
yet we don't need to
readint
wink okay ready to proceed so generous
proceed huz
huzzah huzzah
checkpoint okay wow they're asking so
many questions why do they want to know
all these things maybe they're all
related somehow perhaps mysterious boy
appeared at a certain shine what is he
particularly good at oh you do the thing
with the Le the thing with the leaf oh
the the leaf isn't here folding orami
they made something that looked like
a uh an octopus octopus that's right oh
so would it be the
takoyaki oh oh oh it was not the the
octopus what is
T I believe I've heard this phrase used
before to refer to
octopus oh to her she was merely keeping
them company but to the souls it was
what they needed to move on one boy left
his things and or got me before
departing for the other side elaborate
passage tests the eye proceed Beyond the
Wall to claim a prize oh okay
okay
see must have traveled far if you heard
of the word takoyaki
before it wasn't passing on the street I
want to touch it I want to touch
it did you get it touched it I touched
it I'm going to look it
too oh oh we in the sewers you don't
know what kind of bacteria there be
those are some uh not so fine Waters I
think we must what is the grand
achievement of a certain phoen Oddball
OD the grand achievement a weird would
you rather be an even ball helping a
fast food restaurant repay its debt
saving a kingdom that was on the brink
of collaps oh I hope not taking first
place in a hamburger is that what we're
doing right now
I will say wouldn't it be this one yeah
thank you you are so smart I agree from
the fragment we we we it was this one no
no no I saved the kingdom that was on
the brink of collapse if you did that
I'm going to have to push you off the
edge oh what the the console will now
decide your
[Music]
fate who is the council uh me me I'm in
I'm was in a
council counil decides that you
closest are you doubting my abilties to
save a kingdom that is on the brink of
the collapse perhaps well where's the
proof of this achievement then surely
they would have given you a coin or
something to show off have you Travers
have you traversed through my dungeons
yes I did have you seen the visions of
the past yes I did but it was have you
seen me on top of a cliff where I looked
upon an army and and what of
it I feel it means that I have saved the
kingdom that was on the brink of
collapse I feel like I've seen a picture
where Kara was you know how they take a
picture after you win an eating contest
like oh you're one of the people that
did it I swear I've seen one of Kiara on
a website
ah but that is just what I do as a hobby
my my real duty is to save kingdoms that
are on the brink of the collapse oh
all right all right fine then but this
is not the true
me I think this is the truth no it is
not is the truth speaks I do more
honorable things than that I don't only
eat burgers I save kingdoms the
struggling fast food restaurant finally
saw success and prosperity some say the
hardworking new part Tower is as fire
Fury as the Phoenix a crumbling crack in
the fury ports fall of
may claim reward where others
fall that one was very difficult for me
I remember nice nice I
remember it was difficult for us
all except for
me o o a friend not oh back you're so
powerful hero I'm just need there's
another story
here please read it to us wait what was
I the girl stands on the roadside
looking dazed as though she woke up from
a dream the picture in her hand soon
jogs her memory however all right I need
to find this dog the owner is expecting
a call from her soon so she'll need to
be quick this detective has a reputation
to uphold after all don't worry little
guide I'll find you I promise he's
finding a dog oh how sweet I do love
puppies I must say wa the sewers
it's so deep oh yeah it's pretty
big wow what creatures lay
here what creatur Slumber the
sewers stains
stain I got to get him I have the oxy
clean was it also being sold at the
shopkeeper ah was it I made it myself oh
interesting wow so many
Pathways I dable I I dble out year
Freda The Alchemist oh Freda The
Alchemist I
see I hate
stairs good St I see more letters
[Music]
my what did a certain detective invent
for The Travelers who made it this this
far an a oh invented she invented
something wor Crystal an iron pickaxe
didn't you say all you have is an iron
pickaxe I I I did say
that wait a minute but did she invent it
invent it was there a need for it to be
invented maybe it's a typo maybe it's
what did she bring it but they
accidentally put what did she invent no
but I don't think there would be a typo
in the
dungeon MH you never
know uh I I I I don't know if this
detective was around to invent an iron
pickaxe or a golden
ax I mean this sounds the most
inventable yeah it is the most creative
perhaps yeah the
most interesting what should I say
interesting it stand of it so it's
probably like the other rearrange the
letters then it says Amelia Watson what
what where trying to rearrange the
Leathers it says Amelia Watson don't I
already do not see an M oh if you try
hard enough it works got to flip the
double upside
down and then what do we do about the E
what about the Y don't question it
what's that a chest oh treasure
supicious hold on there's a book here
first wait a moment this sh I leave this
for the hero who will one day visit this
place may it serve you well each chamber
past has offered you a rhyme revealing
Secrets where you've gone before there's
one last thing to find here out you
climb and therefore I present to you one
more a haunting grounds of creatures of
night within its depths you'll find the
hidden light hidden light hiden light ah
warp Crystal this be the
hint we supposed to use the warp
Crystal may have swear we
for a warp Crystal allow you to teleport
to a selective War Point
smart interesting I think you're on some
onto something should we use it I'm
going to use it oh it says it can't be
used here oh just
kidding well there's another place here
we can
proceed this would this be the end of
the dungeon
I think
so and what about what of the secret
treasure SEC the secret yes yes we must
investigate to find the secret
treasure we have the
hint there was a secret treasure in
every dungeon there must be one in here
investigation begins no I don't think
there's one in
here
oh to I they forgot about creatures of
the night must be the stains no where we
were fighting the stains perhaps oh yeah
smart but then it's so we got to answer
one of the questions wrong ah does it
work like that can we even go back and
do
that we can try let's just go back for
once
backtracking okay I can't use the war ah
it's still
here let us iron Pi not let us undo it
oh it won't let me pick seems
that hot air balloon is filled with hot
air H oh can we not go back I don't
believe we
can there's a crystal there is that just
a checkpoint and we can't go Ian there
were stains in like the the hallways if
we can get there
again true
true what is this
hole seems but a mouse hole
perhaps oh can something be observed
with this mouse hole
no tell you no dingon can be perfect
there must just be no treasure
today
no no I do not believe such heresy they
must have forgotten
it such a thing cannot be forgotten we
had an experience her with us oh you
want uh my advice now I can give but I
was waiting for you to requested oopy
depends on how the party feels shall we
request advice from the experience I can
give a hint a hint would be nice I mean
no advice but a hint is welcome indeed
you must return to where the stains were
as uh the one with the Y was
saying we I'm I'm going to die I'm oh no
I'm not which I I'm not sure I think you
should be able to return from here I I
did it like right away
so maybe it is perhaps
broken
no
wait much walking somebody carry
me I think I have returned to it
oh you if you just go back back back you
can go to every question
room and it was before the questions I
think if I recall correctly H oh ah no
wait oh yeah over here I guess it was
was it here where are you probably was
here um uh wait let me try to find you
have we gone too far I am at the first
question almost yeah we're at the uh we
Ina
yeah is it before ena's question it's um
when you let me let me track
back there is I don't think you went
went ahead of us I think that it's back
okay I would have seen a went past
us I'm
lost wa I found another
checkpoint I see no
names but okay there I see a question
again did you girls passed the question
of oh yeah the
detective oh the last we went to Ena
so we're on our way I guess it is
between question five and question four
between question five okay this is now
where we are entering
ah okay it should be should be should be
oh I remember I remember yeah I see your
names hello
wonderful we have reunited I'm looking
in every corn don't follow me that's not
a good
idea I'll go down this
way it must be where she was before no
where she came
from yeah I'm here
there uh notify me when you are in the
need of another hint oh my part okay
okay hey little chat box are you
frozen don't follow me don't follow me
you believe my little chat box is frozen
I I am quite I'm doing suspicious
things in my mind without the company of
my little chat box wait where did you
guys go
here around did you go that's the
question it's getting should I say hot
and cold
perhaps I think
good hot hot hot me hot who's hot I'm
hot hot oh thank you
hot
oh hot hot
hot cold
cold hot hot that's a
very OD place did you hear my
[Music]
wee that's the h
we ah am
hot hot I'm a
smoking oh treasure hidden life how I've
loged for
the what treasure have you found it is
but the disc what does it
say it
says wait I did not pick it up Tik Tock
you didn't pick it up no thank God I
asked Tick
Tock ah what does this have to do with
the hidden light though I wonder night
there's light down there is I think
maybe I was wondering if one I honestly
don't know but I think for one of these
windows where you can look into the
sewers you might be able to see a
light like oh yeah actually I can see it
from
here ah yeah you can you can and maybe
you can see it from other directions too
oh which way were is this the right way
or uh yeah yeah yeah yeah return We
Shall yeah that was difficult to
find no I bet I could have found it
myself little chat box what are these
blocks that they used here I quite like
how they look I bet you could have I bet
maybe it is custom I bet that has the
amount
we shall uh leave this dungeon as soon
as possible to partake in the tournament
I need my honor I ran out my honor I
also
honor but I think that is the door that
will Mark
the okay will you all fight in the
tournament I shall for Honor I must for
honor I'm a all right are we going to
remember oh
oh I wonder if we will unlock another
Crystal core
memory where hop hop hop look at this
maybe maybe I'm the want to
read find ourselves in a white empty
space girl still sipping tea opens her
locket and reveals a number of pictures
each of them shows a girl who looks
exactly like herself one is searching
for a lost dog another is building some
sort ofine machine yet another is
playing a video game she gazes at the
photos with a a video game what is
that photos with a warm smile let's see
where should I go
today all right where she very
informative
indeed you shall witness the memory
oh completed objective investigate the
ancient sewer dungeon your power of
Revelation has grown stronger my
goodness recovered a portion of your
memory sound I'm I'm getting a
[Music]
memory what's with all these cases my
dog's missing my husband's cheating and
to top it all off now I'm getting buy me
some iced tea and make me some pasta
that's not even detective work I want to
work on something big the case of the
century something like the strange
creature lurking around the coast or
that demon carrying a cursed object or
that weirdo walking around town with a
huge sharp weapon the words out on the
streets so why is no one hiring me I'd
be perfect for the job that's why I
decided to take matters into my own
hands I figure I'd Crack the Case and
become a hero
no way but when I dug deeper I quickly
found out that the rumors were only half
the story My investigation concluded
that they're actually pretty nice people
and also that this is a damn good burger
they're all out there bringing smiles to
people can I say the same about
myself time to do something about that
after that whether it was missing dogs
or cheating husbands no case was too
small while I was at it I also invented
an automatic ice tea mixer pasta maker
and teeth brushing machine soon the
whole town will be smiling then the
whole country then all of
humanity okay maybe I won't go that far
but I can at least start with the people
around me like my
clients of course I've still got my eyes
out for that case of the
century a detective's curiosity is never
satisfied
[Music]
hello little chatter box ah I mean Hello
chat I
remember I I think I unlocked my
memories I remember who I am
hasn't psychopath wait what's wrong with
my Hello friends oh she has returned
Amelia Watson I'm back I know who I am
now you know you remember oh
I I am not Jonathan Watson I Amelia
Watson Amelia Watson that's right are
I'm a a
detective not just a detective you're
the number one detective oh I am number
one detective at least of
liestal number one detective of liest
maybe I should offer my
services yeah you
could wasn't there a case of uh someone
ruining the face of the queen or
something there was an inquiry about
that for
detective the graffiti I believe yes
yeah oh I will investigate this
okay all right is it time to trot back
home yes let's go back to the arena wait
how do wa Arena I Will Follow You Ena is
it happening I think it
is oh princess Crystal half okay wait
what we can go to different places with
the warp Crystal
yipp oh should we warp home then where
should we call Leal Castle let's warp
all the way we must talk to the king
hello princess okay oh oh yeah talk to
him ah what the king goodbye
princess or there we go wait wait a
minute I taken the crystal again
detective I think the Crystal's broken
oh dear the crystal you you really goed
this Crystal up I I was promised fast
travel to the
castle I did not I don't have any memory
of making this Crystal maybe perhaps
when my memory
was damage I want a refund of my time oh
the right
way oh I follow
you oh the horse girl is back no that
was just my
horse the horse speaks the horse does
speak ah hero I see return safely pre
tell what Trans in the sew ready to go
back
inside I see as with the ruins before
memories were regained in re awaken as
predicted still not
AG
iome I see you return
safely trans
is I see as the runes before memories
were regained and revelations arew in a
predictable outcome may have but
nevertheless a
work I've never heard you speak in such
an accent before you relation to greatly
empowered but now if that's well
here don't breathe the S of relief for
now at least what with the quick and the
increas in Stand
activity and the world seems to live
closer what thought we could do more to
stay here alas since the earthquake
there have been no further reports of
unusual activity from anywh in the
game I feel this but CL Cal B storm some
something yet more
[Laughter]
terrible is that
a you take this time to prepare train
your combat skills and stock open any
your items you might need maybe your
last chance to make the
most please land up your PA for just a w
longa herea for peace and the future of
the best
oh the the
king sounds amazing we did it we're
ready for the last battle oh surely
sounds
perilous I don't think I run anymore I'm
going to try to get to level 30 before
the arena thing happens it's in like at
half past I'm going to leave the party
so I can enter the dungeon again to find
some stains ah okay good luck thank you
for your
assistance I shall do the same I think
oh okay we shall this B this party thank
you Heroes okay goodbye all right thank
you see you thank you heroes and
villains see you next you Heroes thank
you
oh oh I was so surprised when I saw the
purple one so easily able to climb the
throne my claim to the throne is false
it
seems although now I remember all my
memories so I don't have to speak in a
funny accent but um I will
anyways we
shall I would not want to scare the
fellow Heroes with a personality change
you
know now we must figure out what to do
for the remainder of our time until
the until what is to come I did not know
what is to come I will explore this
Castle perhaps there's treasure
here a bed made of
diamond oh fancy
ah
Throne this must be the kingdom of
ambercoin my nice Castle what of my
husband my
husband what do you
mean what do you mean little chatter box
[Music]
I will stretch
my my dear sweet Pearl hello I am your
Pearl I I heard that you
had you had you had got in your memories
back yes and you
are just nothing I am just a mere humble
Knight I am Jonathan G it's nice to meet
you oh Jonathan G what is what your name
ah my name is Amelia Watson I'm a
detective oh it is a pleasure to meet
you Amelia Watson oh well it's nice to
meet you too Knight I'm here to offer my
services I'm not just a detective oh oh
your
services this do you recognize this I
do you sound it is just like you I
believe I like me it is
you well I will I will leave you too
I wish you much luck on your detective
services oh thank you Knight let me know
if there's anything I can help you with
yes of course farewell fairy well I will
contact you wait what was your name
fairy well I am Jonathan with a G ah
Jonathan with G that's right okay I will
see you around Jonathan with a G I will
see you around farewell farewell
farewell hello oh hello H is this you it
sounds like you I yes that is me I
recorded that yes
oh wow
wonderful yes so was before I came to
this Kingdom and I am a
detective
beautiful your voice is beautiful pearl
oh thank you yes a lot of people have
been calling me Pearl recently I guess I
have made quite a name for
myself oh I'm sorry you John Watson yes
oh no no beautiful I'm Amelia
Watson oh you're a million Waton have
you regained your memories I have
regained my memories
yeah a million Waton what a beautiful
name it makes me want to
go for some
[Music]
reason making me shy that was
beautiful remember correctly you're the
princess right yes yes I am the princess
princess of rocks huh yes princess of
rocks totally not princess of anything
else yes oh are you princess something
else no just Ro Darkness just rock no no
not darkness no just just
rock this I see this is spreading
past
oh this doesn't look
safe oh look look look
um it seems that the Saints have have
have given us a warning of a dead
guy I think I must report this to the
king yes you should report this to the
king are are you not worried that your
statue will become
corrupted
uh my not my daughter
um um where does one
get and don't say I'm a chicken cuz I
know it's from a chicken I have eggs for
you
I mean I could I could get some myself
if you tell me where I do not have to
take your eggs I I have plenty of eggs
hold on hold on hold on hold
on only if you're sure yes I am sure I
have no need for
them this darkness is
[Music]
dangerous all right
my teammates now I remember what you're
called little chatter box that name also
sounds
familiar all right we have 15 minutes
until the uh
tournament ah I wanted to H this is what
I was
doing
uh yes
oh I need
wool h
H how might I make a banner to
mates how might I accomplish
that you're saying I'm forgetting
something a
husband
me is it is it possible that perhaps
some of my memories were overwritten
when I I when I unlocked
the Jonathan with a G that that a nice
night that I met
earlier I have to try to
remember I forget something
H one
moment I will consult my mind's
eye for some new
[Music]
music how can I offer my detective
services to the land of
listal some things might need detecting
perhaps I can check check the uh notice
[Music]
board oh yes there's some type of pearl
on my
head
strange potato
salad
oh this is quite a beautiful statue
[Music]
okay hell hello hello good day
hello I believe they want some
privacy I'll hail the
queen ah so that is a queen
all right I will go check uh where I
might make some banners here in the city
it' be nice if there was a tayor shop or
[Music]
something Queen
Tam ah she does look familiar
[Music]
one moment will I consult the eye of
wisdom for
something ah I
see I have figured out how to construct
a banner thanks to the eye of wisdom
[Music]
oh little chat box do you believe the
tournament will be
dangerous my head is still recovering
from some damage I seem to have
taken very
dangerous was it was it with wooden
sticks we will beat each other
[Music]
ah this is nice
yes I will make I will make some more
banners uh to decorate this bath house I
think I was building this right my my
memor is a a little foggy
[Music]
white it's nice
uh how much how much does it cost to
enter the bath house that's a good
question maybe a few
coin a few coin um should I ask
for well let's see maybe somebody will
visit the bath
[Music]
house oh this statue is looking very
nice 50
coin it's quite a lot
I I do apologize little chat box my head
is hurting quite
so just above my brow it is
[Music]
persistent do excuse me if I am a
little
shy I must consume some water well seems
I'm all out of
water's the chat box do you have any
ideas of what we shall do while we wait
for this tournament in 8
minutes ah actually maybe I should try
to get a sword as I
am I am quite
uh quite barehanded at the moment
although I believe with the tournament
we will only be using
[Music]
sticks ah ah I'm dropped in the dark
Forest maybe we should
gamble maybe we should gamble I have so
much money
ah my head is hurting so I hope I don't
get hit in the
tournament not in the
[Music]
face
enchanting and reset it basically like
give it a different well but now we need
a level again and I would get Unbreaking
next oh wait efficiency Freo wait I can
get it oh it doesn't even take 30 levels
this
time wait did I mess this
[Music]
uped the third one to I must return to
the I must return to I've lost years of
my life oh no oh no I've lost three
years too we're not in Demand anymore oh
dear all right I messed it up I must I
will return okay just go messed it up I
messed it up I ruined it boiled it I
boiled it how could
you rich what did she mess up she uh put
the wrong enchantment on her shovel and
now she's down in her age again Ah
that's a good thing
though ah sorry we're on the call uh but
uh she soiled it she says Ah soiled it
soiled
it no but I was able to get the right
enchantment in the end even without
level 30
surprisingly so maybe you don't need it
either
right a witch cast a spell on me I
cannot
speak okay I need a little bit more
iron a diamond
one uh I guess as a hero that has pretty
much cleared the stains from this
Kingdom I do deserve an iron
sword uh what was I doing oh
[Music]
yeah uh the
arena the big big big arena ah I don't
have
enough I I I can settle with
iron all right we have four four
hello
oh four more minutes until the
tournament the stains are
gone well I guess there's still
[Music]
some I hope that I'm not behind in
training there's a lot of other people
competing in the
tournament and Revelation is Bann our
special moves our special
weapons that the King has bestowed upon
us
[Music]
ah I wonder I wonder if this will be
enough to make an iron
sword should
be I may need to
borrow one such
thing with what I have good day
aha I will borrow some of this iron
public iron
huzzah my ability wouldn't hurt anyone
no it does
stuff it's like a really strong debuff
okay
[Music]
and now we wait maybe we can spy oh not
spy gather some
Clues on the nens of theist
[Music]
princess is displaying suspicious oh we
have 1 minute she's displaying the
suspicious activity
no she's always by the Dark
Forest very
suspicious all right let me grab my iron
and then I will be on my way to the
arena
[Music]
I run IUN
IUN stick
[Music]
ah all right I will get the sword later
I don't think I need it for the
arena for the
tournament
hello hello the tournament is going to
start behind you yes I'm here nice
wonderful oh I'm trading with
you we go y we all here okay just need G
here and then we shall stop I have the
night I have betrayed you what you going
to do about it what you going to do
about it you enemy no you
won't I will is that not a tournament to
the death is it bet no the winner shall
receive five potato salads as well as
honor
oh
sustenance
yes
Magic but the first match shall be
Jonathan and Freda and it's best of
three uh Jonathan and fra
once gathan is here you guys will have
to set it up yourself so one of you
clicks this guy or pokes this guy and
then you you ask him to duel and then
whoever does it first needs to click
Start once the other person's
in does it automatically give us wooden
swords yes okay yes it will it will even
out our inventory so it's his sword nice
yes even is it the Knight Jonathan or or
is it me it is you Jonathan me ah okay
you are against
Freda should I do it now shall we wait
uh we can wait until gathan is here we
can wait a minut or so they said they'll
be here in a moment wait I'm still lost
but I'm wait this is us we're fighting
yes yes so the first match shall be
Jonathan and fra and then it shall be
beu and Shakira and then it shall be
Nina and call and myself how you do that
how' you do that how' you do that it is
what a secret no it's not it's not a
secret secret secret I tell you for coin
I will tell you for
coin I'll give you coin rounds okay I
demand so it's best of three 50 coins
for the information the winner goes on
to the next part of the tournament I
will even give you a tool proed I can
fight I will
UHA because she has betrayed boo do you
know how to get up there will you Rel
this information to me I am trying to
figure it out right now was it the horse
that is cheating that is cheating uh the
brown haad one here the one with the
horse inside
the put that
away but I needed it
you're all cheats oh of course yes I got
up here fa and
square oh oh that's how you trying to
get up there oh I see oh that's how you
got onto the throne no it's
Noto yes hello welcome welcome we waited
cuz your your beloved is going to fight
first
againsta oh I I do not have a no I did
not have a beloved
huhuh you come with me I'm going to kill
your ex beloved I'm going to what do
they mean what what do they mean by that
I wonder if the night is taken
[Music]
perhaps
hello
Reaper oh not to
worry I can hear your thoughts in my
mind
be careful yes be
careful and and Jonathan one of you
click this guy first and then the other
one also joins I clicked it it I clicked
it I clicked it I am ready to
do not you Jonathan Jonathan first her
name is not Jonathan it is Amelia Watson
I believe I used to go by
Jonathan remember yeah she remembered
she remembered wait why does it say dual
canell by
five minutes have not
passed H
yeah he is
gatekeeping he G rules we should not use
our Revelation correct uh you get poofed
you get magically poofed and then you
get a wooden sword away from you not use
your Revelation yes I I am not able to
it says the arena is currently in use
try again later in use H that's Str
let me try it says I've joined the red
team oh
[Music]
uh yes it does not let me join the duel
for some
reason are you in a party I I'm not in a
party now I left it I disbanded the
party it says we're in a party
together h j Chas sword SW the Chas
sword CH sword
J sword user it says I joined uh it says
that I'm
in I left I left the game I'm not party
here I'll just I I will go away for a
moment and come
back okay
sword it seem
[Music]
it it's Lord user should I leave
some people are just some people have
not been educated on how to use
futuristic keyboard okay do not bully my
jade sword member how all right try
again she's wearing a red hat I've
joined the blue team okay we did it how
you of should start it didn't work oh it
says door cancel your opponent has left
uh you got to you got to stay in it and
one of you
okay I
joined you joined yes it says I've
joined the
blue of you red B cake say
stop yummy red B
cake do you have mine doesn't oh it says
cancelled yeah it's I press I pressed
start okay I'll join one more time I
joined
again I
joined all right start the game oh y
oh okay it has to be instant
[Music]
uh take that take that take this no you
take this you take you you take that you
you adulterer you take that and that
it was the ghost ping it was the ghost
ping over here return back over here and
click it
again back over here it's best of three
so Freda is Win oh best of three ah okay
okay best of three ah best of three best
of three okay okay okay best of three
best of
three here we go
oh all right I will be more careful this
[Music]
time I'm God I'm God I'm God I'm
God I will kill Thee I will kill the you
teleported i s that was a calculated you
now you did it you learned I believe it
is the Ping the ghost which hunts this
Arena oh dear the Ping is on my side
[Applause]
today I have lost again I guess I am out
of this tournament a my head yeah you
did very well though I hit my head
really hard she hit my
head oh I'm sorry that was not as I
watch the rest of the tournaments
okay next up is beu and Shakira oh no
and Shakira
Shakira Shakira Shak how do we do this
onward
[Music]
Shakira du click the guy and join the
duel and one of you will have a
start I see okay are you ready uh very
ready okay let's go for Honor oh no
honor
[Music]
I shall watch the tournament
forch strange feeling waing a lot
[Music]
of Shakira Kiara is the first round
winner that's my
binocular she has not been taught in the
ways of battle she shelter has W you are
a princess after all not a fighter yes I
am I am a princess not we shall try
again though round
two I shall train you my princess so
that you can protect yourself from
Evil oopsie sorry the fight excuse me
please this is a good way to prepare for
what is Yet to Come As the king
say again oops oh again oh it says
5 minutes have passed since first
participant joined try try again
okay I've joined the blue
team begin da da die there we go
da ah they're fighting
again what prowess what a hard workking
night oh my gosh I'm I'm eligible well
done
sh perhaps is my
enemy for Amber
coin Amber coin not ambercoin no n
against gathan
no I do not know if I can hurt such a
made an AR well we all equal in
the oh okay think this shall be your
name for tomorrow good name so both of
you click this and one of you will have
a a button behind the desk to click that
says yes I have joined shall I press
Start Margarita
Happ we are starting
yummy Margarita Marcus
I'll just watch the next duel my sister
your sister without your yes is my
sister going against the brain
kns of she seems so
strong KN has the Knight has won Miss
ninoa had almost slayed me so impressive
for round two thank you be careful be
careful with my orange Knight oh I must
eat some meat you have taken a lot out
of
me yes you are a good a good F you're a
good opponent you are also a good game
indeed close game gathan with the G do
we go again yes the best of three onward
onward oh I'll join again okay oh yes
yes here we go let us fight till the end
fight
again there we go
ha
fight here we go
again
fight Orange Let's Go The Exchange
blows orange they tied they are tied now
tied one more one
more
glorious I do why do we keep make sure
we're full full HP first though I feel
like that was not a fair fight make yes
yes delicious it's anyone's game now it
anyone's game okay let us go good luck
night hold on I'm still not full oh yes
yes soon surely
okay all right surely surely I'm ready
go
let us go let us go to battle if you
could press the start fight button
okay one moment little chant I am
looking
for oh they are exchanging
blows will it be gathan or will it be
the ghost
yeah the ghost justs you
[Music]
arounde congratulations night wow thank
you well done G fellow kns you are
victorious thank you that was a great
fight yes it was a great fight you were
wonderful close was close fight I almost
I almost fell the future of C is bright
it is bright very bright join the B
bright oh mother I believe in you
mother I'm not your
mother good good my goodness good luck
mother mother good luck
mother trying to find some good music
fighting music a Bard perhaps could help
us and you I don't want to
sping
there she's so powerful she is very
powerful you were
mothering
[Music]
mothering one moment I'm trying to it's
so hard difficult to find good
tune good tune that fits
this how about this one
seems
good chicks I don't see a start button
do you see a start button so many side
chicks what is a side chick a there we
go ah they
are it's a chick on your side
relationship with one another through
their side oh you have many huh no I
have oh they're keeping their from each
other the voes in my head are my side
chicks seems like we have different
understandings of it no not me got a hit
mother no that oh mother got get
mother
no mother and
father is she a father oh no is she his
W yes mothering so hard let's
go I don't know who I'm rooing for oh
where are rooting for both mother and
father of course family TI how are
theying so many
family what a Twist a Twist what a Twist
what a
Twist how
exciting this is entertainment this time
I was indeed but I shall not lose this
the final battle last final battle B the
final battle the family this time
how
about I have
joined do it again I want to see you do
it again oh oh they're drooling once
more as the sun rises why are they
drooling they are
drooling what are they drooling over
themselves each
[Music]
other who's winning it's so close
but I believe the pink one is
winning I think so the pank
one not doing mistaking for
the oh it's a close bik oh the the
reaper has taken another Soul won the
pink one
has eight eight eight eight eight she
ate what does that at at
yes we have been both trained by the
same Mentor that guy this guy
here are there new parents next one to
fight is Freda and
Shakira revenge on the traitor the
Revenge oh the Traer of
ambercoin this will prove everybody
of what is the truth where is the
traitor oh there she
is I'm I'm up turn wait this time I
wasant to go back and forth oh my oh yes
yes this time you
were who do I who am I fa are you
fighting
Shakira Shakira Shakira Shakira do not
lie mhm her hips does not lie any so
does my
honor the Honor doesn't lie yes
I I'm just not going okay you do it
first do it
[Music]
again yes we should place bets I want to
SP does anybody want to place
BS BS do not have any
coin coin once
again the gambling one bread one bread
PR I be that
now I wonder what is wrong with it
oh I oh I
see it should could you be coin it's
happen I am it's happening it's
happening it's
starting Freda against Shakira who will
Who will win who will take down home the
crown seems that the orange one is
winning my goodness the orange one is
won she's so good at fighting
other
restored you are
a there's still two more rounds though
that's the what did I
hear what what did I hear typical Amber
corn Behavior it is my honor again again
okay I shall be having my honor once
again my hand is bloody ready oh wait
wait wait
wait y do you not get like healed back
up before the fight
I'm oh okay all right let's go let's it
one more time and
go how do you are you good after the
battle the Second Battle has
commenced let's see who will reain over
Amber coin
Defector defecated or oh no that orange
one oh the orange one wow done
Shakira uh good-bye
comrades
well you fought
valiantly you fought valiantly fra you f
you fought well no I will never ever
return to ambercoin I detest it so we
will see about that I detest I will do
everything in my power to see it
fall uh Freeda I me myness I will give
you a booby prize what booby
prize the booby PR what prize a booby
prize booby prize you never heard that
Tom oh what to say booby prize
hey what do you mean by that I want to
trade with
you oh she's
trying are you dead I will be back but a
moment I must get something from my
chest a good luck charm for the Jade
sword member who's still in the
tournament I can find it quickly
think of a booby
prize Reaper Reaper prize when I am sad
I would like to have a booby prized
indeed Reaper are you there well you
have to lose to get the bo PR I would
like to give you I would like to give
you hey good luck charm mother I am such
a loser May I have a booby prize please
take it represent the stain sword all I
lost I would like a boy prize as well
want in my heart you want in my heart no
I'm such a
loser my goodness other kind of I don't
know what happened to her I guess I
killed her
completely too
much leave me to so
[Music]
the booby prize my booby prize booby
prize what did she receive booby prize
let me TR that's what the queen statue
is missing why tell us the booy prize
what leave her alone she's being worked
on I was just I was just thinking theen
was
missing
booby put on the booby prize put on the
booby prize put on the booby prize what
is the booby prize the booby prize hey
we see the booby
prize Burn
thisy Burn It To The
Ground first I will display the booty
wait can I the booty it's booby not
booty our
hat I cannot displ the
booty we are the same after all an Amber
coin no I on it
you I know I know it belongs to you
booby prize I will make a public display
of my my this taste my next is against
Callie
ohap good Lu Jade sword Knight makes
Ruan proud I will do my best but it
seems that the reaper is quite Adept at
fighting
I believe in you show her some empathy I
show her some empathy show her empathy
empathy fight for the king Cy fight for
the
king the please let me fight she wishes
for your wife's hand
what I wish a j for your
wife's what is
[Music]
it oh here we go
or I have no idea who to bet
on for
empathy
you got to be
aggressive I do not know she's running
the Knight is running he's
running
you with the the greatest of them all
you got not to win again oh goodness
goodness is it going to be
orange I believed in you one more for
empathy one more my heart
up I saw that it was the same Strat you
used against me it was very effective
thank you I believe in you just one more
for your wife thank you I will fight in
her memory in her honor so that her
memory may be her memory will be proud
of me my dearly departed wife she's
still
alive she's still
alive let us go I got good luck
night to me get him
gathan gathan
I like them both but I must cheer for
orange because I want to see the orange
battle I
believe oh she's using
the's
go po
[Music]
empathy is
there my memory don't be a sheep don't
be a sheep
think she just showing some empathetic
words to her you know I remember okay
you fought valiantly
cantly all right the last match the
final match even shall be Shakira
against gathan all right I can't G be
true I
you're should it be so true empy I will
do my am I remembering correctly
murderer I will say this is the Battle
of the oranges so if you shall win I
shall lose my title of tanar of the
oranges and you shall be of the oranges
you lose the title you g if I win you
will go to court and face
trial wait wait that's both just like B
what what oh shouldn't it be something
else well if you win I
will die if you win you will go to
court you not watch that I know about
this deal that's kind of like you no so
if I die you get my title of the oranges
if you die what I
get do you have a title I will I will
stab myself oh H what about something
like she says ARA ARA or some strange
cursed words I do not care for those
words well then come up with something
may I take your may I take I have I know
since you will be getting the orange
title how about since you have no title
to give me I shall take your last name
and make you my wedded
person you forc me to marry you I shall
request you kindly only if I happen to
win this
battle fine let it be off onto the
[Music]
battlefield Sak are very high does it
feel are high feels wrong
somehow yipp
real something feels
a there's something greater on the line
they dancing they are dancing come on
gathan she's so
aggressive no oh first round the first
round goes to the just one
round Shakira
just one round God so fast oh no it's
okay it's just one
round no I'm going to have to be my this
my life this is the worst pull yourself
back
together I
didn't come back to us
G Don't Panic Don't Panic it's
okay listen to your listen to your wife
it's stting
wait who is Jonathan's wife less to your
D for your
Pearl Pearl but I I I am the
[Music]
Pearl let's go it is but one round left
no one round left she forgot to she
forgot to heal
but I accept icept this because I will
win the next
fight the Stak are snap it together one
more fight left one to give you oh okay
okay you can you can do it your Pearl
awaits
you my with departed wife this is for
you she's still alive she's literally
right behind you my wife
in what is this
Pearl it has started
those are the stakes are high those are
very high very high do not fool from
them or else you will die has either tra
yet I don't think so why is Shakira not
holding a sword she's not holding oh
she's holding a
sword oh Shakira got some hits in oh Gan
did too ooh this is oh very
even it seems the that's how you
[Music]
married no there is no wedding no
wedding I do not want your title I only
want you to to go to trial you make the
oranges done gathan where will the trial
be held it will be held at the Gallows I
suppose Sor how about we have the trial
the day after tomorrow
oh can I make a proposal because I still
have many things to do uh that I want to
do before I go to prison are you are you
trying to get out of this are you trying
to get out of this you would not have
such knowledge of me not being available
on the last day so um how about tomorrow
I uh get a few more quests done and then
we have to trial the day after the
morrow how about you finish your quest
and then we have the
trial have a
well on the day after tomorrow of
course have right now we shall discuss
it on the bulletin
board you can also get married and have
the trial you can have both
suspicious she she will not marry I if
you're going to courts
anyway true but if you're there anyway
might as well get married no true I like
this logic
who to to you no cuz you the court
belongs to my deely departed
wife I
overheard I know that your wife left
you she did
but spot I am here for disting I admired
you I you in sensitive spot and remind
you you are now single and that at this
court you can I will become a n you can
hit two birds with one I was her Pearl
hit this bird oh
all I remember is going the sewer
Dungeons and I my memor I offer my love
to you and myal protection if you
innocent in the trial
forgot I got my memories back and I
still remember my
pastan come here there and I give you
your potato salads maybe you need a
little bunk on your head will you will
you bnk me then you five
okay one more time can I can I partipate
do you remember I
I'm here I have rocks here ready ready
here here Rock s wait I remember a
diamond anything
now I I do remember a diamond that seems
okay how about you have a revelation
Revelation what is
that it's my pew
pew this way what I have no Revelations
no it's
not here smell this I might remind
you H
butter butter yes just butter yes oh oh
what about what about what about
this oh delicious cheese oh wait this
reminds me oh what about this my loved
one love cheese every cheese egg yes
Eggs we did exchange eggs at some point
I
believe she starting to remember keep
remembering ah my head is still foggy I
may need to rest in Eve and maybe in the
morning I will
remember maybe well I wish for me for
the best thank you I pray for your
return of memories it is very
important thank you thank you for your
assistance I will remember
this the thing is this is like cat or
something because go eat she can be my
lawyer I'm
hungry I hunger perhaps the diner is
[Music]
open a
fish one fish
[Music]
I will eat this lasagna can I cook this
stained
meat oh yes
uh I will try to cook at the diner
or mayhaps I could buy some
bread hey I will
cook I shall
cook what was
that that was a successful tournament
right
sense I
know hello hello hey I will see you
Heroes on tomorrow farewell oh on
tomorrow farewell PE I hope your
memories May return to you oh thank you
yes maybe if I rest my head thank you
yes good day good
day uh Jade sword remember my my my
night in shining
Arbor yes uh I will see you on tomorrow
I bid thee farewell oh I bid thee
farewell too well done in the tournament
thank you so much for join such a
tournament it was quite successful H it
was good to make use of our our Guild's
Arena yes all right bday
farewell goodbye goodbye have a
what did she say have a I missed
that down that could maybe bring her
back Heroes I will I will rest until
tomorrow and I shall see you then yes
okay yes fairly well Watson oh thank you
Jonathan with G congratulations on your
win thank you I appreciate it this is so
heartbreaking I will I will see you guys
what is the matter no no it's it's
nothing it's nothing it's nothing I
really wanted all right I hope do
fwell have a great great night have a
great night see you tomorrow goodbye
farewell goodby
[Music]
fwell all right we shall reconvene
tomorrow little chat box I believe I owe
the gambling house a visit for some
reason I feel like I have a debt to pay
to whom I'm not sure but mayhaps my
memories will return as they say I've
heard a lot of
weird odd things
today oh
well I shouldn't pay them any
mind this Kingdom can tend to cause
damage to the sanity of such fragile
Heroes
Rael of the mind we are
sometimes well thank you guys for
watching and joining me on this
journey Take Care thank
you I'm I'm quite hungry and my head is
pounding so I will greet to thee on
tomorrow thank you for watching
okay and I'll send you guys over to
somebody
else who will maybe continue their
adventure for the evening all right
thank you thank you thank
you bye-bye
[Music]
oh