[Music]
oh man I almost hit end stream
immediately I forgot if I press the the
go go
live what's up gang welcome to seven
days to die where I'm going to be D in
seven days or
less it is I your host shoren of the
noas here with seven days of dying or
dying in seven days or seven days and
dying in less than S days thank you for
the gifts we got some time we're about
to spawn in like probably a minute also
you know what's funny at least I think
it's funny I I don't know about the
others I assume I assume they're yapping
right now or maybe they're just waiting
for the the start soon screen you know
to start soon instead of yapping
immediately oh
wow oh wait oh hold up I'm checking the
time I don't have the the ability to
count
seconds my day is okay I ate rice krispy
like one rice krispy just now that was
my
dinner not sure what to eat later
besides grits what if I even feel like
eating it's a good
dinner
[Music]
uhoh
okay all right I guess it is time to
spawn but you're going to have to wait
oh [\h__\h] okay I now spawned where am
I oh wait where's my game hey I captured
the game perfectly
before oh it's cuz I censored it
okay wow welcome to seven days to
die okay
there this game is a Zombie Survival
game unfortunately actually wait
wait how do i f
e oh good gosh this oh I can sniff this
oh guys you're going to have to teach me
like how to do stuff I don't know how to
do anything in here actually
this game has been in like what Early
Access for x amount of
years you're going to to tell me how to
do things I got to meet everyone too I
got to I got to meet everyone in the
middle probably after this you have no
idea what fudge all right maybe I should
go to the top
right where you will now get covered for
the tutorial I think pressing Tad do
things oh okay we need grass
my technique okay I need 10 grass it's
not just a sniff the
grass actually how's the
audio there you go okay my technique is
to build uh this as fast as
possible uh put that tab okay that is
good okay for now we are eventually
going to use
Discord we oh what oh is this like my
safe Zone what was that
so how it works I don't know if we
tested voice chat yet uh apparently we
did not oh crap how do I do
friends I'm
okay how how do I do friends oh good God
that's combat these are people what is
that what does it mean how do I accept
accept I think I accept is that did I
accept I did accept Okay so now I add I
add everyone I add this I don't know
what what button this is honestly I
think I just added a bunch of
people I have I have no idea what this
button does I think this is
allies okay oh and the party is separate
okay I have I'm not making
friends it is like Discord friends
guys you add them and then you never
talk to them until like maybe a month
later what's this armor sure I don't
know what that
does okay now now the question is vas
around here
oh I spelled it WR but
whatever I should probably collect a
bunch of stuff although it's like the
first day it's probably
okay okay uh we should make a wooden
Club okay so now we
balling we are literally winging this
by uh this is probably useful
here I I wonder if it's worth going into
places all
alone I think do I get rocks here no no
I need to punch like an actual rock
oh oh wait wait does this work hello
hello oh hey I can hear you I hear you
what's up girl how you doing I don't
know I pressed random buttons and now I
have you as a friend
I just watched Kiara die right in front
of me that's hot I'm sorry for her where
she is now should I F Us nearby
apparently do you think she'll come back
for her stuff I don't know I don't think
we have
much uh hold up uh fa's also near so
let's go send her
one and then bi boo is kind of nearby
oh cool yeah oh hey we can have a big
party here never mind I can't steal her
stuff a darn what a shame she's so naked
we're so naked I cannot be seen next to
all these naked people it's okay we can
cuddle up for warmth around the naked
bodies of
course this is the perfect way if we
stay naked we'll never be cold yeah
exactly maybe the zombies will even
think we're one of
them ooh but what do they want to join
our cuddle
pile I don't know but I found a house oh
there's dead
people I can't loot the dead people
though oh someone tried to cook them
bone I think I'm going to die
actually
oh I'm too
weak well why why do they sound like
hungry I guess it makes sense how do I
loot them can you not loot them they
have nothing I'll take this candle it's
kind of
romantic I could not take the candle I
can't can you not take
[Music]
everything
hey what what was that sound
maybe I should not look up these
places uh let's see where is the
middle I'm going to try to come to you
guys since you're nearby oh never mind I
guess I'm going to beibs oh okay we're
all heading towards
beibs okay it's over
there okay my technique is technically
have a bunch of beds and
then I leave it like a spawn
point if I think I'm going to die I
leave
it assuming that works I don't know I
have no
idea this game has been like what it's
old I am not
sure I will also punch trees on the
way can I even make bandages I can't
make bandages I do need a this
one I don't have the ability to make
bandages what am I CVS of course not you
think I grew up to be a pharmacist I
[\h__\h] failed
probably okay rocks are
useful I see a KF over there their
bodies will also be quite
useful okay I don't want to go uh
cucumber we can make a campfire not sure
if I have to do that immediately Stone
spear is probably more useful
there you go um not useful right
now
okay we're going to head to towards
beibs and maybe I don't know is it worth
like searching stuff like Rotting
Flesh welcome to the party
YOLO oh Welcome to our home our party
home it was lonely hi we're so lonely
without you
welcome I don't know what's happening I
think we're heading toward our
yeah you're actually around where I am
fa like near a lake
oh is there a lake oh there's a river
yeah there's there's
water oh my God everyone is so far away
oh my God why am I over
here yeah there's like a cabin near a
lake a multiple of them
actually a
resort I don't know it looks like some
typical horror
Resort she
fancy okay oh you can also press M to
find where beibs
is uh okay you guess I guess we got to
go towards the lake and then Over
Yonder oh oh this is iron I
think this is supposed to be very
useful ah yes the sounds of
defeating an iron
pebble oh I do have a bandage here I
don't want to use it yet I'm not really
sure when it's best to use it
either is that me being
tired oh good God why is she so far
away why is she so far away did you guys
know that there's actually teleportation
commands in this
game do you guys remember the Sham
wow sham wow wait the guy that's like
dead wait is he dead I didn't yeah he's
sham
dead I didn't I didn't know he was dead
either I didn't know either I just know
this this sham wow I seen on TV yeah
what about
it oh I found a sham sandwich oh is it
edible or is it
moldy wait I think it's edible you
should try eating it yeah eat
it yeah eat it eat it eat it but but I'm
not hungry
yet it says it's old but that doesn't
mean it's mold well it's going to get
older later if you don't need it soon
well that's true actually that's a good
point it's not getting any younger oh no
it was made with the heel the heel of Mo
oh I like he the but of the bread it's
like a isn't it called the heel oh
hey the end Lo yeah the end the butt
it's desperate desperation yeah the butt
the Des I don't like the butt of the
bread me neither you I ate I ate it
you're naked sort of wait I think I oh
my gosh I think I'm having a bowel
movement don't look at
me no no no it's beautiful 30 how can
how can we be friends if you don't
appreciate each other's
bow gy how to make clothes this is what
happens when you a sham wowy I can't go
if somebody's
watching there's there's got to be a to
in
here this a zombie it's okay it's okay
it's okay they don't like outside
they're like us
introverts hold up I'm putting clothes
on you have clothes I haven't done
anything is it reflecting on me oh yeah
there's a there's a person there he
coming he's out there for your battel
movement are we going to kill
them you already have a spear yeah I'm
ow and
hurt I can light
wow oh she he's still
alive there you go can we not loot their
bodies
anymore I don't know when we did the the
practice I made a bone knife didn't give
me anything wow that was a really loud
squish sound okay well we can look for a
toilet here if you want
or or we can go to be there has to I'm
sure there is and then you can take it
with you I found a toilet oh God there's
a zombie where in the toilet hold on I
have to go I accidentally broke down the
door so don't look it's okay it's oh
okay I'll I'll distract the zombie I'll
learn them
out come here
Z you actually had to poop in this game
is that even
possible I think so is there a a 20 6%
of the way to a to a
BM actually going to go in the forest
right in front of
everyone no I found a
toilet but the whole world is our toilet
how are you going to play the forest if
you can't even [\h__\h] in
it I don't know I can't seem to figure
out how to use the
toilet I think if you just stand in
there you'll release yourself you know
you reli yourself to the toilet inner
pece okay
okay holy crap she has so much
health oh man she is so much health she
dead now all right you may uh uh remove
your sandwich in peace now I guess are
you done I don't know how is it even
possible I don't think you I don't think
you can actually poop in this game f
there's an there's an icon which very
clearly to maybe it means that it'll
come out eventually on its own without
interruption do you need cloth do am I
wearing clothes actually you are you are
wearing
[Music]
clothes oh what was that sound I guess
my percentage is slowly going down but
the implications of that are so much
worse worse than if you
just go all right I'll try making your
clothes oh thank
you all right clothes are being made um
we we have not progressed far towards
beo huh oh but we're getting so much
stuff cho
cho okay I'm about to drop the clothes
here
thank
you and this one thank
you couldn't bear to look at
my oh I can hear your bow movements is
that a zombie huh no that's not me
that's not me are you sure are you sure
I think I heard it it made a little
grumbly sound grumbly grumbly and your
tumy I'm so
embarrassed I never should have aten no
no it's okay it's okay it's special it's
special oh what's
this look's uh screwed
up lead I can eat
that all
right all right oh wow we we look
dangerous and a little psycho honestly
yeah we do all right did you you want to
keep exploring you want to head to be
skip Parts maybe with something else I
feel like this will give us good
stuff I think we're getting XP and iron
punch it I think you need a wrench if
you want to salvage
cars
oh can I make
stuff here I'll make you a spear
too oh thank you I made an axe
here's your spear the ax is used to um
to harvest items it'll give you more
compared to
punchin wow the music's kind of nice
actually I'm a little
surprised what type of wrench The Tavern
kind but I think that's a
wench okay what else do we need guess we
can make a
bow see
uh I'm just pressing a random buttons
taking too long okay oh no I go
find how what button am I supposed to
press this one no this one this
one yeah yeah let's go find her I
guess
okay wait G is not that far from us now
do you want to I'm on my way
yeah should we go find her go together
oh R is also uh nearby she's right there
oh let's
see oh I sent her a party invite since
like she's literally right there na
across the way yeah getting a chased
by nice
job yeah work man you kill so
splendidly thank
[Music]
you we see
you too bad voice chat only works like
party
wise yeah and it's not proximity right
[Music]
yeah yeah I can hear you
guys
good yeah yeah
even oh
no maybe should thought we were evil of
our out I mean we looked the part but
that doesn't mean we are the
part let's just follow her she knows
here to
go okay
I just saw her teleport oh what's
this I don't know looks important though
shovel or no no I think the ax works
yeah yeah it's
working your axxe it does look
important all right I harvested some
I'll let you have the
rest I okay I'll get a campfire now I
don't know if it's useful
immediately um if I can get claw
fragment that would be
great I just love how we look
crazy what else can we
get we get oh we can get out of coton I
see um if I can make more arrows that
would be good I can't make much
though you
good yes I'm completing quests
oh smart smart oh did we lose Raa it's
okay she's like headed towards one area
anyway she
gone should we should we find
G uh isn't she on the
way I am walking quickly with yeah yeah
she's uh near the lake area and
everyone's gaed
up we can pick you up though if you want
G
it's okay I'm on my way all right well
we can stay
fo I'll be right there in a
moment
uhoh she crazy for
me nice hey shared
XP
yeah what's this hello I open this I
have like a sticky note but I can't do
anything about
it oh okay you pay on time every time
what the
Duke oh crap who's the
Duke do I care should I care I don't
know if I need to
care me got more arrows or
something yeah is a
Duke should we just pick up
Gigi yes
okay we should all right we're heading
towards you Skyrim
style Skyrim style yeah following the
the thing at the
top
oh I'm also following it we're getting
distracted yeah me
too maybe we should go loot more houses
too it's going to be a while before we
reunite with
everyone did they all make I put my bed
here though oh it's a I think it's a
spawning Point yeah it's my cheat
sheet I make a bunch of
punching huh yeah that's us oh yeah oh
hey what's up hi hello hey you got
clothes too I have cloth I'm clothed I
like that we all have very scary hat oh
hey there's someone over there scary now
we look
pretty there's someone there we do mean
that zombie no are they a zombie I
thought they were like one of us they
were look a shotgun I have you have a
shot gun nice why do you have a
gun how did you get a gun I did the
quest is this already already oh my God
I just one tapped him hello who who are
you too bad I can't hear you is
kiaha oh we should add her let me add
her uh let's
see okay sent a party
invite I mean we're going to be on
Discord soon anyway but I don't know
this is kind of
intimate uh hold up let me let me tell
her maybe maybe I got a screenshot and
then tell her you you you click on like
the left
one oh holy
[\h__\h] I thought I was going to kill us oh
my goodness
uh the plus button from
me at the left for party stuff oh oh I I
leave a
party oh I don't know I I just walk out
the
door it's okay we'll be in Disco
soon okay we'll be we'll be in Discord
soon so I guess I guess we head out
towards the
right I guess it's this way are you
shooting
gigg do you have
ammo can you take your ballet gave me
12 I wish give me more ammo give it to
me okay just put it back in the she's uh
headed towards here and then we go right
fine okay I like how we have this ADHD
oh crap what's that oh it's just hair I
don't care kill exp exp I have a gun
don't
worry I missed that's a waste of ammo
though let us RI folks handle
it okay okay I'm clubbing I'm clubbing
her I'm clubbing yeah we clubbing we
partying all night I'm not of stamina oh
rest up myel rest up eat an eggy
anymore I need another sandwi what is
this building over here I'm going
inside you guys already loot this why is
there a dead person here cell tower oh
well R went through here and maybe the
others oh they left Behind These
electrical parts though I hear like
hungry people office chair did want to
take the office chair
I'm hoping if I hit his cross he's weak
to it you think it still works on dead
people
scum you will not touch these beautiful
women well thank you my my
night jiggling and blushing o XD
more glom see you oh wow
anything else
here I'm climbing the cell tower so
hopefully I can get some signal on our
cell phones don't jump off I'm dying I'm
dying I lived I live oh good job I'm
hungry I guess I'll never find out have
egg oh good God I can eat it raw or I
can cook
it ah all right I I should probably eat
this egg
raw you should eat a sh Jam sandwich so
you can also have tummy problems like
fa I recommend it do you do you have a
spare um I have an
egg wait what is this
what I have a chili oh that's good you
found
food I spawned with I didn't find
anything man I Spa with like a death
threat or something
there you go all right they should be at
this house I
think
okay and then after this I guess we all
just inside of a house together doing
what uh
sority writing fan fiction oh
wow a medical o that useful this too PL
of plant is
useful I should probably pick this
up I think we should keep an eye for
pots and plants and general what's
the
strange oh what's that like
icon yeah we
do wow we kind of look like a
cult all right is it time to wait is
everyone I guess we join a Discord call
now I suppose so now we can all right I
I'll stay here though I'll see you in a
bit what's up my beautiful
girls I see hello
sorry we had
ADHD took us a
while we have someone
evil
stop I have no control control
my what's up what's up look at you you
look beautiful look this is my this is
my PC setup do you like it oh
nice garbage I can sleep on top of it
actually or maybe I
cannot can I sleep
underneath got
this where should I sleep I'm going to
find a room you like it very I mean
yeah it's co what happens if we take the
sofa
[Music]
apart I like it how do you how do you
set things down it won't set
down maybe I have to be in a
want to come I want to go try going to a
farm let me just set up home here really
quick let's go okay I come I guess it's
my let's wait for sh sh did you say want
yeah I'll come let me just set my bed
roll okay okay
how let's wait a second how do you is
there a tra here or you guys tra
pretty I'm pressing e oh right click is
there a Traer near this house oh okay we
Haven found one yet we haven't done
anything I off my hat I like that even
in the apocalypse trenda thing and we
all wearing the same style I
accidentally click fion
even either way if you guys open the map
you can set a marker for where home
is right we are going to
get that's nice
I'm sorry every time I tap back in I
punch
someone that's what
happened stay away from me truth truth
truth please don't touch me you don't
touch
me guys be careful don't hit each other
guys don't each
[Applause]
all right I'm going stay back so you
guys don't hit
me I should probably make
another
yeah we're crazy okay this way I think
was the Yep this way wait wait who am I
following everyone looks the same I'm a
little
hungry the one with spear I assume
follow this the the the flow okay but
I'm going to have ADHD on the way that's
okay
at any point you
want oh there's corn
corn
UPN we am I loud this uh amidst the
crowd of very loud
girls am I loud
[Music]
enough I feel like we should probably be
oh they're dead o let's go yeah there is
real in theow okay can we get can we get
to weant themo that from we have
potato okay I I change it a little bit
how is
this a tree apocalypse with corn that's
all I need I'll most of the Corn are
dead though it
seems to B we just can't eat the the
people
what people look look we got seven days
to die we got to have a food
supply say area has three three skulls
on it I don't know if we're ready for
that oh oh does that mean like we're
going to die yeah I I get the green one
the Lo probably really good but I just
I'm surprised there's like skull
images so I noticed that the green corns
actually contain prob oh they
do there's a ear corn they have
something
we could set up a little farm by our
home yeah let's do that oh there's some
real
corn we get yeah yeah so there's some
good corn
here I see you got to find a green corn
this be careful this is the three School
area careful it's not my middle name zes
everywhere what are they going to do run
after us
oh so much
corn all right I hope the corn re like
resupplies maybe a farmer shows up and
take care of things
hopefully where the
farmer I have so much corn I'm going
back home I'm out of stamina yeah I
don't think it gives you anything can I
eat okay we can
eat wait don't leave
me so we just need the beig w
we found
some who wants to focus on getting food
maybe we should split into like certain
groups food
gatherers Gathering and people stay at
home The
Gamers I think it means like this is
someone's I just put that there for the
quest worry not oh I don't even know
where my land claim block is so if you
put a land claim box down
apparently um it applies a hardness
modifier to blocks so it protects it
protects damage on something apparently
I'm still taking your corn so like
you're safe in the zone I guess or
something like that level or the player
who put it down is safe in the zone it's
like your land now that is my land
yeah one in the living
room oh we're in the same uh Ally group
too so we should be good to go it won't
be harder for us to destroy each other's
things if we need to exactly are we all
in the same party I have a question um
no party Ser
six how do you level
up oh level I think he going to
kill oh killing zombies okay yeah yeah
we find he gives Quest and he gives a
lot of exp from the quest does anyone
want to go with me on an adventure to
see if we can find the Traer I know
where he is he's really far I know he is
I have one on my map too yeah oh okay
guess we all have to or yeah yeah he
should I can share this way point if he
wants to trade he should come to us
that's right he's not going to do that I
think is this son not going to be our
Base by the way or he's going to stay in
here house oh
hello I found people welcome
home hi come come in come in welcome
welcome you guys something oh yeah we
started like a cult there's a hat yes
put your
hat what you should probably
like there's a zombie over there kill it
it silly I will crack you a hat oh wait
no I see a hat oh thank you yes put it
on Oh
yay
civilized
[Music]
he I don't know how to share the way
Mark with guys what what if you send
like a
SC gloves I'm missing
gloves okay can't craft anything just
yet
there CL oh I hear like spooky sounds
fix
this me is this going to be your whole
Base by the way
yeah we should probably do multiple
campfire
what is this land CL
block uh it's our our home base now with
this basically zombies spawn around you
see it I put it in the channel over the
map what if we all put our land claim
blocks like around each other so they
won't spawn within a radius yeah let's
let's protect the
house I don't have my land CL block
though
so where can't do anything right make
where oh I have have a land CL block um
I don't know where to put it though uh
it won't let me put it anywhere I guess
I guess fin to sleep next to
me okay I I see not was not expecting
this sorry I of events this is oh that's
not me that's here maybe here there
trying to figure out where to put this
oh yeah I can't put the land clim oh
yeah it's a pretty it's a
put it here I am dying of H I'll put it
[Music]
here we need to unlock
thep all
right put it by the
river maybe here oh we need cooking
items aook oh I like the placement of
the SP oh thank
you it's like a kitchen
yeah and you julig just put it at the
fireplace can't believe
it we should probably try to find um
like a cooking pot and a frying pan so
we can actually
cook okay
yeah oh I found a I found a cooking a
grill outside the house I don't know oh
that's good we should have put in the
house then drink some water we have some
water in our inventory too near freeze
is there a town
nearby uh there's a town very far
[Music]
away I am sickly I see
some that the
hell I'm going to eat scary food oh by
the way night soon everyone yeah oh you
guys have a nice campfire out here
wonderful we can cook s'mores the idea
that I have is that
vc1 is
all the other ones are for like going
out on different excursions
together
IDE that would be great
sorry
here she's here I don't know what to
do well I I think I'm going to focus on
finding food I want to I want
to CH too if anyone wants
going time stroll I'm going to collect
items I'm going to gather stuff so I'll
stick around the
house okay I will debate on what to do I
will might go
solo well I need to figure out how to do
things what is the cornmeal oh can I eat
this
oh oh you need water to cook yeah
realistic it sucks huh I can't eat
cornmeal I can't oh I
can ooh yummy cornmeal like purified
water you have to burn it with is
someone dying
eliminated how evil oh dear
why ter but to boil you have to boil
water I think you need a pot and uh
that's about it also we have to find it
I'm turning this off it's a waste of
stuff right now I can craft cornmeal
yeah me too how do I know how hungry I
am I'm always hungry violence between
our allies is concerning very concerning
how do I know when I'm not hungry how
much do I have to
eat I don't know what the heck okay I
think I'm no longer hungry soon you hear
that yeah that means is here it's nice
your stomach sounds like a
zombie I'm sorry I don't mean it what oh
oh I hear them stomach really sounds
like a zombie I don't needan it oh are
they trying to get in oh IEP up my
stomach uh someone keep keep an eye for
zombies I'm going to try to like build
walls or something I don't remember how
to
though oh we're not supposed to sleep
out SL but it's so beautiful the Stars
like beautiful
com that way how you oh they're already
in I mean to be fair we don't have
closed doors nor
Windows oh fire oh my God we're
fire in a good
way
oh this
anyway I think I build a building block
I
hope how do I change a building block to
something
else
can't I can't man building is
hard May if I just destroy this at this
point how bad is
12% wow that's 12% bad compared to
zero doesn't seem that bad
I need an item that places
items maybe I can SN
too I'm hoping to just put a block here
so we don't have Windows that people can
see us
through good idea yeah these zombies
can't
watch yeah watching our
sleepovers what kind of weird thoughts
weird can you name what dos or weird
thoughts
okay that's a building
block okay um we're partially the door
or
no help I need to get more wood there's
a weird
zombie oh there's a weird zombie outside
M scaring
crony have a
candle I know where to put this no fear
huh ladies I know who to woo
you're not afraid of
anything there you go I hope she
realizes my effort
anywhere I think we're good I think
they're they all look pretty
healed how'd you board them up
Kiara I just want to place a door
somewhere
oh this is
Minecraft
yeah wow we have like nice camping songs
the acoustic guitar
I have a
kazoo oh hey there's a deer here we can
eat unless it's a zombie deer come here
dear a I don't want to chase we just
snap it ran away you cannot sleep like
Minecraft
sadly you cannot sleep oh no it's evil
Minecraft need one more Stone I just
need more wood get the Traer
Quest do I heal if I sleep at least no
no I don't think so you like heal too
it's just spawn point I think
happiness I'm low and stamina and I'm
thirsty how do you use this so much is
wrong with
you you guys experience thirsty oh you
got to turn it on here weird at the
right you see a bunch of wood make sure
it has fuel and then you just turn it on
like
this oh does this building block even do
anything you have curtains that should
be
good building block and a wood block I
don't know the difference tell what you
need to cook something I have to join a
party a recipe I think how do I join a
party you can join
ours different
allies wait no shift click to select a
variant invite
me you can invite everyone right oh sure
wait I received a party invite oh sick
oh oh can I get one I'm currently not in
the party yeah yeah I sent
youa yeah I sent another thank you yeah
yeah I think you press I and just press
random buttons Yi w
Mor crony do you need a party or you
good do I need a
party
yeah
yippe
yipp wow this is so
domestic probably stick around
Harvest man I am thirsty my character is
like never satisfied
wait how do you experience
hunger oh okay oh that's going to make
me thirsty it's a your
inventory so privileged I know my
inv oh now I'm hung okay welcome to the
gang if you use a bone knife could
Harvest bodies
r it's like Harvest Moon yeah it's safe
yeah you can go
out it's day one it's not too bad right
now because it's day
one yeah tomorrow we die though there's
a dog with glowing eyes you think I'm so
excited bad are you sure it's not
hoko barant that's not a sound shift uh
click or shift
click shift click
this build flimed area unless they allow
you have a
curtain oh can you not build in the
house area no we can build I just my
chat just bro yeah we can't place
anything in a claimed area but I don't
know they can I place
stuff I place like random blocks oh hold
R okay let's try about this one no it
just rotates
oh if you like do this hey that's my
stuff wait I I thought it turned into a
wooden block I'll just I'll just pick it
up oh I got to repair it I'm sorry no
it's okay it's okay it's all
right I'm just trying to cover up our uh
for our privacy
[Music]
ohal and what you do how you right click
with an ax
I don't see any animals oh I probably
need a specific resource to upgrade it
yeah I'll go hunting wait really find I
think so I just need a stone ax oh don't
you need to like upgrade with
stone like I have the axe
yeah or maybe I need more wood I guess
we'll figure it out oh oh you need more
wood I don't have enough wood I guess I
got 85 though uh
oh my
a
oh so thirsty anyone got a
pot no we don't do pot around here GG no
pot here I'm out of here not in this
household you will all starve without
that
pot well maybe you should do something
about it
sunny I need more Stone
how do I pick this
up I can't pick this up can I just get
stone anywhere a block this block that I
placed down punch
it punch
no I not getting stoned from this try
try using an
axe God damn it I have to break why is
everyone
dying oh I don't I don't know that's
scary
maybe there's a house the farm I'm
thinking that too maybe we should go get
a pot yeah yeah we
should not because G wants it but
because we need
it let's go to the farmhous and see if
we can get a pot at night what if we
die that's risk we're really oh good God
the zombies can crawl on all
fours okay I'm leading it to you see you
guys you're going to have a present soon
I sure you know well oh good God I don't
have
stamina are you down no no I'm just
really tired she's just a little e oh
there's my base I'm eepy weepy eepy
weepy everyone's
dying I'm just trying to find some darn
Stone just want to fix my stupid Stone
a why do new one so much easier I can't
that's why I need
Stone I'll get some scrap
metal is that you hitting the car oh
yeah like you know it girl you and your
vandalism oh yeah this car is in my way
I'm going to destroy it man what if it's
like from Pixar though you're going to
get us in
trouble
oh his name I forget I I don't know I
never watched it actually black sedan
why I I got a magazine for like making
cars from a zomie oh nice nice good job
you can store that in a crate maybe oh I
already learned I'm hungry again oh my
God all right you're the car person now
that's your job I am the car person now
let's
go is your job now eat your endless
supply of
corn that's not a good
sign scary
all right I'm at the farm in case anyone
also wants to play Harvest
Moon okay is there a monster there yeah
it's really scary probably oh it's
breaking it down oh that's a big one I'm
hiding in the corn a big maybe defend
the that's a big end it's a big
one uhoh why people dying
yeah I'm trying now make a stone
axe oh God I mean I could have fixed one
probably grab it um I think it's over
what's wrong what happened there's a can
he can keep it not our house I'm
shooting him I'm shooting him get
him
ooh so glad I went away oh no he's not
dead okay he just faked
it how many arrows can this guy take ow
all right I'm heading back there oh God
okay I didn't want to use this but I
suppose I
will oh I'm I the corn response okay
hope I don't miss this wa what the wa
you I didn't want to use it going gun I
got my other Arrow what the heck I stole
all the arrow
oh think I'm hearing things oh sounds
like a
clicker all right I'm heading back is it
a lot of zom zoms no we got rid of him
oh good job there's a
big what are these noises I'm
so oh yeah that's the dude that was
chasing
me oh crap I'm out of stamina
here you get him the front I get his
back oh no you're infected we have to
kill you
now she be okay infected with ligma
what's
Lima than you what Lima I wonder what it
is here eat some corn maybe I'll heal
you you think it will
no but it tastes good we can eat some
popcorn some corn corn or some popcorn
corn yummy sounds really good all of
that broke into a house you got I want
to wait till it's day before here come
on Kara I trust you even though you're
infected oh thank you yeah I think in
the end we'll all be infected eventually
I guess
so that's good to it together she's
giving us her Lima
yay you don't want it oh I it was from
you I guess already have it I you
already have it no not yet I haven't
been corrupted yet all right then it's
about time there must be a stay away
from me I won't get LMA
today coffee oh
that's must way you seem very
knowledgeable can I borrow you for one
second in the voice chat okay
I am moving to three okay oh I hear
zombies why do I hear
grunting is it bro what what are you
doing here get a
room I don't know you sound constipated
though thank you oh no I'm not thinking
right
now I'm heing oh where's never mind okay
anyway oh
no back I hear them near me I just can't
see
them must have must have oh they're
inside the zombie inside that's not good
yeah it's not very
po good job
Mor now let's eat him an adventure but
we didn't really find anything so a oh
sorry well welcome back you did
good really our home he broke through
the
door all right we'll have to build
another
door really yes why did you get your
backpack why did you watch me I
that I don't know if this matters here
no no I for theie oh my God this guy has
a lot of loot
wow does anyone have like a pan
composing I read your I read your
magazine again H you
read way pressing R and change
it wall is there like no way to just
make a regular wall like this is the
wall like you know Minecraft question
yes do IR shutters but we can't do that
do I I use an axe for iron not sure
about that probably have to find a rock
and iron maybe maybe like do I need a
pickax or
something or just a stone pickaxe is
fine your junk in there Stone ax I guess
we can only make thick walls
though yeah okay chest or something
cutebe frame oh I can make grill for now
I go find IR how can you make the grill
corn be oh and that takes wood I used a
magazine to learn cooking skill and now
I have cooking skill
up I have to find magazines I want to
find a
magazine oh okay I got
armor I need a cooking grill but if I if
we have a cooking grill I can cook the
corn I think there was a you can leave
the cooking grill at the fire so
everyone can cook then yeah I think the
best way to go about the magazines is
probably to like share them in the sense
that like oh okay one person does all
the cooking one person does this because
otherwise you're not actually going to
anything I have I have two skill points
in cooking already so I guess I'll cook
she's going to be a cooker let
[Music]
me I have corn I'll drop give give me
your corn I will let's put them in the
chest the chest near the campfire is
like food want to come with me around
no
points how about we make a window got
the I'm going to the farm if anyone
wants to come to the farm with me uh
come to vc2 I'm going to materials if
someone wants to come with me
to nothing okay where was
the I supposed to be punching corn do
you think yeah yeah punch the corn and
then you get it but but they have to be
like not dead corn so the green ones oh
God damn it yeah most of them are
dead that one looks alive oh thank God
did you say we had a cooking pot
somewhere no I didn't see it um I'll
leave my corn here although I am hungry
okay do we have to steal a cooking pot
or something yeah yeah it's necessary I
think oh we also need to find a source
of water and like to boil it with a
pot okay do you guys want to try going
to the oh oh my
God I'm are we I'm hungering down here
your magazines oh really okay you can
have them back here put them in this
crate
here window it's really or did they
disappear afterwards yeah the the
magazines disappear oh I see thank you
I'm trying to wait you know
what
[\h__\h] one sec whoops I didn't mean to say
that oh man I'm tired oh shoot oh
hi you see cloth oh gosh it back
goly
goly our Windows worth it can't they see
then like know we're here thank
you Mar together
hey B are our Windows worth it
actually like they're pretty but are
they are they good anyone wants to go it
works both ways okay I'll just stick
with normal then I'm not going to
survive without okay I'll go to the farm
to oh my
goodness can you guys bring like food
and water I'm
dying let's make the stone ax and then
things will go FAS so that's good meal
you can make
cornmeal what is
this and then
you I have a feeling okay they can't
hear me right now uh another thing I
like to do personally it's really stupid
but having multiple doors actually is a
good method of slowing them down I
think it's like you're learning how to
be how does one get kind slows down
assuming they go through like the proper
area like here they might be going here
you can use spikes too but the idea is
that I just like
doors I don't know I'm pretty sure it's
good it does delay them a bit you just
let me know if you want to go somewhere
how how useful are spikes actually in
terms of a gas I'm at a okay I think
that's why I didn't use spikes they were
uh too
expensive however you can have multiple
doors
Quest multiple doors like this look at
that you want a side door you can have a
side door look at that guys a side door
can they even see what's there I don't
know man check out that side door I SP
quite South and that was the Traer it
sent me to yeah look at that they got to
get
to oh [\h__\h] they have to crawl to get in
here uh heck yeah I'm thinking after I
explore this stiff tool area I'll come
too okay yeah I'll join all right I'll
we in the same location though I think
so they're
St okay okay oh there's a
sow I want my snowy area to be there's a
scary dog in there with bright red alpha
eyes no ala
eyes all right I'm uh making sure our
home is up to base or up to code or
whatever how do
you um use your a right click you have
to have enough wood
though do we have enough
do you can never have enough doors
honestly I actually use doors to slow
them
[Music]
down pretty
there's a castle if you guys can collect
wood that would be appreciated in the
snow area my
God would be good later see down down
what do we need for the T man my
character's so
thirsty I am also very hungry right now
yeah I'm surviving on corn I'm sick of
it I just don't know how not to be we're
sorry crony we are commoners we're
peasants we starve
does one become hungry oh okay now I'm
very hungry I guess you have learned the
ways of the the common folk ah yeah so
this is how hunger is yes
unfortunately oh I'm out of stuff oh no
hry I searching toilets don't worry I'll
find food can you find water in there oh
I found some water toilet oh good thank
you oh no my savior anything is
helpful can
IAT you okay
H yeah we're trying to get resources
yeah we're trying to help you and for
the resources you can leave them in a
crates since we'll all be sharing them
okay if we get the cotton plants then we
can make bandages and
heal put this in here this food oh this
this is not
good how do you ever heal from an
infection
you die just accept it do not get
infected accept it good good to know
maybe you just had to have really good
hygiene and it goes away eventually I
don't
know I have accepted this way Al
[Music]
oh I get
all time to get more wood I don't know
what they can be used for but I have a
feeling that they're all good or maybe I
can make more doors what
up antibiotic and honey honey spikes are
expensive do we have to kill them kill
the bees kill like the
zombies yeah only if they're like what
are youie apolog
I feel like you know they might not be
that bad no no I think it's worth
killing them the only answer is
kill okay I'm going back home where is
home where is home uh home is on the map
press
some no problem we go get scared Comm
and
[Music]
oh yeah I'm just killing one looks like
the weather is turning
gloomy oh
yeah oh it's raining a.m. or is it 7 7
p.m. in the game I think 700 a.m. 7 a.m.
okay I think it's 24hour
clock I don't like scary yeah I know
many of you guys are scar
yeah they killed my family hello how how
can we make a farm that's so
unfortunate I I wonder if you need a
magazine for a farm that would be a
better idea uh I think you need to make
a farm plot block you need Rotting Flesh
for that for in this
area I was reading yeah I so I think you
have to get the zombies maybe you desty
what's your favorite magazine Vogue I
really like wiring 101
a good magazine yeah it was so good I
read it
twice two wiring 101 I just missed two
point blank arrow shots on this thing oh
my character's
tired well if I find point blank arrow
shots I'll give it to you we almost got
oh thank you I need to learn how to
aim
o oh there's a zombie for this yeah be
safe though tool shop they have a lot of
stiff tools it looks like oh yeah AIT
scary I scar it said it was like very
you guys probably use a not dangerous
with the both of us here we already
killed two zombies the zombie
true what for
decorations yeah I thought people would
be so happy
when oh yeah they will they're going to
love
my I can't tell if that's a town across
the bridge I want to
go I found a a burned Forest down the
other
way you get flesh from him I'm going to
go across the bridge okay good LU on
your quest may you got to find thank you
good luck on yours thank
you we can go Scavenging for
it this way
Ro
zombies I think there's a town over here
I can't tell this a town chest before
destroying them we need clay soil and
running
flesh dead body is not soft
oh I guess you got just find them dead
we need to find de
[Music]
carasses yeah maybe we should make a
double door in the meantime is that our
bag that must be our bag that's our bag
from the oh it only makes uh 10 blocks
get my bag close
0.1% door let's just grab it and go
great it ah it's going down I'm healing
myself with
honey wa how big is this door why is it
so big if you guys get Lon just look for
um tree Stomps and
uh get rid of the tree stop get the
honey and then drink the honey
that's
good that's that is that a I don't know
why is this door so weird like it's
[Music]
floats no get it get it this this is a
useless door oh my gosh do are usually
not so useless we push I think we can
push I find this to be a useless
door I don't know I don't know oh it's
probably cuz it's this thing I
see oh that's a lot this is not the way
to home what the
hole weird okay I'm just going to focus
on oh
yeah I need water I just drank my last
of water guess I'll just protect the
sides it's a beautiful day yay it's kind
of weak I
guess I I don't know I'm just put random
CRA here find a deer carcass we go Let's
Travel towards the Traer and then
take my double do someone wants to come
with me to the Traer oh go I'm going
there right
now I'm at the home it's like why is
there so many doors here don't worry
about it okay let's put some stuff just
except the fact that there are
doors I'm coming home away okay can make
a maze here actually to me can I just
make a maze put it all away and then
we'll take what we want yeah I don't
know what to do here
be Bamboozled that'll be like why is
there so many fing find some iron if
someone needs by the way there you
go everyone will be
confused I'll leave it here for now
what's up with the doors what do we need
it for
again Wear close I don't think so
stress crafting craf is under pressure
oh we can plant
[Music]
trees FL is for
planting okay okay we do
that okay we didn't go without let I'm
so close to home okay let's just Farm
some resources for now all right I see
everyone a split
off oh this's a building block okay
I am over
here I'll go find that house so what are
all these storage crates are they all
just like stuff it's just
inventory yeah I think everybody has
their own little for now I just put some
I put food in one storage crate since
we'll all be like
hungry so hungry we are I know it says
corn we should God I haven't had water
in so
long seems like I can name it we have a
lot of we can if you guys go near the
farm please collect more corn okay find
a pot okay a
pot oh we can use pot a
pot how are you without a
pot
the let us
know do you want to go to
V treat okay let's do it okay let's do
it okay let and I should probably go to
a different voice chat too honestly cuz
I don't know where going so hungry and
so thirsty and there are so many
everyone's gone here actually how about
we go there monsters GG I mean this in
the nicest way possible but everybody's
starving GG you're not the only I am the
only one Starving in here and I need you
to give me your food
I'm not feeling so well
either are you heading to G taag I am I
am starving I'm about to go forage for
stuff cuz all I have is corn and I'm
sick of
it si of
corn although if you go to the farm
please collect more I'm going to go to
the town hope uh hopes of finding pot
but please get me more corn yeah where
do I get water you have to find a River
and then I think you still might need
pot or a water bottle to collect water
from it are you kidding me right now can
you turn snow into water maybe you can
drink from it with your hands I don't
remember oh it gets heavy
here all right I'm about to wander off
see you guys goodbye good there only a
few guess I'll go
[Music]
here oh I can try taking them on yeah
and it's like a small room so I can't
like really kite them oh hello I'm about
to head towards your location hi support
us in our B I found a cooking po we can
we can make corn when I get that oh
yummy corn M I love my
grits I also found some be corn pork Oh
pork finally
meat but we need water I think is now
the issue
oh I see there are zombies Room what to
do about that to be honest
yeah okay I got
up there's a bunch of people oh my God
I'm just a lot of shipping crates up
here there's a lot of stuff so if we can
get them
somehow so I'm King them outside so if
someone wants to go all the way up
there's like a lot of stuff I'll
try hiting them because I'm on the roof
right now
did you guys finish looting the farm out
of
curiosity I think one of them no one of
the houses
but okay H I see I see never mind I'm
skipping down a
farm well that's bad okay actually maybe
I'm going to kite them so they come down
maybe yeah are you on the second floor
too CeCe I'm on top of the oh that'll do
it here I'm pulling some of these dudes
out they here in this house I see them
oh my goodness holy [\h__\h]
jump okay one went back in and two
down I need make sure I don't get
cornered I think they took some damage
from
that I wonder if hitting them in the fo
weaken them makes some
limp oh there's a lot okay I oh by the
way there's some more people coming uh
maybe like four zom zoms just let you
know okay and there's like a big
one there's only one with me upstairs
right now so I'm going to loot
everything yeah go for
it I found a
paper oh
crap yeah there's also two like right
behind
me I will uh do this technique
called medal
J nice
oh hey what's up found some vitamins
hello oh thankfully they're dumb wait I
think I'm
lagging oh I think the server yeah I I
was going to say they're dumb they're
caught in the
fence
oh okay she's
dead all right he wants to S
py he sounds like me when I'm hungry
[Applause]
here he's after me so you can probably
hit him during that if not
[Music]
busy reinfor chest and I will spend some
time e he birthing
uping clear out here now yeah there's
only like two zombies who take up a lot
of hits
yeah man he has so much health I'm going
to kill the the zombie that's
upstairs I'm
dehydrated we need to find water well
there's some water here it's just too
bad we can't just eat the snow
I know wouldn't that be great if we
could just eat
snow isn't it
take I'm not drinking your yellow
snow where Linate sorry I'm not that
into your Jewel of
emotions snow of
emotions I'm out of stamina SN found an
egg oh you're not starting like a
lemonade business with
it man my character is tired go away
zombie I can't okay time for me to drink
m i don't have murky
water oh that's how you do it it's going
to take some time to
heal okay I'm
at oh he's finally dead he's not dead I
lied tra oh my gosh oh you're up here
come on
I will help
you okay I'm just going to leave this
guy to you guys I need
help use your
axe oh I I'm like too weak in
general no you you can be like mentally
strong it's okay bro I'm tired my
character is
thirsty this guy is like too he's too
big in
health okay I'm leaning him towards you
good
luck so uh what do you do before the uh
zombie
po see uh I was designer actually oh
wow what did you design like a yeah
mostly like yeah mostly you know rich
people they would hiire
very oh hi
Mor oh thank God that guy would not
leave me alone thank you focus on floral
vintage
Aesthetics oo sounds fancy and then uh I
was pretty lonely for a
while in the zombie apocalypse but i'
you know i' found groups like this
before but they never they never last
they never last
let's leave him outside we don't want to
get narrow
here I'm ready to open up again we're
glad you're here thank you thank
you welcome to be
honest that how about you what did you
do dang look at
you look at you you just killed an IT
guy unemployed I had no job I preloaded
so I'm kind of glad Society fell during
this zombie apocalypse so everyone can
start over and be equalized because I
was theum of the earth
you you your life is better now than
before yeah my life is better now cuz
like everybody everybody has nothing on
the same like playing field now yeah
great okay don't you think usually you
would want to push yourself up instead
of people down well well now now I can
now I can you know oh so you feel like
this is this is this is my second chance
at like yeah and now you've become like
morally very positive and supportive and
exactly before I was just like you know
unemployed looking at wow all those
people with their um switches and PS5
and I was really jealous but now nobody
so you like a
vtuber
p I understand it's good I'm happy that
you get to put on a leave okay I'm
opening it oh
ohing for fun one first eight kit pipe
baton if anyone wants a
baton armor pling mod um I'll take this
scrapping for I'll just I'll just oh no
someone else can take it I'm can I water
from here please someone want to be a
nerd I have electrical TR magazine AAL
Journal Jal I can do medical stuff
I don't want to be a nerd I'm
stupid do you want to pick this up
I'm see scrapping for
fun bandage
armor maybe I scrapping instead of
medical I don't want to make decisions
before we talk to the others maybe they
decision it's raining
yeah there's a house there
I'm going to keep uh looking around
here oh
nitrate we still have not found
water yeah water's the big concern here
yeah and you can't even drink out of the
toilet I think we have to oh okay I can
take the rest I'm not sure going to I'm
just going to put some flowers I don't
know if we
need okay I I think there's like a way I
don't know how but I think there's a way
to like a water like okay oh yeah
there's a
zombie I don't
want I just put some random stuff in the
chest oh your phone I want
that you're still alive
okay um how are we feeling
time oh 2: p.m. only yeah we can keep
adventuring if we want to but pretty in
cucumber maybe we should head back to
the farm just once to the farm not the
farm sorry off home okay okay okay okay
let's head back home put all our stuff
back and then oh if anybody wants extra
arrows I put in here cuz I don't have
any room oh nice I need arrows okay nice
nice nice Arrow where you put them in
this
CH
P
trash do you think
I'll just me
myself man they have so much health I
also feel like this is coming
alive uh anything else
here no okay I'll go back for now I
assume I assume they've been here
already there's a fireplace this house
is kind of nice
actually it is pretty good I feel like
this is a place I've been in well
whatever the other one has a
yeah you're right sorry have they been
here and the and the and the what is it
called this gives any more planks I
guess PCS yeah the PC set up
on yeah all right nothing work we didn't
go under oh he scared
me did you root everything no I just
looked around and killed
things
okay yeah so the general rule is uh vc1
is our home base and then all different
groups that are going out on excursions
together yeah cuz we don't really know
if Poss tat really works in this game so
it doesn't it only works in party I
think was really weird because it when
we tested it didn't it Kelly yeah did
which is extremely strange maybe it's
based on if there's like less people so
smaller amounts of people could
work we were the same though we were
four earlier and we were for the other
day as well yeah I I tried it earlier
during testing and no one could hear me
when I was out of the party it only
worked when I was in the party yeah and
even then it wasn't proximity in the
party it was just uh General chat
General yeah whatever like a
radio oh Alex okay I feel like this is
working espe when we in the little bit
smaller
groups oh I think so
oh I found
gasoline
nice oh he's alive beware of dog I'm out
of stamina in here okay I found pumpkins
and I found eggs and so much meat's meat
something okay I will let me I guess
I'll just uh solo
everyone as uh as usual I'm going going
to go drink corn my my
or sorry go eat go eat more corn maybe
that will give me some boost and
strength I'm having to reinstall
everyone's having a grand old time and
she's just killing
[\h__\h] wonderful I will hop over when I
get
home okay I'll just
uh having to cook some corn and some
meat and some stuff I I just want to
search over there
can they even fall
off cannot hear me huh oh nothing no I'm
I'm in a barn with like three things so
I I'm trying to figure out how to kill
him without dying here let me let me
come help you first and then we can head
back together sure I was just looting
this place near your
farm wow my character's like so tired
I'm just too thirsty y I can't even
drink glue thirsty I didn't know you
wanted me that bad I can't help it I
just look at you and think like wow my
beautiful yellow
snow which Barn are you in there's like
three uh just press um you're you're
near it just go left wherever you're at
see I
see it's just like if I do one thing I
lose like 20 stamina immediately that is
how tired I am I am I am not tired are
you down oh be careful there's like
three crawling zomb zombs like right
there I know aren't they kind of
cute wow I hear the
music yeah me
too all right I guess I'll I'll try to
help
out thankfully they have very bad AI oh
there de de one you're so quick okay I'm
tired please please carry on are you
upstairs or downstairs I'm still here
I'm right behind you oh okay here it's
just hitting takes up so much energy I'm
so
tired I got a knife
that oh maybe it's cuz I use a
spear like
oh good God there's more I think she
wants my autograph oh she can jump she
can jump oh my good God on okay thank
you oh man I think my axe
broke oh there's more of them okay seven
days to kite okay I got one another one
maybe she going to I'm I'm behind you
there's another one there's like two
more the what the huh uh-huh over the
what the ponder over the ponderer I
thought you were like a
pondering oh look at you you shank so
good for someone who didn't do anything
in past life you shank really well
you're like a native
Londoner oh than I had one skill I had
one skill in my in my in my past and
that was shaking people to survive so
wonderful my hero so you're the Shaker
she's the Shanker
she's
a okay there's like literally not much
here uh there's clay okay we're good
this place sucked I have come here to BR
you for food over I'm sorry we only have
corn well no I have some no we have like
a bunch of meat we have like 30 uncooked
meat well I'm surviving on
corn I continue eating my corn what's
you want to go home so we can cook the
the corn and then I oh yeah sure yeah
over thank you see you okay over see you
there over see yeah
over ooh egg so so what what were you
before the
apocalypse H I actually think I have
amnesia oh wow yeah hit your head too
hard huh I know probably got run over by
another freaking truck I could have
sworn that before all this I might have
been in this world that was all squares
and blocks and everyone was like really
really
crazy crazy a I was
crazy you were crazy what happened then
did you make a movie called The Joker to
and
flop wait I haven't I haven't seen that
but I've heard like the memes is it
really I heard it's bad oh what is you
heard it's bad I heard it's bad that
actually makes me want to watch it
though
oh D's my
axe was was the first one like really
good okay the first one was actually I'm
dying of dehydration holy crap uh the
first one was actually
decent the first one was like good I
see well uh you can watch both and then
you can uh proceed to enjoy one of them
oh it was meant to be a oneoff but they
made a sequel anyway according to the
voices in my head yes that is correct
I'm dying from dehydration beeps I just
want you to know that you're great here
I'm going to drop you some juice here
come
here take my juice it's not lemonade
well even if it was I think I have no
choice but to drink
it oh thank you oh finally musical for
some reason yeah so they like so
characters just break off into song yeah
pretty much oh that's cool yeah there's
also some uh some very kinky things I
guess why is my running in place
my is she running a place for you or is
it just
me how do I put the
cooking uh so at the right you see like
Fel right and then there's tools put the
the pot into like any of those
tools oh okay yeah there's already fuel
in
there
[Music]
oh oh okay I'm going to oh thank God we
can finally eat something like fried
corn now I'm going to I'm going to make
31 cooked corns oh blessed the
corn oh cooking grill required I can't
oh I can make boiled eggs though we we
will have to deal with the eggs then oh
here we actually have 15 eggs eggs how
about I drop it for you and uh should we
join the other voice chat now here's the
the
eggs
oh oh I can make bacon and eggs okay
cool yummy okay let's join the other
voice chat
yep honey honey we're
homecome
[Music]
home I
brought my cooking
I have I dropped like 30 meat on you I
can make bacon and eggs and I can make
boiled meat oh thank God blessed the
heavens t let me cook we're so we
have
y can you make tea too B boo um
the you need JS for that would
you oh I oh I found a golden rod
flour
nice oh you can make you can purify
water as well yeah yeah we need that um
basically if you have murky water I can
purify it I have I think we have some
wow that's cool okay I'm going to
we have two uh murky water I'll drop it
for you here
go thank you yeah all natural murky for
the murkiest
reasons M
yummy closer to the tra yeah actually
it's okay since we're near a river with
our empty bottles we could theoretically
go near it GA of water and just like
boil that endlessly I hope wao you guys
have bottles I don't have I
hope infinite water trick I don't have
any bottles open your mou just open your
mouth just look up oh you can't anymore
why would they do
that what about glass jars how do I
split a stack I'm blind I think
right I'm just going to do a
quest oh I
fig do I have a quest I don't see any
quests any more cooking books uh
challenges I guess that would have uh
helped I guess this really would have
helped looking at
it am I have some Golden Rod
flowers them so that I can drink
them we
drink thank you how do I give it I think
living off the so we get more
food I would like more brawler I don't
like fist
though gain
tolerance maybe healing
factor out of food okay so I need I need
one more level in more benefits from
food if anybody has
any cooking magazine cuz I can't make
tea just
yet
okay the sells the tea that you're
making for 144 coins I don't even know
where to get coins Dam that's oh the
tra thank you
sir I'm happy for you cook a bunch of
meat right now I found some acid if you
think that can help stomach
problems it would help with the liquids
I
guess oh be you want to put the the
cooked food in this one the storage
crate which one the right one and we
should try to figure out how to make a
farm soon the one that the one that
you're looking at yeah this one are
where I need to go for myet Quest when
did you take this Quest oh I think
you're sharing cuz we're in the same
party Del it for you don't worry well
how are you already there oh I was just
walking wait I don't think I can do it
for you doesn't let me okay I'll wait
here coent
there oh you can label the
boxes okay I'm
wayy what you call we can make we can
make glue I can eat glue I don't know
how
to I guess some's using it I'm just King
meat at the
moment okay awesome a big
sleepover
yeah I love it you look like
delinquents how do
I one instead of all the it guys I
don't control right oh water I'm sorry I
got to drink
some I've been dehydrated
water control oh am I finally like not
as
dehydrated no I'm so thirsty as
heck why can my skin not absorb the
water from from the skin why not cuz
you're DEH glass jars just disappear
that's
stupid eat them why why would the glass
Stars disappear after using them am I
just going to crap out glass like shards
now that makes no
sense oh that's some storm
rain oh too bad we can't drink
it
open opening your mouth
yeah yeah you just have to look up at
the sky oh my too bad I already drank
all the
water excuse me you still the
quest please I'm so thirsty and so
unwet am I am I
drinking I can't tell if they were
kiding no we're not you just you have to
wait it's very incremental I see too bad
I've already drank oh spooky storm
okay
I'm is there anything we can do at
night
prob C I'm going to grow mushrooms at
the basement I love crying me too going
to find supplies in here I hope the
mushrooms grow inside
there what zombie what's
wrong where is he stuck at my three
doors no I think she's doing a
on your way I'm on my way I'm farming
behind I missed all this it's very
scary oh maybe I can't Farm
here I probably need to farm
plot a rotting
flash what I need for
this man I can't make my hops I hope you
enjoy my triple door
TR totally F yeah I have to go to the
Traer anyway I want I didn't run any R I
just thought if you going to do
something El I got to go there
anyway going to take a couple minutes to
but I put I put F might be one upstairs
it keeps saying me oh Char meat yummy no
no no no Char meat is the food it is the
food really Char meat wow Char meat is
look at my my wonderful Chef that's the
option that's all I can make right now I
need one
more make better stuff it's okay it's
okay yum yummy you're going to eat my
Char and you're where's the boiled eggs
o it's so nice and dry okay I'll I I'll
eat it I'm d I'm okay I'm going to go
wash the why are you
ding no you should be here you should be
here am I am I washing the tape off the
mouth wait should we go into a VC yeah
we can go yeah which one two four
okay
what uh was it two I
I this isn't four
sorry no one went wait wait what what
are you guys doing are you going to the
Traer oh we're doing Quest right
now and were there and said if you're
not in you autom fail the all right I'm
going to number four see you guys love
you all right we're going to four right
I'm making I'm making boiled eggs if you
wait like a couple
minutes all
right oh it's so longer raining my water
is
gone what a shame I know they hate me
they just want to dehydrate my
butt
evil oh give it to me and I can
purify
it I'm going to put in the food actually
here I'm going Drop It On The Ground I
really need water actually how can I
unlock
this okay there you go okay took them
okay that's huge that's a really big
deal always check toilets ladies toilets
are full of water that if you boil it
you can drink okay one minut cook let me
cook I am cooking okay and then we can
definitely we can go to the tra the tra
is pretty far huh yeah it's an adventure
sry 9:00 p.m. we might die but that is
true well just prepare your spawn points
you got your beds
already yeah that's true also you know
we did it last time it's fine it'll be
fine oh who's this a little water drink
and then we sorry you water still you
guys have enough water you guys have you
guys decent water I'm starving and
dehydrated but it's okay I am hydrated
but I am
hungry oh there's a c i see how cooking
works is that why your meat is
charred Char meat's pretty good
actually no it's guess it's okay you was
going to be serving us up sirloin staks
pretty soon I know
it oo I can't wait let go my Gordon
Ramsay oh does it go into like straight
into the storage cases if I take it out
it shouldn't that's kind of strange by
the way was I meant to head to
the
H I'm heading to the trader now I hope I
don't die okay
we'll go we will go as well but if you
want to go ahead do it I'm getting items
too I am okay hold on before it hits
night okay here you go here's some water
all right ready to
go thank you so much B let's run ladies
let's run close the door maybe you guys
can probably catch up I'm just
walking there's ominous music now though
my
C
should my map got marked with a
traitor are they
sus we don't know yet we have to the
Traer is very hot H does seem like he's
on fire no like she's a beautiful lady
wowful lady yeah too bad she just won't
let us live with
her yeah I know a shame right I know
no oh I hear them I'm on me way zombies
can run
not all right hope you guys catch
up yeah me
too you know where you're going I'm just
following you I have a mark uh a marker
on my thing but I'm also dancing with a
zombie right now
[Music]
oh everyone has
died oh that's old never
mind is the marker for the Traer is for
you guys is it the uh the orange one I
think so it's called White River citizen
for me but I might okay yeah me too
everybody died what happened uhoh huh oh
hey I see you guys running I'm just past
the river Let Me swim to
you oh I'm
wet maybe it's
because
collector say it you
won't you challenging her I
won't you think I would for that trick
you yes how
um hello guys I feel like it's important
for social hierarchy to find out how how
old everyone is in the zombie apocalypse
CL oh that's not you guys that's someone
else oh man I thought this was one of
you you first
over okay I'm
um
minutes what really wow you took forever
to die kill it can you take it over eat
it running away that's a shame
over I'm
actually
[Music]
forever I'm 38 guys I'm
38 so that means you should do a lot of
things for us as the uh the older one
I'm I'm your
senior you
me I'm you say you're I thought you said
27 I'm 47
[Music]
yeah am I a
dog I guess you are now guys I'm so
stupid I keep like taking my hand and
putting it on my ear like a phone
my MTH man I better be getting points
for
this hello oh oh hey hello I just killed
like so many things on the way let's go
where's the tra up here
okay yeah we got a Skyrim pretend you're
a
goat is everyone here actually or is it
just you wait do goats go back I I don't
know but they do now
did you did you know that that they're
actually goats and sheep hybrids and
they're called Sheep
[Music]
oh isn't the tra
cling wait there's a time limit to when
he shows up what
oh I'm thirsty drink the water if you
guys if if you look up in your map I I
found a whole like house area maybe that
would be
nice there yeah I think the Tred okay
let's let the CC Mar yep yep you got to
go to The Cece Cece's pizzas
you9 I don't remember any
commercials pretty cheap oh I found some
Char meat oh this
reminds no mine has a special
touch yeah a Special
Touch little bit of yellow snow in it
just just because I shed a lot doesn't
mean it gets in the food that there's
like a houses actually well yeah I have
a lot of hair she sheds hair she's a
wolf yeah I shed like a
[Music]
dog okay we're here oh the Goldsmith
okay I am here go around I am in the in
the garage the garage I hear a bunch of
zom zoms yeah there's two at the door
uhoh get a little fast ow I'm maybe he
wanted to
die I need to
heal wait why why is the door close all
of a
sudden we don't get ambush from the I
think we might get ambushed inside
though yeah but it's safe it's okay all
right okay I need to make more
bandages now I will close the door
okay hey don't close
it we have less space
inside yeah it's not a good
idea you want more space
we're in a gold smith house right
now yeah we're like Smith but gold we
did it
y be great we can each have our own
homes oh sorry sorry I didn't mean to
close the door on you here uh uh come in
come in sorry I thought you were a
zombie come in come in come
in oh I hear
them I'm going to make more bandages I
cannot make more bandages make
CLA you
okay oh
nice I've got much I found I found a
oh uhoh that seems bad you okay I fell
in a
hole all right I guess this place is not
very safe
a lot of
people it's a little hard to cut indoors
though oh not
chapped
okay oh crap oh crap there's two of them
on me I'm going to die guys I love you
good night good night I'm
[Applause]
dead I should have put a a resting thing
here
there's two of them in the garage as a
headset oh I can spawn near on my
backpack oh that's
cool but I found a really cool
area that's
cool I died it's over it's okay you
found a really cool area though I did
find a really cool area I'm cold and
naked is it safe to get my stuff in the
G I think so are you guys in a garage
you place like a boat there oh my
God I know I'm in the hole but in the
hole is there like no take off they
following me up the
hole is there is there R R I see okay
want to panic oh hi
my you guys look a little
different oh
I can't see anything is
tra
yeah well we can spawn near a backpack
so I think it's fine un let's just
punishment I'm
infected all right well might as well
die for
everyone shoot I'm stuck I'm trapped
actually I'm trapped it is a b b
call
[Applause]
okay of a schol
world I would like to spawn near in my
backpack
again out my oh jeez leave me alone oh
jeez
oh you wh Rick
huh someone make me a spear because I
can't afford
anything I think we're all dead
yeah yeah pretty much uh I'm I got to
get my items
back however I think the tactic is to oh
shoot oh shoot what is this what is
this what is this
beep oh good God it's over this is very
interesting I'm
I'm okay
okay here I will sacrifice thank you
thank you you're welcome you're
welcome I will now have to get my items
down
there okay as long as you guys give your
items
I'm I'm going to go get my items again
what is happening holy
ho you're not that far actually I got to
get my items again um you guys just get
your items and get out then maybe we can
come back as a
group I can't get it's cuz it's on the
Upper Floor and I can't reach okay I got
my you can it come here never mind I'm
totally dead I don't want to die now
because St all right I will have to go
and
search a man oh this place
sucks we got this we got this
oh they broke the
ladder oh my
God I don't know okay I'm just going to
kill everyone in
here if I have to die I will die again
and again and kill everyone and take him
down with
me all right I'm coming back for you
guys mark my words
here okay all of
it no I'm sorry I'm going to kill him
slowly but
surely would you be able to make me
spear then I can help a little
bit oh
I'm just punching them
all I out that's good I'm punching all
of them even through all the
pade all right I think they should at
least be out at least I hope they stay
that
way they should all be outside hopefully
when you me out of
thank
you always never to ask guys um it is
call put your clothes on oh sh you're
right I'm
naked yeah okay oh they're after you
they're after you might want to run
C
actually that's your item okay they're
after me does anyone want to come after
them
guess everyone
busy no no I should I should keep them M
you oh
that's you want
to okay yeah okay okay just keep running
think I might die in like 5 Seconds keep
running
okay so you said they R the ladder uh
yeah I got to go back there though for
my item
oh I got my stuff nice if you can get my
items that's good too it's at the bottom
of the hole though okay I'm about to
die all the
upstairs that's
fine oh I can't
[Music]
see
I'm for
okay I'm going to try to get my
items okay kind of quick I got a I found
a sniper magazine like a sniper book I
could really use
gun that be fun how am I supposed to get
out magazine all right all my items are
recovered even if I die I don't
care
y oh thank thank you
for
thank Tech Planet I'll take the
snip okay I'll give it to
you oh what is up with this peaceful
music get out of
here no there's still one after me if
you guys want to
help oh there you go actually I don't
think what a
pain we need
to I don't know if it's a good idea
living here though unless we put all our
blocks down then it could be okay yeah
yeah maybe if they stop
spawning we I'm probably going to choose
crouch on the floor do you sometimes see
those like tiny holes do you know you
can only do control control but it's not
much of a Crouch yeah it's very
pitiful we could also build our own home
near the trader but it's kind think
building is at the beginning is going to
be kind of diff hard right yeah I think
so I think it's best to like y a house
okay do you guys want to go to the
trader then or do you want to stick
around sure let me go there my two
Health oh no
do we pick everything here did we
everything I don't think so I still hear
them in
fact hi
my hello oh gosh the floor is locked I
know I think they're probably below you
guys go back inside oh you guys are I
got to get my corn
meal ooh roty flesh yummy yum delicious
I know
I am a bit over encumbered if anyone has
space and would like to share the burden
no space I I don't really have space
either I have like one slot
open can't run
anymore it's over maybe you should eat
all your
corn I don't have any corn oh an archery
[Music]
guide guess I'll use that I could use
it SCB
this eat my corn
meal stay nice and strong I know heal my
five Health
yeah all right there's other houses here
oh I haven't been hungry in a while it's
just because we've been in a death Loop
yeah maybe maybe it's a good tactic
though what's the punishment of death it
might be you shame that's about it
that's not I don't have that not much of
it
that there are a lot of houses around
here right for the picking though
especially yeah I mean if we can respawn
your backpacks I think it's worth doing
it um more you should put clothes
on I don't know why yeah you're naked I
accidentally have your clothes I think
when I picked up your backpack it
automatically put on your clothes on me
oh that's okay I'm just making new ones
no okay I can come down I'm just getting
some she already made
it is there any spam mail
you think is in this house oh Urban
combat who wants to learn oh this is for
stealth Urban combat's good for everyone
actually Okay who wants to excel at
stealths I might go for archery oh I'm
doing agility so if you want to give me
stealth stuff you can okay let me know
what you want I'm not going for strength
or anything but I'm going for I want to
go for
strength speed and Parkour
Speed look at you guys killing like an
overworked nurse I can't believe
you all right uh blue uh Beams I think I
almost call something else here's your
Urban combat
Bo almost
apparently now go collect your Urban
combat thank I'll take your corn in the
meantime it's probably someone in the
closet oh what a nice
fireplace one sec I'll be
right oh medical supplies in the
bathroom a
[Applause]
PG stream oh my
God can I do it
paper there's an option to turn off
Friendly Fire yeah we don't want to do
that it's more fun this way it's fun oh
man I have way too much
crap he maybe we should really look for
another base close to the trader huh
yeah I'm but walk I think I'm going to
go back home because like I can
literally not walk yeah I might do that
too do you guys want to do that drop off
all our items come back let's loot this
house if I searching this house and then
we can go yeah okay I'm I have like two
slots left so I can't think I can I'm
just going to go be uh in
cucumber someone's mad I stole her
coffee beans so I'm going to be slow you
guys I'll just go home that's okay I'm
going to be slow too we're going to I'll
be slow
SL yeah I'm nice
yeah that crotch shots don't work on
zombies I don't think they can feel
their
crotches
maybe they can't feel the love
[Music]
tonight I'm playing a dangerous game
there
I don't know what you're talking
about what a small house oh I got a
little achievement but it's not the size
of the house that matters you're welcome
now who is complaining about my cooking
did I complain or did I say it's uh
wonderful beautiful
amazing guys back me up isn't that what
I said didn't I keep praising her about
her great cooking oh oh yes I I remember
I remember that the 21st of
September no I don't remember that
anymore I have
amnesia but I don't have real Amnesia
have plot Amnesia so it's okay o ask for
it I don't know what's going on
apparently meat will make you thirsty
though so be careful that makes
sense oh no you need I'm wash down your
steak are you ready to have back yeah
I'm just going to equip the medical
thing um I learned medicine just now
because I don't want to be incumbered
okay when do you when do you want to
head back that right let's head back
yeah all right head back theone will be
mine eventually all right oh can we
invite shy to the party so I can see
your marker better oh yeah you oh I'm in
a different party how do I leave a
party I sent you a a request oh okay is
this technically cheating on my other
party no you're with us right now okay
is it this one oh wait how do I join
your party how do I leave a party
oh I guess I got to got to kick people
out here I'm make GG leader see see you
guys you
go excellent and then how do I how do I
leave
party oh here it
is
okay I can join a party now you might
have to send me the thing again okay
let's
[Music]
see thank
you great now let's head back to home I
suppose I hope they don't think I'm a
home wer or technically you guys are a
home
wer I guess so that I mean have your
relationships in that party been your
relationships already well well fauna
put her bed next to mine oh
oh yeah I and then I put like a candle
in the room I haven't had time to like
sleep next to her yet though cuz we
can't really
sleep that is messed up though I can't
believe you would do that to her oh I
didn't do anything it's you you guys are
the home wers they didn't like commit
yet they didn't sleep next to each
sleeping her on and that's I didn't do
anything I think you guys are the home
record look at you you little do
anything we didn't even know where sleep
next to each other you never asked now
you have to take responsibility you have
to put your beds next to
mity will not remove the guilt from your
life I a little guilt it's
okay I'm morally flexible
today I will cook eggs oh what's
this oh wow we did catch up to you yeah
I told you I'm really
slow you're not slow you're great oh
wait no that's C okay never mind we'll
catch up to you
eventually I do need to find a yeah
you're actually closer to the home than
I am I think because I'm really slow Y
and I'm growing tired because you're
cucumber I am I am I am
cucumber oh I didn't even know that we
could hold more stuff than we have it
just makes us slow yeah it just makes
you SL I mean it depends on the weight
too
probably and this music is actually kind
of
nice you have music yeah I mean it's
part of the
game yeah why don't we meet CeCe to help
her carry some stuff where is she she's
still slow she's not on my map oh she's
the yellow
one oh oh we're almost here almost
home man I feel like a like a Jaguar
something running for
home yeah you're really bounding
bounding yeah I hippity
hop have
holes I don't think so I think they just
like sleep wherever well I mean some
animals have dens but I don't
think those that big cat does have like
a d I think those are should ask
yeah home you think she just Rams around
steals internet from people yeah just
like
beep what oh my god oh you did say that
you were like a mucher in your past life
didn't you oh oh yeah Street rat
yeah but but she's turned off a new Leaf
but it it really talks about how much
you feel that you're openly talking
about it you know yeah
yeah now
[Music]
everybody so we still need to learn how
toing
something might be hiding
something
know let me let me ask for the book
maybe make gunpowder sure why not oh
never mind they're like really far
all right we can eventually shoot
things I can't
wait yeah we definitely got to talk to
the trader because that's going to be a
big a big Point turning point for so we
better go to the trader soon yes yeah
the next two hours or so that's about
all we have right
yeah maybe we can make a little list in
the with magazines that people want that
might help yeah yeah I want to be a
farmer I want anything dead built
related and
cookie
okay I want to be a med and maybe
something like I haven't decided like
Electronics or mechanic or something
maybe mechanic I'm I'm not sure yet oh I
have a I have a tech
dkey you're W you are
panting I can hear you okay uh the
sniper I don't remember who wanted the
sniper I'm putting it in here
I'll be an Archer farmer I'll give you
this magazine it's a tech junky that
might be good for you yeah okay
electrical traps set the one
more honestly we do need a different
base I don't think this base will hold
out for like seven days oh hey the tree
screw up seven days to die
yeah did did you end up making new
clothes by the way armor piercing ammo
okay I'll take that
all right should we head out soon to the
trader so we have like plenty of time to
loot as well yes one sec I have to like
organize all this stuff since it's
morning time let me see if I can
back you going to go
[Music]
Club how do we make that oh glue short I
need four short iron pipes I think we
have that they're in this one one I'm
standing in front really
yeah but I'm interacting with it one 9
mm what what use is 9mm how can you tell
like pistols
maybe also we should try and go after
air drops there should be one every uh
hour but I don't know how to tr oh they
can leave us supplies but they can't
pick us
up yeah sadly messed up right yeah
oh I am yay and then what was the last
one so much stuff I'm a little bit
overwhelmed pipe
shotgun yay I'm making a pipe pistol
nice I will remain primitive we have a
do we have a box for like bullets that I
can put it in no I don't think so we can
make one I'll just use the one with the
magazines then if you have if you have 9
mm you can give it to me use it I put it
in the Box okay how do you name
boxes oh there's two of
them um hold e and then there should be
a rename option I think
oh here let me rename the food
one there you go
food what's this one how how is the Box
what's the name so I can make
some huh
what is it called in the in the in the
in the building menu oh to make a box a
CRA hold up building
block I think and then when you place it
down I think if you hold R was it yeah
hold R you can change it to different
shapes okay I also was able to do it
using the crate thingy I think is this
the one yeah okay thankk you oh yeah
y I'll just put all my stuff in here and
then if you have like a lot of items for
it you can upgrade the building blocks
oh cool iron building blocks at some
point we want to make we want really
fortify our home for the first rush so
finding out iron how to make iron blocks
might be really
big we were we'll have to look for
it oh some
here in my bed in my home you might want
to make like traps and stuff that as
well to put around yeah it'll be
fun what's
wrong did you fall in your own Spike
trap what
happened what you such a jump scare
huh my candle gone no no no no I I one
shot I one tapped you in the head with
my gun I just want
IAL I didn't think he would kill her
like instantly I didn't you don't think
a gun could kill
peopleo you so messed up humans B
boo Mur yours mess
up you served a I think this good
though here I'll give you I'll give you
some meat as sorry take take my probably
use I accept your one charred meat can't
believe
it well your life is only worth like one
charred
meat that's horrific I feel really sad
about
that oh
well I just had to test it one time okay
the intrusive thought took over I didn't
kill you and people thought I was bad
huh see where can we put
Spike probably around the house maybe a
little distance
though I'm going to try to make a
balcony so we have like an Escape Route
or a place to shoot
from good
idea oh I can technically make I don't
really heal yet I need one more Med kit
medical and then I can make first eight
bandage oh nice but I think can I do
that wait I can't
need five
medical I like how we just forgot the
traitor okay I'm ready whenever for I'm
ready okay okay just don't get in my way
or I might accidentally shoot you but
W accidentally on purpose these are
crossbow does this
work I was recommended I scrap them can
I not do this yeah that challenge
[Music]
oh yeah iron iron okay we got to do
something with the iron though we got to
figure out how to cook it or something
like that I think you can make a furnace
at some
point
[Music]
potato I feel like we need to find a way
to like be able to get
regular water drinking water there must
be a way to Mass produce water I think
they like collecting like collecting
water you know like rain collector stuff
like that ah oh my God the spikes but we
also get water from the trader when we
do quests he gives you like rewards and
you can pick water I think water every
single time yeah all right is everyone
ready yep ready to go okay that en I
must not let my blood take over oh can
CRA we can craft a du collector that's
what it is col so yeah if we do that
that would be nice yeah we need
something called a polymer something or
another he a workstation too we have
polymer oh yeah workstation uh so a
certain skill will unlock being able to
make the workstation is it
robotics oh we like 100 scrap
advancing I see well let's head to the
Traer for now okay and then try and get
the advanced engineering skill under
intelligence you guys that'll help us
create Work jop Work benches okay all
right why does why does someone put a
random door in
here being a little
silly all right Traer
time guys ready to run a kilometer
together yeah I have to run this is a
bonding experience bonding let's go 27
health
a song I'll sing a song in German uh and
then we all do it together wait how does
it go you know it's like there's 10
bottles
on but in
German 10 bottles on the door but in
German will be the night that I fall for
[Music]
you over
again there's another door in here
[Music]
and then
um I miss you where are you I miss
you and I'm so
sorry I cannot sleep I cannot eat
tonight tonight will be the night that I
will we you are don't
wor song like I didn't know this was a
German
song so we have to shake
her this is oh right we have to what's
up right oh I just heard am I crazy I
felt like I just heard someone join the
voice call never mind never mind oh like
Koko's voice maybe yeah it was like yeah
I thought so too
right
B maybe I'm just going
crazy kill what the B bow
what I I know I can't believe you I miss
you oh it's so fast for me to shoot wait
where is it where is it where'd it go
it's uh over Over
Yonder oh wait how do I how
is this really worth
it how do I cancel Maybe not maybe the
meat isn't that worth it may yeah I
don't think it's worth I can't even
collect the B of funny yeah let's not
let's not do it I can't even collect my
arrows
again all right that makes no
sense it's the Ping okay I missed
because of the
Ping faders S wheel I tried
I'm pressing doubt oh right click this
this server is not close to me there is
definite ping here but people but people
haven't you I mean the Shakura haven't
you learned about your past experiences
it's okay to admit weakness sometimes it
means gross yes and I will admit
weakness but it was definitely the Ping
of oh okay so this you're admitting the
weakness of the Ser it was not a skill
issue itself is weak like
a I I get it you know my dad told me
when I tried to play the bass in his
band one time he said you know it's okay
to admit when you suck at something
[Music]
a and then you beat him up to admit when
you suck at but that's not nice hey I I
will admit my flaws like I will
definitely go for the beef and
fall oh understandable yeah yeah I've
seen I've seen you have Tru so I believe
theyy with the Traders how do you get in
tra wck wait wait this is not the
Traders never mind this is borb bar
Fields oh that's the different yeah oh
we can collect corn here though oh I
need corn I'm
hungry go to Carl's cor car
car car
car is anything else here friends though
we become one with a
corn corn they're
cor
Corner corn is cornering hery I found
people it looks like they're digging
their grave oh really are they
MC as it as it w and Clon are here
digging their grave oh that's
nice yeah I thought they were like real
people anyway I'm going to the traitor
yeah I'm also I'm getting distracted but
I'll go to the as well okay I wonder why
they're digging maybe they're getting
items or do you think that they're
preparing their
grave I'm at the board barn or something
Bob is Bor have to get stop getting
distracted I'm coming
car's am I supposed to go to the
barn you can avoid it if you want this
is a nice house though no it is a nice
house this is a nice house are we going
in then fireman's
magazine I need eat more corn it's not
nice anymore they're keeping people in
CES no that's that makes it even nicer
actually it's like a
holiday yeah what if they're like well
fed and taken care
of yeah it's like a spa experience have
you never wanted to be in a you know
just like Grace who's Grace behind I
mean you've done that a lot I I have
I've been in jail basement do not want
to be in jail again can you believe
bio's been in jail that's crazy to
me I can believe it she shot you do you
do you really think that's crazy when I
shot you in the head Point BL and killed
you I mean but that's in the game right
no we're talking in the game oh look at
the piggy wait AR we don't kill the
piggy I like the piggy ah never mind
kill the piggy kill the
piggy the piggy that starts that's
down I'mma eat your body tonight baby
good job let's get this pig okay you
shank
it makes a point
yummy oh maybe they had like a little
wrong way I'll see you guys at the there
is a pig oh what is this there's a pig
in a cage I leave this pig for now but
if you do anything to me piggy I kill
you Gordon Ramsey recipe picking a
cage I might die soon Gordon Ramsey
recipe I I'm indors it's
Smokey why is it so Smokey I think
probably follow kie she's like basically
at the Traer right now oh sorry we went
in this house we're doing some looting
first yeah I got distracted I found some
shoots distracted again oh they have oh
wait there's another Pig bees prepare to
kill this pig in case it's me but for
now for now maybe it's okay oh I think
it's just eing okay leave it for
now oh there's a
zombie good job it's not dead
yet eat my bows and
arrows somehow okay now I got it okay
there's a hot girl in the in the the
trailer not the trailer the the
beginner's course
video a girl who's this guy sorry I'm
only into like fictional characters let
just an honest independent business
owner okay you have to stop being
so superficial he's got a lot of good
inventory but do we even have any oh he
yeah sure what did you think of Leon oh
he's oh oh it's here he's cute although
I don't know how to feel cuz like he
might have a thing for aah so I can't
trust a man who might have a thing for
someone else still although I think
that's the old version yeah oh there's a
cooking
grill you got the cooking grill I can
make corn with it okay I got
it man okay I'm probably going to let
myself die cuz I only have five Health
anyway I
got got
money me the drill I'll hold on to yeah
here I dropped it thank you no problem
corn now nice
I can scrap money that is a big that is
a big
thing
good food look at you
strong regular food with the grill are
all the pigs just Nam
Grace all right ready to dig well I
don't know what happened in this house
but I there's a
story they weren't digging their own
Graves they were digging for for buried
treasure
build makes part of
quest I like the idea of them uh digging
their own Graves though I think sounds
fancy I have a I have a weapon for you s
this one's better probably oh thank you
oh I actually have that too I just don't
use it I'll use it
now oh that one's like not
broken okay what I what should I get rid
of
candles look for that supply
Crate yeah diggy diggy this snow all
right are we done here sure yeah let's
just go lat now all right I'm coming
we're coming to you
guys oh that's the
pig let get back the kitchen
whoa you here
BS uh I I'm outside of the farm I'll
wait for you though oh wait how do you
how do you get out what's the best way
to get out I J I jumped out the window
that's a good
idea I will uh destroy my way out
actually give me give me 5 Seconds maybe
10 minutes
girls girls what's
up too sleepy I think I got go to bed I
was going to ask you see a bit Yeah
s I'll join again
tomorrow have a good sweepy
[Music]
weepy tomor see you tomorrow home
recer home what's up here come here huh
oh hi anyway I was going to go the other
way but now that you picked me up I must
now with
you I had to leave in style you see I
had to leave my mark in this territory I
see must be in
there let's go to the Traer I too must
eat my
dindon how how long do are we going for
tonight oh what what the heck hour and
30ish
minutes hi
you I get
it is that it down
there finally the trader can't wait to
go to Trader
Joe's is he a hot
lady that that would be Trader Jill
then oh my character is
tired Trader wrecked cuz I'm going to
get wrecked
wrecked TR W oh it's not a cute girl
what do you mean Mory tra W looks kind
of weird have to pay it's not a cute
girl at all I know I was Li I scammed
what are you standing there for don't
you have you going to buy some food or
just stand there like a goddamn I'd go
broke with more customers like
you what L he's kind of mean too yeah he
just said he's going to cut my God vepon
throat at least he's not cutting our
balls no I think we need
them I really want to shoot I know I
know you got to keep in the bullets oh
but he has he has so much stuff I guess
I can't shoot him yeah you can't steal
his stuff either I
guess man how long does it take for me
to feel cool
cor not do
much I don't know grit does a lot for me
personally she's not here can I can we
at least loot his house no we need you
can try well what he doesn't I don't
want to use the caned food that's
actually important compared to Corn what
is that button on his over anling
block guess I'll make a bunch of
fragments
what is that I got a stone shovel don't
worry about
it there is stuff you can loot they do
we really want to loot the Traer though
I mean I don't see why not but if it gu
it's in trouble kill us looks like he's
got three shotguns oh actually there's
oh can we take his
corn use
beers oh no he has a land he has a land
claim block I think a I I hear that
sound when you try to destroy
something all right are we going to dig
a hole or something yeah yes we dig a
hole all right what does he want us to
dig I guess by the exploration point I
have no idea yeah
yeah buried supplies let's
go okay let's go
[Music]
am I too warm or something I got a fetch
Quest I think did you guys get the
buried treasure Quest yeah there right
now yeah not that I was paying attention
but
yes here's a fetch over here actually
looks
like that's oh faed supplies is
nearby okay we're I'm going to go to the
berries with supplies first cuz me too
cuz I already marked it wonder if
they're going to do F Quest too bad we
can't just take like uh credit for their
hole they already dug
it can we see our Quest on
our thingy oh yeah I dug I dug the hole
already
oh I still have the to do I
think oh thank you for the redirect
hello
CeCe have a good good night CE yeah good
night put your bedro next to
[Music]
mine I thought I thought you put it next
to FL oh no I didn't she did it she put
the moves on me
yeah wow makes Quest together kind of
difficult but oh
well we just have to work together
wait do you guys have uh the berry
supplies in this area near the
farm oh you have it in different spot I
guess so it's the near the place of the
pigs we were at okay yeah then I guess
we all have to do it individually yeah
sadly but that's okay we can still you
know talk to each other if you want talk
you want me to
socialize yeah yeah socialization is
good even in the zombie apocalypse we
hate each other Ling to people how do
you do that my parents used to force me
to socialize awkward silence your
parents used to what oh they used to
force me to socialize I didn't like it
oh really yeah yeah they may me join
like freaking clubs every
Sunday May you
yeah oh why didn't music stop us spooky
all right I'm digging I hope this is it
I'm digging too I'm hungry oh my God eat
corn I can't believe you don't have the
same like Quest
though why did she do that to
her maybe she needs to get put out of
her
misery they quests are Auto shared with
party members that doesn't seem right
but does it yeah yeah yeah yeah I can
see your fetch Quest so if you wait for
us at the fet quest holy crap that's all
at once together okay so let me just
finish the digging
one and then we'll come over oh this is
going to be such a long digging Quest
and I'm like
tired my character oh this one gives
water I'll eat it now
it was not enough water I need
rain I'll just chill around
here around where the fetch Quest is
okay I wonder if we should just help
each other with our uh digging to make
it go faster
yeah if I finish first I'll come to you
and then we can go to T together same
ADV for yeah I thought we would be in
this we would have the same oh shoot I
hear
them I hear them but I can't see
them time for a
swim I see them
now actually there's a question mark
near a
tree that's good and then I will come to
you
after very first
nothing can be
shared okay I think I need to dig at
this hidden section I'm going to go back
and turn it in cuz I'm cucumber and then
I will come to you go ahead not going to
drown don't be silly wait what's this
E I just I just pressed e oh now I dig
okay oh wow you're far I know
get a little wood on the
side when you get here I would
appreciate you cut down the tree so I
can see
[\h__\h] okay thank
you you're
welcome wow just like a
Minecraft what's up I'm
go I'll wait the yellow exclamation
point for them am I just like digging
this entire area like how deep was yours
beibs it was I'm getting close
apparently if if it says if it says
you're getting close uh dig sideways oh
I think I see it a little
perception that's that's the outskirts
actually okay I'm going in agility
oh I'm tired
sure I can just level something up so
since you since
you have the fetch Quest already yeah
you already took it for us right
yep we're in the same
party all we got to do is gather at the
same area where the golden exclamation
point is okay cool and then I won't
start it until you guys are here all
right I'm going to help story first and
then thanks I'm stuck in a
[Music]
hole it told me I was close near a
treasure but my character's just way too
tired and I can't even drink
glue oh no not even
glue yeah did you do the thing as a kid
where you like poured glue all of your
hands and then spent like an hour peing
it off because it was fun not it was F I
had to do it yeah oh you had do it well
I mean yeah if I used a lot of glue and
it got on my hands I had to peel it off
but you never like put it glue on your
hands on purpose to not on purpose like
it was going to happen it was going to
happen in arts and crafts
anyway oh good God my character is just
so done tooed and
tired dang you need
stamina do I drink this murky water I
guess I will that shot damage is pry
good ooh
yummy need
cardio it's cardio like stamina that's
just sprinting from it looks like cardio
is like running and jumping and
sprinting and so stamina I need a dig
all right I can't afford it anyway
actually oh yeah I want more bullets so
G
it's in the outline Circle this
one I thought this was just like the
circle uh getting stuck I don't know
where I am actually it was in the circle
yeah I'm pretty sure I'm with in the
circle maybe need
like I'm hungry
oh yo are you here yeah yo
yo H I'm out of stamina it is so
horrible gosh darn I'm actually I might
be stuck I think I'm
stuck I'm here please help me my Brave
One my character is just such a
princess and you sure it's not in your
inventory if you press tab you don't see
a box in your inventory I still see the
outline Circle so I don't think it's
here actually I think I'm going beyond
the outskirts from there so you might go
this way which way this way uh whatever
I'm looking at yeah oh I see it I see it
look look oh you see it oh thank
God oh I found oh nice you found it oh a
sandwich and murky water oh huh yummy
what was that oh I think I mix your leg
with the shovel oh I see okay how do we
uh all right
that ooh so heroic he
that Dam why he's so fast oh he has loot
wa here you can have it biibs it's a
guns and Forge steel brass I I don't
have space
uh okay it I will drink my murky water
let's go give me my denter 12% let's go
oh we got forged steel out of that
that's cool o I have diarrhea
Yummy's helping me all right I guess I
got to go back to the
trader yeah and then we'll go meet cie
we can do all right I'm going to head
there
BBS before my diarrhea sets in I'm going
to break these tables real fast and then
all right oh breaking your own Pebbles
can't believe you get
[Music]
broken oh I see him hey there buddy I
guess this is what fauna was feeling she
was not feeling
[Music]
fun feeling
F owie owie
owie getting kind of cheesy now I got
28% of that
diarrhea it's actually diarrhea is
actually a thing yeah yeah but I haven't
crapped my pantses
yet you think it was just a myth a
legend
beeps
Yes W diarrhea I've never heard of that
before
dang oh about dentary
this is how I've heard
of well you won't know if it's fun until
you try it so let's go find you some
food to give you some diarrhea I
[Laughter]
guess oh
hello all right trador
wct here's your darn
Quest yeah what well look here boys we
got ourselves a real life here
and now he wants to be paid I think I
rather take a
pistol I meant I meant diara in the game
by the
way thank you for having to clarify I
have I feel like I have to clarify for
some reason people actually believe I
got work to do if you don't mind getting
your hand it's a deal dis you'll find
yourself on the wrong all right I can go
to the fetch Quest now okay let's go to
the fetch Quest
yeah after this I'm a
rest it's the easiest way
there man my headphones
hurt I still see your tier one fetch
Quest so okay maybe it was a different
quest for some weird reason that's awes
we all get different
Quest oh I think s accepted it different
class that's why oh cuz if it shows up
for everybody clear the area Quest oh
yeah that's what that's a new one I just
got I based it on what was
closest but I'm going to go do the fetch
Quest yep we're coming wait where are we
even fetching W I don't
know oh no now I have the dizle too hey
welcome to the rist
club I just wanted the Sham sandwich
well you got shammed I was a sham you
got sham W feel
silly you know what would be like
[Music]
funny if all this time um our Discord
was muted for one of
us that would be pretty silly I know I
happen
now I am not shio
silly it is getting kind of Darker here
oh dang R just kill
crony why does she keep doing that do
you think um probably like past memories
of being married I don't know o I got
casin oh I got an actual
pistol nice nice I anything sandwich at
22 that's very I'll open that
later zombies what if we hide out in the
water I was thinking that might be a
good idea well can they down they don't
have
lungs true well yeah but they might be
slowed down by the water and then we can
kill them from afar maybe oh yeah
there's an
idea I wonder what happens if your your
diarrhea percentage is like super high
does it affect you or something I wonder
mine's going down slowly yeah mine too
like I don't know how it affected
me yeah maybe it just like makes you
hungry or something like that maybe or
you feel shame you know oh let's share
some of our shame with you then
bio no thank you I do not want but
you're the jewel of emotion so you have
to feel our emotion of
Shame
that's I I I'm I'm empathic for you I
feel bad for you but oh you feel bad you
feel
bad you have to go through a r motion
not your not your physical ailments
that's not how it works yo myy how did
you get there did you just
swim yeah I swim across dang look at you
my little buff buff
girl no it's you you can't swim can
you oh God feeling fear feeling fear oh
they're coming out he can swim well it's
night time like very poorly
actually but zombies can in fact
swim yeah oh crap I think I might
drown I'm
good you'll be okay I'm oh thank you
gr my
Tommy my Tommy my tummy
go wow I guess it makes sense that you
can uh fall in the water when you are
out of
stamina thankfully I have enough
[Music]
O2 ooh I think my character is about to
crap
themselves yeah
the wood door wait don't do it yet I
want to
see well that's up to my body I can't
control that beses I want I want to see
and laugh at you oh you know as then
I'll throw all the the results at
you oh never mind are you sure I don't
know we got to spread the jewel of
emotion CH my
mind how sweet yeah you can you can join
too I guess B you and I are suffering
the same issues you know I'll pass I'm
okay I see I
see away foul
beast and I'm slowly swimming
there you don't think they can swim
right well I'm slowly swimming towards
there I hope I don't
drown I think they can swim
just slows them down a little bit oh God
what's
wrong there's a bunch of zombies I
really hope they can't
swim
uh
yeah oh wow this is like a big
area now he's doomed to live at the
bottom of the Le he's oh my go oh
man is this place close
let me
in oh you can you have to press e close
the door your stamina goes down as
you're in the water oh I am I in the
right place oh good
God wait am I not in the right place
where am I oh
no where's my baton
[Music]
oh well I guess if I die it doesn't
really
matter ooh everything's going
dark
yeah all right time to go back in
there oh no now I have
diarrhea
diarrhe the
diaria
DI am I even in the right place
here we go oh I have to I went the wrong
place I am near you though what is
this not far enough away to sneak
yet have you guys seen the
video I have a bad case of diarrhea I
have a of diarrhea I have I have not
seen that but go on I'll send it to you
guys
no don't really know if I'm interested
no it's it's cute why do you think they
word made to say that they're they teach
they teach you English words through
aerobic dance and one of the useful
English the most useful English words is
I have a bad case of diarrhea I don't
usually tell people that how often would
you use that number one number yeah this
this like your introduction to people
beibs oh hey oh hey is this you found
you yeah hey anyway I might bring some
people in
here I guess it CRA it's useful it's
useful to like tell someone that before
you know it happen just to give them a
warning you know right you don't want to
just do that and without any warning
so I he's this other meme I like yeah
it's it's a big it's a big meme it's a
famous with the times okay well I'm
going to have to send it to you guys say
I need a bathroom quick that work works
or like I'm just going to the restroom I
don't even give them details you know
yeah he wait why why shouldn't should we
take this Quest now like what's going on
actually waiting for B can't we just
like wait here though she's swimming oh
it's dangerous here okay this is a huge
map I mean good you know there's this
one m i like where is this like if
you're about to talk to someone here's
some tips that you could talk about like
giving topics and then you kind of just
crack under the pressure and say I'm
going into
labor what yeah yeah that's what happens
when you panic talking to
someone but you can do a U-turn and you
still bring back the conversation to the
original topic if you bring up like box
manufacturing really what's a box
manufacturing how to make a
box how you how do you make the
box I don't know but you got to think
outside the box are you okay so do I
just make stuff up like talk out of my
ass like okay yeah that's what I do all
the time
yeah anyway that was a maybe I'll try it
next time try it try it okay try it
right
now
so you know carboard boxes are crazy
because what are they even made of like
I know paper's made of trees but like
like cardboard How do they even make
that stuff you
know uh
uhhuh oh I thought you noticed us I'm
here by the way okay well we're about to
go into
labor yeah oh I think you to spawn out
of nowhere hey I leveled up though let's
goel station Delta shall we start the
mission yeah there's a lot of zombies I
like how there just a Giant floating
exclamation mark
how do
you oh there they
are they're behind
us they're very
fast oh
crap yeah thankfully one of us has a gun
oh crap oh no
I nice
[Music]
job oh there's too many of
them okay how about I kite them THS I'm
going to kite them
yeah H okay K not
working however we can do it your Brute
Force oh you can't escape either use a
band to stop bleeding I'm dying bro
n okay I'm about to get Nom nomed I just
hope there's something behind
me oh I got Nom nomed and
infected oh that the
Quest for me we can fail a
quest I guess if we all die oh man
that's hard
okay I do need to get my backpack back
he loot has loot I'm taking
it oh boy oh you can't redo it dang I
ran out of I ran out of bullets so
quickly so many of them me okay I'm out
I guess we got to go back and retake the
quest huh that's a
lot you better there so
teleporters all right how do you get
that
he's very far go back
together yeah let's go back
together yeah let's head back maybe we
can do a different Quest that's
closer yeah are you swimming beeps what
are you going to do time for some
swimming where where are you myy let's
swim together yeah I'm going back to the
TR I am I see you getting chased
actually yeah I'm right next to you all
right get me they'll never get you
alive uh Quest fails for players as soon
as they die okay oh that's a little hard
to survive
though yeah well for now I guess let's
just take quests that are you know easy
not too tough yeah and not I thought
that was supposed to be a fetch Quest by
the way there was nothing fetching about
that oh we were supposed to grab
something I
think I'll be okay don't worry about out
of stamina in the water I'm
fine yeah we're like mermaids oh hey
there's a
zombie cool kill it okay that's a
waste not
yet I'm hugging the
shore the more the better Vehicles you
can make eventually oh really let's make
a tricycle they found me that's r
are you still okay
beeps yeah I'm okay I found Callie I
lost you that's okay I'm making my way
towards the thing anyway I'm hugging the
uh the
islands
okay yeah we can still pretty much see
each other on the map so
yeah I do not have a lot of bullets left
only two shot I they do do do you have a
shotgun yeah I have shotgun to you you
do yes my
hero my hero
Academia am I over encumbered no I'm not
I'll read one of these wait uh come here
and take them cuz I'm over
cucumber cucumber okay let me see if I
can find you oh there you are you're a
cool looking and cucumber oh give this
to someone else thank you okay here you
go already read it
so thank you
bullets bullets do you have any 9 mm at
all let me see I might people under
bullets yeah I do I'm fine with my
arrows I'll drop and then here this is
also for you you might want it it's
armor magazine it doesn't do me any
good well if you you you know you can
there's multiple levels of it right oh
really but I use
it it's okay when I used it before
cuz I tried to use it again and it just
disappeared from my inventory and
nothing happened so I don't know if this
worth
it we're swiming
[Music]
together that noise it's probably more
zom zoms sounds like a pig to be honest
hey
what if you hurt the the zombies
feelings is very
spooky I hope I'm going the right
way I am it's the cleric
[Music]
be it has it has that clicker sound and
like
the yeah what it was behind me this
whole time
ow oh no blast
them oh it's one of OD ah it's
jumpy it's just peace for me I did find
a
house but I'll probably die on the way
there nice you got us there's another
one there another
one wait should we just like stay at a
house or something the camp guy is going
to be Clos anyway isn't
he it's like 2 a.m. isn't so bad but
Quest at night is probably a noo yeah
I'll just like stay out his
area oh yikes I'm getting really beat up
you're supposed to stay people not
destroy
them oh yeah like it's pretty rude
huh oh my God
jeez these things do not die oh dead
oh
no don't eat her no don't eat my to see
your hell dwindle away I killed it I
killed it thank
you let it ruin your
body all right I am at the
traitor I assume he's he's
closed all right after yeah I mean it's
2: a.m. or something um this is where
I'm going to go and uh end it for me so
I hope you guys have fun yeah I'll see
you tomorrow or whenever I play next
okay see you byebye for now
yeah
oops all right uh let's go I'm not sure
when they're going to keep or how long
they're going to keep playing for but
let's go and send them off to Mory since
she's the one who had the idea for this
and I'll see you guys tomorrow
uh probably the same game
yeah for now it's denden time and I
don't mean people for dinner byebye
[Music]
see wow the the music really does not
help in this case anyway have your seven
days of Die music