[Music]
[Applause]
n
[Music]
[Applause]
pap
n
[Music]
a
[Applause]
[Music]
n e
[Applause]
n
[Music]
a
[Applause]
[Music]
n
[Applause]
[Music]
oh K
Kitty what a
[Music]
BP
K welcome to
days with Ollie C
Ollie yeah if you didn't know Ollie has
a little
game uh ever since recently a few days
ago like one or two weeks
ago I was waiting to play it very very
eagerly in order to also just support
Ollie I just want to show all some love
and
support so here I am there uh is there
were some bugs but uh with the English
version apparently they were mostly
fixed there's one bug that I was told
about is still gamebreaking and still
there uh since the new
update um and I
forgot where exactly it was but I have
to switch to Indonesian language for one
moment in order to survive that uh I
wonder what it was do you guys know
otherwise I have to go for my lik tweets
or so there's two of
them
uh-oh which
ones ah about her wait yeah that was the
one question where
before no when she asked the question I
guess before I answer I have to switch
to uh Indonesian in order for it not to
break best is of course she's not not
not be asked the weight question at all
second last is the set what second
last is the setting
what uh first is end of chapter one the
interview question how
tall so both how tall and how how much
you weigh
second last forting Oh you mean you're
telling me now here in the
game ah how to change the language yeah
yeah okay okay thank you thank you
second is chapter Freedom mic issue okay
so even weight or tallness now you guys
are giving me mixed uh Vibes about that
which one it
was H why does my fro already hurt man
let me take a fro C
there some of those days some of these
days is just uh right away from the
Geto wait so the weight or so and uh
what was the other one thing I just
read uh the mic issue question so when I
see a mic issue
question is when
I not before right because how would I
know you guys would have have to tell
me but okay before no when I see the
when I see the mic issue question and
when I see oling me how
perfect uh the mic issue question and
the the weight or the the tallness
something like
that hey what's up what a perfect race
well perfectly
Tim
M only I'm going to play this game
now should be a comfy little journey
into or comfy little peek into ol's
heart not is it not
comfy all right guys I'm going to get
into it this might be a short stream I
know I always say that but I don't know
I don't I don't think the game is too
long H what is good because I think the
rest of the week will be longer streams
as you may have seen the schedule for
the week
so what I mean it's I'm sure it's kind
of short what no that's 6 hours no I'm
kind of tired today so so I'd rather not
have it be too long anyway yeah also I
have to cook I have to cook and
yesterday I ate the rest of my salmon it
was so good so the salmon and the
wait I forgot my phone the salmon and
the the salad the freaking amazing
radish apple
salad okay okay okay okay okay I'm here
with my phone and I will admit I I did
bring one tiny small emergency chocolate
because I'm craving chocolate so hard
I haven't eaten any chocolate
today today yet but I'm craving it so
hard it's just it's actually it's from
from Austrian
Airlines it's the chocolate they give
you in the airplane that's pretty much
all the chocolate I have here right
now sorry I moved the microphone again
in my
home is it 85% caca I don't know uh I
don't think it says any ingredients on
this
one the struggle is real see I at least
was so smart to not buy any new
chocolate uh at the supermarket to be
available for me at home so now all I
have available is this like Air Airline
candy
but it's okay it's really small it's
like not uh big at all it's like a coin
a flat coin of chocolate
and um
yeah I've been I've been trying my best
okay but it's I as many people pointed
out
um for people who are out of the loop
I'm trying a little diet thing for the
first time in my life but as people have
pointed out the amount of what I eat is
not a problem really I don't eat that
much in general and also I mean yeah
I've been snacking some sweet stuff here
and there but the the par in particular
breakfast lunch and dinner what I eat
for that is generally not so bad um at
all actually if you look at the dinners
I cook all the time they're genuinely
healthy you just want to get a little
bit more fit um but the pro the problem
is I probably need mostly I need to get
some workout but yeah we're getting
there anyway whatever blah blah blah we
want to see we want to see days with Ali
let's go
[Music]
oh I think I think in my whole life I've
only played like two of this kind of
genre of
game I
think so this is really really uh fresh
for me again it's been a while since I
played something like this uh the other
one was uh one of them was um Love
Hina well I mean okay okay maybe it's
like two or three or so because back
when I was really really young I played
them on like a browser like love Pina
and there was like one
more that's pretty much it and then I
think I played hot full boy not did I I
don't
know no actually I don't I don't think I
really did but yeah
um so embarrassing anyway is this me
talking or her
probably me today is finally the day
it's the day where you'll be interviewed
for the position of a reporter and not
just any reporter but the reporter for
the one and only K
OE a reporter for
her what like am I writing an article on
her or
what that's me and now it says me that's
me
[Music]
you today's my interview
woo wow I am canonically a really uh
energetic person just like
Ollie you can't help with prance around
out of excitement feeling confident you
took out your little pocket
mirror can I oh my God is this going to
expose my
face wait I want to move myself a little
bit more so ah [\h__\h] yeah cool poses damn
look at me dripped out I'm so glad I
bought myself a new suit I am stunned
how about a little pose yeah looking
good maybe some more wo superb
oh wow I'm why am I so excited
about
myself you were so into your little pose
off that you didn't realize that people
started staring yeah no
understandable don't look look away mom
what's a that person
is this a
mat reference or just a
random friendship mother
[Music]
lady she reminds me of famous Japanese
uh
comedian that noil Senpai also sometimes
references or
is this
it I don't know anymore is this like a
reference sh don't point at it what if
it bites let's not stare too much those
types are usually
hostile
what what you you you're talking about
me like I'm an animal now come along we
can't bear
it bro you know fun
mom uh did you just call me an it in
front of her kid yeah and hostile like
what the [\h__\h] not even a weird person I
can't let this one
slide
uh nah just like let it happen like it's
already over they're already walking
away thank God after you gave it some V
you decided to keep your cool and not to
confront the mother and the son you even
went the extra mile to lean into onto a
tree just to ooze off more of your
coolness lean
very cool what you're back what the [\h__\h]
are you back I gave you a chance to just
go
away oh now I must I must I must
Bo look momy suching leaning on Tree on
a tree even when the S says not to do
so there's a sign that says not don't
lean on a tree I seen like Signs like
don't don't like like walk on the grass
or don't sit on the like a fence or so
but I I don't think I've seen one that
says don't lean on a tree is this IG
drassel or what what kind of special
tree is this sh don't be rude now
obviously no SP can fre doll
SPX
wow what do you mean what do they mean
that I'm not supposed to lean here as
you turned to look at the set tree it
said it was either the Christmas tree
from uh whole life English Minecraft uh
Christmas or whatever or it was the
drassel tree that f is building
therefore don't lean on
it no oh actually okay this makes sense
it's a synthetic tree so don't touch wet
paint me pulling out the old reference
princess was it a Christmas tree the one
that uh cie I think C cie was destroying
and traumatized her that's the tree that
I was thinking of from
GAA but was that tree supposed to be a
Christmas tree or was it just any any
kind of tree that she was building I
don't know it's ages ago long time
ago the new Hol life fans do not know
any of this
[Music]
that was when i' I'm pretty sure myth uh
Ian was only myth back in the day oh my
God that's so crazy
now now we're up to
Advent we we once we're only five and
once we were only
zero but then we were five and then we
were 10 and then no first we were six
and then we were
11 she
long time
ago but yeah wet paint makes sense
oh there goes your inate chance to go to
the interview ruined just like your now
yellow painted suit
oh oh damn shouldn't it be
brown tree
paint
[Music]
what
what what
that can
happen
[Music]
what wait can you go game over in like
typical Japanese visual novels or is
this very special because it's crazy
aie a the win yeah so much for a win
what am I supposed to uh push
here what does this mean depends on the
game
I mean more like like romance type of
visual
novel I don't think I've I know of that
but kobal kobal try again okay well good
that there's some Indonesian speaking
people
here oh my God okay okay okay so we're
not it's not like any choice is
okay okay hm H then I must confront
them is it is it here I think it's
around here yeah I think not getting mad
just walking up to them but we might
still get mad you couldn't just take
that insult so you decided to come up to
the mother and son to confront
them mom Mom it's that thing again from
earlier but wait if I fail in anything
later on do I always start from the
beginning I guess I should be saving a
lot okay
okay
oh okay um I guess I've saved
[Music]
uh-oh sh don't say that the mother shush
her child as she tried to hide you from
her son wow see you're supposed to teach
your child better so as not to call
people names I'm not a parent myself yet
but at least I know this much I should
do something before her child says
something even
worse
really that's
h no we're not going to SC to child for
her the mother is a problem excuse me
ma'am what do you think you're teaching
your kid you know better than to call
people it imagine how you would feel if
you were in my shoes I mean even a
mental person wouldn't want to be called
it think ma'am think that's just
dehumanized in have you no shame do you
want me to sue you for human rights of
unpleasant actions like
this can
[Music]
we oh the woman was too stunned to speak
but you keep yapping anyway after a few
minutes of reprimanding her you ended up
feeling
tired who knew that yelling at people
would take so much energy for real it
really does
[Music]
I think I've said enough they've gone so
silent I think this is enough I should
forgive them and let them go I'm sure
they have reflected on
it yeah hopefully I don't think they'll
really change but yeah why you saving
just just because I I need to save a lot
yeah I overrode it on purpose because it
seems like it was okay seems like we're
through well I guess I'll let this slide
for now but don't you ever do that again
remember consider others feelings even
if they're actually mental everyone has
feelings so keep that in mind good
day after getting repented the mother
and her child silently went on their way
yeah you better but unknowingly you
actually just convinced him that you're
actually
mental this is this not leading leading
into a game over right no okay good I
think we're fine you then went on your
own way to holler I headquarters on your
own on your way you forgot where you're
supposed to
[Music]
go I'm getting really really paranoid
now was this the way again I remember
the stab sharing the exact location uh
ah I was right I have to keep going
straight for 500 me and take a left turn
then turn right after another 500
M and side note the road straight ahead
is kind of uphill
uh the road to the office is quite far
is there any shortcut I can take you
started looking for a shortcut is the
whole game mean looking for
Ollie at the finale is finding
her uh to the office with your phone map
and found a quicker detour though as a
law Bing citizen on a busy morning you
decided to put your phone away oh
because yeah in Japan even though nobody
listens to it they say Naga
aruki is not good nagara just means
doing anything while doing something so
and aruki means walking and guess
there's there's really really so many
people on their
phone either calling or uh just looking
at the screen while walking is like I
guess so bad that they make it a
[Music]
thing but also I would say also don't
eat while walking is also a thing that
they try to enforce with that
[Music]
so yeah okay and for the map that you
memorized you finally reached a t
Junction do you guys when when you use
Google Maps I use Google Maps a lot to
get around anywhere but do you guys
actually start the route somehow I don't
like uh like the
way how it like Zooms in and everything
how it looks after you start to Route so
I always have it
unstarted
same same
same okay some of you start the route I
mean not when like driving when driving
it's probably different but what if
you're just walking
when you're just walking I feel like
it's it's way more like easy to look at
without starting the route and just
looking at the the path overall and
maybe zoom in on your
[Music]
own yeah yeah yeah I don't like how it's
like working once you started it's
like and it wants to give me commands
and
whatever oh my God I'm excited you guys
feel the same way
[Music]
y I don't live in a walkable area oh so
you can't relate you mean when the map
kind of turns around as you yeah yeah
yeah for example he hey hey hey for the
map that you memorize you finally reach
the T Junction oopsie okay all right so
if I remember correctly next up I should
go for a oh no oh
[Music]
no so we're past this now so we can
override
[Music]
um
uh it like okay there's no way I could
know maybe a residential area for
Elites Maybe This Way dot dot dot oh I
mean there's a picture for it
so oh yeah looks beautiful by the way I
love those bricks I love those bricks
you then made your way into the elite
residential
area the further you walk the smaller
you feel since the houses here are huge
and
fancy damn wonder how much these houses
cost must be a
fortune hopefully one day I can get
myself a house as big as
these I also you know when I lived in
Japan when I started out there were two
places I lived in as many of you
remember the first one was the tiniest
tiniest most
normal um not suitable for streaming
typical Japanese one room apartment with
really thin walls which I got out of I
think like 1 month
in and then the second place well
besides me staying over at my manager's
uh house besides that uh then I moved
into a house which sounds nice had two
floors sounds nice but it was extremely
run down very in need of renovation kind
of spooky over all and just weird uh and
not in a nice location like no was the
location was not dangerous or anything
it was just really far from
everything and yeah then I was living
there for like the rest of my stay in
Japan so I was I was only in Japan while
being in Holo for half a year so it
wasn't it didn't really make any sense
to get something super expensive and
nice uh and I didn't have that much
money saved up yet at that point so it
had to be cheaper cheaper options but
now I've seen so many whole life members
live in really nice really nice places
and I'm like man if I would be living in
Japan now I would totally treat myself
to a nice living situation like
this uh I hate that I had
to live like that damn girl you live
like that what back in Japan I wish I
could have enjoyed Japan without being
freaked out by [\h__\h] rats or [\h__\h] like
that yeah where I live now is nice but I
I don't know would have been nice if I
could have lived more comfortably in
Japan when I was there
[Music]
Casper yeah man Casper in hindsight I
like him
but I mean it's a different story when
you actually have a mouse or a rat I
think I'm still not sure what it was but
yeah living in your ceiling terrorizing
you had to warm up no I had to cool down
with him actually I had to leave in
order to miss him but I think the
biggest reason why I started liking
Casper is only because of the super
chats that were role playing as
Casper that's the only
reason by no he was invincible he ate
the RB chocolate and didn't die he ate
fruit of plastic and the
chocolate
both
toxic
poisonous but
yeah you kept on walking all on the
while of imagining how great it would be
to live in an elite residential area
man so
relatable while looking around the place
you heard a familiar voice calling out
to you you turned around to see who this
voice belonged to and turns out it was
your high school classmate
Rudy
Rudy the most arrogant kid in school oh
no oh no
what are the chances of actually meeting
him here once he yaps it'll be over for
me what we're a yapper too we can't be
judging other yappers Rudy came closer
to you he's kind of cute you're telling
me this is like an arrogant
dude H hey you're an SMA free graduate
right uh one of the wee
kids uh excuse
me it's been so long it feels like
yesterday since I last heard you sing s
s what's that you feel your face turning
red from embarrassment and quickly
turned away looking for a way to escape
for Rudy's yaps also what does he mean
SAS does he mean SAS oh that sounds more
familiar
uh H I think just leaving is the least
interesting thing so they would not do
that it's one of these
maybe I'll have to do the dumbest thing
I think so pretend to be
possessed yeah I think so too it's
probably the dumbest
thing maybe I just pretend to be
possessed because that's how a logical
thinking person thinks and what they
would do yeah yeah yeah in order to get
rid of someone yeah yeah yeah because of
course more reasonable options would
have a bad outcome that would lead me to
a game over no no no no no the only real
way to win is to act absolutely
insane no I would love to hear why the
others would make me game over we'll
see ra I am the ruler of the forest I
am seeing the fear in Rudy's eyes you
merked while mentally patting yourself
in the back this will definitely scare
him off though the fear didn't last long
Rudy brought himself together and
quickly called for help a friend in need
for exorcism is a friend
indeed uh oh no just came a scholar a
cleric and a monk
what
what okay it was a game
over you were exercised with various me
effs and ended up late for the inter
guys did you perhaps know that this was
going to happen and that's why you told
me to do this I felt very confirmed in
my actions by the
chat I did not think you would lead me
towards a game over you little
shits
ah kagi also starts from my last day or
damn it that's probably
salesman although that's also kind of
[Music]
crazy let's
try
[\h__\h] I guess we just load from
[Music]
here
do what could we do
let's try to be a salesperson because I
think with the other people we also just
walked away and then that didn't work so
it's probably not walking away I just
pretend to be a salesperson oh good
morning sir
[Music]
I that is also so
ridiculous like
what she might actually try to buy
something what are we going to do then
I'm from the XXX company I have some
products that may interest you what
yeah it worked we're offering a 50%
discount what do you mean it worked what
what he's still there and he's confused
he's not necessarily believing us what
do you mean it worked we're offering a
50% discount on our newest frying pan
products cat got your tongue
huh this should do the trick now I just
need to keep babbling until he goes
away you then proceeded to offer various
of madeup products to Rudy
it's also game
over yeah he was interested and kept
listening to your office so you kept
making up new Pro oh
man oh
man
laggy
really is it just walking
[Music]
away
so no way
it's kind of a hard game Bo did you play
it
too go whatever I'll just run away huh
why why are you
running not wanting to embarrass
yourself any further you decided to book
it
out
oh wait
is
is is the is the
no
way no way no
[Music]
way I thought we were in the right
place maybe this one at least is a bit
further ahead
[Music]
[\h__\h] it was not the residential area
I'll go for the damaged
Road they did I was like oh they drew a
wait this is a picture in in in a filter
in Photoshop so I feel like it can't be
this one either like I was so certain
because the other one had a proper
illustration but this doesn't even have
a proper illustration so I feel like it
is you think this is the
way you think so
maybe I just should do a double chck
just in case is this really the right
route you decide to check again on your
phone maps and apparently this is the
only way oh
what you're sh and Traverse the Broken
Road anyways all while trying to keep
yourself steady from the rocks and mud
God this is not it what if I saw my
shoes I don't think they'll let anyone
with Muddy shoes into the
office but if it's for o Chan I have to
pass the interview still what do I do
now
I'll make a separate
save uh what would be the best way to
best thing to
do well I would say walking on the road
Edge but then I might fall into this
hole and
die that's all I'll keep these on he
kept his shoes on and decided to just
walk on top of the road Edge after only
a few steps [\h__\h] you slipped and fell
and
died yeah yeah as I said and as I
said as I said though at least I saw it
[Laughter]
coming okay then it's taking them off
and then washing them somewhere I
guess but that's so that's so disgusting
because I'm probably not going to get to
wash my feet so I'm just going to have
the dirtiest feet ever inside the shoes
afterwards
after I'm done walking here that's crazy
that's crazy you decided to take off
your shoes and walk for the mud with
bare feet slowly but surely you reached
the end of the muddy
Road oh it is a game over yeah because
that's stupid I saved my shoes but not
my pants
what Oh you mean my because I'm wearing
long pants and the bottom edges of them
got kind of dirty
too shut the [\h__\h] m
please tell me the third option is at
least
good oh my God this is a rage
game why do I always choose the wrong
thing let's walk
slowly Barefoot that's never a good idea
maybe if I just walk slowly I'll be fine
you kept your shoes on and walked slowly
avoiding paths with deep or wet mud
hooray on your way you notice there's a
smooth path on the other Road side you
considered the
option a smooth what stand cross the
other roads and cross and take the Lower
Road well what's the what's the Lower
Road oh God save again well it's too
late
now it's okay it was not that much time
that passed in
between um
but no I'm probably going to get is
guide if I cross I'm probably going to
get iside
right but I like to I would like to see
that Let's cross and take the Lower
Road wait Something From Another
Dimension told you to look before you
cross so you did yeah but I might still
get Easter
yeah go
I told you too predictable too
predictable oh oh It sped past me yeah
but then what if it comes suddenly from
the other side Hong
Hong wait I oh no I am
dead you managed to save your own life
from The Crossing but I didn't save your
suit that is now a drenched in
mud well we got uh almost e gu there was
definitely only a truck uh in the street
involved
K
[\h__\h] oh my god what have you done what
have you
done
[Music]
W I would like to stay on the path
but wasn't M you'd rather not risk
crossing their mud and dirty puddles
everywhere you decideed to stay on the
current path you'll eventually reach the
end of the road soon anyways after a
while you got off the muddy Road only to
arrive to A very dark
tunnel
what for goodness sake I'm just trying
to get to an interview where is this why
is it so dark you tried to check your
phone map but to no avail due to signal
loss but why did did I walk
in stay
out I can't check my map do I just turn
[Music]
back uh let's go through the
tunnel why not huh why
not nothing I can't handle it's just a
little dark surely I can pass as you
suppress your and walked into the
darkness after a few minutes of walking
a glimmer of light AKA death shimmed at
the end of the tunnel oh is that the
exit I'm supposed to be happy that I'll
be out of this dark tunnel but why do I
feel
[Music]
uneasy
um well there's already light why do I
need to turn on my
[Music]
own but how could this also how could me
turning on the flashlight now have a bad
outcome maybe I would scare some animals
that are in the tunnel that are then
going to attack me when I uh turn on the
light oh it's a [\h__\h]
train wait the light at the end of the
tunnel is [\h__\h] train right wow it's
so dark and gloomy just like my future
oh wait I can use my phone flashlight
you cursed at yourself a bit you could
have just done that from the start
exactly why didn't I think that haha Sly
me you took out your phone and pressed
the flashlight button with the light now
shining your whole surroundings you took
a good look on where you at
uhoh there you found hundreds of
terrifying apparitions surrounding you
all around
you well did they start going off or why
did I die what
what wait
apparitions what's what's apparitions is
is it ghost I was thinking of um AAR
just like uh
machines I speaking of
machines all right it was Ghost well
that's
fine um anyway let's try to go for the
tunnel one more time there is one more
option it might still be okay yeah if I
don't see the ghosts what can they do to
me
huh curiosity kills the cat but I'm so
curious I'd rather regret knowing than
regret not knowing with curiosity at wi
your fear you made your way to the light
you got out of the tunnel and there you
saw all these
bestie y being chased by EO but that
that's a good thing right I mean she's
good with EOS and at least we see some
some colleague of hers so that must be
good
right oh
cute cute
this is good this is good this must be
the the good route
right now father I don't want to go
home yui looked like she's in distress
so you decided to help her you followed
the yuu back to the secret lirer and it
didn't take long for the aliens am I
going to get
abducted
malen was that on purpose in Indonesian
in
in do uh Alien speak
Indonesian no wait that's that's not
Indonesian I think or is it sounds that
no that's the
English alarm
signal s people CL the exit aliens
scared and surrounded you in a Flash
wait wait wait I can explain
yeah
okay okay oh it's supposed to be like
germanish you got abducted by S sad
aliens and forced to be enslaved in
their home
planet it seems to be very hard to find
the
way Yi why the [\h__\h] did you not help
me wait I think there was one more
option to turn back but is the turning
back once you're already in the tunnel
the same outcome as the turning back
before you enter the tunnel I
wonder cuz there's one
[Music]
here and then there's this one which we
didn't choose yet so let's
try no wait that looks way too
suspicious I'll just follow my guts and
go back you scared back to the entrance
however the tunnel somehow got longer
and longer longer the answer somehow
disappeared and the road became
endless you're trapped now in the shadow
realm
forever
Ollie
Ollie you little
[\h__\h] OE I swear to
God I swear to God I thought I was going
to legit have this like cute little
banter with all the girls trying to win
all these
heart and this is such a
pain okay then we tried uh all of these
options we can turn back now or we wait
until our phone let's wait until the
phone CES a signal oh there you go your
phone called a faint signal as if a
miracle just happened you immediately
open your phone map you check the map
and turns out you don't need to go into
the tunnel mhm you just needed to take
the path that is apparently right next
to
it wouldn't we see that path and think
it it would be a a
more logical
option oh good thing I didn't go inside
three times getting possessed and
there's the last thing I
want a mysterious giggle echoed from the
tunnel stay
inside without wasting another second
you booked out of the place faster than
your internet connection you make your
way through the path your map showed you
your eyes at ease with the many bushes
and trees decorating the road and
somehow somewhere you stumbled upon a
vast flower field you don't know how the
rocky muddy Rock guided you to such a
place but it didn't matter because you
can feel your fatigue being washed
away did I make
it oh
God oh
God it watch what wait what
what's from
afar the flowers just the flowers okay
you didn't want to ruin the flow yeah
otherwise somebody's going to be like
don't step on the
flowers it's just such a beautiful sight
while admiring the flowers you notice
someone or something in between the
flowers you squint your eyes to get a
better look there's still a pretty lady
dressed in pink
we y she's so pretty it's as if she's a
part of the flower field herself
is this just a game for Ollie where she
can just fantasize about
her ID
colleagues is this not really about her
is this just so she can yeah Troll And
also
just imagine all kinds of
scenarios with her friends
but what could a pretty also wait what
if you in reality is me h no
wait what if you in reality is Ollie
what if I am Ollie and it would it will
be revealed in the end that is that I am
just OE and all of these experiences
that's why I'm so wait I figured it out
that's why I am so
energetic and and like nervous and
and I don't know everything
K wait I am Ollie that's why I also
never get to meet
her wait I think this might be
true that makes a lot of sense that's
also why it's more about all of the
others than
herself oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] I am
[Music]
Ollie wait did I figure it out
what could a pretty lady be doing all
the way out here I wonder if she got
lost H as a kind-hearted person I have
to help her her Brown almost dirty
blonde hair swayed in the wind and her
emerald eyes shimmered like the Dew
drops on a
[Music]
leaf wow the closer you got to her the
more Enchanted you become but then you
notice something so familiar yet so off
wait huh is that a
tail to and trans with a shocking
Revelation the lady screamed
cute who who drew these illustrations
they're really
[Music]
cute who are you how did you get here
you must be in stalker you were suddenly
attacked by a bouge of nuts it's so
over please wait don't kill me I know no
no you got pelted by these nuts and fell
unconscious
death by these
nuts all
[Music]
right wait is it does it keep on
resetting me to hear because maybe this
path is not the right one after
all not sure but okay let's uh I mean in
the end interacting with eoi was
apparently not the right thing to do so
maybe interacting with lisu is also not
the right thing to do best I just leave
it I don't really have the time to enjoy
the flowers I got to grind going to grip
me I'm trying to get to ollie which is
me I have to pass and become a report
wait if I am OE then this is very
schizophrenic maybe maybe I'm not
Ollie may maybe
or I lost my memory maybe I'm only and
as any any protagonist in any game I
lost my
memory and when I arrive at the
interview it turns out the whole
interview OE advertisement was just a
search party for Olli they were trying
they lost Ollie in an accident because
she's still alive but she lost her
memory so there she wanded off and their
way of fighting
is by putting on all these
advertisements to like interview Ollie
because she doesn't know that she's
Ollie so if they would just say we're
looking for Ollie then they would not
find her because I would not be like hey
I am Ollie I'll go there no no no but if
it says interview Ollie I'd be like oh
that sounds interesting I will go there
and interview Ollie this ol person even
though it's me but I don't know that so
um
[Music]
okay I'm trying to get to ollie let's
go really I made it through by ignoring
both the tunnel where eii is and the
flower field where lisu
is
[Music]
really I did not think that that's the
way to go in this game wouldn't I want
to meet
everybody I guess I would have to like
take all the
L's just just for finding the girls
because you want 100% the game you want
to see every single
[Music]
path I was trying to stay focused when
when first they brought out that mother
and and her child but
going away from them didn't work so H
you shook your head and decided to
ignore the flower field you followed
your phone map and arrived at the
highway this is a Highway you checked
your map again just to make sure you're
going the right way you're so close to
the office but then you suddenly got
unbearably
thirsty I'm so
thirsty uh-oh will I die
imagine in the modern world in the
middle of a
city
someone die like no don't don't no your
eyes shifted around until a land until
it landed in a small shop not far from
where you are standing it's just across
the road no no don't isaky me it looks
like it has a bundance of drinks for
sale well I'll be I could just buy a
drink there you looked for a crosswalk
no no no
no the first how ever was getting to you
so you decided no no
no
[Music]
no but even with the decision made you
don't really have an opportunity with
the cars and motorbike zooming on the
highway oh so I'm not getting
across
oh half bow while crossing very
Pol uh
if it's a highway I think generally they
will not stop for me but if someone is
as crazy to actually start walking then
they don't have another choice but this
is really not not good I'll I'll I'll um
save and I'll wave while
crossing maybe I could wave my hands
while crossing then they'll maybe slow
down and let me
cross maybe isn't really the best word
words to use in a situation like this
but you tried to cross
anyways you took a step onto the road
but a really fast car drove right past
you well past me sounds like they didn't
hit me but your foot was hit by a
speding car and half of your shoe got
blown away only half of
it that's that's still pretty
decent I guess I should bow
[Music]
I should bow because that's
ridiculous maybe I'll try half boing
while crossing since it's considered
more polite in this way you mly do so
despite your halfback knowledge and you
managed to cross the
road why did the Wawa cross the road
guys why did she do it how did she do it
oh I crossed the road I didn't expect
that would work so well as you were
celebrating you took a look around and
saw your
own dead lifeless body in the middle of
the
[Music]
road this is such a [\h__\h] rage game
this is just a rage game come
on this stupid face I can't see it
anymore
olly it's good that I didn't spoil
myself with this game by like any other
streams because I had no idea that this
is how it was going to be
wait until I get my chance like
sometimes I thought I thought in the
beginning that the most reasonable
things would be good and then it proved
me wrong but then it proved me wrong
again and we went back to the reasonable
things
so it's like a mix like I never know
this is the reasonable thing if anything
I shouldn't be Reckless it's a busy
street I don't want to be run over by a
car patience is key I'll wait until the
road is less busy you waited for a few
minutes and sure enough you got your
chance to cross the road without any
delay you made your way to the small
shop across the road oh my God it was
that simple that looks so
good that looks so good days with
Ollie it will take days to meet Ollie at
this
[Music]
rate Hony Hony I I almost don't believe
it I I feel like this ah oopsie I feel
like this might just still
be like it was might just still throw us
back to the
beginning just absolute troll all of
this was for
nothing days two
OE days to meet
only now I'm safe okay oh my
God okay I'd like to have m
I think they have corro I'll take the
corro please and one of the ice creams
you have do you have
um vanilla or lemon or or anything
really I love
anything please I thought the shop was
small because I saw it from afar but
this shop is actually so small
oh hey there young one what can I get
for you
uh no wonder in the shop is so small but
the shopkeeper Auntie is also small I
want to buy a drink what do you have in
stock everything except brood drinks
what does that mean like like
alcohol I have cold and non cold drinks
no hot
drinks okay so cold and uh let's to say
room temperature drinks then why does
she sa things so
weirdly oh like coffee what I have is a
what I have is a small shop not a cafe
after
all uh okay I'll
buy
[Music]
um how about wait what could what could
happen does there are some options that
have no impact
right what what could
happen oh I could if it's a soda
if it's a soda I will open it and it
will go all over me right but I don't
know does it actually happen with any
carbonated drink I've only ever had it
happen with like like Coca-Cola or so
but I guess it can happen with
any any carbonated drink but that's
probably what's going to happen the
syrup is going to be
sticky somehow I'm going to spill it and
have sticky [\h__\h] all over me so maybe
just
normal water
just cold mineral water please how much
one two a
dozen why does she think I need a dozen
just one Auntie I'm only by myself small
medium large there's no small medium
okay maybe yeah there
is medium ah is she's serving it in cups
okay cup bottle oh bottle bottle what
the [\h__\h] which brand aquan Jan for or
tamarat
this is getting
[Music]
annoying I don't know I don't know this
is the first and the third one is the
same thing what what does this do
[Music]
even
um
um uh
one more question I'm
leaving uh she kids these days are no
fun go ahead pick your choice in the
fridge oh it's 7,000
each
Yen even in Yen that's crazy even Yen
has a lot of zeros but 7,000 is not
normal the heck that's so expensive also
I thought she would take it out for me
if I'd known that I could take the
drinks myself then I would have done so
from the beginning despite your
annoyance you still took the mineral
water yourself and paid the amount you
drank half of the bottle and continued
on your way as you walked you could see
the giant whole life buing from a
distance your heart race says you smil
uncontrollably finally oh no we're still
going to die right away right oh
Indonesian
rupee I'm finally here yay Ollie I'm
coming am I though am I really
really oh more drinks
we're getting there you got so excited
that your steps turn into little skips
yeah that could very well
be you took a good look around admiring
the other tall buildings until you
realized that you weren't the only one
who were wearing a suit with files and
CVS could it
be could it be that there all my job
Rivals shoot there's so many of them but
I can't lose here not giving up that
easily I got to up my G name in between
all your files you pulled out a book
titled interview answers that could
easily charm any job recruiter and
started reading it as you walked it
didn't take long for you to arrive at a
ramp that leads inside the whole ID
Office Building as you climbed the ramp
a granny with uneven colored clothes
bumped into you oh there's a lot of like
older ladies in this
game what does it mean
oh
granny oh my I'm sorry dear I didn't see
you no it's okay I was looking EV with
the book on my face oh my what a
diligent boy my grandson doesn't like
reading books he always has his eyes
glued onto his phone
too well oh that can't be helped it's
hard to pull children away once they're
hooked on something my grandson is 32
years old
a dude I thought their grandson was a
kid kids are still
dudes oh I see um by the
[Music]
way granny are you alone here why aren't
you at home are you going somewhere why
why am I asking these
questions mind my own
business are you going somewhere
um
it's I want to mind my own business I
want to I really want
to damn granny's in a sour mood want me
to accompany you hello I have something
to do hello moshy MOSI Earth to
myself
uh pow you received a heart slap with
her AB normally happy plastic
[Music]
bag oh it's not over yet good happens I
can't believe kids these days you're
trying to hit on me aren't you hitting
on a fine lady like me
[Music]
unbelievable yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
let's let her believe that maybe she'll
feel a little bit like happy at the end
of the day that people are still
interested in her
[Music]
before you could UT a word granny
laughed at her Grumble following her
steps hey yo I'm still alive and she's
leaving
oh
[Music]
no what what's the problem what's the
problem what's the
[Music]
problem what what what the problem
why aren't you at
home am I not allowed to go outside you
little
[\h__\h] is she angry I'm just asking
[Music]
though I'm just asking thank got curious
is that something I can't ask about of
course you can't it's called
privacy now I'm a
stalker what why is it the game
over why your definition of game over is
also kind of
[Music]
different not need a [\h__\h]
oops no I pressed the wrong
thing
oopsie
um are you alone here that's also not
going to be good
right scroll wheel
oh I can go back and forth with this
I'll just back I think
okay well how far back wait
what scrolling forward goes
back H what I don't understand why are
you telling me to use
that oh if I made a wrong choice I don't
have to load H granny are you alone what
the [\h__\h] kind of question is that
too oh she likes this
one you don't feel insulted by this one
yes it's my grandson asked me to buy
some apples he wanted to eat apples
granny then gave you a peek inside her
big plastic bag you could see that it's
filled with a brim with
apples poor Granny she's already sold
yet she's still being asked to do arand
errands her grandson has no shame did
your random come with you Granny shook
her head no he didn't but he said he'll
pick me up here I've been waiting here
since 9:00 a.m. but he hasn't
arrived a heavy sigh escaped her lips as
she glanced at the busy street hoping
that her grandson would pull up you took
a glance at you watch it's 10:00 a.m.
granny has been waiting for a while so
you want to help her but your interview
is at 11:00 a.m. I can't just leave her
alone she's been waiting for so long but
my interview is in an hour shoot the sky
isn't really looking that most sunny
either it looks like it will rain
m i
mean taking her to the nearest police
station
feels like maybe the best option even
though I think it's a bit too
dramatic uh but telling her to go home
will probably result in her being isek
me taking her home will result in me
missing my
interview
so that's how I'm feeling
[Music]
we just got to we got to think the way
the game
thinks it's okay if it's okay may I take
you to the nearest police station it
looks like it'll rain and I don't want
granny to get caught in it but like
wouldn't there have been another option
like taking her to a cafe nearby like
have her sit down there to wait why does
it have to be a police station oh yeah
her grandson doesn't wouldn't know that
she's in the police station right
uh okay
M uh yeah the police maybe will like
just doesn't she have a
phone I don't know let's just let the
police take care of
it don't worry the police will take care
of it granny the most important thing
right now is to get you somewhere with
shelter and
supervision what's this this feels
almost insulting to me if I was this
Grandma I felt this Grandma felt so
insulted by all the other things I
said that I feel like us implying that
she can't take any care of herself and
that she can't survive in the rain or
[Music]
so like I don't know man I think she can
take care of herself to a certain degree
she doesn't seem like she's so lost in
life if she was so lost in life then her
grandson would probably not send her out
to get apples on her
own you know what I
mean but
[Music]
okay she she seems very reasonable right
now and accepts
it
interesting that
is an interesting route that we're going
but but my guess was right that this
would be the right thing it seems after
some pation you managed to take granny
to the nearest police station while
walking you found a police officer busy
with his
walkie-talkie
oh is it subu Senai good timing excuse
me sir I want to make a
report qu the police officer signaled
you to be quiet and also said it out
loud
what the heck is with this police
officer uh sorry to disturb you sir but
I no dude dude okay stop talking to him
just go inside and talk to the non- busy
police officer police officers
inside I would say she's just going to
get
mad again the officer signaled you to be
quiet what's the all the Shing you're
sounding like a okay
protagonist uh are you [\h__\h] dump
right
now sir this is important oh my God he's
going to shoot me enough of your Rambles
the police pinched your mouth shut oh my
God wait excuse me excuse me don't touch
my lips ew what the [\h__\h] why does his
hand smell so
[Music]
e after a moment of silence the police
officer took his hand off of you and
proceeded communicating through his
walking all without a glance at you
[Music]
we are we find ourselves in a tricky
situation we can Shout at the officer
take
revenge not something that goes lightly
in some countries or snatch none none of
this none of this is a good
idea other places um than
Japan uh all
[Music]
right
um oh
no oh no let's shout sir reporting it
earlier I found your sudden shouting
took the officer off guard so much so he
had a heart attack
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no no no you
don't get arrested for murder when
somebody has a heart attack it's not it
was
not that's not
murder oh okay thank you
[Music]
what the actual
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] no no that's not
manslaughter either
no
ah I smash the walkie doy but is that
not also
Revenge oh I'm so tired [\h__\h] you didn't
have time to play along with his shushes
so you took his walkie-talkie away in
the Nos and then what am I going to do
then oh
[Music]
no so I want to make a report oh
granny
oh he's the grandson well
perfect what instead of scolding you the
officer's gaze landed directly on
granny oh so sir yeah this granny was
granny I already told you not to buy
apples but you said you wanted apples so
I bought some apples I even got these
expensive green apples look well that a
PL Choice the officer knows granny I'm
assuming he's the grandson yeah 32 makes
sense good grave granny those aren't the
apples that I was talking about oh do
you mean do you mean yeah do you mean
apple as in like a
phone I never said I wanted apples I
said I wanted to do a
preparation for attending a ceremony
app okay this must have been a little
bit better of a joke in
[Laughter]
Indonesian good try though huh how could
apples do the ceremony the conversation
doesn't seem to be going anywhere you
could only face pal at the situation no
one is paying attention anyway so you
decided to leave but just before you
could the police finally took notice of
you and who are you
[Music]
um stupid stupid answer stupid
answer I'm just a passer by
Sir then why are you just standing there
if you're passer
by oh oh
[Music]
oh I brought your grandma here dude
why are you even asking you saw me
bringing your grandma here you saw me
like I mean she was next to me when you
looked
up what the
[\h__\h] you better f up before I cough you
up but I'm only trying to you're
definitely suspicious you if you truly
inter understand you wouldn't be
stuttering I caught you r hand grandma
say something grandma
Mama
Mia Mama Mia Grandma why do you leave me
out here to die now
[Music]
Grandma
why 17 wait are you whoops are you
counting the amount of times I'm I'm
dying in this
game wait what the did I just okay who
do you think
sir yeah okay are we being logical now
we're being logical now the officer
glanced at the granny and I'm back at oh
he might think I'm I'm his grandma's
boyfriend am I am I canonically a guy in
the
game no okay he gets it
now I see so you were the one who
brought granny here thank you if it
weren't for you Granny might have been
waiting for me in the rain you're doing
a lot for society but maybe pay more
attention Okay not only did you make her
wait she said you'd only play on your
phone every day ah it's him ah yeah
right he's playing on his phone all the
time you said that is you said that as
if rep ring the officer though instead
of admitting it his faults he only
seemed
puzzled playing on my phone but I don't
oh
oh does she think his walkie-talkie is
the phone
I think she's mistaken my walkie-talkie
for fall it's kind of broken see I want
to get it fixed but the technician was
out so I've been tinkering with it
myself oh thank you don't really oh wow
we're having such a reasonable
conversation oh my
god oh I see well I'll be taking my
leave now that took longer than expected
you're welcome sir if you'll excuse me
I'm going to be safe on your way you
smiled rarely back at them and made your
way back to the Hol ID Office you check
the time it's 10:30 let's go we have
time for one more side
quest oh is this late already I got to
get back quick you dashed up the ramp
hoping to make it for the interview the
only thing that you have in mind now is
to get to the interview and be qualified
to be Ali's
reporter
yes that's the only thing after
traveling for an hour you arrived at the
Holo ID Office all of this for holo ID
shees finally I arrived at the whole
life Indonesia
[Music]
[Applause]
office holy moly this is awesome as an
abbid ho life fan you couldn't hold back
your excitement it started prancing the
interview will not be starting for
another half an hour you decide to
explore the office until then H where
should I start
M hopefully none of this is a bad
option let's start in the main
[Music]
lobby yeah what can happen in the main
lobby
[Music]
huh uhhuh uhhuh uhhuh nice this is
indeed exactly what it looks like I can
confirm he returns to the lobby and
return burn uh-huh and scan the area H
nothing interesting here four chairs
four tables a receptionist desk and two
reception
ladies the longer you stared at the
reception lady the more she starts
feeling
uneasy how about not
staring so oh my God just going to the
main lobby was already a came
over can't stand it anymore the
reception lady called to security to
kick you out of the office for
allegations of
harassment okay
okay
okay probably should not interrupt a
meeting in a meeting room let's go to
the merchandise area maybe I can buy
something that's a SCH
school that looks like a school
following the signs towards the
merchandise area you began your Voyage
reaching the meriz area whoa wao this is
heaven on
[Music]
Earth wait isn't this the Kani for
students this is a school
[Music]
don't worry about
okay wait did they use like free to use
copyright free images for this game cuz
I thought I I just assumed they were
painted for the
game but if they use copyright free
images then it's probably that's why
some images are not like so suitable
and this was the most suitable they
could find for that
scenery
a yeah yeah
yeah and the lines of merchandise were
lined up needly your eyes sparkled at
the view fortunately enough there was no
other human besides yourself they would
think you're crazy again although I
didn't notice this with the pictures
until now everything else was
like besides the one picture that was
had a filter on it I I wouldn't have
really questioned
it that one and this
one wow this is all's birthday
merchandise said
oh
uh that reminds me of the days when
there was um hle
project uh shop in Shibuya
where you could go and they were selling
a lot of merchandise there but they
closed it at some point I think they may
be have some replacement now but anyway
I went there so often and then I never
had that much money so I I never really
bought much I was just looking at
things buying merch without paying for
shipping yeah yeah but like it wouldn't
it be nice if H life just had like a
general 24/7 not 24/7 but like for the
year General shop in like Tokyo where
you can go and buy things at
anytime like anything that is in their
General stock in uh on the website if
they had a shop for
that maybe they already considered it
and thought it's like too expensive to
maintain an IRL
shop
maybe
H oh I guess maybe they they already
have like sections in like shops like
animate in Japan I wouldn't know because
I don't
know but maybe they
do they might
actually have special like whole life
sections in some shops yeah but not they
don't sell that much right in those
sections just a few things right
[Music]
H oh well also this is unrealistic
because birthday merchandise is like
made to order and you order it online
and you get it half a year later there
will be nothing like lined up in a place
like this no no no no no unless it's
just for
display oh there's even a bath bump holy
this is awesome wait did ollie ever do a
bath bump for her birthday merchandise I
only remember cie ever doing that for
her first merchandise thingy she did the
bath bomb and I remember I actually
remember her manager at the time
bringing her the
samples to smell and try out I was like
there wow that's a long time
ago wait that was for her third birthday
oopsie what you mean for Ollie because
for CI I think it was very early on
shut the m i scrolled back because I was
scrolling in
chat he that was more
recent I swear that happened when I was
still in
Japan maybe they gave up on the idea
after sampling it I don't know
anymore only like one or two years ago
really what's going
on everything's so oh I wish I wasn't
pennes is that oh all these
mascot silence
[Music]
please you could feel a figure with an
immense St stature appearing behind
immense I wouldn't call it
immense who are
you you can't just come and make a lot
of
[Music]
noise
sorry
sorry so so sorry
you want me to kick you
out uh
sorry
I'm I am a job applicant that is the
truth I'm a job
Seeker my applicants should be preparing
for their interviews you're better off
doing that than Ling in the merchandise
area ah who am I King enough excuses you
look like a fief you can't fool me
[Music]
you are really really bad at your job
dude really really
bad really
[Music]
bad as if as if in a in a like building
like this where you're offering to have
like a merchandise area to for people to
look at as if there wouldn't be more
people that would go there and be a
little bit excited actually it would
probably be crowded
generally okay what if I'm just a
[Music]
fan uh so should I be impressed oh wow I
apologize
dear wow very
disrespectful okay security guard was
not trained to do his job in this place
in particular
whatever
scram
okay you were kicked out yeah that's
fine can I just go back to the main
lobby never mind the main lobby is also
NG for
me let's just wait outside In the Heat
of the Japanese summer how about
that I'm just a passer
by how did you end a video explain yeah
I don't think this this answer is like
really a good one but okay spill it out
you're here to steal the merchandise
right
Thief I am kiaha by day and fif Joel by
night right now do you see a moon in the
sky no so therefore right now I am just
kiaha I am not fief right
now only in the night
I mean I do want all these merchandise
but I wouldn't steal this is a false
accusation no sir I'm not a Thief what
kind of thief would be wearing a suit
this isn't my the most flexible thing to
move and carry
things and I know that because I am a
thief by night but not now okay this
could be a disguise to trick all of the
employees in the
building
um are you like are you just cosplaying
as a security guard by the way because
you seem to be like just some child who
likes to play detective games you know
maybe you should be kicked out
ah this is my first rodeo Thief there's
a lot of Thieves who disguise themselves
as
fans oh my [\h__\h]
god oh my [\h__\h]
god why is he being so
skeptic okay okay
[Music]
uh how about a thief disguise as a
security guard oh I want to say that
even though I think it's like letting
him no if wait maybe he is a fief and
then if I let him look for his for my
back he will steal my CV and then I
can't go to the interview is that
it oh what about a bunch of nonsense of
course not Oh I thought who knows maybe
there's actually one closer than we
think wait are you accusing me of thief
I'm accusing you as a cosplayer the
security guard swiftly took the mighty
weapon hanging on his
trousers
uh excuse me what sexual
harassment what a [\h__\h] oh oh I can still
go back
okay a
search my
[Music]
bag give it
here he began to ramage for your back
meticulously not even 5 minutes he
handed you your back back couldn't find
anything suspicious you wearing the
thief after maybe but then I mean by
your logic also I don't have any money
with me so I'm also standing at the
merchandise area with no money therefore
not able to buy wouldn't that maybe
strengthen your you believe that I am a
[Music]
thief but okay we're through with it so
what are you doing here actually I am a
candidate for a job interview but I have
some time to spare so I explored the
office a bit I see that sounds like
really reasonable like anybody would
do yeah right I know thank you may I ask
where the interview room is I was told
it was on the second floor just take the
elevator to the second floor it's the
first room next to the
elevator okay thank you
[Music]
sir ah wow okay sheesh you excused
yourself and began walking towards the
interview room as it was almost 11:00
a.m. reaching the second floor you were
greeted with a shocking sight the second
floor was packed with other candidates
waiting for the
turn a d like this
candidate number 102 candidate number
102 oh they're calling with numbers why
aren't they using our names gosh why is
the number 102 here number
102 wait what was my number again you
quickly took your phone out and checked
the messages from the whole ID staff oh
shoot they messaged me half an hour ago
I didn't even realize I was number
[Music]
97 oh goodness gracious give me a break
turns out you missed the message from
from the staff regarding your candidate
number and five candidates already went
after
you well can we say we're one2 then
where did this guy run off to they think
this is a game huh number 102 isn't here
cross the
out joh next
candidate got it candidate Number 103
candidate Number 103 shoot they must
have crossed my name out already can I
still join I've come this far I can't
just go home like this I was excited for
this I I could finally get a job what if
you just show them the like the the the
phone message would prove that you are
97 but they would probably still be mad
that you
[Music]
late
um let's just give up and go home end of
stream now let's uh ask the staff you
approach the staff standing by at the
door excuse me since number 102 isn't
here may I be subbed in
I'm a candidate number 97 I was late you
what happened
here please I beg you allow me to come
in for the interview please I can bear
being jobless oh I can I
can I can't bear being jobless anymore
please help out a fella I'm sure you
know how hard it is to find a job wow
I'm so desperate right now why can't we
just be more normal
I just want to be more
normal oh
y give me a hand you were practically
begging the staff but all they can do is
stare in confusion not knowing how to
respond really why are they so
incompetent you were late and now you're
being you're beg you're begging to be
subbed in you must be out of your mind
security SEC no he's my
bestie it's okay bring the security I'm
bestie now with security he was holding
me up anyway the security was holding me
up so maybe that can count as an
excuse
nope two security guards appear behind
you out of th air you were kicked out of
the
office let's just watch and see what
happens I had a feeling that that might
be the right
option there's so many candidates here
I'm screwed if I ask directly I should
probably stay quiet for now I can't be
too
careless despite the racing of your
heart you tried to calm yourself
[Music]
down someone bumped into hard all of
their stuff scattered on the
floor oh it's
102 it just said 102 but it was like
hidden kind of in two white on
white uh repent the person them or
pretend nothing happened or help
them uh
help since you are kindhearted you
immediately help the person who hits you
earlier as you helped the person picked
up their scy of belongers from the floor
you immediately noticed an olly brochure
all of their belongers are now back in
their back they went to the staff who
was busy calling candidates for the
interview excuse me I'm candidate number
102 I was stuck in traffic may I still
be allowed for the
interview H nice another candidate is
also
late oh that will not be allowed there's
a zero tolerance policy for candidates
who aren't able to come at the appointed
time well generally I understand that
generally especially if you have
apparently over 100
applicants then I I feel think I
understand
[Music]
that
yeah but but the traffic was out of my
control that is unfortunately even
though it's really [\h__\h] annoying also
not any anything to reason
with unless you got
isy that traffic is also out of your
control and that is the only
exception after receiving rejection
after rejection from the staff that said
candidate gave up and began walking home
if that's how they react I probably
don't have a chance either maybe I
should just go home but my dream to
become ol's
reporter it's almost 12:00 p.m.
candidates above the number 104 may take
a lunch
break
oh wait what about the
what about the others then I guess they
assume they're already gone so you could
just say any anybody who's still here
can take a lunch break we'll be
continuing the interview session at 1:00
p.m. candidate number 104 is required to
stay and come into the interview room
when candidate one of three leaves oh
okay only that one
dude has to
stay thank you for your attention
candidates began dispersing to begin
their lunch break even the staff began
tidying up their files
no I can't give up on my dream I need to
get interviewed today whatever it takes
you must it up the course to approach
the staff before they leave for their
own lunch break excuse
me you are uh I am you also late
uh
[Music]
uh uh
I just want to get to
Olie I have a do I have a valid reason I
mean I saved the
grandma and your security guard was
accusing me of
fing wait I hear me out please I I I
have to get this job unlike everybody
else here I actually have to get this
job no I don't want to hear it you're
just wasting my time there's no excuse I
haven't heard over slap TR some old
cliche excuses
Classic No but what about my
excuse come on come
on I have a valid reason how is this any
different from the other from the other
situation that we just had I wasn't late
because of traffic or my own
carelessness and you think I care you
are late please hear me out it has been
my dream to take part in this election
much less being a candidate for the
you uh-huh I won't give up with my dream
I want to be H reporter are you going to
crush my dreams just like that I've made
it this far yeah just start crying how
about that I have to admit you have a
away with words really really I do
thanks for the membership renewal how is
my words with way way with
words any
different than the other
guy doesn't mean I'll give you a pass
for being late this procedure from the
company there's no use trying to win me
over oh I think we can let this slide
for
once father the
train I was touched this candidate's
dream is so
Earnest
really really how about we give him a
chance and listen to his
reason if you're late you're late but
this one seems different from the
previous one
no well we are different people yes the
previous one was late because he was
stuck in traffic they could have left
earlier and might solve the problem so
let's hear what the reason this one has
for being
late uh fine what's your candidate
number I'm
97 hearing your answer the two staff
were hesitant they turned towards each
other and
whispered this one's even worse than the
previous one
yeah just tell this candidate to go home
this isn't even wor our time but still
let's listen to what this candidate has
to say for himself I can't explain it
but there's this inkling feeling inside
me that we should play
Splatoon uh what what do you mean why do
you want a game now uh yesterday you
said it would rain but it turns out it
was scorching hot all day I regret
bringing an umbrella what this is
different I'm sure about this one trust
me oh my God can we just meet some more
cute
girls I want to meet way did I miss my
chance to meet waya already somewhere
outside they weren't exactly being
silent about their Whispers you could
hear what they said as clear's day
seemingly they were going to give you a
chance based on the reason you'll give
fine we listen to what you have to say
if you say any excuse that is okay okay
what why why like this of course I
understand all right now spill I was
late because I got lost in looking for
the interview room I was hanging out in
the merchandise area I have no idea the
interview system is going to be like
this oh is this the interview
already is this the
[Music]
interview and thanks for the raid
uh I don't think any of this is a are
good answers we should just say that we
saved our grandma and Dad one of the
security guards was wasting my time by
accusing me of being a
thief because both of this is not really
on me the one thing with the Grandma
will show that I am a
hero H and the other thing will show
that you guys are incompetent here and
you will will have to apologize to
[Music]
me freaking security yeah they assaulted
me they tried to kill
me uh but what the [\h__\h] am I supposed to
say this is not good this is like why
are you wasting your time in the
merchandise area when you come here for
the interview that's your fault for not
managing your time
better and getting lost okay maybe
that's still the but that's also a
stupid stupid thing like how can I be so
[Music]
late be because I got lost like I mean
that's also on me kind of like that's
not a good answer even none of this is a
good
answer H you think this one at least
might mention the security all right
let's try it
out it was really hot outside I better
cool off there then come here all sweaty
right uh I think if you want to cool off
sit in the
fridge
oh
okay is that what you
do you're mental y'all are mental in
here I don't want to work here
[Music]
anymore fridge at your
house okay so much for
that I got lost when looking for the
interview room plain excuses it's not
plain it is freshly well
seasoned no it is well
reasoned a joke ye
oh also game over he threw me out the
window and killed
me nice I guess I didn't know the
interview system will be like this I was
not informed regarding the candidate
number oh okay we're bringing that up
oh I only got my number an hour ago what
I was informed was to come for an
interview at 11:00 a.m. in fact I
arrived at the office half an hour
earlier then oh oh oh we're killing it
now okay right at 11:00 a.m. I arrived
at the second floor and the message from
my number came in which was candidate
number number
97 M can I take your word for it what do
you mean
like you know that this is how you guys
were planning it there's what oh come on
what is this we sent out the candidate
numbers a day before the
interview yeah check my phone I got it
like recently it showed the message I
received and for my arrival time you can
ask the security guard at the
merchandise area
[Music]
oh this is like oh oh
objec
she
[Music]
n we obliterated
him with good
reasons yeah a journey let's
go there was no answer from the staff
only a look of shock remained as they
saw the time of the message their
attention shifted between your phone and
you oh this is a special candidate for
sure you almost kicked out a special
candidate why why am I special because I
got the Le the message so late shut up
okay I was mistaken stop bringing it
[Music]
up here's how we're going to do this you
will go into the interview room after
candidate Number 103 we apologize we
didn't realize you are a special
candidate yeah special special because I
am actually Ollie
yeah same font Platinum Panda same
[Music]
font wait what if wait a [\h__\h] second
what
if
reporting reporter for Oli is a Mis
transation or so
because I already thought that sounds
like I'm interviewing only but what if
that is a
misunderstanding I thought I think I'm
interviewing Ollie but no no no I'm
interviewing to be Ollie to join the
company like I mean
obviously oh but I guess the game still
thinks I'm a guy but
wait what if this is all of this is just
me interviewing to become Ollie
no no no new Ollie Ollie hasn't debuted
in this timeline yet her merch is there
oh oh stop breaking my
logic don't question me and my logic
[Music]
please
don't damn it
it damn it man my everything's crumbling
my whole world view is
crumbling so I must eat chocolate now my
fruit hurts in general today what the
[Music]
[\h__\h]
man we inform candidate number 104 to
wait a little
longer okay
just as the staff finished telling you
the good news cidate Number 103 came out
of the room pale as a
ghost the happiness disappeared as soon
as it came nervousness running through
your veins it was your time to shine and
you didn't know what to
expect
Oh wait we're going to be interviewed by
Ollie I think
right
because because you guys were telling me
about like no wait wait no we're not
being interviewed by Ollie we're
probably just being interviewed by some
Randle and they're going to ask
questions like what's all these
weight and stuff like that because that
was something that will crash the game
so I remember that question oh the one
spoiler just am
Rando I'm in
let's
go where am I supposed to go after this
special candidate number 97 you may sit
down the voice startled you you didn't
know where it came from sit where I
can't even see your hands how am I
supposed to find a chair anywhere or
maybe I'm allowed to sit
anywhere
[Music]
um let's feel my my
surroundings waving your hand you tried
to fill your surroundings trying to
figure out if there's a chair anywhere
as you met with nothing you Tred to
explore a larger
radius suddenly you felt something
something rough and
hairy what in the world is
[Music]
this make a work
let your imagination R Wild also we make
our own ending now thank you so I have
to do the work now I'll sit on the floor
since you have no clue where the chair
is because the room is Pitch Black you
decid to sit on the floor this action
brought back the memories of your
freshman year in
college special candidate number 97 you
may sit down on the chair the same voice
from before came
back I'm sorry I'm sorry sir ma'am I
can't find
[Music]
the this is part of the interview this
is the challenge finding the chair you
could feel it heartbeating a thousand
times a second fear of saying something
wrong however it was not they're testing
if you have night vision or
not because that is apparently necessary
to work for Whole Life guys I'm
sorry or you can bring night vision
goggles if you're smart enough if you
know about it you can cheat the system
you can do
it this is why I'm a cat today h this is
why I can actually see the chair I can
see it and I'm showing you the game for
my
eyes yeah a yeah both I'm s
by she has night vision goggles that's
how she made it yeah yeah it's not like
you had any choice as it is impossible
to see anything in the room oh oops
apologies we forgot to turn on the
lights you're so funny as if that's not
something you would notice right away
that's like in front of your [\h__\h]
eyes CT as ctas every single light in
the room turned on one by one what what
does this mean is this like
a what is that is that a sound
effect I thought we're chatting
something see a s c a s c a
s finally Illuminating the
room oh my
God this
game would you look at that the chair is
right beside me I look like an idiot
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I thought I
wasn't able to feel it h h lifting
yourself from the ground you swiftly sat
on the provider chair facing the long
empty table in front of you not long
after after you hear footsteps from the
distance this is it it's time for an
interview with Ollie with
Ollie
really wait hold on I need to check my
appearance I don't want all oh yeah
bring out the little mirror again never
mind I'm sure I look fine now must be
all these footsteps oh I'm so excited
your heartbeat quickens it the closer
the footsteps sound however you could
hear more footsteps coming at the
background more
is it all of her generation or
so oh maybe all is with the other staff
that would be interviewing me shoot I
need to tidy up my suit Creek the door
on the other side of the room so maybe
it's all the ID
members come on please please I need to
see some girls now please otherwise like
why am I playing this game I'm being
absolutely scammed right
now this is it I'm finally meeting Ollie
in the flashh this is huh
ana ana is this you
[Music]
Ana
Anna I mean if anybody I think that's
maybe
[Music]
[Laughter]
Anna Ana we're not supposed to collab
oneon-one get out
we're not supposed to be together alone
in a
room Ana emerged and you were unable to
hide the shock on your face we're not
supposed to be together all
alone unless it's a totachi
absurd the open Button revealing too
much no her her bare feet revealing too
much than you comfortable with this is
the real reason why I don't collab of
Ana I have a feet phobia
[Music]
yeah this is the
truth but doesn't waya also have bare
feet in her
default wait does she no okay she has
shoes why do I remember her
feet fauna
yeah well I don't collab much with fauna
either do I tells you
something really tells you
something I have a feat phobia and I am
no longer scared of admitting it there
are many people out there who have a
feed
phobia it's not just me
I'm not alone right I'm not alone it's
nothing to be ashamed
[Laughter]
[Music]
of okay there's just some weird dude
here am I in the right room is this a
prank as much as I'm surprised it wasn't
Ollie nothing has prepared me for this
man's outfit what it's
fine just kind of Yakuza not Yakuza but
like w to be gangster Vibes even being
interviewed by a grasshopper would be a
lot better than this grasshopper you
say are you hearing
[Music]
this I have prepared my own
grasshopper no no it's a
grasshopper after all of the staff was
seated down the atmos feel of the room
shifted the silence was deafening why is
he looking at me like that I should be
the one giving you that look uh maybe I
should take the initiative let's start
with um self- introduction I would like
to introduce myself self I am candate
number 97 I am here to do an interview
to be always reporter the room went
silent as if it wasn't already as silent
quiet and empty as your heart
why are we suddenly in depresso
mode you should greet him
first I I did by introducing myself but
okay oh okay I can still go
back uh okay let's greet
him oh good afternoon Mr hrd from Whole
Life
Indonesia uh yes good afternoon to you
candidate no number 97 no need to
pleasantries oh even though the game
Told You So we get straight to the
questioning
session what do you know about our Holo
ID Talent Ki
AI uh she
is all of all of the above so nothing
wrong
here um a zombie
Idol she R from from the dead but had
Amnesia when she finally managed to
return home she found her old oh I I am
hitting him with the lore I am yapping
the
L that really proves that I have watched
her debut stream I indeed have I indeed
have I think I think I've watched uh
like all debut streams of people that
debuted after me including also um I
mean live when we're talking live I also
watched uh all of the the debut streams
from uh uh the fifth
generation uh I think I also watch the
fourth generation live mostly but with
the fifth generation the special thing
is that me and the girls from myth we
were as you may imagine cuz there was
one month in between our debuts we were
watching them like
together uh in Discord
and we were getting really really
nervous watching the fourth gen together
did I ever tell you this that we did
that we did
this yeah we were taking notes and like
it was hitting us with the realization
that we were up
next and I think I
also ah that was like I saw them all
using like uh music that they produced
or commissioned to be produced for them
so then I also commissioned the same
person who made those two legendary kiar
bgm tracks that I rarely use
[Music]
nowadays oh did we watch her frd debut
together I'm not sure about that but we
definitely watched all of the normal not
3D normal debuts from the NEP labo
generation yeah oh oh man that was still
the Calm before the storm pretty
much and I think we weren't even
announced at that point of course not
yeah we weren't even announced so people
didn't even know people even didn't know
what was coming to them people didn't
know that there was going to be an
English generation an English brdge very
soon
after people had no
idea sheesh
but yeah I got really nervous after that
after watching their debuts I was like
oh their debuts are so high quality
because like
after after each
generation the debuts would like be more
and more interesting and higher quality
I think at this point they have um kind
of like
stopped growing in quality so immensely
but there was like I feel like there was
this jump of uh quality
starting from the nip yeah maybe from
the nipple label
generation not that honestly not that
lower so to say lower quality lower
effort deuts are not interesting I think
like just having normal ones is fun too
um and also just like having low effort
stuff like PowerPoint is really charming
and funny and interesting like that is
absolutely
valid but you know everybody does it
differently oh yeah Kobo coding her own
website like people kept on after Li
nipo people kept on trying to make it
more and more interesting so that their
debut would uh stand out and honestly
that was a difficult predicament to find
yourself in I think trying to have to be
really trying to have having to try to
be really unique and all that in your
debut doing something nobody has done
before is really difficult at this
point so I think it's okay to just do
normal debuts again at this point we can
like cycle it like
fashion like 80s fashion gets popular 20
years later and then ' 90s fashion gets
popular 20 years later and so on you can
cycle the trends like in
fashion perhaps
H retro debuts yeah bring me bring me a
coron style debut
please yeah money what's up what's up
it's ele in
it Kon style or I don't know who else
was like just uh who else stood out
because they had a really simple or
weird debut back in the day I don't
know no I was I uh I was thinking even
older than Canada
[Music]
Senpai it's been too long too long some
members even privated their debut stream
I think so sad I want to see it
no intro to streamers if you oh oh that
would be so
bold you expect a debut stream and they
just start playing Minecraft or
something like from the Geto and act
also just don't even like introduce
yourself just act and talk to the chat
as if you've always been there has
someone done this
before like a
complete normal stream
no not not c on it no no that was still
like like we're like a debut like
introducing yourself she just gamed at
some point but I mean you should just
like game from the start until the
end just play a game for 1 hour and be
like hi welcome back guys so we're going
to play Minecraft you let's go so I've
been building this
thing oh yeah I can said but had a phone
debut yeah that's one of those things
what I mean with like an old uh unique
weird
debut anyway let's continue
sorry she found her old house had
already turned into a Ramen Shop the hrd
knowledge and satisfaction upon hearing
your answer we did our
homework no bit no B at all then what
was the reason could you only chose to
become a
vtuber we should safe again but because
I feel like somewhere here soon enough
there will be a
gamebreaking
bug uh she wants to reclaim my old house
oh hey I didn't even have to choose the
answer now on to the next to the serious
questions yes
sir uh of course as all is reported I
will be required to have prior knowledge
of her Origins and now I'm getting a
little nervous I wonder what the next
question will be they say it's going to
be serious and this it felt like it
already was serious so obviously this is
a flag for some not so serious
questions don't worry I got this I
pulled an all nigh for this interview
you stroke your chest to calm yourself
down oh I'm am I going to get kicked out
for stroking my chest
now please
no you never know you never know I
wanted to answer this quickly oh
God how many stitches
the [\h__\h] where all but aren't some
stitches covered by cloes second what
color is all right eye beside red and
green F what size are all these feet is
this one of the game breaking
ones the feet no right this is not it
right you guys got to warn me next what
game does Ollie often play in collab
wait wait wait wait what what there can
I answer in between
next this feels like a g a game quiz but
OLED he sounds like he's rapping is this
really interview this feels like a prank
just a moment
sir oh we're back to oli's feet
size
uh
next what will I ever get to
answer is this like a a thing where I
have to say stop like you're spinning
and spinning the wheel of questions by
just saying them out loud and I I have
to say
stop which generation of whole ID does
all belong to
next or is this like I'm actually no I
am indeed not g getting any time to
answer s
sir
uh uh hold on
sir you start with me K you just speak
normally and what do you mean hold on
I'm not going anywhere
[Music]
um my apologies
sir apology not
[Music]
accepted what the
[\h__\h] h i mean I wonder if any of these
would have been okay or if I have to go
even further back I have I doubt I doubt
other interviews ask questions like this
not only that why are you even dressed
like
that oh no what are we getting ourselves
into as someone in position there is a
need to look the part thus you should
wear proper business attire to keep up
appearances oh no oh no lastly I should
have been nervous when asked but I'm
just overwhelmed the questions also
should have been related to the job I'm
applying for sir at least that's how it
is in movies
sir what an
argument I didn't expect a candidate
would lecture me like a mother but I
have mommy issues so I love it my
apology sir was that being too
[Music]
presumptuous was I being too
presumptuous haha calm down calm down
I'm actually delighted to have a rookie
so okay I didn't have to go even further
back okay we were on the right track to
have the initiative to express their
thoughts and opinion you're one
interesting fellow Brave and unique he
judged me based on the knowledge you
gained from movies well I will be
accepting your
application he heyo wait did I skip
Those gamebreaking Questions by not
going to the other options or so
[Music]
before uh uh uh
heo auto win auto win oh is that later
okay but still I win kind
of you held your head low the fear of
being reprimanded runs deep however the
feeling was quickly frown out the window
and you were able to look at the hrd eye
to eye again for real sir I will be only
reporter not necessarily reporter
it
oh apparently you were accepted as
director why is that game over that is a
a probably better paid job within whole
life failed
successfully director
y directors are like they have more say
and
everything I'm over
qualified
she
what okay I think
maybe should should I try this one too
then or is it all game
over you don't want to falter I didn't
raise my voice you probably wouldn't
stop please slow down sir what if I had
a panic
attack then I'm too weak for this
job feels like being chased by a demon
you're calling me a demon w w you're
going to game over me
[Music]
right explain myself that's not what I
meant sir no
excuses okay
Bute I think maybe we should go further
back so we asked him to hold
on what if we sa for Yo's sake calm down
maybe maybe hearing the word Yago brings
us
further oh we didn't say Yago in the end
you raised your voice out of reflex
wanting to catch the HR D's attention as
he was rapping faster than Eminem
himself realizing your voice had come
out higher than expected your hand was
quick to cover your mouth oh shoot I
raised my voice at hrd please please
please please don't be angry I had to go
through all the effort to perate the
staff I can't act like this you were
spring bullets scared of being kicked
out
but
haa ha my apologies it's a bad habit of
mine I ramble I don't even notice it
until you said
[Music]
that how was this more acceptable then
hold on
please wa where is the difference
anyway no did you see like I clicked it
away pretty fast but in the like down
here it didn't even say yo down
here like we said the sentence without
[Music]
yo but I'm impressed no one has ever
dared to raise their voice at me I
respect your courage I will repeat the
question first how many stitches does
Ollie have okay I think we
were able to
um move
on but probably a a big amount 13 if I
remember it
correctly y yeah I mean the others would
be too little but even 13 sounds too
little but okay what color is all right
eye beside red and
green probably yeah
yellow I think but I don't really I
don't really have it in my memory right
now to be honest even though today I was
watching her
[Laughter]
stream ah it was correct again y w w who
who who W but next questions I want a
firm answer answer me without any hint
of Doubt
okay so I can see you sure if you answer
yes sir I like enthusiasm we need a
courageous and passionate reporter next
H oh that's it that's it that's uh I
have to change to Indonesian I
think so yeah
okay then I it's also a good excuse if I
get the answer
wrong uh Cali okay
[Music]
H I don't know
man
[Music]
serious oh uh I think well she's
definitely not
172 this is a pretty small difference
like I'm thinking uh I'm seeing her
visually right
now uh I don't I she I think she's 159
because I feel like I don't know I don't
really know she's not too short but
she's also not too tall but these ones
are both that but she's probably
ha I think I got it
right
right oh I got it
wrong ah damn
it okay can I switch back to English
now
oh I think I
[Music]
think I can switch probably
right okay
hopefully Splendid among all of the
previous 10 three
candidates they were other 103
candidates you're the first to answer
correctly until this point
y Oh Oh you mean oh oh sorry that was me
being dumb I mean the translation is
very off here and there but for once it
was my brain that was
off you mean you
[Music]
mean I was just going by you know the
translations so far
being
well well you know okay we got it what
is the name of all Tedy
bear uh
Udin yeah I think when I first heard the
name of
her uh Little Bear I
felt I I might be wrong now but I feel
like I felt some
connection uh with tales off Symphonia
or so wasn't there an
Udin in a tailes off game or so
and I was like oh oh that sounds like a
yeah was it unen and I just like mixed
it is there is there any
UD yeah the water summon oh but I'm
happy some of you guys know
it close enough close enough yeah yeah
or wait wait is that wait let me let me
Google just any Tales of Udin
[Music]
Udin there is an Udin with an E I
think at least here this video says
Tales of arise finally defeating
Udin and also Tales of
Symphonia
but in tell of Symphonia at least in
German
here it says UD maybe it's only in
German uud d i n
e is the water ghost maybe I was not so
wrong I don't think it's with n it's u d
i n
[Music]
e hey let's go I wasn't so
wrong next when did OE deut the day the
day
oh no idea it was definitely not
Christmas I feel like it might be
14th a
fourth thank
you December 4th no
okay
2020 wow yeah I guess it was in the same
year as us smth a while after us yeah
yeah second gen ID was not so uh not so
late after
us I
got new Co High weren't they My First Co
eyes
anyway I think so and then yeah cuz I
was so excited it was my first Co eyes
and then there was a bird there another
bird because whole life has so many
birds now but if you think about it I
was kind of the first one because subu
Senai let's be honest she's not a real
bird so I was the first one and then
they kept on adding new ones after me
though like they found a liking for
Birds afterwards now it's like every
[\h__\h] generation has a bird but it
wasn't so much like that
[Music]
before yeah so I was really excited no
birds beforehand but the moment you know
way debut I'm like oh my God it's a bird
let's go we have a connection I was just
happy to have uh like one automatic
connection with
someone why do you lie to us like this
of course she's a bird of course she's
part of hon you know but just for making
sense of my point we have to for one
moment be honest to
ourselves just so that we can make this
point that so
somehow Birds became way more common for
some
reason halfway through all of the whole
life Generations more or less how how
could they get so far without debuting
any girl H girls without debuting any
birds and then right after me like they
every freaking generation had a bird how
does that happen
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's just weird to me it's funny to me
thank you for giving me the
oh wait what no this can't be time
difference may make one of the areas a
different date by one day but how can it
be December 4th 2020 in Indonesia time
and December 1st in Japan time
I finally realized I was just you know I
was just right up to here
but
[Music]
yo huh do you know what you're talking
about maybe I should replace you dude
what is ol's
Talent yeah I'm pretty sure Ollie is
multi-talented
yeah oh
[Music]
because she worked in a Ramen place
would it be cooking but also I feel like
she was showing off some good
impersonation
skills but yeah I would have said
language originally if it if it was up
here yeah I feel like yeah didn't she
even in her debut stream didn't she do
some impersonations I don't I feel like
I remember that but I might be wrong
oh yeah is this based on her debut yeah
right there were impersonations right I
I really vaguely remember there being
impersonations yeah yeah yeah
yeah next including her how many
siblings does she have
oh well wait IRL
siblings
IRL oh this honestly I don't know
[Music]
three four
four
uh do you
know four four four includes Ollie okay
then
free ol is the youngest
a what do you mean she's the youngest
she has a youngest
sibling uh no I mean what I just said I
mean she's the
youngest can't fathom how a fan doesn't
know you're just a seasonal fan of Ollie
aren't you ollie mention this pretty
often is sorry I messed up just one
question don't don't be so
mean really sir how come I've never
known what you think I'm lying
oh okay so maybe what what what is he
implying Ollie is the youngest what what
what do you mean she's the youngest what
does this mean what is she saying I
don't understand
him why did we get to this point how did
this happen what what's let's try
four
okay
what I oh I have to include her in the
total
okay
okay what languages can only speak if
I'm not mistaken she could speak free
languages well thanks game for telling
me Oh but
okay uh well it's obviously this one
mhm next who's
Olivia
ah
wait uh out of these options I feel like
it's all of
[Music]
them a fake
fan free okay you guys know better you
guys know better in this case from
Another Universe gave you a long stare
it was nerve-wracking ha you're so tense
it's so funny to tease you um I'm here
to flirt with Ollie not with you so [\h__\h]
off don't worry answer was correct this
is the last question what is the main
reason you want to be Ki O's
[Music]
reporter
uh huh
I think this is not it it's either that
or that I feel like this could imply
that I'm just like a
stalker but this could imply that I
would be fine with any job as long as
I'm a reporter so I don't have the
passion for it specifically for
Ollie but I could be looking more
professional with this answer while this
one might not seem so
professional but okay let's try I like
Ollie because I like Ollie Ollie
motivates me with her funny contents as
a fan I don't want to just receive I
want to give back to ollie and the
community this is why I want to be oli's
reporter the hrd seemed satisfied with
your answer he nodded along your answer
as if you were serenading him slam the
hrd stood up harshly and out of shock
the quick stood up as well with a kind
smile the hrd extended his hand still
confused to decided to play along and
shook his hand anyway I'm accepting you
as K always reporter welcome to Hol life
and
you've shown me an outstanding and
impressive
interview
y woohoo let's save I [\h__\h] made it
but how much more is there in this game
I still have not met
Ollie or waya or a bunch of the others
where's wait Ana we'
met Ana we'
met Yoo y
YooHoo what it's so
long
oh
oh oh this is only
[Music]
25%
oh uh okay I was expecting a shorter
stream
H my fro isn't doing so well
today
no
no maybe I can't play the whole
game I'll play a bit more but no I
thought oh man I thought it was shorter
[Music]
ah part
two
[Music]
H I mean I I can yeah
but that was also not the
[Music]
plan okay well we'll see we'll see I'll
do it a bit more thank you sir thank you
so much you thank them bow to the hrd
many times he seems slightly L annoyed
though that's enough now please follow
me to the other room uh for what purpose
sir isn't it obvious to meet lady Oli
you don't want me to introduce you to
your work partner I still don't really
mean understand what it means to be her
reporter am I writing a book for her or
an article or do they is it a
mistranslation and I'm her manager or
what am I even to her what am I
let's get
moving you neither are we her
assistant it there stream
restrictions
still I thought maybe they they were
lifted or
so wait up to
[Music]
when yeah she lift up them right
until you meet Ollie pretty sure she
lifted them is she still
online we can ask her I can I don't even
need to play this game I have like
direct contact with
Ollie yeah I'm pretty sure it was lifted
come
on
Flex you were quick C on your feet to
follow the
hrd oh that's just that's just a that's
that's that's that's
just
that's wait that's just why did I why am
I in her home why am I in her
home what
okay wait what well
what this is not appropriate she lives
in the
office the next you we were starting to
see Ollie in the middle of the messy
room
Ollie it was you after
all sorry Ollie's currently busy trying
to find her missing
item uh
okay suddenly a loud ringtone snapped
the both of your attention it was the
hd's phone
I'll excuse myself for a moment you can
introduce yourself and get to know each
other for now only will give you further
instructions uh on your
responsibilities I'll leave you to it
finally Ollie finally
finally Ollie I'm alone with her in her
bedroom I really want to ask for a
picture and then
I
cute that's like that face that's like
[Music]
cute
Ollie she's even cuter in
here just
kidding wow
cute Oli stood up and patted her skirt
gently she stared at your Direction with
a sharp stare oh hello I heard you're
the one who will be reporting me right
nice to meet you
I'm pleased to be working with
[Music]
you police will be working with you'll
be all these report of this you were so
nervous that you mimicked all these
speech
earlier P
Polie nervous aren't you sorry I'm
pretty busy right now I'm looking for my
missing item how about meeting again
tomorrow oh tomorrow of course Ollie the
journey back home was filled with
satisfaction you was ex ecstatic to
successfully become all these reports
order let's go oh hey my room is much
cuter what the
[\h__\h] ring ring ring the sound of your
phone disturbs your sleep disturbs
thinking it was your alarm you ignored
the sound and went back to sleep as it
is still too early oh no was it her and
now I'm losing my job because I didn't
pick
up however the ringing never stopped
unable to continue sleeping you got out
of bed and checked your phone turns out
it was never the alarm it was a phone
call from an unknown number you had no
choice but to answer despite being half
asleep uh moshy MOSI that was me of all
I'm Indonesia am I speaking to K always
newest
reporter yeah yeah that's me great since
you have been accepted I assume you set
to work I'll be waiting for you in my
office at 10:00 a.m. got it is there
still a million game overs at this
point after being accepted
yeah what am I just going to die guess
I'll
die guess I'll get
fired
[\h__\h] uh today I thought work doesn't
start until
tomorrow
uh yeah I mean if I work for Whole Life
Indonesia I should know Indonesian
[Music]
which I totally
do this is a
Minefield ah [\h__\h]
uh
oh ID Bros anybody
[Music]
anybody
ah ah
one this sounds like raina's lyrics
I mean anybody any ID members lyrics
really right I'm on my okay
thanks like right now right now
understood I'll be on my
way good good my office is on the second
floor just beside the interview room
don't be late I don't like tardy
employees I'm hanging up now I have
other business to attend to no that's
sir you didn't even got the chance to
finish your sentence but the H already
hung up you didn't think much of it and
quickly got ready to go to work hi is
not on your side you can't afford to
waste any time by taking public
transportation you opted for a motorbike
taxi as your method of transportation is
very Indonesian
[Music]
now wait motorbike taxi what I just I
was just joking because uh in in
Indonesia there's a lot of motorbikes
so
yeah met Ollie for 60 seconds I
[Music]
mean I honestly feel like
like since the protagonist seems to be
very Star Struck with her and all that
and a big fan I think this is uh how it
should
be like it should feel
special once you arrived you sprinted
towards the hrd office okay calm down
bre brief wait you guys said this was
like chapter one but is there ever any
indication of new chapter or are we just
continuing or like are we already in the
new chapter and it just like you guys
just said that because it feels like a
new
chapter ah okay the CG is the end of
each chapter oh so we are in the new
chapter okay calm down
brief all I need to do is knock on the
door and greet him with a smile no
problem as your breath became steady you
did as you practiced knocking on the
door you can hear the hrd shout from
inside yeah come
[Music]
in stepping into the office you greet
the hrd
politely excuse
me Ollie's here again
Ollie you're surprised to see another
figure in the office beside the hrd in
his eccentric outfit the figure was the
person you've always admired she was
sitting on the sofa flashing you a white
smile eccentric honestly
the way he
dressed reminds me of one
certain staff
who it it doesn't really oh yeah work
with us anymore but
so not so far off
maybe just a dressing
[Music]
style om go
no the figure that was the person you've
always admired she was sitting on the
sofa flashing you with a white smile W
my
idol um
okay here's the thing to be realistic
obviously if you're such a big fan of
her you should not be hired to be in a
direct position working so closely with
her I
think that is something we would like to
avoid wait she's my work partner now I
should be cool about this exactly
come on you got this be cool I can't be
acting like a freak in front of her
fighting okay you two get comfy with
each
other I need to leave for my appointment
huh well well do sir they hrd left
leaving you alone with
Ollie she's so cute wait every time I
see that face it gets
me every time hey we meet again Porter p
was she did she want to say
partner who the what who the [\h__\h] is
Porter uh oh
reporter
oh yeah yeah we'll be seeing each other
more often
now why is Ollie calling me Porter oh
same question I likes to give unique
nicknames easier to remember reporter in
short matches you with your work oh I
see all of a sudden Ollie's eyes began
scanning you from the top of your head
until the tip of your toes it feels
intimidating all's gaze it was as if she
isn't fond of you no she loves me I am
her
Ori which is kind of surreal to say uh
I'm very happy to be anybody's or she uh
like from my colleagues
[Music]
H and it's actually kind of special with
Ollie thinking about it that I wasn't
her AI from the
beginning probably because she just
didn't really know me before she joined
like she probably didn't like pay much
attention to me beforehand but by
working with me
IRL and you know just like experiencing
me both on stream and off stream behind
the scenes is how she decided to make me
her
OSI after Gathering many many many
informations from many other members you
know like getting to know all kinds of
people yeah yeah it's like with me and
Amy yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah she made an informed
decision and that's really special to me
because like she she knows me
IRL and maybe that for her even more so
added
to her finding a liking in me which yeah
that shows that she doesn't only like me
like superficially or
so she she really likes me in all ways
and I feel honored and happy yeah I uh I
it just feels
really I don't know like an honor and
[Music]
genuine I'm so
happy
yeah
[Music]
man
yeah no I it really makes me happy to
hear
that both from Ollie and and Theiss up
honestly it's um really surreal to
me cuz like I'm I I'm always curious not
because I expect I don't expect anybody
who debuts as my cooh high to bring up
my name as the Senpai to that they look
up to I don't expect anybody to come up
with my name I'm just curious to hear it
anyway um
so like having anybody say they like me
out of all the Senpai that they
have makes me so
happy
yeah why isn't this Bang Bang song
listening to my
input bang
bang Porter you don't even know
Indonesian why are you working for
me H the porter forget you or you just
don't know Mr bang bang
hello as much as you triy to recall
anyone named bang bang in your life you
can't seem to find any I only know Ollie
do you
mean to the next to the each W is that
what you mean Holly do you want me to
take like a Tik Tok for you or
what seriously the man who just left is
Mr bang bang oh see he never told me his
name
this is exactly what happens when he
doesn't listen to all his
input he he or
me you don't fully understand what Allie
was talking about but it's just secured
you never known the hd's name until
now I specifically asked Mr bangman for
an eye
candy wait you wait you're saying you
wanted your reporter to be attractive
and are you saying I'm
not what and my PO should know
everything about Allie and be about my
needs
what
[Music]
what wait why is it Indonesian
again wasn't the last option also
Indonesian uh
should I like is this like fixable like
if I go like
this and then here
again no it's still
[Music]
Indonesian uh
I bro I
[Music]
Bros am I not handsome enough
Nar it's the first
one freeze I know everything about
Ollie even though I'm not handsome I'm
sensitive is the second one
uh am I saying this Direct to her or to
myself I don't know am I not attractive
[Music]
enough do you not see yourself whoa whoa
whoa whoa whoa if we were to choose
between you and a naked
morat I would choose the naked Mo
wow I think this is out of character
only
why are you why are you putting these
words into your own
mouth she would never say this never
never never never never
never not to someone she works with
especially emotional
damage never meet your ois for real for
[Music]
real man
it was as if an arrow had struck right
through my
heart do I
quit how does it feel to have your heart
stabbed at by someone learn your place
me what what do you mean why why do I
have to learn my place what what did I
[Music]
do I'm Keen of my surroundings though
what does that mean are we talking about
my looks or the surroundings oh really
if you're so Keen why haven't you made a
drink for Ollie didn't you know Ollie
was streaming a moment ago Ollie is
firsty Ollie is only here because Mr
bangman called he told me he got a good
reporter what good did he even seen
you hey ol's talking to you ollie will
ask for anothera Porter Ollie kind of
acting like a [\h__\h] princess right now
please don't out of panic from all these
words the words came out of your mouth
quicker than you could process despite
being shocked you still went and tried
to make only a drink from the drinks
Corner near the wind Oh wait we're
surviving are we surviving with shaky
hands you managed to successfully made
camel Mal tea until the glass slipped
out of your Shaky Head splitting the tea
all over the
floor dot dot dot dot dot dot dot dot
dot dot dot dot dot dot wait 1 2 three 4
5 6 7 8 9 10 11
13 14 15 16 17 18 19
21 22 23 24 25 I'm already
above the right answer that we had
[Music]
I told you there would be
more
huh over 20 the stitches I'm counting
stitches not dots
guys don't you see my mouse on the
screen Ollie once said she hates
when oh thought sorry I'm scrolling in
the chat
when yeah I think I remember
that I feel like I remember her saying
that she doesn't like it when dot dot is
more than free dots or less I guess
[Music]
also so sorry I'll make another ah you
can't even do such a basic task all it's
not even first
anymore forget it just C Mr Bang's
carpet Porter
[Music]
wait is this just continuously in
Indonesia maybe it is maybe it would be
better if we stop
here I'm becoming Tim
Allen
no can you chill out make it to yourself
oh that's not that's not going to end
well I tripped over the folded carpet
floor and burnt my face with the hot tea
no I held on to an extension cord oh no
reaching for the cupo next to your
support you moveed to stand up however
you grabbed your the drinks Corner
tablecloth by mistake watch out
Kaboom too late the teapot spilled hot
water all over the life extension Court
your Misfortune didn't stop there as he
turned towards Ollie her eyes were
filled with fear and she was shaking In
Her Shoes her hands slowly Rose and
pointed
at fire yeah and we all
die Kaboom I told you yeah Kaboom
indeed when you open your eyes the
entire office had already caught on fire
Ollie was nowhere to be found it seems
she has left you to die
Anna she will kill
me she's all this do hire is incompetent
so anyna will execute the layoff for
you Ana will kill me the fire was going
to kill me
anyway what do you mean
[Music]
I mean ana ana this is my first time
seeing myself really Ana why the [\h__\h]
are you
watching Ana help me with the Indonesian
Parts the aners are Indonesian for some
reason now wait I'm scrolling back uh
where where
okay stop getting angry you'll get
wrinkles okay no that's definitely not
going to be the right answer answer I'm
not even going to try stop no I think
they're all
bad stop complaining if you're patient
Your Grave will be cool as if there's an
air conditioner remember
that
what huh what do you know what do you
know well what does Ollie know about
Graves huh what what what why are we
fighting
H oh it's just just no no fight at all
alllie buried me on the same
day there's no winning in this there's
no winning in this game
35 I can't
win I can't win with this
girl what was this one then stop getting
angry you'll get wrinkles no she looks
angry all the time all is dumpfounded
with you Porter you're not attractive
not keen or sensitive you don't even
know anything about o that's not true my
interview I nailed it o is zombie z o m
b i e i don't
H shoot that's right oops my bad I'm
only human or Phoenix you know I make
mistakes sometimes so anything other
than humans are not allowed to make
mistakes is that what you mean help me
guys I don't understand this
woman such a loose
mouth I am not prepared enough for this
yeah I never thought the only I've
always admired is a [\h__\h]
princess
huh [\h__\h] princess you call me [\h__\h]
princess shoot I said that out
loud oh okay it's Indonesian again
is it just because like I have to
restart the game or so or is this part
not
translated it's not even my fault if I
get uh Bad
[Music]
Endings to if I remember correctly oh
thank you oh Ana with the speed
translate Ana for once not translating
like Japanese for
someone but translating Indonesian for
me thank
you wait wait what did so what wait wait
wait wait wait it said I'm the scary one
who else B bang bang son is the scary
one yeah that is
true bang bang is scary no way I'm
talking about you ol I mean you're cute
bong bong is the [\h__\h]
princess so Cru you stuttering it uh uh
what is Ollie that ugly for you to be
hesitant when praising
Ollie uh no
like isn't that what makes people
stutter someone's
Beauty you're obviously mocking Ollie
and what I
mean and now you're playing me with B
B Porter is so cruel all he hates Porter
[Music]
olly you're breaking
me you're breaking
me all cry was so loud and no find the
other understand the staff came into the
room to check the
commotion I was fired because I made
Ollie cry well at least I didn't die in
this
one and me getting fired is better than
me quitting I think in terms of
pay that's a good ending at this point I
don't know if I can work with this
woman uh
who else would I be oh no that's not
going to be good here this one I'm I'm
scary you're a bad
liar you were mocking
Ollie no no no really I'm talking about
myself H oh
really Ollie walked over and sat down
next to
[Music]
you do you know ol real
[Laughter]
she's bullying the [\h__\h] out of
[Music]
me Anya Ana I would like to pursue you
instead of Oli can I
please I I I don't want to be her
reporter anymore can I be Anya's
reporter please please I don't
want I'm been only
enough I'll get over my feet
phobia I I I I can I can look
away I think Ana left so I have no one
to turn
to so Porter Ollie would advise you to
be honest or Ollie will not believe
anything that comes out of your mouth
anymore oh what Foria
eia it's okay I'll get over it I'll get
over
it Ana Please Release Me From This
suffering yeah I mocked you because
you're being really
[\h__\h] know it ol was right I can't
believe you Porter that's it I've lost
something you ask me to be honest with
you ollie I can't believe this Anna what
what can't you believe this Behavior me
Ne Me
NE but you said to be honest I don't
even want to know anymore you're a
[Music]
liar I met I
met be strong Ollie don't trust that
Liar come here I'll com Fort you s heart
no no wait wait no no no no no wait I
take it as a win I would too if she
didn't also call me a
liar is this a good
ending cuz at least we got to see
waya and the real
Ana and we also saw wiu and eoi a while
ago
why do they show up so randomly like
this
why a good place to stop maybe yeah cuz
I was I was not expecting this game to
be so long really I expected a 1 hour
game and this has been so much emotional
damage I don't know if I can take it
anymore but I'll go back in save um
although when you save and then load
that save can you still scroll
back so okay I have like this safe as
well
um goodbye Ollie maybe me leaving on my
own we'll teach you a
[Music]
lesson sheesh
man my heart is so
[Music]
broken man
where could I have met kobble and the
others I
wonder auto win right man
man who would have
known who would have known that it's so
[Laughter]
difficult this so
rough oh I don't I don't think there's
many more visual novels that are as like
ruthless as this
one is Ollie like actually a a
[Music]
a
sadest so many endings yeah I mean they
definitely went all out on the endings
there's like probably hundreds I've I've
seen a few
M she
B uh this particular developer has this
style what of like
ruthless uh cruelty or
what well thank you Ana by the way for
um showing up happy to see you
uh I I shall oh I can't click exit
what oh there we go okay it just took
some
time that was quite
something
I'm I I I really think I took some
emotional damage from
that I think I'll have to write Ollie a
message hi Ollie
I am in
pain your
game
was not what I
expected I thought you loved
me and yet you have just been so cruel
to me
in fact I don't think that was the real
you surely the real
you will have more compassion towards
me if you want to take down that
impostor together with me
I will do my best to Stand By Your
Side I know the real
Ollie the real
Ollie
wouldn't do any of
this I believe in my heart
one thing I will say
though all in the game
was
visually very
cute
period visually I really typed that I
really wrote
[Laughter]
that oh my God I should just put that as
a steam review for the game
[Music]
yeah
personality oh I turned into uh Star
Wars
creature I think Ollie is sleeping
pretty sure she streamed like twice
today yeah uh speaking of streaming let
me really quickly show you the schedule
for today uh this week I mean in case
you haven't seen it but we might want to
talk about it tada it is uh mostly
Hardcore
Minecraft um I wanted to say it's kind
of
funny that this event is happening
because on Saturday I had a h talk with
what I stand
by and I think in the Stream sorry the
burpy mini burps in the Stream uh we
mentioned a little bit how no one's
active on Minecraft anymore and then
after stream we talked a little bit
about collabing and this and that and I
told her
like yeah man I I I would love to play
more Minecraft you know I love Minecraft
but I kind of need something to do you
know and then we talked about yeah would
be nice if they're like if they bring
out a new update I wonder what was the
last update if I missed one I don't
think I did but like it would be cool if
they put out a new update so that people
come back to Minecraft we're just
talking about like oh yeah eventually
they'll come back for sure and then it
will not just be you what like we were
just talking about it and that was on
Saturday on Sunday pekora Senpai sends a
message to all of
us that the following day on
Monday this event is
happening really short note this first
of all maybe other people maybe she
messaged some Japanese members uh
earlier I don't know
but it was
actually like so convenient like I mean
I feel like oh what the Miss ire this
must be exactly what you were praying
for like a nice way to revive Minecraft
after such a long time for everybody uh
now there's like so many Japanese
members uh participating
not so many ID members um but I was like
thinking H well I'm definitely taking
Monday off and I wasn't sure if I wanted
to participate or not I thought about it
all of Monday and that's also why I
didn't put out the schedule earlier I
was like really really contemplating it
because um actually it would be good in
this week I have a lot of time I think
in this week I don't have any other
plans really that I really need to
follow through I don't have any other
game going on only days with OE I I said
a while ago that I would play and I was
waiting for it so I wanted to give uh I
I wanted to follow up uh and through
with
that um but like besides that I was like
well I actually have a lot of time and I
like Minecraft and this is so good
opportunity you know but then I was like
I'll be honest I was really
contemplating um
like if I should because I felt very
insecure
um like because I watched like 5 seconds
I I jumped for 5 seconds into like the
first stream that they did like P Senai
on this event and I saw them all like
what interacting
happily and I was like
oh no I don't think I can do this so
actually I wrote a message to because P
was like she wrote hey we're doing this
thing uh if you want to particip ipate
DM me and I DMD her and then I watched
that stream for 5 seconds I was like oh
nope nope nope nope nope nope nope nope
nope I I I I don't feel I don't I I
can't do this why I have turned
into an
Inya while like more and more while I'm
in all life feeling more and more like I
can't do this
um cuz like
my connections with Japanese members
also haven't been so strong for a while
now which I thought it would be also
nice to like regain that but at the same
time it was so intimidating and then I
deleted the message and I realized
oh I hope she didn't see it because she
was streaming but my message like even
though the messages are deleted it's
still at the
top of like most recent messages so I
thought oh well she might see that I
I'm up there but if she checks it she'll
just see nothing so it it'll be
fine but then after her stream she
messaged me back and said oh she saw it
and like I I I I I'll tell my manager to
tell your manager to relay all the
information I'm like oh damn it okay
well this is maybe um giving me the push
that I
need but then at the same time I was
like messaging Ena like you know I I
feel really I don't I don't know I think
I want to participate but I'm not sure I
don't I want to only participate if I
know that like someone that I am really
comfortable with uh would be open to
like you know hanging a little bit with
me cuz I I still thought by that
impression from that one stream the
first one that everybody's like
constantly together like in groups and
so on but then today I saw a lot of
people are just like on their own enoan
Ena Chan who's Ena Chan Ina was also
just like I I zoomed for his stream and
I did not see any interactions besides
chat interactions uh on her side
honestly so it seems like she was mostly
a loner
too no that was not the embarrassing
moment at all
um so and then only today I was also
watching she was um interacting here and
there but also a lot of it was doing her
doing her own thing so I realized Maybe
it's okay even if I end up being a
loner but uh yeah I was yesterday I was
still writing to Ena like hey um just
checking would you be fine if I join
some of your Hardcore Minecraft streams
that you have like that I see that you
have scheduled and she just like roughly
scheduled them um uh but I just thought
maybe I'll join those cuz they're these
ones are a good time for me um yeah
generally around noon as you can see the
5:00 P p.m. one is not me adjusting to
Ena it's just uh just uh because I will
probably be alone for that one that's
fine um but then she didn't answer for
so long and I'm like ah maybe maybe
whatever and then I after hours and
hours of no reply I wrote ah whatever
you know it's okay I whatever uh and
then she finally replied and she was
like no it's okay come please please
please
yeah no problem I mean the times might
change but it's all good and and so I
was like oh okay okay okay okay
okay then I felt um
more um secure about joining so then I
decided okay I guess I'll join but I'll
be a little bit late to all of it
everybody's already like doing stuff and
they're doing challenges already and
they've built houses and all that
they've Advanced quite a bit already
so I don't know I might be kind of late
but the stream that I'm joining on
Thursday that I'm doing on Thursday is
only ena's second uh time as
well yeah so I think I'll I'll I'll
hopefully find my way into it but it's
just I I'll have missed out on a bunch
of challenges so I've I'll have missed
out on a bunch of diamonds too uh so
yeah just don't die yeah that's the
thing like I can die but it's difficult
but I can be
revived um I'll just be careful who
knows yeah I might die early and then
maybe I don't do the end of streams but
I think I will so I think we'll be fine
and somewhere at the end of this I don't
know if it's really Sunday or if it's
like the coming Monday
uh because it they they didn't give a
exact date they just said after a week
at the end of this we will uh k build
the Ender Dragon and all that together
so if you survive until then you can
participate in that so yeah I'm just
like uh you trying to you know be part
of it as long as I can and uh that's why
also there's earlier streams because um
you know Japanese prime time is around
that time yeah so I might even start the
first day stream 1 hour early because I
just saw some information that they are
uh doing something right at that
starting time so I thought oh maybe I'll
start a little bit earlier to find my
footing first and then I can join into
the thing that they're doing uh right at
that time you know what I mean yeah so
maybe I'll start one hour early oh I can
get up that early no problem
yeah this is not that early
dude this is fine totally fine very easy
for
[Music]
me sounds like a plan yeah and tomorrow
uh you know I still thought I should
bring you guys a members only stream so
we're not starting tomorrow yet I just
thought I might as well just start when
ena's playing again yeah you do plan to
interact well I'm sure there will be
interactions um I don't know to what
extent uh I'll probably stick uh more to
um like Ollie and Ena probably I don't
know who knows who knows what will
happen but m
yeah while I felt really insecure about
joining I'm going to try to mingle a
little bit with
everybody uh May yeah I'm worried
but I'm going to give it a try I'm going
to try yeah I'll still talk mostly in
English don't worry but obviously when I
interact with Japanese members there
will be some Japanese in here and there
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah h no for Ena again these are not
like she told me these are just rough
times and she's doing some other uh
times as well but that's you know her
thing I won't tell you her schedule
especially cuz it's probably you know
not set in
stone
yeah but this seems to be sometimes
where she might be playing so h
except for
Friday yeah yeah I don't think she'll
release a schedule at all at this
point I know you're introverted but
still you've got amazing social
skills yeah I do have good social skills
but like I
really I really feel like over the past
year or so I've I've buried myself into
a hole of
uh yeah
Darkness I I just I have yeah
yeah yep hermit
chill yeah yeah now I'm going to try to
like look outside a little bit
Peak this is a bit scary I feel I don't
know I I have some feelings um it is
what it is I'm going to give it a try
I think I think we'll have fun we'll
probably have fun oh Ana wrote to
me
oh Ana still
listening
oh but I hate you area stop listening to
my
stream don't worry too much Doom posting
burned out ooshi you can do this no it's
not
burnout I wouldn't call it burnout at
all it's just you know
things I just I in the first
year first two years maybe even I tried
my best really to and I think you can
attest to that to mingle and make
friends a
lot
um yeah and I don't
know I've kind of stopped trying so
hard you were the glue yeah and now the
the thing is I don't I'm maybe I tried
to be the glue in the beginning
with a bridge but now there's several
Bridges and I'm it's not like there's a
need anymore ah this sounds so H don't
whatever uh let's read super
chats let's right super go let's go
let's go before I talk myself into a
Hole
uh where am
I where am I oh is it is this uh where I
made myself
invisible no where am
I ah wait wait wait wait wait here I got
it I got it I got it
oh
oh I don't got it
ah I found a version of
me
yay yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I found me
all right so that's uh what the week is
uh it may be mostly the same game I hope
you guys don't mind but we haven't had
Minecraft in a while and I feel like you
know it might be a fun experience uh
Minecraft always was you know a nice
game to just do whatever and chitchat
and yeah it's been a long time and after
that they will probably not be Minecraft
again for a long time so it's just all
very focused on this
uh weak but it won't be like this always
of
course oh
sure I really like Minecraft so I don't
mind it being back for a little while
with something to do it's nice to have
something to do so thank you to Pon
Senpai for creating a nice little event
maybe she was feeling the same way cuz
like she loves Minecraft obviously maybe
she was also feeling like ah I kind of
want to play Minecraft again but nobody
else is playing really besides m h what
could I do and then she creates this
event for everybody to have a a good
reason to come back to
Minecraft which is awesome it's
awesome
D
Pai yeah it was it was always a stable
and then it stopped being a stable
people just moved on to other games I
feel like they was this this
one phase where it got phased out kind
of was it around the rust times or
so where everybody got really hard into
another similarish game similar from
like being able to play together I feel
like maybe it was partially rust and Arc
and rust yeah maybe both yeah and then
people didn't go back to Minecraft I
thought people would go back to it but
they just didn't really
and Minecraft was never the same after
that Minecraft never recovered after
that whole life Minecraft just kind of
sad kind of sad pal word was really
short I no I don't know if I would uh
blame pal word for
that it was already dead before
that wait I'm looking for some bgm
how about this oh yeah
[Music]
cute a bit too toxic
rest I don't know if I would call
toxic there was just
more
[Music]
uh oh like M uh PVP like it was based
you know PVP in Minecraft people were
never really like um aggressive towards
each other it was mostly
peaceful but at R is just uh more PVP so
maybe that makes it a little bit toxic
but not really
though a the finale of the first rust
season was so
good cuz wasn't I also kind of late on R
man that that also sucked if I was
earlier I could have made more impact
although I did have a good like moment
in the finale like you know making
pekora think I'm on her side and all
that I did kill her
once
yeah oh I guess it was accidentally
really was it I don't remember if it was
accidental apparently it
was and you're not an early bird of
these games yeah for for MInecraft it's
just like it was so sudden I mean it was
at a moment where I was still able to
change my schedule so that was good but
it was like I'm not
sure but it's okay we're going to give
it a try we're going to be positive
about it give it a try got to
overcome you know any kind of
worries that's the way to do it right uh
Super Chat reading time sorry I missed
most of the ending there was a fire
alarm in my apartment but may have
unironically saved the life of my
elderly neighbor by calling for
wow okay
sheesh what a
hero you are a
[Music]
hero okay Super Chat uh starting from
Headbangers I think
[Music]
this was so fun man this was so
good I had a blast me too was so
fun actually surprised not more members
play this game in their stream at least
once it's so good okay ja
[Music]
47 thank you I did get to do a little
bit of sightseeing yeah it was hot
as [\h__\h] I saw a temple
though um like up close uh actually I
would have liked to also see it a little
bit from further away but it was mostly
up close uh but it was like so freaking
overwhelming and beautiful holy [\h__\h] so
detailed my God like I've
seen these like religious what you call
them religious religious buildings from
several cultures now and Thailand
wow was one of the most impressive if
not the impressive from the the
impressive the most impressive from the
architecture I only saw the outside
architecture of it but that was
crazy yeah absolutely
insane wo so
detailed millions of
detail so Ty
but I was so in awe and I wanted to take
it all in slowly but it was just so hot
and in the middle of the day with no
shade whatsoever just Sun everywhere
burning into me I'm actually really
surprised I didn't get a uh sunburn I
like slight
put on
sunscreen um but I don't even think I
covered uh like everything properly cuz
I my back or shoulder was like exposed a
little bit and I or quite a bit quite a
bit so I tried to put it on there on on
my shoulder the back of my shoulder on
my own I don't think I covered it
properly but somehow miraculously I did
not get a sunburn at all
sheesh sheesh that's really lucky she
got any good photos of those locations
uh little bit I didn't take so many
photos um but yes I have some some stuff
[Music]
uh uh yes
in a form to
remember I do burn easily
yeah I do I do where was I oh yeah
motion of fancy thank you for the red
super chat oh my God that's a huge
peny waa thank you so much M for going
totally
overboard FY the one red Penny within
the Sea of blue pennies golden I danash
Psy danash Slavic fellow Dan m danash j
sui D RS D logical Paradox d r d no no
no no
captain
[Music]
planation haven't had a speedy Super
Chat reading like this with no red or
pink interruptions for so long in a
while now I got interrupted by a pinky
from na too much FS no more FS please K
less FS okay
[Music]
careful such an Insider but this is like
my favorite
meme at the moment for our
community it's so versatile too you can
turn it into a lot of
things golden I Dan m d t d the quest
also arst D for the pinky hey boss
recently saw a trailer of EDF 6 where it
showed you sh and your virus wear in it
are you going to be playing it when it
comes out uh I think that's the plan
yes when is coming out again honestly
this is so crazy
because I recorded voice lines and
everything for this many many moons
ago and then didn't hear anything about
it for a long time and even when the
trailer come out came out I I wasn't
really notified anything like I just
found it normally like we get notified
like hey so this is now happening but
nope it just happened I'm like oh oh
it's happening now okay so I really
don't remember anything um but I
think uh oh yeah there are streams
planned but they are not collab
streams you are getting a solo stream on
the game from each of
us
separately h
[Music]
maybe if we all enjoy our solo streams
that are
sponsored if we all enjoy it if we have
fun with it maybe we'll uh do a collab
just on our own from our
own um
will if we all like it which I think
Iris uh likes this type of game
anyway GAA will probably have a good
time with it
too I feel like they would they will
like it maybe we'll organize a
collab I know a lot of you guys were
looking forward to a
[Music]
collab it's a team game anyway so will I
have like NPCs in my team if I play
alone or you guys like is it always
online I I know did the Finish Grand so
I told her yeah okay okay like she
messaged me and I was like okay good to
know uh let's try to get something going
within this month
perhaps but now I don't know if beu can
participate I got to ask
her there's some EMP maybe that help you
uhhuh
[Music]
NPCs H well there's still some time to
go for EDF it's still a while
later
so I love how you caught up the grand I
heard it so much that it would also be
like
more like while it's like still on topic
you know what I mean I heard so hard oh
my
God for [\h__\h] sake I felt mostly rushed
by Ena already being like 100 or
something and thought okay I got to
hurry the [\h__\h]
[Music]
up yeah yeah yeah I mean totally
understandable that Zetta didn't have
time and all that and I
mean she doesn't have to force herself
to play it fast or
so if she doesn't feel like it you know
but now she's finished
[Music]
I don't know if I remember the game play
but I'll probably no I think it was
pretty simple I I'll get in back into it
yeah we'll all have to get back into it
except for Jetta like she played it most
recently then me and Ena will have to
maybe get back into the
feeling no anyway thank you the quos
artist Guru Guru D
Kon oh Kon wait glad to he that the
short while in my country was enjoyable
ever consider revisiting us for a longer
period our internet is surprisingly fast
bet you can stream
here for a longer period Well I mean not
long as in a month or so but yeah I'm
definitely uh thinking of coming back um
and combining
it combining having a proper
vacation next time too um probably like
not until next year though
late next year probably is what it looks
like
currently but still very much up in the
air I'll be back though probably
probably yeah na C the D sh for the
pinky welcome back Tel I definitely
didn't miss you too much and bch listen
to your album every day all weekend long
nope not me certainly maybe a little
binging thank you there's never a little
binging you got a go all in I'm sure you
did though thank
you yeah that is a good way to spend
your time when the Wawa is not streaming
perfect t d space waterful d thanks to
the red super chat Kitt glory to KI hi K
today's my birthday are you here today
T it has been a rough day at work could
you please give me some compliments and
words of encouragement then I can use
this Uno reverse card thanks for
creating kfp and inviting all of us
chickens kfp Forever Wait are you
[Music]
here happy belated
birthday happy birthday to you happy
birthday to you happy birthday dear do
tag happy birthday to
[Music]
[Applause]
yo yay
congratulations so happy to hear from
you again too I'm sad you're not here
right now but that's okay you'll
probably catch up with the archive right
right
right but then this means since you're
not here right now you cannot use the
Uno unao reverse card on me you know but
rough dat probably by now you're already
you know over it cuz it's been a couple
days so maybe you don't even need those
words of
encouragement see this is how it is you
got to get over those hurdles and then
at the end of the hurdle there's a
bucket of gold coins and a little guy in
green nice now take those gold coins and
throw them at me in the form of super
chats just kidding
no but it's always worth getting over
those rough patches so G do your best
sucer
attack although it's really not cool
that you had a rough day at work on your
birthday they should have been nicer to
you [\h__\h]
them happy
birthdayy
Channel no big UPS to chagy for helping
me with my YouTube shorts
again did you
see hey
Bo let's
go hey Booty boy let's
go I finally did
it
yay I really like um how the motion
turned out it looks really satisfying to
me I watched it uh several times because
the bouncing
of the Motion makes me so happy that it
looks so
good and I changed to the swimsuit yeah
the the the the skirt swimsuit ver which
is really cute too I think I'll use it
more often because um I think I like it
a bit more than the shorts right
now yeah I'm glad you guys liked it too
it's a pretty simple dance but I put a
lot of energy into it I could do the
rest of the dance too but uh it doesn't
all fit into 60 seconds so I just kept
it
short but yeah um that was one of the
things I recorded
[Music]
yesterday there's another dance which
was the actual one that I was hinting at
like a the secret one is a different one
which is just secret because not not
because it's anything special it's just
because I didn't talk about it yet and
I'm just going to keep it a surprise um
but yeah there's another one I took and
that's coming sometime in the next week
maybe but yeah I I have a little bit of
or actually quite the insanely sore f
right
now not because of the running machine
but because of me dancing yesterday not
because of the boogie boogie bang bang
either because I mean okay I just
yesterday uh after I got up and had
breakfast I immediately put on my motion
capture
stuff
and I uh started actually I wanted to
take it already on Sunday I was just
practicing on Sunday and then ended up
not recording it because chagy said ah
it's okay I won't be able to like work
on it right away anyway so I was like
okay then I'll sleep first cuz I'm tired
um then I got up I had my breakfast and
then I started recording it and I um
after a few troubles with like
calibrating weirdly I was able to record
it somewhat
well at least so I thought then I sent
it to chy but when I reviewed the D
within my own software there were like
parts that looked really like rumbly
glitchy to me and I thought eh why
why and then chagy showed me how it
looks on my model but I was already kind
of set that I had to re-record it but on
the model it actually looked mostly fine
but I was like whatever I'm going to
re-record it anyway because I'm going to
I forgot that I wanted to do the boogie
boogie Bang Bang song as well the pokka
dance so I thought might as well re
reccord the first dance that I did on
that day and then also record the boogie
boogie bang so I got into everything
again getting more and more faster in my
process and then I recorded the song
again and then I recorded the Bo boang
and then I took it off again sent my
data happily and was like all right this
will be the last time I had it on for
today turned off every tracker this time
because like in previous times I would
just like take all the straps and The
Trackers off and just leave it be but uh
this time I always turned every single
tracker off which takes a while because
you have to push each button like six
seconds long for every tracker and
there's like 20 or
so um
but this way I saved the batteries and
didn't have to charge in between and
having to charge every single tracker is
also
annoying but yeah then I realized oh
wait I also wanted to motion capture the
chicken so after a while a few hours
later I put on the suit not it's not a
suit but you know I put it on again to
capture the
chicken uh chagy maybe would have been
able to do some
generic
motion from an MMD or something I don't
know put it onto the chicken but I
thought it would be nicer since the
chicken does have the ability to be
motion captured by me that I might as
well do it
so I did some simple
movements that should work with that
little
body I became you yeah I put it on for a
third time
yeah I became the
chicken and I was thinking of maybe
releasing um cuz I can put the same
motion onto any body right so I talked
to chy and I said we should put the
motion on me and release it as a like a
I don't know behind the
scenes so you can see how the that dance
looks like on me as
[Music]
well o music
bgm yeah uh but not right away I think
he'll be working on something else first
also he said he'll be he'll be he said
he's kind of feeling sick right now so
maybe
I don't
know let's hope he um doesn't get too
[Music]
sick what would it look like if you
recorded with shutting down the trackers
one by one for a short uh I don't think
that works I
think um I can take them all off without
turning them off but once I turn one
tracker off the whole system kind of
shuts down I think from what I
remember yeah but I don't know uh it's
just it just looks like the usual like
you take off one thing and then it all
like becomes like
[Music]
zombie that was the case with the hand
trackers h ah
uh
ah what did I stop like all over like uh
in that
stream I think I did
[Music]
right yeah once my hand tracker died
everything died I think in the Euro TR
Sim ulator
Stream So n okay let me finish reading
these no no I'm reading super chats no h
ah Nathan caught on asking for one
tangent in his pink Super Chat let's
just say this one counted right this one
definitely counted thank you for the
Pinky
na h
a h h
ah let's go this is what I
wanted
[Music]
okay he already watched two season two
seasons on his own I only asked for you
to watch one season he liked it so much
he watched
two wow okay guys you guys really have
to uh admit
that like
you you guys like I mentioned a lot of
shows and you guys are like like her
shitty taste in shows and blah blah blah
but someone like hokan who is usually a
very critical person I would say gives a
show that I give him a
try and likes it a lot and it's like
kind of a girly show too but still I I
don't know if I I I think it's not like
a girl show but still like girlier than
I don't know know some Superman movie or
so yeah it is great so you guys need
to like doubt me less with
my
recommendations
yeah okay let's see I can see why you
recommended it to me Mitch is gold on
scene yeah and her interactions are
funny especially with suie yeah suie is
just so [\h__\h] funny I [\h__\h] love SU
she's like such a great character holy
[\h__\h] ah so likable to and other
comedians except lemon I thought that
Joel will be there once but it was nice
to see him still here and having almost
a good relation with Mitch yeah yeah
yeah yeah like he even when uh you know
they're not together they're you know
you know yeah yeah they're good treasure
hunting was a bit fun so far what what's
treasure wait uh treasure hunting h so
far I like the second season more finale
of first felt a bit messy for me I don't
even remember it anymore for me it has
all melted together into one big
show uh Arc at the resort was really
nice ah the one where like she's in the
swimsuit and like they they crown her I
think they crowned her as like uh Mrs
shrim suit or something like that uh and
they finally left me wanting more what
surprised me in season 2 during
weissman's and Mel's dinner that Zelda
and mate speak Polish ah
wow you actually understood them oh yeah
cuz I don't think they subtitled it one
thing that doesn't leave my mind though
so can you answer me yes or no does
Mitch get her suitcase back the one Joel
took in the first episode oh God I have
no memory of that I don't know I don't
think
so I don't remember a suitcase
ever no I did not see the trailer for
House of the dragon or rings of power I
think today the rings of power one came
out I didn't watch
either I kind of wanted to
stay
um
just
unknowingly
innocent or I was thinking maybe I
should watch it on
stream wait I saw the house ah really oh
yeah so I did want you to G with
you okay yeah that was kind of my plan I
guess I did do
it so yeah I don't know hokan are you
planning on continuing to watch the rest
oh yeah ring ring of power no ring ring
of power what what what the [\h__\h] what
are we talking about stop confusing
me stop confusing me House of the Dragon
oh yeah I mean h i mean rings of power
came out today the trailer for the show
to continue in
August you want to watch more let's
go oh I think you really have
to like you really see her journey
throughout the whole
show the Journey of her career and it's
really interesting the end
also is you know it's it was sad for the
show to be over because it was just such
a good show but I think the end was uh
pretty good too so please please watch
more I'm so happy you liked it you guys
should watch it too if you haven't
watched it yet The Marvelous Mrs masel
very good
show rice of reden oh happy belated
birthday and you're saving money for to
me
f at least you're like kind of on the
same continent so the flight shouldn't
be too crazy
expensive yeah but the accommodation
might be expensive ensive so yeah I hope
you can do it h and have fun happy
birthday to Y
yay uh fre holes loves beans numbers dun
whatever that means
CH space
water big
brain with a red Super Chat what the
[\h__\h] how about this many pennies for
some thoughts
Nathan thoughts you want some more
Thoughts From Me Red Super Chat I kind
of have to give you some
thoughts uh I can tell you my
embarrassing inent
[Music]
maybe paint will help me with
this after sleeping a night over it
I felt
like I still feel like in the moment
this was so embarrassing I wanted to uh
hide in a hole and I kind of did but
when I will tell you this now it will
probably not get the feeling of
embarrassment the cross as
well as if you would experience it
yourself but
okay it's a story that comes from my
garden let
me okay it's really simple I could
probably draw this with
two two
scenes um
this is a wall this is a a
knob this is the part where the water
comes
out and I had
[Music]
a a hose attached to it you can maybe
see where this is going oh friend it's a
friend yes it's a friend but only if I
make this part like red though then it's
a friend oh
[Music]
friend
so I I don't know why I did this because
I I know that I kind of
knew logically that this would
[Music]
happen but I I I I wanted to uh water
some plants so I but I wanted to do with
not with the hose but with my watering
can so
I I kneel next to
it I
[Music]
take I take the stuffing
[Laughter]
I
I I should know that this would happen
because I I I I I knew it already I
experienced it before but without having
an accident like this but I take it off
which means just like pulling it
downwards and
immediately a big stream of water SPL
bashing against me I startle I get up I
stand there and it's it's like the thing
is like moving like a snake and it's
like still directly at me really strong
and like also all over me like my pants
my shirt my face everything was wet and
it went on for like it felt like uh 20
seconds but it was probably like 5
seconds but I I I I I moved a little bit
to the side and that amount of time but
it followed me and then I moved a little
bit to the other side like just like in
tiny motions and because I was I think
in shock or so I went step back so like
but still it was like whoosh no but also
in one moment I would like take try to
like kind of lean forward to take the
hose but then obviously it was like
still spraying right at me so it was not
possible it was just all over me making
my whole body wet and and then it
stopped and I was I was
like I was like what what just happened
and I was went all over and I I I I I I
pray I pray and I I looked around me
anxiously
carefully if someone saw I I think no
one saw but I'm not sure I I hope no one
saw that was so embarrassing that was so
dumb I was so soaked for
real it's it's really
embarrassing it really is don't say it's
not embarrassing it was so
embarrassing it was like full power of
water yeah that's it that's it that's
why I told you when I'm going to tell
you this now you're not going to be able
to really feel like the embarrassment
that I felt it should happen to you I
hope this happens to
[Music]
you so
embarrassing
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] but I think the pants I was wearing
were tie pants is like the only thing I
wear right now uh
I have like three or four different tie
pants right now and the pattern on it
and
everything uh it it didn't make it look
like it was wet it was soaked completely
but it didn't look like it was soaked at
all it's just my
face was
so I was so drenched it was just such a
strong stream of water I was so so and I
I felt so dumped because as I said I
kind of
knew about this that even when I have
the water turned off there's still
remaining water
inside of the hose but I didn't think
that it would come out that
way in such a strong
manner in such full power yeah with that
much pressure I didn't I I just thought
it would maybe like slowly go like you
know like like just have the holes fall
down on the ground and we just like
slowly make a little puddle there but it
goes like and literally send the H
flying
too oh you'll protect me thank
you I don't know why it's under pressure
unless you have a trigger nozzle yeah
there is a trigger nozzle at the end m
yeah yeah so maybe that explains it to
you so would it not happen if there
wasn't a triggera I guess
[Music]
so it really got me it was so funny
though I had to laugh at myself and also
I was so embarrassed at
myself I went back inside and I stood
there and shock contemplating what just
happened okay here we go hope that made
you happy Nathan G are
Ed water the
g
h Dr loyal
[Music]
a
t Lord T simply t
[Music]
uh I think I'm ending it here sorry I
didn't get really far I finished that
one at least but I need to go to idle
meeting and I need to
cook and then tomorrow we'll play Studio
Valley a little bit on my members only
because as far as I could tell there is
permissions for it to play it as Members
Only my mom and is just going to be
really salty about
[Music]
it
but I
know now mommy don't be embarrassed
about it if you're watching right
now don't be embarrassed it's okay it's
okay I it's okay I don't know how you
did
it
but seems like my mom is watching my
memb streams through my
account I I've have seen the evidence
mommy like a while ago a while ago quite
a while ago I was
like somehow making a remark that haha
you can't watch my member streams and
she was like oh I have my ways like just
like sneakily saying that in such a
sneaky way but not saying how or so
which is very suspicious like you could
just say no no I have a member's uh uh
subscription on my account or so on her
account but she would she didn't say it
like that so she was obviously like
hiding something and I was like H what
does she mean with that and then weeks
many weeks later I notice I check my
YouTube history quite
often um and I saw in my YouTube history
like three of my members streams in a
row and first I was
like did like the JMA maybe check my
archives for some reason or so but then
I realized wait a
second wait a
second maybe that was my mommy that it
makes sense with what she said a while
ago and that's how she's catching up
with you know my members streams like
every once in a while she'll she thinks
I won't see it I think sometimes she
also deletes the the history but then
this one time she didn't and I think it
happens it happen several times now that
I saw my own member streams in the
history of my YouTube account and I'm
like I did not watch my own member
streams it's not
[Music]
me but I didn't say anything to her
until this point
I don't know if she's listening right
now I kind of felt like I'll I'll have
you I'll let you have this little secret
I'll let you be sneaky I'll let you
consider to uh continue to think that I
don't
[Laughter]
know yeah it's
[Music]
okay
yeah she'll probably find out about this
even if she's not watching now
okay I will go now uh so yeah see you
tomorrow my mom will eventually be able
to watch it too I'm
sure the start Valley Stream
[Music]
tomorrow yeah thank you guys for
watching um
I don't know if I'll continue this game
on stream next week don't get your hopes
up it was fun though you guys should
play it it's pretty cheap really really
cheap just 999 Yen which is like a buck
or less on Steam so go get it support
Ollie I'm sure she would really really
really really appreciate it try to get
through her somehow I don't know man it
seems impossible to me
[Music]
if you can tame this kusogaki
princess then you can tame anybody
man is listed at 7 year oh really then I
guess it's really cheap in in Yen oh no
never mind I I miscalculated 999 Yen
yeah okay yeah yeah sorry sorry sorry I
added I in my brain I removed one
number still please support her please
do do please do in German we say Al
V
bye-bye byebye have a nice
[Music]
evening perfectly timed with the bgm