[Music]
e
e e
[Music]
for
taada
hello
everyone wait let me just put some
background
music uh now that I want to say hi one
second
no hello everyone I just woke up
[Music]
oh my
gosh good
morning I I just woke
up I literally just woke up yeah I went
to sleep around too late too late too
too late too late too late I'm
s deprived de deprived how how you even
speak English anymore can you speak
English if you sleep the
[Music]
priv
because why why am I sleep deprived you
may ask because yesterday at 3:00 a.m. I
decided to thow
I'm like why am I even doing
this why am I even doing this at 300 a.
am but you know when you feel inspired
you feel inspired it is what it
is
ah what can I
[Music]
do I am my brain cells are low today
tell me how you doing
today how you doing
Chi are you doing
good we're chilling I'm fine about you
I'm I'm
good I'm good I'm actually happy playing
Monster
Hunter I want to play Monster Hunter too
hey I want to play Monster Hunter
now I play
down I want to play
now I wish you could play now I wait a
bit
but good thing I have a good news which
is yesterday I delivered like something
I had to
deliver so I'm quite happy today I'm
like probably I'm going to
[Music]
uh I don't want to tell you what it is
I want to tell you what it
is no I'm not going
to no
spoiler it's top
secret okay let me join now seven days
to
die theis never die
they
[Music]
Immortal my day is restored and
happiness rep happiness replenish thank
you Mama you don't type mama with One
MK
hey have have a quick question what are
your favor flowers just try keep on M
not my favorite flower that's a
difficult question I don't know never
asked the satino flower is my
favorite
[Music]
flower I don't
know
uh I
like I don't know can I tell you later
I need to think about
it Cho flowers are my
[Music]
flowers
yeah going to tell you
later I'm too e for this
oh I can make
coffee I want coffee dang one more I'm
making I'm making coffee and I'm making
some tea
okay you have to be this rude every time
yeah one coffee I think so I think so
huh I didn't say e tea every time but do
you like
tea I mean somebody has two and forged a
head up here you got to use
those oh by the way I got a treasure
map Doo bad it says to whoever finds
this note friend the end is near the
moners are breaking down my door but in
my final moment I can think of how I
want to be remembered not as a coward
but as someone who thinks of others I
leave you this map to one of my many
secret Berry chest to you God bless you
Jennifer Jennifer let's go get her
thanks Jennifer I think I think if we go
to a party together you'll see the the
treasure map maybe nice nice can you
make me a fire spear as well or like a
fire club or something uh uh I found a
mod for that so you need to find a mod
okay but um what it called incendiary
mod or something like no it was
something else but I I would I would
like to tell you but I just lost all my
stuff I see the treasure oh you did you
lost all your stuff maybe you died good
no like yesterday when I loged out I was
on this car and I had all my items and
now I I am no I have nothing what are
you out are you the one are you sure you
logged
out what are you sure you logged out out
yeah cuz it's day 15 we're trying to
figure out who is
AFK who is running the game with
somewhat they had to have
died is he the chosen one
she was she chos cuz that might have
mean that you died you were AFK and then
your stuff
despawned
oh
you all right maybe
oh oh oh no oh well we can help you get
your stuff back there's there's plenty
of stuff in the house that you can take
there so sorry
guys
hello hello no it's fine don't worry
hello hello yeah if anything this is
good because now we know you know what
happened yeah now we know what happened
what happened then uh apparently R State
AFK I knew it I knew it I knew
it I was the no I saw I was the second
as I was the last one before Raa to log
out and when I logged out I even said to
my chat oh isn't there someone isn't Raa
still AFK like in the server cuz I saw
her standing on the car I loged out next
to her I was wondering is she she looks
AFK I'm sure she'll remember hours oh my
God something else so did a raid come I
wonder I think it did and it probably
destroyed Rara over and over
again destroyed by the hord multiple
times
no unable to move what then we missed a
raid what does this mean for us that the
next raid will be super strong we're
ready we're going to do it we're going
toy it strong together I think that it
also has to do with our levels and stuff
so since no one leveled up I think so
that's how it wasn't the better at least
so
fine f we are so we are so well
fortified but that means today there is
going to be a raid
then right no seven no seven days so 14
7 21 so that was yesterday yeah the next
one was
so we're still on track
right Lally the same it's good just one
week it's it it was calculated guys
calculated um yeah oh God yeah can you
guys give me like some wood if you don't
mind because uh there there's a bunch of
stuff in the house go ahead and feel
free to
take there there's weapons in there too
as well so you can take
weapon I even I even double checked like
I when I ended my stream I was still
worried about l so I checked like if I
could see if she's online on Discord or
on Steam friends and so on on on Discord
it just said that she's like playing
Monster Hunter or so so I was like oh I
guess that's fine but no oops crazy I'm
make you but hey R you collected some
water for us cuz you kept it
on thank you for collecting water for no
I'm not going oh my God you already did
oh my God how much water was there it
only unfortunately it caps at three so
that
wask welcome that was calculated as I
mention
that three people
here
you and then wait hey I made some coffee
and some
tea I can't find wood okay see see
here's your
oh thank you you're welcome it's my God
bless you y can't do it bless you're
welcome drink
funny ra here's your
coffee thank
you
yummy can I get some of that tea oh okay
I'll make another
tea sorry Chef you're working overtime
to I don't want to give you the XP
penalty I thought we don't have an XP
penalty level are you there is a penalty
yeah how do I find out on Tab second
taben
was my beautiful no
hesitation my goodness
beautiful has 23
deaths what 20 what 2 deaths you had so
far but I think deaths
15 wait where do you see your
Dev I think she probably just died once
and then just was in the respawn screen
probably and then yeah because and then
probably back you dying a lot sorry I
understand why people have to die is you
know you restore your health and I have
eight player kills
eight blank you murderer
wow okay thank you I'm not thirsty or
hungry anymore it's
so let's start preparing for the third
raid yeah okay yeah I'm I'm still trying
to to to find my well it not it will not
happen today but yeah we can take it
relatively easy I guess Bo can you cook
me uh some corn or something yeah do you
have
any yeah I do I'm cooking up some
cornbread oh nice I'm coming home
popping off I'm coming
home yeah the cooks are going to guys
the W the toilet the the some of the
boxes here respawned so like the toilet
was empty right oh because because it's
it's it's the ra cuz it
stop it re
everything yay I yeah so I have some
more water if you want oh oh because she
was
online well some positive
effects here I was standing where you
went who were standing I'm I'm behind
you oh stairs here oh thank you
nice so far if you grill the corn does
it give you more Health back or
more what you call it more hunger back I
think so yeah I'm pretty sure it's more
efficient as a food to eat it
grilled yeah maybe we should for food
too I know I'm but we have like we have
60 steaks at home from the Big Green
boar oh wait did do we did we cook them
all not yet but but you know I think we
might have cooked them all really I
think so I mean the steak conversion
ratio is so bad five raw steaks to make
one grilled steak wait that make wait a
minute I wonder the green four
respawns we can kill food farming place
I
think uh I would hope that he wouldn't
respond cuz he's already in my
nightmares true that guy sucks yeah it
was too strong and too big I'm trying
satisfying kill though yeah give
[Music]
thees
wonderful
yeah oh yeah if anyone wants to come
with me to grab the treasure chest
treasure hunting I want Oh you mean the
loot no I have a treasure map oh I see
oh it is hold on a sec what wait I see a
drop is is it the yellow thing bi booo
no oh there's a drop though you get the
drop first before it goes away oh okay
and then we can get the buried treasure
wait where did the treasure go
the my I don't know I only ever saw the
drop on the screen I saw the treasure
chest oh it might be the drop
maybe must be it okay well let's let's
go over and grab it
yeah never yell ready I'm going to head
that way am home oh if anybody wants to
come let's partty them up yeah yeah can
you invite
me yeah well I'll invite you me too I
want to do the treasure chest thingy it
sounds
fun oh yeah I see the icon the treasure
icon on the map okay I think only you
can see that then bio so you're going to
have to lead the way to that but let's
get let's get the W the airw
W uh if you guys have a stone
axe um and get some wood for me because
by hands it takes too long oh I have a
spare axe if you want it oh thank you
I'll take
it
Z zp zip
sorry just quietly sipping from the
River with my straw hat not even tea
just river
water hey as long as it's flooding FL
Flo how do you say that flowing flowing
as long as it's flowing it's healthy oh
I made I made the
ax you made one yeah I made one why are
some of the zombies super
hot because because some people are
super hot yeah turn into hot zombies
zombie reflects the
streamer wait can we go into the snow
area don't we freeze to death or
something oh we have clothes it should
be okay I love snowy area yeah ah it's
too bright my eyes
flashbang why would they why would they
put the drop here they don't even care I
you the one who uses light
mowing yeah hello yeah
does what are you guys planning on
doing hello my God
the be careful are we just balling yeah
we're balling right now okay yes we're
doing class increasing our skills Loot
and loots we're going to build a little
house
together oh people coming
in um you are the farmer uh you if you
have some time today can you try to
plant our super
corn yeah yeah I would love to plant
some super crops super
corn okay um if you uh the the the super
corn seeds are in the new house next to
the fireplace in the food and Medicine
Chest um there is free uh ears of super
corn don't take those just take the
Super corn seeds there's five of them
and if we need more with more grown ears
of super corn I can produce more seeds
because I have some recipe but for now
it's just five seeds here you can a look
is will the FL be at the new place
nothing cool in here um anywhere is fine
I think I got I got some magazines
though
magazin oh blade crafting I need that
knife gun I I have heard that the second
w has already been finished
[Music]
yeah we survived the second wave
unbelievable are we still going to be
using this house for another wave or are
we doing a different house now well we
might use this house because it's it's
well reinforced right yeah reforest okay
got to continue using what what's good
still M all right make the most of it oh
my gosh there are those lions or Tigers
what are those big cats mountain lions
big cat I am a big cat big cat means big
trouble oh big cat hurts oh that was a
bad idea mhm yeah I'm dangerous you
better be are you guys questing right
now are you doing stuff at a new
location
uh um bble has like a treasure chest and
we want to go there yeah I have a
treasure map that I'm looking
for um where did you guys go I left but
I'm waiting for you somewhere close by
okay well I'm going to go to the other
home so I'll stick in a a different VC
I'll see you guys
later right next
to okay treasure is can you kill me oh
ah big cat I see the big cat guys I
found a like radioactive gigantic green
boar it did respawn it did resp it gives
a lot of meat if you want to oh if you
hunt it you want to kill it help okay we
are going on expedition to the Northeast
cuz that's where the
treas I am
around going this way and
even knows where it is it's it's kind of
a far track into the snow so okay well
we should be fine we're not be
careful how many
k
uh how do you tell well if you mark it
on your map with a quick Waypoint it
should it should tell
you so like if you open your map with M
and then you find where the treasure is
on the map 400
and
meters that's not bad yes okay oh we got
a CL up a mountain
though be like a Skyrim goat should we
get in a different VC do you think oh
they all went to a different VC okay
cool now it's just us explorers
explorers explorers y
yay I hope it's a lot of bunch of a
bunch of good stuff yeah I hope it's
good I am
around Jennifer do us
proud uhoh high
expectations no no we can do it jump
King jump King jump King we are jump
King oh there zombies up here how is he
able to climb on the mountain so EAS hey
if you see if you see a mod for my
spear thank you
well this is difficult
climb oh I'm going to die don't die I
got
you stupid Mountain Man dumb Mountain
Man big dummy guy the mountain
dummy what a stupid guy you tell
him you feel bad he's dead already he's
already dead
Lally do you do you need do you do you
need cash for something in this game I
don't know n money has no meaning any
longer I maybe we can burn
it yeah you can use for a fire oh
there's a there's some Villages and
houses around
here when you stand on a cliff like
that it's difficult to
climb just try try your best keep
jumping don't give up jumping yeah you
can do it just become cat I wonder if
you can you are cat you already are cat
ow my
knee my knee oh there's Bears watch out
be careful
of no
bears do you guys want to check
out how close is the treasure it's 100
it's on the road it's like next to the
road I'm going to go around found this
bear though cuz I'm not yeah I have 7
HP careful about the
bear okay oh this wait I have a shovel
okay we have shovels we're fine if it's
buried treasure it sure is so they say
bued stash
oh be careful oh
okay let's go
I don't see you oh is that you oh
there's a lion a mountain lion oh dang
too okay I wack it I'll ignore never
mind oh no my bun is broke no oh you
still need to dig okay I have a big
circle right here we got to dig for it
all
right
C get to digging
ladies if we all together it'll be
really quick work I
coming must be around here there it's
there's a big circle now
mhm
um so we just you guys are in the circle
so okay I guess I'll go a little bit
further so we have a better yeah Circle
radius you are right on the edge okay
and
it's shouldn't be too bad then it's a
big radius uh-oh usually it shrinks the
further down you go oh
okay there's a guy behind you oh is
there a dude shooting at us no I'm I'm
shooting at him oh you got it Cece's got
this hello I'm
back welcome back welcome back is this a
place big old hole no no E's you
he's don't
don't oh he died onp oh he's not dead
never
mind
man oh no my exp I'm in Deb
[Music]
now well that's bi's backpack it just
looks like he's wearing it cuz he fell
down
[Laughter]
like is this a place
yeah I think so but bi was the one that
had the circle so yes this is this is
the place it's a very big radius though
yes we got to keep looking just as much
as we can they're going to make us work
for that treasure
okay so just do your best all
right have a broken leg I need to here
anyway okay if you look if you stand
where you are
Callie yeah and look where I am this is
how as big is is the circle you're at
the edge of the the circle I'm at the
edge of the circle so it's a it's quite
a big circle let's try di around here
then hopefully it shrinks over
time careful R behind oh it says we're
getting closer to the treasure
nice I don't have
weapon you don't have weapons who's
being freaky stop get off my lawn I made
a weap
nice
whoa
nice yeah where were you where I said we
were
closer um I was like right here
is
okay
oops watch out watch your head I don't
want to blonk
you now we're a great diing team look at
all this work we're getting done yeah
yeah I'm glad you guys came with me this
would have taking forever by myself let
a
hole hole
that yeah I hope it's worth it I have
high expectations I mean it's a treasure
map how could it not be worth it right
yeah has to be amazing what if it's her
like emotional emotional treasure it's
like a
letter a picture of her lover it's a
picture dang it how is this going to
help us
survive it says I'm getting closer to
the treasure again okay okay so let's
dig wherever bio is sorry my God you
gave me a fright there I dig you myy
please don't oh I did you too you're
great okay I think I've repaired my
shovel enough
got to be around here
somewhere
somewh keep looking for a box ladies
yeah uh also let me open the box since I
have the class if possible just tell us
what's in it yeah I I'll let you look
and I I'll share I'll share the loot we
all worked hard for it yeah it was a
group box yeah what's in the box what's
in the box what's in the box it's all I
want to do is just see what's in there I
don't even need the stuff supposed
that's the most dis satisfying part just
opening it right leaving it behind like
when yesterday when we did the you know
when everyone was D fighting The Horde
during there was some downtime and I
went to the backpacks and opened some I
didn't take anything but I
opened I looked at
them wor super yeah but I I didn't need
the things so I didn't take them but
there's I hit over here and it said
getting close so all right all right
let's go near where bio is okay I'm glad
that the game tells you when we get
close oh that's Rock that's oh we need
to hit the rock too or I don't think I
don't think we're supposed to dig the
rock I think it's probably the dirt part
oh
okay same Friendly Fire ended up not
being a very good idea
it's funny yeah it's silly silly funny
time keep digging ladies keep digging my
thingy broke okay oh your
shovel yes it's okay I repaired it I
tapped it I I had to stand talking with
it and it's okay now I what if we do
have to dig
down oh
sorry I don't I don't think so I think
rock is the
the limit B yeah so the limit actually
you can break the rock but you need a
better shovel you need to
upgrade well again the the the whole
perimeter is really really big it's like
really really big
so I think yeah you guys aren't even at
the edge if you dig that L off okay it
is getting pretty late we're going to
have to be careful yeah
yeah wonder where we can maybe we can
find a place to hold up in the
night there was a house
nearby stay in the house yeah pull up in
this
hole maybe we could actually like make a
literal you know like a little to like a
little oh like a little Hideout yeah
yeah yeah because like if they can't
they can't jump so if we have a place
that is in the middle of this but is
surrounded by hole they can't get to us
true we can set up a little camp
together and chill oh it says we're
getting closer
again oh the hole the hole got smaller
okay start digging in this way Direction
okay oh that way okay yeah this
way you got it
Captain this treasure is going to be
great I'm
sure I like shovel it's one of my
favorite things to do in this game yeah
it's nice and easy
it got it got even I think it's like
somewhere over here you guys are on the
very edge of the perimeter now mhm um so
like somewhere around where I am
maybe
oh hope there's some food in
there okay I'm getting we're getting
close again this we're at the center of
the perimeter now so it should be around
here we dug that huge big
hole that's just part of the treasure
digging experience you
know sometimes you got to dig oh yeah
more my character is super hungry though
my character is like yo we've been
digging for so
long give me something to eat silence
treasure is important maybe there
rations in there oh oh never mind I saw
thought I saw something sorry no that
was my so excited I think I was
someone's foot I was like oh oh never
mind that's just a
foot oops
ow
zombies again got smaller
okay I'll take him
out
mm
[Music]
MZ it's night time getting
late one minut
my leg feels
better
good uh I'm going to drink coffee now
yummy coffee
did I BW it okay do you like how I BW it
okay yeah yeah it was okay it was just
okay the apocalypse you have to turn
down the
expectations oh I found it guys it's
here oh you found it I'm not going to
open it you people go okay hold on oh
does anybody have lock tapes oh my god
oh
oh no but you can destroy by hit okay
let's let's just just smack it a bunch
yeah oh ow ow ow someone's hitting me I
let let's let's let's dig let's dig a
little bit more around it so we have
room
to I'll be I'll be the the torch holder
now you can guys can see thank you B up
I dig
[Music]
everyone
yeah all right I want to make the hole
bigger so we can all smack it
yeah so we can all gather around it like
a campfire
yeah that's going to
take someone's hitting me again all
right oh
no no it's really fast look it's
already it's already 1%
wooo stop
this is a zombie Oh I thought it was you
guys
uhoh I'm
breeding kill him bio kill him what I
killed
you messed
up bro can't believe bro I'm so
sorry it is what it is I'm no my
friends oh it's dangerous to do at night
for sure that's okay though it's
okay I'm freezing I'm free got this we
got this we got this we got pke him poke
him poke him okay he dropped we dropped
something W he dropped a lot of
stuff are you sure that wasn't my
backpack no no no no your backpack is in
the
corner what do you drop he dropped
coffee a vehicle Offroad
M schematic ooh oh you can you
[Music]
can oh you can CRA vehicle lights I
guess wait why it says I'm cold now I
was not freezing
before I think it's just because we were
naked for about a moment oh though just
hold a torch or something
all right we'll be opening it up in no
time oh yeah look
[Applause]
yay almost there you know I've noticed
that I don't really have an exp penalty
even though I've died I wonder if they
took it sry if they took it off for our
server wait didn't they say they did
they might have said that and I I did
level up recently even though I died
recently yeah I think that happened
we're playing on Ultra easy
mode nah it's still hard it's still hard
it is still hard why would you hit me I
got I got your you can kill me you can
kill me if you
want I want you to check the
XP if you die it was RA it wasn't me it
was ra ra you murderer I am a
murderer no I don't think so dang it
that would be awesome I think she meant
like um if I get an XP debuff now but I
wasn't even I wasn't level five
[Music]
so what was
there keep it up ladies keep it up this
has been quite aing Tas but I hope it's
great I hope the contents are aome it's
going to be so worth it it's going to so
worth it at least one golden locket with
the lava's
picture mhm mhm I agree
you're wet okay you are wet we wet to me
it looks to to me it looks like
someone's healing it can you heal the
treasure chestal itself magic is the
optical oh
okay no it's magic get it if all us work
together oh we there we there yay
all right I'm going to open it okay oh
man sorry open I just want to take a
look there you go you can it's full of
stuff oh it is full of stuff oo mostly
ammunition all right I want to take the
9 mm
ammo and there's a ball there's steel
pots there bullets bullet casing shotgun
shells silver and gold
nuggets
gunpowder ooh a mod as soon as we can
make bullets that' be great what's the
mod for I'll take I'll take silver and
I'll take gold okay I will share the
treasure feel free to take stuff okay
what goes next okay I'll take the
shotgun I just want the shotgun shells
and then for the steel Club Parts I will
take those just because I'm Club M so
I'll take those um and yeah there's like
a whole bunch of really what is this
there's robotics there's a wooden bow
people like bows there's a bow you can
can I get the
bow there's another I'll take the
robotics
then cuz I kind of wanted to go into
like engineering maybe this bow is going
to be so cool yay yeah make sure you
read The Bowman magazine in the magazine
I am I am leveling up the
bow yeah there is a a Bowman magazine in
the box back at the house you should
read
it yeah good cool oh I have a oh it's
robotics Parts okay I don't have any
space I want to take it yes
I have this for you a mod for your
spear thank
you
oh it's
cool beautiful here is
actually no no no no no what is this no
that's my so we go to this little town
this little area col yeah looks like a
the flag on top and I I am over in
cucumber so I can't take the I am
cucumber too I think we should at least
take the ammunition because I don't have
any guns but for keep modify you will be
able to make bullets
eventually eventually
oh that's a big
cat I want just swap some things nice to
make oh oh that's like a c y or
something but it's dark and do you see
that with the red eyes behind you right
behind you in the tree where I'm
pointing with my arrow when I'm pointing
with my arrow oh oh my God what the I'm
going to shoot it is that oh my God are
you sure got to shoot it yeah let's do
it oh boy that seems like a that's a
werewolf it looks like a werewolf a
werewolf werewolf kill it kill it a
wo it's really strong I don't have
Spears all where is it where is it where
we are oh God no those pce
Arrow oh my
God care that mountain lion is camping
where my backpack is to and a bear bear
is hunting so
strong why is the bear attacking me what
have I done against the bear that's just
rude what is that
creature ow ow
ow uh-oh no uh-oh
no
uh-oh got
this behind me I didn't think I did any
damage H I'm
cold I I crashed I'll be right there oh
okay uh can you make sure my backpack is
still there I hope it didn't respawn
everyone's backpack is yet still there
so it's
[Music]
fine I'm coming okay okay okay okay we
can try kiting him between oh three
shots you three shots but it's going to
be so worth it you can kind of jump out
of its out of its attack if you jump
backwards oh yeah darks it a little bit
Yeah Dark Souls it okay okay I died just
make sure that it doesn't deago and run
away shoot it every once in a
while someone's eating my body I can
hear it mess up going okay that's my
backpack is it yeah it
is have spear
arrows they're friends with the zombies
it seems
like yeah maybe they like wh dog zombies
or something my back right there and a
bear all chilling together in the same
area camping over your backpacks my
backpack I'm going to go for my
backpack try and lead him away get okay
I got I got I got the backpack my
backpack I'm taking care of the
zombie
ah oh my back back my backpack my back
fight this thing we can we can it's just
it's just we just got to we just got to
kite it somehow it's possible it's
possible TR him in the hole maybe light
him on Fire Light him on fire good idea
he does not catch fire he does not catch
fire okay I killed one I killed one nice
I killed feel that do do any
damage I why not why what makes you say
that like is there no blood when you hit
them or
yeah maybe
your oh yeah now it it does okay never
mind okay I just got to drop some stuff
then I I I I I put like 20 bullets into
the wolf maybe he's almost dead I don't
know yeah he must be okay I'm going to
shoot him oh there's two of them oh my
God there's two now and AAR and
Aon well we're not in a good situation
everyone I don't know we got this we got
this we got
this wish I could snipe him your arm is
broken where's my arm broken
no okay maybe we don't got
this maybe we should oh I'll keep going
shoot him shoot
him he's just standing
there oh I killed him I killed him I
killed him you kill him oh my god let's
go nice nice nice oh he gave so much
loot oh oh what did he got I don't know
but I'm going to die
oh
Lord I'm dead again
murder I'm dead
again I think we all are a little dead
inside especially after that it is still
night time so they are super fast
still didn't even have time to run
away oh Yik oh God the bear too now
please P
me not the
bear no I broke my
leg how do you keep breaking your
leg A J you
cursed you
cursed it's messed up man leave her
alone
I'm so
cursed
stop wait wait don't shoot them yet
there's like a bunch of zombies behind
you kill them first oh I
go and somebody my death count has gone
up so
much it's okay it'll be worth it I
wonder what the other guys are thinking
seeing d
probably they probably think we're doing
like a super hard raid or
something I mean it is in a way it is
hard no no no no no a me leave me alone
leave me alone leave me alone leave me
alone oh I have so much
stuff is the loot really worth it
treasure is pretty
good wait don't shoot them there like
two people behind
you terrible
sh okay I'll poke them oh okay my leg is
not broken anymore okay that's good I
guess
nice the the the the werewolf healed me
thank
you see it's just
misunderstood okay my backpack is
surrounded by three dangerous
animals you could like go slowly and
then run grab it run out my look at the
animals I can't shoot the animals down
you can you can't yeah I can okay oh
okay it's the wolf is going to run
toward me I'm just going to b b it
okay run run run run run oh they found a
different Target oh they found a
different
person it's me it's
me
help ow sorry you got in the way of the
the my gun I was trying to shoot okay we
got one we got one
we Stu I just wanted I just picked up a
flower and I
so yes Kitty yes okay I'm going to go
for the bear now the bear probably gives
a ton of good
meat
yummy okay bear is Dead bear is dead oh
ni okay one more one
more yeah for the
wolf it's okay he'll go towards his
aggressor yes a bajillion Stakes forever
everyone D level up level
10 okay it's only it's only the wolf
left if I can shoot the wolf Dad will be
good okay okay right I got a shotgun
it's terrible shotgun we can maybe make
it
work dang
it yeah yeah eat my body yeah yeah eat
my body no
geted are wolves no no no no that's you
that's
you
no
no should be almost it I put like 20
bullets in that guy
ow we got this confuse him come on yeah
yeah yeah confuse
him okay ow my
[Music]
body
oh be make sure to don't get me the my
backpack because we died in
the
killable yes I killed one I killed one
before zombie just killed the freaking
wolf what
what kill
stealer I want to see what it
is I want to see the loot I'll take
those and the what are the zombies
behind you wait oh
God she sorry I just took I took shotgun
shells that's it I took shotgun shells
and a club magazine oh I'm taking the 9
mm
um and I'll take the juice cuz I might
get
thirsty I think I'm going
to
[Laughter]
die oh wait actually I can make myself a
what anyone I guess I guess this one's
about to be
broken well that was interesting H KY
I'm going to drop some ammo for you
thanks I'll take oh sorry I took
someone's primitive outfit
[Music]
here where if I didn't repair something
in time is it broken forever no you just
need a repair kit uh here oops sorry I
will here I dropped a repair kit for you
thank
you nice cuz it was my rer can't I can't
pick up my bicycle unless it the storage
is
fcy
oh okay like laying on the side yay
should we go to this area now yeah yeah
let's do it okay let's go okay you guys
go ahead I'll be there in just a
sec I think this one shouldn't be too
hard oh never mind no no no no no no no
oh no no no no no no
no
why oh it's pretty it's pretty
strong
SC they shoot
me I I I I don't want to do that oh this
one I I have a perk where if I step on M
they don't go off ooh
that's pretty
cool
idiot oh by the way can you invite me to
the party I I guess I got off when I
locked off I got you thank youcome to
the party welcome to the club this do
seem pretty strong yeah maybe we
shouldn't go
here
guys guys are you sure
no I don't know if it's a good idea it
might not be a good
idea box me regret we can mark
it oh hello
oh is there a dude up there oh there is
a
dude I want to go up yeah go up up
there
ow why it doesn't have a shoe
[Laughter]
drop some cool loot or something
lame I just got to Bonk him in the head
uh there is a giant bear by the way oh
oh hold hold on this one is Giant on
let's shoot him and then climb up onto
this yeah good idea no good idea not
good idea climb up climb up he can't
climb he's stuck he's stuck he's stuck
he's stuck wait
uh wait he's stuck he's stuck he's stuck
what is it booty
hole he's big oh no no no no no he's not
stuck anymore oh he's dead I killed him
nice good
job yay that was way easier than I
thought it was going to
be oh yucky I see something weird in
green but I don't know someone is
spitting at us
oh it's the big pole oh he's throwing up
e
e e dude yuck
no oh it's the uh oh
guys oh he had mag guys there's a bunch
turn around there's a bunch
of they broke the door a really one
what is the on my screen was like a
giant world
no not like
this
e place it would
seem why did you go there we can take
eating
me I got the I got the penalty by the
way you got the penalty yeahp penalty
yeah
really oh no actually no never mind I
didn't oh my leg is spray that dude
won't die that's
crazy the ones with the orange eyes just
don't
die well the loots probably really good
good I hope
so guess we'll find out I went into that
one building and there seems to be a
cave underneath a cave yeah the building
with the open
door where I'm standing right
now let's go another police guy be
careful oh
ew not not me not me not me not
[Applause]
me
okay he can
climb I
can't I'm so bad at this all right ooh I
got
XP help this is like the strongest enemy
on the plan at following me if they have
or I got you I got you thank you okay
that was rough I think I need
help okay where are you so here but my
backpack is on the top of this Tower and
there's a zombie do they keep uh spawn
spawning up there there's no way there
was that many up there no she just I
want to I want to I'm just going to
snipe him okay thank you he was
following her and then
okay oh thank you more for
sacrificing I got some good hit
in oh
God guys he exploded the the stairs are
not there anymore now okay you can build
new stairs I think how stairs oh this is
more guys I think we're a little bit
under underleveled for this so yeah
maybe yeah maybe we should leave maybe
we should keep stuff let's get get R her
stuff
first
uhoh I died oh my poor my poor beard is
mad I need to find a way to get my stuff
back these dudes are crazy strong
actually
I'm freezing
death we got some good loot from the
zombies were that were that we killed
though that is
true uh I'm sure that we can take on
like two and three skull places though
yeah yeah let's just
try let's try building her like a
building building blocks no yeah so that
you can go up yeah should be fine unless
someone can make St of letters I don't
let's see I can make some building
blocks up get
my it's a lot of enemies it's a lot of
enemies okay no problem building block
oh
you don't hit me please I always stabbed
you let me
see more coming oh wait we can make
wooden lettuce as well ow ow ow did you
just break them to me
messed up
okay oh my God so far
it oh they are they're so big all they
on my body we're doing we're doing it
we're doing it okay I died in front of
there maybe someone can kite them and
then someone builds the the stairs uh
the stairs or ladder like I have a
ladder maybe that's
easier uh
so ra since you don't have your stuff
try to kite them away from where your
stuff is so that we can build a ladder I
am the bite I'm the bite come here guys
hello yeah yeah come here I'm there but
I don't there's too much stuff in it
hold
up wait I can I can go
up I
think I think yeah come on
[Laughter]
okay good one sec I'll TR you don't die
never mind oh my God okay that should do
it I finished the stairs thank
you you got
this
yay thank you now let's get out of
here okay
now Mak like a banana and get out out of
here run run run run run run run
okay okay let's go back
home time to
leave it was very
bad ding ding ding
ding hey where worth
it worth it worth it worth it worth it
worth it oh God no he's
it worth it worth it fast you think so
let's not give it
up should we go back home do you guys
want to go to the trait or do a quest
sure let's go to the
tra he is still following
me um I think if we follow this path
it'll lead home back down go
okay yeah zombie eat the chicken the
chicken looks really delicious eat him
are we going to the new home or the old
home
home h i wonder to recuperate maybe the
new one okay know we go hit the Traer
and do some Quest till we all get B yeah
don't
know don't know oh new house oh that's
really oh it's right next to the Traer
okay okay makes sense yeah I think
everywhere is pretty far at this point
cuz we're up in the mountains the
mountains dangerous we're we're at like
the higher level area
mhm yeah but hey now we know yeah who
would have known that five and a half or
four and a half schools is too hard for
us a little maximum silliness
moment my back stuck in the worst
possible place you have to find out your
limits sometimes to test your limits
mhm I'm on top of the
mountain you're Queen of the world I'm
Queen of the world I got all the way on
the top that's pretty cool I'm following
people think yeah I'm just I'm just
going the road path because my bike
probably can't climb the
mountain okay I'm going back
down
I'm may take a while at least I'm
exploring the area too by doing this so
unlock new map
oh it is a big
map it is yeah you know R you had a
quest activated uh to clear a house oh
oh is it this clear the area head to
Rally Point thing okay yeah it's like 1
km away we should we should all go to
Trader and grab Quest so we can just
okay hang them out we can we can do
Quest today and we can do everybody's
Quest at one we can level up big time
sounds good to
me I'm still wondering how we get number
one the workbench number two make
Amo workbench I think
is make
the forged
magazine no I think it's called
something else does didn't kiata have
like a bunch of them she said oh she
must have found them I hope she keeps
working towards that CU we behind in
terms of workbench yeah let me double
check uh she said
workstations yeah it's called
workstations magazine and she has them I
think maybe maybe today we get some
Magazine from the from
this
request hopefully yeah well also what
I'm realizing is that a lot of the
houses around here especially are like a
lot of schools like we thought three
schools was scary some of these homes in
the snow are like five skulls yeah yeah
I think snow area is probably later on
we can come we can come back but no for
now for now let's just stick to the area
we're in and try and Conquer that
area yeah we got the treasure here
though that was nice there's there's so
many cars in this snowy Village that we
can loot though but I'm
leaving I don't have any any space so
cucumber
space there a lot of
zies what zomes in the zombie
game messed up how can it be why there's
a chicken in the middle of nowhere I'm
going to kill
it why why did the chicken cross the
Wall oh here we go cuz it wanted you get
to the other side
he's not a chicken wait I I I haven't
thought of a joke yet what oh an air
drop I'm close to it okay so we got to a
new
home oh okay I why did the
chicken cross
the some why is
it cuz it's wanted to go go on the other
side no because it is trying to get to
the stupid person's house knock
knock huh knock knock who's there the
chicken chicken you
[Applause]
stupid pretty funny wow that is really
mean can't believe do that people would
you not nice Shame Shame what do you
mean shame it's a good joke it's funny
I'm going to go to I'm at the house
because I followed the road I'm going to
go to Shi and ask if she wants to join
us if not it's okay too okay I'll be
right back oh I'm at the old house oh
no I followed the wrong
wood well never mind because doing that
means I can just go grab my
stff are you okay
yeah I'm okay close to R's
Quest but we can go to the
trader let's meet at the trader we meet
at the trader okay Traer okay I'm going
to drop by and drop stuff at the old
house cuz I'm cucumber okay me
too so sad that I lost my spear with
fire yesterday yeah we'll find it again
it was very
good
Noble going to grab
everything I
can so I can move to the new house
a lot of supply drops are happening I
wonder if I wonder if they're like
backed up or something from ra being
AFK oh yeah yeah yeah was all
planned of course that's why we're
getting all these air drops
now so I should call them supply drops
that's what they are supply
drops why have a so many Stone
Spears and these I can got the
arals
iron 100 wooden cubes that's kind of
nice
iper pleas die okay I'm going to oh
yummy I'm going to get some
food probably a good idea does anybody
have wood to Fu the fireplace so I can
purify some
water I do have wood but I'm very far
away I'm at the trader okay
that's I wonder what the others are up
to right now maybe they're doing their
own thing can I can I request some meat
uh I put in the
Box yes but I need I need I go grab the
wood fire wood I go grab the wood okay I
am the
Woodman
Woodman The
Lumberjack get in
food that's my life
now oh yeah find something to make your
life's work in this game that's the best
way I'm not a very good killer so far
though right
now don't worry it's difficult
anyway
yeah okay people I got the food for you
and I'll drop here
thank
you okay I
[Music]
will
cook here for now take the take these
corn breads for food
[Music]
M I don't know why you
bleeding okay
okay n
n oh I want to make a bunch of of bacon
and eggs oh it sounds good oh breakfast
you yeah yeah you can have some I want
some of that could use a
breakfast but I'm at the
Traer I'll bring it to you I'll bring
you breakfast breakfast delivery yeah I
brought a guest a guest hello I brought
a guest hello can you invite to the
party hello yes I would like to your XP
if you will have me yes of course we'll
have you no problem well thank you don't
tell the other party why I left
them oh are they not getp right now huh
oh no uh I was going to try mooching off
of them but they were too far away to
mooch off of so it was not helpful
a I see yeah you can mooch exp off of us
anytime oh well thank you I appreciate
that ow ow ow sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry I couldn't see sorry I was I
was
Fus sorry excuse me thank you we're a
bit of a silly
Bunch all right I am here to benit okay
we're ready okay we're going to tra
we're going to do class pretty soon
we're just at the at the house at the
old house store and stuff and making
food okay I will head to the trader in
the meantime okay
wait wait we we all going to go to the
Traer in a second I think you want to go
together if you want to go on the way
okay okay I have I put more farming
magazines into the old house chest by
the way sure oh thank
you please Harvest Moon for us I beg of
you yes Harvest Moon yeah I think at
this point I've died more often from ra
killing me than
from can I you haven't died from my SP
but La has six player kills she is the
second most player killer besides me
messed up you guys are messed
up okay I'll put this duct tape
here I guess they got close to the door
unless that's you guys D near
it oh
maybe okay would they attack it randomly
if there's no humans there though I
wonder I don't know so I think they
would have gotten further ifun but maybe
maybe they did
okay buy some lockpicks there's
something called a gatherer surface
cooling increases the rate of De
collection have okay I'm ready the
breakfast will take a while to cook so
like while we party while we quested out
breakfast will'll be ready when we get
back yay all right
okay oh I need a
new head I'm going to check on the farm
near here okay they have not grown from
what I have uh last
Saw
why cuz it takes seven days to
grow it takes seven days to die it takes
seven days to
grow a
I don't know but it feels like it it's
technically been like two
weeks okay I got B do you have the meat
for by any chance um I I'm using the
meat to cook bacon and eggs but it will
take
like it'll take
about 10 minutes cuz okay no problem it
takes a lot of wait wait the farm plot
has to be like loaded in to actually
grow so if it's too far away from us
this doesn't grow Oh that's oh really I
don't
know it's kind of lame okay unless
unless to harvest it I can IFK for seven
days no it's grown yay yay okay okay so
tired of we actually have to
harvest I'm so
done so done with what with the spikes
in the entrance I'm breaking them
why she keeps dying well we we need them
when the raid starts no just you just
have to go straight just here they one
just no I cannot go straight I'm
sorry she she would fail like the drunk
test yeah yeah you know the glasses test
I'm I had
enough she's done with it I I'm going to
go all right well we got some oh
actually okay I okay there is this one
area that I really want to go to and
it's east of where we are right now we
can go to it I Mark I marked it lots of
stuff and it's just like it had like a
like a store with a bunch of magazines I
already took a bunch of them but is this
big like area
with shry I have an outfit for you a
farmer outfit it's in the farmer weon
ammo chest in our
okay I I will go equip uh your new
fashion thing we got it just for
you thank you
bye how kind I'm coming to this if you
look at the square uh you know this farm
that looks like a flag and then the road
keeps going and then there's a little
like an h and then at the body of the h
it's like a big area H well I don't know
how big your map in that area if you've
been there so uh can I mark
it uh maybe we should go to the trader
first since Callie's waiting for I there
oh okay I didn't know that yeah point I
got to now are we going to the Traer
right yeah okay I'm okay okay okay can't
wait to eat my raw
egg yeah yummy yummy I love Ro egg now
oh you do yeah I ra egg over rice yes I
love raw egg over rice but I have I have
to like uh filter the whites out cuz I
don't like egg white oh it's too it's
too goopy yeah what I like to do is I
just break the I break the yolk and I
keep the egg
whites you you break the yolk and you
keep yeah wait wa don't you fry your egg
when you go put it on Rice oh I think
they mean raw yeah you just raw raw egg
off I feel like that's um that's what I
comment in Japan isn't it it's not
really it's not it's not really I don't
know if it's safe to do in the US it's
not it's definitely not I don't think
it's safe to
do it's safe in some countries but most
most countries it's not so yeah America
hates us though they want us to choke on
her own
eggs but I tried it I tried it in Japan
like egg over rice like with eg it's so
good
tast
yeah I want to go to Japan eat all
the I want to go back too actually I I
went to a Denny's in America and then I
remembered the Denny's and Japan and
it's
like I think I don't remember if it was
was it Denny's do you know that one
place where I got hamburger like onion
soup french onion soup with hamburger
and chees cup that
was Danny's in P that was really good it
was not like it wasn't it wasn't french
onion soup but it was really good I
really liked it I never been to the one
in America but everyone keep telling me
that the the one in Japan is
better well it's totally different
because Denny's in Japan is like a
breakfast Place primarily and Denny's in
in Japan is like a family
restaurant it's it's a quick stop for
truckers I always stop there to grab the
rice with the burger and the demig glass
demig glass oh the the hamburger Hamburg
steak thingy oh it's so good you guys
are making me hungry to be fair it is my
fault sori and I would just go to those
family restaurants all the time like
Denny's and joh we were just like let's
go get food and ice
cream oh yeah the perfect they make
there is crazy good too they make
amazing
parfit the other day I was like okay you
know this was I've been having a lot of
fun I want but I want I want to um
what's it called uh treat myself and I
was like okay theoretically what if I
you know for because has thank you ra ra
does have like uh um space because um I
I and since we're in different we stream
different times right I was thinking if
I visit her I can just steal her PC and
I was like okay what if I go just just
to S and
food yes please thinking
it I'll be there in a few months and
then you can have you can buy something
have your food too yeah make of you guys
who want
pasta me pasta
y make P for everyone actually I I make
amazing meatballs my meatballs are C
because my grandma taught me how to make
them do you do you use breadcrumbs in
your meatballs yeah
a we should all do a food party yes a
food party I love that
yeah I'll probably head back there at
some point next year we should do we
should do a food a food party but themed
so like for example you can only bring
like a dish that is the first letter of
your name so I would bring a b dish
that's cute yeah I'll bring is is my
second name okay yeah yeah
whatever dang it Pizza Pizza I'm here
I'm here I'm almost in I'm here
too pink yeah I do look like pink Keanu
um ask a question real quick bi boo um
do you I saw in you have the you're in
the room with the big bed right on the
second
floor no that's me oh that's you you
have two forged to head magazines are
you going to use those cuz Kar is really
close to yeah no I told her I told her
that she can take them but I don't know
if she heard okay cool maybe she maybe
she took them already um but she okay
I'm here maybe I'll tell her oh wait
you're at the Questa tell her I'll be
right back no I'm at the I'm at the
trader I'm gonna accept the quest and
then we can all do our Quest
together the same I just took whatever
is the closest Quest it's okay we can
take double of the prizes with one Quest
by wait are all quests like shared
automatically yes okay okay just you
know don't die is the
thing cuz if you die and you've done a
bunch of quests lose all those quests
okay yeah we have to same
Quest yeah that's okay that's fine
that's good oh I got I got a special
job huh oh yeah cuz you got your bike
you already did we are expanding trade
route to the southeast tell the folks at
Trader genen oh we can get Trader Jen oh
oh I hope she's
nicer yeah there's a cute girl she
that's the cute girl by the way Mor
you're a little quiet for me I already
have you at two
hold on just a sec let me give better
now do I like talk what do we do I talk
any Quest or yeah take any Quest and we
will we will I'll share it which one
should we go to first um oh hey do you
guys do you guys see if you zoom out of
the map opening trade routes B Boo at
the South I I see a fetch quest for you
um it's fet it's southeast of the trade
it should say opening trade routes B do
you guys see that I will I will just
follow you South where southeast of the
map if you zoom like out as far as you
can if I zoom
as I I will follow you uh if you if you
if you don't see it that's okay we can
do other people's Quest first and then
I'll grab that tree I see I see like
tier two fetch bi boo yeah okay that's
the one I see and then that's probably
just a my special Quest then so we can a
bunch of quests we got to do more quests
yeah um I want to meet the cute
girl oh special class is not shared okay
I see oh okay that's why we got to
that's why we got to go do these quests
okay let's do let's do you guys' quest
first dang look atana Reeves and her her
pink hair
H I'm coming people can you try
something can you take out your breath
icle uh hi you
Conant so sorry I miss I miss a
piece um okay I'm standing on it now try
which dang it it doesn't
work apparently you can get a seat for
your bicycle though that you can carry
to people oh that's so cute that
be oh yeah I want a motorcycle that's
what I want ooh car and then I want to
drive into the
which are we going to are we going to
the highlighted one in Orange I don't
know I was going to go to your uh your
fetch one cuz it's the closest
one oh yeah Clos I don't see that tier
two fetch B Bo okay I'll go to that tier
two fetch B it's next to the new home
no yeah it's pretty close by we're all
kind of close to it hi hello am I going
the wrong hold on a second you're going
the right way you're going
right yeah cuz I too am near you oh nice
okay you and your
bicycle moving compared to me and my on
her
bicycle you you w get bik you just got
to do a few more class you know oh how
many want to do 10 oh I don't think I've
even come close to that I
I in general so all the which one is in
home that one okay I am at the
residence just come to B Boo's icon I am
at the exclamation point okay heading
there oh there's a swing it's really big
I see it
too
nice wish we could just take these cards
uh by the way later can we can we go to
the house because I don't know where it
is is this this one okay yeah yeah don't
forget to leave like a a checkpoint
there so you can go back
anytime okay are we all here yep I I'm
near your fetch Quest oh wait I'm up the
wrong one I'm it's a different different
F Quest it's a yellow yeah oops okay
thank
you let me just pass the Washington it's
very close ow ow sorry it might have
been my
make my is tired kie every time you say
clap you have you afterwards you have to
go okay I am now at the McMillan the
club the
club we at the
club oh nothing good okay ready to
go I got to start let's do it all right
I can't wait to
move someone hit me
I don't want to hit
anyone so I will just stay put oh
they're good job see we're good many
hands make quick
work what if we what if we bait all the
wait wait wait wait guys guys guys guys
guys we bait all the zombies and then
put them in here and then we turn on the
vial and then they burn to the crisp
sounds like good
idea okay I'm going to wait here at the
vial oh oh never mind you can't turn it
on again you can't turn it on again
never
mind lady oh they were doing something
they were doing something strange in
there
Yay good job good
job got I got you I'll be the lighter I
will light the way
you light the fire you are the light you
desire we aspire
spreading out like wild wild
fire never ever have I
ever
[Music]
a right
there is it such a cute K what it's
lagging a cute
house like this spear time without the
there's some cornmeal in there I don't
know how oh I'm also low in
stamina oh can you climb this rope to
get up here
a you can
[Music]
oh the fire Jee wait hey let
me hey I hear I hear
something it's the
baddies oh you did it I can't do
it get
there wo okay my spear takes at least 10
hits you'll have time to
help any loot oh I want this cat picture
I want it can we get it no can't tell if
it's
lagging yeah I can't climb the
Rope got
it never mind how the heck did you guys
get up
there what why your things still on fire
wait you just climbed the Rope no it's
not working ow
ow what the entr oh sorry I thought you
were a
zombie I have a name on me
inar going to bleed
out
cool um
goodbye see
you oh no you
died to death I have punctuation I'm so
sorry a
knife D that what do you got there I
think we can go down here oh you can
come down but I am surrounded by Yes
actually come down I will not go down
then oh finally I will shoot from
afar
uh-oh well he's wearing a
helmet like fish in a barrel come on no
no good job no
yay
y nice
job I'm I'm back welcome back good good
good job
team I found steroids cat
picture you going to take it can I have
the cat picture oh cute cat I wish I
could get the cat picture yeah I want
the cat picture so bad but but you can't
did it just get destroyed you can't keep
it I no you just destroyed a there was
also dog
picture
o broken all right we can destroy things
to harvest the materials at
least okay I finished the class how
about you I
have you have to you have to check like
the distance the distance away from you
you have to check the
distance I found
it everybody has their own their
own got a f ah I found the White River
but I didn't pick it up oh my God what
how do you know the quest um if you if
you're done it said
it'll oh my God I don't see anything oh
maybe because I
died I don't have the quest anymore
oh I think that might have been the
case so I need to find something it's
called a sack
okay here Stacey I'll give you a present
as a sorry I killed you no it's not
maybe I just did something
wrong uh 3.3 2.2 it's probably upstairs
it's a mod that reduces uh durability
loss I'm go in the kitchen and try to
climb up cool thank you
yeah I think it might be up
here W you guys could not
climb hey I
found
[Applause]
yeah oh good job good job oh my oh yep I
found it it's up here behind
the got it all right we're good who else
needs what I'm still looking for mine I
am unfortunately a little blind is it up
here maybe it's behind this thing this
is where mine I don't know but I think I
think it's below here or near me right
now cuz I'm 7 up here in the Attic oh 7
it's got to be below you unless oh okay
oh it might be in the Attic like I'm in
the attic but I don't see anything it's
a it's like a brown
bag yeah Brown Bag okay it is below me
okay let me look uh underneath
then not the corer Satchel oh it is a
corer satchel I found a cooking grill
but there's something in here
can you get it somebody else is oh that
then that's somebody else's cor your
Satchel maybe down here the second
floor wait is that mine
no good gosh I will never find I a
little bit confused about how to like do
the quest so what it says on the top on
the top right what it says the winning
residence I think if you died then it
probably like stopped already oh yeah
you failed the quest if you died I think
yeah oh okay okay okay no problem wait
for me we still have plenty of quests to
do yeah it's fine it's fine no worries
just might want to make sure that I'm
not accidentally like not doing the
stuff
properly cuz I'm a little
slow no problem and it looks like a
satchel right yeah it looks like a satch
it's not going to be
okay look like
AEL let me know if you guys find a
satchel in the basement perhaps I I know
what is this satel I mean I don't know
if it's the same for us for you it's um
it's going to be her own Satchel oh own
sat it spawns it spawns satchels for all
of us I
believe okay then wow I am not really
good at ice
spy do your
best all I know is at least like near
the attic or below the attic that's the
only issue yeah beyond that I don't know
okay how about how about what I do is
I'll go to the attic and I'll destroy my
way down okay yeah that works okay okay
that's going to be my thing now re force
it go for it
yeah it's a great idea oh oh there's a
compass bar too
okay most dissatisfying thing is when
you find a secret item kind of oh why
did you oh sorry sorry sorry sorry
that's a mine where is it to be and then
it's like empty or it has very little in
it yeah it's my favorite I don't see oh
I see a satchel on the attic oh it's
hiding it was hiding behind that's where
mine was over here
oh oh you're so smart thank you my my
beibs yeah wait but that's what mine was
hold up oh it's empty actually never
mind it's not mine however it was very
cute of you to have almost found it you
don't think it's going to be at the like
the freaking roof right wait there's a
locked door right here wait can I see
here sat it's not it's not up here is it
we can we can see each other's satchels
yes I'll check the
roof it's in the ground floor it tells
me if it's up or
down it's at the first floor okay I'm
going just going to destroy my way
down I don't need to go on the roof but
you know what maybe I has to be at the
garage
okay yum
there was a satcha at the garage I
think okay it has to be it has to be
like here come on okay I see it I see it
right below okay to something I haven't
got it
though got it don't don't don't say yeah
yeah wait is a freaking vent is that how
I couldn't find it oh my freaking
God messed up it was in a vent okay I'm
done nice okay shall we go North to do
the one up north yeah
yeah just be careful night time me and
my yeah it should be an easy one just a
let's go should we wait until it's
morning because the zombies are a little
bit more strong no we're overpower this
is only
two yeah guns I'm going to stay
behind okay
but
eggs this one
right oven that's still burning how I
think it's the one over here
actually yeah it's the one it's the one
over
there wait wait uh my my quest already
activated here for some reason oh maybe
you have two different ones no no no no
no Maybe not maybe
not never mind well she di I think I
think we do this one twice because
there's Callie's Quest and Ra's Quest
easy
okay
okay okay now I see it it says like
clear areas and stay within yeah I hear
them the
area okay oh they're behind they're
behind behind the door oh no behind us
us good job still alive the zombies are
for helping us open the door thank you
zombies appreciate that oh just kidding
they're not here I'll keep the door un
locked so we don't get
cornered good
idea that's a lot of and we should
probably close any
doors I think I want to I'm getting
shreded uh does anybody have food
because I'm dying I have some steak I
have eight eggs you can have some eggs
stay down you dead okay thank you no
that's not it I hear them ah there's a
there's a basement there's a basement
you got to be
careful there's a large lad watch out
for the large
lad hello large
lad I found a
key I'm going to say behind I am
bleeding
B you're bleeding you
bandage uh it's okay I have one I'm
using it oh my God the eye F the the
light flickering it's so much uh try not
to Spooky down here guys do you have the
key here Shi here you have it too
there's a key here do you see it as well
or is it uh a key I just have clear
areas I don't see a key know right like
hanging key or behind you oh hanging key
I found if you come if you come to the
basement I found like a little secret
passes okay well if anyone finds
something that's locked like a door or
something that says requires que let me
know because I found a ke okay I need to
eat all my eggs I am dying your eggs
sure eat them I I am I have eaten all
eggs I otherwise the quest is not going
to be
[Music]
complet wait where we going now
I oh we can climb up there's an attic oh
okay the
garage I got a farming book for you
sorry oh thank you I live up my days and
sem my pece what doesn't me
me I'm like near death so I'm just going
to
chill uh who is using arrows were you
using arrows me me too okay I have a
book for you for that too where did they
go did you guys go from the basement we
going for the basement we found some
loot but no enemies so you don't have to
your enemies and I do not want to die
okay wait where are you I'll save you
I'm going back to the garage oh no I'm
not dead
yet it's just that you you stabbed me
pretty hard my girl oh I'm so sorry I
have bandages it's okay it's okay no I
already fixed it I I was going to die
from blood uh blood loss though I
finished we finished now we got to do it
twice okay we got to do it again do it
again y
YY out of curiosity if you die before
turning in a quest do they reset like
what happens yeah you don't get that
Quest so let's try we have to be careful
not to die at all not to 149 so just to
die okay everybody repair yourselves if
you need you need a bandage maybe I can
make you you can make that yourself take
this thank you here's a bandage
this will that heal me I killers and a
blood bag for me wait not that one I
drink the blood for okay oh oh here okay
thank you she's almost dead wait that's
vehicle Adventures why am I why do I
have vehicle Adventures wait that was
supposed to be Southern farming where'
the farming go yeah no you you want me
to ride a bike or something I'll get the
blood
bag where where the thing go I think I
can make a I dropped it back
maybe oh I can craft a first I can't
craft
yet I will oh I didn't know I
painer nice oh if you have one vehicle
Adventure I'll give you the second one
people because then we can stack it
because I'm almost over
INB does anybody has a first eight
Band-Aid oh I do no I can't craft it yet
either or food maybe Al food will help
here you go I dropped it oh thank you
shouldn't you dehydrated I'm going to
die oh people use it yourself yeah yeah
yeah yeah oh I have a first AK I'll be
fine oh okay okay
dehydrated that's fine oh
no what that
sound that
was waiting you know let's just you know
hit up a house or something I level
up I'm going to go get some one
we can't eat the
snow eat cat
food yum yum yum yum yum yum is this
yummy cat food
yeah this way
is I can't see my cursor that is the
river behind that house oh yeah I'm back
W my bow now makes 20% more damage you
you
naked yeah I was going to make one of my
I'm having an armor issue but problem is
uh I don't have any cloth to make new
armor so it is what I have I
haveth you have cloth yeah take
it thank you I need as much cloth as I
can get thank you all right let me drop
you some here you
go
cloth can someone come to the river with
me I'm
thirsty okay I come I come with you uh I
have no I don't have juice they nearby
water I mean I have murky water but I'll
I'll like lose five Health if I drink
murky water right now let go let's go I
come with you let's go I think it's this
thing yeah just behind the
house is it
here yeah it's down
here okay I am dying of dehydration holy
crap I am so glad that there is a river
nearby how do you sip from the river
uh stand next to M you have to have
empty hands with empty hands yeah
oh but you might get diarrhea that's
okay I'll take it over
death I am now not too bad I
guess oh also yeah I need a little
water let's see I found a cookie po but
how do you make painkillers they're
really
good I don't know so oh someone needs to
like take medicine or the
magazine I am still good to go actually
I have not been uh hurt by the water yet
that's crazy to me I
know I need to heal I'm so thirsty how
much do I need to drink you need a sip
sip G GP how do I heal um oh I'm I'm
taking
damage I am taking damage you should
should be able to just equip the bandage
and then left click it no I did it but
I'm still like
40 uh-oh no don't leave me I hear
zombies and I don't want to
die that's wor maybe you took damage
from drinking or something oh yeah I'm
pretty sure I did oh they're
chasing okay we can do the the mission
again you guys yeah okay wait in like 10
minutes we're almost ready oh they
dropped something yeah hey there's
another oh that's you
okay I need
food uh I have one egg you can have if
you yeah food will be nice here here
here I have one egg feed me lady
sandwiches I'm sure if we do the quest
they might like respawn the boxes and
maybe we can find some food in there
yeah okay okay I have
blueberri here you go have one egg fresh
from wait oh oh no the sandwiches made
me
sick oh uhoh okay we for the quest I'm
okay you're just going to have to fight
with Dent Terry sorry didn't oh no I'm
hungry now oh no Dar it it's okay it's
okay I'm going to break in didn't mean
to do that all right I'm going to stay
behind so I don't die yeah just stay
behind we we'll tank it for you hello
I don't want to hit
anyone think I can do much this
time I'm staying behind actually
especially as an Archer yeah yeah no
worries you guys stay behind we'll take
care of it tank thank you I want lose my
quests oh oh oh wait hey there's people
here I thought there were
zombies look look it's a whole gang yeah
there's Chi faun
and then thank
you what's
up what's up oh I think they they have
to wait for us to finish the quest for
they to start uhoh oh boy up here
there's a
zombie I need food in the trash it's
really strong help I need food in the TR
I found wood oh thank God for shared
XP you guys are doing great thank you no
I'm going to die I'm up in the attic I
don't want to get
hit no I think we
good don't
die okay we good we good okay I'll just
light up the wait for you guys thank you
no props I think there's one more zombie
down here maybe in the basement oh we're
in the basement right now I hear it I
hear him yeah oh there he is ow
there you go okay we're done good
job you really shank oh nice art this is
nice she stabs real hard I'm
sh Nice N uh should we go to the trader
and deliver those quests yeah yeah I
don't want to die with this many Quest
any
further yeah let's not RK we got a bunch
of quests to turn in
okay oh wait I have a quest oh I got
some food and whoever was hungry oh I'm
also I am hungry as well uh also we done
should we should we let tell them that
we're done with the quest if they wanted
to do this
yeah we're done with the you tell
okay
yeah did someone have
pistol oh yes I use pistol I found I
don't know if this is pistol I found
a magnum
enforcer oh I am going to use Magnums
whenever I find one
that okay I can use that I'm going to
here it is I'll put it on the floor get
back thank
you okay so we heading to the traitor
yes yep okay I'll just follow short of
you okay we I am blind to the map preach
your head it's okay I'm hungry and dying
oh actually do you have your food
uh I only have the food that damaged so
I don't think oh okay I'm notam is not
good for you the diar sandwich diar you
like a great job making it though you
yourik I found it on the floor it's okay
I see maybe that's the issue probably
the 5 second rule doesn't work in this
game have
infected oh wait wait wait wait stay
still stay still be I found a shotgun
weekly
kie oh it's I honk your horn instead
hold on to that for me I'd be
happy oh we can have like a little bike
gang yeah biker gang yeah that will be
fun I want that bike too I hope they're
going to give it to me there was a bike
at the base I think it's one of yours
though oh it's it's just mine I see I
see messed up I don't think anybody else
has a bike yet unless they did the class
I think
uh it K should be able to make one
because she has a lot of vehicles
thingies I she has like 10 or something
but she needs I think she needs the four
the work shop thing I have four vehicles
on me I can give to her as well nice
nice maybe we can feed them to her and
then she can make us
bicycles yeah what cars or
motorcycles oh this is this is the new
house we can store stuff in here I'm
going to going to store stuff in here
okay okay oh yeah I should uh put the
farm plots here then oh what is what is
the new house let me check on the M oh
yeah I think I did Mark
here how do you name
crates um hold uh hold e in front of it
okay I
here old e
uh let's see oops I have any seeds oh I
got an
outfit all right the farming outfit I
didn't end up seeing it short oh wait
that's the I need to get the outfit
actually oh pink uh shotgun weekly Kelly
Kelly where are you I should probably
keep one p okay okay I'll just I'll just
keep it for now then
yeah okay yeah where was the outfit
again I forgot fa left
it not
sure
uh I got to a new house to deposit stuff
because I don't have any is theas this
one right in the inventory ammos and
weapons uh this
one yo when does he open open up he's
like oh yeah I guess oh he's open nice
all right put shotgun we oh I'll just
I'm stupid okay never mind way stay 17
so in 4 days we're going to have another
we yeah
yeah actually need to find my spot I'm
going to leave this here for now and
I'll only equip it when I'm harvesting I
think um Sur for farming do you need
like rotten FL or something I think so
yeah yeah you can leave in the food and
medicine box it's food and
Medicine yeah you're one yes I have a
silly question how do you name your box
a and then one of the yeah yeah yeah
nice I got a B
bicycle
yay biker
ging nice nice nice speci
J okay I'm coming to the Traer now me
too oh I should take some
food oh finally I can
the much
better much
better to make a where did the farming
outfit go I just put it back in
here I did not take it
hey oh never mind I have it okay oh I'm
going to leave it behind so it doesn't
get
damage this place is cozy and then I'll
get a Repair Kit
[Music]
Repair have a room just for
me so it armor
part wow we're hungry
people so we're hungry for zombie murder
and knowledge honestly if you think
about it like how badly we want
knowledge to read I just want to read I
just want to know the world I just want
to
learn okay okay okay I'm heading to
Trader now me too I'm going
Traer oh yeah I need the coins I keep
forgetting about thein there you go
tokens wait is it is this a different
Traer Callie isn't this this guy I have
to talk to you guys oh
yeah he just going the new one after you
talk to
[Music]
him crafting skill magazine I love my
money oh
no not your money okay okay I gave back
my trick I did it I finally did a quest
good
job that's my first one okay I I say I'm
want to go sleep now
[Applause]
guys maybe I should go back home
actually first uh so I don't spawn
outside next time did
I could be a good idea byebye
[Applause]
bye wish they sold water in here dang it
you can drink it from the river but you
know at the cost of Health
I'm good pass on
that dang not into the the camping huh
nah not really my
style I still don't know how you collect
water like you just lose the
jar yeah I just going to take it and
then if anybody needs to buy anything
I'll buy it for them uh I don't need
anything at the moment I don't know what
want things for sale even to an idiot
like you okay what should I get for I
had tactical m what is a lock pick I
don't think I need
it you can purchase purchase drinks from
vending machines
[Music]
oh
no magazine capacity [\h__\h] goodbye
goodbye [\h__\h]
[Music]
by psycho I got a bike
yay and now you can also take the
special Mission everybody with a bike
can take the special Mission great oh
yeah I guess crafting I've got work to
do if word of advice next time I'm so
happy before coming to a job
interview and then if you get this
special Mission we can go do it together
oh even though we got it it's
technically separate but we do it
together uh do you guys need a refle
sorry refle world as a magazine rifle
world I think Kara needs those uh rifle
okay what about armor
up yeah everybody needs those I think in
general oh the armor yeah I'm going to
use those actually oh pip
bombs o
those could be very helpful during the
I'm taking the pipe
boms nice wait how do you get this
special oh special job okay opening
trade I got some [\h__\h] work it's a deal
got me and you'll find yourself on the
wrong end of a rope nice
sir people do you want a home cooking
quickly oh yes please okay I'll drop you
here
thank you h s I'm going to drop farming
go and harvest tools here go uh thank
you I guess I should do tools
digest o i can get coffee
coffee I'm going to put those in that
chest I don't think I need did you take
a tier 2 clearing Quest B I did okay
maybe I can take to focus on clubs again
I think CeCe did right I'll leave it for
her
then I'm taking I'm doing I want to try
this cycle oh okay I'll give it to you
here you go big Bonk thank you take your
club and go
clubing time to go
clubbing
yeah love you pisy kids and your clubing
I should take my class actually I
forgot oo oh my God that's so cool
who's doing Spears any of you guys or
sharp sticks I am Spear and arrow
usually okay here this is for for you
RAR sharp stick I'm
jobless oh is that for me you I'm coming
now doing sharp sticks I think oh yeah
yeah I've lost my big
cat I am outside trying the bike
okay take your time oh I have a quest
here actually actually see yours beibs
so I'm going to go home and then uh go
meet one of you I got a rogue Hood wow
how you get out of the
bike oh just press e and then if you
want to put it back in your inventory
hold e and then hover over it and click
take thank you so much
oh can make a workstation
yay okay I'm here
awesome oh right over here this is your
sharp stick magazine oh thank you so
much yipp you're going to make the
sharpest stick oh yeah sh did you get a
bicycle nope a man I guess we get a
bicycle doing a lot it's okay it's okay
I be
farming I'm a stationary
woman
okay d strong
together all right let me see if I can
Harvest her stuff growing growing nope
not
yet okay would you guys like to go meet
the new Trader together oh yeah yeah we
can do you know what it
is yep how do you know
well you took the special job didn't you
oh opening trade route right yeah is in
here
okay okay then oh my character is so
cool look at how cool my character is
yeah I love it I love your hairstyle
then you look good so good so good
everyone want did you fall in a hole
Yeah you can go okay I'm just putting
some stuff away before uh going Back To
[Music]
Yonder
guys need
help how' that happen where's
the was
that where's the new Traer uh if you it
if you leave your house of the it's just
keep going South Road on that road and
you should be able to meet up with us
okay I mean I'll just follow you anyway
okay I'll see you guys there
[Applause]
[Laughter]
okay I got out no I don't need help okay
my I'm following you okay follow me
we're
biking oh thirsty what a lovely bike
what a lovely Trail a biking trail even
yeah what a lovely dewy morning bike
biking time
yeah I love the bike I'm so
happy oh this is terrific oh no this
this doesn't look very good this looks
like not very pretty told to not go into
I like oh is it a burn area yeah it's a
burnt area
ooh those are well I don't know how it
is
actually really scary everything's kind
of you know charred
likeing the a Vibes a aw Vibes maybe I
like
it yeah for
sure I wonder if we can Rush all the
quests by this next Trader and then get
to another Trader I
wonder okay I'll be a new area I hope
they have better stuff me
too I bet she will and I bet she's nicer
oh I don't know
about you think she might be mean I
think she's mean I don't see why not
maybe that's even better oh oh that's
what you're into oh you like the mean
ladies say yeah you like Mean Girls oh
she likes Mean Girls I see oh just like
the movie huh no that's not true I I
just like you know maybe when I don't
know you see like there special the
crisp residence get it cuz is crispy
their house I get
it now they're all going to go fast
feet where's everybody else going it's
ominous here I'm behind you this bike
mountains
yeah this is why you go around the
mountain around okay we can do that
that's doable oh oh no no no no okay
scary The Sounds here it's like a little
windy road a windy Mountain Road what
we're for this spooky mon don't you
think I
I okay yeah follow the windy road I
think biking I used to use my bike all
the time oh yeah you a biker I love I
used to love biking now I don't bike
anymore a I like biking but but but my
my parents would wake me up in the
morning at like 700 a.m. be like oh yeah
we're going to go out to the park and go
biking and I'd be
like and then but it was nice biking is
fun but not at 7 in the
morning yeah that's totally something
that Mama myy would do too we're going
walk on the trail it's like 500 a.m. oh
my gosh my dad is the kind of guy who
goes on my dad doesn't use the bike is
like the
the uh like the electric
one oh the scooter or something yeah a
scooter guy and he goes around uh oh
okay man my parents just woke me up for
church oh my gosh speaking a
church there's a church down there you
like church is chicken are you okay I
saw
that where my
oh there's a big city here or something
or a
factory J Clinic oh it's a clinic
there's a lady there's a lady I hope
she's not hope I haven't lost my back my
my my my bike oh no your bike is still
there it's by your uh it's by your
backpack uh I'm in the factory
actually
oo wow she lives in a
church
wowor when you talk to her you just look
straight at her stuff and her stuff does
she have good stuff like good wees um no
well yes she has some good stuff yeah
see she's nice I told you she'd be nice
that's good oh did I go through here
she's got blueberry pie I need to go
down ah
no stim packs but but brother addictus
loves stim
packs thanks
lady oh she's got tier my bik is
back how do you oh I can repair
my start a quest oh that's she is that's
a really nice place actually yeah have
you been here before dance cleaning
no she's nice it just looks nice yeah it
is like a turo cream we can finally make
medic K us out
ni it would be nice if she lets us stand
like the other
[Music]
tra woman
congratulations now
yeah that's my lady oh she's got Goods I
want your goods yeah she's got a lot
okay um
goodies we can clear zombies I'll do
that she'll never forget me oh she wants
to kiss me
oh hey no
fair did she tell you
that yeah she said just you should I
should I get the first aid kit or the
magazines I think magazines is more
useful yeah we'll just have to tank
dying and technically you don't really
lose that much when you die cuz you
still level as you can always quit a job
if you feel not really of
consequence yeah I noticed that
safe supplies right
here well I'm probably okay
here oh
money make a ton of bandages
now how do you make
bandages a you you to unlock medicine
don't you I was hoping we could hang out
a while yeah but I have a decent amount
of
medicine
nice think of what to put my stuff in
four first aid bandages
penetrator oh oh she sells um you can
you can loot the houses around her
compound here by the way yeah let's do
it well wait for
me I can make wooden Club quality 6 now
yay wait baseball bat quality 1 I can
make baseball bats
cool R do you use
bows I use no I use mainly Spear and bow
oh okay well I have a bow a bow uh
magazine oh yeah I will take that here
you go drop that thank you you're
welcome what wait let me check what do
you need let me just check oh I found an
engine wonder what that does we can use
it to make motorcycle or
somethings
okay is anybody here doing the
wiring
magazines not me not me you can use it
if you want looks like a lot of our
quests are near each other except for
Mor's at least one of your let's go to
the want to near each other first then
maybe yeah
okay there's zombies around here yeah
the zombies are trying to get
in the door is literally
open do you guys have any leather by
chance I no there's some at the house
okay at the house
then I need to wait four minutes because
my my bone is she is the nicest lady put
stuff in
cooking can you believe that I thought
you was going to be mean she's oh I'm
feeling Rowdy I I got a I drank
beer feel Ry oh I'm said I'm feeling
Rowdy where didd you get the bruskies I
don't know I just F oh my vision is so
blurry oh
no uhoh Grandpa's also so right now what
a what an idol I should we head now
while it's still d time by the way I'd
say so yeah done did anybody have a
drink the beer did not quench my like I
thought I am
thirsty supp to bring money to her there
is a there is a vending machine inside
and they sell water and other drinks Oh
yay okay hit that vending machine
ladies there's red te I too am thirsty
who has
money I have money what do you want I
just want water or any oh sugar butts
they don't really have a lot of that
they have like coffee and beer and like
but uh anything that gives food I guess
is fine anything that gives food you say
yeah wait was I supposed to bring those
tokens that look like Arc yeah yeah yeah
those
are those are those are
money some Dr all right I I could
appreciate some oh really into coffee
but I'll accept it
tea I'll take tea drink
it let's see um I got yuck oh finally oh
it cures disent
juice Yuka juice yeah something like
that o thank
you Yuka
Yuka yum yum my moment I hope satisf
very
quickly yeah I'll wait until it
satisfies me okay let's uh head out I
guess you ready to head out mm yeah I'm
need to wait 2 minutes because my leg is
broke broken but in two minutes I'll got
fixed oh
okay she's
great yeah
H how do you dye your
stuff I have a crash that's a good
question oh
I I finally unlock m
come have a look you got to make she's
smart because she grills stuff
in my bike is pink
no
oh vulture oh good job
yeah all right I'm ready where are we
going hold on Row's leg is broken let's
wait that's right okay
sorry fine fine we're just killing
things they look like from a legend of Z
actually oh these burn dudes
yeah yikes that's rough buddy okay let's
see the next Quest we want to do uh we
can do the Mori tier 2 fetch which is
very close it's only 288 me away yeah
let's do this one hold on I'm cucumber I
I think I can slowly
come yeah we're going to need to go up
The Path again I think
we might
need the fet clear
Mory I don't know if we can Skyrim horse
it up this this wait actually can
there's a path uh uh BS did uh there's a
call going on if you wanted to attend
first a
call uh for the Encore thing with the
dog oh yes um yeah here how about we
stay in here really quick uh we can try
doing a two call if you want to do two
birds and one stone yeah let's let's
go yeah we we'll be we'll be right back
after get kicked out here huh we're
going to meet you at the quest spot but
uh we got to do something really quickly
so we're just going to leave the voice
chat but we're going to head to the
quest spot yeah we'll be right back
after these messages okie dokie okie
doie I'll meet you guys at the spot yeah
wait what
uh
okay you and me Rob you and me let's go
are you are you are you going
by with the bike or I jumped up the
mountain maybe it's actually
I'm the jump King though it's no problem
oh yeah you are the jump
King you know what oh yeah I'll do it
myself I'll do as
well now I healed so I can actually
come yeah
yeah just try Jo me join me so excited
to make my baseball bat and put spikes
in it oh I want to see it it's going to
be great baseball bat baseball bat
is it like the club um in
Advan yeah I think it's so I got up to
six level six quality for clubs but I
feel like baseball bats like the next
thing you
know I think I think I
hope surely it is I like to uh to attack
with a range because I'm not super good
at the you know avoiding attacks so
usually range is good I like range yeah
we need a sharp shooter who can shoot
from far
away I'm here yay with the workbench I
can also make better arrows I think heck
yeah well thankfully I think Kiara's
going to make a workbench for us so be
nice he was really grinding on that
that' be very nice oh I see it
okay yep I'm just hanging around
outside I climbed the
mon looks like another church oh oh no
no no no no no
oh I fell oh no you fell or did you
break something yeah oh
no dang it it's okay it'll heal no that
takes 2 hours I need a splint
splint well you know the trader has
splints yeah but I think I need to go
back oh man I wonder if we can craft a
splint let me see it takes a uh like
glue and materials that usually you
don't find easy ah yeah I don't have
duct tape or wood it's okay I can go fix
my leg now oh dang it
oh dang it I go back to the um I think
that they'll still take a little bit so
feel
free yeah wait
here take your time thank you okay I see
the traiter from here
so yeah no
problem oh
no I'm going to make a stronger Club in
the
meantime that sounds like a good idea
yeah yeah wait a minute wooden
Club don't need
that parkour yeah I believe oh it's day
wait what why is suddenly super
bright and to BU the
plint I thought that cat always land on
the
feet that's not what I thought I thought
that cat a wastelands on the
feet
oh finally
not hold on I'm coming I haven't seen
you for a while I thought maybe
something bad had happened oh my God she
said she said I I haven't seen you in a
while thought that something bad
happened so
cute I hope you feeling better she's so
sweet that is pretty
adorable here
nice I'm going to buy extra splint just
in case someone will need it you know
I'm sure I have something yeah just in
case oh she already's here as
well I'll let them know I hope you come
back and see me
sometime okay I'm coming back now it
would take like a few
minutes okay
then we'll get
started that can still Jump
Around yeah is it just your arm you
broke or maybe your leg it's my leg no
not the leg that's the worst I
know pi use the bik to go
faster that's
cool yeah we're doing a lot of good
progress
though and the base worked very well
too I was
surprised def I'm just glad that we got
to the next Trader cuz I I felt like we
were at the first one for such a long
time we got to smoo through these
Traders
oh
yeah I I didn't I never played this game
so I didn't even know that there were
multiple
Traders
and yep there are a bunch of different
ones yo she's definitely the best one
though I'm never going to go to trade
and wreck ever again but it's pretty
far I know right we should move over
here actually that could be a good idea
like make a new basement
here I think
so okay I'm
here yay the gang's all here at last all
right I'll go ahead and start up the
quest
then okay if everybody's
here wait oh biu and Sh they're right
here though what do you mean it says
you're out of
range maybe they have to come closer
there we go we're good let's run
it uhoh there's a
dude oh that was a sh wrong
weapon he's dead
nice ooh is this a
mzo we can go
underground oops
search
casket we need to clean the area and
retrive supplies
okay
mhm there must be supplies we can go
underground oh what's this just bones in
there oh well we can go underground here
there's a
mum okay
oo how do you go to
the underground
uhoh I hear zom
bones that's from no I'll be light them
on fire really quick so we can
see what is the what is the entrance for
it where the
underground entrance oh it's uh
of spikes here too hang on
um I'm I'll go find you I'm still like
outside I'm here look uh look where my
arrow is yeah look for my
arrow oh here here this way
oh thank you all right we got to find
the White River supplies apparently mhm
we station has been made Let's Go
careful to this
fight I need
food yeah me too
starving I'm about to die you're about
to die too be careful oh yeah those
spikes oh my
God you're you're about to
die I can't that use oh
boy M Mar no
no dang it I failed the
quest
ah the dang spikes
man she was behind you yeah I hate the
spikes
too
a oh well
he pretty
strong
okay well as long as as you guys found
your stuff I'm sure it's fine
I need to open those
boxes find White River supplies
mhm is in
here got to look around for
it I found a hunter J
no
okay and a Knife Guy
improve blade crafting
skill and improve Savage tool crafting
skill and oh that's for
B pie
pistol people use the pistols
right I think so
yeah I still have to find the White
River supplies though so I need to find
look around be careful the
spikes no maybe
here
no maybe on
here I
D I'm scared
well okay hi
people oh I'm coming I'm coming I'm
looking for the white rer supplies maybe
we have to get even lower I think
so is there
another let's keep
looking no no no
no uhoh oh dang it I faed the quest
too this a tough
one I couldn't see the the spikes
either no yeah this Quest is kind of not
great not the best Quest
a let's see if they found theirs
man maybe perhaps a different Quest
would be better yes I'm going to get my
backpack Mar can you come with me for
the light
source oh yeah thank you
cuz it was right there oh there you go
thank you you're welcome I didn't want
to go into the spikes again I couldn't
see
them oh I think they got
theirs f it do you want to get out
no scrapping for fun prove Salvage to
crafting
skill okay I'm going to use this one a
Knife
Guy does anybody here use
knives I think bio uses a knife okay I'm
going to keep this to people
done go back to the TR
then maybe you can get another
Quest oh yeah we need to go back to the
tra there now I think so yeah it would
be a good idea it's also getting kind of
late
though
yeah returning home maybe we should just
return home I don't know yes maybe
that's a good idea
how far is home oh you know the new
house isn't that far actually it's
actually not too
bad it's still
600 yeah it's okay I'll go back to
home yeah let's go back
home she did it I'm so happy awesome she
made it work
Ben oh yeah she did oh let's go oh oh
yeah she did that's ska nice
kiaha okay let's go check out that
workbench
then it is no music it's
depressing I know right I was kind of
like maybe we should just bring our own
music at this point but sometimes like a
subtle track will come in yeah yeah yeah
it's very atmospheric and then it messes
it up you know I
know sorry my nose is really bad right
now so I'm kind of muting myself a
little bit no don't worry are you
sick yeah I've been sick for about a
month and a half
oh yeah that's so bad sorry about that
that's all right
I'll get over it don't over do
okay we need Alie
more I'll do my best to try and heal a
little bit but it's bad timing all the
fun stuff is happening recently I feel
like I'm missing out all the time fun H
fun stuff
happens yeah that's always when I get
sick dang
it I know take care of
yourself try my best thank you
a go
stuck okay don't let the hills defeat
you
RAR they're just
Hills you got this
yes yeah it's actually pretty close to
their new house not too bad think a good
one
I'm going to jump into their
call okay I could as well
yeah ride me with two armor crafting
kits for each piece they want and then I
can what's going on Gamers hello
hello yeah hello helloo hi the
workstation yeah it has been completed
but uh oh good you should let me craft
things because I have the highest
skill you're the one that can do it but
every piece of armor needs two armor
crafting kits and then 10 claw frag
fragments I have a couple of these
things but barely enough right now I see
especially like armor crafting kids and
I can make armor crafting kits but then
I would need uh like more duct tape for
example I need a lot more duct tape
thank you B that's CRA you guys have
either duct tape or I think I have some
duct tape in
my or just the armor
crafting the arm server so we know what
to give you and we'll just put in your
box if you could label it okay you were
doing vehicle too I have four vehicle
magazines o nice we can make cars there
are some Legend Parts in here you
actually need those to craft the
strongest version of whatever weapon you
have so the strongest version of the
club level six you need one legendary
part and then the basic Club just so you
guys know what that's for I'm going to
make a baseball bat so I don't
necessarily need a legendary Club but
I'm just letting you know that's what
the parts are for
okay yeah oh shotgun weekly let's go huh
where are you in the house there ah yeah
take magazines if you need B you want to
go together to to base again to drop our
crap or do you want yeah I'm going I
want to go to I want to go back to the
quest Quest or not the quest Quest the
new house I want to go to new house I
have oh am I
muted I hear you hi here yeah I have uh
something for you I think I want oh you
do oh well give it to you now that you
here before I
leave uh oh I am not I am not at the
house yet you can put it in a chest
though and then I'll grab it if you if
you it do it says that you right there
next to oh no wait no no sorry that's
wor never mind yeah I'm pretty far but
you can put in a chest or something okay
okay what is it h no it's nothing it's
just like a knife guide the magazine and
I have yes have a she going to shank
even harder people where are you right
now I have a I have some we're at like
the the desert or something I'm coming
to we're coming to the the the new house
though we're I got stuff for you too
Kiara hold up uh in the house oh yes oh
good gosh why is it so hard to control a
bike by the way how does the bike take
damage is it like if you fall or
something no I it's it um it gradually
reduces its durability as you use it so
you're going to have to the main thing I
wanted to give you I think I don't know
oopsies thank you oh no that's awesome I
know you you like I've never taken care
of a bike
before oh wait how do you do that I'll
press
x what was that yeah I hear scream there
screaming screaming ladies are coming
watch
out small
raid maybe yeah it looks like a small
hord is
coming already my
blind yeah there are a lot of them going
I use this one I will help
you I'm punch let's go let's do
it hi bebs
hello look at us having a nice romantic
bike ride together yeah in the forest oh
ring
together these screamers these ones
freaking
[Music]
reloading oh yeah do it's a peaceful
peaceful existence in Canada and uh she
just killed
someone so
peaceful yeah the most peaceful o
loot yeah I wonder if these guys drop a
ton of loot I got one they're not really
dropping much at all except EX
which is good something you
fools Hunter behind here yeah hit him
call yeah I got him with the are they
outside I'll park my bike next to yours
there we go oh
okay I'll leave it need wa that lady
looks like she out
of all right this club is extremely
strong now
and lock okay I locked mine I think I
need to go now everyone so thank you so
much for
being thanks for playing thanks for
playing byebye byebye W see you this
time I'm on next
time I'll be care okay you made
everything respawned so it was
awesome it was and of course all are L
yeah byebye everyone see
you call you got a
Bic all right everyone I need to go now
I'm so sorry I need I need to do some
stuff at 1
p.m.
so I'll see you guys tonight though I'm
gonna stream again tonight oh we're
gonna do some art
so yeah before the stream of tonight I
need to you know plan SC for next week
and wait let me put some music actually
actually this time I'm going to log
out I won't do the same mistake ever
again let me do biger
biger hi
everyone B go big cut means big
trouble um so yeah I'm going to go grab
some breakfast or lunch I don't know I'm
I'm like right now I'm so running out of
energies because I haven't got any food
uh I just got like straight up coffee
but you know I need to eat I think um
and I need to get some you know energy
for the
day so yeah I'm going to go grab some
lunch and tonight we're going to stream
so I'll see you guys tonight and go rest
if you have to thank you everyone get
some
Curry that's such a good idea um you
know I think I will get some Curry today
I'll let you
know today technically piz today but I'm
you know trying to eat healthier so
probably I'm not going to have any
I need
pizza anyway everyone thank you so much
for coming and saying hi and everything
KATU Curry now I'm okay you know what
I'm ordering KATU Curry I don't usually
order
food but you guys made me hungry
also thank you Mr bite for all the gift
thank you so
much thank
you ah my gosh I'm not used to streaming
the morning I need to get used to it
again tomorrow is my day
off and so I'll see you guys tomorrow
and today and tomorrow I'm finally going
to
rest yes so see you guys soon
everyone thank you for watching bye-bye
everyone
[Music]
T good
night
[Music]
bye-bye bye pap
n
[Music]