[Music]
hello
hello hello hello hello hello hello
hello hello hello hello hello
what's up
oh
man behind the scenes setup be going
crazy what's up
i hope you guys are doing well welcome
to the holla live uh new year uh mario
kart uh 2022
i'm in my ryder outfit
let's go
man i should have put sunglasses on as
well
check your settings check your setup i'm
warming up the fingers thingies okay
what's happening
oh right yeah i'll go cold out
[Music]
is this okay
hello
bum bum bum
i got cold out i got called out
i feel like everyone and ian's doing
really well sweaty fingers and
shark tara please please for the love of
god please don't don't show up now choke
taro please no all right
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
we're starting oh my gosh we're starting
oh my gosh oh oh my oh my gosh we're
starting
okay where do we go first where do we go
first where do we go first okay um here
we go um
um um oh no my fingers
my fingers are sweaty already
um
you know what leave it to the rng
random always well
mike thank you very much
leave it to the random
wait why are we missing oh we only have
10 people that's right
i was like why are we missing two races
it has begun
i forgot to tweet
[Music]
oopsy
um i uh i forgot i i forgot to tweet
whoops up oh my chat
we're going we're doing amazing all
right
okay
[Music]
wait what seriously we're starting off
with baby puck what my today
ma i haven't gotten a single item yet
okay this is very concerning this is
absolutely
extremely concerning
oh my god i'm scared give me something
something
[Music]
give me something to protect
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
okay
we were doing amazing i don't know what
happened man
tricked her
bruh
bruh it's all right
wait does that mean i have to come top
five
good recovery not bad starting out wait
who came first
hey
why would we start off with an rng map
that's okay not bad
you came first i didn't even see
rainy
damn rainy blessed and also skill it's
only the beginning we've got six matches
you can climb our way up
should i be choosing maps instead of
going random but i just kind of want to
leave it up to random
[Music]
[Applause]
it's okay we gotta calm down i'm feeling
a little bit buzzed because you know
it's the beginning of the comp it's okay
here we go
[Music]
let's go
bad start baby bad stuff that's up
terrible start you are a terrible start
but it's okay
because you still got
the drift in you
drift like a queen
drift like a
queen griff like a queen i need an item
demon item
drift like a queen
nice
nicer you are savage bae i love it
kiara you stole my item yeah yeah
yeah oh my god this is bad this is very
bad he's very bad indeed
you think
come on
stop choking baby stop choking stop
choking
okay focus breakfast
[Music]
my nose is
i'm getting sabotaged
oh my freaking god okay that's that's
great it's great it's fabulous
i know this is itchy
um
a bum
it's okay
it's fine
it's absolutely fine
seriously
[Music]
it's tough it's nick nick come on come
on come on come on come on come here
come here come here come here come here
nice
it's over
bad it's over ladies it's ladies it's
over
ladies it's over i jerked
my noise was itchy
okay
we gotta choose one that i'm good at
let's go with mario kart stadium
just breathe babe i'm breathing
i'm breathing i'm breathing
there's still four matches left
it's okay
[Music]
meet city
me city's not too bad
i'm still reading chad don't focus don't
talk okay okay okay okay i'm not talking
here we go
[Music]
all right
oh
nice
[Music]
what always
oh no
[Music]
no no
no no no no no
[Music]
foreign
channel get that item
[Music]
no don't rush bay you still got time
it's bad boys
you're bad boys
boys this looking bad boys
face choking
shhh
[Music]
babe they can hear you in who's
commentary yeah bye
oh really
i'm serious too here we go
[Music]
now
oh
[Music]
nice
clutch
okay
it's okay
not too bad
it's not the worst
i'm still second last what the heck
what the heck
okay
um
this is too hard okay
i still want mario kart stadium
not lasting with the clutch
[Music]
you serious
what
what incarnation
[Music]
so
i hate this game
um
[Music]
wow
now
[Applause]
money
hmm
[Music]
i hate this game
that's not super good
[Applause]
i hate this game
i hate this game so much
i hate this game i hate this game okay
amazing
thanks guys for coming it's great
amazing all right i'll see you later
i hate this game
thanks guys for watching
i have no words it's fine
taro is the ping
a game
yeah it was a good game
it was the ping it was everything but my
skill
is the orangey
let's go that means i have to make
another thumbnail
oh yo
alright
see ya
um
what do we do now
what do i do now
um
oh okay all right i'll see you guys
later at the taco club
[Music]
do
you