[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
ah
Kiki
yo yo yo yo
chicken again
[Music]
oh wow
it's been a while a little while
and wow what's up oh what's up guys
what's up guys
it's been a hot minute
thank you it's from blue blue made me
another asset I'm like so cluttered
it's only been two days ah but it feels
pretty long I I actually never
take two days off in a row
um I may take two days off in a week but
not in a row
so that felt weird
um
foreign
foreign two days in a row for real for
real and I forgot to upload the clip
damn it I forgot it I saw like one time
um I saw one reply on Twitter telling me
reminding me about it
um but I was I think like lying in bed
or doing something I was busy so I
didn't do it
you guys need to read my mind
about when I've been reading the
messages
[Laughter]
you know
and send it to me or or
you don't even have to send it to me
when I'm on my PC you just have to uh
guess that that I when I would be
reading it and and then aim for the the
time when I would be on my PC and then
yeah I mean skill issue in the end from
you guys but yeah
write yourself a note I've been living I
have a really long to-do list actually I
bought like a cute to-do list memo
um
little block
of paper and I've been writing my to do
things there there's like Czech thingies
to-do list
thingies yeah yeah it's really cute
because it got like cats on it
um cute cute black cats with like big
round eyes like they're like really high
or something
um yeah yeah I still have a lot of
things to do but
at least I got some things done some
some things
um
some but like maybe half maybe half
but the annoying things I left I did the
the less annoying things first the more
fun things that I had to do like
recording
a song and recording
um another voice related thing
stuff like that for sure
that was more fun no
ah
okay we got
iced tea we got water we got some weird
chocolate that's not even good and
that's probably why it was 50 off and we
got a sandwich
um
with some nice
um special ham and and I think
mozzarella cheese the snack yeah I'm
prepared of a long stream hopefully
um and
dinner has been made two days ago
should still be good so I don't even
have to cook if I don't want to
so
um but you know what comes first in my
in my tltk streams
you know what comes first
is
it's not gonna be an hour long no
no no no no no no you're you are
exaggerating oh
hey welcome
welcome to my crib I just finished the
side quest
um and we're gonna hear what she says
about me finishing it because this is
one of the I feel like it actually does
a lot of side quests where you're not uh
one of those things where you don't have
to bring it back to the original person
um anyway uh before that that's because
uh
album oh where do I start I tried to die
yes
I tried to document what I was doing
okay uh
I showed this before
yeah
this thing I saw uh the elsewhere
in a Dom tendo stream uh video
he met this verb statue somewhere else
where I think it was like a quest and it
had like meaning you know
so yeah I'm sure now we have to get back
to this eventually but anyway where
why did I live off
um maybe
not this
ah I think you didn't see this before
yeah this is I think where it starts
I mean what I did is like one full day
of Farming Farming
farming and exploring farming materials
and exploring I didn't do many quests
but yeah well first thing uh randomly I
found a star fragment or two
uh you know they they follow uh off of
the sky quite often no I didn't get the
Metro's mess no no I just killed one
Lionel but not underground I want to do
that on stream you know um
what happened what happened here
what was I what was I trying to show ah
the horse ah that horse in front the
most frontal horse face with membership
yo thank you the most frontal horse is a
quest horse
that I got it's kind of supposed to be
special yeah it was it was really
dangerous oh my God the fondant was
always striking like so close to
everything
dangerous yeah but this one yeah spot
the horse spot is from a side quest from
the stable the mini stable and The
Outpost thingy yeah so I did that and
then
I I guess I got kind of into horses
because I went for horse search
I I got to keep it but it's not really
good
um it's just cute what was I doing here
what's this supposed to mean
who knows I had a crack I wanted to flex
that from this distance I randomly just
by looking over one second
uh I saw a clock can you see it
and I shot it from here with a wing a
wing attached to narrow
yeah oh then I found my first Sage as
well
which is interesting because
it confused me
um
Sage as well the remnants of a former
Sage is resolve if you gather four of
them and offer them two goddess statue
you can deepen your connection with the
Sages
very very
interesting
got it
it's like
say Sages
what what
[Music]
um
uh I think I
mean whatever I did I did another
um I didn't ever Shrine a couple shrines
I think I don't know how many but I
think I'd
got enough to get another heart and
another wheel
I think this was just
I just took a screenshot because it was
fun flying over I guess I don't know
uh uh ah here in order to explore I
tried to make
something with the things that I had
cause I think I was
trying to get to I was trying to get to
another star piece
um or to an island
or both yeah maybe both
and I could not separate these these
these cards
so I tried my best and I used some of my
capsules
um but it still failed miserably it was
really bad I built it like this
uh
uh yeah
I had hopes for it but in the same time
in the game engine glitch oh no these
were like I tried to separate them but
it looked like they were one thing but
it was really weird to me like why
because normally they're all like single
cards I don't know
maybe some card surges like this who
knows
those are meant to be attached um yeah
okay
God damn it that's a hot mess
I mean there's a system behind it
there's a nicely placed battery there's
a rocket in the back you know to lead us
higher there's in the front for me the
the steering wheel and then there's just
two turbines to keep me afloat you know
it's not a hot mess it's a muscle car
yeah
[Music]
and then
I was trying to get to that Island I
think you know see the ones that hard to
see but I think I was inspired by the
sages and whatever I don't know I want
to find out more I'm going to go to that
Island
like it works but no it was um not good
then I did
ah I activated two Fair
so two fairy quests
um
and upgraded some armor already I also
bought some new armor because I did uh
the diamond not diamonds but like um
gems gems side quests in Goron City so I
got a [\h__\h] ton of money from that holy
moly
um and with that you know I bought some
armor sets because I didn't know what to
do with the money
yeah
but I don't know
I think the only set that I bought that
was really worth it was the Chica set
the stealthy one
yeah what was I doing here
ah ah I was I accidentally the dog got
caught into my horse uh thingy and then
I was like dragging him with me and
somehow he really enjoyed it as you can
see our friendship got improved by me
dragging him along forcefully I do not
understand
like maybe this is a way of petting your
dog
maybe because normally you get the
Friendship up by giving them food and
you cannot pet them but I was low-key
touching him I guess I was rubbing
against him by dragging him I took him
for a walk yay
yeah yeah it's weird but it worked
somehow only one stone and then he kind
of fell out of it out of the contraption
you can make devices to pet them no
[\h__\h] way why can't you just pet it
yourself
that's that's ridiculous
nah okay uh yeah then he laid down and
left me
I wanted to let you guys
see a little bit of the fairy moment
well oh
they're the same fairies right as in
breath of the Wild
they look the same to me
no
oh oh
I found this crazy guy
ah kilton who is also in breath of the
wild if I remember correctly he says do
you have any business in this cave by
insurance I'm sorry to say but right now
it's you know couldn't go into the cave
because his brother was in there and he
has a brother
[\h__\h] freak
[\h__\h] freak meets kimono
and as you can see he's dressed up a
little bit look
Hey look
so [\h__\h] up oh my God
but his brother is dressed up you know
like those bunnies and frogs and all
that
yeah cause he yeah I will never I would
never give up characters
so he wants to become a Saturday and
turns out that those bunnies and frogs
they're also a type of a Satori so he
goes into cage cave caves to you know
get the the the the the Frog seeds
thingies that we've been collecting so
finally I know what that's for because
we had I had to give him one
um but then he disappeared and basically
you have to find him again elsewhere to
give him more and then you get rewards
oh yeah and that's how I got one mask
of um some the the moblins I got a
moblin mask
so they will give you the the moblins
yeah
they will give you the masks in exchange
for the
uh the shiny things but I wonder there's
probably no other
uh use for the shiny things right
I would assume because it's weird if
there were two things although there's
so many caves
they don't just give you miles I guess
monster Parts too okay okay
um
right what's the Majora's Mask
um in breath of the wild obtained
through
um this this guy
the left guy
if you like finish
his quest the last thing he'll give you
is the Majora's Mask no oh that was
perfect okay
yeah anyway I only did this once so we
can meet him again together guys uh
the Romans are true they always have
crates right now okay I've called a
bubble frog and it close just
ly
yeah they all have those those ears
um
I was
failing
at getting the chest nearby because I
was lazy as [\h__\h] uh to make something
proper ah here okay so in The Outpost
in The Outpost there is a side quest
or sad Adventure I don't know uh with
the lady who says she hears a voice
behind this opening and she's too scared
to go
and thus I go but I did not expect to
find what I find found and this is not
even
what I mean but there's this freaky
statue that I think was there before
yeah uh you I I haven't really made use
of it like I talked to it and then it
took a heart away from me and I was like
what the [\h__\h] give it back and I talked
to it again and it gives it back but I
guess normally you trade
money for stats or stats for money I
don't know
yeah but turns out yeah if you go
further there are many paths
long long long long long paths that lead
you deeper and deeper and are feel it
feels like they're never ending they
lean deeper and deeper into the castle
underground and then eventually inside
the castle castle overground and it is
[\h__\h] insane I was scared I was scared
with every step I was taking that the
glooming hands would suddenly appear
because it was getting gloomier and
scarier Ryan
um but yeah apparently it's for the
night set I did get one piece I didn't
find the rest maybe we gotta go again
and you guys gotta tell me where the
rest is
um but I was like when is this ending
when is this ending there were however a
lot of materials and all that too to
mine so that was cool
um
I'll take care of everything this won't
hurt a bit and then it took a [\h__\h]
heart a bastard oh yeah this is the one
I got the soldiers Grieves this one I
think you get pretty early on
so I think this is the first one that
you get
um there were some weapons too but the
weapons were kind of useless I would say
no
but I didn't realize it when you push
the video button that it will take the
30 seconds that already happened and
after 30 seconds in the future but it
worked out fine because this was me
uh this is like a stream this is me
finding this huge cave
where obviously that thing in the middle
is an enemy hidden under the rocks yeah
I did not open everything up but this
was a cool cave it doesn't look so cool
on the video it's also kind of like uh
bad quality but there were a lot of
shiny stones and I don't know uh there
was there was another weird opening
there were many weird openings and then
I found a cool royal Shield whoa 55.
what the [\h__\h]
55.
huh
then I found this what was this again
this was ah ah at this point I think uh
following up the stairs I ended up
getting uh yeah outside of the
underground and was like we're doing
recap yeah don't worry and then I was
eventually in the castle but yeah uh
they said deep beneath this land our
Mighty first ruler imprisoned The Demon
King lore
so this is like basically what we're
learning about right you know how they
first first ever
imprisoned The Demon King like the game
has been telling us about that so yeah
cool cool cool to ensure that King's
magic would hold we erected a castle
here to protect the sacred side
so the castle
oh
when they first imprisoned The Demon
King the castle was not there yet they
created the castle in order to protect
that
and that's why it was secret what was
underground wait oh I'm just realizing
this because we were questioning first
why is why why why for so many hundreds
of years had thousands of years uh it's
not even like the family
the royal family was allowed to go down
there why do they not know of anything
isn't it important to know okay I still
think that they should know at least the
royal family I think Zelda can protect a
secret
um what would have happened if she would
have wouldn't have gone down there on
that day
would she not have triggered
Ganon who knows who knows but so
basically the castle only exists to
protect that and keep the secret you
know interesting interesting interesting
they forgot it was very very critical
information though hmm
seems like the seal is breaking anyway
yeah was it was that hmm
game logic
yeah without the castle in place the
site may be just may be disturbed
allowing the Demon King's hatred and
rage to be revived
it's like
if it wouldn't have gone down
it wouldn't have been Disturbed and it
wouldn't have been revived don't you
think that that's what it implies
so basically it's Zelda's fault for
being so curious that's that's what I
think
so
[Music]
yeah
you could say it was already waking up
but I don't I feel like no you have to
like trigger it
[Laughter]
hmm I don't know
the preservation of this Castle is
therefore tied to the prosperity of the
Kingdom
yeah damn and yet you get it destroyed
and over and over again and now it's
floating in the sky for [\h__\h] sake
oh so this is how I eventually got kind
of stuck because I could go up but I
couldn't go down anymore I I saw this
like oh
the gate thingy
um you know Great Gate thingy and I
looked up and I thought oh there's
something up there so I went up
uh and I I I I saw this room
the guards chamber I mean look at it
there was omnius music playing there was
Gloom all over it it was a big empty
room though
there is no way that there's not
the Gloom hands chilling there once you
walk in properly
so this is where I stopped yeah yeah
this is this is where I I I I I after
after like 40 minutes or so of slowly
exploring this hole on the ground
there's something there is there not
there's the missing gear in here damn it
that's so close
are the hands in there
no that was
enemies but no hands damn it
ah damn it I didn't see any enemies
clearly
where are they
weird oh no surprise surprise Whiplash I
found another fairy well I got another I
activated another fairy
um
Shield yeah because I had so many
Shields and I kept on getting Shields
and I didn't want to throw them away so
I just kept on combining Shields of
shields I mean why not
um
what's this ah
this was a shrine Quest where you had to
go under the island
uh
uh I think yeah
to get the shrine
Stone and then you guys know what this
is has anyone been here
to get the shrine stone and you have to
bring it up with a platform if you fly
out again and because it's quite
difficult but you know so it's quite an
effort to do this but there's a lot of
those line platforms here that you can
borrow
but yeah I went there from another of
those islands that has the the lower
Stones
um
but all the other islands in the back I
also explored
I put a shield on your Shield so that
you can block while blocking
Rockets make those quests a lot easier
I'm kind of bad with controlling them I
think so chassis
um
uh that's a funny Contraption I did I
guess so that was difficult though that
one was difficult surprisingly difficult
and
it is
I am I don't know I don't know what I
was doing I think when I looked up
because I had to lazy [\h__\h] I looked up
where spot was the horse
and then I think because of that I saw
that there was another horse quest
um when I looked up the guide it was
there was never a guide about a
different horse this one which was
apparently more important but yeah I got
the gold now the golden horse this one's
close to the dragon uh the The Ice
Dragon
yeah uh
uh it isn't too difficult to find this
one I mean you normally don't go here
this is at the very end of the map of
the ice region yeah
you don't really go here normally I
think although there was and there was
one Shrine and that I did and there was
I think a
I think there was some uh the the the
the the ground painting thing one two uh
oh oh I got my first froggy armor oh wow
oh my God Frankie mama is gonna break
out once I have a full set but let's go
let's yeah yeah yeah
I saw one I marked it on my map
um yes fraggy sleeve uh
what's this about
tell me guys what was I capturing it
might have been an accidental screenshot
what
ah
you got it because you also must have
done it I drank the water yeah I I was
just randomly riding to the next area
that I wanted to go to uh to do side
quests
um yeah yeah and then I I saw like a
weird uh stone that was obviously meant
to be exploded I was like okay monster
was behind and then
is suddenly the water is being drained
and I'm like what what the [\h__\h] on the
other side the water is being drained
the other side of the the this wall and
then inside because here was the stones
that you got rid of inside
we find another post statue
what
you found the snow because the statue
told you to go there oh I found it
randomly
um
yeah and what the [\h__\h] oh yeah it says
come to me in the Temple of Time ruins
up the road on the plateau to the South
now I did not do that I thought maybe
we'll do it together or so I don't know
in Temple of Time ruins up to the up the
road on the plateau to the South
so that's like where you begin in breath
of the wild right yeah it's a funnel
Quest
an oil build Quest oh really oh I had to
look up what the post that she was
talking about to free it for the quest
at the end of it it gave some really
good words
oh yeah I was running around with
Zelda's golden horse this was apparently
this is Zelda's horse but in breath of
the wild she had a different horse right
and this one's just ridiculously golden
and shiny
Zelda's previous horse was better
not gonna lie what's
worse man did it die
my balusters inspired you to buy a
switch damn have fun I mean if you buy
switch now you have the chance to get
you know one of the newer models which
is also nice
um I just have a I have a really basic
gray switch the only cool thing that I
have is the Animal Crossing duck
and a Splatoon controller will never
played Splatoon before
yeah but I don't see why I should buy a
new model
when I always play I never play handheld
most of the time I don't play handheld
so um
yeah
gotta wait for a switch too anyway I was
uh what was I even
trying to capture here I don't know
maybe just that I just left that place I
don't know ah I found an ancient blade
that has [\h__\h] 50 fuse attack power
you can put it on the arrows
and I think I've read something
about this that they are and I'm not
sure if it was this but there's a
um there I was I was watching a guide
about killing the lionels in the
Colosseum on the ground
I can really tell I'm so nerding out on
this game like
but so uh I heard that I think it wasn't
that guy that um I heard that there is
one Arrow attachment that one hits the
lionels
I think
and it was either this or a different
thing
was it this maybe I'm not sure
is this the one holy [\h__\h]
is this let's go
nice
yeah one hits lionels what the [\h__\h]
oh you don't get the loot if you do this
oh really
eh for real
foreign
it's completely oblivious enemy holy
[\h__\h]
well hmm
usually I feel like when you do the
linels you really want the loot because
their uh weapon attachments are the
strongest ones you can get in the game
and and and you can make the strongest
weapon uh with in the game with Lionel
attachments and what you want to do is
like get those uh and then before your
weapon breaks you always want to like
disattach the attach
um the attachments in the place that you
later unlocked and I don't have unlocked
yet yeah
um
I know too much I'm such a nerd
for the totk nerd I I have too much
knowledge in my brain already
yeah oh man
oh oh the cool thing is that okay what
there's this cool strategy I don't know
if I can ever do this but if we ever do
the Colosseum I I want to try this out
um so basically
[Music]
um
you make a strong weapon ideally this
would be your strategy on the second run
or no
no no maybe um
the second Lino I guess no no whatever
but what you can do is you put you know
your Lionel attachment to your on your
weapon but you don't use this weapon for
anything but killing more lionels
because
um when you are on the liners back your
weapon
your weapon does not uh lose it's
you know uh it doesn't break more so but
uh you can do this cool thing when you
make this weapon and and and and and and
uh well I forgot how exactly it works
but the durability yeah but you get your
durability to like you know when it says
it's about to break so what you do then
is you shoot the Lino give him a a
headshot so then you can run over and
mount them and then with the breaking
weapon it will do more damage somehow uh
I don't know I think it's because you
use a base weapon that does that because
some
some weapons have that it does more
uh it does more more damage when it's
yeah double damage oh
hold it there we go all weapons do
double damage when they're about to
break so so
understand
when you're on the Lionel's back
durability does not
proceed when you hit him so you go and
use a breaking line of weapon
that is the strongest you can possibly
get and then oh my God you can be so so
so so so dominating you can assert
dominance over the liners holy [\h__\h] and
you keep on repeating that just be
careful to never use the weapon uh to
just hit him normally you always have to
repeat pew pew pew headshot run over and
then slash with your breaking weapon um
and then and then you know eventually
you can go to the detaching guy and he
will take off your Lino uh attachment
then you get rid of the the
um breaking weapon with orange is only
the base weapon it's not the attachment
that's breaking only the base weapon so
so you can get rid of whatever stupid
weapon you had it attached to get a new
one attach it there and you can use the
Lionel drops forever forever oh my God
so then you use it you know in normal
daily totk life Until It Breaks and then
you're like okay I need more Lionel
attachments so you go to the Colosseum
with your breaking weapon you kill the
liners really quickly
and with your strategy of the breaking
weapon it will be even easier because
it's already breaking
and then you go back to the attach make
a new weapon do your daily dotk totk
live you know with your really strong
weapon you know you keep on keep on keep
on repeating this let's go
they're about to patch it out because of
me no wait why that's is that a glitch I
feel like this is just normal normal you
know implemented game Strat
I think I'll be able to pull it off I'll
like I don't know
although I think that the prompt of hey
your weapon is about to break is usually
pretty obvious and I always notice it I
always take note of it
so no no
Sonic let's just an oversight that's
what I thought yeah
anyway cool story then I got another
horse my third uh Quest horse
the big ass giant horse
I was just into horses on that day I was
horsing around
um
but for Dad
for that I had to go pretty far I was
exploring quite a bit
this is like in a really hidden place it
places where the horse called the older
horse God this is the horse God I guess
what everybody talks about
um
look comparison [\h__\h]
fudge man
I end but
it's it's it's kind of rowdy
I don't know it's kind of Rowdy I think
I won't really use it I don't know oh
it's not the horse gun okay it's just
giant yeah but it's connected with a
quest someone wanted to see a giant
horse so I brought it over to him and I
brought it back
I got a heart container
and I found ripen Flint let's go let's
go it's let's go let's go on my second
try actually thank God yeah
and I killed a Lionel because I am cool
and
uh yeah
this I just saw today actually yeah
right before the Stream
says this is a side quest at kakariko I
think
um
uh
which is also kind of connected to the
sages so you find a book hidden with uh
behind like a Monster uh Camp it says
filling in the blanks I think it's
basically saying talented individuals
become sages by taking up secret stones
oh that's it
and that brings us back to
here
see it didn't take an hour it didn't
take an hour
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
just chilling out there
uh you know there was two I have argued
about offense and defense since they
were barely old enough to walk they just
praised each other's vegetables
hmm
okay and now it's like a brand new day
for those old cools
we need other zucchinis and and carrots
we've also got some stock back in so
it's happy days all around that reminds
me please take this during Karen yeah
you like my recapping yeah I thought you
guys would like to especially if I do
this much if I just play for 15 minutes
off screen whatever but since I do so
much stuff off screen I thought it's
better to compile it each time and tell
you what I was up to um
and they're a carrot that's called an
Endura carrot cook it to gain stamina
it's a precious natural remedy it's been
priced since all times and it's become
remarkably rare of late please take it
with you on your journey thank you truly
please drop by anytime
uh did I buy this or why is it empty
and they got pumpkins
[Music]
hmm
yeah I'm good I'm good though
um
[Music]
so we're still not properly gonna
um explore kakoriko Village but
see this is the region that I
I guess I unlock
uh outside of the Stream
where is the Zora Village is it here the
Zora place
is it this area
oh one of these
Midwest Northeast this and this one
under Elden oh this one
hero shows me oh okay okay mid East okay
so probably this one oh
okay
um
before we do that I wanted to check
uh about the quest
um ah this one I think
um
no huh
no that's not what I meant
[Music]
um
the stone slabs
I want to show the stone slabs that I
already have
two no
[Music]
this one I think
stones have been found in the ring ruins
that fell around kakariko Village but
has come to see the writing on these
Labs but is afraid of heights and can't
visit the runes is this the one
if you read what's written on each slap
let him know what they say you have four
more to tell him but wait this is also
in kakariko didn't we find him holy [\h__\h]
the rain didn't we find them
the first time
is it the quest that I'm thinking of
yeah it's a different slab
the ring ruins wait I think I've been
there too just now
one is allowed to visit the Ron ruin
that's floating above to ah
that one oh ah but I went to the one
that's on the ground
but if you've read one of the slabs in
any of the other four runes tell me what
it says
what you went to see them for me what
did they say
I usually it's not enough to be
exceptional you need a secret Stone to
be Sage or so it seems at least but what
is a secret Stone if it's worth special
I'm sure it's the beauty wood its beauty
would put a diamond to shame thank you
for telling me about that slab truly
fascinating stuff just free left I can
only imagine what discoveries Line Store
ah well okay that's not what I meant uh
where's the guy
is he still in in The Outpost you know
the one who needed us to take photos of
the texts In The Sky Islands
is he still here
you should be here now
no I think he stays in The Outpost I
hope so
I gotta go [\h__\h]
God damn it
why why are all these guys in kakariko
oh
God damn it okay I guess we'll talk to
PIRA while we're here
in the broken open building okay
is this something you can do with cherry
pits guys like
making a cherry tree
not that I have a space for one but
I got cherry pits
linky welcome back I've been hearing a
lot about your adventures
no idea
are you keeping them
not not purposefully
a serious cold front
a full shortage and a ship floating in
the sky and read a village
the cold and the food shoulders we
already took care of what about the
Zoras girl
I know wait that was all the same
then over in Garden City The Gardens
were fixated on marbled Rock Rose and
had stopped working yeah we took care of
that too
and someone who looked like a Princess
Zelda was a princess was connected to
what happened in both places whatever
the case may be I'm glad the retail
Gardens are able to get back to business
as usual yeah we did that
seems like interesting those areas to
you was the right decision after all
it's become clearance day that there's a
connection between Princess Zelda and
the upheaval things are much more
serious than I previously thought I need
you to hurry to the remaining regions
and soon
and we need to investigate the other
villains I'm concerned about too
okay
which one
home of the shika tribe it's off to the
southeast in the nekluda region I
thought she was going to tell me about
Azora Village
and so night ruins each shape like a
ring fell directly on top of the village
there's got to be a special reason for
it right now the zonai survey teams
Elites are taking on the investigation
if you want to know about the zonai you
should talk to them if you want more
info talk to Atmos down on the shelter
he can probably point you in the right
direction he helps to deploy the deploy
the monster control crew squads where
they are needed and has extensive
geographical knowledge but we already
know where kakariko villages
um
I can get help from the research
division for this but I'm entrusting in
the investigation of the remaining
regions with the phenomena to you
hey you've got to be kidding this is
exactly what you should be using your
pure cat for did you forget or something
well I guess that's in character for you
isn't it I guess so can I see the pure
Pat yeah
I look like pure with my glasses
whoa now yeah right the locations and
she told me about them before there are
two locations left
to the East and Garuda region to the
Southwest monsters are pretty active to
the South anyway so you better love
sticking closer to here you know
oh
oh so she's warning us from uh the
bottom left okay which honestly makes
sense when I went down to the Faron
region
it wasn't like crazy dangerous but it
felt like a little bit dangerous I met
some
some Thunder
um lizards by the beach
and and those were difficult to fight
they had like a big Thunder aura
that was a ship
I connected with a side quest and there
were like two two liners close to each
other I marked all of them on my map
um
you did the Gerudo first oh
you sassy Parker
um
anyway if you need a Refresh on what to
do check your pirapad keep me posted
apples
okay I mean I guess I'll talk to the guy
but if he just tells me where kakaliko
Village is I swear
um which one
which one
and some no
he looks like
he looks like someone from
Ocarina of Time I think
weird weird
um so if you follow it then yeah yeah
yeah I followed it and I regretted
spaghetti
where why why don't they have names
unless I speak to them
up growlins
no name what the [\h__\h]
I'm not gonna talk to every single one
of them
huh
remember him
ah Monte
hi it's a mad guy oh thank you
wait that's that's like a newspaper guy
not mad guy oopsie mysterious
[Music]
map map no name map guy
Atmos
oh oh it's you link pardon me for being
lost in my work here this map tends to
get all my attention are you interested
in the different peoples of Hyrule and
where they live that's my entire field
of study when I'm out with only
deployment with the monster control
correspond hours pouring over our Maps
um no I already know all of this
okay let's go to kakariko
I think unless there's something else I
should do here before let me talk to
these peeps up
I really appreciate you fixing up my
balloon I'll try things that auto
building was pretty amazing I should
have a good thing about all the
practical uses of that someday oh that
reminds me listen to a big update here
your premium pad can be equipped with
sense so that's the texture oh
I thought there would be no sensor in
totk because the shrines are pretty
obvious
this mission is important oh my
we're impressed I'm the first one in the
Nile of Hyrule who noticed the shrines
after their people so I created a sensor
to detect them only thing is I can't set
it up here at Lookout Landing
hmm
there are a ton of hidden shrines yeah
the cave one's true now now
I guess so
but they're they're more obvious in this
game because they glow and I don't know
I thought noon wasn't necessary
I'm gonna be nearly impossible unless
I'm at the pure pad research lab in
hotel Village
please tell me where hatano villages
somehow I look up so many things but
where hateno villages is the one thing I
have yet to look up on even though I'm
like constantly looking for it
that's right he doesn't laugh that it
came into the announcement of the pure
path which Pura and I developed once I
am in that lab and you join me there I
can further improve your pure pad
starting with the sensor you'll find the
lab in East Dakota off in the Southeast
corner of Hyrule on this far side is
having a Southeast Wellness Cipher okay
bottom right
um
go a bit for further than that and
you'll see a mighty peculiar place don't
let the looks fool you it's a
cutting-edge lab all right I'm going to
head over there and we'll be waiting for
you to arrive see you there see I'm not
in the mood anyway right now to
immediately
um
do the big thing right away so that
floats my boat uh
all right that's Western cluda
so I'm guessing it's like somewhere here
I could go
from wait I did not activate any Shrine
here oh
yeah I went through here ah I thought if
I went there
maybe I would find hateno but then
eventually like this area is [\h__\h]
difficult for some reason I I kind of I
think I gave up somehow
oh is the quest not activated there we
go ah
hey for the recipe chat
a certain Sunshine oh not yourself
oh wait it's here
oh okay see it's so [\h__\h] far
oh yeah I think I went that way oh I
remember now I was like struggling so
hard because I was I saw
um two
Towers
yeah
the um
[Music]
but I wanted to activate
and
I think I couldn't get to either of them
I tried
and I was I don't know I was losing my
mind about it
um the towers and yeah because I think
they're like kind of close
and I was trying to get there but it was
so annoying
it's easy to get to hatino from kakaniko
okay we can do that
you mean maybe from here
and then that one or follow this path
and probably connects back here
let's go to calculator
[Music]
you can jump from a town and skydiving
um
yeah I tried doing a lot of things on
foot or with the horse when I was
playing off-screen
hmm
people eating good after the ID passes
what happened
foreign
let's find the guy
I love the stone slabs oh broken house
what
broken house
I can't see
was that a broken house
[Music]
are you the guy
Wordsworth
that was him that looks like the thing
yeah
yeah oh link good for you to come too
curious to stay away who are you again
what a droll sense of humor oh it's me
words with the ancient I really in
scholar you might not Lookout Landing
aren't you curious about my findings
here
is a picture of the stone tablet that
fell from the sky it looked out Landing
I managed to decipher the inscription on
it using my notes on the ancient
hyrulean I had in storage at this
research lab
here's what it says
once held
uh
once held why honor else
to King raru and Queen Sonia is this Old
English really
or is it a stretch
and queen Sonia there
thereafter to his sister onto princess
celda
uh
[Music]
Old English wasn't like this I think
you're still set to German
yeah the voice acting yeah this not
Old English okay
her own day is pretty stand on 12th more
with all make why and it mean time
people Royal familiar it's getting worse
it's getting worse
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
there is not much to go on but you can
clearly read the names of King Rao and
queen Sonia the founders of Hyrule it
has the only clear thing
the name Zelda is clearly legible
elsewhere in the text the author
finishes by saying that she will write
about the Royal Family's daily lives in
13 seconds oh that's what these things
will tell me
their life
[Music]
what it's certainly seems to be a royal
diary left behind by a Chamberlain or
some of equivalent station the part that
catches my attention is the third name
mentioned Zelda there is no record of
anyone by that name in any of the other
texts with Unearthed so far but this is
evidence that the name Zelda is much
older than the princess it dates all the
way back to hyrule's founding what's
written here must be the start of a
first-hand account of Hyrule did you
notice the number 13 there that means
there are 12 more of these
um it's an interesting perspective on
the day-to-day life of the era one which
the history books don't mention there's
so much we could learn from this
okay yeah I found two
um I think too oh
have you already found something uh if
you've tracked down a picture of Stone
tablet like the one that looked out
Landing I'd love to see it
all exciting
which one am I showing
okay I don't know which one is at least
have Hebrew Sky archipelago
honestly getting all of this was really
fun really
interesting I'll get right to it
incredible
well here's what the original text says
the King was late why come this even so
make it the queen to share entails of a
land of she Ryan's old granny igloo and
shrines that are glowing green okay
of early days since high rules funding
have
diverse monstrous
ha
[Music]
besieged
assailed
what
I know
answers
and
unsuccessful
in strife
they belonged to dispel Focus leaving
hahaha
no maidens King on quen is
[Laughter]
with might of light on the poor driven
about
the royal couple made these shirins to
sell and him away
[Music]
way
it's the lens real last name henway like
that actor
[Music]
what a stretch
that's holy cylinder been Eclipse shoe
lines of lot
great king red the queen why thank you
your photo one boy welcome made into a
[\h__\h] helmet can you just tell me yeah
thank you
the subject here is the actions King owl
and queen Sonia and it took that long
after hyrule's founding
[Music]
with the kingdom established they were
worried for their people so they set out
to eradicate the monsters traveling them
they created statues called shrines of
light to seal the monsters away
so that they could never be revived
there's more here about light and time
too the sense I get is that the two of
them I have had Supernatural Powers
though it's part of ancient history it's
a fit those of us living today should
still be grateful for truly an important
Discovery hmm
those green shrines were supposed to do
that
they certainly don't do that now oh
this is not German they're the fake
words no it's not Austrian German either
I think I have another one
[Music]
I should
let me talk to you again oh oh he's
putting it up
huh
I put what you brought me over there
oh
what
you're welcome to come and have a look
at the research lab while anytime
oh
here and let's just read what he has to
say like the tlvr okay this one's from
West nikluda sky
oh
um
okay so King Ronaldo's oldest sister was
named mineru kind of cute name oh here
we'll learn a bit about mineru but we
haven't seen no wait
ah is it the one
that becomes one of the
you know
one of the team
the one with the
delicious floppy ears I don't know
it says that she neglected to eat but I
think yeah and I think I know which one
she neglected to eat or sleep while
making something called a construct she
made it
it was part of her Research into a means
of returning to Life as a spirit
possessing a new body should her
original one die
she's like the Elon Musk of ancient
Hyrule
oh my God
what
[Laughter]
to you alright this sounds less like
history and more like a sort of ghost
story
mineru mask
but remember who we're dealing with they
may have had unfathomable powers that
made such things possible
the Revelation that minero was a fellow
researcher makes her feel like a kindred
spirit to me and yet the Chamberlain who
inscribed these don't have the streets
made out of such care and kindness that
it warms my heart hmm
very good I thank you not just with
words but with this as well
oh [\h__\h] damn money
do I have another one
I don't know if I do
oh I guess I don't because he's not
offering it to me
I see
oh
no I don't okay it recognizes when I
have another one
okay so now we shall go to
um the place
are there
can I get a horse here no no Stables
um
how should I go
yeah the best uh
it was just the first thing that Sprint
in my head that I've probably mean
someone else
yeah the Chica slate it's not chica
slate there's a pure ass slate pure pad
this is from blue blue made it for me
hmm
Tony Stark No that's not one who I was
thinking of evil I think but okay
just use the road
I wish I could get a horse though
um which way this way
[Music]
oh
nanny
all right come here
and what
have you heard it's written forbidden to
get near that ring
Jack use the road
yeah
Princess Anna oranges but she's [\h__\h]
dead so just let me through
came up
Zelda
came out to kakariko Village the other
day and told everyone to steer clear of
the Ring ruined that's not the road it
is a road
on the map
she left in the Heritage I didn't quite
catch why of it all and surely you've
noticed these runes could come crumbling
down at any time so folks need to keep
away
that doesn't seem too evil does it
oh
[Music]
hey
and now now we got in
now we got we couldn't
can I kill these yeah no probably not
trying to hurt chickens in the Zelda
game
doesn't have good history does it
[Music]
nothing here
okay
but I do Wonder
um something I wanted to look up
but I didn't get to it
um
question
what happens if in a stable you know
there's often like goats and all that
what happens if you kill them
can you are people gonna get angry or
what happens
there's like
so much meat that you can just take
you can't because I always wonder with
the goats especially like can I get goat
milk from them somehow
or nah
mule but see see my stamina it's too
far we have come full circle
oh hi dragon
hi Zelda
hmm just seeing if he would turn his
head I guess it's not Zelda
I think I came from here when I went to
yeah I did
I think I did
when I first came here
um
well can you guys be my GPS
ah this one's already fixed yeah yeah it
came by here before okay
know where to go when I need to go
somewhere
um
[Music]
build a bike
you mean I'm actually rolling bike
actually I know you know what I'll do
uh
[Music]
uh oops
which where do we go
how long do I follow the road
should I just I'll I'll just just
continue
hey
yay fun
sliding on my shield down the hill
oh sliding with my shield
I was not uphill oh there's a chest no
there's not a chest
no no no
that was a box
do a flip I did a flip when I uh jumped
on the shield
okay and now
Ah that's stable
it's not the one that I already have on
the map
who
farting on my ship
signing on myself down the hill starting
on my shield but not uphill
damn
lame
lame lame
yeah why did I not get the shrine uh I
think I was regretting it myself too
why did I not get the shrine here
uh where is the shrine
ah
I don't think I saw that one
I think I just simply did not see this
one
also it's really up high
um
but we could do another fairy Quest here
I haven't done this one
oh wait maybe can you actually
ascend
from there
oh yeah
yeah oh my God
Ah that's maybe how you get up there but
is that like a cook
oh it is
[Music]
has been a while wait how do you
oh no the other one huh
maybe this way
no no how how
might need a rocket for this for real
don't you just have to oh
no
is that nightshade
distracted
no sweet spot a swift violet
oh God am I drowning
no
how can you drown here
it's not that big
see I was like one meter away from
standing
um I don't know you can lose up
a rocket on this right now
um
all right rewind this
and thus we will reach the shrine easily
where where does it actually go oh does
it go up all the way
oh because a lot of these Stones don't
actually go up all the way
never mind see it that's what I was
talking about
well well well let me check out the top
of this actually
there might be a clock here too
what is this
is
one of those stones too
eat eat
yes
yes distracted
with this one we could reach an island
okay
oh
it's not the one that I already did
though right
there
the one I already did look I'm somewhere
else I think ow
oh there is ah I see the stone oh
they all look like that no
if if you activate the stone before the
shrine uh I think it still works the
same way it just tells you where the
shrine is
instead of the shrine telling you where
the stone is
wow look at that
follow the beam to the to its end and
off of the crystal there do so now offer
you Glide that vanishes evil
okay okay I don't like this so much
sometimes they're quite difficult
but we'll see
where is it is it higher or is it lower
because we have some stuff here
hold on
a glider too
I just try to see
where it actually is
oh oh it is lower okay
over there
yeah yeah that shouldn't be too
difficult should we take the glider or
should we take this
a glider right
it should be a glider
fall down yeah
and we're already
put it in the right direction
so we don't have to do much
uh adjusting once we're floating
glider cards glider plus cards is
controlled
what no no ah glider slider on top of
the car
or or cards on top of glider that would
make no sense to me at least with the
with it on the bottom we could
um roll off the cliff I guess
like this
but I touched the kind of shitty
I wish I didn't have to wiggle to do
this because sometimes it messes up the
positioning that I already put so much
work into
wish it was just a button
um okay should we use everything
you can shake the controller too oh
okay we'll do a classic
simple
we left Japan yesterday after a much
needed vacation oh Japan was dedication
oh
you want to go to Austria no if you want
to travel more
man I would be happy but still I feel
like Austria should no I there's cooler
places yeah
there is way cooler places
ah
you're eating Sparkle and separating
your rubber properly honestly
I guess as uh apparently an Australian
coming to Germany
the way they separate their trash is
very very
like
new to you but
Germany isn't even the worst when it
comes to that kind of stuff
by by my own experience I know Japan is
the worst with that
the most annoying and depending on the
region
like some regions
like separate like
into like 10 to 15 different things
what [\h__\h]
do we really need both batteries
um
[Music]
okay but usually it's more like up to 10
I would say
it's really annoying though
when I was living in Japan I was like
what the [\h__\h] do I do with all this
stuff I don't know if I'm doing it right
and sometimes I would put things
um out out in the morning or in the
evening and then they wouldn't take it
so I'm like what did I do wrong huh
I thought I did it right I guess I
didn't
it was a whole mystery to me okay is
that it okay
don't forget the stone
same at least you don't have to deal
with that anymore right
okay with a steering wheel this
shouldn't be too much of a problem
oh God
we can already aim and blow it down I
suppose oh
go for it go for it with confidence
okay okay
[Music]
oh
nice huh
nice
not the best landing
oh it works what else was shaking
everything
not the best landing but still pretty
decent best pilot in the whole life
I don't know about that
this is usually
um blessing shrines right because you
already did the challenge kind of
you know today is one of those days
where my breathing isn't very good so
hmm I hope it will get better
hmm
but I'm I'm happy besides that
I had a a rude awakening
recently I've been having many
nightmares I guess it's because I'm
stressed out
but you know actually a whole life
member even appeared
in my bully dream
yo yo there was some other [\h__\h] that
happened
as well
in my dream but I'm not that I think the
reason the whole life member appeared is
just because my my brain was trying to
fill in faces and and there's just not
many faces oh
no
50 more efficiently used
uh attached to another device holy [\h__\h]
what
the [\h__\h]
nice nice one it always gives batteries
usually okay
um
yeah I think my brain was just trying to
like auto fill some faces some familiar
faces
um
so one of them was a em member and then
I think there were other faces I
recognized but I already forgot by the
time I woke up you know but I got
bullied so much
and and I I I remember in my dream I was
like like screaming and crying trying to
make them understand and look at my
point of view or so but no they wouldn't
listen and they were all ganging up on
me that was so sad when I woke up
[Music]
um
oh man I don't want to be the type of
person that gets upset by the dreams
because it's just dreams but
recently it's been upsetting
um
you know scary another part of the dream
was more scary than sad
because it was basically
a fan
that I didn't know was a fan it was just
acting like this person randomly met me
somewhere and and and recognized me but
acted as if they didn't know me and then
I was just being nice to them and then
they kind of like
use the interaction
against me
later on kind of like exposing me
also not very nice
interesting
anyway what was I doing I was gonna go
to the shrine below
uh where is it
I guess I could still like check out the
other islands close by but no thank you
not right now
uh it should be
here
blue
yeah I have bad dreams
[Music]
no need for this oh and I think I
realized what I did wrong with the
rocket on my shields uh off stream like
I think I told you guys that I was
having trouble with it but I think I
figured it out you're not supposed to
I I just used it wrong I think you're
just supposed supposed to pull it out
your Shield right you're not supposed to
do anything else you just pull out the
shield I was trying to do the shield
jumps
don't know what I was doing
no idea
the Press is still remember your dreams
I do forget a lot of my dreams but
recently these bad dreams I remember
them roughly because I made myself upset
um
let's do this
but
um besides the dream yesterday I had a
decently fun day
with my friends you know
I meet my friends
every like once a month or once in two
months
and usually not usually
um every three months Maybe
roughly
those oh combatron Shields oh
uh every three months this meeting
turns out to be often a
ooh and a convention
so I don't wanna miss those
opportunities you know
I have to use my shield as pose okay
maybe we have to Parry
wish me luck
[Music]
um
and also because I mean I went to this
like tiny ass convention there were
actually
uh I think I think there were two
oh I just realized I still have this
in the comments
um
this was like a tiny convention that my
friends were getting hyped about
especially one of my friends who was
like performing at the convention and
um
yeah
um I missed another convention that my
friends went to like last week I think
I couldn't go there because I already
had you know streaming plans and then
the next one that I can think of that my
friends are maybe going to where I would
want to go to is dokumi and you guys
know I'm not going to dokumi
so I'm like I feel like until dookomi
there's no other convention that I would
go to
so
I'm like okay I guess I'll go to this
one that's why actually I already had
this day uh planned out as my day off
because I wanted to go and hang out with
my friends
um
it's however uh the first time this
little convention was
um
happening and actually it was like
it was like a warm-up convention because
so they they created this new convention
that's supposed to start 2024
um but because I guess the organizers
were really excited
they organized a small version of their
convention
as a beta version or so
a year before like a test run more or
less but different location but but kind
of same convention and same organizer
and all that yeah like a smaller version
of it to just test run it I guess a
pre-convention yeah a year before
so that was happening it wasn't anything
big or special but my friends were going
and I'm like okay I guess I'll go
because I don't know when else I will be
going to a convention
yeah
[Music]
um
thank you oh I guess
pre-convention yeah
okay Randy shield and Perry
hmm okay
first time was panic but I can do it
I can do it my topic skills yeah yeah
well done can I do it again can I do it
again can I do it again oh two hmm
yeah
myself the element of each attack and
choose your Shield according accordingly
wow because look I'm not supposed to
pair the other one because it will be
bad
all right
I'm gonna die I need to cook
mmm yummy
deep fried drumstick
[Music]
I guess I'll eat that
what
that's how I
think that's how I block the the other
one because they don't move anyway
laughs
[Music]
and now what do I do about the other one
I'll try
[Music]
[Applause]
I can do it
I am capable
[Music]
but anyway so you know the day I
canceled my stream I realized that
I
I I'm not gonna be able to do the things
I need to do on that supposed day off
either
um
and that really stressed me out so I
decided to
um take one extra day off to get some of
the stuff done yeah
um
yeah but the convention was all right I
kind of went there pretty late
uh because again I could not sleep oh my
God another one
again I couldn't sleep
um
[Music]
I couldn't sleep and
you know
I don't know I had to prepare some more
things
and yeah
but then actually worked out well
because my other friend
uh I was gonna Uber
but my other friend was also on the way
with a car also very late and was like
ah you know I can pick you up
so I got a relatively free ride I only
had to pay for parking
he said oh I'll drive you if you pay for
parking I'm like
and that's the deal because I'm actually
saving a lot of money
yeah
okay we got the shrine
let's go to where
ah let's get a horse
yeah and then when we when we watched
the convention and
and people were already in there having
fun it was pretty late
um
I just
you know I went in and I'm pretty soon
after my friend's performance was
happening why do you guys look the same
all right
okay course look at all these horses
flexors big kalkini I didn't you guys
didn't know the names yet
let's take flexors
your brothers are twins hmm
I couldn't think of good names but I
wanted to have good names so that you
guys would laugh when you see them
yeah
big footprints
where's my horse there oh
how many people honestly it was like
like a huge container one big
convention hall inside like what felt
like a container
I can't just go straight over there
surely there will be like a path that I
can't overcome
okay let's see
how many people I honestly don't know
it felt pretty full for what was the
first of its kind somehow
somehow there were like plenty of people
there
you know
oh my mommy yeah
no no I don't want to fight that one now
but I'll mark him
there's a Kodak here
possibly here yeah
I only saw two arrows I didn't even need
the third Arrow
do you see anything about the Golem game
nice uh no I think I uh saw nothing
Gollum game
I think I only heard it's bad
I didn't even realize such a thing was
already released
oh ah
I know
can't go over there there seems to be
some blockage
although maybe we could
seems like it's just Monster blocking it
and the rest is Mountains and the lake
uh can I not go with my horse
I want to go with my horse
there's a path there you mean at the
where the monsters are yeah oh
hahaha
meow
he has a beehive on this weapon
interesting
I almost had him
just ride through them for now okay if I
can huh I shall
oh but there's
stripes
Stripes I can't I don't know how to
English there's
um spiky spikes spikes spikes see very
close
what the [\h__\h] he's huge
t
was just squatting
very intimidating squatting
all right I'll blow you up
oh half damage
[Music]
all right all right bring it on baby
Bring it on Bring it on
yeah
[Music]
fight fight with me fight me bastards
wait I want to switch weapons
foreign
[Music]
already dead how did he die
I saw him having
the
I have the HP after though
oh he came out of nowhere
after the blow up I know he's still
there I guess he's looking for
a weapon
nice
stolen is one versus wanting that dude
it is it was baffle fruit I'm having
everything under control I mean there's
so many ways to get control over a
situation like this
and we have out so many materials might
as well make use of them
[Music]
is
doing
what are you doing the whole time you're
just letting your minions die well
you're looking for a weapon there's so
many anyway
I left him alive for the whole time
oh bad Commander yeah they were meant to
die
but yeah cool cool little fight
that was fun
what else is there okay
yeah anyway the convention it was kind
of like easy to oversee because it was
just one big ass container and you know
it had all the typical things like a
stage and uh
and the maid Cafe I I find made cafes at
convention is pretty cringe so I don't
go to it but apparently they had like
some nice drinks there
oh
I I
they're moving don't don't don't don't
roast my aim
let's go the horse
poor Horseman
oh
I hope I didn't hit the horse
um
what do you guys think of maid Cafe is
they're nice for men it's more for men I
don't even know like I mean it's not
like they're like Japan quality
made cafes usually they're
um
like yeah not that good
I did hit the horse no never tried
before
I think the the make cafes in Japan are
cute like proper ones but the ones of
conventions I don't know
anyway we cleared the path let's go
why I can't control this [\h__\h] horse
so hard to control
yeah I don't know
it doesn't exist here not interested
they don't quite get it yeah
maybe I should join one and or maybe I
should organize or like create one
I'll be a manager of a maid Cafe at the
convention because I I feel like with my
management with my direction I could
make it real more and more killing like
for real for real
only I know what's best
it's like I'm starting to manage a idle
company but no it starts small with a
with a maid Cafe which I I feel like you
know it provides similar type of
healing and names for similar kind of
um
values there's a chest over there
what the [\h__\h] is that sound
oh the beans beans the bees
that I heard those
I'm gonna try to get up here
sort of yeah I mean you know being cute
and being say so you know that kind of
stuff
what are you guys doing
oh a slime thanks toolin
easy
the beans
hmm
I don't know I'll leave it not worth it
man
where's my horse
well we don't need this right now let me
explore it a little bit I feel like I'm
I'm fine with like actually not making
too much story progress today
I kind of want to do like a chill part
today I think
but while still progressing the story a
little bit I'm gonna be gonna plan for
the next two hours oh where are you
going
I have a safe flight please do not open
the emergency exit uh right after
landing don't ever don't ever
don't ever open it unless you're in an
emergency you know
who's supposed to be here
oh wait call up we know Caleb don't we
they're calling adult people apartment
name for it apt name for it I'd say
strange words fell from the sky onto the
plans this sort of thing is happening
over Hyrule unfortunately the neighbor I
know my home will harm but such an event
is sure to have caused major damage
elsewhere the more outlandish rumors
suggest that Hyrule Castle has risen
into the sky rather difficult to credit
that one what could have caused all this
I received a visitor he was a researcher
from some outfit calling themselves it's
a nice story team he claimed to be
merely passing through by area but
clearly he had come to draw on my
expertise
Northwest of his house the ring ruins oh
um
he joined them okay
you left some stuff here
do open the door okay it was no have you
guys heard of the story like uh I think
it was a Korean Airline
um
like they landed and then
five minutes
before they would have been let out or
so dude opens or dude or a person I
don't know why they did it
opened the emergency exit why why I feel
like even if it's your first time to fly
you have common sense
to know that you're not supposed to open
any doors on your own unless it's a door
to the restroom
like what is your huh oh oh I didn't
read the actual article I heard it from
my friend but was the reason that they
were being suffocated from the air in
the but still
a classroom if it was a claustrophobia
thing okay but then still like you can't
open that you talk to the cabin
attendant or so get up and talk to don't
do something so it's ridiculously stupid
so stupid that's [\h__\h] common sense
that you don't do that honestly oh my
God the more I think about it the more
upset it makes me like unless it was a
prank okay I cannot see like why people
would do such a stupid ass climb
I'm saying climb climb link climb
yeah
um
common sense that 10 years ago
it's so obvious like it says don't open
but um if apparently there's a really
huge fine
can I catch these
nope there's a really huge fine if you
do [\h__\h] like this so
get [\h__\h]
Bass
turn up the base oh [\h__\h] I'm gonna
suffocate I'm the best of getting gonna
drown
holy [\h__\h] that's a strong uh strong
okay drowned
okay
um
oh there's someone there
let's go let's go let's go let's go oh
is that another enemy camp
um
I don't care about it oh
anyway
[Music]
um
speaking language of the ancient gods I
am
uh
left or right
I go this way
seems right uh what was I saying oh yeah
come on
yeah my friend
my friend was
um performing in a play like a theater
play like she's in this like theater
group that does like a convention
performances like not dancing also it's
just like theater kind of plays for
animes they always like choose an anime
and then for the whole year they go to
conventions to show off that play and
they've been doing pretty well and like
people are pretty hyped about it it
seems and yeah yeah and they had this
one about Demon Slayer
and I didn't watch Demon Slayer so I
have no idea what's going on but I
watched it anyway for my friend yeah
but you know it was like so immersed and
breaking because Demon Slayer is like
pretty popular in general at conventions
there were so many Demon Slayer
[\h__\h] you there were so many Demon Slayer
um uh cosplayers
hey my father was special over here
maybe there was a Kodak or something
foreign
[Music]
interesting area interesting area
trees are weak yep no no they kind of
available
King horse
it's not a flex horse at all I'm just
embarrassing myself with this horse
and right
right there you go
move on
yeah
um so what was immersion breaking is
that like since this was a small
convention that only had basically one
room
um
one big haul
like the place the stage was like open
and people
because they were kind of not many paths
to walk around it it seemed kind of like
far away to walk around the stage in the
audience they always were walking
everybody was walking through between
the audience seats and stage and the
stage was kind of low
so it was very very annoying to me
and you know some would walk through
slowly like they didn't give a [\h__\h] uh
like they didn't know what's happening
and some would walk through very fast
and run some would do a Naruto run I
guess because we're at a convention
that's what you do
uh
uh yeah and and and okay I mean I
understand there's not many paths
through
to go through but you know you see
they're doing a theater thing so maybe
you could try to walk somewhere else oh
wow okay you get used to it
because it was a really long play one
and a half hours
but then
then
let me eat something and solve this
puzzle what could we eat
maybe this
um
every now and then a lot of
Demon Slayer cosplayers would walk
through which is like why why is this
Demon Slayer cosplayer here when they're
also on stage it was just immersion
breaking and some of them
you know there's like for example like a
muscular
um character I don't know what they're
all called but there's this muscular
it's actually two characters that are
supposed to be kind of muscular I guess
but the the
one you know they were all great actors
and it was a good play
but the ones that were passing by
were actually
um some of them were like aesthetically
like for example more mus muscular
that actually should already do the
trick
maybe more muscular than the ones on
stage
you know so it's like oh
oh
this this one's way bigger and way more
musculine um
I don't know it was kind of weird to see
them
continuously run by and some of them
passed like five times in one and a one
and half an hour five times the same
person a lot of them were always the
same people passing by over and over
from one side to another
oh my God and then some of them would
have this really smart look like
we'll have a smug look
hit it I hit I felt like some of them
did it on purpose yeah
not everybody but some of them I feel
like they would
they would do this
okay look I'm doing the same cosplay as
what you're looking at on stage right
now huh funny funny look at me look at
me I belong on stage look look
man
maybe I'm overthinking it nobody annoyed
me man man oh man
but it was the problem with the venue
because
even I before the play something else
was going on there
and is this gonna work yes nice first
try
something else was on on happening on
the stage and and I had to run over
because I saw my friends on the other
side and I didn't know where to go
because like everything was like placed
in such big blocks that running around
would add like a lot of extra time for
me to pass by but
I made myself small
yeah I made myself small when when going
over to the other side and and the thing
that was happening on stage was anyway
uh nothing was happening on stage it was
happening on the screen which was much
higher than the stage so I was not like
obstructing anyone's View and I was not
the only one
running over anyway but
um anyway I wasn't obstructing anyone's
view because it was really high up okay
um
I became Musical
oh I know who knows even I even know
that wow
my friends
you know we are this friend Circle so we
were supporting our friend on stage and
my friends some of them watched the
anime
so they were like giving me a few
explanations of what the [\h__\h] was going
on
[Music]
is the one who's in the Box because
apparently uh she's a demon and if she's
hit by daylight she will die so that's
why she has to go into the box
huh wow somebody help me
okay
from one
of you being attacked by the squirrel
[Laughter]
alert come on okay
you good now
oh cupcake hmm no I think carrot cake is
pretty decent
I never eat it but oh speaking of cake
my tangent another tangent it's just a
quick one just a side note actually
I went to the to the big supermarket and
I found something that I wasn't even
planning on buying yeah yeah but perfect
because I kind of wanted it
um
yummy uh I saw I saw
a typed
um
time for froggy
mmm froggy froggy froggy froggy froggy
there it is
does it already work a tight uh form why
it doesn't work yeah
I wanna go up here
it's hard for him attack form you know
where you can
um serve it already in the form like the
the the
bottom
the bottom the bottom is like separate
oh [\h__\h]
ing whatever
and you know what I wanted that because
I told you the other day the other day I
told you about the extra butter they
sent in my hello beep recipe and I sent
a recipe for a cake a tight yeah
so now I have the the pan for it
so now I can make the cake the tide oh
my God this is
oh let's go
let's go yeah I want to make the cake
soon
I have the butter and and the pan I just
now need all the ingredients
oh my God it looks so nice with the
shroom slit up
I thought you guys were about rice
is shrooms your thing I didn't realize
foreign
just keep on following me
an apple tree
yeah I'll make um an apple album tart I
think
very nice oh can I take these probably
not
wow cute it's pretty
carrots they're farming a lot here Mumbo
Mumbo I thought the mushroom lamp was
talking
no matter the weather or the time of day
wait he looks like a chef is that like a
chef hat
I'm always here checking out the scene
oh Manny what's the matter you can tell
me weirdly handsome dude you look like
you've been places showing things
peaceful and Old Village but it's a
jungle out there in the world that's why
I stick around here uh out in the scene
making sure no strangers put the moves
on Mrs ivy well I mean that's why make
sure new strangers come in from outside
to distribute the peace ivy
huh
you forgot to miss oh is that miss Mr
Mrs miss miss miss
Ivy is the poster girl for the East Wind
General stool
there's no problem if you want to talk
to Mrs Ivy just keep the naive I just
moved here and won't somebody show me a
round active minimum
not that anyone could be as young guys
or fashionesque as me
by the way quick question
what kind of present do you think would
make her happy I'm not asking for me you
understand a friend of a friend wanted
advice and I'm having a tough time with
the answer
I just can't go ask her directly so oh I
feel like this Quest existed
and breath of the wild or a different
Zelda game before
already
I remember this
same guy
give up if you have to do the same thing
in the sequel even then you're doing
something wrong it seems
um
this is the Fashion Place
oh I've said multiple times now I can't
admit free customers at present
I want to see Cece's new stuff that's
not every day and mega famous fashion
designer debut uses new material
everything I'll hurt sad this was some
uh offices best work I'm so so sorry but
we only have one entry ticket remaining
and here I come
suddenly out of nowhere
and snatching it away from everyone
wait now I realize those hats that these
fashion ladies have been wearing are
also like mushroom inspired
I like this fashion
you go later
um what are you saying we kill some time
in the dive shop oh okay
elaboratory Ah that's why that's where I
go
huh
so now they all left and I can go in
awesome
thank goodness they gave up oh oh I'm
sorry to keep you waiting are you also a
tourists to come to see my sisters I
mean the new line of CC products as long
as it's just you you're free to go into
the shop CeCe herself is in there right
now in fact nothing we'll see is for
sale it's only an exhibition right now
start to disappoint
what kind of stuff do you have
oh
dad hat
I think could improve my britishness by
a lot
whoa amazing
Flawless anything else only the Hat
um
passionate old personal only
what do you got in there oh
oh okay I know we have the the left one
but what's the one on the right the blue
one with the white cuffs
she's stealing my clothes
um I said the royal guard set oh cool
another Practically Perfect Masterpiece
it's an excellent plot of the form from
every angle this is the sort of thing on
which I've built my diamond reputation
as the world renowned CC oh oh pardon me
are you an admirer here tomato
incomparable [\h__\h]
um I must say you don't seem to show any
sort of interest in fashion welcome to
Vintage Clothing the only Boutique in
the world which carries the CC brand and
if you aren't aware
[Music]
oh the very woman who changed his busty
Old Village into the birthplace of the
world fashion as proof I present to you
this
the sexy hat the newest and most
magnificent work by yours truly so say
oh
do you see that luxurious cloth do you
know wouldn't you call it the Pinnacle
of perfect Perfection this piece is so
special that I dare not assign a price
for it it's not for sale I shall only
part with it when I find someone truly
worthy of owning it only the most
depressive fashionists and high rules
trendiest Villages worthy of such a
crowd
hmm
once you're on this event I was trying
to use the village I don't remember
approving any new slogans for hatano oh
look who's here what can I do for you oh
Steve mayor Reed
and when I saw you I tried to stop him
from coming in like you asked but he
wouldn't take a note for an answer
you have to cut you have got to quit
later in the village with your weird art
pieces
maybe you don't is that
imagine you know we had to do some
serious [\h__\h] in other Villages imagine
here their problem is a very serious
problem that art littering of
fashionista is happening
laughs
maybe you'll not realize what plants
need their sleep too those eyesores are
so bright at night I like them that
they're keeping the veggies awake it's a
real problem for the crops
Foundation is it's proudest what are we
going to do if it fails
[Music]
there's no need to get so worked oh I
think some of the people who actually
like her art you know only be better to
hear her out I like it
don't fall for her line of twiddle she's
got everyone in Latino wrapped around
their finger already my duty is to look
after the village and that's what I mean
to do
looking after the village you say
oh do you supposed to uh you have to
thank for those rejuvenation
I didn't need rejuvenating Village is a
peaceful place where folks live quiet
lives that's the way they like it
no day then let us leave the matter to
the people to the Sun by Evan God
approach versus the major is quaint by
gun ways the citizens will decide which
Outlook will drive the future to the
Village by holding a mayoral election
you're calling for mayoral election sure
suits me I'll win it pretty easily
Sophie I allocate management of the
mayoral action to you
come on clavia I don't feel like
sticking around here any longer it's
time we headed back home
this questline is interesting well it
seems interesting but is it a sad class
oh you again I've got a long to-do list
of preparation for the memorial election
and the sooner I get started the better
the answer should go without saying oh
I'm on this island
oh if you haven't yet thrown in your lot
with either candidate then welcome to
team CeCe that Saddles that I trust it's
plain for all to see that I have a show
in for the next mayor or so one would
think
yeah there are straggles in this Village
still supporting read they need a mental
makeover and so I have a fabulous plan
to give out mushrooms to read supporters
synonym synonymous with CeCe brand
fungal fashion is the sexy way
the mushrooms I give them will paint
them inside and out with fresh vibrant
CC brand colors although Sophie and I
must mind this shop where will we find
someone we can trust to carry this out
um
I don't know can I do like both sides at
the same time
CC fashion
I do both
yeah okay cool well I have to okay
thank you Hylian shrooms times eight
okay
mushrooms are for the villagers uh we'll
just read supporters it's easy to
recognize them by how unstylish they are
ew disgusting my supporters are all
expert fashionisters I am don't there's
also no need to give them to Children
Travelers so any temporary residence
like the Chica research oh okay
none of the family no no children no
Travelers and no chica researchers oof
okay
eight eight people okay
[\h__\h] off
um
okay we'll do that but first
um we shall also
go to the ancient place
wait that's a unfashionable person
wouldn't you say
more or less I mean they're wearing the
Hat though
but they all wear them
are you one of those who can't see ah no
he's interested
the Mind behind it is my own
dad
oh
he's the dad
okay he's probably supporting his
daughter
anyway it's in the middle of the night
and it's raining so I'm guessing most
people are just not outside right now
which is a good time to go
further ahead
foreign
sound crispiness
is my horse able to come over here yeah
okay let's go
what was I saying before yeah convention
don't watch the play and then well I met
so many cute girls like I made new cute
girl friendships yesterday
very important don't you think
like I don't know what's going on but
recently
I'm like
hanging with so many cute girls and a
lot of them are much younger than me
which is kind of depressing
but
it's it's still nice they're also cute
um
hard work paying off oh wait you don't
hear the audio anymore what the [\h__\h]
yeah
that's [\h__\h] weird why
there we go
and and and and and
yeah hanging out with cute girls what
else did I do
hanging out with cute girls hanging out
with cute girls
what did I do
ah nothing
oh wow
I probably didn't do much more than that
and like uh I was kind of waiting for my
friend until
uh he would leave so that again I would
get a ride home
[Music]
um but my friend kinda
like stayed pretty long so I got a
little bit of the taste of the awkward
after party but just the beginning maybe
later it was more fun for them
hmm
but I didn't like it
there were not enough people really
anyway there were like five people or so
or ten in the dance area and the rest of
them were all by the drinking drinks
area
so hmm it's like you know a school ball
kind of awkward no one actually goes to
the dance floor
um
oh yummy
thankfully
you know we sat down at a table to talk
some more because we were in the middle
of talking
a lot with one another between friends
and then the friends realized oh right
that's [\h__\h] loud we can barely have a
conversation we're all screaming
so then we were like okay let's leave
finally
and I was driven home my friends also
were there
oh but you know what was an interesting
topic we had
that I am very very
interested in right now
because some of my friends are
photographed photographers and I also
like to do
photo editing in Photoshop
so just like yesterday or so maybe
Photoshop released a beta beta version
of their newest invention
it's like an AI thing within Photoshop
where you can add anything like they
they show it off like that that you can
add anything you can imagine to a photo
and like all the all the previews look
really convincing
uh however they use stuff from their own
database you know that's what I think
makes it very uh
convincing and and professional and it's
a relief
that they're used they use their own
stock photos because Photoshop has their
own stock photos the uh that you can use
if you have
a
Adobe product
so yeah it's ethical but that means also
that their database is not endlessly
huge either
and
but in the previews it looked like you
know it was plenty and you could do some
really cool things
and it would be edited in pretty
seamlessly pretty easily
yeah
yeah yeah yeah so uh we actually after
the convention we talked a lot about it
at the convention after the convention
meeting we talked about it
um as well like I got home and I was
[\h__\h] tired but I was still so curious
about it and I wanted to test it out but
I was too tired so I already was
chilling in bed and I called one of my
photographer friends and I'm like yo
you're on your PC right now okay show me
right now show me your desktop
and interestingly my friend actually was
about to check that stuff out anyway
at that time
so I was just watching you know but I I
was like do this try this try this and
that
can do it too I guess because I have uh
Photoshop legally I think you can only
Cur do it if you have it legally the bet
the beta the beta you can only have
access to it
if you have it legally oh my God it's
[\h__\h] hot
backseating
yeah so I want to try that too I just I
was too tired yesterday
um
uh
wait what am I doing why am I still
using
oh my God so many horses
um
here I need uh unable
I can't when you
of course I can
I can't which makes no sense I don't get
it
[Laughter]
what the [\h__\h] that backfired oh cause
I'm in the village technically ah
[\h__\h] hell
oh this looks like it's pretty deep
oh it wasn't too bad
uh why is this well so endlessly huge
anyway so we found out that it wasn't as
perfect and easy as it seemed to be in
like previous of course they only show
you know where it really works the cases
where it really works well but like for
example we would try changing like hair
color on the picture so basically what
you do is you you Circle the area of a
selection tool
where you want it to be or you want to
make a change and then you type in what
you want
[Music]
and
we would type in like change hair color
to this to blue or so
and I have the biggest laugh because you
know we wait we wait we wait it loads a
little bit and then it it switches
it gives you a couple options yeah
but it completely replaced the head with
a different person's head and the hair
wasn't even blue
but it looks so
and then we had like different options
of different people's heads
stuck onto my
uh onto the the photo yeah so like it
doesn't work so well
um but we tried other things like adding
Hair Works decently you just have to
give it a few tries but other stuff
again doesn't work so well like we tried
doing some adjustments on clothes
that did not work so well at all
um when it doesn't do so well actually
is removing things I feel like it does a
better uh adding things
then removing things
yeah it's all got bumps and and maybe
they need more stock photos to work with
hello foreign
hello
[Laughter]
oh [\h__\h] hell hello
uh what
um
[Music]
yeah
um
what it did pretty well is for example
if you like select an area in the
background and you're like you you type
in trash can then it was pretty
smoothly naturally
add a trash can
to the background and kind of like also
makes it so that it matches the overall
lightening and colors and all that
um
attack up with six holy [\h__\h]
in the picture
like the fact that it matches the light
and the shadows and everything
that I think is very valuable
you
yeah why a trash can I don't know I mean
whatever or like what you can't really
do is like
um add anime stuff or so
like drawn stuff this is more like for
photo manipulation not art manipulation
which maybe will relieve a lot of
artists
because
adobe's
stock photos are just stock photos
no
um
hello
no illustrations or anything yeah
photos they have permission to use it
and
you can't do like like anime stuff with
it no no no
um
maybe they won't eventually have
illustrations who knows but um are we
are we done with this am I going
backwards now I don't know
oh wait that seems new no no it's not on
it did I see everything
yeah there's other AI for that but
generally the Photoshop uh stuff is uh
oh one thing was weird
um
generally they have a a like a like a
function
to not have people use this in an evil
way
uh there's guidelines
and it stops
people from using it like to
make like risky photos for example of
someone or whatever I don't know
um
that would damage someone's reputation
or whatever you know
you want to know how I am guessing
because we kind of we we found out about
it by accident we weren't trying to
trigger it
but I think it recognizes like skin
color and all that kind of stuff
and when you're trying to remove
something or add something like that
uh it will tell you
uh yo no stop this violets are
guidelines here are our guidelines
please read them we're not letting you
do this but the problem is that the
trigger for it is very sensitive so
basically if we had a picture where we
wanted to remove like
um
uh
like
some trash for example that was on skin
yeah
and uh
basically my my friend first circled it
and then didn't type in anything he was
just hoping that it would just disappear
like recognize what we want to do
sometimes it doesn't
um on its own reads your mind
but it already said sorry this is
against our guidelines even though we
just circled that area
and it's uh it didn't do anything
yeah I just said sorry you can't do it
then I'm I'm like okay I tried typing in
what you actually want so we type in
remove trash from skin for example
and it was still refusing to do it
is this the same well that I just
entered
so even though we weren't trying to do
anything bad it was telling us hey you
can't do this you tried to do something
bad read out guidelines
this violates it
so well
kind of too sensitive
[Laughter]
oh cute it's a classroom maybe there's a
quest here I don't know but I'm kind of
busy we should activate that shrine
oh the dragon is so close holy [\h__\h]
videos
[Music]
it's blemish
no I didn't mean pimples I meant like
some some kind of I don't know like a
sticker or whatever just anything that
maybe a piece of clothing or so okay
that again that's
oh armored carp
I'm not I'm not trying to remove like a
shirt or bra fully
look like a small part you know
something that bothers you because it
shouldn't be there oh [\h__\h]
please please it takes so long to load
up the stamina
[Music]
um
that's the problem when you have so much
stamina it also takes up so much of it
okay yeah the AI clowns table apart yet
but I feel like if we had so much
trouble a bit I feel like a lot of
people oh [\h__\h]
are going to complain about it and they
might make it less sensitive then
[Music]
but inferior it works pretty simple
like some things that we tried out
worked like the trash can and adding
hair or whatever and other things were
absolute failure
um
you could for example easily probably
add like Road lines on the ground
or add some signs you know do some
composition like Photo composition to
make a photo more interesting
you know
I can see that coming in handy
being useful in some ways
did
Ahmed
do this Shrine on stream
somehow it looks a bit yeah yeah it
looks familiar I saw her doing this a
little bit
so early
no I guess
depends on what you prioritize huh
was it for the rice eh
um
what was the thing here though
[\h__\h] hell I can't breathe
a connection I guess wait ah I think I
remember what I saw
now it's rolling
um ah
I don't know if AMA did it like this
oh wait no we should maybe attach
this is what she did
I think
you can choose that what do you mean
bringing them up by attaching
one by one
to each other
or attaching them to the big roll you
know yeah you can
I don't know if I would have gotten this
idea if I didn't watch I'm a stream but
you know
never thought of that if the ammo way
I have a channel
well how many balls do we need anyway I
just know we need balls I don't know for
what I think I stopped watching
in that moment
it's the arm away
I don't know what we even needed for
only one this
now
then she did it for nothing
as well
oh God is it gonna fall off
oh
they're stopping there wait you only
need one then what did AMA doing for ah
because there's a treasure chest in
there did she know though I don't think
she knew or maybe the chat told her
that's why she did it
um hi oh dear oh dear oh
uh yeah um many balls
I am I am offering many balls which one
do you want
that one okay
[Laughter]
she turns chat off until she finishes
the shrine wow okay
let me find the treasure chest then
ayabi
time to attach some more balls
what was I talking about before this ah
the AI thing
yeah I find it really cool this seems
like a big new feature that
photographers and editors will have lots
of fun with so
um I wonder maybe it will help me create
thumbnails who knows
I mean
I'll test it out
yeah you can test it out and then see if
it helps you and then sometimes it will
sometimes it probably will not help you
but at least it's for free like if you
have
Photoshop already you don't have to pay
extra
I think
I see the chest
oh sure
yep
[Music]
ah
um okay we have space for that even I'm
surprised
we got the chest we got the ball is
there more
Photoshop yeah Adobe is very expensive
and I feel like it was already expensive
before they changed to a subscription
mode but now ever since this is a
subscription I feel like it's even more
expensive oh that's it oh
okay
[Music]
um
well I can write it off so I thought
okay why not
why not
you know I need a lot of the programs
I'm using uh Adobe Audition
for audio recording I'm using Premiere
Pro for video editing I'm using
Photoshop for
thumbnails Etc
uh what else do I use I don't know do I
use anything else
here's Affinity photo
oh I think I tried that one
that one or another one
I feel like I did
um
well I basically have everything oh
actually you know what I like the the
fonts that come for free with the
um subscription
uh which is very helpful for me because
just like game permissions I can also
not just use fonts randomly freely
uh even if they're offered for free so
staff tones to use the Adobe fonts
because those are safe to use
and so I am using them quite often
they do have a decent choice
[Music]
um
yeah for example you know when they call
this
actual picture I feel like that would
make it look really pretty
that should work pretty smoothly
[\h__\h] hell I wish I could breathe
and one second I'm gonna close my wind
my my door
ah
air oh give me give me a minute outside
of my plans
[Music]
foreign
no
but maybe the air pillow will help
um uh oh
kill them
probably not get out
get out because they're part of the
village
I'm too scared to try
there's a whole herd attacks me
what was I talking about
what the [\h__\h] stop running stupid ass
horse
laughs
no I wasn't wandering berries I was
wandering mostly veggies but my plants
are somewhat alive
I bought special Earth soil
for my my blueberries my Heidelberg Oh
They'll be fun so yeah
I bought special soil I hope it works I
hope it works out
the veggies like tomato and girl can
cucumber
work fine with normal plants soil
apparently
but um
the blueberry is
needs
some special stuff
our Channel pasture
can I go up from here yeah where is this
thing
did I miss the red path
I feel like I missed it
oh
the path which one this one not this one
right
doesn't really feel like a path
a racing Kodak
I'm gonna get you I'm gonna get you I'm
gonna get you come here come here
I got it
when I got 12.
actually quite a lot now
what's up here
maybe a bird's nest
no nothing okay
okay the was it the other word climb the
cliff behind you and you should be on
the path but I want to take my horsey oh
God oh God
that's so embarrassing dying like this
oh it's Link's old house in this area
ocean
um okay we should check it out maybe it
has some cool stuff for us
Hedgehog
all right they only drop nuts I forgot
that
okay okay
um
let me try to find the right path that I
can access with my horse although
maybe there's this path let me just
follow and see where it goes because
we're all pretty close
mmm
[Music]
oh yeah it goes up
I think
yo
now that's good enough
I'll climb from here
mysterious place
uh I should be able to make this with my
stamina
okay
after GTA we don't press up yeah I am
traumatized by what you guys have done
to me
we made it I remember this place from
breath of the wild too
but has it changed
it's been too long I wouldn't really
know
ancient Tech Lab
oh
hello
Robbie wow what a pleasant morning it
changed a little
this used to be prayers left ah yeah
no it's only for Robbie
ew oh pure pad lab poor touring is ready
for us to do some great things together
first let's get the sensor working let's
all take a moment oh
I don't have to do anything for you
I thought I'd had to do something for
him yeah that was easy just coming to
her channel was enough
um
now the sensor will make a sound if
there are shrines near you whoa
cool
all right now that I've installed the
sensor how about you walk around the lap
to test out if it reacts
Shrine of light nearby indeed
it did
it
oh you want me to find it
is it it can't be the one that I just
went to right yeah
what I already talked to you and you
didn't like react particularly okay hold
up right here
oh walk in the direction oh okay
I thought it was outside
threatening something right here now
y'all
this part is when I'll have to walk
slowly oh
[Music]
um
the sensor must be detecting your Shrine
down the slope in front of the lab is
there really one that close by there
must be because my Creations are perfect
unless they get broken in some way now
why don't you go check down just a
little bit in the direction that the
sensor was indicating
so is it the shrine I already did a
camping surely they would use a shrine
for this example that I can't find
otherwise
we should activate that Tower but damn
that looks difficult
it's a different one okay
uh
okay
I lost track oh
maybe it's
and the sky above us
wait is it is there a well
it's inside no
is it on top
he would know if there's a shrine on top
of his house right
it stopped
oh no no it's back it's back it's
getting stronger is it in here
no
but wait there's lore pure
hell yeah I grew frustrated with being
treated like a child so I received my
age booster experimentations in Earnest
oh the anti-aging device reversed more
than 100 years in an instant so I
reflected on that result and moderated
the output when I cautiously exposed
myself to its race I returned to my 20
year old form just as I had hoped
success I'm so happy that I can once
again reach high places without using a
jet pack my 20 year old body doesn't
suffer from sleepless nights at
researching and what's more my skin is
perfect no complaints
free volumes of my diary are hidden away
now I'll place the last one at the
northeastern edge of akala the lab there
is perfect for hiding things it's just a
remote location I'm sure no one will
ever come across it
foreign
tell me the locations in your diary
if someone finds one of them they'll
find the other one too
anyway it was really strong some at some
part
of the bridge
I guess I was walking in the right
direction oh
what not this way
maybe this on top
is one of those ancient robots up there
I know I know it might not be that up
there but look look this is actually
pretty special oh
the last remains
oh let me collab I wanna see
yeah up the arms
don't tell me there's no Kodak up there
they should
I should Place one there
finally finally my Kodak sensors are
also working
hmm
the view is good too
[Music]
no no no the one Tower is there
which should be of this area
oh one is far far this one uh the ones
that I haven't found yet though are lit
up right
so that one is like over here somewhere
should I ping it I mean this one's like
pretty obvious but yeah sure uh
uh
no
oh
hi
big face
uh that one I guess I found
oh
that one I still have marked red
oh and this one
okay
what's that red mark oh I've won it's so
far away
okay here is
um
a tower and here is
a tower I'm gonna start walking
um yeah I don't know if we should go
there right away
um
but first we need to find that shrine
what is it
ah
I don't get the direction I don't I
don't even I don't even get it yet
wait
can I blow something up here and it's
underneath yes
yeah okay it's pinging as well oh
Thanks
new members welcome
there's so many apples
the chicken she used to like these apple
trees
it's an apple chicken maybe in chicken
meat and its eggs will taste special
if it eats apples
thank you
is it trying to tell me something I mean
I would have known oh [\h__\h] without you
[Music]
get a candid read some Forest cave
there it is
I was fast oh there's an opening here
are you missing your stone no
no okay so we can just enter normally no
us
there you go that took a while with the
I guess it takes a while with the
boomerang
I think when I attach the stone to it I
just had no other weapon to attach the
stone to so I just went with that cave
oh it's an ax on the hammer oh
oh okay
oopsie
um
Ransom is massive spelled
is that why you guys said it's important
no
[Music]
ah somehow I thought maybe the master
sword is in here but like I mean we kind
of do have the muscle so don't wait
no wait it's gone now
but hey
interesting magic scepter ah I kind of
attached a a gem to it but I can attach
a gem to anything why would I
particularly attach it to this
took it away from me she's taking good
care of it I think hopefully
hopefully hopefully
oh
the fourth Shrine today
nice
looking got stamina or a heart you guys
would probably go for stamina
hmm
I'll think about it
Africa I don't see my little things with
a pinky I'll read this another time
maybe especially when I can breathe
better
today is pretty bad I don't know what
like triggers it
oh
I always want to catch the bunny but I
don't know if you can
no I don't have allergies
whatever I'll survive
how long have has it been only three
hours oh man
I want to scream long
wait is that the whole well it's a
different hole
oh
what is
didn't I
hey this was already open
and I rode past it
because I entered from a different side
right
and but I also rode past this
how did I not see this I guess it was
dark right
I'm so blind yeah
there's ducks I'm gonna get stuck
cute speaking of dogs did you
his new outfit
she's dressed as a chicken baby chick oh
my God it's so cute it's like a baby
chick pajama honestly if I ever did a
pajama outfit I would probably do
something like that too
but now I feel like me and somebody
already did it I can't do the same but I
mean chicks are kind of my thing so
but she looks so adorable
doesn't she
oh my God
it was so cute
you know there's a lot of like loot
pajamas out there but super this is so
adorable
so stay so and challenge the duckling I
think it's more of a chick not a
duckling but it would make more sense if
she made it a duckling is it a duckling
it just looks like a chick it doesn't
but don't ducklings look different
Oh No I gave me chick vibes
I guess we're just very similar in our
baby form
all right I want to get it tinkling uh
pajama
oh and ducks dive their head on the
water it's so cute
[Music]
Robert drumstick what's that also duck
what is that
I guess it's also a duck
so cute
music
I think I see eggs up there or something
else
do I
I feel like I see something
yeah I saw the nest actually
positive one either no
um
okay what are we doing should we go back
to Robbie
oh wait oh is that thing not an animal
you're looking for it
oh
wait oh [\h__\h]
I didn't even read what I was doing but
you were
supposed to
you're supposed to get it right I'm not
denying mushrooms are nice to look at
but to go from that to wearing them as
well and I'm not the only one who thinks
so the couple at the end didn't see eye
to eye about the same thing oh she's
giving me a hint who are the next people
I should ask nice
I guess it's tough times tough sometimes
to be married to someone of different
tastes than you but I can see you mean
well enough with the gift so I'm happy
to accept thanks but if you're here on
Farm business you'll have to talk to my
dad at the farm I need to get my hands
on a message bottle floating in the pond
quick I finally found the leather of my
great grandpa left but I can't reach it
my arms are too short okay that thing is
a it's a bottle
mmm
I mean I guess I have an idea
maybe another one
because I don't see any other tools
so how about we get it with
a long stick
no I'm not making a boat I'm making a
wait
there's tools
okay
well either way it would work I say
but
I like my stick idea
and that way my view will not be as
obstructed either
yeah that shall be
my technique
you think this will be long enough
actually dropped the Kodak uh Leaf I
think which I could use to make wind
with on the boat
that's kind of why I didn't do the boat
thing because I would have to use a
one of my own fans
my fans are very valuable to me
so I didn't want to do that but never
mind this is still not long enough
okay let's just use the boat
you you got what I was saying
did you get it you get it
okay
[Music]
um
where is it
oh wait do I have to attach it to a
weapon
oh hmm
I'll uh pick the other one back up again
in a minute
where it could be
here oh I have actually a couple
no I'm stupid
[Music]
so this is the perfect combination
it just makes sense
attaching it to a tree branch don't you
think so do I have to do it backwards
I would think so but I think we're just
still
a little bit too close
to the shore let's go
yeah
I need a sale
I don't have a sale do they
so what what's the recommended method
here
one more log would reach yeah what the
hell
foreign
man
okay my ax My Boomerang axes
being used quite a lot today
after all
okay
I shall do this
you think I will reach maybe even if I
stand on
my boat
it should work
yes
oh
yeah perfect
we got it
normally I don't want to do side quests
on stream but today I feel like doing
kind of a chill
type of Dallas stream
so why not
I unlock the best food
um you mean rice because I'm in hatino
yeah like that's the reason why I always
wanted to come here
oh it's cute it has like a glowing
flower attached to the bottle
not rice
oh
I'll see when I don't know okay I told
you whenever you're after I'm too busy
to oh
that's it
did you fish it out for me thank you
there should be a letter in the spot
with advice for getting a farm back on
its feet let's see here wait can I use
the farm
okay here we go oh hi Mrs Grant a great
my grand Grandpa Great Grandpa's little
handwriting his penmanship was so messy
that no one but him and his family could
read it oh I hadn't thought of that new
specialty with mayor
cheese fermentation mayor are we gonna
scrape off cheese off of the mayor's
feet
can't name too early
yes this could work sorry to run but I
want to put great grandfather's advice
into practice right away if you need me
I'll be back at the house
okay
I mean is that mayor
what else would why why would she be
connected to the mayor
and you know like we talked uh I think
girls talk is kind of at fault because
and girls taught me why
talked about
foot cheese didn't we
I think there was a topic somewhere
I think my hellbird yeah I don't know if
I really care about it
oh
should I give him
didn't she say something about
well he doesn't look fashionable
I mean he kind of does actually but not
the lane
that they meant
I'll try
it oh [\h__\h]
he seems to be a fan of CC well I mean I
probably have some of my own so if I
have to sacrifice some that's okay I
can't give it to wrong people oh okay
don't get me wrong I appreciate the gift
but me and my daughter Queen and oh
don't care much about girls okay okay
if you told me you were here to pick up
some fresh milk I'd have been in a tight
spot makes no make no mistake don't tell
me you haven't heard of my Farm's fresh
milk can I get fresh milk for free here
or is it like special not the goat milk
with like special milk
I've been having trouble getting my
hands on acorns oh that's why there's so
many squirrels around here maybe
sometimes I dropped acorns they're
carrying the cheeks cute
I need at least three
I got those I got you man no apparently
I don't got you one second oh my God so
many cyclists
I'm gonna get some more
you shitty Square let me let me get
those acorns
it ran towards me
so it just heard the shot it didn't know
where it came from
all right all right all right the next
shot I will make it worthwhile
foreign
s right
I would think so
oh no that's a goat
that's a lizard
hi goat what's up
yeah good
are you anyone's goat
or are you just yeah goat
how did that lizard not notice me
and run away earlier
um
where are the squirrels I find so many
other animals but where are the screen
Wells
I mean if the animal runs right into me
can you really blame me
[Music]
um
put this to jump please show yourself to
me
I don't see him maybe I should sleep
to have a better View
I don't see anything running away from
me either
um
all right instead of the squirrel
let's first go inside
and talk to the lady
[Music]
there she is oh she cooked something we
let her cook and the result is
oh you shut up look at this
[Music]
cheese
potato cheese
I think I didn't see cheese before in
the game did she just invent cheese
that message my great grandpa Left
Behind had the recipe it's springy on
the outside but melty on the inside and
so delicious you'll think you're
dreaming it does look really good but
back to the reason I called you here
it's you know I couldn't have made it
without you so I want you to be the
first to have one cute oh
this is the kind of cheese that I like
because I don't like all the moldy
looking cheese
I like more normal looking cheese like
these but especially my favorite cheese
might be mozzarella and burrata if you
can even consider that cheese and and um
but just normal butter cheese
I really like normal at least here we
call it butter cheese
um
oh and I love
uh what's it called again
e
[Music]
h
no uh I forgot oh my God
oh goat cheese is nice too
no what oh my God my brain I mean the
very the very orange one
yes
why was I thinking it started with e
weird
I love cheddah I like gowda too I guess
you know but my favorite sorry The
Buttery the really mild ones
[Music]
um
so can I get more of this here now
River renovation is this gonna be a
cheese place
I can pick up cheese are you gonna sell
cheese
oh
it is a shop now the hotel Cheese Shop
nice the next step is to get those folks
over at the General Store to start
stalking it that reminds me you won't
get this offer anywhere else but around
here I'll give you some fresh milk and
some rupees
I made the dream my great grandpa gave
up come true and this Farm will be
busier than ever in the bargain oh yeah
I'll come again
I mean you give me milk instead of
rupees if I sell something
ah you mean
ah
ah no you accept fresh milk as a trade
um
wait but am I not supposed to get milk
from your dad or so
after I give him acorns oh wait look at
this oh you can make a pizza
oh my God
what I didn't know about the pizza yet
okay
we gotta get those acorns
I'm so excited about cooking in this
game you don't even understand
let's go
how many do I have
um
oh that's not I thought that was an
acorn
the tree nut is not an acorn
where are the acorns
foreign
I have one
okay gotta kill two squirrels you and
your twin love watching me really thank
you your twin
ooh speaking of twins
um
you guys want to know
the twins are kind of the twin tangent
is kind of um
it's not really a tangent but it's kind
of connected to the
um Discord kitten tangent that you guys
might wanna know right my life was off
for two days
I have made a tweet
where you guys were questioning where I
suddenly got this topic from
right
well
so I tweeted what's uh what's a Discord
kitten
and even though Mommy answered me mumai
was not the one actually I'm sorry to
disappoint or maybe it should not even
be disappointing but a relief
but this that didn't come out of a
conversation
with a whole life member no no no no no
I went into a little YouTube a cringe
YouTube rabbit hole
don't don't you could upset the
squirrels
um oh what
happened
I caught that Beetle before Oh wait
there's another one I think
time for my stealthy armor
where is it
I am super stealthy now there's no way
this Beetle can find me
uh yeah
bladed Reno rhino beetle
okay so do continue please okay okay go
go again
um
we got those two and so I was watching
some YouTube videos
[Music]
from some guy called Vladimir
who was pranking people on Omegle by
dressing up as something that could be
described as a Discord kitten sometimes
and uh he really looked like super super
cute the only thing that he fails at is
the voice the voice is not so good
but then you know eventually he would
reveal himself
uh like show his really wide chest and
his really buff arms and be like what do
you mean my name is Vladimir but
you know it was quite funny I like like
Omegle prank videos every once in a
while they're quite funny to me
but it's always the same like he does
the same thing over and over and over
again
so it gets kind of old
but uh
it was quite funny and then and then you
know the the term Discord kitten came up
a few times like he didn't really dress
up purposefully like a Discord kid and I
think more like an e-girl was the goal I
don't know if that if there's a
difference
but
um sometimes the people who would find
him on Omegle
would be like oh my God it's a this
Edition or whatever do you want to be my
Discord kitten oh my God you know they
would freak out and I was like the whole
time is like am I missing something here
what is a Discord kitten
yeah
and
I found out then if I see you guys
we're freaking out a little bit too much
I would say though your reaction didn't
quite it made me think it was like
something really really really really
really crazy
wasn't as crazy as you guys made me
think it lies in your reactions you were
all like no
no okay no stop no
like as if I just Unleashed
hellfires
but yeah I I figured out what it is and
still I don't I I think I mean first of
all I don't understand the value of
Discord related items such as nitro
like
oh I I don't understand why you
would need to be someone's Discord
kitten
to get Nitro what I don't I don't get it
I mean is that really something
you would want that desperately
um
apparently apparently it is but I can't
relate
I don't get it
like like it's not even like it's not
even like it's I don't know like the car
kitchen or so getting a free car or so
which I would understand more but like
Discord that's not even something you
can use in the real world you're you're
asking for something that you can only
use in Discord
I don't get the value
yeah but I understand what it is now
this code is real to me
for internet addicts
where are all the squirrels though I
don't care about Discord kittens I care
about Discord squirrels right now
why did they all disappear there were so
many maybe we should do something else
for now
[Music]
shall we
should I go back to Robbie do you think
he wants to talk to me again
probably right
oh here's the real path
there's a Kodak there too and a weird
tree that's very stressed
you can chop down trees does that don't
bring squirrels down
oh I knew it okay my sensors for
collects today are much better than
usual
nice
acorns oh it drops acorns well done
isn't this big this tree kind of too big
yeah these kind of big ass trees you
can't chop huh
anyway sorry guys it's disappoint but at
least that it made a really
interesting tweet apparently
people were very entertained by it seems
okay
maybe I can get acorns here was that
even a squirrel
maybe even no
tree branch
and apples
is it specific
um
trees or
oh the connection to the twins was
basically just because I was watching
those videos I got like some more Omegle
related recommendations
and I mean this one was really boring to
be honest so I only watched one and I
was like yeah this is not interesting
there's like two actually triplets
who are doing like a triplet prank on
Omegle
they just sit there in the Parker like
one sits there and then he leaves the
screen quickly and and quickly comes
back in a different Parker and then the
Omegle people are supposed to be like
whoa whoa how'd you do that just changed
color
but everybody pretty quickly catches on
to what why and what's going on
I think it's kind of lame
yeah but they do it with triplets so I
guess it's super special but no it's
kind of boring it's kind of lame I like
the the e-girl one more
anyway Robbie I'm back
Robbie you still here
oh yeah
do you find Shrine yeah
just listen to it sounds and you find
your way to the nearby Shrine what you
found it I expect nothingness
wow
I've told you what you need to know
about that sensor but I fear is gone in
one ear and without the other so hang on
a minute
oh and we may have indeed done that
oh very good oh
am I gonna get other sensors as well now
you begin to see the true potential no
I've already saw it before
twins pranks is cool but they get away
with triplet spring what no
what
actually like every time I watch Omegle
videos like that I keep on thinking I
want to do something like that as a
YouTuber
but not live because obviously that's
very dangerous on the side like Omegle
um but like a cut video version
oh
why why
it's funny
what the heck is this kid and my twin
sister connect with that word
and my twin sisters what
you mean Omegle what
please don't join the cringe pranks I
don't even know how how I would be
pranking them I don't I can't even think
of a specific way of pranking them but
just by being a YouTuber on Omegle I
feel like people would freak the [\h__\h]
out like oh my God are you are you an
anime
thank you
hmm
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] you're an
enemy well
act like an AI
are you anime oh what whoa are you like
Sailor Moon
that would be rude people yeah like so
that uh Vlad guy a lot of people are
really rude too
it's so weird like
laughs
like especially girls would see him and
be like oh my God you're so ugly you you
failed and Alive oh you're terrible like
oh my God they would like immediately
the moment they see him like roast him
to death and then then he brings out his
Vladimir voice and shows his muscles and
suddenly suddenly they're like wow
so cool I love you like once they find
out it's a guy at first they're like
kind of like I would say jealous of how
cute he is or she like in that moment
they still think it's a she
and then once he shows who he really is
then they show some like interest and
respect and and and appreciation
um like those moments really make me
cringe so hard
man I know we're near done yet I have
some more prototypes of extra features
and can get them on your pure pad
anytime that is with some help from you
getting some final data I need an order
no do you want those pictures those
photographs
because I'm not gonna provide you with
those
let me tell you that
what do you want in exchange
including the most essential one the
travel Medallion feature that lets you
oh that one's important though unless
you set up gates for instant travel
anywhere there's also a Heroes path mode
okay I
was gonna say I don't care about that
but I saw some videos like at the end
you could see at the end of the game you
could see like when you walked and it's
kind of cool kind of cute
finally Sandstorm plus which helps you
find more than shrines
um
test data
oh oh I can choose which one I want
first
um
[Music]
either the travel Medallion or the
sensor Plus
or would you guys go for first
it's maybe sensor Plus
I learned very good thinking oh I can do
all at once okay
um you select what you want Lipa blue
you need to no uh five types of monsters
okay okay that's not so bad okay okay
five
and then the others are maybe like five
types of food or whatever
needs
up in the northeastern corner is there a
car or ancient Tech Lab which is also my
home that's where my prototype of the
travel Medallion feature is I started to
work on it back there what the [\h__\h] why
don't you just do it here
I do I would get it myself but word is
that some dangerous trespassers have
made themselves at home there oh
that's why I'd like to have you with all
your great talents go there and fetch my
travel Medallion prototype oh I guess I
don't I just have to go get it like kill
some enemies and I'll get it for free
oh
the journey back he's gonna make it easy
oh he's gonna make a portal here okay
okay okay it's a bit of a hike to get
there I didn't do that until much later
yeah I won't do it right away
the photos of the monsters though we can
do that like today
while we're doing everything else
I'll ask what he wants for the herald
path though
data from 15 final caches I feel like I
already have that
yeah I must
nice but the heroes path won't be
visible to us until we finish the game
right
so
[Music]
you can now use the map to see the path
you've taken on your journey footstep by
footstep you can save around 256 hours
of gameplay if you exceed this amount of
Play-Doh the oldest process will be
erased as new ones are added hmm
do you guys think I will
have more hours than that hopefully not
can I watch this anytime
not just at the end oh okay
it's like watching you know the the
process of me painting in past part two
it's kind of satisfying to watch stuff
like that isn't it
sped up
[Music]
um
oh
I don't why is the icon just such a
normal icon of a person
so modern too
I can use it to show what I've done
asking I don't know I feel like it's
kind of fat too fast and too like
hard to see what I actually did
okay well maybe we should watch it once
when how does it work
oh
and I want to go from the start how do I
go from the start ah oh
foreign
oh my god oh that's a lot of devs she
keeps on screaming when that happens
oh
you're gonna make it any faster no oh my
God that takes a lot of time
uh yeah okay
huh
okay we don't have to watch the whole
thing
um
okay we did that
that's why you guys said that was
important all right next shall we go to
the tower next
and then maybe to Zora Village
so uh where are we where would we be
going anyway
wait a second let's activate
the regional phenomena
it is in the above region okay
um sounds like a plan all right let's
can I fly over there
confused
let's activate tooling
it's such a chat like even when you
don't need them for flying
in the moment like he's actually pretty
helpful
for
um
oh
for fighting as well
like he will actually help quite a bit
not always in the very moments where you
need him the most but
you know
unexpectedly
unexpectedly yeah he does good headshots
especially with like annoying bats or or
little like enemies that you don't want
to bother with right now he will just
kill while you're doing something else
sometimes when you get
attacked by like five enemies at once
it's also pretty helpful
and he does like cute little dotting
damage when you're fighting a Lionel
once in a while
he will help out
this is the best path to take right now
I wonder
is the most useful in my opinion
oh there's a shrine somewhere
oh
sting why are they outside aren't they
normally always inside
mmm must be
must be protecting something special
[Music]
um
nice good damage
one hit drop that Treasure Chest please
and everything else
he wants just protecting the chest I
guess okay yeah since when are they
outside
oh yeah I have one Diamond left over
from
um
the quest with the lady in the goal
Gordon City
so I've used it because I'm like ah you
know what
you can make powerful weapons out here
yeah right now the diamond is like I
think one of the strongest uh fusing
items that I could get my hands on to
[Music]
um
yeah I didn't really feel the need for
much money anymore because like the
quest gives you so much money holy [\h__\h]
oh hello
but this thing's also really cool I
spread lizel thingy the attachments yeah
it looks like a diamond and it's pretty
strong too
[Music]
oh no
Boomerang
you you probably will be wanting more
money oh I think though you can can you
not actually do that Quest endlessly
with the lady
she's always gotta give her ex
specifically
what she wants
[Music]
nice
one buddy
oh yeah you can continue it forever
right
even after you went through all of the
gems once
it's repeatable
because yeah even after the diamonds I
think she was still asking for more gems
pays really well holy [\h__\h]
I didn't didn't even know what to do
before that money
oh hell no oh hell no
no
good no no no no no
I don't wanna I don't wanna but how else
do we get there
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] off
let's pick that up
I hope they don't
kill me when I pick it up and do I have
to
build a rocket
let me
know more or I'll try to be fast
didn't they drop one that fell down
[Music]
ah
there it is
should be gone now eh if I go there it
won't respawn once this one's gone
really oh my God that is very valuable
information holy [\h__\h] I thought they
will always come back to the same spot
oh are they basically dead once they
drop that
foreign
oh my God that's awesome
I thought you know the whole area you
know close to Goran city was like
infested with that and you can't really
do anything but if you just like change
them once
oh
I didn't even dare to attempt it another
time I thought maybe this is like for
much later maybe it's too advanced or so
for me
I should feel something to this to these
other things
wow that's such a like a coward way of
fighting them
we stop
that's a bit much don't you think
[Music]
give me
oh I forgot to snap a picture of damn it
well we only need five so
anything we'll do
on this area they seem to spawn a lot
outside huh
raspberries way out although raspberry
is always in cold regions here
this game it's very interesting hi
get up get up
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait
I wait actually no no no no uh
they're so fast
holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
that's why are they running so fast man
um wait can we get like this one
but um
something normal tooth
[\h__\h] up yes okay that one was one hit
right the ice ones are one hit if you
use
um
do I even have anything to oh
man
does this work no
if you use uh the uh opposite element on
them
why do I even bother with them
whatever wait can you not uh throw them
somebody told me I can throw them
[Music]
I don't want to waste my bombs on them
yeah
nice okay
yeah the good thing is they dropped like
always
some sort of gem don't dang it
so it's definitely worth
taking care of them okay I want to feel
something
um
what should I fuse
um one of these on I think I have one
more thing that I could use let's do one
of these
okay we'll make a
strong donut sword with a horn
and
whoa
make a Eightfold Blade with a modern
horn a horn even though that looks
stupid I could fuse this one too this
one too yeah I'll I'll keep this one now
warming that's a lot easier when you
warming
oh it's a pickaxe now oh I guess so
it really does I didn't even recognize
that I guess it really does look like a
pickaxe
The Horde for the hordes no I'm an
alliance type of person
I feel like all the cool people were
always in the hotel
my mom also was a horde type of person I
feel like everybody was always making
fun of people who weren't the alliance
wine
we're not that lame okay I mean yes a
lot of us maybe are choosing our group
because of Aesthetics and we want to be
pretty we don't want to be the [\h__\h]
Goblin
[\h__\h] Shrek
yeah okay true
oh wait I remember this from breath of
the Wild
that's why the dragon is so close here
too ah
Goblin slander
The Horde Community is not gonna lie
this
no no what I'm praising The Horde
Community I'm saying the alliance
Community kind of at least me I just
chose it because of the Aesthetics and
and the whole people were kind of the
cool ones who cared more about I don't
know
um
playing the game than being good looking
unless you chose a blood elf of course
then you're choosing for Aesthetics
let's be real
[Laughter]
you know and nowadays they have many
more choices but in the beginning in the
OG World of Warcraft what did they have
that looked pretty nothing blood else
were added later on they had nothing
they were only ugly
ugly ugly
yeah vanilla vanilla horde was quite
something
trolls are kind of cute
I mean I I can see their cuteness like
overall like of all of them nowadays oh
yeah tolerance especially talents I
think at least on German service the
towers were like
the number one least popular one I think
a trolls too or maybe Towers were even a
bit more popular than trolls I'm not
sure anymore but I felt kind of bad
because I I felt the fluffiness of the
towers kind of made them desirable a
little bit
I like them now oh man I want to play
World of Warcraft again
hmm
ons Are gnomes gnomes were so cute
um I played a gnome for a while but I
always preferred the starting area from
the humans
whenever I started with like a dwarf or
no no my felt kind of lost it felt
really difficult to start out there I
feel like it's it's it's the harder it's
more difficult there
for more experienced players
a lot of alcohol
[Music]
I played like so many different ones
I mean I miss it
um
oh yeah I've kind of noticed temples was
playing with recently yeah
but I want to play with girls or if you
guys hey I should just play with you
guys again and have you guys give me
free stuff and kill the enemies for me
but not always
hello my name is nazmi I'm a treasure
hunter and adventurer extra coordinator
undaunted by even the coldest snow in
this area is frozen
solid and packed with monsters no one in
the right mind would sit but here you
accept me of course a nurse surely
amongst me treasure resting here on this
mountain where everyone else fears the
trend that's what drove me to travel all
this way to Mountain room World of
Warcraft kitten
I guess I am
oh man
[Laughter]
until I saw you I really thought I'd be
the only one
honestly okay I really get that Concept
in for MMORPGs
I do get that I okay then I I think
maybe I can relate a bit more to Discord
kittens
why they would do that maybe
because okay Discord stuff is not
important to me but Stefan MMORPGs is
very important to me
up
at like man like I I oh I I
value stuff and I'm a more pictures way
too much
I
I need like cash shop items I need the
drip and stuff like that
like cosmetics
[Music]
laughs
you must be here for the same reasons
you'll be wanting to know what I know
about the treasure but I'll only tell
you if you will be my tutk kitten and
then I'll give you the treasure the
truth is bye luck I overheard a legend
relating to the treasure and this
mountain when while I was I was going to
read the rest normal
is for assuming there was a treasure on
Mount lanairu do you want to hear the
legend too great then listen up before I
am nazbear the treasure hunt I love
nothing to hide
mm-hmm
skim across snow from the spring high in
the Heavens to the mountain below
just came across now walk over snow from
the Spring High
in the heavens
like from Up
to the very bottom
pass for the rings of light
oh is it
another one of those like falling quests
from a sky island
to see the light of blessing when you
think interesting
despite the spring high in the heavens
wait didn't I already do it this is the
one no the one I did was elsewhere is
there another one
oh I did something like this before
unless it's different
I don't know what to do with the rings
of light but I don't see anything like
that around here
um maybe it's even higher up then
[Music]
okay interesting though and let's see
what what is going on here
the spring of wisdom
talk to me oh
it's okay pray
Is this different from the others the
bad swordsman who offers his prayers
hear my please oh and this one at the
snowboard oh I can no longer sense the
presence of the mother goddess statue
which dwells in the vast Canyon I would
ask you to go to that land and bring
Tidings to me of the mother god statue
please I beg of you
okay side quest
that I do not really
understand right now and I don't want to
do it either
can I even climb this stuff I I have to
use one of those stones right
let's see can I climb around to where
the the stones are dropping
hopefully one fell down here
oh
um
actually it might be reachable I see a
gap here
no problem
oh maybe I should rest
[Music]
why is so [\h__\h] noisy all the time
what oh my God
[Music]
I reached it
this was a challenge right for this one
or do I have to do anything else
can I already use it
easy
okay
this might just be the highest sky tower
out of all of them maybe
we can get to nice places with this
that will activate this and then fly
over to
that Island
isn't that one of the stone slab Islands
wow
[Music]
this is
what you mean from
Fire Emblem
now that you say it
there's a lot of thumbnails up here
that's a big ass area but a lot of it is
ocean
are we even gonna like explore that
there are some little Islands in it
we can build a boat I guess
[Music]
the yeah the uterus Island
is there a uterus Island as well in in
totk
I feel the need to know
wait is this a different one
[Music]
well this island looks Mighty
interesting too oh it's a it's a shrine
but it's also missing a stone
ah
is it
yeah oh
oh but wait
oh wait is this the one we just learned
about a different thing this one's
better
[Music]
oh my God
so shall I use a shield because actually
um
I found these
on on an island with a
gacha gotcha gotcha expensive Esperanza
sitting there
there's Shields there's all my Shields
I guess we can use that
oh no oh this
oh so does it like work even better
damn it but look at all these cool
Shields that I have
all right we'll use this one
[Music]
but where the [\h__\h] does it go
do I fly afterwards
scary
what if I fail wait is that even the
right one
okay uh what
what
it's [\h__\h] crazy
[Music]
okay holy [\h__\h] it killed me why
was I some oh was I supposed to undo the
what's that
oh there's a flag first I thought
oh man
no way
I thought somehow
you will survive that
[Music]
oh come on when you Gladwell surfing you
maintain yourself really
they didn't tell me that
oh
the shrine will be created here I
thought it will be created up there
okay
well thank God I had a fairy
although I didn't I really didn't want
to waste one of my fairies on that God
damn it
okay but now we have a cool sled Shield
but do you have to attach it to the sled
to your Shield or can you just use it on
its own
[Music]
and you're telling me this was not the
quest that the dude just talked about
because it's kind of like
asking me to do the same thing now
you can use any Shield to sled just it
adds the gimmick oh
um
yeah I was wondering if you can just put
a steering wheel on the sled too
what this is not a blessing shrine
ah
oh it's one of those trains where they
get rid of all my veins
uh Proving Grounds Ascension
what
it's my first one
of this type
oh my God Ascension oh
ybs
I have to ascend on to one of those
okay uh if he sees me is he gonna alert
everybody
I don't know if I can shoot that far
I have so many arrows it's too risky
[\h__\h]
hmm I should take photos of these guys
sure okay
um
[\h__\h] seeing me though
[Music]
I [\h__\h] up all right
let's fight them all
right and no problem with me this is the
aggressive way of doing these kind of
shrines
but there's no problem with that you can
totally fight like this too
it's not like they're all coming from me
right now anyway it seems
yeah okay
[Music]
I just wanna have a whoa
what was that
wasn't he froze something
[Music]
oh what is that it disappears oh he's
got like unlimited stones
[\h__\h]
open it open it
[Applause]
it was Ultra
foreign
with the stupid kids
throwing stupid [\h__\h] at me
oh why they didn't drop anything God
damn it
okay I could fly to them
okay
put the candles in and then we can go
but
um
as well
I don't really want to use that platform
this one it seems like too too
complicated to me
wait ah
[Music]
um let's see if I can do this properly
now I can just fly up if I pull out my
shield right
whoa okay let's start at the top
thank you
oh quick wait for me
okay I'll kill these ones while I'm here
oh wait
um
this makes it quite a bit stronger and
gives it spice don't let him don't let
him no no no
no no we'll put this on scrap this one's
strong
holy [\h__\h]
no
deals
okay
[\h__\h] my weapon uh
once one second I like this aggressive
way of doing things way more
yeah no need to do stealth or whatever
[Laughter]
I gotta make it strong I can't run
around with a [\h__\h] wooden stick can
we shock fruit
okay
uh also might as well
add another one to my Shields
okay
oh there's five fruits here
and
okay
we'll go down here
oh
is that a oh
all right well that one's bad I think
[\h__\h] milk
used up my
uh
my freaking
torpedo for nothing
oh I'm coming for you just wait for me
be patient
fan meeting with everyone I'll treat
everyone equally don't you worry give me
that no
give me your droppings oh look at that
who's left maybe only one
that he fell to the ground
I don't see him
Corner
he's hiding
I'm so cute what
We're not gonna have any of these
weapons I think when we leave
well we're just gonna get our old ones
back so do I have food
can I eat the chocolate well I can I can
actually eat the five fruit in the shock
fruit
I guess I'll do that because I'm scared
to die now
but if he does that [\h__\h] again to me
I'll die anyway ah there we go
[Music]
I was like a lemon ah wait that makes a
lot of sense because if you eat a lemon
you're like
oh I like that that makes a lot of sense
[Music]
of
that
oh I already have my things back I was
just gonna say hey did they drop uh
freaking
Ruby Ron what the [\h__\h]
speaking of Ruby
did you see your zombie I don't
um like two days ago they released for
that song an English version
foreign
yeah I listened to it today
um I think I think the wrap was pretty
cool
but
because they didn't make things rhyme I
think so in English it seems kind of
weird but in Japanese you don't rhyme
really and it works fine
but I don't know in English it makes you
feel like something's just off they
focused I think very much on making the
lyrics the same like very much the same
as in um the Japanese lyrics
and it made the English ones maybe a
little bit all weird but generally it
was good and and the original like
singer is still singing it
and her English
um pronunciation was pretty good it
seems like I read the credits and it
seems like she was like trained to
protect uh to pronounce it properly
even though it's such a difficult and
fast song Ooh Soldier free spare nice
so she did really well
[Music]
um
you guys should listen to it maybe
afterwards
that is Opia
oh
oh I guess it's not their first English
song
wait which one which else do they do
that often anyone still be translating
things to English I guess so maybe I've
heard one before and I just can't
remember it right now
what what song Idol you know the one
that everybody is vibing to right now
[Music]
[\h__\h] Bob I'm trying to learn it
so I can sing it in karaoke because we
have instrumentals for it and I want to
add it to my repertoire now I can
actually try to learn the English and
the Japanese version so I have two songs
in my rapper tour
isn't that nice
um
okay what do we Where Do We Go From Here
we should try to aim to go here now
so maybe I go up to the tower again and
try to see how far I get
I don't know if they're working I'm
getting my songs approved maybe they're
just like are fainting ignorance
maybe maybe eventually like after two
months I'll be like hey did they like
ever receive my requests and then
they'll be like oh seems like oh your
request must have failed or something or
somehow we didn't receive it at all must
have I don't know it must have been a
bug or maybe you input too much and
there was a limit or so I don't know
who knows who knows what happened
nah then there was no limit nobody ever
said anything about a limit I even
actually there wasn't a limit but I
still
um
made an effort to separate like you know
I did like a hundred songs from Venice
cobal I sent it in and then I opened a
new form and I did 100 songs from cute
you know
I always
I was switched
okay green
let's follow the green lights
um
it seems like there is a construct
battle platform over there at least
that's what it looks like to me because
it's so flat
oh yeah
wait a second
that's where we want to go right but
that's not where like a tower is
did I not see and mark the Tower of this
region I guess I didn't but it is over
there
so I could attempt to go to that
this this region already looks
interesting
where are we going anyway region
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
wait but we never collected rice
okay I'll do that Upstream
oh what's up
oh I'm running out of stamina
maybe I should land on over there once
well I will have to make a decision
or not
I can't design oh my God
stop please
is it a I tried finding a level two once
and it was rough but I did it off screen
and I was thinking maybe if I do it on
or on screen then you guys can give me
advice
and then it won't be so difficult
they really want my attention don't they
no wait um which one this one
can I reach like this
please
no I don't think so
[Music]
um
okay what level is this oh
foreign
okay
oh wait what
ah I should use that moment to
like pull it out of him
[Music]
okay nice
yeah I fought one Lino off screen
and it went quiet well the shitty it was
a blue one though which one is the
weakest and which one is the strongest
one guys
one
I think it was a blue one red is the
weakest I should have done the red one
first
uh
oh
no I didn't want to rewind but uh [\h__\h]
no wait ah
what if I make it fall down off of the
islands actually what happens then blue
is level two oh that's why not even that
bad hey I'm doing this while trans and
saying oh my God I'm so proud ah okay
but this is the part I think well I was
like okay what the [\h__\h] am I supposed to
do I was trying to send these back and
it didn't really do anything
am I supposed to fly up which is
good but what if you don't have that
well I guess you could ride
ah you could
ah you could go out
you could go up on one of them and then
ah
okay no but I'll use my shield now
if I may
[Music]
oh
okay
let's get some more hits in I know I
never do the charging attack I know I
should
oh we're going back to normal Farm okay
thank God
oh
show me your chocolate side oh it's it
changed
okay I thought maybe it's
apparently it's not okay I'm sorry I'm
sorry sorry
if I eat I need to cook
we need to cook guys
let me cook after this
oh
[Music]
the orange chill
I can't get behind him
um
would be nice if we got a flight if I
could fly up again
holy [\h__\h] holy [\h__\h]
foreign
blocks again okay
okay that's it that's it
and
oh what was that what was the ads okay
it was enough
ah
well they dropped two
aren't they even
oh a card uh-huh I never had a card
before really
are they the same but just double
because usually they dropped one
it's the same thing right
Let's see we should fuse it to something
but what
um
this one perfect
oh wait ah I thought it was two separate
ones oh it's one thing oh okay cool cool
cool had a good weapon too
to uh oh
fuse it with we got a sage will that's
my second one
mmm
interesting a sage will
I don't think you could get those from
this kind of enemies
yeah
okay which way we were going this way
hey thank you guys for giving me some
hints but I feel like I went pretty
smoothly
now I'm not so scared oh my God is that
the Death Star
no I'm not so scared of fighting them
alone anymore
um
how do you know I think when I was
fighting it alone I was thinking
fly up but I had nothing really that
would help me with that quickly in that
moment so oh
it would be nice while we're up here if
we could reach that Island to
[Music]
um
you think I can reach
might be a close call
[Music]
um
should I get something
try it let's go
load faster load faster maybe we'll
reach the very very bottom of the island
looks good looks good and then the tower
is right beneath I did really is that
the one
oh we were just on the perfect height
how do I take a picture for [\h__\h] sake
is it gonna land on the ground and I can
take the picture down there
can I stay on it
what oh come on
[\h__\h]
okay well great
[Laughter]
okay but wait
okay
we must go here first and then we jump
down there's a lot of Gloom here isn't
there
yeah I'll take a picture on the ground
um what is the catch here that the Gloom
hands will attack me or what
oh yeah
not glue it's not glue
Pakistan
what
no no water
it's moving what is that
hmm
seems safe
yo what is this
it's not lava it's like
yeah
reminds me of Zone Knight because it has
a little bit of purple
maybe it's donut lava
it's not just mud
oh but okay
it's the entrance what if I touch it oh
slower
that's it
oh oh dear
there's a fish stuck here and the
entrance is also covered in it
what if I use this like newly acquired
um water root Splash fruit
and then maybe
it turns into something that I can blow
up
where the [\h__\h] is it
[Laughter]
[Music]
is this oh
what just easily dissolves well that's
an easy one
oh you're welcome buddy
you you saved me thank you I was
shameful that this should happen to me
captain of the Zora of the people that
film suddenly began falling from the sky
it solids the waters around here and in
Zora's domain oh that's your problem ah
sounds like a you problem
everyone is at their wits and because of
it that is why I set out to investigate
the surrounding area myself to think I
would fall prey to Falling sludge myself
oh man [\h__\h] eh gotta clean my fins if
you add not sprayed with water I shudder
to think what would have happened to me
please take this Zoro spare unless your
inventory is full I guess
oh
yields a high attack power when it gets
wet
uh
fighting in water is not something we
really did much until now wait does rain
also count
maybe ring counts too
oh my honey
I guess that's okay nice nice
our second tower today
[Music]
second tower let's go
right after the other one actually so
fast speed running the towers I think
I'll only have like two or three left
or maybe even four
[Music]
is that the month
oh
why is there a Death Star
[Music]
four left that's not too bad
oh
the water is all muddy in the door I was
sitting
[Music]
sand
try landing on it is it gonna attack me
[Music]
hmm
interesting
oh the ball is on there too
the dev said how much I love Star Wars I
think they were already done creating
the game
when I shared my love for Star Wars it's
got this gonna attack me isn't it it's
hurting like a planet
obviously everyone would get curious
once they first see it
is it gonna turn into a straight
platform when I land
we fight immediately huh oh my God it's
like for running exercise
like a hamster oh it's trying to
Trifles
before it Turns Upside Down let's
activate it Go in quick we're safe
inside
that's it
I thought they would be something really
evil inside
hmm
a flying device oh sheesh
sheesh
okay
well another thing or two about flying
devices but there's two directions that
we could take
free actually
how do I decide where to go does it
matter oh actually they're flying
where did that come from underneath
this one has a ton of solutions okay
hello
oh oh there is something underneath
okay well my instincts first were to go
left maybe because I'm left-handed so
I shall do that
of course not I'm always very hesitant
to
immediately
put it on the rail
okay
do we not get the book do I not deserve
a butter bomb
mean
oh is it trying to teach me that I can
use this the same way
can I can I
no um no
I was bamboozled
I'm supposed to attach my ah
I'm supposed to attach my uh floaty
to it yeah okay
maybe I should have watched it first and
see the route of it
okay okay
that's probably why there's a still
standing one here so that I also see
you know
at the other ones you know they fail at
achieving their goal but this is a
really
shitty lay of attaching it I don't like
it
I'm Gonna Roll away though let's do it
here
shake shake shake shake
oh God okay
and my dad will go to the other side but
what if we would have just started by
going to the right side right away
[Music]
when that all of this be obsolete
should wear a little bit
oh
Phoenix bored
maybe stay
if you want
okay because maybe we'll need it
the bomb
here Eva but there's a chest there
well I mean
if I just bridge the gap because I don't
think I can do the jump
where's my super cool
airplane
then I can't I actually just
go up with my superpowers
you know feel like this
holy [\h__\h]
I'm a chance
wait where is it it's the shadow uh
kind of yeah
Bridge yeah
bird bridge if if anything
[Music]
aren't you guys happy today I'm not
doing that much story progress you must
be so happy
okay we got the chest there's probably
just one chest in this Shrine so I guess
don't worry I saw the the fan
all that's left to just fly over now
right
can we make it
because there's only one fan
you are hoping for more story for real
have you ever been on the ground or in
the sky yes yes yes is this your first
time you're watching my Zelda stream or
what
of course
I prefer though at least in my streams
to stay all on on the this level
because it just seems
should we start a little bit further
back
it just seems I don't know
more aesthetically pleasing for streams
I know that's a weird reason but I feel
like you know on the ground is dark and
very repetitive looking
and you know
you eat with your eyes too and don't you
want to like look at something like nice
yeah I'm thinking maybe it needs a
little bit of a running start but like
how much
things should I have instead placed the
the fan underneath so I'll fly higher
this way I'll just lie faster I guess
first time watching don't [\h__\h] me
wait worst case we also have the Guster
which will surely help us too
I'm scared that I would be using it in
the wrong direction though [\h__\h]
[Applause]
can I get my glider back when I revive
well we barely got anywhere
what the [\h__\h]
maybe I do need a tight
I mean I turned it off once too early
but I don't think that was necessarily
the problem
so maybe it does need this
you place it at the top
what
you think it's just because I turned it
off
actually like this and might not even be
rolling
don't okay
I'll give it a bit more of a head start
let's go
oh God it's gonna turn off so fast
I can't fall off that easily
can we really make it
yeah
I feel like I'm already below
did I do it wrong
what
I thought I could get higher if I stand
in the back should I just stay in the
middle
I'm gonna die
hmm
okay
and maybe uh maybe it doesn't need that
much of a head start
the fast way too flat just play straight
down really really
okay I have been warned
ah I can use recall to start higher true
that I guess it needs a long start
don't need the car
and why was it there
I said if I
is it because if I started on the other
side I have but I understand this shrine
I donated okay
stay in the middle like you little no no
no no no no no just say it back
oh that works fine
foreign
[Music]
streaming addiction
another Shrine in my pocket
you know what was what was one one of my
favorite things when I was younger
holy Pocket Polly Pocket do they have it
in America another under continents too
honey pumpkin was the best thing
hahaha
let me see what I get here yes
do they still create Polly Pockets
things Polly Pocket things
I want to buy one and play with it
it was the best thing
oh Mighty Max what I've never heard of
that I don't think they really had that
here at least it wasn't very very
present
hmm
and I always I felt embarrassed to ask
my my mommy because I felt like I was
already a little bit too old for it
but I always wanted one of those baby
born baby born one of those really
Advanced ones when I was a child I
wanted one of those because because you
know those baby born the advanced ones
they could do so many things they could
like spit up milk and all that
I wanted a fake baby but don't it you
know it was quite popular for
girls young girls you know
oh
I've seen this in Creations on YouTube
we only got one though
does this ever turn upside down for me
thank God I got healed I was about to
die
is this so you can if you land
underneath you can
warp up
can I stop it from turning I don't get
them
yeah how do I get down
[\h__\h]
I can always go back to the shrine I can
always go back to the shrine uh opening
opening opening please
hey I'm going back to the shrine
should I really stop it okay I mean I
think you could have entered without
stopping a tuba makes it easier probably
I missed the website they had
with a lot of dress-up games
back when I was younger there was also
this website then I love to go to they
had so many fun games for little girls
I was a gamer girl already back then was
kind of a different kind of gamer girl
but let's be real is the best type of
game of girl you know you know
you can't tell me that why is it still
turning oh because it makes sense you
can't tell me that I wasn't the gamer
girl
I was literally a girl gaming more than
I am now because now I'm a woman woman
gaming
okay is there like a specific way ah I
should have
how do you climb guys how do you climb
when he's already flying
[\h__\h] hate him link I hate you
because I can't turn around and [\h__\h] I
don't get it
I don't know
pull out your ball and blink will snap
oh
I think again a hard reset is that [\h__\h]
okay it's fine
but
can I properly enter now wait
climb down let's just climb down oh but
I think it's over there
how do I know how do I know it's in the
right place
let's see
I know there's only one entrance
like I was lucky two times to have it in
the right place and still failed to
enter
so now I'm brute forcing it now that was
too high it wasn't that that high
it was not that high
[Music]
face it and turn what yeah
I don't get it guys ah wait I get it now
I wait okay I get the logic now sorry
the hole just needs to be like half
right like for example
like this okay I get it now
I guess yeah yeah I know it was okay
moment I admit it
okay this better be worth it
in such a special place there should be
a special item
okay we're being spammed with those now
I need to
find out how to further use it
oh [\h__\h] I went back this is my third one
I had one Upstream in lab two on stream
lucky but it's like it's Destiny
okay uh we flew up from the Skyview
tower now I guess holy [\h__\h]
oh is that
is that the like the
dungeon here
but wouldn't it be because for the for
the for the burbs it was like covered
spoiler alert I guess maybe it was
covered for
sake of
spoiler alert I would say right That You
Don't See
[Music]
um
maybe that's not it at all
but anyway
let's visit the Dora
The Village
[Music]
oh there's so many interesting looking
places here oh my God
[Music]
Friday
can't take a picture while I'm flying no
Yahoo
all right bye bye then
let's land right in the middle wait
actually [\h__\h] maybe that would have been
a Croc
at the very top of that Crown looking
thing
God damn it
I should have checked that
that would be pretty mean though
wouldn't it
you don't think there is there is oh oh
two contradicting statements
but look we're here
oh I'm so sorry everyone has been
treated now but we have used up all the
splash for it we'll be needing a lot
more of that huh they were more interest
and anticipated please accept my apology
oh she looks like a hammerhead shark
oh my God
I don't think I have seen this kind of
Zora in breath of the Wild
you have nothing to apologize for you
did what but she has no name she must be
special
whoa she's unique
there was one
oh
this is a grown-up version
nah
[Applause]
most importantly I'm grateful that
everyone is all right now if we could
only do something about that statue well
I can fix that
you're there are you a traveler
I'm sorry that I did not notice you
until now she looks very special indeed
yeah
if she's got like special
Ruffles on her neck and jewels I mean
they got Jewels too though she looks
special doesn't it doesn't she look
Story related
I'm sorry that I did not notice you
until now I was focused on a matter of
great importance there was the main is
in troubled times at present due to the
slush falling from the sky things have
finally calmed down
hey this gives me a sunshine Vibes I
clean the [\h__\h] lunch
with water
oh makes me happy
um
Super Mario Sunshine
Mario Sunshine
things have finally calmed down at least
for the moment however this place
remains covered in sludge
such a shame as this particular statue
is so incredibly important to the story
after the main
we were just discussing how we need to
wash away the sludge I apologize that I
cannot provide a great deal of
hospitality please do make yourself at
home here I don't recognize her should I
be recognizing her was there green
one back in the day I don't remember her
I feel bad
yeah
there you go I did it
want me to do the surroundings too I
don't know if I can oh she is new okay
oh
it's the hero
riding
on Azora wait was the statue always the
same or did they like build this after
breath of the wild because link was
riding on
on one
it is new too oh that's sweet oh
that is very sweet
it's a memory from breath of the Wild
what was there before
I see you managed to wash it away that
statue is a symbol of Hope for the Zora
it is very precious to us thank you so
much for cleaning it up and truth that
statue depicts The Majestic forms of the
pair who saved the pair the couple
mifa probably told him to tell the story
of us as a pair a couple
[Laughter]
the pair who saved this cherished domain
in the past
that is right oh
wait a seat on not me for oh [\h__\h]
princess over and his very best friend
sir link the heroics Hylian Swordsman
all right all right it was you done my
brain tried to correct the story
um
oh wait it's rumbling sound
crumbling rumbling
it is simply wonderful is it not I would
love to meet him someday hello hello
it's me say you have a similar stature
to the Italian hero here we will he will
similar eyes as well oh oh oh my and
you're also a Hylian
and The Swordsman
wait could be here
yeah I guess I don't like to flex but
y'all mean
I've also already helped out too I'm a
region successfully
are you link
swordsman of Legend
please remember to mind your man is
chroma
oh oh please accept my apology
yes please pardon our rudeness I am
quite surprised to learn that you are
the legendary swordsman Sterling
I have heard mention of you nearly every
day since I first arrived at this domain
ah
I'm guessing I can't make a nipple
comment because fish don't have nipples
huh
I am Prince sidon's
oh forgive me I am your best friend's
fiancee
whoa okay sorry sit on that I was just
about to comment on your fiance's
nipples uh I didn't I mean I'm just
making like biological observations you
know
um awkward I hope he is not gonna find
out about them
my name is Yona I'm truly honored to
have the opportunity to meet you sir
link
hey fiance huh are we gonna see sedon
I oh I was curious about her English
voice a German voice I had heard that
you were missing along with Princess
Zelda if I may ask what brings you here
to think that such a thing took place
beneath High Road Castle and now you are
traveling the kingdom to investigate
so you search for Princess Zelda is what
brought you to this domain
in that case feel free to investigate
the area around the domain as faroli
thoroughly
as you see fit oh I have a lovely idea
if you do not mind I ask that you please
go and meet with sidon I'm certain that
he would be delighted to see you
February
sedon can be found at the mifa court
where you can also try to court her if
you want she's dead though
um yeah
but you don't seem to mind doing things
with ghosts
lady Jonah it is time I feel we must be
going now
forgive me sir link but I must be on my
way
bruh oh
but if it pleases you after you have met
with sidon perhaps you could visit me at
the infirmary on the floor above
I am determined to be of assistance to
you as best as a cancer link I always
bought this but the Zoras
City
is just design wise so cool
man
it's really impressive and it's thorough
and oh my God it reminds me of tales of
arise
you remember that place I was all [\h__\h]
up
especially this path reminds me of it
yeah yeah bull runs play Palace yeah
yeah that's what I mean
um
nah they're kids no way I mean they did
puns
with Japanese names tabasaki but no way
they're doing that in English no [\h__\h]
way
nah nah nah I don't believe it no that
is like kind of too too sensitive of a
pun as well is that your PIN oh
oh we could cook can I just cook a
little bit really quickly
[Music]
I don't need it that originally but I
want to cook some things wait can I bake
the pizza oh wait I have one cheese oh
[\h__\h] we can make a cheese pizza
it was
um
cheese
wheat tomato
am I missing something
I don't want to mess it up it's only
that right
tomato tomato
we don't have corn I think yet although
this kind of looks a little bit like
corn and this looks also like corn
everything looks like corn
no I don't think so
doing
can we make croissant no no
mushrooms ah I think once you have these
three ingredients you could add things
onto it and it will still stay a pizza
but I don't think it'll necessarily add
the ingredients in in the picture and
title
this should be it
oh my God
oh I want to make so many recipes with
cheese
oh it does specify Tomato Pizza [\h__\h] I
wish I had more cheese I want to try
mushroom pizza even though I hate it but
it should work
interesting
I'm gonna make a lot of pizzas when I
get more access to to cheese oh the
picture looks good
um
what else could I make oh
oh
I can buy cheese with rupees I guess
yeah because she was also gonna make
them stock it at the General Store
I want to make
um what's the stew recipe again it's
milk
and
what can we make
of milk
fish to me
I haven't done that before either I
think
oh yeah right I can do I can check my
recipes with how how
do I check it again
oh it only shows here
but I never made a stew before I think
[Music]
did I
I made a meat steal before
and vegetable curry
could probably make the curry with meat
as well or fish curry that you can
probably make a fish curry right okay
let me try it wheat corn spice
and fish
I don't really
have an appetite ever for fish curry but
it is a thing I think
right
um
just want normal fish
no come on see it's the waste of corn
spies
who made fish curry
I guess it's not that popular is it rice
not wheat [\h__\h]
it looks so similar man you can't even
blame me what if it still doesn't work
man
Seafood rice balls okay but I could have
done that without the Goran spice as
well
God damn it
okay uh
[Music]
um
what shall I make
a beef ball
yeah let's make some stuff with rice
indeed
um
I want to go buy recipes though
yeah but I can only select uh recipes
that I've done before I want to do
something I haven't done before
let me try it raw meat rice
and
I wanna I wanna list of momentum list
totk recipes
that sounds good
I don't think I've made that oh Yum Yum
Yum okay
how about
okay this side is good
whoo
I think it's good
oh okay
yeah yeah where do you get crabs
anywhere I'm gonna do crab recipes
prime meat and seafood fry
salt grilled gourmet meat holy [\h__\h]
simple though very simple ah let's do
the seafood tomato
it's a tomato
and fish any fish okay
at Coastal beaches I was looking at the
beach but didn't find any maybe I was
just unlucky
um
what did I say fish right
any fish
how about some Zora
[Music]
okay
that could be potentially really good in
real life
um
veggie cream
I don't like mushrooms but mushroom soup
seems very yummy fresh milk rock salt
if I make all these once I can like
already always do it simply quickly
for you the recipe button
[Music]
any vegetable and a Hylian mushroom
any vegetable
um
maybe tomato
and the Hylian specifically Hylian
mushroom
does it have to be Highland mushroom
really
corn stuff corn soup is like my favorite
soup
eh
the Tomato overpowered the mushroom
what the [\h__\h]
I hate when that happens why then don't
say any vegetable
[Music]
how about
istanbulb maybe or
damn it
foreign
there we go yeah yeah spread that
propaganda wait what am I doing
I need
um mushroom and milk
[\h__\h] propaganda
[Laughter]
oh
no
[\h__\h] I did it wrong
um
what was I doing Hylian mushroom
let's put it in the stand bulb I wonder
if another mushroom would work as well
should work right and then this
and then the milk
yeah
if that doesn't work then I don't know
what to do
yeah
it's a little bit energizing too
okay how about
um
poultry Curry lots of poultry Curry
I like chicken curry
there's Prime and there's normal poultry
Curry
I can do
Robert I'm trying to okay let's do this
uh Goran spice and Hylian rice very easy
Curry is so simple for real for real
Alan Rice
and
corn spice
let me cook
I am in the mood for some Curry now
God damn it let's make a a prime Wonder
oh wait I don't have a prime one I only
have a raw bird fly
interesting oh no that is the one
Goran spice and Hylian rice
it looks oh looks a little bit different
it adds the the bird leg thanks guys
[Music]
um
mushroom risotto I love risotto but
every time I look up rosada recipes it
feels like they always put in
ingredients or some some ingredients
that I don't like
high and rice gold butter that seems
very accurate for
uh
horizontal wait where is my do I need
the milk
no
any mushroom gold butter rock salt
learning cooking basics
with tl2k like parmesan
oh you like mushroom Rosado it is a
Parmesan
nice nice I just want to cook new on
your things
don't have a crab oh fried egg and rice
very simple crunchy fried rice wait
let's make this one any meat wheat
actually no rice necessary for this one
ironically
any meat okay why do I have so much raw
prime meat what the hell
[Music]
um
bird egg
oil jar
nice
and
why did they [\h__\h] me
the [\h__\h]
huh
I used exactly what they say on there
sometimes it just fails anyway they're
not like making it clear
huh
made me waste my bird eggs
what did I do wrong
I do need rice why does it not say it on
there
what why
Road egg oil jar
better be good there we go Highland rice
fried up with meat in high quality oil
yummy yummy
okay
I can make a meat pie
any meat
gold butter
rock salt
foreign
I've never had a meat pie before I think
it's got a kind of like a that looks
like beans though isn't that a uk-ish
thing it feels like like it could be
uk-ish
you need an extra napkin to deal with
this juicy pie well perfectly baked
minced meat oh perfectly oh so this
means
yummy Savory pies are so good I never
have those but I'm interested
um
we can make the same thing with fish
oh
Godfather
rock salt and any fish
where's the fish
I want to use normal fish
that's the shape of a fish cute do you
guys actually do that I wonder
when you when somebody makes a fish pie
the rest understood has always come in
the fish shape that would be really cute
well I can make bread
mmm
wow
[Music]
what are so many cool things you can
make I can make a crap whoa wait wait I
want to make that can I make that I
think I have the ingredients for it a
wild bear there's different kinds of
there's three different kind of kind of
crabs there's a plain one there's a wild
berry one and there's a honey crap
obviously I'll go for the Wildberry one
because that's my favorite kind of crap
let's go
let's go we need
fresh milk
um bird egg
wheat
uh cane sugar and Wildberry
that's a crit
normally it does 10 Hearts apparently
yeah
yeah yummy
me down
there's the same thing with honey and so
on let's make let's make a nut cake can
we make a nut cake or fruitcake
okay
wait I want to do fruitcake first
um you can even say Tomatoes is a fruit
so I could add a tomato right
you say it's a fruit the game kind of
told me the same thing
um
cane sugar and tabantha wheat
is it because I use the same one twice
or what
what
I hate when this happens
hmm
oh this looks yummy
let me make
um
it's a dessert really wait how doesn't
it's like cheesecake
does it taste like cheesecake
[Music]
oh I've almost like I mean I skipped a
lot but I reached the end of the list
actually
um let me attempt the nut cake
because we have these chickaloo tree
nuts that you can use for it
not cake
that's my last one so I better work
cane sugar and goat butter
checking again if I'm correct yeah yeah
it doesn't say how many so
like custard oh I love custard that's a
quiche yeah
is it like a quiche because custard is
kind of sweet oh look at that oh it's
like sugared almonds on top or so and
pistachios
sheesh
nice
there's a cooking stream now guys
do we still have one more milk
yes
um
cane sugar four
an egg pudding perfect shape and
perfectly wobbly
of caramel drizzled over it you're
hungry now me too I have a sandwich
I've got you my sandwich
there's so you can make um Candy
just candy but I don't think it's worth
it
okay I want to do
look this is a fruit too right it's just
fruit so
let's just also works so fruits
and any fruit except Apple
and
honey
fruits nice
y'all can use up some of these fruits or
maybe the ice fruits
it doesn't say though if it needs to be
three different ones or if it can be the
same ones let me try with the same ones
because I don't need these ice fruits
that much
it better not fail because that's my
last honey
hi Tommy
hi it's okay
um
okay maybe last thing
[Music]
can I make this I think I have stuff
still
yeah yeah
rock salt
and any mushroom
what do you think that makes
um
oh
a mushroom omelette oh my God but it
looks like exactly what you get in the
store because even in the restaurant
Japanese Omelette Restaurant
yeah even has the sauce on top of it and
the right shape it's almost isil even
though it looks like it's filled with
fries I added no rice can you make
omurizer
I don't think so I didn't see it
interesting
one more
I don't know why this is so fun to me I
like uh doing all these recipes sorry
and we need food anyway
um
bird egg butter rock salt
and any herbs
okay how about the Hyrule herb I hope I
have all the ingredients correctly
vegetable
omelette nice that's more my kind of
thing don't like mushroom omelette okay
cool we got a lot of yummy food
okay back to the main thing
it's been five hours now by the way
but I feel okay now the breathing has
gotten better
thankfully
was this uh oh
yeah hi General historic but you're not
selling anything
the splash for which we procured to help
deal with the sludge except we ran out
of it if you see something you're like
please just grab it from the table huh
I don't see anything
no I'm not selling
let me see what
huh
oh right here I'm a blind chill they got
rice
and Swift Violet Swift
oh for movement speed I only have four
of these those are these ones would be
nice too Tomatoes tomatoes
um no I'm good thanks though I'll
remember it
[Music]
my Yahoo
oh I'm disturbing the ladies in their
bath but I guess for Zoras being in
water
and also being in a bath like this is
really just very casual
oh wow that's deep are you healing her
oh has she been glued no it's sludge
ah this Lodge is really quite stubborn
ideally hope our patients recover soon
I went into this Lodge and it did
nothing to me
yeah it's literally a bed for them
lady you wanna sir Lucas here at last
um I
I am drowning help me
oh you really came how fortuitous
fortnite us I was hoping to speak with
you about an item that you entrusted the
domain with repairing your Zora armor
must have been in between breath of the
wild and tltk
I don't remember him doing that
the repair is mostly complete but it
does require just one more thing wait I
won't have to buy it
I need an ancient arowana
have one I can finish the armor right
away if I can somehow acquire a scale
from that fish
we have not seen our ancient our Runners
around lately and I have no idea where
they can be found in the sky islands
actually
yeah no I remember the armor but like
why did he give it away to repair it
why was it so broken huh
what
um since they are used for making armor
then to the blacksmith may know
something about how to get one no I know
I would not know
oh climb waterfalls for real just the
armor wait
you could do that with the armor
I thought the climbing up waterfalls was
like a skill from mifa
no mifa was like Reviving you huh oh
wait that's a really good armor
okay then take my fish
dear lady
hmm
okay nice we immediately get it wow
was damaged from link rectal in his way
to save the kingdom in breath of the
Wild
but the other armors were not damaged it
seems and we had to buy it again
even though it's the same ones
why would why do we have to buy it
and they're not even like lost like
other armor pieces
in treasure chests or so
lost over the years no no I have to buy
it they stock up yeah I guess they just
made the same armor again
so our armor oh wait is it just the main
piece
do I have to buy the rest
okay
if I want it but it seems like I don't
need it can I
ah okay it will not help you with
climbing iguanas that have been tainted
with sludge I see
oh wait ah you know those islands that
have waterfalls falling down
and let's say you want to reach an
island like that but the stones that
bring you up with time reversal don't go
up that high but they go up high enough
to reach the waterfall
um
I don't know where that would apply but
it would probably apply a lot in this
area
I'm cooking
with your great scale Sterling I'm
certain you will find a way up that
waterfall clouded though it is
oh please use this wealthy investigation
into Princess Zelda's whereabouts
oh thank you
um but we still gotta meet seed on where
wasn't he like a level above
we also have something that makes
climbing stairs easier
okay
oh my God is your children
where is he
much sit on
he's on the mountain what oh I must have
misunderstood something
which one that one
right up there probably
I see something there
should I shoot him that's him maybe it's
not him
wait is that actually there
oh I should just checked the quest
marker very true
[Music]
um
oh
oh dear
I could probably stop those
the time reversal clean them with water
and jump on them and then go up maybe
but
I don't know
take a peek at the flavor text
oh we're crafted by a past summer
princess for our future husband
and your future husband
[Music]
that song was written by mifa it seems
Ahoy Wanna Fall
Oh indeed that one doesn't seem to be uh
bothered by this lunch
okay
actually Betty's Global has a song like
that too
[Music]
I like that song
[\h__\h]
get in there get in there oh
oh
this couple Channel first time sanctum
Christine percent
probably Christina now it's rifle wants
to uh say it very
English
is that the
King
he's sick too that's not sedon who got
really fat though right
hello
or is it
like get this big
thing I found it early
foreign
what is happening here
oh God who approaches is that you so it
is link
oh did you find this place what a cruel
point
why would I be plotting something
oh boy other loyal musu if you speak in
such way without
explanation link here will only be
confused as to what is going on
oh
ah Dora fan Nazi done
hmm
I heard Neighbors on the balcony
hello link it has been some time since
we last spoke they probably heard me
talk
I had received word
that you went missing
I think they were like um uh punching uh
uh
carpet carpet it sounded like carpet
punching
now let me open
[Music]
it didn't even meow when I closed the
door I think
[Applause]
whistle
yes beating the carpets because they
were very very very evil very mean
why does everybody always bully carpets
guys
they get punched they get
sat on they get stood on they get
trampled on they get walked on
why why why do they always get bullied
has anyone ever thought about that why
does no one think about the carpet's
feelings huh
yeah yeah they let it be Dusty too
they get [\h__\h] spilled on them
they got cats throwing up on them
all kinds of [\h__\h]
carpets have it rough yeah
I'm just trying to help him out you know
you know I mean because I had a dream
about bullying last night so now I'm
like hey
think about the point of view of the
victims aka the carpet huh I want to
take a bite of my sandwich let's see if
it's good
Justice for carpets
[Applause]
okay
hate it when sandwiches are not fully
cut through because then obviously
there's like one part of the sandwich
that that's only bread let me rip this
one open really quick
my sandwich OCD is so strong
like but also I need to readjust the the
ham and the salad the salad oh the ham
is okay the placement of the ham is okay
but the salad is absolutely terribly
placed
let me fix this
it's not enough salad everywhere in here
okay
I'm a ham placement XL sandwich
placement expert ah
hmm
there's a tomato in here too
some kind of spread
um
what's a meatball sandwich
never had that before
oh man ciabatta bread makes my hands so
flat flowery flowery
meatballs but meatballs how are you
gonna Place meatballs
wouldn't it be better if you just put
like meatballs but in minced meat form
like in scrambled form like scrambled
meatballs
which is the original form what if you
call minced meat scrambled meatball
no you know look at it from from a
different POV again
look at it backwards that's a sloppy joe
oh
never had that again
[Music]
um
I've heard of sloppy joes I didn't know
it was that kind of thing
it's not just ground meat exactly
well I like that way of saying it
scrambled meatball
um so today we're doing spaghetti with
scrambled meatballs
or I'm feeling a lasagna with scrambled
meatballs
[Laughter]
sloppy goes sloppy joes are meh super
messy
I gotta try one
I had received word that you went
missing along with Princess Zelda
why have I come here
why have I come to you specifically what
are you how are you are you a quest
that I found too early I don't like
going to places that are connected with
quests before I even have the quest
do you think that such a thing should
transpire for the hero of Hyrule to
Princess Zelda as well you you'll expect
us to believe that princess Thelma
simply disappeared just like that do not
selling our ears with your lies
so Princess Zelda with my own eyes right
after the phenomenon at Hyrule Castle
took place
calm yourself muzu Link's eyes betrayal
hint of deception he remains a trusted
friend of the Zora exactly thank you for
being so reasonable
there must be an explanation link I will
now tell you what happened when we last
Saw Princess Zelda as well as the reason
behind my seclusion here in the pristine
Sanctum
we encountered Princess Zelda just after
Hyrule Castle ascended into the sky
floating islands appeared as if from
nowhere sludge and fragments of ruins
began raining down
musu and I had left the domain to
investigate these strange occurrences
that is what had happened Princess Zelda
descended from the sky accompanied by a
slutch monster slash monster
do we have to clean too like in the
sunshine oh my God exciting what
happened next to us by I took us by
surprise she then unleashed the beast
upon us
King Dory fan valiantly vanquished a
threat however he was Gravely injured by
the sludge during the battle
wait when I asked you guys if we ever
saw like a Zora like this before
did you guys mean this Grandpa because I
guess I think he was already an
assistant to King durfan in breath of
the wild was him huh
makes sense as well Princess Zelda she
vanished Without a Trace if Lord got out
that preached Zelda lost her mind and
harmed the Zoro King the resulting
terminal would be devastating honestly
it's kind of understandable if she would
lose her mind because after so many like
times of
same [\h__\h] happening over and over and
over again in The Legend of Zelda maybe
she shows like question if she's on the
right side
maybe the evil side is the good sign
even if it's a different Zelda still
like she must know
she must feel it the deja vu's and uh no
no
there should be a Zelda connection
network
that is why we're temporarily remaining
hidden within the pristine sanction
according to your story Princess Zelda
disappeared suddenly in the death's
beneath viral Castle
on the other hand she suddenly appeared
near Zora's domain and unleashed the
monster upon us there were others of
Truth I've become mercury still but from
Zora's perfect perspective no one thing
is clear It All Leads back
the sky with sword uh Sky it is disaster
to sludge the monster and even Princess
Zelda
it may well be that the answer to these
ridges can only be found Skyward Sword
sedon or the giato
a historian well acquainted with ruins
to investigate
I wonder if any progress has been made
okay so basically this is just never
way of saying go to sedon
a oh
is this a direct waterfall to him like
an easier way like if I would have taken
the first waterfall I would have
struggled more also there's something
else
that's just that ice okay
take that one
there's a shrine somewhere
maybe right up there
trendical
oh even further up
should I go even further or should I
look around oh
there's something interesting here
nearby
what
oh
no problem gives me a moment to ah
that would look very good on the start
that will probably kind of like trans
transform it into a katana
okay what
Boomerang oh well I'll go wait
um no uh
let me get rid of this
and then let me take this and then
let me take this and then
I'm gonna attach it to the boomerang I
guess I'll
probably not look ideal
and maybe I'll put it on wait what am I
doing wait wrong ah for some reason I
thought I was attaching the lizapo's
thing just that I saw just now God damn
it I'm stupid head empty okay whatever
whatever works what is this
learning stuff that Zora anecdote one
the solid water and the fluid spear As
Told by Prince Eden
and so are not associated with water
because of our Dwelling Place alone we
each also to varying extend possess the
ability to actually manipulate water we
use this gift for many purposes we use
it to swim faster to achieve Mighty lips
from waves below to gather fish and so
much more for me the true Awakening of
this ability that many of my childhood
jumps already charms
already possess Came Upon me quite
suddenly one day as I was training at
veiled Falls the rains look at my grasp
causing me to drop my spare I reached to
grab it but it was already why is
someone's like personal life story
written on this stone slab what the [\h__\h]
foreign
it's like so personally written like a
diary huh
so it would fall to the bottom of the
cliff never to be seen again
I knew that I must take hold of it and
at that moment droplets created the
stream extending from my outstretched
hand the water stream twisted and turned
until it finally took hold of my falling
Spear and definitely returned to my
grasp
the [\h__\h] why is this person here
right this wasn't breath of the wild it
did feel familiar
um
mifa
blue okay
oh
because that's all there is here
well there's a pap
uh
kind of a path leading
around on the left side
raise written first person so feel more
invested in the story
[Music]
should I go up there I'll take the
I'll take the
waterfall again oh
go in the dark snail a little just in
the fresh Corner what snails
it looks like a beer
movement speed
Coolio
up we go
okay
well then keep on adding on to it is
that seat on
is it you my bro
what's up
that's nice fish here
I need to try higher to catch some tasty
fish for my family
fish eat fish oh my God
wait these are the most
um
what's the word
you do that in real life too yeah true
but these are the most cannibalistic
species in the Zelda world
like the birds don't really eat birds
much I would say
the girl ones don't eat gorans unless
you see gorans as rocks but they don't
eat the corns grow and say no wrong
it's important to eat well okay I'll get
those fish
no
it's so hard to like get to the right
direction
where'd they go
I'm going to drown up
[Music]
and give up what do I
got enough stamina
can I take another bite off of my
sandwich
um
[Music]
sandwich debuff yes yes that is totally
it oh this elbow
alrighty
14 base damage
pretty decent
we could take the waterfall again but I
kind of want to walk
mifa Court yeah
she don't listen mifa Court
oh
whoa
oh crazy
[Music]
interesting
so weird
wow
try let me go to Shrine first hey
priorities
oh
no way
that's the first time I see something
like that
open that up immediately
how's the shrine even affected by that
didn't even have a door yet
um
[Music]
hmm
what kind of Shrine will it be hmm
okay
what
never been here before
[Music]
that
the intended way I mean it was a pretty
obvious one
but they were free of those like maybe
some people made themselves stairs
but what I've noticed is this is one of
those platforms that just stay in the
air on its own
um
so if this bridge alone doesn't do the
trick
and we might as well might be able to at
least jump yeah okay it doesn't it's not
long enough but it's long enough to jump
over
it does fall
wait what is this thing for did I not
attach it properly
oh it doesn't activate it
oh
I have to activate it
not under which time
wait
there doesn't really seem to be much of
a time limit
oh this is a little bit tilted but
okay okay
it does work now I almost never use
these no I haven't this is the first
time I see them no maybe not the first
time or the second time I see them in
the game
what is that for
there's two of those
um
I would think
ah to fly back oh okay
is it still activated yes
okay okay
nice nice nice nice
pretty simple so far
well we have an activating thingy we
have a ball we have many floating
activated oh capsules and the fingers
over there okay let me see it does it
push it away
that's what I thought whoa okay
so if that would consent us and the ball
to the other side
maybe even both at the same time
[Music]
foreign
I could shoot it
well is there like a
is there is a chest up there
wait before I go
that easy okay okay
um
okay
uh what
easy
[Music]
and Rose okay
so we got the chest
which was also very easy
overall
very easy shrine
there's like big versions of these you
know around the sky islands and all that
they're also just stay stay where you
leave them in the air this is like a
small version
Shrine sometimes it's nice to have easy
shrines
for six hours of streaming
okay I hope we get the cutscene so soon
we'll see fun maybe we'll get super
super
is that his name
I hope you get a cutscene I want to bite
in my sandwich while I'm looking at the
cutscene
who's that
cell phone I'm glad phones aren't this
big yet they're getting bigger and
bigger if they were this big I would
just [\h__\h] lose it
it's a switch but I'm sure you know that
you're just teasing me
[Music]
the action on the switch it's a pirapath
but it looks like it could be a switch
tooth
oh well
[Music]
um
oh no it's so short
he looks older now
but his voice is still the same very
young relatively young sounding one not
like a child but
um oh well
[Music]
I think he became taller and a bit more
strong looking
hmm
what
Donuts live the longest I would think
that's the stone people maybe because
they're just stones
[Music]
what what wait it's Stone people AKA
corones
um
if they die
do they become one with the mountains
and so on
is there lower on that because I feel
like
that's kind of cute
if they just turned back into normal
stones
and become one of the mountain or so
I think even if that is not official law
I think that's how I want to think about
it
eh corns are in probably Immortals since
an oot gorns get mountains at well yeah
I don't remember that [\h__\h]
no I think it's just kind of sweet to
imagine that you know they become one
with nature and in the end they're just
rocks
um give it back to Nature yeah
and then get eaten again maybe yeah
um
link it has been far too long I received
word that you had gone missing and was
beside myself of concern whatever could
have transpired
to think something like that could have
taken place beneath Hyrule castle and
after that you mysteriously awoke on a
sky island the sky could be that the sky
is the key to everything at all
hmm it seems so yeah ah my apologies I
have actually been wondering if those
floating Sky Islands could be the source
of the falling sludge
um
I mean they're literally coming from the
sky yes of course they are
that is why I have tasters or a
historian
with investigating ruined fragments and
all historical documents related to the
sky
yeah look up
as for me I am not a liberty to leave
this spot at present
as I am uniquely qualified to deal with
the Celestia although I mean I think I
see his point like um it's not like all
sky islands are bad
it's just something that's happening up
there I guess on those Sky Islands
specifically
yeah
so it's not necessarily the sky islands
of default it's just whatever is up
there
um
[Music]
wow that's pretty that's so pretty you
see old friends this place is the source
of the water that flows into the Zara's
domain domain
that is why I must use my power of water
manipulation to separate a sludge from
our water in order to clean it oh
we're not doing a good job though
if I seize Then I then solid water will
flow into our beloved home and there
will be much pain and suffering that is
why I cannot afford to live here no
matter what
say link does it seem that Prince
Zelda's whereabouts might not be related
to the floating sky islands and the
ruins if so perhaps you should go and
speak of our historian giato his many
years have blessed him with great wisdom
oh is he gonna be my buddy
because like
um
it's not gonna be you
I wonder the lake by the way I hope you
know that I'm truly happy to see you
again after such a long time apart my
dearest friend because I don't think
Sida is gonna have time to be my body
yeah I'm just very busy now busy man now
y'all my questions are often just for
rhetorical
visit me anytime you like
[Music]
oh
um Riven Raven is fussing again
his only daughter danma is on a solo
assignment I can understand why he'd be
worried but dunma is over 60 years old
oh
sure he's she still has some of the
mannerisms of childhood but she's a
first-rate soldier
as a veteran Soldier himself is simply
not fitting for him to get distracted
just because he's part apart from his
daughter
okay is that a quest a side quest
oh yeah
mifa court security report
day in and day out the sludge never
stops falling thanks to the tireless
efforts of Princeton the water flowing
into the domain has been kept somewhat
clean but the mountain path to Total
Lake and to dunma is completely covered
in sludge but you want to sneak over
there remember to bring lots of well
where do I get them
the reason why I have barely animals
because I was
they're like nowhere to find
[Music]
is there a good source for them
the yellow trees
yellow fruit
none here right
my first crap
what's it doing here
oh
it looks like a Pokemon
Pokemon
brain rot
I can't escape
oh
[Music]
did this exist in breath of the Wild
I just don't remember this for some
reason
let me kiss your feet
your mouth is fine too
you're so big mifa what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
that's so pretty
laughs
why is there oh there's a guard I was
gonna say why is there no guard to
protector from oh
please protect us
from me
oh
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
I'll stop
oh ancient um
hey
come to me
come on
thank you
that's good protect people from me
okay this is so pretty wait did you guys
tell me
if this was here before
ah they moved her from within the city
oh and they I guess they replace the
statue with the one that is me and sidon
makes sense
laughs
where is your friend
oh that's not so bad I'll just roll you
down the stairs actually okay this one
I'll do normally I don't like this
that you have to move around
but this one we can just roll
enjoy this one because this is basically
like a
uh a water slide go go
me
thank you
hello
come on he stops here okay no problem
oopsie
[Music]
I mean this is the most fun you've had
in his life
it's water slide
kind of anti-climatic how it stops
all the time
um
I'll just carry you
you love bullying them
I don't have the time
bully them unfortunately
[Music]
okay
uh
where are we going now
huh
total Lake
hotel Lake
cocoa
Lake
photo lake is Coco Lake what color was
that
um
a different blue where's my other blue
I'm gonna get rid of it
was that for
don't need that anymore
okay I also don't need the green one
anymore I think probably wait it's like
a purple actually not blue
okay
different flu known as Purple
oh this drains my stamina
and I
oh no ah okay only when I walk but it
rains it much faster
I mean I'm gonna Dash
turns it much faster than normal dashing
[Music]
okay what is the best way to get there
is
it's not that far I wonder if I can just
jump on the mountain and the rest will
go by foot while exploring I don't think
we can finish a whole Temple today
unless it's relatively simple
um
six hours I mean maybe we can
I guess it's all just a matter of
motivation what is that
why is that
is that normal
it's something that needs to be
investigated oh
is that gonna explode
the boxes three don'ts
yo hey I threw him down
um
[Music]
are you motivated
I'm still motivated especially when I'm
eating this yummy sandwich
that's me even more motivated
[\h__\h]
where is it oh okay whoa it's time to
eat my yummy food that I put meal
prepped look at all these dishes there's
so much variety too
a lot of those just have four
um
let's eat this in my food
oh wait there's
um
big yummy piece of meat
oh
[Music]
how do you do this correctly oh
fun
no
yo this weapon is really strong
because it it's got like
plus attack
sheesh I think the base weapon has lost
attack right
crisp a piece of meat oh
[\h__\h] the egg tart looks so good
[Music]
lots of lasalkas here
okay
it's pretty big
we will get yeah a chest Styles just
about to say Yahoo
for all this trouble
nice
should be done now
[Music]
oh
no I will present you with a bump
[Music]
so that he's definitely 100 in one shot
amazing chest ahead Oh you mean just one
word different one
oh
for free
wait line it's a boomerang attached with
Lionel stuff holy [\h__\h]
get rid of the normal Boomerang let's go
yo uh first Lionel weapon I could make
one
because I have some vinyl parts
I'm fighting one only once
but I'm still waiting um until I get to
the Detachment place and this was
looking really interesting to me I guess
it's
nothing in particular
okay let's follow the path
lots of Ambrose
or Splash fruit nearby did I miss it
true
oh there I see some
more enemies
game is so pretty
I think it's uh the prettiest one is
like sunny and bright because when it
gets kind of gloomy
it's it gets kind of mushy if you know
what I mean the graphics
really hard to see what's going on
[Music]
yeah the textures get muddy
but when it's sunny and on daytime then
it's I think fine
[Music]
stop messing with me
give me your insides
oh is the month making these sounds
like there's something up there
[Music]
nothing okay
okay
oh well hi there
what a waste
of my wife
oh my God
don't don't hey I feel bad for him is he
stuck or is he playing no he's fine
right
is he stuck
does he have nowhere to go
I feel bad oh no he made it oh he made
it I was the one that made him stuck
okay
you're just as slow if you dash
as if you don't Dash
in the mud okay so better to not try
because you just lose
oh we're here already
you just lose your stamina
I saw him
saw him
you also had a nightmare also had
nightmare today
gotta always stock up on meat I'm sorry
guys
oh
could you get here from the
from the wonderful
perhaps
oh
but we got a cool chest and we explored
you know hmm
don't don't always have to take a
shortcut
can't I drop my phone it got absolutely
destroyed then at the end I met
remembered that I had insurance it was
super high what
dreams are weird
ah we got a lot of Splash road too yeah
I don't know I'm gonna understand the
ways of historians can you not conduct
investigation more cautiously
oh dear I certainly hope that you did
not overhear me
um grumbling to myself like that it's
not as it sounds really jiato keeps
interacting with dangerous things when I
object he insists it's necessary for his
research
that makes things quite difficult for me
as it is my job to guard him that is why
I gave in to a moment of Gremlin oh
right do you see that opening here
yeah
he's cute isn't she
at the nightmare that kill ducks are
breaking into my house Through the
Windows
killer ducks
so super super little gone mad
damn
can you guys read on your own now I want
to take another bite
um
[Music]
it's broken
is she old oh yeah he is
dignified presentation yes the writing
looks like waves upon the stormy sea
extraordinary this ancient stone slate
was written by our door and answer
stress from the distant past and left of
Left for us to discover
um stand upon the land of skyfish
a droplet the Waterbury Bridge
Alice I cannot decipher it
um
oh link
my apologies I was deep and fought in
any case I have news I've made them
Monumental discovery about this Monument
this is undeniably an ancient door Stone
slate better still upon the surface
there appears to be a text regarding the
sky
however the Slate is broken and so I am
unable to read it in a satiety I deeply
wish that I could view the full text
unless I fear that my fins are tied fans
are trying to hit
uh what did I say
um
um it may not be clear for you but I
think this should be pretty clear to me
no
can you repeat
is it a riddle no you're gonna not
repeat you're not gonna repeat it for me
okay so think about the sky fish and
standing I think
yeah we have to repair it okay is it
like close by
um maybe above
yep
it should be blue
what was that
what is that
huh
is it just shiny ice oh that looks that
looked very magical to me
[Music]
um
colder that's all we're learning okay it
doesn't seem to be related to anything
or anyone
she's blue maybe she's a piece
you're not really blue more like purple
purple is just never blue
and green is just another yellow
and pink is just never red in the end
every color is the same color guys
just related to one another
you're now very good at shooting
close-up people either huh I'm not gonna
judge you because I wasn't deeper
my favorite color is all colors
it's all propaganda
you know back in the day you know in um
I don't know the 40s maybe
30s 20s The Roaring Twenties people used
to see black and white yeah
um evidence is in the black and white
movies yeah
but you know it's just like you know
there's there's there's obvious proof
that this is a fact by the looking at
the black and white movies people saw
and they also wear black and white yeah
and yet it's something of like a similar
matter as like you know whether or not
the Earth is flat or around
obviously the Earth is round and there's
proof for it but people oh
oh no fairy people still somehow seem to
think sometimes that they are that the
Earth is flat
um now here I am on the side of the
round office because there is preferred
but
there's also proof for the Earth and
everything to have been black and white
before
yes yes
always in the end I say follow the proof
guys
the proof is in the pudding
um
even if pudding doesn't clip me anymore
still then the proof is in the pudding
Trust
[Laughter]
another one that has forsaken me
[Applause]
no it's okay
it's okay oh yeah he still has full
apocalypse
um
probably just busy he surely hasn't like
completely forsaken me like next set
right
we're sad
uh that's it I'm exiting
and going to the next Set uh company
next company
what's happening what's happening I'm
not I'm just trying to make jokes I'm
just roasting you know but I'm not I'm
not I'm not mad I'm not mad
I mean I could be if I wanted to if I
wanted to be mad I could be mad
I'm not necessarily mad I'm just I'm
just playing it off
[Music]
okay now
on this day they're not man
the slab is close to the guy
I'm already too far
is that a chest
drop it
it is I think it is but drop it close to
me
hi
[Music]
oh you got a special
swords don't you
oh
oh pal sword
what is the old pal do
hmm
should I keep the labs is it good
I guess I'm not keeping it
um where the [\h__\h] am I going
um
real for real
father
whoa
maybe that will be really useful to use
in the temple
because I assume
maybe this stuff will be in the temple
as well
I thought
yeah
something guys
but it's okay I still have some more Opa
so I could use it it's great for the
past let's go go I can use the temple
then even if I run out of this one let's
see
um
I want to
I want to turn it like
[Music]
um
no you get what I want right
wait like this and then
this
[Music]
oh wait it's not a crook
whoa
thank you
incredible I can finally read it yes
it's my favorite real can stand upon the
land of the sky fish
okay and behold it's laughter view among
the floating rocks you see a droplet
Waits For You
okay
fruit is droplets shoot an arrow with
the mark of the king
do this task and you shall reveal the
most wondrous thing see the watery
Bridges resting spot with your own two
eyes that which connects the Zora to the
people of the Skies
can I write this down
never should take a picture
this important text actually tells us
how to journey into the sky though in
truth that mystery just leads us
straight to another one difficulty has
been overcome and yet another has
appeared in its wake
as it mentions the mark of the king
perhaps it would be prudent to consult
ah this is where you go find him
I assume that he will be returning from
his investigation of the sludge shortly
haha I know where he is
that's quite the riddle yeah I like the
the Rhymes though
do you have any song zones rhyme but I
wonder if they make this this um
these riddles and these like uh poems
rhyme in the game in general even
hmm
anyway where was the the on that side
that's the same waterfall right where
king the king is we had to talk to the
king now I assume
we did like spinal kids in this domain
to figure out where he is
oh
awesome
it's all connected to this waterfall
no
if I wanted to get a custom made full
print shirt with koala artwork made by
hookah bubble
I mean if it's just for you privately I
think you can do it
really
wait on it
[Music]
as long as you're not selling it
you just want to do it for yourself
and you can do it
I feel like some people already do that
kind of stuff anyway
or you know himself
I don't remember going up such a dirty
water
it's uh a different one
find it
music's nice here
because his music wasn't playing when I
first entered
whoa
it almost feels like it's a fairy
um
altar or something like that
[Music]
um
wait I did
was it that one
that was that one
that's the one I got it don't worry
don't worry don't worry
nice feel oh my oh thank you
I shouldn't
I shouldn't wear it though it feels like
a waste but if it breaks
we got so many Splash fruits I wonder
how many we'll need but now that I know
that the opal also works
fine
water texture looks nice especially with
the light reflecting
yo
I'm coming back
I'll see you sir King
and then what did I do
no I went I went ah wait I went straight
behind it I didn't even take the first
dive wait wait wait wait
keep on swimming keep on swimming oh
shh easy
okay
I wonder what the kids say
where he is but
in any case
we don't need to know hi
hi what if I splash some water on him do
you think that'll help him
[Music]
yes progress has been made indeed
so you have spoken with gr2
you say that the mark of the King was
mentioned on the stone slate that was
restored
oh lion did you know of it
the mark of King refers to Zora King's
scale oh
your scale doesn't hurt if I take one
hmm
please let me have one
Shrine underneath the first place oh I
don't think I did that one yet
um but it's okay we did another close
one for now we clay
might want to take a couple I make cool
armor um
I have a rooted called by the name you
mentioned in an ancient ritual however
none remain who know how it was used
oh you just refuse it to an arrow
probably this particular scale of mine
may prove useful to you by all means
take a few a few
there is no need for restraint this is
nothing to me if you run out Simply
return an acquire more then grow back
fast
he takes it with humor
you gave me five oh yeah
you gave me five two oh they look pretty
after all that has transpired enough to
much reflection I've come to a
realization I must truly be getting on
in years to have allowed a mere monster
to catch me off guard
perhaps the time is nearing for me to
pass the title of King on to sedon
in any case
that is the matter
for another day
after the chaos surrounding this launch
has quieted
please inform us lead on about my
situation
and about the king's scale
tell him that there is no need to worry
about me tell him that he must go forth
and do what needs to be done
alrighty Coolio
wait wait
if we just go back to see it on this
here and it's still in the same place
then we could just go here yeah
ugh
what a massage
oh by the way uh no schedule for next
week it may be Sunday but no schedule
um
and
Maybe
maybe I'll keep um
it's a secret like
until each day whether I'll stream or
not like it'll be happening very
spontaneously
because well safety
it's not only about my safety but about
I'm a safety so
please understand if things will be a
bit mysterious
hmm
[Music]
but I think I'll stream tomorrow
oh that is the door armor it really is
perfect on you I have no doubt that it
will help you when you search for
Princess Zelda speaking of have you
found anything
my father was attacked by a monster hey
and that Princess Zelda Unleashed it
upon him what could that possibly mean
well for now I feel all we can do is
take my father this word and try not to
let all concern overcome us
link thank you for telling me about my
father Princess Zelda descending from
the sky not to mention the monster and
that filthy sludge it seems our courses
Skyward Sword we now know that the mark
of the king written off on the Slate
refers to my father's scale the only
remaining mystery is that of the land of
the sky fish on the floating Rock and
the shape of a droplet
hmm
stand upon the land of the sky fish that
must be referring to an actual location
of some sort I'm sure that if we locate
the land of the skyfish it will lead us
through the floating rock that is the
shape of the droplet
um Scottish
maybe that's the shape of a fish when
looking from above
because that even looks like it's not
sludgy and I can even go up
[Music]
let me look from Sky Map
oh yeah yeah that's it
I got it how do I tell you
my head
but I know should I take a photo hmm
[Music]
okay maybe I should take a photo
or I go up there alone
[Music]
I need to do the puzzle what puzzle
puzzle
oh I need to do the whole thing on my
own like stand there
and do the whole thing okay
[Music]
you don't mean with puzzle uh that I
have to add all these little Stones back
onto the islands right
hopefully not
[Music]
um
nice girls around
very nice it's a cute
cute
this is like
the
washing game power power
washing what
no
I lost its power or does it have to
charge oh okay
I just because now I didn't do it did I
do too many after one another
I'm watching Sim
[Music]
s Mario sunshine sunshine yes Super
Mario Sunshine
oh Blue Moon uh blue uh what Blue Moon
Blue uh
Red Sun Moon
I have no idea what I'm saying
oh
what am I looking for here
it's scary
let me take a bite and you guys can look
at Zelda being crazy
the
um
the previous dungeon the fire one
we did that one pretty fast I think
right
two hours maximum
do you think this one will be longer
or shorter
under two hours right yeah I think so
cool
this one's even easier okay uh anyway
what the [\h__\h] do we do something like
droplet that says something about a
droplet this one no what what what I'm
looking for
cool
uh and then what shoot through or fly
through what did they say
[Music]
or do I take a picture
I found it fast
you found it the same way shoot the
scale oh yeah all right yeah yeah
fruit or on
there it is
okay I thought it woke up it would go
lower
yeah yeah
what
Noni
what does that do whoa oh
is that the path to the temple
oh
I hope there's no caught up here
what's that
ah should I talk to siron
oh hello
on Moshi Moshi
I did something really cool
something incredible
what
should other him wait no one Cura
lady
isn't that your wife
's fiancee
oh yeah it made yourself a play mat um
next month like a wallpaper oh
I don't even remember what I I'm getting
for next month but I'm getting something
for sure
I can eat no
lady Yona it is far too dangerous for
you to be here is she gonna be my
companion oh wait she could be she looks
special
darling I came here because there is
something I need to speak with you about
I have been thinking for quite some time
hello there link
oh
what has happened my friend did you
figure something out
well if you were looking up there I feel
like you would see
it's kind of even looking in the same in
the in the right direction the whole
time
but maybe he was distracted by his wife
um
yeah he probably was distracted he was
looking elsewhere
yourself to ancient stone slates written
on the pillar a pillar of light appeared
if the words upon the stone Slade are
correct the path to the sky may open up
if we investigate that location well
done link this is a huge development
I see
my dear sit on
because like
this doesn't always have to be like a
different one than from breath of the
Wild
it always is so far a new character not
the same one as before that helped you
so it will be her yeah
[Music]
as I was just about to say for a long
time I have been concerned that you are
holding yourself back and not acting as
freely as I would have expected but my
love if you and Link
no
are you another one from you oh God damn
it
I'm certain you shall I want her
she'll be able to overcome whatever
danger awaits
that is undoubtedly true however
whatever is troubling you sit on why are
you hesitating so oh it is simply that
monster oh
no worries
flashlight
ambusher of mifa chord
oh easy easy guys easy
we can take care of the water at least
for a little while do not fret about the
domain
you're right it's ever it is up to you
me lady link please I must ask you to
fight with me one more time
yeah I can do it alone
the Beast is protecting its body with a
sludge
it is by the opponent certainly but we
must not falter when an opportunity
presents itself call out to me
and
I shall use my power to envelop in water
justly shielding you from our film to
that at that point you may shoot forth
the water as an attack by swinging your
weapon
[Music]
I can do that with my opal weapon
but it is also Shield okay
uh when students always tried she can
create a bubble of water that blocks an
incoming enemy attack if you swing your
weapon is one a little bit child into a
long range strike
if I do it without him
[Laughter]
I'm not even gonna let him participate
show me your inside oh
whoa thanks dude yeah
is it gonna turn sludgy again
it's got free legs okay let's let's try
let's give him a chance
oh okay what Aya swing button oh cool I
thought it would be like a little bit
wider though
it has to be pretty
um accurate
Poland was helping too
it might ever swing a wag weapon oh okay
makes sense because I'm using a lance
weapon
yeah yeah everyone starts your blue
hey we are unharmed thank goodness lady
your life something had happened to you
I in any case it is possible that
another monster will appear I suggest
that you return to the domain at once
thank you for the sentiment siren
however more importantly we must
consider what Sterling spoke of earlier
the pillar of light that he said
appeared at the reservoir begs to be
investigated
this may be our opportunity to learn the
cause of this Lodge falling on the sky
or even princess Zelda's whereabouts
leave this place to us dear student your
friend needs your help getting to the
bottom of this mystery okay okay you do
not entrust this task to us already we
will not be on our own for long we shall
be just fine
but
my darling just shut up and go elsewhere
I want to be alone with my girls
but you're the princess of the Sora one
day you will lead the people of your
beloved domain I can see right through
you whoever you want me to or not you're
yielding to the fear of losing someone
you love again
you must overcome your past and face
whatever the future holds of Courage
demo demo
enough is enough you're acting not like
yourself
[Music]
foolish you must leave this place to me
sweet you don't do not get lost in the
past you must keep moving ever onward
just follow your heart as you always do
[Music]
I want to take her instead can we leave
sidon behind
he's got like you know leader duties in
my opinion
um
especially you know the thing is you
know how how
um
dying the king is right now
if you are in a kingdom
and there is no one there of the
kids
of a king when the King dies
there's a high chance
that they will overthrow you
know
and when you come back when the kids
come back the kingdom suddenly belongs
to someone else
so one of at least one
of the
with the word I forgot
at least one of them should always be
there like
kids otherwise you know he won't be able
to assert dominance heirs he has heirs
yes
um
saying that has the same kind of
situation but you know
because even when there were Starks in
Winterfell I feel like they got [\h__\h]
over often yeah
anyway it was all right I swear it I'm
not going anywhere
I see and there it is Claire's day I was
giving in to my fear of once more losing
someone I love
I I
I leave this place to you my love
haha
he's motivated let's go I shall Blaze on
the head my friend
it seems Steven has finally put his
doubts behind him and returned to his
usual Fearless self he's Fearless ah
I'm so glad
all this time he was clinging to regret
over being unable to save his precious
sister mifa my poor tormented suit
and to think he was unknowingly
paralyzed from taking action because he
feared losing me as well yet he has
overcome his trial and placed his faith
in me at last the synonym I knew and
Love Has Come Back to Me
please take care of him
okay let me just open the treasure chest
yeah okay
our
gems more powerful when they're in a
magic scepter
I'd like to know
is it worth keeping
yeah 100
um
[Music]
should I make another water one I'll
just make one when we run out
um but I want to make something with the
scepter
or could we fuse
oh we could fuse
something like this
I don't know if you use these things yet
um
[Music]
Maybe
this would work well I think
I think that fits the Claymore too
oh
what's up
gems good for one sapphire is good for
scepters
oh Sapphire specifically
[Music]
hey where am I going
where am I going
[Music]
this way is it
okay I guess we're going into the temple
Pokemon show
kind of wrong direction
not cool but
to the reservoir
it's in the city isn't it
still quite a bit oh really
we're going uh to be at seven hours
in 10 minutes but I'm I'm all right I'm
fine
I'm okay
who's that
is
falling into the water
mmm
question mark is what I want to be oh
okay okay thank you
okay
sit down what's up tall man damn you're
so big
oh so that is the clue for reaching the
sky
can I eat this is a sign that I can eat
right
oh
[Music]
hmm
what is he doing
oh wow
he had the absolute left
um
[Music]
does that mean that like
the
[Music]
um
what do you call that again
the thing that we're just saying right
now I saw something like that somewhere
else
maybe it's not
like
meant to be dodged maybe it's meant to
be jumped into
oh yeah Whirlpool
um
I thought that was like
really really dangerous
oh like in Wind Waker it might take her
somewhere yeah
hmm interesting
IRL is dangerous yeah
where are we
are we on the ground
no we're still we're still
in the surface
supposedly
okay
the chest
we could probably um just Ascend over
there
but why are these like pieces there as
if I had to build something
oh
what
[Music]
Shish
RV my God
I guess I'll get rid of little Sapphire
sword for now
dang that's not even uh fused to
anything yet
I'm already so strong
right I don't think it was fuse oh
there's a there's a thing for water over
there
for for exploding it
but what if we first just sent and then
make it explode
oh wait a second
this has got to be
a bit closer
15 on base but the wet above oh
see their wet puff is also uh because
like what oh wait I can't ascend is it
because all all Zoar weapons have a wet
buff
okay
baby
[Music]
yeah
I almost missed
nice
does that reveal anything else
not sure
maybe before we go inside we should have
gone to a shrine once
I mean there's a shrine actually on the
way again
[Music]
right there yes
no a shrine I didn't mean a shrine I
mean the the statue to get uh
an extra
um heart was a potato
actually after that one maybe we can get
both
if you're having fun can I love again
you'll live let's go
that was some really short two hours it
feels like he told me that yesterday
actually that was long two hours long
two hours
well you told me that yesterday
uh
what is that more water do we just have
to keep on adding more and more water
and then we'll reach the point where we
want to go
very nice whoa
whoa and all these things I can't take
but this one's kind of weak it's such a
true masters of this Shield can redirect
attacks as a rock
redirects brushing water
what
I'll take it because on its own is
already stronger than that one
throw it up there
yeah yo oh
does the Royal Shield breaks super fast
in this game too I actually don't know I
haven't really experimented with it
maybe it does maybe it doesn't
there's a
one over there
do I have anything for swimming speed
yet I don't think I do until I
I mean in terms of I'm there
nice work thank you hey
what's this
whoa that was close
let's go be careful
[Music]
that's open
uh that's that's where I came from
you almost shot me
more friendly fire please
oh
oh I could teleport up there I guess
I just want to see if I missed anything
no not really
okay
I'm walking
did you hear
me oh oh [\h__\h] won't I
isn't this dangerous
will it will the water break the gate
yeah I mean I can use uniform but I'm
more thinking like won't I get like
stuck like in the Titanic
uh oopsie
[Music]
oh no it's pretty low okay I thought it
would fill up everything
how do I get out though because it was
so close
wait is that the shrine or is it not
oh what
no problemo
oh well that seems familiar doesn't it
it's
something we saw before in temples but
only in temples
[Music]
ah that does bring me to the temple it's
not a a shrine but then first let me see
if there's something up there
a new Little Mermaid no I didn't watch
it yet maybe I should maybe I should is
it on this night plus or do I have to go
to the cinema
I think I thought that it wasn't Disney
Plus
there was a chest and a pipe what
what there's only
um oh yeah
um yeah
wasn't that good
wait why did that not work
too wet to burn
do I need to cover it
wind
s
[Music]
yeah
that's snowing cute
um what
you're still in and then fire
I think I blew it out
oh
[Music]
wait
don't go away too then
a double click
okay
um
that just makes no sense guys
I want to believe but
yeah I know
I think you are making up things but the
thing is I was thinking they're too far
away these things
I can't reached up the planks
and I think we're at the maximum level
of
um water
um
I dropped my flame emitter
ah man I don't care it's probably not
that important what's in there anyway
thank you
yeah some gem or a charge who knows
[Music]
oh yeah oh yeah
thank you
[Music]
oh
water temple in the sky are we gonna
find if it would have just been
underground but I was just uh at oh
at least they teleported me I was gonna
say like that's gonna be annoying to get
out again
a waterfall a waterfall this sentence
from the sky
link what happens is you're doing
so you activated a mysterious device in
the ruins and then the waterfall
appeared ah I believe I understand to
Azora a wonderful is no different from a
path that must be the demeaning behind
Waterway Bridge
um
if we climb this waterfall we shall
Ascend into the sky
link I know you could do it my belief in
you is that it's well places ever
I don't know for fish it feels wrong for
him to have such
like okay when he when he doesn't smile
like that I guess their zigzag shape but
when he smiles
they just seem so human like
[Music]
hmm
was it normally always a male voice
until now but not that that sounded like
Zelda normally it was always like
whoever you know they are connected to
but that's Zelda calling me yeah
like Fortune his bird ancestor was
calling right
right
oh it's been a year since paper night
really
before night anniversary
oh yeah
I feel like I thought it was longer than
that
oh
oh he heard it but wasn't she called it
for me
okay let's go
um
Napoli we can activate something at the
top
what's up
and then we'll leave once to go to
um
get another maybe stamina
whoa
[Music]
okay
we go up high but not as high as last
time in the burb Temple
what the [\h__\h] is that
new enemy
I swear the bombs
interesting
why
is the reason
we are not in not up that high
but suddenly when I fly the gravity you
can't tell me you they fought that
through properly low gravity and jumping
but once I use my
my parachute
it suddenly changes what is it whoa
I'm inside
is it gonna hurt me
no
okay
um
am I supposed to like move them can I do
that oh
my oh my and then can I shoot them to
activate them faster
no
[Laughter]
other bubble
wait can you activate them faster
somehow
[Music]
your chest
I mean
I really don't need to rely on these
bubbles all the time but oh well oh
smash them on the ground
[Music]
okay okay whoa come on okay
I killed these weapons
[Music]
I wish I could like place them somewhere
ah [\h__\h] you know
so pause topaz was electricity right
um yeah okay
we'll take that
sad
yo
cool stuff what do you say sit on
oh what is this place my body it feels
as light as a feather this is a strange
Place indeed but right now we must focus
on locating the source of the sludge
link it is time to divide and conquer
let's split up for the time being
oh you go the easy way yeah
what if I follow him
let me know what
what to do what it's all night huh he
just left them there
soldiers
what am I supposed to do can I swim up
the sludge
can I clean it oh wait oh honey
can I fly with the bubbles I can be one
with the Bubba
bubble bubble pop bubble bubble pop
oh
swim sweep don't worry link you won't
drown in there
okay I'm ready
take some time to get to the destination
doesn't it
well
it takes a bit too much time I have to
wait for it to
I could spawn these a little bit earlier
I wouldn't mind
[Music]
oh there we go yeah it's so slow
because we need to learn to work with
patients
oh no
what's up oh [\h__\h] whoa what are those
come on
thank you
oh they're strong I'm fighting in slow
motion in my knobs
I feel like I am or is it just a weapon
I told him it's not fighting in slow
motion
it's been to win okay
just a weapon oh
[Music]
it's the water hydrants all over again
that we had to use in the fire dungeon
as well
what the [\h__\h]
what
what the Mars rover
oh my God this is literally
Super Mario Sunshine oh my God
it's about the same amount of satisfying
too
to clean everything up
let's Splatoon free
oh another map
for underground right or was it
overground yeah underground
um
at the bottom right
thanks
a girl
now hold on
are they hiding something special down
here that they don't want me to find I
[Music]
wish
no
I won't get rewarded for doing this man
okay
ah
it's already annoying me a little bit
a little gravity is it gonna be in the
temple too of course it will wanted to
oh yes it will
but this will help us at least what the
dirt we don't have to carry around the
stupid hydrants right
yeah that's right because you can attach
any Zona at The Voice
makes sense
come on
please uh
nothing
oh boy
oh another treasure chest
it's more alive kit
a hydrant in the capsule
if you look at it differently
hydrant in
bubble
my opal sword is badly damaged how do I
clean that up
I feel like I have to yeah because it's
it's malfunctioning
ah but even if I fix him he's just gonna
spit out water huh
okay
maybe he doesn't need fixing wait a
second
how do we move on but no
what this is not the right path because
how do I get from
I guess I climb
but this one's okay never mind
[\h__\h]
there it goes okay not gonna do that
again
aim of iPhone and whoa the shot
but am I not gonna throw my
uh sword then
um
or is it not the case with these kind of
weapons
oh oh
I'll go there maybe
but even though it seems separate yeah
but of course there's a chest
of course
what other fruits are your friends too
yeah
reactions right now
Zelda Link what are you doing stand up
[Music]
oh I don't think I've had any of these
just that's actually oh that might be
one of the most useful
uh capsules you could get because
you can place them anywhere and use them
as a nice platform
to cross anything
so I reached a shrine but I kind of
skipped this place should I go there too
I'll activate the shrine first
shoot them for platform arrows what
love them
they seem very helpful
and see it's this thing after all that
has to do with the temple but this time
it's not covered up like the other one
um
never mind oh
[Music]
mm-hmm
this one no good
let's try no good
I really you're giving me
for that
I almost feel ashamed wait can I rewind
this ah no way
the chest though
oh
hey
interesting way of getting it
holy [\h__\h]
do you get it back
I had too much momentum
[Music]
a response okay good that's so nice of
them
okay
um what what where where
I am here
wait I can't do it while I'm inside now
we're going with the chest
hopefully not making it more heavy
oh wow
okay
I'll wait until it's my turn only time
you really lose items is with something
like a falling
star falls into an area and is destroyed
oh
okay
all right
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
oh that's mean
let me go
back oh oh let's save
yeah
ah
wait
is it like a should I place it like a
ramp like diagonal
I think that's maybe good enough and
does it then
stick to it or
let's go
oh
what ah it bounces off I don't know if
it's supposed to do something else but
it at least reaches a good height
okay okay okay
as long as I'm part of it
oh this is doing it the way I imagine
okay
oh sure and this triangle is kind of
nice and also as I've been noticing you
don't really take fall damage and with
this
kind of gravity for sure
let me take one last the very last
because then it's finished huge bite
from my sandwich
um
[Music]
[Applause]
that was smoothie
hmm
okay no more snacking unless maybe some
chocolate in between but
the big snacking is over
wait how many did I have I don't say
things
I'll go now
[Music]
um
I'll just go to Lookout Landing again
Maya please ask a question please just
ask the question
what does the low gravity water ball do
to the ramp booming
that was a flat joke
um
right is that new
I'll take a stamina container and a hard
container because now I got two things
[Music]
addicted to this game
no how many
you guys I went to the
pet food store or pet store pet food pet
food store again
that has you know like a million
different types of cat food and I
realized that you know I've been feeding
my cats uh
the food that has been kind of
recommended at least the brand that has
been recommended from the
um
[Music]
pet
doctor
vet
and I realized so that that one
it actually
also has wheat
and that kind of stuff in it
and generally I mean I don't know I feel
like my cats are fine with it but over a
long time I don't think it's so healthy
so I thought okay how about this time I
buy something else normally normally my
cats will pretty much eat any kind of
kibble I have yet to seen them reject
one
so I thought I would this will be fine
and I asked the lady at the store which
brand here does not do
we took
in their Kibbles
and she specifically pointed out one to
me
that had like so so many different
flavors and I thought oh fun my cats
will appreciate that surely
um and all of them almost no I think all
of them are like somewhat
um focused on meat and they have like
crazy kind of combinations
like I feel like something would say
wild boar meat and rabbit or something
like that
you know
it's a very wild one
a lot of combinations sounded very wild
and it was usually like 70 meat and 30
like veggies or so but no wheat I
thought okay good you know what they
have like tiny portion or small portion
bags middle portion bags and huge
portion bags but since I just want to
test it out I'm gonna
just buy from almost every flavor
just a tiny one and
I think one tiny bag of those would
maybe work for or be enough for a week
or two
that is if they would eat it now I
bought like nothing 10 different
flavors and this food is pretty
expensive I spent
60 bucks at the pet food store
um and I I started by giving them a
choice of two
and they're rejecting it they they don't
care for it
they don't want it that's the first time
now I'm wondering if I should give back
the other ones before I open them
because I feel like the other ones are
not going to be much different
the two that I did open they also have
like a a really strong
meat odor I guess like people is also
smell strong I would say but this new
stuff fish it smells very meaty what am
I doing I don't know
and what I understand I understand
so yeah I think it's like too strong
taste and smell wise for them or they
just I don't know maybe they're also you
know typical cats just although not
typical because usually mine don't
refuse this kind of stuff
um
so wild force so the last kitties that's
what I'm thinking
so maybe I should bring back the other
ones so it's kind of sad because I was
hopeful
about it is I felt like I was giving my
cats like good quality food and I would
say it's definitely good quality food
it's not what I expected
it is what is happening
but not quite the way I thought
okay
what's happening
yeah anyway definitely high quality
uh
but I guess too high quality for my cats
it's actually not the first time
whoops
because whenever I try to offer like you
know raw meat when I'm cooking
Robbie for raw chicken or whatever my
old cat used to eat that
these kitty cats nah
but even when it's cooked I also think
they didn't like it when it's cooked
to be honest
oh you scare me
what am I doing yo
you're nice
okay I don't need to I don't need to
apply my mother
[Music]
um
can swim up here
I suppose
what kind of food have you been
successful with any kind of kibble
that looks more normal
from packaging and yeah like the
supermarket cables they're all okay but
they they all [\h__\h] have wheat inside
all of it is infested with it
we go this way
it's not kind of far
hmm
yeah we could we go
[Music]
oh I meant even the waterfall looked
kind of little
um
anyway I guess I'll
guess I'll go back
and bring back the rest as long as it's
not open and I do have the receipt still
I think
sometimes I just don't get the receipts
because I feel like oh I won't need them
but in this case I did get it and I'm
actually glad I did
um just had to switch to anti-alert
Allergy prescription food
I love it it's ridiculous expensive of
course it is of course it is
yeah I'll see what our other food they
have that has no wheat hopefully
different brand also has
no no wheat Kibbles
[Music]
they deserve the best but when they
reject the best what can I do
what can I do
they say it was true
yo prioritize your kitty cat
you're you're real
kitty cat
I'm a cat lover I would absolutely
support that
whoa oh
I rarely get like one shot headshots on
these guys
[Music]
I got so much stamina
did the other one died
what the [\h__\h] is that damage guys
I'm glad I got one extra heart
the items fall so slowly
or was that just my imagination
[Music]
thank you
might need to upgrade some armor oh
actually
I mean I upgraded some but I I mean hmm
not the right one I suppose which one
did I upgrade I think this one
no did I
I upgraded the wait where can you see
where can you see what you upgraded
I think the most basic one yeah this one
are two stars
and created those I can totally take off
the
yeah the the
[Music]
cold resistance things
eight
I still need the top but I can switch to
this
eight
I gave those two upgrades
um
this one I'll I gave one upgrade
the Barbarian armor I gave one as well
yeah but my set my the one full set that
I have with
uh double upgrade is the basic one but I
could still go down and upgrade the the
the
swimming one
because I guess we'll be wearing it all
the time
at this point most of your arm I want to
be upgraded twice minimum for real for
real for real
I think for now within the Temple we'll
be fine with two upgraded pieces don't
you think
or should I go and upgrade the Zora
armor
we have strong weapons at least
this was the first temple I did you'll
be fine okay yeah I mean
that seems
like it makes sense let's get rid of
that
holy [\h__\h]
those weapons are looking crazy
okay
um
[Music]
why does it continue
whoops
let me get an overview oh
yeah that was where I needed to go
did you come from the other side
yes why let me join you
let's travel back in time what happened
to the other one
let's go I ain't got all day
hurry up hurry up
disappointing
probably because it was already chilling
quite some time
what is ah this is the generator
also at the pet store the pet food store
elaborate Labrador
um a puppy it's so cute
it kept on getting distracted
and it was so small and was like wobbly
oh my God puppies are so cute looking
out
[Music]
I I said this last time I think but I
need to go to this pet food store more
often because every time I go
the animals are made I meet make me so
happy oh what is this
hey why are these here
am I making a bridge why are there so
many of these platforms
hmm
what
am I making a bridge
above me is a chest
[Music]
maybe if these ones are for me to build
a bridge so I can stand on it
[Music]
teasing so much
hey thank you oh my god Trevor G Super
Chat incoming I've noticed you only send
one when I sneeze these games
no no no we're good no we're good
I can see the future
[Music]
can they give me other things
this one's about to break I guess I
gotta make a new one with the magic
scepter anyway
yeah
ah sneezery snooze
out of my nose
okay in my nose
thank you thank you thank you guys
where is he
what happened and yeah I'm guessing
we're making a ramp like in the shrine
because that's the only thing I can
think of to make it go upwards
I would say
is one enough
okay that's pretty good is it
all right don't oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah probably fine
yeah very long bridge she could do the
trick too but what have we learned and
the shrine often what you do in the
temple Shrine the shrine right before
the temple
just shows you
what you will have to do later on as
well
[Music]
don't be a weapon don't be a weapon
don't be a weapon don't be a shield
don't be a shield don't be a bull
just what I need to make my new scepter
oh
sneeze a day it is
how much have I sneezed today too many
times
oh by the way I was too shy to ask if I
could uh pet the puppy but I can tell
you yes
I am full of regret
as you could imagine
why did I not ask to pet the puppy
[Music]
oh radish is pretty rare I feel like
I'll be too cute
you feel no sympathy
no worries you're going to see Bubbles
and Bubbles not a puppy anymore
but yeah sure sure
yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
I love Amish dogs
you know I enjoy Bubba as long as he's
like on Amish stream like a voice
so
in terms of that I'm still like a
teammate but I feel teammates real
teammates but still still enjoy Bubba
IRL
I am
I am not a good teammate
I actually know I mean She Knows by you
know first-hand experience
that I am
not that impressed by Bubba
because I am after all
a cat person she knows that
do I need anything else here
oh he's already there
you little [\h__\h]
so much for parting ways how'd you get
here huh
don't believe it don't buy your story
what's with these weapons
if this was your first dungeon you got
some crazy ass weapons
this is obviously not a dungeon you're
doing the first try at first first time
what the [\h__\h]
why would you do this as your first
dungeon
foolish chicken
oh my God
oh
God
abort abort ship oh
it flies
but that went up so steep
didn't feel safe
here we are
this really is such a strange place my
body felt light as air allowing me to
soar surprisingly high when I was
climbing the waterfalls as we are in an
unfamiliar place let us proceed with
caution link please take care as you
forge your head really that's all you
say
[Music]
he did it
um oh there we go we lose a weapon
good stuff
[Music]
don't make me bathing that [\h__\h]
oh oh I was wondering why I couldn't
move yeah okay
for real wait
uh-huh
okay Noble mighty
mighty
uh yeah get rid of this one
It's mighty
24.
where's the stuff
what's that is that one of those laser
thingies
should I
should I Forge these uh fused these
oh
do I have something oh yeah I could feel
this
okay
beam emitter oh
[Music]
okay
I got them okay
because then I guess it just emits a
straight beam
um
[Music]
I could see that being
interesting
um
that's not nearly long enough and misses
most of the time really wanna heal up
yeah but look at him once we're inside
right
from what I can tell all of the sludge
waterfalls are flowing from the ruins
above here in other words if there is a
source for this sludge somewhere it must
be
like once you're amply prepared let us
Dive Right In
am I going into a battle
oh okay because it sounds like
you need to be so careful
I'm not even straight up going it's not
even forcing me
I guess he's leaving okay
um
let's have a fresh pie
oh let's go
oh
what about these other things
I wanna explore
whoa
wow
Temple
the great Wellspring of Hyrule
[Music]
interesting
a
lot of Temple Music very pretty
[Laughter]
wanna go on the side uh wait do I have
that is this Temple wait it seems kind
of small and so easily to overview
what
so I'll be going up there anyway
probably home
doesn't quite feel like I'm in the
temple
it's so open
how magnificent to think that such a
structure was floating in the sky above
our owns or is the main
link look
ugh
that is surely the source of the slush
I'm certain of it
yeah
looks like a slime on
we must do something about it
what's it called in English
I think slime on it and German but
sludgemon
by any chance
slash
is it called sludge the Pokemon
a Grammer
Muk yeah that's the one
ah
yeah oh
sorry I yawned so often because I'm
trying to deep breather breathe a deeper
but I failed most of the time my my
Yarns get interrupted
[Music]
like you see it do you not yeah I I said
we turned them all on the water will
overpower the sludge or clean it or
clean what's like oh maybe that under
all this Lodge is a monster and we'll
fight that
once we clean it
if we could only make use of that water
or maybe not maybe I'm just imagining
things and it's all in my head
in any case we gotta activate the gate
to really make it begin
I had that doctors at a stressful what
not being able to finish doing yawns or
feeling like you can't breathe
oh
it's here well I saw that I saw him it
seems it did not work
but you saw it too did you not
using the mechanism did have effect
there simply was not enough water water
is there any airport yeah it comes out
if you're dirty ear
like you can't fill in your lungs stress
foreign
[Music]
this is small it only has two floors
it's really small smallest Temple
it happened yet again only this time I
heard the voice loud and clear and
German I don't understand German maybe
you can translate for me link yeah oh oh
is that true we have to activate all the
best awesome well I'll leave it to you
link
you do the thing
um
[Music]
whoa okay it shoots a straight beam if
you do the jump attack
um
okay where to go first this one seems
accessible
relatively
you gotta go now okay bye bye thanks for
coming
you guys take care of this one hit
wonders please
it's not worth my time
[Music]
nothing besides a pretty pond
I'm glad your history and Buzz thank you
you it felt weird to stream again after
two days of not streaming felt like I
had a vacation
because it's like rarely happens
but it wasn't it was still stressful
though
I've had lots to do
I really need like a real vacation where
I don't have things to do
oh [\h__\h]
in a way guys
oh there is a ball
okay if that dungeon is so small oops we
really don't need to
be too careful with our materials really
ouch
oh is this one stronger the UK trip hmm
yeah I guess for the UK trip
I don't think uh I don't really know if
I could like stream normally anyway I
think I was gonna just prepare videos
anyway because
well it will be a really short trip and
I don't think I can stream in the hotel
and I also feel awkward like you know
with rmt
I remember one time when me and rmt wait
it's a bow it's a bulky wow it's a bull
um when I was in in Greece with her
I felt like
um
also not comfortable to stream right but
but
we have to
fix this
oh yes
ah to go up to the next one
but I did I didn't stream but I I had to
do one recording
um
remember them I went I woke up early
early in the morning of my vacation
to do recording and then we waited for
like an hour
because someone was late
um
where does this ball go I didn't see a
hole do we send it up there
but during that time I send rmt away
basically she was just gone for a little
bit maybe we send it up
hmm yeah yeah yeah
okay let's try that
we joke about when you're away but it
would all be more sad knowing I could
take
it forcing yourself to stream when you
don't want to I'm not
enforced I don't feel like I I am forced
but yeah
yeah the rmt trip it's
a little adventure trip
yeah I I almost like you won't be
streaming but I think it's only like
what three nights Maybe
let's swim on the water or will it
fall down oh nice
ah wait
ah okay
it seems like we do have to drain the
water
hey wait for me wait for me
well shouldn't be too difficult
let's just stay of course not
but I mean
which rain is for
some time
should we just wait
thank you bye bye
Bali in the future the Bali or anywhere
I don't know I don't mind I don't care
where but wait it's gonna ah wait uh
even has
the perfect size for it oh wait don't
have to activate it first
was it activated
[Music]
but I told you last time that I don't
have
time for a prop application until a
couple months later until like late fall
what a wheel
what what'd you say about the water
wheel
you see
do you wanna
do something here
[\h__\h] did I miss
did I miss
Charlene has to do with you
[Music]
seems like a stretch to me what we just
did I feel like tooling would have
worked as well
[Music]
indeed
the light stick okay I can count
thank you
hey yay
next we go to
music changing
the other side with three of them
three three
of them
but there's a B12 are we like in
ah wait locations are here thank you
I wonder which one you should go to next
mini boss soon I wouldn't mind the mini
boss
um
got to be one
oh okay
try oh wait is it here
[Music]
I go from with my water Shields
foreign
[Music]
there needs to be a ball in there
he's over there
um
foreign
[Music]
how do I get you over to the other side
ah
[Music]
um eight hours tend to be gaming well
I did warn you guys that it might be 10
hours but I didn't even believe myself
when I said that oh
oh
so much yawning and sneezing today
I ain't fooling around yeah
just like old times hey
yeah well we'll definitely finish the
the shrine I I will not at the temple I
will not
um
ended before
that'll be ridiculous
what do I do
don't don't
look maybe I can
um
yeah well hmm
they're too far
platforms
hmm
oh wow
do you think I can grab it from the
other side really really
yeah oh oh gravity
what about me
oh wait oh super easy now
what
it doesn't even go that high
but I can grab it and
can I actually also Ascend into them
Mamma Mia
oh you just have to believe guys
in all the possibilities
now I also now know how to keep the ball
in the hole because I was wondering you
know isn't it gonna fall out
we use it like
a step cell
uh
water stopper oh wait huh I'll leave it
a plug yes
come here come here let's not miss this
time come on straight
there we go I know you could do it you
want wow
[Music]
this place is nice actually right now no
good voice good voice okay be one finish
don't need to go to B1 anymore that's
all they put there
though that pond is mysterious to me
it's like a Mozart piece
foreign
that is the mini boss is that what you
tell me
is that
is that a laser or a flame over there
I'm confused
and next one
playing
ah the minibus was the like collected
but that was outside of the Temple
what
should it be in the temple normally
go here
can I reach that though
I mean
[Music]
uh
uh I'm moving on rewind yeah
it seems kind of
too simple don't you think
[Music]
I could go there I don't know I don't
know I don't let me out
he's a rocket Shield but no you're
supposed to always
do it with the things that are given to
you at least we should be able to do it
with that
tools that are at hand
it's so weird
weird weird weird
it won't go there again
think
the spares
what what
disappears
[Laughter]
a way to see it now
I actually could throw an arrow with
water inducement as well
[Music]
quick that doesn't work the way I
thought
oh yeah I'll just throw on the Arrow
with water inducement as I could
I can't oh my God he wasn't inducement
have you ever heard such a thing before
KFC
water inducement she says water
inducements I can't believe it's this
[\h__\h] she calls herself whole life
English
hola
hello hello
Ella Ella does this [\h__\h] work on YouTube
what are you gonna spit
fly a balls
not scary
I am a phoenix
don't you realize who you're dealing
with but if you're a fire
how you like that how you like that
boom
look at you now look at me look at you
now look at me look at you now look at
me everyone who doesn't know uh uh K-pop
will be like what the [\h__\h] is she saying
is she [\h__\h] crazy
does she have a seizure I think she has
a seizure
[Music]
what
it was a black pink by the way
black pink and you're wearing yeah
by the way blackpink I like I think Lisa
the most but I like Rosie too
[Music]
no no please bring me back
please hello please bring me back
no please
no please bring it back why can you not
bring me back
[Music]
why are you gonna be so complicated
I was hoping I was hoping he would lend
me a hand
but I guess not okay
[Music]
yeah it's kind of refreshing I guess
because like in the
in the fire temple
I felt a bit suffocated you know that
air just felt kind of heavy
and because it was so dark and like wow
intimidating wow
yeah you know
um hello sit down
yeah
do I have to activate him again follow
me
[Music]
oh there you go what are you doing
yeah and this is like more
I can breathe it's open I don't feel
like I'm like
getting claustrophobic
if you want to see it in a positive
light that is a smaller dungeon
okay so I know what to do here
of course I know
just gotta wait
I have a friend who has survived talking
like wait it doesn't work
yeah unlike IRL
it really comes to the quality of a
quantity with this game's done for me
did they
okay I guess so gotta say the dumb tando
was not impressed
it was kind of sad
which made me understand a little bit
um more because it's the first time I
Loki more memoryless maybe first time I
experienced this
I think
we're a streamer
that I like
doesn't like something that I was really
impressed with and looking forward for
him to react to
I was like yeah yeah I guess this is a
good step in the right direction but it
still isn't quite it doesn't quite feel
like a temple it feels more like a
Divine beast but improves
and what he said and I thought he would
be like super hyped once he reaches the
first dungeon
so I was like yeah really I thought you
would like it that's kind of the point
yeah maybe because Divine beasts were
such a big thing
and divine piece I I don't think they
were bad
either I don't think he really thought
it was bad either but it just it's just
that he prefers temples
[Music]
um
well anyway what are we doing
what's the matter here
it's not working
let me go up once and see what's up
since I have the ability to do so
um nothing
I'm not understanding what the issue is
here don't I just
ah wait
maybe before I blow the water at it
maybe I want to attach some of these to
the wheels for some reason I don't know
why but
isn't that why they're here
foreign
that they were all aesthetically the
same and didn't have unique gimmicks
oh
okay this game fixes both of those
issues but they're still not really
temples it does feel like a I mean
it's it's I think it's a little bit
difficult maybe to make it feel like a
typical good old that dungeon because
it's just
type of game that this is but maybe not
um
because the dungeons in for example
skyward Swords
which is also for the Zelda
that's also like a normal dungeon I
don't know I don't know
I think they're really good though
that's what I'm trying to say I mean
this one will probably disappoint him
because it's really small
maybe who knows maybe he will like it
but it's definitely even less
temple-like isn't it I don't know
[Music]
my brain is like after
eight hours is getting Mushy Mushy Mushy
Mushy
okay sorry sorry but I was going for Dad
I was going for that trust me eh oh no
okay okay not like that okay
turn the wheel turn the wheel
most difficult to turn it
why is it so difficult to turn it
should I just attach one
maybe oh wait it's getting it's going
somewhere but what am I doing
maybe the other way around
I just saw like a yellow bar there
calm down
calm down okay
okay one side is activated
what about this one
it's glowing Stone
[Music]
oh
hello well it wouldn't his water even
like
that it would be too easy but
um
[Music]
let's do with this
Now give me a new one please
what do I do with it
and push it through there was no hole at
the top maybe it can go from bottom on
an um
hello hello
I don't know if it will disappear so
better hurry
foreign
[Music]
wouldn't it be funny if there was a
uh
a tooth toothbrush paste toothpaste
bread that was called accidental
I know I know the word Dental is in
there
[Laughter]
you'll be so fascinated by accidental
that you feel like
you didn't even I don't know I don't
know
whoa aggressive
you're on the same side
[Music]
more or less but you don't understand
that you are because in the end you were
just protecting this land
you were just training doing what you've
been trying to do well don't
temples
are they also about five dollars wait
wait wait wait wait logic logic logic
check
if these temples
[Music]
are built by its own night and first
their purpose
was not this obviously because you know
the the reason it makes what it
currently does the evil thing is because
it's been infested so generally the
temples are are not they had a different
purpose right
so
what was that purpose
uh
what was that purpose and what a dead
zone I actually protecting here huh
worship sites
interesting
this was to make water
oh interesting
and the verb one was to make air or what
what
[Music]
explain that to me huh sure sure let's
go with that yeah
okay what's the deal here
there's something there
I have to drain the water probably to
get underneath there
okay
there are floaty platforms there are
sticky platforms there are water
that go
and make
nothing at the current time
there is a chest there oh
maybe you guys see that chest in your
own playthrough huh oh wait there's a
big screeny thing up there holy [\h__\h] I
noticed that spinning from a distance
what
why is it spinning like crazy why why
could do it before the gate
okay well I'll have to swim here
okay but
[Music]
maybe like this
let's go let's go
what I was trying to do the normal
puzzle I but ended up just shooting it
with good timing
what
chest
look at my genius ramp solution
[Music]
yeah okay
let's go
and now oh
that's what you're talking about wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait what do
you shoot what do you shoot what's that
you shoot ah
please turn again please turn again
please turn again please don't okay
wait
no problem
wait so you're supposed to like stop it
in the puzzle way normally not a hold on
now I end up doing it the same exact way
is it what I have to shoot higher don't
I
it's like suddenly it has eight sides
not just four
[\h__\h] hell
it takes time to go away what oh really
you've seen most players do it like that
really
hmm
it just seems to be spinning
ridiculously still you know fast I mean
that's
like asking you whoa okay ah wait
what the [\h__\h]
oh isn't it
unslunched what's next is there like a
a thing I have to hit
with another arrow
you just kept shocking stuff at it
okay oh yeah okay that's what I thought
okay
hello
still high enough I think to get a good
shot in
okay
I would be curious to see if there is a
different way of doing it that
seems more intended or if this really is
the intended way
it's a fun way
sit on
uh-huh
[Music]
the designers have to love seeing this
or like everybody skipped as a puzzle
yeah it didn't seem very puzzly that's
why
it seems wrong
yay
dungeon finished just have to kill the
boss let's go
I thought it would take longer but thank
God it's actually
a short Temple
here
wait what
ah we just use the
we just touched the gate again okay
and then we fight here in the middle or
we're gonna fight in the sky again or in
the water
here it is we have Wall bubble
the boss is in a water bubble
yeah the middle platform is
kind of fitting for a punch I guess
I didn't make my own weapons
oh
yeah
oh my god
[Music]
oh it's like this reminds me of
something where there's a way bigger
Beast behind it actually
awesome
[Music]
if I want to feel something I have to
put it on the [\h__\h] ground
what do I put on your menu
let's see if it gives me an opening uh
oh yeah maybe maybe
maybe we went the other way
don't shoot off my opal please
wait let me
already uh
equip and
[Music]
um
get a little pile out
I have time okay it looks like it
who knows the battle has just begun
oh
I see
[Music]
oh
yeah
okay why did it not work the first time
come on
not easy easy
one weapon
[Music]
can use my Splash fruits as well
haha
wait you miss me stop me
maybe not the best attack
[Music]
fine I have too many weapons in a way
all right you kind of too easy
give me something more interesting
oh okay
what
[Music]
halfway through something's happening
oh
yeah I'm not bothered by that you think
this will worry me
it doesn't concern me
let me just clean up oh
Yeah clean up a little bit or should I
just not probably could even do it
without being
without cleaning at all
stop talking
and be doing
[Music]
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
all right
uh
[Music]
my bowl is broken
wait I have an idea
no
[Music]
I have to get brain have all the money
okay wait what no problem no problem
it did [\h__\h] help
[Music]
come on
oh I got him I got him I got him early
but it's not enough
all right I'm waiting for him but
um
what should I do
you know what he said is it a cheat to
use a
an eye
[Music]
a man
Spin Attack with the scepter hmm all
right I forgot myself about my scepter
I'm gonna clean up
so messy and where's my magic
it charges the ages and I missed
I'll do the eye again if I find one oh
yeah
[Music]
it works just as well and I have enough
space to run over and give him
[Music]
I think he has a tumor in his brain
though
it doesn't look normal
yeah it seems like he wants the
Mastermind after all not the crocodile
it's an OCTA rock yeah it seems like a
like a [\h__\h] up version of a doctor
Rock
plant lives attack it was a taco that's
the infiltration at kfp
and they Inked everywhere
what a mess
I'm gonna call Ina tell her to clean up
personally
[Music]
stream hot containers
well
it's not tainted anymore
Lortab lower time lower time
let's go where's my hot potato
[Music]
it's already staring at it he's hunger
power power hungry
Mr Frodo
oh
my God
we're gonna hear the same story again
[Music]
inside
foreign
[Music]
oh yeah
in Vegas
[Music]
because this is very familiar
Gardens
[Music]
same script too
is
I mean you could argument that they do
it because
you don't know where you go first but
they also don't know
they don't care about an evil with all
the other lore stuff like the memories
why tell this four times but with the
memories
like you could make it so that the first
geoglyph you go to tells the first story
the second tells the Second Story
Etc
is
[Music]
unless you're a speedrunner
foreign
[Music]
it's very obvious because it's like so
huge wherever you go
you can't ignore it [\h__\h]
speaking of that
I would like us to go
check out one afterwards because we
haven't seen one today
[Music]
I was quiet moved after tuning and even
after unable where it was the second
time we heard it but this one doesn't
move me
linked to campfin maybe now
this is always the part that gets me
by voltage
is
foreign
[Music]
um
things are always pretty cool though
the music is just chef's kiss
don't break my fingers crack crack
foreign
[Music]
I was weaker than before
emblem engage
spooky is
[Music]
foreign
how long did that take not very long huh
felt very short one and a half maximum
very very short
if not just one hour honestly
hmm
yeah but good for me because today we
did a lot of other things besides the
temple that took up many many hours
so thankfully this one was short
oh he's getting healed
eyes look wonderful
[Music]
ah everything's cleaned up nice
nice
[Applause]
[Music]
very very awesome
it was fun to enjoy indeed we're just
gonna I think grab a memory and then
that's it
or maybe even two
depends on how accessible they are thank
you but dive and Uncle Jones
link welcome back
have you seen this Lodge has vanished
Without a Trace
laying things to your courage to the
opportunity
safe once again no words would Express
to death suit by gratitude thank you
hero from the bottom of my cocolo
thank you as for you see Dune
I bought links certainly played a key
role your own efforts to save the domain
where nothing short
uh of a magnificent
[Music]
I've always believed in you Seaton now
you have unequivocally proven you're
worthless to Bear the crown
one sitting in the archive we didn't
watch
haircut oh yeah wasn't that one like
number eight or so though
that is why I show joyously take this
opportunity to pass the throne to you
now
well you're probably already very very
old so I mean it might be time
Long Live King sit down
no it only seems that way in truth it
has been every on my mind for some time
sit on my son
sit on this Friday
it is time to ascend
as the new king
take Jonah's hand in this one lead to
throw his domain to a brother tomorrow
oh my God
that is incredible that is such a huh
an obvious pun that's right there but
only works in English
me the king
hmm
thank you Father I will not let you down
I swear it
that is the spirit my boy
no we accept wait a second it's not kind
of corrupted that the daughter of the
assistant
of the King end up marrying
the air kind of corrupted
a little bit of corruption doesn't hurt
no one doesn't
not his daughter what oh
okay okay
they're both green
and they both have wide heads
it's royalty to somewhere I mean I know
I know I know
I know I know I mean
if anyone that I know it's normal it's
normal that's what I'm saying it doesn't
hurt
[Laughter]
just monarchy yeah no no no no normally
what monarchy is
is marrying off your daughter to like
Royals of high high high status from far
far away from other countries to make
other you know deals like economy deals
and all that
the assistant that you have normally no
that is like not very desirably
desirable well actually
was so actually
so yeah yeah yeah
um that makes sense that it's not his
daughters and statues from a different
domain
[Music]
um
yeah yeah she's from elsewhere which
makes sense
so maybe it is about politics and
economy and you know
now except your place to put on the
throne to find The Swordsman in all of
Hyrule shall bear witness to this
momentous occasion well I'm so honored
we got a cutscene
oh
this is an important moment after all
cutscene please
come on
[Music]
silence everyone
speech
I hereby inherit this Crown from my
father
that was fitted to my head now the
exalted door fan from this moment on I
shall be king of the Zora
yeah at this same Precious Moment
[Music]
I ask that you also open
your hearts to your new Queen
my beloved yoga
oh my
[Music]
God
no no
blow him up
ah the sludge threatens us no more we
are once again free to swim through
Crystal Waters beneath Azure Skies
without fear we could not have achieved
this without our dear King sedon our
heroic Sterling and all of those those
who call this domain home
so proud and so very grateful
like the greats in my body
[Music]
there are many of those greats so I am
extremely grateful to count myself and
my grades along the Zora of the domain
right get it wait is this same in
English
wait what do you call the
greten
it's Creighton in German wait it's not
funny if it's not the same if it's not
great
oh [\h__\h] you ah
fish bones yeah there's really small
ones the ones that they have a million
of not gills no no no you know when you
eat fish and you have all this [\h__\h] in
your mouth and you try to not choke on
it not Gales no
not scales no
inside is like bones but really really
freaking tiny
I guess it's a fish bone
[Music]
that joke doesn't work only if you kind
of know German I guess
although you read it differently it was
great and fish great and great and it's
what you call it
[Music]
German
uh
German not always works
no
it was funny in my head that does not
mean that all matters have been resolved
right you are my love coming up
so long as Darkness looks in the depths
of Hyrule this piece we have fought so
hard for could vanish like a bubble on a
needle
we shall not allow that it is now time
for the Zora to help link Prevail
everyone I ask you to lend him your
strength doing just that shall be the
first task that I in my partner in life
in any leadership shall undertake as
your king and queen
let's go
royal wedding
and I witnessed it
let's go
first things first my friend regarding
the whereabouts of Princess Ella when I
obtained the secret Stone
we saw a vision of that woman
a stage of time I'm certain it was far
more than a passing resemblance that was
Princess Zelda whom you and I know so
well as for the Princess Zelda who
appeared in the domain and attacked
father could it be that the princess we
saw in my ancestors era and the one my
father saw in this era are not one of
the same
hmm questions about questions it is
painfully clear that you will not find
out until you clear all four temples so
please go to the last one immediately
link as I have just a senator Brown I
must offer my sincerest apologies for
being unable to accompany you
still I shall continue gathering
information about our Lost Princess
Zelda
please promise that you shall once again
gracel Pharaoh Zora's domain with your
presence sooner rather than later
Dr fanboy
whatever comes to pass know that you and
I will always be connected by the power
of a sage
no less
what about the other sages I still don't
know about the other sages what is this
about
[Music]
Coolio
Coolio Coolio
[Music]
already
we did that
now
what's up
oh hello link I should have known we
would run into you here because it's
just how it always happens once you
finish your temple
to investigate the geograph in this
region what is lunch falling from the
sky complicated things fortunately the
mock is gone now and our reference to
research your local geography May resume
I've been wondering have you found a
geoglyph in the Gerudo Holland or no
the map the map of the Forgotten
terrible show the Duke of shaped like a
person we enter to investigate ah that
geograph as well
for tomato
one thing after another in the right
order or else
I cannot
deal with this a [\h__\h] wrong game
here
uh
I did
the one
second from left that you see in this
picture right
last time now we need the one whatever
it's not it's the one before the one
that's person shaped I guess that's
maybe the one that they're just talking
about we need the one that looks like
it's kneeling the third one on this
picture right right
so
and and that one is
uh
ah
is that actually what the Garuda
Highlands are
huh
funny okay and after that would be I
think that one
so pretty close
[Music]
I have yet to ever go there but I I had
a mark where those the towers for a long
time
oh damn it okay
um
wait what's my closest teleportation
point
this one
shrine
okay
you would wait for that yeah
why
get into that memory it's gonna say
something really
yeah no
the hard area
um what do I want Skye
um
hmm
I can't go there yet because I guess
this does it's a shrine that I didn't
solve the shrine quest of
oh yeah I didn't know you can see what
you can get when you hover over
oh cool very cool
very cool um
I don't want to go underground
I guess I should have activated it
um
if you want to I'd recommend aiming for
the first Tower first and then dropping
down yeah
I mean I don't know what exactly it is
but
okay
we'll see I'm a pro gamer guys
I want this memory and I'll go get it
I want the memory
I don't want to just continue gaming I
want to get this memory specifically
this memory
I want lore
I cannot just go without lure
when is Seafoam boy gonna be able to
catch one of those memberships ah
kfb always gives away so many membership
boosts oil
seafoam boy always here thank you
I mean when are you gonna get one of the
gifts I'm not saying you should get one
to buy it particularly but
let's get my horse my Flex horse Maybe
[Music]
Union
oh you would want to sub to all 10.
ah
who wouldn't if they could
no I want it now I wanted that ah it's
fake
my golden horse am I disappointing horse
[Music]
wrong direction no right correct
okay
and this way
I mean the tower is pretty close I can't
imagine it to be so difficult to reach
it but who knows the bridge seems to
maybe cause an issue
or is it gonna be
okay
there's a bridge intact
oh it is
dig dog
suspension bridge
[Music]
ah
what's that
what what is the matter
it's not supposed to be a horse that
listens to me well
hey buddy if you're going to grow the
canyon over the suspension bridge you
better be careful I used to have a stale
on the canyon but ever since the people
sent the weather all scary horses hate
that place
oh
the horse is meant no Travelers meant no
business for my stable I was ruined I
had no choice but to relocate and open
the mini stable over here
okay but boy do I miss the old spot
still got both of your ears or did I
talk one of them off no
let me know your name so I can confirm
that your stable number
[Music]
okay I got a point
thank you
looks like you've built up a nice little
pile of points
oh it's okay
oh no I already have one but
okay
huh
only the weather I mean hmm
okay there's a person
can we talk to them too
on rainy days like this it's really
important for me to cook the perfect
meals for everyone
could be a recipe
I haven't seen you before why are you so
excited what's going on oh yeah it's
true I'm the one in charge of keeping
members of the researching team healthy
and happy and I figured out the secret
to keeping them energized you want to
know what it is oh of course you do I'll
tell you it's all about what they eat
when it's hot outside you should cook up
meals using shoes
[Music]
thank you
oh there's a strange spherical Relic uh
you and then you have been studying or
is it Shrine oh wait oh no that thing
the gacha machine
similar relics have been cited and two
other places kakariko Village in the
East and Terry town in the Northeast
perhaps I should try studying each of
them to see if they have a common
features oh there's a gacha
oh
thank you
just know that after you've crossed the
bridge the guard up ahead is gonna give
you a test
that's right all the questions are about
how to deal with hot and cold weather
but no matter how many times I try I
can't sleep to pass no I think I'll be
fun
oh it's like a noob test
okay
what
so did they all fail the test is that
why they're still here
we go man
that's not a gift you didn't you
activate it yourself just now
he joined on his own
yay
you saved the snipers yeah
[Music]
back in the chicken uniform
okay I want to see what this one has
might have something special apparently
there's still pieces or gotcha rewards
that I haven't gotten before
the steak
Springs
that stinks
yummy
oh yeah
oh it's raining
I didn't think of that is it always
raining here no
oh is it her who does the test over
there or is it you
I am sorry about being disappointed you
why just followed our friends but I have
returned I lost sight of them in the
canyon we had a great to meet here if we
got separated but there's still no sign
of them the longer they're gone the more
worried I get what if they're lost or
Hood ah
okay side quest
s
no problemo
oh I'm not gonna I'm gonna try to not
spend uh waste too much time
I just want to go straight to the Moon
remember there has been an abnormal
weather Beyond this point blazing hits
during the day freezing cold at night
it's dangerous to bring a horse into
this area far far too dangerous or to
even try okay if I wear you I'd head
north yeah
I'll just leave it here
it'll be fun
oh good do we want to do the test or
at the end I'm going to ask you a few
questions okay
okay I'm ready
question number one how can you best
warm up when it's cold
big girls you find myself put water on
my head stay near fire
correct but the first question is do you
just won oh the second question is a bit
more difficult so pay attention when it
is very hot out where should you go to
cool off
a shitty spot
oh that's why I'm glad you appeared to
have some survival skills by the way uh
dousing yourself in water would also be
a good way to cool off the Blazing heat
keep that in mind question number three
is very important and more difficult
than the last two what cooking
ingredients is effective at finding off
high temperatures
chill shroom
yeah
last question where in Gerudo Canyon
would you could you go to avoid being
affected by the extreme temperatures day
or night
I don't know I haven't been there before
okay if
maybe a cave
because
temperatures in caves
seem pretty regulated always
okay
really
oh one spicy pepper
seems fun right now
oh oh
is it gonna get hot now
not yet
I said bunny
ah CK
but I don't have time I'll have to go uh
there hmm
okay wanna try to be fast
oh thick stick I thought it was a
chicken leg
take this pepper it will keep you safe
just one single pepper
I'll try to oh there we go it's hot oh
I don't think I have
a flame armor doesn't work does it
yeah okay do I have anything to eat
for that
heat resistance four minutes six minutes
eight minutes six minutes okay
that's
what I need right yeah okay
I think I just accumulated those
ah
waste
but it doesn't look cold
wow
when did Allah say if I wonder
um
I don't know
I thought well desert hot it's daytime
portions are cheap
okay
I'm cheap too I don't wanna
wait what do I even have for a cold
oh this cold resistance
eight three nine
okay
wait for that I have armor
okay for now
okay we'll just ah ah
true
God damn it
but if it's hot I can't use the golden
armor right that one it's kind of
different although I feel like it makes
no sense if it protects me from Flames
it should protect me from the heat right
weird
what
but I guess it's more like
yeah still
still
even if I try to explain it to myself
even then
guys there's kind of a path here
I'll probably explore off screen or
maybe there's a chance
maybe I'll play tltk
yeah maybe I will maybe I will play tltk
tomorrow
but maybe like a little bit shorter than
today
it's been almost 10 hours I did not
think I would really go for 10 hours I'm
gonna be honest with you guys
yeah Monday's dream
rare very rare
not only with me but I've I think it's
generally we we tend to take Mondays off
don't we
I missed the code I'm not looking for
Clorox right now but was it that stone
oh nice Richard damn
you
[Music]
oh there's someone there
talk to them I'm curious
oh what it's called you're going to
freeze out here if you're not prepared
to the swing and temperature from day to
night sure makes traveling tricky
preparation is the key I always keep
Alex stairs on the hand that can hit me
up or cool me down without them I'd be
done for what if you like have
uh like stuff to make a fire with and
let's say you only have medicine for
cold weather and then you're like [\h__\h]
now it's hot oh how about I just sleep
will the game let you sleep through like
a night
to you know go back to the weather that
you're prepared for
oh you can
[Music]
um
seems like
this is made for people to climb up here
or is it from enemies but I might just
yeah
[Music]
no no
no
you
know
let's go I was gonna who's gonna
land on there and wait but I already had
no stamina left to even bring out my
paraglider
can I stand on this
[Music]
how do I I'm so bad at this I'm so bad
at like jumping off
a surface
and doing what I want to do
how do you do it
do a back jump
okay thank you
thank you thank you
foreign
oh I see it
[Music]
See The Temple at the tower let's go
start piece
subscribe the sky
oh spooky trees they got here oh
look
where is the there it is
I'll do this one oh there's the sakura
tree
Sky computer
[Music]
well then during stream no it's not it's
not an endurance when you're having a
great time
and when it's not even on purpose
also
you random tangent the other day
I went to
uh restaurants
[Music]
that have Korean
yummy yummy yummy
hot dogs you know those corn dogs that I
ate in Korea with nabita that I really
really liked
my Korean teacher told me about a place
that has them
um
[Music]
so I went there alone the other day
and I got my cell phone and I have to
say somehow in Korea it tasted a little
bit better but it was pretty
like accurate I would say
[Music]
and they had a lot of different
oh my God
this is worth it this is definitely
worth it
with no more fire now
dragon dragon
I know see a dragon
[Music]
.
where'd he go did he fall down
ah come on
the battle is over
right
dragon
I'll say a dragon
what was I saying
oh is that it that's it
that's it
[Music]
right there what was I saying yeah it
was really good
I got like uh you know the the potato
topping but you can also do like noodle
topping or no topping and
there was one more
topping that gets fried together with it
and and then oh you could do like cheese
inside too with the sausage but I did
only sausage
what's the problem here
and oh maybe here
and I topped it with ketchup and honey
mustard I think it was
I'm not sure anymore what kind of
uh
condiments I had
in Korea but I thought they were better
which generally was really good I was so
so scorching hot my God
so so hot
I don't know if this has to do with the
shrine with the tower but I'm assuming
it does
and that I have to get the other thing
up
speed run all the towers now that the
first boss I mean why not I I get like
that you would be curious about seeing
all of the map first
what is down there anyway oh it's coming
up
this is enough
oh
ah you're the one who's gonna open up my
shrine at my tower God damn it
hey
hey are you the one who got the Alberta
working I came to fix the terminal
easy easy I didn't even know that
someone was down there that was just my
intuition thanks dude
okay thank you man thanks very nice
oh his name is sarson
I figured it out sooner than you but I
knew that was something to do and the
only thing that I saw
what's that anyway yeah yeah food was
nice and they also had like some other
things but I just wanted the corn dog it
was nice to eat it again for the first
time in a while I loved that so much
when I ate it in in Korea
ah so good
I don't think I've seen it in Japan
before but I'm sure they have it in
Japan too
because I saw some like smaller Korean
snack focused restaurants like walking
by
last time I was there surely they have
these corn dogs too I should go check it
out when I'm in Japan you had it in
Japan
[Music]
yummy
I feel like Asian countries know how to
make good desserts
but I mean Europe doesn't also know how
to do we all know I think we all have
like
good dessert ideas
everybody has their own
okay oh
what is that interesting looking Sky
Island
yeah desserts
they have to be good everywhere
Bush okay
oh
I'm losing my cold resistance but I
should be fine with my armor um
um um
memory let's go
this is the one right yeah yeah
oh snowy that's so weird
but I guess
is that their problem I wonder if that's
their problem
the fact that it's
cold in the desert
and snowing
is that what we have to throw for them
actually then we're already in the in
the right
um
area for the next Temple or the next
phenomena
so that is great
we're ready next time oh I see it I see
it although there also should be a crook
I think I see the Kodak also
but I'll do the because it's up up at
the top I'll do the
memory first
oh wait maybe what I saw was a shadow
for the korok but no
oh well
I feel like every geoglyph has a
portal
this thing spawns so late are you guys
ready
for someone more
[Music]
German lure let's go let me fix the
audio too
[Music]
thank you
sit back and relax
Ed
um
foreign
respectable
there's no entrance
is
foreign
[Music]
ah more more more
no no no no more more more more more and
more
more more and more
more more more more
more and more
um
[Music]
it's a twice song I really like that one
ah
the next one is like
um
should be like here maybe
the next one is like going here
[Music]
it's half past
it's under the wheelchair dude and it's
a little bit to the right
it's in between isn't it
so it's like um
here
it's in between that's a little bit to
the right
foreign
on Monday it's Monday now
it's kind of kneeling no no I'm not
talking about this one yeah that looks
like kind of dwarf kneeling we're
talking about this one but wheelchair
one
north north of it a bit higher
I mean north of this one
let's climb up there maybe we'll have a
good view
you can't stop me
now
more
and more that was short what did we go
all the way up
but that's okay it helped me
okay dragons
[Music]
really
dragon
oh there is eyes really far
Oh you mean Oh you mean a different kind
of dragon what you mean
you mean the you mean the three-headed
dragon I mean
here
oh that would be a problem yes
you're a [\h__\h] bright man
not nothing you nothing
thank you
oh that's just a wizard I used a wizard
I just wizard
it's just a that's just an octoark
that's just an OCTA Rock
[\h__\h] hell
it's scary
what the [\h__\h] is that
uh uh yeah okay
I don't care about you
keep on sleeping
um
I'll do anything
to get another memory
let's go let's go let's go go go I'll
climb over the mountains I'll just swim
all the oceans
I'll do anything
oh
the coral
okay
might as well
they're always supposed to like attach
something right and then
maybe I can make it drop down because
now it has weight
really
I don't think I've ever successfully
solved one of these
maybe one
more way
go to sleep no
I'm not tired
I want to play more and I just want one
more one more memory
I feel like we didn't have so much lore
today
[Music]
I'm on edge
just one moment
[Music]
what
can I find my city
signs of an addict
what is this heavy sound
you know boys if you
it's just me I felt like they were like
heavy footsteps
ah
I
can do this I can do this come on
last second
another
magician I see magician
uh how far
we're uh we already did half of the path
please do not pay attention to me Wizard
I'm not here for you
I only want to find
the next
uh I wonder if I ever saw it before
actually from a distance I wonder
it's it's close to that weird Mushroom
Island
area huh
[Music]
oh
and I feel like maybe I did see it
before okay from here if you fly from
here
here get there is it like
what am I looking out for like what kind
of a mountain or Cliff oh there it is oh
wait is that the wheelchair one
no it's not
that's the one that's the one
ah yay
we get more lore
uh and if this is like by any chance the
seventh memory which no I don't think it
is but then we could watch this the
eighth one but no this is the the fifth
Maybe
with a fourth only
I don't want to be too loud because it's
already late but I'm excited
to Memories for one
I don't think we're quite there yet and
I don't want to like skip anything
no I know that this is the next one I
know that
oh there's a shrine in the water
maybe I'll get that off screen because
I'll stay here
and then I'll
end my stream I promise I promise you
some memories are hidden by story
missions
oh okay
I think that's good so you can't like
rush for them I guess
[\h__\h]
huh
oops
[Music]
is that oh
you're actually here
ah cause she just talked to me about it
yeah
anybody you want to see this one
together
oh well if it isn't linked so you are
investigating the geograph's children
how diligent of you of course yeah
That's it man it feels kind of lonely
also I didn't get to ah
I was gonna say I didn't get to really
look where the tear could be but it's
right here
I guess so
I'm just gonna I'm gonna watch it okay
all right then all right
memories
[Applause]
witness me it [\h__\h]
ah maybe she already saw it yeah
now she can't see it only I can
[Music]
ah
um
foreign
be happy
because
she's spending more time
better on purpose she doesn't want to be
with me
anymore
[Music]
not new
does
Link in Germany
um
ah
[Music]
first in German
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
I feel very happy
oh oh let me look up oh
okay
two three four five six seven eight
oh it's still a couple until we've
reached the one that we accidentally
already reached but I didn't watch that
one
I did not watch that one we just skipped
it because
I didn't want to see it yet
yeah yeah the first one will get
probably at the end the first one you
don't get first
no matter how hard you try like me
to do so
see
[\h__\h]
how long was I here
how long was I out
you just what the [\h__\h] does she not care
anymore what I thought we were doing
this together man I feel kind of sad
what the [\h__\h] happened to our connection
s
[Music]
what happened man
she doesn't even listen to what I saw
man Prue and Piper and Paige always
listen to what what Phoebe saw in her
premonitions
they always listen to it what is that
it's very very interesting
um
yeah anyways
because while I have enough seats for
weapons oh my Soul possibly yeah
I'm gonna no no
no more no no two two in one stream is
enough I would say
in terms of you know process and all
that
I'm not gonna I'm not gonna do this
right no no I'm I'm just gonna I'm just
gonna stand here
and do it alone alone because you guys
are telling me to go
shrine
I'm just activating it and now now I go
now I go
[Laughter]
really I don't wanna go
yeah no I'm not gonna play no
the whole day is already over holy oh
[\h__\h]
I just had to realize this
[Music]
the realization when life catches up on
you after 10 hours of streaming
[Music]
I was hoping
no it was already it was it was always
impossible it was never realistic kiwawa
as long as you had a long stream today
it was never realistic for you to do the
thing
just do it tomorrow I just do it
tomorrow just do it on Monday when you
wake up everything's gonna be okay okay
you know what tomorrow short stream
um I don't think I should do another 30
application I
need to do some things
um somewhere in the evening 8 P.M or 7
P.M my time
uh yeah I don't know what I'll decide
when I get up
[Music]
yeah
but my God I feel so but this is work I
know this is work I don't I don't I
shouldn't feel bad for playing for too
long this is work in the end this is
work this is work
[Music]
thank you guys for watching
I mean at least we didn't do like crazy
progress
I'm kind of did we kind of did and at
the same time we didn't
we did two towers
we did one Temple
we did two memories
and some stuff that I don't even
remember in the beginning
I don't know what we even did
some side questy kind of stuff
um
some shrines really like eight shrines
we did do a drawings
true true the pirapad stuff
now we did a lot if you think about it
[Laughter]
yeah
let's make it nine no no no no
I can't I have to go I have to stop
myself oh my God I have 60 M's
oh
no I will write those now
six not sixteen no no no
okay and in German we say
uh hopefully that's it and good enough
I feel bad making you guys watch 10
hours of stream but
see we gotta make progress you know we
have to
have to email
yep it is what it is so
good night
uh
and see you tomorrow
I feel like anxious right now
oh man okay bye bye bye bye
bye bye oh
did you know Alyssa Milano was an idol
in Japan as what
what
[Music]
unless
you can't what
oh
here's why Alyssa Milano was so popular
in Japan
there are a lot of celebrities who had
no idea who we had no idea had
music careers
but doesn't mean a lot of people from
Trump no way according to her co-stars
we know that what working with Milana
was like on Trend and we know what
Millions uh
we apparently didn't know that Milan was
was up before no no it doesn't look like
she even remembers who wants to remember
a lot about that time ever she had a
full-fledged music here at one point but
no one knows about it except for Japan
Who Loved Her Five albums here's a story
about how Milano became Japan's Britney
Spears
oh why do I not know about air
like the only like like really long long
time ago
for an idol in Japan that I know of is
Leah Dizon
I mean but this seems to be even before
that
she started in acting career in 1984
with the film old enough and shortly
after she won the world of Tony Dance's
daughter and who's the boss soon she was
established as a teen Idol but she had
no idea she'd soon be a Teen Idol in a
completely different country at 12 she
co-started co-starred with Arnold
Schwarzenegger and Commando which did
nothing to inspire critics but
apparently it inspired one record
producer in Japan to offer Milano a five
album record deal
what that's so Random she signed up the
Japanese record label Pony Canyon Inc
and released her debut album look in my
heart in 1989.
it picked at number 68 on Japanese
oricon albums charts and produced The
Singles look in my heart What a Feeling
and straight to the top later that same
year she released her second self-titled
album this one made it to 15 on the
Japanese chart and was certified
platinum
in 1990 she released her first
compilation album the best in the world
which reached number nine on the chart
then her third studio album blocked
inside a dream in 1999 1991 and her
fourth do you see me in 1992 in 1995 she
released her final album The compilation
record called The Very Best of Alyssa
Milano
all of his songs were written
Milano was entering into the market at
the tail end of Japan's Idol system in
which younger singers were paired with
professional songwriters and musicians
to put out a series of well-crafted
singles while the Idol's personality and
kawaines were promoted in magazines and
television appearances this is a really
interesting way to describe what's an
idol
Milano sang some songs in Japanese and
toured all over Asia which she said was
a weird experience she would lip sync in
a lot of the country's various variety
shows one time she was surprised on
stage when a huge group of choreographer
choreographed dancers came out to be her
backup dancers without her knowledge so
Milana was a multi-platinum recording
artist at 16 but why didn't she bring
that success back to the States well she
thought she'd be laughed at like every
other actor who releases an album oh
that that seems to be at least in the
past have been a thing with actors
trying music careers and failing or the
other way around to
a lot of actors who release album Sarah
laughed at she explained to the Los
Angeles Times I'm not interested in
crossing over I'd much rather have it
released where it's appreciated than
laughed at
I mean I kind of get it like
I I wanted to make music in Japan
and had confidence in doing so in Japan
but I never felt like the type of music
that I wanted to do like Idol music
would ever have a chance or really be
appreciated overseas or would be even be
taken serious or I would even find any
any label or so that would take me
[Music]
um
she's embarrassed by her music career
[Music]
oh
speaking oh no
oh no Jimmy Kimmel speaking to Jimmy
Kimmel in the talk show her Secret at
least the rest of the world music career
which she describes as bubblegum pop was
brought up in Milano got embarrassed
you'll like the Japanese David
Hasselhoff in a way Kimmel joked
oh no Milana revealed that she's not
been back to Japan since her teen idle
days even though she recently praised
the country for its strict gun laws even
if she has terrible memory or suppressed
most of that time in her life but Milano
couldn't even remember her biggest hit
when Kimo played a clip to Joker memory
she held her head down
I wonder if they asked her if they're
allowed to do this I mean they must have
there's no way
hey
okay when I end the stream I'm gonna
listen to all those songs and watch the
music videos holy [\h__\h] I want to hear
her sing in Japanese what the [\h__\h]
that's the that must be the earliest
like
White
uh
white Gaijin Idol in Japan ever
holy [\h__\h]
I'm going on a deep dive after this
two minutes away oh that's good I I want
that 10 hour mark
[\h__\h] what this knowledge
who gave me this knowledge who was it
who was this again
whoa you blew my mind is
yeah
this is wild
oh that's Japanese bro he knew
foreign
I had to share when I found out today
damn how did you find out
[Music]
um
how old was she in the beginning of
Charmed I wonder I wonder how long after
that was
hmm
were they say already
no so
okay we can go to the ending screen
bye-bye damn
[Music]
watch along with the song real quick
okay wait which one should we go
Alyssa Milano straight to top maybe this
one
foreign
[Music]
oh my God okay okay uh on zero
three two one zero
[Music]
oh
it has idle Vibes and it's really old
though
sheesh turn on Pike
[Music]
foreign
that looks more like her what
[Music]
no way
I can't even imagine
Japanese people listening to this it's
not there's no nihongo
[Music]
oh
was it filmed in America though
[Music]
I guess so
thank you
[Music]
I mean it's very different from the
modern more modern Idols that I was
watching supporting
this is like a mix of old Japanese Idols
I guess and and Rick Roll
gives me Rick Roll vibes
the music and the video that's just
because that's also old I guess
[Music]
oh yeah I mean Japanese animals
they don't need to be able to sing well
and she's yeah not like an amazing
singer
[Music]
colliding world
and I should altergate to this
she's an idol
ketchup ketchup
[Music]
oh my god oh yeah do the dance
no way
now whenever I I meet a Japanese Boomer
I gotta ask him do you know Alyssa
Milano the X Idol in Japan do you know
her
[Music]
all right
ask your uncle yeah
[Music]
okay bye bye guys bye bye thank you for
10 hours
[Music]