[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
this is
[Music]
I'm gonna go back
oh my God I hear my own screen
[Music]
um yeah your hair oh wait wait wait wait
wait wait I have my stream wait wait
wait wait wait I have myself
I hear
possible here
are you still
is it echoing still
[Laughter]
fixed
okay good okay
[Music]
all right all right all right
this distance Kiana I hope you hear me
okay welcome
one two okay of pizza
should I should I flip the camera maybe
like you know
maybe that's less
or like more realistic because I guess
it's flip right now let me see it
probably looks better if I flip it
although even it's a little bit of an
angle
um
iPods a professional proper camera
finally
I felt uh inspired and motivated I mean
I kind of wanted to try it out for a
long time but I didn't really know like
what I was doing is this okay I mean it
might be confusing at first but I think
you'll get used to it
I think this might be better because
that's where I'll and you don't see my
ends upside down
and kind of for me that makes more sense
what about you it's fine
you'll get used to it maybe
now it's a little bit shocking first
you don't see it but I'm wearing the
happy apron
because I noticed when we made the first
test Pizza that you know the flower
flies everywhere we'll be using that
word a lot oh my God guys the oven is
hot and heated
um and a little bit too scared to move
the camera around
so you won't really see that but it's
the almost the same model as the one
down
there
yeah
ah
happy April 1st guys today we are
turning kfp
[Music]
not turning it was always always has
been okay of pizza the bean campus
that's for pizza
hey I am from Austria I have beautiful
Neighbors in Italy who have come up with
this beautiful thing called pizza and
you know in a normal kitchen oven you
don't you're not able to make like the
Perfect Pizza okay so you need like a
really hot pizza oven I like to call it
Pizza chamber ever since you played
matchford Prime the other day
but so I this is I mean uh my my pizza
friend who's like so into Pizza uh told
me that like you know if you have in a
normal kitchen like a like a normal oven
let's say that is like zero and then ten
is like a professional pizza restaurant
pizza oven then what I have now
let's say it's like a it's okay I will
say it's like five maybe
zero is the kitchen oven 10 is like a
professional in um pizza restaurant oven
what I have is like okay maybe four
because there's even better ones for
home use
but mine is already like we tested it
the pizza that you see uh over there
yeah on the bottom right of the screen
is our test pizza
and I think you can see just by the the
texture of the of the dough that this is
a proper pizza Welcome to Italian
Austria
yes now this was my first week I did
that myself but yeah I needed I needed
to get you know a feeling for it I'm
really scared here are some points
we only let it rise for three hours
yeah
it took us a little while to do
everything get it to that point but it
means possible if you have less time to
let it rise you put in some yeast so we
put in quite a bit of yeast but
unfortunately use the stinky and it's
not so good to add more but it's not
really you can't really taste it in the
pizza so it's okay
but ideally
uh you wanna have just you know
tip of a tip of a nice amount of um
yeast
and then
the other parts of the dough is just a
good flour and
ice cold water
which we also you know we were measuring
how cold it is and all that
and a little bit of salt and that's
really what all you need kind of and
then you go put it into the kitchen
machine and goes like some videos on
Twitter
um
yeah yeah I learned a lot already yeah
yeah
um
but fresh pizza turned out good
um the problem is though that
um normally so if you if you have time
you want to let it rise for 24 hours
sometimes if you have a different kind
of flower you would even let it rise for
48 hours even but ideally 24 hours would
be ideal so we kind of sped It Up by
adding more yeast me and my pizza friend
was like really into Pizza
uh yeah I'm nervous chill nervous yeah
that's me uh we spell it up but it's
fine like it works and and oh let me
show you I bought this I bought these um
containers because you need a round
container
and then oh it's kind of hot here
because it's standing next to the oven
okay the oven gets so hot like this gets
much hotter than like a normal kitchen
oven I think and it's like very
contained in like a small chamber anyway
so in here is my my other pizza balls I
have three more
if I'm if I can handle the stress and
the nervousness then I will try to make
uh well at least two and if we have some
time left over maybe I'll make it for
everyone well maybe I'll make that
after the stream because I'm so
the worst thing that can happen
if I get a hole in the dough and that's
so scary it didn't happen for the test
Pizza I was so careful it didn't happen
but the thing is like if you don't
like I mean I don't know if it's really
in that connected I think so but I
understood correctly if you let it rise
longer and all that and if you have a
better kitchen machine than mine then
the dough will be better and then the
holes
I think my friend said it's more about
the kitchen machine in my case
it's about the you know it gets like
holes when you spread it thin
and that's really bad
it's really bad
what's with the camera angle get used to
it you have to be thankful because this
is a huge upgrade I am
Focus
this is uh is it a DSLR I don't know I
think that's what you call it is
the focus
it's gonna be probably confused where to
focus but it is focusing wow
[Music]
cameras when I was trying to attach my
my shitty webcam uh today you know it
wasn't working and I tried to ever use
Facebook and it didn't work and it's
always like that and I just like can't
keep on disconnecting connecting and so
on and that works so today it wasn't
working I'm like [\h__\h] this [\h__\h] and then
my friend is also really a lot into Tech
so we started talking about other
webcams like new and then they're really
good for streaming and well against all
my time from South and high speed right
now because I'm nervous
slide it up split it out
um but yeah and then and then you know
we're talking a little bit of things
about these webcams but then I was like
you know I wouldn't mind like buying
like a private proper camera as well
so you know we looked through like some
of the like good ones for streaming and
and so on similar like using it uh
instead of a webcam which ones are like
the best ones and there are a couple of
popular ones like the 6400 for example
Sony 6400
um damn it gets really hot in this room
because of this over the whole [\h__\h]
um but I bought the ZET 10. you can see
it on my Twitter the packaging yeah I
just bought it like oh two hours before
the stream but it looks
it looks on it was so easy to connect I
never did this because I thought it
would be more difficult but we literally
just have one USB City cable connected
to my PC so that's it that's it it's so
simple I'm a little bit worried about
the camera uh battery dying on me
because it came with dead batteries so
we charged it for
30 minutes and now it's still connected
it can do this while charging I'm just
worried that it will not be able to keep
up so then I will cry if that happens
um but I'm so happy
so hyped but okay okay so what are we
gonna do
we're gonna make a funny pizza because
okay here's the reason the other day I
saw
um
the other day I saw
um Little Caesars in America a
restaurant that I've never been to
it's bringing out a corn called Pizza
which is a pizza with like full
horn clowns
like on every cut
corner of the pizza
and then some butter on there too and I
was like my God I love corn this is
amazing and I believed it and you guys
are like how can you believe it they're
talking about two liters of butter and
I'm like yeah but I didn't really like I
think the moment my brain heard corn
crop Pizza it was over I didn't listen
to the um apparently unrealistic amount
of two liters of butter
didn't even seem like anything weird to
me when it turns out that was a joke
like how can you joke about that Little
Caesars what the [\h__\h] that's not
something to joke about corn called
Pizza it's not a joking matter no
so I was sad I was really sad because I
was looking forward to going to America
one day and eating the corn cut pizza
with friends because how can you eat
that alone impossible full Corn Pops
breaking out alone I am pretty much
Alone
um my friend is still here just in case
a fire starts or so
uh just in case just in case
um but you know it will be fine I'm an
independent woman I will be fine
but what I'm gonna do I found this fruit
and even a viewer of me even tested this
out
so I don't want to actually use like a
million corn cobs around the corner
that's weird we are recreating that and
then adding my special
originality to it but
oh wait we haven't even commented
have you noticed something
we haven't even talked about
the surface and I'm
prepared
so you noticed something
some
it's cardboard
and yeah it's um it's a cardboard
table
listen listen
getting my dinner table into this room I
was ready first I was ready to cook in
my living room but then I realized my
brother has my gaming laptop right now
so I don't have it so I have to use it I
have to stream in my room
now so then we're trying to get because
I need a big surface for all these
things ingredients
a dinner table please first of all it's
so [\h__\h] heavy even those two people
and second of all it wouldn't have fit
uh through everything so we were like
[\h__\h] well what else
so then
I have this like
huge mirror
in the cardboard standing around for a
long time already because
I wasn't sure if I was really going to
use this mirror
but it's really big like it's a big
white uh mirror mirror mirror on the
wall Kiwa is the cutest of them all
and it was however the cardboard was
covered in a in a plastic okay so it was
it's clean and I was gonna do it with
the plastic but then I realized oh oh
it's reflecting so we got rid of the
plastic
um so it's clean it's fresh cardboard
and cardboard is Extreme so it's
basically a tree table it's fun it's fun
but my oven is on a different table a
more reliable one it's right there
unfortunately you can't see it but it's
basically it's it's a it's this
this one
I'm spending several hundred bucks
almost a thousand on this camera but I'm
using a [\h__\h] cardboard table oh it's
being supported by two chairs one on
each side
they're pretty stable
it's so stable it's surprisingly stable
don't worry guys we tested it it's fine
it's fine okay so
let me drink because I am freaking out
um I want to drink some water
oh
Mamma Mia when I tried the first pizza I
did it with my bare hands and I have to
say the dough is amazing dough is so
fluffy
but I don't know how it will be with
gloves I have these plastic gloves they
should be I've done some cooking with
these like when I make dough or when I
make like hamburgers you know minced
meat and have to shape it then I use
these and it it's actually pretty fun
because they're like pretty skin tight
so I think it'll be fine I have some
stuff here okay show me
the first maybe I should cut this first
I should cut the corn cob so that we
have something to put on the edges so my
viewer one of my viewers
tested my idea out because of course we
all know I'm a genius and they thought
the same thing so okay we are not gonna
use the whole corn cob and also I've
been told to not even attempt
to cut through it
like that I've been told there's a
ballet kind of pre-cooked but they're
grilled corn so it used to be posted
really perfect
um the advice I got was
you notice how [\h__\h] freaked out I am
I did have a Red Bull today but that's
another story
um the advice was to like go through
here cut
and cut here the whole line and then try
to go a little bit under and get it it's
been tested out it works apparently
I think once we have one out there the
other ones will be easier to get out
it might be a huge mess yeah I'm hyper
too right now we should play EDM because
that's what I feel right now in my heart
I feel like it I'm on ADM okay
well this is why we're starting first I
don't want to put this on the flower so
I guess we'll just okay I don't want to
do that though
oh you'll see a little bit here let's
see a little bit
what if this not works then I don't know
I have a lot of like other corn though
we're making okay we're making um a lot
of four different types of pizza I gave
up on the chicken barbecue I'm sorry
we're doing Margarita because I need I
need something simple I need something
simple oh yeah the reason why even
though that was amazing even that pizza
the reason why it looks a little bit
watery even though we drained it the
mozzarella is still kind of watery
somehow so if you ever make your own
pizza drain the [\h__\h] out of the
mozzarella because you know okay chill
out okay
okay I can't be hyper now because if I
cut myself then we're [\h__\h]
uh
okay how do I I mean I probably have to
all right
cut a little bit of the Corn oh
I'm in there I'm in there
I'm in there I can't I don't think I can
yeah I can't really go much further okay
so I made a cut here maybe one two three
gross one of the reasons why I'm doing
this is because if I rarely went full
outs with the corn cob and put a full
corn cob around the whole pizza
then I needed like eight corn cobs or so
probably and that wouldn't probably
wouldn't even fit under the under the
hood of the piece of chamber
I like to call it Pizza Jamie all right
I'm cutting the second cut
my corn into pieces this is my last
resort
suffocation no breathing don't get for
damn if I [\h__\h] this pizza up
okay we need to calm the [\h__\h]
Pizza is making me nervous and uh the
corn is making me nervous right now
everything's making me nervous
okay what now what now
this is not
how would I know this
we said to the fan who tested this out
said to like kind of like go underneath
afterwards once I made a cut
um
worst case we only make one quarter cup
pizza
cut out a bean
um I mean one aside oh there's some
there's already a cat here on there oh
wow I wonder if the cat hair will like
burn inside of the pizza oven
put the corner
are you telling me to put the corn look
at this the corn dog
you can even see what this quality you
can kind of
even see where I made the cut yeah
where's the other class
I see it okay
cut my corn into pastures
um well it might be a thin layer of corn
oh God oh God oh God
this is how we do it this is how it
works it's a thin layer though that's
fine
I just want the Optics I just want the
illusion of porn
yeah oh God this is concerning
oh that is too thin koala
Finn
ah
yeah I mean we can make it work
oh
yeah okay that works that works that
works it's kind of thin but it's okay
it's beautiful it's beautiful oh it's
beautiful
[Music]
absolutely insane I'm so insane
so insane
how many days ahead one two three
one two three one two three
one two three one oh [\h__\h] okay
that's okay that's okay all right we're
making another this wasn't so bad
so difficult
I mean it's not not perfect not the
perfect ideal thing that Little Caesars
teased me with
I wanted to be real Little Caesars why
can't it not be real
that's why we can't have nice things
huh
I'm getting under it
okay
right
[Music]
okay oh
oh would you like a row of corn oh
[Music]
a beautiful this is what the inside of
corn looks
but the outside of current looks
beautiful look at that high quality oh
my God my cooking streams are gonna be
like this from now on
not only my cooking streams I should do
other kind of streams too crafting
crafting streams
oh
are there any Italians watching
anyone
I'm gonna try my best to make a pizza
worthy of your country
say yep
me
Echo
Italiano
hello
because of the Corn
it's kind of vertical I don't know what
vertical means to be honest
this is fine
fine okay I made a cut here and now I'll
do the same thing how many do we need I
wonder I mean look at a whole corn club
and that was
yeah that's if I listened to Mozart
I hyper when I listen to normal so I put
today it's just a Red Bull and the
excitement and the new camera and
everything
oh God
I mean grill time for the pizza by the
way is only five minutes
they get done immediately in this
marvelous Pizza chamber
so
I don't think we have a Time issue
[Music]
oh I'm a [\h__\h] trainer okay no I
didn't come up with this idea I would
have probably tried to cut through here
but this part is like really
really tough like it's so hard I don't
think you can really cut through well
um
I know you don't want
look at this
camera
hi
hey
that's confused
whatever
I guess nothing
I'm gonna look at the maybe it's too
lewd
[Music]
making a nice cut
after we're done with this it's
basically done like everything else is
prepared I even cut the the pineapple
into halves like there were already
pieces but I cut them into more like
thinner pieces because they were too
thick
um I got the recommended for my pizza
friend the recommended
tuna that's already in olive oil I got
some fresh basil a plant I got some red
onions I got some mozzarella I got some
salami and some butter I'm thinking if I
should put the butter on the corn I
probably should but it will be melted by
the time it's out
[Music]
you guys tuna Pizza is normal in Italy
okay
so it's just not that common in like n a
but don't question it try it
try it before you uh like cancel me
about it okay
it's really good
it's like really good like I don't even
like seafood much
but even I
this isn't like the one thing I
absolutely love okay I have one more
roll of four
what should I do about that
well I'll I'll cut I'll cut them yeah
I'll color free room
I want the four the four is gonna like
completely ruin all my Aesthetics
sure
but the pickles gotta be round so I
maybe also will cut them in half like
this
um
ah
nobody around yourself Pizza in what
world are you living in what country
pictures everywhere maybe not like good
like Italian style pizza
but it's worth if you look for an
apartment
it's worth to like
decide where you want to live depending
on if there's a good pizza place
fun we have more just in case I have
like three more
okay uh should I change because these
are like no I'll just uh
I might change up as well
okay
breathe breathe let me find you well you
will not [\h__\h] it up you will not [\h__\h] it
up you will not [\h__\h] it up
okay
okay there's some flour in here
so basically what I have to do
is drop it in there
and I have to try my best to drop it
right in the middle which is a challenge
and that didn't work last time I did it
but
I know oh my God wait battery my
camera's battery is like dead
it's still working but I see it's it's
like red
oh God when maybe we can only make one
pizza
okay let's just do it let's drop it all
right did I do this right there was
nothing else to do with me I shake it a
little bit shake it shake it shake it
get out of there good
we're running on a tight schedule
Olympics if it if it's dead maybe it
would just take a break to eat the pizza
and then turn the camera off and hope it
charges a little bit in the meantime
okay this one does not want to come out
this ah it's moving now it's moving
yeah yeah
it's loosening
oh I think I see it do you see it I
think you guys can see it from your
angle how it's like slowly
you cannot scoop it up no no you have to
let it drop and you have to let it drop
in the middle
just wait oh God this one has like a lot
of holes
[Music]
um
that's so sticky what the [\h__\h]
you
hey I'm trying
should I help it by like raising the
container
away from it
it looks like a spider weapon oh wait
it's working it's happening it's
happening
if I I'm not supposed to touch it yet
oh God oh God why does it look like a
spider
[Music]
this looks so different than the other
one
I'll just
come on
yes it is
[Music]
I might have to ask my friend if this is
okay
wait wait it's almost it's almost
separated
okay
um
what the [\h__\h]
that texture
it's rough but I'm just gonna go with it
uh wait so when I say supposedly I'm
supposed to cover it I think
we'll cover it
first coverage don't touch it when it's
not covered but I think I need more
flour
soon after this one oh I think I'll
manage with this one I'm gonna cry when
the camera turns off
all right
ah it's so soft it's so bubbly if I
cover it in flour I will not see it's
flaws it's okay
it's okay okay okay okay okay all right
I want to show you a little bit more
okay
okay okay okay
I'm like so careful with it because I'm
so scared that it will have holes but
all right then while it's still in here
I think
I'm gonna try to get the air out but
from the inside to the outside I think
I'm still I'm supposed to do this now
from the inside to the outside
I'm like pushing it
carefully
let's give it silk some shape already
from the inside to the outside
yeah okay okay I got it and then and
then I think I turn it around still
inside my bowl
it's so fluffy it's so fluffy okay I'm
supposed to lift it
and then um turn it around and I mean
the shape will probably like fall apart
a little bit
um
am I supposed to drop it on the
cardboard already
I don't think so okay turn it around
remember I remember I only did this once
okay
and my nervousness is probably like
getting rid of all the knowledge I have
okay
it looks good that looks good that looks
good so far I think all right I think
this is okay now we put it on the
cardboard
wonderful
camera is still working okay
[Music]
look at my wobbly thingies laughs
okay there it is
good job thank you thank you
okay
now we shape it a little bit I think ah
no wait my friend says there's two
techniques
but I'm scared to use them
I can like stretch it out
like turn it turn it when stretching
I've been included when stretching
you can also lift it up and all that but
I don't have to have confidence
I don't want to stretch it too much
either
because I'm scared
I'm a little chicken
okay now
um if I had a more like durable uh dough
then I could just like do it without
these probably but these really helped
um this came with the pizza oven
I'm just gonna put it on top of there
Mamma Mia
Mama me I'm so nervous
what's going on so far no holes yet no
holes
all right
just so that I can like then put it in
the oven easily if I just poop you know
all right all right
okay
um I barely have the shape of the it was
way bigger last time the shape of the
like outside crust
hmm it's all right though I think
science is actually still a little bit
a little bit too Molly had it was much
bigger we can make a small pizza
oh no
no I'm trying my best I'm an amateur
I am an amateur but the the spider webs
are gone now so it's okay okay I think
it's fine I don't even I don't even want
the the outside crust to be too big
okay because we're putting on the stuff
okay
um first step
no versus
first is the tomato sauce
yes this is going on the menu of course
we are after all a pizza place
not doing anything wrong I think I'm not
doing anything wrong this is not so
difficult
okay putting on
don't matter
if you're in Austria and you want to get
the same brand this is recommend from my
pizza friend this one's from the brand
Muti m-u-t-t-i
we're using
hey we are using monkeys tomato sauce
which is literally mommy in German
Mommy
sauce
so you're supposed to like still see a
little bit of the pizza dough shining
fruit so I think this is already
a good amount let's see [\h__\h]
okay
cardboard afterwards don't worry guys
I'm not gonna reuse it I'm gonna throw
the cardboard away after this
but now it's fresh like I knew it just
still had the the plastic on it and I
got rid of the plastic so now it's like
I'm completely
so
okay then a really sheer layer of uh
parmigiano but I have only the fake ones
cheer oh what the [\h__\h]
you little [\h__\h]
that was a big
big crumble
not making apple pie here
no no no maybe one day I will make apple
pie Kiana fried pie Kiana Kiana fabulous
pies Kiana's fabulous pies kfp
okay
yeah yeah that's probably good yeah
so just a sheer later don't worry this
is how it's gonna be done now I'm gonna
place
[Music]
the corn corn the corn the corn the corn
this is
this is oh I think it's just enough no
no wait no [\h__\h] maybe I need that one no
[Music]
okay maybe some
some spacing might be necessary
well the problem is I feel like the the
corn is gonna give off some hydration to
the
Pizza which is not good
necessarily good
I'm gonna leave some space guys I don't
want to open up or uh you know there
should be one corn called per Pizza
actually which I think that was
surprisingly
[Music]
eating eating oh yeah come on
okay and now so I want to do half half
because I'm doing basically four I want
to do four flavors but I'm gonna do two
pizzas so I'm gonna do half half on both
let me I want to show you
I guess I'll show you afterwards too but
it's how it is now
beautiful I'm so glad I bought the
camera
yo Investments
okay
okay now
[Music]
um
I already I mean I think I'll do
I'll do
um I'll do pineapple
one half pineapple I love pineapple and
pizza oh wait
ah I forgot the ham ah [\h__\h] I'm gonna go
get the ham huh sorry I couldn't believe
we're gonna go to him uh
I'll be RV
please wait for me
foreign
[Music]
it's so hot
so hot I found some some ham guys
how's it going
there was a ghost
none
let me cook
you say you cook the pizza no already
bake at the pizza so let me bake
I'm just using the random ham that I had
um in the fridge still it's not so
important
I was just like
probably one slice it's even gonna be
enough
[Music]
it's a it's a good handle
but you could even use like toast ham
like the cheap cheap ham for toast
let her bake
okay
like this
good then we spread some more pineapple
on it which is also
is way better than the mozzarella I
think so
um
I don't know
got a little while staying
it might be like swimming when I take it
out okay but this
fine
the my Hawaii house
except
this is okay Pizza I make the decisions
okay and the other half I'm gonna do
tuna
nah
I'm gonna do
salami
I think because the other one will be
tuna and Margarita so I think we have to
balance out
the ingredients a little bit
ah
okay
salami yeah idea I had you know was
barbecue chicken barbecue Pizza which I
I sometimes had in the past and I
thought it was really good
um it's basically
um like chicken marinated in barbecue
sauce with I think it had like a red
onions corn Perfect by default corn and
I think like pepperonis or like
or pepperoni I'm not sure it has like a
lot of ingredients but it's like really
good because the barbecue flavor holy
moly
oh I don't think that many problems okay
so I chose a small
a Hungarian
salami oh that's oh that's too many
fun yeah that's fine
okay
[Music]
almost done now on top
we add the mozzarella cheese
that's at the end
we could add some basil it doesn't
really fit though the ingredients I'm
gonna put the bags of my pink on the
Margarita online
I mean basil is always good I know but
you know
we're almost done to put the the first
pizza in the oven camera how are you
doing
it's still ooh it's still saying you
know no battery but it's surviving hang
on just just let me do the first pizza
okay just at least one pizza you can die
on me afterwards maybe but so you should
cover all your bases
the mozzarella like you can go all in
with it
like all over
all over
don't fret to use a lot of mozzarella I
do have a lot anyway
more cheese yeah yeah yeah don't worry
I'm gonna put some in the middle
yeah surely you heard a big Jam right
what's that say oh back up what's that
mean
Rebecca
yeah okay good
um there should be more here
more here
or here
no more here
rifle material then but even I have to
say like I I am waifu material
I am
every day I wake up and I'm like wow I
should be my own life bro
I think I am now last you drizzled in
with some olive oil I actually prepared
some a mixture of olive oil and garlic I
think I want to use that on this sound
and here just normal olive oil
yeah where's my small spoon
knuckle almost dead
maybe a finger
yeah that works
[Music]
actually that gives me good control over
it
yeah some pressed fresh garlic
beautiful beautiful
okay
now the question is should I
should I put the garlic olive oil over
the corn cob or should I try butter I
have more control with this I think
what do you think
I'm a bit worried about using the butter
all right
clean up fresh butter
okay
[Music]
it's still a little drizzle
on the right side
it's kind of difficult like a spritz oh
God
that's good
all right I've calmed down a little bit
soothing pigs are making you soothing
now
oh really
all right here we go we have some
how do we do this I'm I'm just gonna
place
don't want to swim and I'm scared of
like
I can't put too much we cannot risk
putting too much
or maybe I should just like rub it
rabbit rabbit we don't want two leaders
we do not want two leaders
I know it sounds amazing but
it was so hard to heart attack inducing
this works well I think this is good
wrapping is good right
just like too much already
yeah yeah yeah yeah I think this is good
I don't want the butter to mix into the
pizza after all you know we just want it
on the corn cob only
looks good
all right all right
it's done
before screenshots
post on hashtag kfb
tea
beautiful let's go so
um five minutes okay I'm gonna open this
now I'm so scared oh this is so hot oh
even the handle is hot
okay I'm letting out all the heat down
subscribe okay
okay
oh okay oh it's hot it's hot okay I'm
just gonna lean out like oh
okay okay perfect laughing we're letting
go Mars
close and
five minutes starting now
[Music]
um you can even hear the
but I'm speaking and probably picks up
there's a timer on it that's perfect
[Music]
okay in the meantime
I don't want to start making the next
pizza yet because I I'm nervous I want
this one to like
you know be finished first let me just
spread this again I think it cost
another corn crop though in the meantime
I think I'm okay with doing that
and maybe
maybe I should get some more flour in
the other container
[Music]
what I don't need now is salami and the
ham so maybe I'll just go get some more
flour and I'll bring these away okay so
I have a little bit more space I know I
guess no more of those okay okay are you
guys okay and can you wait for the pizza
a little bit please don't go please
don't go I'll be right back okay please
wait and make sure if the fire starts
just
all 9-1-1 okay I mean it doesn't work in
Austria I think but you know you know
you'll be fine Brownlee probably
[Music]
thank you
I'm back
did you guys call the fire department
yet
no birds no more
some more flour okay oh
God I'm scared
I hear
I hear plopping sounds should I be
concerned
this is the corn turning into popcorn
that's what popcorn is Right corn okay I
will not open them I will pray we have
to pray now
right
[Music]
wait a popcorn only works so
it doesn't like a popcorn does it
oh God
The Next Step popcorn Pizza
it's probably just the the you know the
liquid like the the juice
because it's like really [\h__\h] hot in
there and it's probably gonna be like
really like a like an ocean of pizza
because
even just with mozzarella it was already
you can see uh over there
you can see that's how it the first
pizza turned out I think you can really
see it as like oh
really wandering
and I put like real even more watery and
this
pineapple on this
my heart like my chest feels so tight
you have no idea
[Music]
I want to say about hmm
how far are we oh
ah
the light is turned on red what does
that mean
the door is not closer but
it's moving
yeah it's almost on zero
[Music]
I don't think I can eat I'm so nervous
then I've got
it
the famous queue have a plate
can you guys notice that I'm nervous is
it noticeable
that was quick yeah that's like how it
should be it was a proper Pizza Oven you
can even make it with some pizza ovens
you can make it in two minutes
my friend Pizza Oven can get you a pizza
in two minutes baby
is your hair okay
I'm gonna open it sorry guys you can't
see you'll see it in a second three two
one
okay you can bail you can't even see
that's what I mean okay the corn looks
great
ah yeah the crust uh interesting
interesting interesting I see some of
the pineapple but the juices are
overflowing interesting
all right I'll try to I'll try to you
know grab it with this
huh
[Music]
look at this masterpiece
you see some pineapple you see baby you
can see the salami it's still brexeling
Brooklyn uh cooking it's still cooking
let it cook
um oh it's setting now I think it's
setting
recipe look at this detail oh camera
thank you
we got a little bit hot over there
oh
okay I have to quickly get um all the
stuff out of the there's like some you
know
I have to make sure it stays clean
because you can't clean the [\h__\h] very
well
it's just a wild dust and I mean for a
couple of weeks it's gonna be fine with
them
and then I have to quickly close it
again so it doesn't lose the heat oh God
it's [\h__\h] awesome but it's scorching
okay
are we slowing out those fires
I'm gonna open the
window a little bit I think wow oh God
oh God I'm gonna kind of heat stroke in
here
oh
okay
that's good
I turned a terrible idea
into a nice one good one nice job I
can't read the full comments kind of cut
off there but thank you I know what you
mean you let me cook
oh I should cut the pizza a little bit
and taste it I'm too nervous to eat it
all but I want to taste a little bit and
then you know these are really good when
you warm them up too
but I think to cut it up you're gonna
have to put it on the cardboard
yeah
okay
let me cut it
smells good
I think the the
garlic I can I can smell it
all right I will cut it in the middle
unfortunately I have to go for the corn
ER
hunting through the
cardboard no
and I don't want to cut it on the
surface
um this one can I cut it in my kitchen
guys
sorry I want to call it in my kitchen
this doesn't feel so good it doesn't
feel stable and I feel honestly because
of the Corn probably but the heat didn't
really Reach the the outside Crest well
so it feels I mean
not raw blood
I'm not a big crust fan anyway give me a
second guys BRB don't
don't leave you know we have a good
amount for that don't you dare leaving
two more minutes I think I'll ask my
pizza friends
therapy
foreign
[Music]
difficult the the margarita we made kind
of turned out more like crispy like a
good crispiness this one feels like a
little bit more raw like a little bit
but
fine okay okay look at this piece
this is the tsunami piece
it looks fun I mean you see some
you know
it doesn't heat there yeah
and in terms of thickness you know I
would probably a pro would probably make
it fitter but I'm just really scared to
have holes in the in the
dough so I had to be careful I didn't
want to make it too thin so it looks
like like this
oh okay
still very hot I'm gonna dig in
I'm gonna just take some bites off of
this underneath the rest later
it looks perfect yeah
[Music]
yeah cord all over why don't you guys
not tell me maybe you did it's really
hard to see because the comments are so
far away
oh well we have corn around it the next
one I will not forget next one is
important
laughs
okay
uh
um oh wow
oh yeah oh yeah ah
yeah it's pretty thick I could make the
next one thinner because the margarita
was also thinner and it survived
um
so it's a little bit more on the mochi
mochi side
it's all right to look
um
yeah I really don't like this one oh
it's very juicy
the tomato sauce that we use I think has
a perfect flavor
very fresh
tasting mmm
hmm
it's very juice very a very hydrated
Pizza
wow voila I'm gonna bite into the corn
cob part okay
oh
[\h__\h] this is amazing
[Music]
I should have sprinkled some salt I
don't have any salt here right now but
that would improve it
um
oh yeah
that's really good this is way better
than the whole corn cause because like
this you can just bite off
the whole corn cups we would have to
take it off the crust and then nibble
around it
yeah this way you can just
wipe off
oh God
here
see you all right
[Music]
don't assault your food
I do taste the butter could be a little
bit more
very good I want to try the Hawaii
called Hawaii here
I haven't been breathing much
have a good second pizza I'm gonna end
it I can't take this
please kind of streams always like you
know
these are the end of me
but yeah here pineapple pizza with corn
cob crust
ah you know today is a day of jokes but
I am like 100 serious about it you may
think it's a joke no this is serious
honestly I feel like in this form
it's totally like it could be a special
you know pizza restaurant
because
it actually works really well you get
some extra flavor from the pizza
it just works really well you can just
bite into it normally it's just like wow
it harmonizes surprisingly well
and I don't even see the separate dishes
now because before I thought you know
with the little seasons one you take the
corn cob off and bite in so it's kind of
like a separate dish
but this one is like a combination oh
um
[Music]
hmm
oh
[\h__\h]
no pineapple
hmm
you're so good
all right now I'm confident
I shouldn't be too overconfident Joe
Joe okay I'm gonna switch this
because I noticed some
one cat hair on it and it's hard to get
off
step
yo and why why am I all wet inside
what like this is it's not sweat
but inside this kind of gloves
damn you get hot
wow
I think you're drenched yeah the
humidity okay
oh
damn it's gonna be difficult to put the
other gloves on
so humid
in a moment
let's get into this
monsters first
what
what monstrosity brought upon this trend
excuse me
Trent I mean I'm the trendsetter because
like nobody was really taking the
corncraft pizza seriously but
that's why we can't have nice things
guys
because you don't believe in the things
that are possible in this world
just do it don't let your dreams be
dreams
[Music]
I have one on okay
oh good
oh okay
um
we're staying away the thumb I think
I think
just
so hard to get into these
hi
it's not like they're dead skin type but
somehow it's still hard to get it
do it don't let your dreams with dreams
laughs
do it do it
make your corn called Pizza dream
beetroot I'm gonna
um I think we're gonna close the window
oh
[Music]
pizza number two
hmm
next one is also some pizza that many
people question me for which really
shouldn't be a thing
I don't understand
why it's a thing
because tuna Pizza is absolutely normal
[Music]
oh my God
all right now ah why don't you do the
corn Club first I mean I have to do the
corn Club
um
I learned Italian before but
yeah
you know how that went not that well
all right we're gonna make consoles for
you again because I think the free
worked out perfectly
well this one's dirty but whatever I
mean it's the Beats of dirt so whatever
it's all the same it's all getting in my
tummy
the people our technique
if you guys you
are
today
I'm not being sponsored and I'm still
saying this is really good believe me
I'm really enthusiastic about it please
try this at home please do try this at
home
but if your child doesn't maybe have
your mommy do the the corn cutting
Parts because
for me if I can do it you can probably
do it too
you know
okay the first one is I think the most
difficult
[Music]
it's easier to do it in my hand guys
don't worry
Ashley use your phones like I can't cut
like some people cut for example uh
potatoes
with like in their hand or like like
I don't know how to do that I can't
that scares me
I'm very careful don't worry ideally the
corn on the other side should stop me
okay I think I got it
I think I'm in
[Music]
every time I eat a corn Club you know I
see like how there's like still somehow
corn in there and I always wonder is
there a second layer that they're hiding
from me but I mean there really isn't
there is only one layer right guys
but it almost looks like there's still
like something yeah
there is only one layer right
all right yeah it feels like there's
more maybe there's a mutant version but
I feel like I say that it's like
something growing there but it's not
really edible
going like
trying to grow out but it really can't
I think I think it's just one layer yeah
there's a secret chord it's a secret
corn and they're hiding from me this is
really hard to reach
I'm so happy
so happy but I'm so stressed out guys
okay
free a row of freight here we go
we have to free the corn right of course
no shit's falling apart Stay Together
okay
strong
got it I got it I got it I got it I got
it I got it
corn cutting skills for the roof oh
oh I'm getting like a pro at this people
should hire me to make their corn crop
Pizza
I am a revolutionist and I am uh what do
you call these people
who come up with new businesses from
like Silicon Valley or whatever what do
you call them
what's that
you know I'm an innovator and yeah I'm
an entrepreneur
yes
right could you call this being an
entrepreneur
am I not doing entrepreneur things
you know I would say so
I'm everything I'm everything I want to
be
confident as [\h__\h]
play my dreams
wanna thought another corn layer I love
layers layers are beautiful
and it's fitting right
yeah
on trip on Triple entrepreneur and
entrep entrepreneur
that's me one two three
whoa why does this also does every corn
have the same amount of rose
not like everyone around the world but
like from the same place they come from
from like one you know because this has
the same amount of Rose guys
I also leaves me with one row one is one
single row isn't that amazing you know
what's more amazing
after buying the camera one two three
after buying the camera
I was a little bit hungry so I wanted to
get some chicken nuggets just a quickie
just
chicken nuggets yum
remember my bread story
the thing that I've always been waiting
for that apparently is more common than
having you know
how many was it seven pieces of bread
instead of six
it happened with chicken nuggets I
ordered nine chicken nuggets and I got
[Applause]
I opened the package that was like
that looks like more than nine on first
book
[Music]
yes yo I was like history repeats itself
and history
Rewards
for Life rewards the ones
that deserve it and I deserved an extra
chicken nugget man
10 chicken nuggets for the price of nine
whoa
absolutely amazing
one two three see it really leaves one
real again amazing I like this this is
perfect for OCD people if you have OCD
which I don't think I do
I mean okay I mean it's also kind of
like angering when only one bro
is left over
I guess I could have done two rows like
two two two two two but then again it's
the same as before and that is satisfied
on its own isn't it
I would say so
okay I want to end this stuff so soon
because I'm dying I want to know how it
is to be able to breathe again
and my shortness of breath is
overwhelming
I'll be knocked out in a moment
oh what are we doing tomorrow find them
right
oh man okay
again one left over
I'll eat that anyway okay
all right
it's time for the name the pizza
they're cleaning up all this will be fun
too
probably will still have most of this
around me
okay I'm bringing in holy [\h__\h] that what
is risen like a monster
oh my God that was huge that sounds so
huge now it rises more when it's um
next to like a warm environment
apparently and it definitely was that's
like that's huge am I getting more pizza
out of this now
what's good the more it rises the better
it is
I can't really
over rice I think it's huge it's way
bigger than my first one
oh my God
filling up the whole container
am I baking a cake
this one's so small they grow up so fast
look at this baby
bubbly
it's a bubbling
[Music]
okay
oh it's it's stinky though the yeast is
so stinky
I'm gonna Drop It Like It's Hot
okay
please go well hi
second the second second second
[Music]
shake it shake shake shake
Shake
[Music]
yeah
it's falling it's definitely falling
I just gotta give it some time and it
wants to go out slowly it's not ready it
loves this warm warm container let's
heat it up by the pizza chamber
give it a tap no I can't I have two
hands full I have to hold it but if I
see it leaving I see it living
oh
yeah yeah part of it is already there
and one one step
at a time
oh
I'm so proud of you you can do it you
you like
extremely grown piece of dough you're
ready now I know I know you are I know
gonna I'm just gonna rip it off like a
bandit
I think it's so sticky because of all
the olive oil because like I lined this
was olive oil but you're supposed to do
that
supposed to do that
I don't know
I'm gonna let go I'm gonna let go like
in Titanic okay
there's no space for both of us on here
in this container
it's time to let go
you have to go now
let's go
oh there you see this you see her uh
come on let's go I don't want to rip it
I don't want to be too rough oh God it
looks terrible on this side see that
and that's the spider webs inside okay
come on come on
come on
[Music]
adult life okay it's time for you to
become a big big grown pizza and
everybody wants to eat come on
I'm five meters oh
laughs
really
oh God I mean this is probably not ideal
don't ask me it's my first try today
but it's it's enough though okay we're
gonna spread the
power I'm now
already experience this is my first
pizza
I have never even
um made like one of those
supermarket
um do it yourself
pizzas before you know the ones with the
the dull
um
the dough that's kind of square that you
roll out and bake in your home pizza
oven at normal oven yeah
I've never made one of those before I
think maybe like when I live with my mom
maybe we made one together
but
yeah I skipped that step completely and
I went straight to like a more Hong Kong
Serious Pizza yeah yeah there's no chew
to hamper in my life no okay now we
gotta get rid of the air remember guys
remember boys I'm gonna move it a little
bit over here
kind of get rid of the air
but don't you have to leave
a little bit on the edges okay like
bring it to the edges bring it to the
edges
nice be nice
okay that's enough probably
now
turn it around
hi
okay we do the same thing on the other
side a little bit
and now way less nervous about it but I
still have shortness of breath so that
is a problem the camera is still alive
holy [\h__\h] it's hanging in there
I am
are you guys happy with the camera
quality
[Music]
I'm so happy but I want to watch the
archive it's so pretty I'll try to like
figure out
like now it's like kind of on a tripod
and a little bit at an angle because I
can't do like really
um completely
straight from the bird point of view
well I'll try to figure out if I can do
that in the future and maybe it will try
to mount a camera around my ceiling or
so
I don't know
yeah it's very beautiful right it's
clear and it's not like over light
not over but over over what's the word
after that
you know what I mean it's not too bright
it's like a realistic color the colors
are realistic all right hi
look at that
no well
kind of ripped on the on the corner
interestingly
that's I mean
acceptable
it's kind of the doll is uh kind of hard
on this side I wonder if it's like the
heat that pre-breaks it
because it's when they get rid of the
other one that's over there oh no oh
that one already reached the top and
that one wasn't at the bottom I'm like
put it as a tower next to the pizza oven
this is not so good oh well oh wow
are we still edible
okay now we're staying for the pizza
like a profession I'm not gonna do the
thing no no no I'm not gonna spin it on
them unless no
you need to be I need to learn to be a
little bit more rough with them
this part this that is weird
okay
still again I don't really have the
thick edges the contrast
but again I think that's okay
because of the corn cob that will be the
thickness the thick layer that we need
pick corn saves lives
okay I think I'm happy with that I want
to put it on the
on my supports my my AIDS
is this age is this age I got that from
the climbing video but is this
considered a
I don't think so why did I do it like
this
but I'm already like feeling so like
oh good about this like I'm having a
better time at like you know getting it
under it did it do silver matter do you
remember the days
or the hours the minutes we're
struggling to get it on top
um I'm not the same person that I was
back then I'm not the same Pizza Baker
that I would pick and I was like this is
not my fault this is not my fault
okay that's not my fault it's kind of it
has a different texture over there I
don't know why
all right
yeah I'm ready
I'm actually surprisingly
still spread this I think like myself
okay
nice
I think like this side feels a little
bit thicker than this side but it's okay
it's done it's time for to make it the
second pizza or the first pizza
it's a relief
from Mommy not really but the brand is
Mommy
[Music]
ingredients are so important but making
a good pizza but the most important is
the dough the most important ingredient
is the dough
remember that guys you have to find the
right though
trying to find a pizza specialized
store although
I did buy it as a set just in case I did
buy some
um really good they had good reviews on
Amazon a good
um uh flower on I bought it with the
oven on Amazon and my friend said that
this one's also pretty good it's called
Caputo Caputo
c-a-p-u-t oh I don't know which one the
one is that we made the dough with
sounds an even better one
the Caputo one is fine but apparently I
bought the dough
that make that that there's different
versions of that that flower and I
bought the flower uh from Caputo that
needs you to let it rise for 48 hours
and there's a different one that even in
high end it's about a flower there's
differences there too there's different
this for like 24 hours rising and the
one I bought was apparently for 48 hours
hmm
so that's the wrong one
but I'm just I can use this normal
flower as well of course
the rise of 40 48 hours that's fine too
if you know
you know
and go for it
okay I think this is fine
and actually wow that's a lot of
tomatoes it's just one container that
like 400 gram actually
okay we're making
yeah maybe first the crust again
Uno
the left
Bellissimo bene
[Music]
um
all right I'm gonna start the two now
because the other one will just be
simple I'm wait no I almost forgot the
this one first a little bit of
parmigiano
baked parmigiano because they didn't
have the
parmigiano already
um
what do you call this shape
I forgot brain horde
print empty you know what I mean
this one's just fine
yeah
uh-huh do I need a tuna yeah I didn't
drain the tuna but I will not just like
drip all the oil on it
[Music]
I mean I'm just not gonna drizzle the
oil that I was gonna drizzle on it on
that side
because you know maybe I should do the
onions first actually
the onions first
the stand it just like with the
margarita what I learned is
then you're supposed to put the the
little uh basil leaves under the
mozzarella cheese because the mozzarella
will give it some hydration and then the
leaves will not
will not um burn so maybe we have I mean
I don't think this will burn but maybe
it's nice that they have some hydration
a little bit you know
and a little bit more visually pleasing
if they're on this side huh
okay
interesting right and I said yeah yeah
you'll see you'll see I don't know I
will use the same technique again
okay I think this is
kind of enough
I want to spam it
ban Pizza I wonder that that probably
exists yeah
I'm not gonna be the crazy one to do
that one I will leave that to you guys
I'm the one I'm the crazy lady with the
Corn Pop Pizza the the span Pizza I
believe I don't know two Australians
that's kind of their thing isn't it spam
spam right it's not it's not pan right
it's spam I'm questioning myself now
crazy corn like that's me
put in the pizza Community as the crazy
corn lady
I want a lot of tuna on it Tuna on Pizza
is so good I want a lot
but I have to stop because it's gonna
give up so much water
okay okay and then the other one is just
mozzarella
I'm just gonna I want a few more last
time I only put
food
these are so good
basil is like like a cheating weapon of
the kitchen
pay to win basil is basically a Pay to
Win option
you cannot put too much basil let's be
real
pay to win
small one
okay pay to win basil
ICA
well if it's dead now it's charging
right
so at least it should at least be
charging let me let me like attach it to
a normal socket you will see it looks
like we'll take like a shark named 15
minutes break maybe I don't know oh
that's sad but it held out so long
without being fully charged yeah and it
was like on bread the whole time
um
oh
is that in there
yeah it's charging okay
we will be back shortly
How does it go you know which one I mean
[Music]
I forgot
let's just find it for like 10 minutes
I'll try to
what you already seen the pizza in a
really late stage here I'm just gonna
add the mozzarella now
it's already basically finished in in
the last picture you see on the Stream
this needs the coin now you know what
should I really
maybe only on the tuna side
I'll add some corn
oh some corn dropped on the other side
oopsie yeah we need more corn [\h__\h] it we
need to Corn everyone come on
the popcorn after all why did I doubt
myself I don't know who I am anymore I'm
sorry guys I'm not I'm not the courty
lady anymore
sorry I will avenge myself
I will redeem myself
I'll fix it
I promise okay here here here
there's a good amount of corn now
continuing with the mozzarella now
more corn
isn't there like a heavy metal uh band
called corn
should be what's playing now imagine
corn playing in the background now
instead of EDM maybe that would have
been good that would have probably
giving off a similar vibe to my
intention at the beginning of the Stream
come on where is that band from because
corn was okay I mean it's not how we
ride corn and
um
in German
and how do we call corn in German mice
mice called mice
and the corn cob is that mice called Ben
they're from oh they're from LA
oh they're American okay okay okay okay
I wonder why they called themselves corn
do they also love corn maybe maybe I
should give them a corn cob Pizza are
they reachable
and I sent them are they still active do
they still make music can I send them a
porn called Pizza
hello my dear corn band members if
you're seeing this I would love to
invite you to give our special corn cup
Pizza it is very very yummy please let
me feed you my super new specialist
Kiana fried pizza
for free of course I'm inviting you guys
for free
I just want you to taste this beautiful
thing that I made because of course you
were probably just as excited about the
prospect of a corn cup pizza from Little
Caesars as I was and then you probably
felt just as deceived as I was when it
turned out that it wasn't frail and then
they are trying to make it up with a
pretzel pizza I mean come on
you're not gonna do it gentle don't
tease me with it at all
you're not gonna follow through with it
it wasn't even April fools could have
done it on April Fools and then maybe I
would have doubted it
but you did it on a normal day
on a normal day of course I'm gonna
believe it
life is just not fair my pizza is kind
of ready to go should I wait to put it
in
but it's almost 10 pm and I kind of
wanted to finish around 10 pm
should I take a picture maybe I'll take
a picture because after that it's just
gonna end enough is gonna happen
anyway let me take a picture of these
dirty dirty dirty ass hands
I'll put it on the string just don't
worry
to clean my phone afterwards
okay
we're beautiful oh
I will need a picture on my phone anyway
of this as a commemoration
and I didn't take a picture of the first
one I'm never gonna remember it I'm
gonna forget about it it was so special
to me
me
okay okay I took the picture I sent it
on our food group Discord making other
people hungry
I have it on video yeah but it's not the
same yours we want it in both forms and
the screenshot it's not good too
Indian staff members are reacting to my
face oh what I got like a questioning
Emoji as a reaction to my corn cob Pizza
what are you questioning look what is
this funk Emoji eh you got something to
say to me huh
because I'm gonna say
anything wrong this isn't natural this
will be the new hit
this will be the new hit I'm telling you
every pizza restaurant in the world will
sell this Oh Mamma Mia
oh it's beautiful so colorful too
there's green there's purple there's
yellow there's red it's an RGB pizza oh
my God uh clockwise I counterclockwise
current state
is
beautiful oh my God it's beautiful
beautiful there's no blue yeah
I haven't even blue
Pizza like anything natural I don't
think so but the purple is pretty close
to Blue
excuse me we're not having it oh wait
you know what I need to put on one more
thing I have to um put on the the the
honey the butter
[Music]
wrap it in
yeah spider
[Music]
I swear the cat hair is coming from from
my table probably
don't get on the pizza
a little bit okay
um
almost got it
one second please
[Music]
I'm not spreading it with my finger now
I'm spreading it with a knife the big
knife
it's probably okay
I wonder
I wonder what you guys will think if you
try this please can someone try it at
home who's
it's right at home please please try it
it's not that difficult anyway you just
need like one corn cob for a pizza
will someone try it please
please will someone try it
not me I volunteer really not me why not
tell me why not I vote thank you
no friends
no why I will thank you I will thank you
[Music]
um I can't why not I mean I guess you
need a proper armor that's a problem you
need a prep Robin but I mean the one
that I got isn't that expensive and
gives you like a good result
that you can be satisfied with and start
with your new hobby then you will never
be able to let go
after that you will never forget and you
will get more and more into it and try
the profession
nice
your pizza making skills
I'm ready to
enter the pizza chamber
are you ready
opening
three two one
okay
okay perfectly placed
oh yeah
five minutes
maybe a little bit longer even number
six yeah not even six five and a half
minutes
time is ticking
[Music]
that will make everyone happy
I'm gonna take out the gloves
the picture's still up yeah it's fine
I'm I'm still gonna wait a little bit
give the camera some time to charge so
you can see the final product I'm gonna
do it until the last moment
so now we can have some good pizza
footage
commemorate this moment
okay
you gloves
oh let me go I want to see the comments
closer okay
[Music]
foreign
what season is this there's mozzarella
on the top and a thin layer of
parmigiano
uh on the very bottom on top of the
tomato
so colorful it's so beautiful
are you sure
fine Lulu thank you I also explained
everything you know very clearly
but it's probably
uh what's the hashtag kfb kfp
just can't speak
[Music]
five minutes are like over in an instant
we are
getting there
at least
this one the first one already very good
like if you like Hawaii amazing
salami one was really like basic because
you know salami in my mind is basic but
really good too like definitely better
than like a Frozen
uh shelf Pizza
the ones from the Frozen Shelf
and
there's like one uh pizza place that I
go to every once in a while and they
have like not the most perfect pizza but
definitely like
pretty good my pretty Italian tasting
pretty good
but I I think like my salami Pizza can
definitely keep up with theirs and my
husband picks up they don't even I don't
even think they have a Hawaiian pizza
oh it's popping again
[Music]
what in tarnation the reactions of
people just cutting into the stream and
like what the [\h__\h] did you make what do
you think I was making judging by the
Twitter
advertisement and the title of the
stream and the the thumbnail what do you
think what's gonna happen here huh
when I do things I do them seriously I'm
always very serious about what I do okay
there is business it's not a joke it may
be April 1st but it's not a joke
I made a masterpiece yeah it's so
beautiful
bye baby my baby
my baby
it's one of the best purchases I've ever
made this pizza oven I will say
maybe better than the air fryer
yeah but you guys clearly don't own the
pizza chamber
and maybe not even an air fryer
[Music]
maybe it's time to get one
I would recommend the pizza chamber
it's Pizza Oven Pizza Oven for home yeah
clearly
the word flips I have so many
ingredients left I have one more dough
I'll make it off stream that one I
wonder which one we should use like all
the ingredients for that one
I have so many ingredients love
hmm
make some pasta with some of this like
the the onions the corn
mozzarella the best of the the tuna yeah
tuna corn tuna corn definitely I like
that pasta I've had that before tuna
pasta
maybe I'll make that tomorrow
under the pineapple
I guess I'll eat those for breakfast
maybe it was some yogurt
um yeah
and salami just some sandwiches the ham
also
yeah I'll figure it out
[Music]
try very quickly
can I afford to really quickly try to
get my camera that's working
oh it's it's it's cooking
it's cooking
I hear it so clearly
probably have to refresh it
oh
yeah uh turn it on possibly
right
I feel about that
um
seven percent
oh wait
[Music]
oh wait how's the weather okay camera is
so new Adam
I don't know what this camera
okay
um
you know what to understand huh wait a
minute I have to take a pizza off first
oh
okay hmm
[Music]
let's figure out the picture
okay I have to turn the mode on first
pizza looks good though
um the
Margarita part is like swimming a little
bit
but besides that
looks really good because the onion is
like asserting its dominance
oh yeah and you see that the tuna as
well okay okay
let me figure out the camera real quick
we got it to work
uh disconnect once okay
connect once
[Music]
okay USB streaming activated I am my own
I.T person
all right
oh yeah it's working I think
seven percent just enough to end the
Stream
yeah I don't think so
it's back
ah wait is there that's the other view
right yeah that's the phone that's it
that's it oh
[Music]
this one looks even better I think the
crust on this side is pretty decent
the corn looks really good better than
the previous one I think it did the
couple seconds made the difference
the tuna part yes the you know the
margarita it was just like all melt
together it's kind of you know crazy
looking not so aesthetically pleasing
but y'all
my God that is a beauty that is a beauty
yummy looks amazing right oh
big jump this beautiful way I want it to
be
gonna take a screenshot and take it now
[Music]
okay okay
let me
uh cut it real quick and I will get a
taste test okay
see you in a moment
good
foreign
[Music]
is black now
but I can still like blow it off
I'm gonna go over the side and blow from
there
I will vacuum clean up the woods
yeah it's fine at least nothing's like
sticking like it's only a flower I think
but nothing's sticking like tomato sauce
or so nothing dripped out no hole either
and you know
I'm not the only one who thinks this is
great my pizza friend said that the corn
crust is actually a genius really good
and then the overall pizza was also
insanely good I'm so happy I'm a genius
okay I'm gonna try the tuna
I'm gonna die but I'm gonna try to tuna
um a little piece of cup
oh
that I love the focus it shows the real
beauty of this pizza
oh okay
it's still very hot
it looks so good oh
my camera is so far away but it still
captures my face pretty good thank God
ah
oh
oh yeah
um
that is really good
[Music]
everything's harmonizing perfectly I
wonder how to
I mean
of course it won't work I'll bite into
the crust again ah
enough Red Onion yeah
I think so I understand some that you
don't sit underneath you
um
corn
perfect
tuna perfect
o
onion perfecto
perfecto
very small
oh
yeah
it does have a crunch it has some some
um
fluffiness like Ben is still very fluffy
and then the very bottom has the crunch
in it
so perfectly balanced as all things
should be
the bottom of the pizza is maybe a
little bit too flowery
so good
hmm
I love it what
I really can't eat while I'm streaming
like I'm I'm still and like on how do
you say it I'm so on on the fence no I'm
on edge on edge on the fence and on
there it's just kind of different thing
but
that was my special April full stream to
you guys please
consider this a reality
consider maybe trying it yourself
sometime if you get yourself a pizza
oven like it's a good investment if you
want good pizza
and maybe Little Caesars if you're
watching this
you I I said you should still do the
corn cut pizza but maybe do it like I
did
and then sponsor me
because your idea wasn't really
realistic okay I'll say it now because
the corn cop you know you know it's not
part of the pizza it's just a separate
little accessory if you don't like me
it'll work out and it'll be like
marvelous
um
[Music]
you're welcome I'm
[Laughter]
also really thanks to that viewer that
helped me out with figuring the the corn
stuff out as well
Little Caesars I'm waiting okay here
let's go and corn the band I'm also
waiting you don't school you're at
school you know school okay
please contact cover
um or me on Twitter you can reply to me
I'll I'll check my replies constantly I
never miss one I think so I probably
that's probably safer and then I'll DM
you okay Little Caesars and corn I hope
uh corn is on Twitter I know Little
Caesar says I follow you guys you can I
follow little Seasons you guys can
directly DM me actually you can skip
that step you're well considered so I'm
waiting with open arms
okay thank you guys so much for watching
how did Germany today and I am for some
reason out of breath yeah
yeah well let's go asthma
[Music]
bye
bye see you tomorrow for finals
I'm waving at you guys it's kind of
awkward but I'm waving at you
in Serenity calmness now
uh some I'm so done
I'm gonna have free beats us welcome to
KF pizza today only time Limited
[Music]
awesome
foreign
[Music]