ah hello
[Music]
and welcome to the first I would say
full collaboration but now we have
Council so it's the first almost full
collaboration of Polo Indian and
Indonesia
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
it's going to come back the Discord
fight on this is actually probably
watching this
can I see the tweets from Discord
yesterday with all the screens on Mario
Kart
so we're glad to have the Discord
support today and hopefully also the
viewers support today because uh today
will be a very very passionate and
dangerous and fun and exciting events
[Music]
yes exactly the drivers best Riders no
we're not here
everybody
I made me a bad driver but I'll drive
you guys nuts
[Applause]
I think we shall start with some
introductions of each member and now
let's start with
whole life Indonesia
[Music]
hello thank you for having me this is
continuation thank you everyone I can't
wait what's your what's up
what's my ikigomi um to not be um the
last last place at least
that's good
[Music]
[Applause]
okay what about
[Music]
um
generation one
so my motivation tonight is
um to show you my practice I guess
oh
show me what you got
it next up how about rainy
hi attention please I'm probably Iranian
from whole life ID generation 2. my goal
today is to be number one in your heart
and also not that loud
yeah I thought you were good you and
Iris have heard good good good news
about you
we had a good practice yesterday right
right
[Music]
thank you
next time bye
hello
my name is
[Music]
what's the motivation for today oh well
I I want to be at least not on the last
okay
[Music]
okay next up
Indonesia and thank you so much for
inviting me to this collab I'm so happy
though I'm so excited
thank you
[Music]
my motivation for today is that I would
like to have fun though although yes I'm
not really confident but let's have fun
all right
[Music]
guys
foreign
motivation I plan on ranking pop so that
you guys become my bottoms that is my
motivations
on top I don't know what else is
expected from your motivation only
I'll pin you guys into bottoms relax
okay we're already here
we won't be dominated with that easily
sometimes
[Music]
some ID I think I did
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
all right let's introduce the E inside
let's start with Iris
oh yeah hiris is Iris holy live English
project hope B singer here
um my goal today is to get first place
Victorious
and looking forward to your driving
skills thank you so much for having me
here so I heard that you waited for yeah
come on we're literally in the last
version that I think it's because before
you it was an elf that's what that was
German we were 11 people
[Music]
thank you next up how about
um
this is the I own I heard you only
played Mario Kart so far in the members
only stream but that's about it
yeah I won in that one too oh oh okay
I see you oh then you might be the
hidden winning choice that no one is
of course the Wild Card Player welcome
amazing
um
[Music]
um I'll do my best I think we have a we
have a future competition to be not last
and to be first so I'll do my best
you know I was also taking this very
seriously in her practice round so I'm a
bit scared of Ina um I don't know
I'm still falling off Maps it's fun oh
yeah it happens oh Kelly joined just
nice
[Music]
hello everyone my name is Kawaii my
parents are still asleep and probably
can't watch the news this morning
because it's a bit early uh so excuse me
for that guys but I'm very excited just
to be here I really didn't think this
was gonna work but it's working
thank you Sally for joining even though
it's such an early time and it kind of a
Troublesome with some setups and all
that I'm glad you're still here and you
know what you being so Whispering calm
might be a good thing for driving
because that way you might be able to
focus more videos
[Laughter]
English and I'm kind of sick today and
if you're watching on my side I just
need to say this now I've had some
technical difficulties very suddenly so
I am made of cardboard I'm sorry please
well it was not my fault it's out of my
control right now so anyway
I'm PNG tuber Doma Summit does a PNG
tuber Let's Race today baby I'm the wild
card today
[Music]
well you know on the screen there's
there's gonna be a lot of things
happening so your viewers should be
looking at the game and not you anyway
so it's fine I'm cute of course they
want to look at me right guys
[Music]
all right that leaves uh me I think yeah
yes
welcome everyone I wanted to do this
tournament for a long long time uh I I
think my viewers have heard me talk
about it since months ago and finally
it's happening uh and I'm very glad to
have all these lovely girls here
together it's the first time we're doing
a tournament like this so I I don't
think anyone has to feel bad about you
know not being so good it's all fine
maybe we'll do it some more often in the
future so please don't stress yourself
out let's just have fun today
[Music]
I think we will go to the roots but
before that let me say thank you is the
hats and the cards are sponsored by
ninoma inanis yes
they look lovely so cute all right let's
uh everyone switch to the rules image
please thank you
okay tournament rules easy there's not
many rules basically uh all characters
all courses are allowed however if you
choose uh please do not choose random
courses please choose a certain course
that you want to actually erase but if
that course has been used before like if
it has actually been chosen before
please do not choose the same course
again
[Music]
number two items are allowed number
three uh we are racing in 150 cc with no
assist everyone please check if you have
turned off your assistance I think you
can check by pressing y
'all all right
now okay
if uh wait a second it's if you press Y
and select your character at the point
where you select the card you can press
on a plus
the plus button and that's when you see
the the three options on the right side
if you press l
uh if if there is a if there's a sign
that says no
then it's uh all the staring off that's
how it's supposed to be okay
yeah it's supposed to be crossed out
exactly the other ones you can ignore
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
this whole time so unless I have
something to say I'm gonna be muted
don't worry if I'm a little quiet I'm
still here with you guys in spirit yeah
okay okay
and next row uh oh yeah there's no more
rules there's basically it's just the
system we're doing the first cup all
versus all big mixer for races but then
we get we will mute each other by the
way during the race and just to focus
everyone on what we're driving and then
we get back together and Discord talk a
little bit then we go to the second cup
which is en versus ID six versus six yes
when we will separate each other in uh
The Voice channels by team this one in
this one we will actually talk with one
another if you wanna and then we uh give
some comments together again when we get
all back together in the same channel
and then we do the first cup with random
randomly thrown together teams no Ian
versus IP but like all mixed together
naturally beautiful
random random random we will just like
I'll count down and and then everyone
everybody wants to be
well then we're gonna have to do it
again and again
perfect and by the way just just so you
know the the those like team cups will
basically be
um like the same system as the old
versus all the difference is just
basically like if you throw items like
red shells or whatever and there is a
teammate in front of you it will not go
to the teammate obviously it will go
directly to the closest opponent's
driver uh that's around you so yeah
that's how that team system works I
think
[Applause]
I'm ready
then everyone who's ready mute yourself
on Discord if someone's not ready then I
will ask you why you're not ready okay
[Music]
I love you love you too
all right guys now it's just you and me
so yeah
um I am a PNG right now because I had a
very well I don't know the app all of a
sudden is just not participating not
cooperating
uh
apparently I have a brand new error
issue going on and I didn't have enough
time to fix it and I didn't have enough
time to set up something else without
uh installing everything also my setup I
don't know what happened but like last
minute all my all my audio went wacky I
don't know man I'm just here we're gonna
just race okay also I woke up from uh
when I woke up and I'm not feeling so
hot so anyway we're just gonna race
today I've got my Pro Controller I got
my Pro Controller and I'm gonna try hard
a little bit
um but if I can't be the very best then
I'm gonna be the very worst
wait what do we do oh okay we pick up we
pick up uh any banjos quick where's the
banjo one ah
there we go
[Music]
Let Me Wait what yeah wait what
so my game audio is really loud for me
too
it's unfortunate isn't it
I think we'll be okay
[Music]
no it was so close
I'm going to win I think I'll be okay I
think oh
[Music]
I
this is so loud in my ears
okay
[Music]
let's go baby
[Applause]
foreign
well we're off to a great start
[Music]
it's okay we're gonna get like Bullet
Bill or something something good is
gonna happen
[Music]
foreign
everybody shut up
wow
[Applause]
[Music]
oh that's unfortunate
bye Watson aha
[Music]
foreign
we're not in teams yet we're not in
teams that was our our warm-up round I
guess not that bad for a warmer Brown
also was that Calliope Mori in front of
me
did Wyatt were my eyes to see did my
eyes to see the mirror was that Calliope
Morrison what is going on
Cali
I'm waiting for everybody to unmute but
yeah
that must be the thing am I right did
you guys see Watson go off the edge at
the end
Calliope Morrison
I don't know this is not part of the
world but we didn't get it yet so I'm
gonna choose it again did I just break
the rules
wait I thought we were doing
[Music]
I thought we were supposed to be in
teams now oh well it's all right
[Music]
dang it
all right let's go again let's go for
first place
hello
hello four races not a single race oh oh
okay I see
when I hold down the button
[Music]
all right all right
it's all right we can come back from
this we can come back
[Music]
I oh no oh yeah
oh okay oh boy
foreign
[Music]
let's see if we can hit somebody up here
sorry
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
place I'll take fourth place
yay Ben we're doing all right so far
okay and please everyone do not use
cheap cheap beach or a Mario Kart
Stadium anymore for your race selection
thank you I'm gonna try and remember
that but I don't know yeah yeah nothing
that looks like a beach and nothing that
looks like a fancy night life place
right but isn't there multiple Beach
uh yeah but the cheap cheap beach the
one that we just did from the DS version
not anymore okay okay okay are we doing
team wait when are we doing teams
uh we still have two races to go of
course okay
nice hat you know she's muted okay
are we oh sorry okay
[Music]
everybody was muted and I was still
talking I'm sorry
I haven't practiced this game at all the
last time the last time I played this I
think was
the last time
when did when did I I think I streamed
it did I stream it I don't remember the
last time I played it
I haven't practiced any though I was
going to I was gonna try and learn all
the shortcuts but I don't know I decided
not to because it's my real car it's
Mario Kart
trap come on good
it's too slow
[Music]
stop pushing me
damn it
[Music]
come on
stop it I'm safe don't pick on me
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
it's okay
from it don't worry about it
don't worry about it we can come back
it'll be worth the don't worry
[Music]
this is a squash
I was gonna say it's a strap but I don't
think it oh oh oh oh oh oh it's fine
it's fine it's fine it's fine it's fine
it's fine don't worry watch this I'm
gonna come back I'm gonna come back
don't worry
[Music]
I told you I'm coming back I thought I
thought it was a strap I thought it was
a strap don't worry about it
now
[Music]
Here Comes
[\h__\h] I'm trying to make some back here
[Music]
everybody
oh it's not garbage how do you swap your
items
that's fine come back fourth place I'll
take it
now come back
how do you swap your items out
[Music]
oh you can't can you imagine if I was
able to use my star I was gonna swap out
for my star at the end there dang it
that's all right though I'll take fourth
place again
uh I'm going again for warriors gold
mine
you trust me we're all right we'll take
it easy I'm gonna sneeze wait
wait no it's going all right mashing
button items
fourth place unlock I'm doing fine yeah
I'm doing fine God I love Raymond's do
you see rain is hurting me is so good
I love the lines of the mouse like it's
it looks like she tasted something sour
and she's like
[Music]
give me my Wario gold mine what is this
it looks like iris is in first place
with 34 points oh no no you don't mind
you know it's in first place with 39
points pardon me
are practicing paid off
[Music]
wow what happened
all right
[Music]
[Applause]
I will kick your ass yeah
oh
yeah boys playing something like that
for my voice let's get out of my way
[Music]
what is this garbage game
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
I think I should come back from this
don't worry about it
[Music]
foreign
wow that was garbage
what carb that was garbage okay about
the disconnect
[Music]
I'm not sure like normally it seems like
in the whole of Japan tournaments they
automatically give the one like well the
like this qualification like last spot
if you uh oh if you are oh wow uh
congratulations or everyone cannot mute
themselves now yeah
[Music]
but she still was a fourth or what so
yeah
I think that's just how we're gonna take
it it is what it
[Music]
so uh let me let me just uh enough was
number one right number one
congratulations
[Music]
I I saw you kept on selecting Rainbow
Road
you know
one you know
what yeah yeah she practiced on that one
a lot I think that's why she was going
for it
'll be ready
we'll get it oh okay someone has to uh
yeah wait uh wait who was number two
okay
no problem who was number two though
[Music]
I was how did you how did you manage to
get number two today I I did bad on the
first race so that really pulled me back
but yeah Ina Senpai was very quick but I
did my best I did my best
you were amazing
oh wait me and Elena were third are we
tired
good job good job oh wait wait are we
complete in the lobby right now one two
three
okay
okay well then shall we continue uh but
Muna senpa is currently unavailable
[Music]
but I don't know my my battery is 100
but it's a low battery so I don't know
which one is low battery oh
the ones that you like
do you think you're fine to go or you
need some time
everyone who needs coffee go get
yourself a cup of coffee
I have the caffeine shakes already so
I'm banned from coffee
I was actually really surprised about
ama's driving too like I thought you
know because she didn't like we didn't
see her practicing we didn't see her
play the game a lot
yeah
screwed over
here
as planned right it's all part of the
plan
or whatever yeah no it would have been a
waste if you would have shoutcasted how
you uh suggested I mean because you were
such a good driver we need you we need
you
all right then let's uh okay only okay
okay
are we picking teams like dodgeball
no that gives me really bad flashbacks I
don't like that
does that mean someone picked last and I
don't want that I'm gonna go up my full
power now because now I'm fighting for
the en ladies
this is where we put our all in it yeah
of our teams
I'll just warm up now it's not really
looking yeah actually this is good
because Iris two of the strongest ones
are in Ian wait me too
oh my God
I'm okay at not getting last place so
that's good news yes Columbia Morrison
is a good asset to have I want her on
our team hell yeah
guys
will have to carry uh Indonesia's uh
back yes
[Laughter]
[Music]
everyone please split into teams by I
think let's just um Ian go to a voice
channel oh one thank you okay
and number one let's go
wait a second okay okay okay and Cali's
missing if Kelly get the memo can
somebody drive Kelly oh never mind this
is
hello ladies I'm back hello hello what
is our strategy for winning against
Daddy
[Music]
but like um you know for items do they
automatically um not hit our teammates
yeah it only hits like oh okay that's
really nice
but I've never parted teams yet let's
see how we can select that I think we
will um like every every participant
will have a choice to win which team
they can join I think that's how it
works let's see no more items no CPU all
vehicles race four races let's go
let's go so long as Watson doesn't drive
off the edge we should be home
okay oh
I I I'm the one doing this okay uh Cleo
was all erect yeah no no wait no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no how do I cancel
this no
I have to like you might have to
okay no problem okay it looks fine okay
oh communication
all right
I'm creating the room right now
I did a little mistake because like I
thought uh oh yeah you know uh
okay you can join them again
okay
yeah you can you can join in again it's
open again I think it's closed once you
can join again
thank you sorry
[Music]
it's ready to drift
S
as much as you can that's that's how
this works yes but not overdrived you
know you know there they are open into
the Laurel phase the bald one is back
using her full power with the baldness
[Music]
I think we are okay
no CPU all vehicles
[Music]
yeah at least a little Baldy
so you guys know what my mom is watching
hi
hi are you sure you don't want to say
anything
[Music]
what is that Anya okay okay now it's
eaten let's go anymore
[Music]
Let's Lose
I want to do Wario Stadium
music Park I like music parks
are they using a tactic yeah they're all
overloading the probability
no I think those they're they're
definitely teams
[Music]
when do we push the go button on the
tube
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
your perspectives afterwards
okay we got it we got it we got it we
got third place
[Music]
that was my red shell I believe
right
[Music]
no yeah
oh okay
okay one map guys come on okay
Bowser Castle Bowser Castle which belt
or cat no no that's me the crown called
whatever it's called I like Mount Wario
or like the animal crossing map is easy
like easy as in it's like oh no you
gotta make it difficulties
can't wait
we have crowns
[Music]
okay okay
what no I don't like the cheese one no
see it's not the lactose
I have practice in that one
isn't it
[Music]
just has a lot of traps and a lot of um
obstacles
okay everybody don't suck I'm his evil
now
it looks dirty
I was number one for one second I love
that one
I like this music
[Music]
I'm not even
status
[Music]
but look at it so everyone's eating it
okay
[Music]
thank you
protect yourself
[Music]
these Corners are tricky
oh no I don't like it
is
pretty good yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
monkey mode Let's Go
[Music]
involved
my mind
[Music]
oh no oh no
oh no what oh no
wow what a play by Heidi and the
lightning oh rain and moving up the rain
I feel like they uh I feel like they're
definitely getting tactical on us here
you guys
we're good but we shouldn't jinx it
right guys
no no rainbow rose rainbow road on the
crown yeah rainbow everyone in the crown
okay
[Music]
cheese versus rainbow
yeah
one one
[Music]
but how high are the chances of it's
gonna be that one don't worry it's gonna
be Rainbow Road and I hate it
I feel like it's covered cheese yeah
it's too much cheese here
oh
[Music]
why do they like that one so much
they must know something we don't I'm
Robbie is probably really good at that
one that's why I chose it oh probably
trying to get the points back we can't
let them all right we'll get him we'll
get him you have a good Head Start yeah
Kelly yeah oh I'm gonna burn out I'm
just kidding
[Music]
thank you
I didn't even know that was a shortcut
I know the shortcuts were in trouble
okay
oh
[Music]
oh yeah
all right
thank you
come on guys
[Music]
foreign
that's the last doll
for the way Indian rainbow rainbow
s
but we have Ina so okay yeah I don't
know I'll do it guys
so I don't know anything short let's see
but the shortcut is just go down in
space Anna
she'll carry you some areas through yeah
with her gravitation gravitational I
don't mind the earth
I know the shortcuts for that
oh
[Music]
I love you guys yeah
like the lower rankings
yeah let's go we're pretty ahead though
we can do it
just don't fall off the edge
[Music]
thank you
I'm so slippery
[Music]
okay we are one two three right now
okay
that's fine
on my back okay
[Music]
when I'm in the tunnel
oh no always
[Music]
coming
[Applause]
no it was so nice
oh my God nope
[Music]
okay okay
chocolate
[Music]
nice
okay
[Music]
oh it's so scary there
until the end oh unfortunately
still not last
[Music]
one
oh yeah
[Music]
okay
we're going back okay we're going back
congratulations
[Music]
Indonesian team uh what was their
reasoning behind choosing uh the cheese
one and the baby Road I like cheese
because
[Music]
knows the shortcuts and stuff yeah I am
yeah
what uh do we have uh some uh comments
from the winner Ina it was number one I
think
yes uh I would like to thank my chair
mates
[Laughter]
for this opportunity because of you I
was about to be like yeah go let's go
okay
[Laughter]
okay so uh we're doing random teams next
there's four more races so please
everyone be careful to not choose any
roads that have been chosen previously
that I would appreciate that
um
[Music]
well even if you accidentally choose one
that has been uh chosen before don't
worry it will probably not be selected
so let's just let's just try to not
choose the ones that we have uh raced
before then I will do the random teams
now actually there is uh we don't have
to do the voice chat thing because there
is actually a way to do it here
and then once the teams are selected oh
there it is okay so uh invoice chat zero
zero zero one we want uh gura hi Ina yes
all right
all right all right team got this in the
bag we've got Ina as long as I remember
his place we win but oh rain is with us
too okay that's looking good all right
all right
okay we can do this
is not dangerous just push her off the
push off
[Laughter]
you want
another
um
oh they're going for the airport
let's fly to the Bahamas
[Music]
okay okay
okay
Ice Baby
okay okay good memories of that one I
think okay actually good all right let's
go okay yes
[Music]
Google
because
I don't know it is
[Music]
um
oh
yeah
I'm trolling I'm so sorry
I misdrifted fine okay all you can
follow me
[Music]
you
don't come on
there's always a question who the hell
hit me this time
[Music]
oh
yeah
[Music]
who was responsible for that who is one
two three I'm sorry sorry I got blue
shells right in front of the Finish Line
we're still pretty much at the top so
yeah we got a lot of it
Iris oh she saw my tail
this is the most adrenaline I've had in
a very long time hey my heart is like
[Music]
all right now
I'm like surprised like I didn't think
it would be this much fun to like have a
full tournament with everyone and we're
having a blast man
but now it is like every every half year
we should do something like this yeah
what is whatever
there's a lot of the airports
I forgot
no problem we didn't have that one yet
no that's the womp womp womp womp
again yeah baby
Choice
blessed by the RNG
guys
I hear you
okay
[Music]
the humanity
[Applause]
okay this part I usually killed
[Music]
right here
now be careful
[Music]
myself
oh my God drunk during this race
right
iris is scary
I was right behind he's running behind
me
eating dope yeah
good job everyone good job
[Music]
good job
for the airport because they really want
the airport
foreign
[Music]
Iris
oh my God
[Music]
hope you guys enjoyed that And subscribe
I just got screwed over like you would
not believe
[Music]
behind you
absolutely
don't worry
I got it
let's go
[Music]
let's go let's go
oh yeah
and Iris okay
oh
wow
this is not looking good
okay I believe in the RNG I
come back
[Music]
I don't know how to use the how do you
use the paraglider
[Music]
Elena came here
oh
[Music]
my gosh
oh my God everyone in front of me is
booty
whale again
a lot of something a miracle happens I
don't know I'm not feeling this one yeah
I can't come back from this me neither
this is unfortunate
okay it's okay
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
okay
someone dropped out
[Music]
um
you gotta come back are we gonna come
back are we picking
one
drop down
wait a divorce
and I don't know if she can join in time
wait stop someone please don't join
don't choose a race yet if you can
because this has more time
again okay
[Music]
oh oh no
it is
rough okay there's 12 choices at least
I don't like Ollie's Ollie's me it's
smug
[Music]
okay that's good okay all music okay
here we go let's go
last round two everything we can
you gotta come back
[Music]
oh
my God
[Music]
already
[Applause]
it comes
um
[Music]
hot
pot
okay one more one more one more
let's go let's go
that's garbage
[Music]
oh
my God
[Music]
I do see the Red Tails
it tries
assistant
[Music]
[Applause]
are we finished the course
I was disconnected
I said sarcasm
[Music]
we got it anyway
s
this is our favorite course
[Music]
okay
foreign
[Music]
got deleted that means that the last
round uh final result is not really
accurate
um but that's okay but let's just say
the last round was an extra Encore for
fun and and yeah and I would like to
give out some golden juggles
right so okay they're not showing up on
your screen
but I'd like I would like to give one a
golden juggle to Ina for winning almost
everything
[Music]
by Speedy congratulations
trophy
[Music]
[Applause]
and I would like to give uh another uh
golden Yago as uh to Iris for also being
absolutely amazing
[Music]
another golden juggle goes to Dana for
being I guess the strongest in the ID
team holy moly
[Music]
for being absolutely the speediest truck
I've ever seen yay
[Laughter]
damn Wild Card yo honey
[Music]
[Applause]
Ninjago goes to Muna for being amazing
I didn't see you that much on the race
but I think it was still shining
brightly as as the moon always does
the darkest time
and now the golden yellow goes to only
for being also surprisingly damn good
yeah
[Music]
[Applause]
easy too thank you for participating
[Music]
and another golden Yago goes to Cali for
actually really you know I don't you
surprise me you surprised me Callie I
was I was looking at you driving there
and I was like damn well what the hell
man she didn't even do practice arts and
she's so good maybe her mommy
[Laughter]
I didn't get last place even
[Music]
don't mind me uh chat I'm not gonna be
able to fix that now I think one two
three four five six seven eight nine ten
eleven
wait who did I not give up
you are so
stupid sometimes I have I had an eye on
you thank you congratulations
[Music]
thank you
thank you very much everyone
um I hope you all had fun
um can we get like a last last comment
from everyone let's start with anyone
oh me okay
um that was so much fun but I have to
practice more
it will definitely be a next time yeah
room for improvement
thank you
[Music]
Kelly what's your closing comment
uh let's see my closing comment is Kiara
thank you for everything you made an
amazing tournament you worked so hard on
this you had a logo commissioned you
made all of this stuff in as well for
helping with the assets but like oh my
goodness you organized the whole thing
and it was a blast and I just wanted to
have fun with my friends and I was able
to do that because you organized this
amazing thing just thank you so much for
for working so hard on it because it was
a blast thank you I'm so glad you
enjoyed it thank you
[Music]
oh thank you I want to say thank you
also to Ina and Kiara for all the hard
work you guys put into this tournament
thank you and I'm very I'm proud of
myself for not doing nearly as bad as I
thought I would and I would like to uh
say that it was probably because I fixed
my switch legs so I didn't have any lag
let's go Gamers let's go
no excuse I watched and I won though I
can use that excuse
[Music]
yeah no practice baby
that's good
let's Go
Roblox please
yes so I'm just uh thank you for
organizing this and now we have uh
mishaps and some travels early on but
yes thank you for this golden young I
will cherish it and talk to you okay
thank you so much
thank you too thank you thank you okay
I've completely disappeared I'm sorry
guys
okay Iris closing comments please thank
you so much for inviting me to this
wonderful tournament Kiara and thank you
so much Ina for the very very cute
assets and yes I will practice more so
that we can I can get go against Ina
yeah my goal is Nina yeah I'm really
excited to do this again hopefully one
day yeah thank you
[Music]
thank you I hope yeah one day I want to
win against Ina to dance a big big goal
that would be a big accomplishment it's
not that big of a goal
[Laughter]
s
I'm so glad I'm so glad you joined Holo
Ian because that's what made this
tournament possible yeah I'm really glad
to be able to join this wonderful
Tournament being part of the cool kids
all right Ollie clothing
okay I'd like to say a very very big
thank you to Kiara Senpai for organizing
this I've organized it once and it was
really hectic so I can't really imagine
the links that you go through
logos and stuff and even the thumbnails
those must have been hard and also for
each and five for making all of those
acids so quickly like you guys really um
how do I say it I really appreciate it a
lot and I'm sure all of us do so thank
you so much for your hard work it was
really fun playing with everyone and um
I may have not popped everyone but one
way or another you guys will all be my
bottoms
I forgot about that goal yeah
you'll get him someday only you'll get
him
thank you thank you all right
[Music]
um first of all um
I mean I I don't think without without
you organizing we will do me like this I
mean it's it's rare to gather all the
whole lives
that's true yeah I'm so thankful for
that and also
um big thanks to inatsu for making the
assets it's really hard thank you so
much and I hope in the future we can do
it again
yeah yeah
yes yes yes I hope so too definitely I
was thinking like maybe on on uh like
around Christmas or New Year's Eve we'll
just do something like that yes
please yeah I'd like to say a big thank
you to uh Cara for organizing it of
course I know like organizing collabs
and everyone in different time zones and
like schedules really really difficult
but you really put a lot of effort into
organizing it commissioning like the
logo and everything really thankful
um and everyone feel free to use your
hats and cards like in your Mario
costumes in the future too
[Music]
and uh yeah thank you everyone for
joining us today like it was so much fun
like playing with everyone and um
this was a great collaboration between
kfb and Taco Taco Bell taco eats
definitely
[Music]
um
our fast food franchises are meant to be
together
[Music]
okay okay
closing comments please
okay I know you said stuff but thank you
thank you so much and I had a lot of fun
oh there was a little miss out there
there was a little disconnection issue
but overall I had a lot of fun and I
would love to have this kind of
tournament again in the future let's do
it again yeah no thank you
training so I'll get better everybody
next time
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you
install closing comments please
okay so it doesn't end there I would
like to say thank you
to everyone here also especially uh
Kiara and Ina like those are amazing and
also okay uh I'm really happy because I
could actually uh gather and play with
all of you guys here yeah yes like I'd
appreciate it more more more
collabs like this so if you guys are
planning to do so
I I'd love to add but I would be happy
to participate oh yes
so much I love you
[Music]
I love you too okay
well first uh I'd like to apologize
or if I was salty if I curse that you
guys oh no yeah
[Music]
uh and uh yeah thank you Kiara and and
Inna you guys work really hard thank you
guys and thank you everybody for
participating it was really fun I know
it's hard to organize these types of
collabs everybody's so busy and
different schedules thank you and I had
a lot of fun thank you thank you
you know now that we have um now that we
have whole Council we can like we don't
have to relay on these exact 12 members
anymore so next time if you want you can
do shout casting
thank you thank you everyone for
participating today
um I hope I hope everyone had a great
time even if you know maybe you were not
number one number two number three
that's fine I think today was really
just about getting together putting um
two communities to Fan communities of
hello Ian and hello ID together and just
feeling United definitely and I I'm
always glad to do stuff like this again
so I would gladly invite you guys again
whenever you have time for it and want
to join and I'm sorry that you know
because since it's such an international
collaboration
um it's not going to be an ideal time
for everyone so I'm so sorry for the
girls who had to wake up at like six
seven a.m or something like that I'm so
sorry I know it's tough it's no problem
it was fun
I just wish my parents could watch the
news
okay I hope your mom enjoyed the
tournament I think she did I think
[Laughter]
well well then with that I would like to
officially close to hollow Ian Holo ID
Mario Kart tournament everyone take care
of your golden yagos to polish him every
day he wants to be shiny and sparkly and
yeah I'll see you guys soon thank you
everyone
[Music]
hi everyone