foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
oh my God oh my oh my God
we're wearing headphones and our ears
are broken now yay
[Music]
um
yeah you were sniffing me all the time
yeah like a dog I'm a dog
oh no more like a cat I think cats sniff
more dogs lick I hate cats
really
what
you're a dog or a cat I'm a dog why
can't no gun oh yeah Lena told me if I
want to say you little [\h__\h] I have to
say yeah
oh my God
good job Rainey I'm sorry it's okay oh
my God my ear okay
muna's career is over because she lost
her hearing yeah no more it's okay
well then what are we doing now
well we're gonna play this game but
before
our sweet Ollie brought some turret cups
[Music]
she offered to read my everything
and my my maybe my present tense oh my
God
is he already read Muna it was so funny
was also upside down my God believe it
or not even though she mixed it yeah it
was happening you want to put a circle
so there's no way there's no chance
foreign
[Music]
s it means that wait
um it has something with changes but I
forgot oh but uh I I feel like there
will be a new one and you will be taken
into high and newer heights yeah
you will change you change New Heights
laughs
I just I just showed something
do you understand
huh
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
you changing into butterflies yeah I
thought so tell us like wait she's going
to die
there's something something incoming oh
I'm probably gonna change
[Music]
you didn't tell me
why should I tell you
[Music]
yourself cards what would you like me to
read
um
okay first of all how about a general
Overlook of my 2023 okay pick a card 20.
20 20 23.
this year okay okay
oh God am I gonna die
um for this 2023 this card advises you
to rest a little bit more it's okay to
take one more time no
you don't need to force yourself
is as the card indicates uh if we don't
risk now you might dress forever
it doesn't matter I'm a phoenix okay
it's okay it's okay can I take a second
card
[Music]
I'll sit down
but upside down so basically if you keep
pushing yourself if you're trying to go
uh if you're trying trying to get as
many jobs or doing so many stuffs all at
the same time you might go downwards
instead of upwards
oh
I mean that's why you need to rest
will it change what they said it might
give you a solution okay solution
Solutions
oh yeah so the the solution is
um marry a king no no no no you just
have to be careful with your your
financials you can uh you can always go
back to your financials if anything no
yeah yeah so like maybe if we ever do
get sick
um you have insurance
it's a very shitty insurance but yes
yeah maybe you want to look back into
the insurance they might help you who
knows if anything just in case
[Music]
I need I need to find the love of my
life oh no no when it happens when is it
gonna happen
um not soon
because you know actually this card um
eight of Wands it symbolizes movement
and about being fast if it's upside down
then yeah no well okay well wonderful
good for my job
okay
you asked me you don't need love I mean
oh man I'm your love
if you want to know what your uh Future
Love
um
uh do you want to know what your um
significant other will be like yeah yeah
you can tell me that yeah
let's see
this one
it's upside down again
no it might not be um I I guess you
could say that they're kind of a Sunday
area they're not very good they're not
very good at saying uh what they're
feeling like they're not good at
conveying their emotions
oh my god well maybe that means um
yeah
I mean that was my uh sounds like you
[Music]
I'm getting back together with your dad
think of it oh yeah
[Music]
good for you yeah another for the child
yeah
that makes sense
[Music]
you have to bring it back yeah sure
Lego
I got a boyfriend
okay please good boyfriend yeah
hopefully I have to check if he's good
good enough
like this one like this it depends it
depends you pulled it out like this so
maybe like this like this okay one two
three
oh wow it's it's the same card so um
someone who is actually financially
ready that's what your boyfriend will be
like
so I can spend many money
um I guess he's the type that will treat
you yes his love language is definitely
material
okay that's my that's what my boyfriend
looks like right it's like not looks
like yeah it's like okay okay where when
when will they meet where yeah
next card okay I feel something hot here
oh something hot okay
what is this
um High Priestess it kind of
um
I wonder because
um it kind of high priestess I would
usually associate with like say sonus so
maybe when you're a little bit more say
so
[Music]
the more say so I am the the quickly the
boyfriend will come yes maybe the guy is
looking for say so lady um
a long time right
now guys oh my God you you don't believe
me I'm I'm kind of religious people you
know you know we should start playing
Nintendo
[Applause]
cheers
I think what what it means is more about
you being a little [\h__\h]
you need to be a as a good child yeah
yeah also to Mommy right more more
respectful to Mommy yeah
and to me
yeah and me too
okay no okay yes yes okay then how can
we play this ah so I'll play four people
okay one two three four three
oh also by the way when we're done
playing there's one more surprise ride
that we're gonna do yeah exciting the
ladies have prepared something for me to
eat yes and I'm only partially excited
for it I can't blame that wait should I
link that no you don't need to just
press OK I think okay
[Music]
actually they've brought a lot of food
but there's something very special
yeah game audio too loud
is it somebody said gay Mario to them no
by now it all started with the green I
forgot to turn on Superstar maybe even
all forgot about it but that's okay it's
been such a long time after all
travel through this pipe and that
Journey began oh it's it's vibrating oh
it's vibrating
is this all these sweaty the Super
Chicken
where's everybody it's almost time
and we're here hello look at us we're
here such a long time
the Koopa troopa's a little nervous
but this is the opening
first I want to thank you all for
assembling here
I want to thank you
okay
I love this experience life cover
[Music]
I'm glad you're enjoying the experience
still off
really super chats off thank you once
it's on give us Reds
red guys
this is my first time
[Music]
what a surprise seeing you here
oh no no this one okay no
okay it's yellow
thank you then I have to fix myself
just choose a random one
what I had to fix myself okay okay
[Music]
oh my God
I was so happy when I was like um oh you
know I was like just humming Moon night
[Music]
yeah I'mma keep up to people
K-pop
like I thought you were singing the uh
the jyp19
[Applause]
please let me in
you guys know all the songs I'm so happy
we've been vibing to uh new jeans before
the stream yeah and dancing
oh my God that dance move is like it
looks like an old guy like
pants
why okay how about you
I'm gonna make a new room I guess okay
you are me bye bye
okay this is
okay oh you set the password loud
I mean nobody got Jordan
the password is two to two guys
[Music]
I am inside
wow are you guys so big
[Music]
only one did you sniff Muna she's almost
good
[Music]
I'm joking I did take a shower
oh
yeah again is this like a Indonesian
culture because Kobo also keeps no it's
only Ollie no coin only yeah
obodium
all these sniffing what does it smell
like she smells like shampoo oh
hmm no did you wash your hair I washed
my hair last night I see is this one
okay and that should be maybe make me a
little bit bigger
this one yeah okay all right okay okay
yeah all right guys sorry guys why am I
so tall
just a little bit
okay okay we have the same high but I
feel like you're taller than me
and wow we're back okay do you know how
to play yes yes yes
[Music]
oh
very nice
because it's purple because he's purple
yeah
nice it's just like it looks like I'm
Italian guy oh
uh which one should we play anyone
anybody who's that's something most
difficult no okay
the only one I have never played before
is the horror land I think ah the most
difficult okay
can you sitting it for me okay
but
um maybe do 15 turns because we can't do
so hold on I'm Stars yes
[Music]
my skin is more yellow than yours all
types
[Music]
yeah and more pinkish pinkish
couple nice nails my hair is a little
bit bigger
than you I have the biggest one is that
something to flex wait flex but okay
oh
that's what made it this is horrible
I should have done my nails I should
have gotten my nails done so I can look
filter for the ID Girls
no no I have a nail extension if you
want it's just fake nails you mean the
fake nails these fake nails no that's
okay it's okay I don't need I will make
everyone look at my eyes and yeah
beautiful eyes you can't stop staring
but it's true
it's my real life
I think it's a soft lamp
wow
oh
no what was that mean yeah
the biggest number go first oh only you
should with the terror cards tell us who
wins who will win oh my God
um we'll see maybe the third can uh oops
sorry what kind of person will win I
can't really spell out the name okay
something blue no it means that someone
with the the worst luck in the game
might just win oh so someone who like
first does pretty bad and then later on
they will surprise us most probably oh
okay
well that that happens quite often in
Mario Party
last time I played Mario party I won for
the first time in my life so wow
it's kind of like Monopoly so basically
you have to get to the store yeah but to
get when you get to the star you need to
have 20 coins to buy it the one with the
most Star wins oh okay so the objective
is the star yes all right okay you never
played it before this is her first time
nice she's using my uh my the the game
that I brought what is Warden Ward means
you can look around well dice block
means that you're just going to go
[Music]
you're on the bottom right I think
uh you can't see because of the stickers
oh yeah yeah we will you have to
probably go this way and then maybe this
way but the directions can change I
think I agree okay right now I'm just
trying to get uh wait a good dice number
what what should I do with this no no no
no you'll know when you get there yes
quick quick four four three two one play
dice hey hey
[Music]
yeah so you're pretty close ah and then
let's see which one's closer yeah number
22 so eight yeah
what was that for it's very good that we
have a newcomer here so I I think I'll
I'll win again soon
the thing is you really don't have much
money right now so you should probably
first focus on getting money that's for
real I'm not trying to deceive you see
here we go
[Music]
after every round after everyone went we
play a game together or against each
other or one versus three or two versus
two yeah mini game
[Music]
received 10
10. oh man again
we should not get skewered okay okay so
you gotta protect ourselves okay
I mean it's not the worst one for solo
but it's still difficult
okay I'm good
okay yes that when this is just a
practice Press Start
plus and then we could go okay I wish we
luck wait
huh
[Music]
oh
hey
yeah because I missed one person
I need to stick together one wins
everybody wins yes
[Music]
gaming girl
why are you going so far you got it but
do you have you have
[Music]
any things you could have totally said
no thanks yeah why
right
the first star and now okay next one is
not so far away
yeah I guess you have to go that way but
now no you have to actually go around
okay but you need the key
[Music]
it's okay
I'm not going anywhere
[Music]
I'm just waiting for a new star position
it's so sad
oh wait where am I you're still close to
me don't run away from mommy don't leave
mommy behind me behind my mom
this is very competitive
skeleton key yes
good job she's investing
and I feel like the keys are most of the
time not not so helpful but we'll see
though it's okay
minions
[Music]
I remember this one yeah we just need to
get here oh she needs to
she needs to go to that area but we have
to stop her I'm ready
I practice this with aniki a lot oh okay
start start start
ah well now you have to press the plus
we need the ball yeah we need to capture
Cobble oh
foreign
[Music]
the stars because I'm not 48 that's so
far what's so far oh we have to go like
around yeah yeah
see
now you have no money that's why you
should have said nobody exactly I'm
going here okay
buy something nice
um
go down to zero really yeah she is
really well damn yeah it's like you're
playing Monopoly what is this
items I think oh oh all right or that
okay can we finally get going Daisy
please
[Music]
I need to go far
Tom
57 no for two bye
ha ha ha ha
ha ha ha ha ha ha ha I'm getting the
money
[Music]
from me yeah
if you land on the field you get the
money but if you only go buy you give
them money I think if you walk by if you
don't land exactly on it I think
uh item
can you guys teach me some Indonesian
some important Indonesian something
something important Translate
what word do you want to learn yeah what
do you think is important for me okay so
uh let's say that uh Kobe is being very
cute
you want to say
oh
yesterday yesterday yeah I learned what
was it uh
what because
no the other one
which one the other one yeah
[Music]
her face is like
I'm thinking about this
where can I get pass like you can get
past I have the key oh you can only get
uh get to the place when when it's night
time I believe you can do go at three
times
[Music]
wait can you circle around I can't I can
yes yes
oh thank you
oh now he stands on does he stay on the
other side yeah
I need more Indonesian
um
[Music]
what's that mean beautiful yeah you're
beautiful
yeah thank you
oh I know the words
kitty kitty kitty whenever whenever you
saw some uh someone who doesn't have a
money
they don't have money I'll go get it
yeah
let's go what's this oh all versus
everybody ah it's this case you turn and
you turn and then you shoot it's not
that wait what is
yeah this is really difficult actually
to aim
we're not aiming it's automatically oh
it's
oh we just like press a um
and the right timing on the right timing
okay
don't shoot me
no you play valorant
[Music]
oh
it's not reacting it's
saying
we're playing offline
[Music]
two times now
um
Mommy
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
my God
[Applause]
it's not your mom but I'm present is
okay don't fight am I ready for Apex yet
wow wow but I saw you were like doing
all kinds of crazy games and in Apex
right but this is the car the Mario Kart
what yeah yeah that was actually a
really fun
[Music]
I'm gonna do another one one day
next time maybe I can join
[Music]
no no if it's like these kind of like
random games and not shooting then I
think I can join
yes crazy okay
I only got two
okay
[Music]
double dice
double right eight and oh and I can go
really fast
okay I need to go this way anyway nice
[Music]
no thank you
well I can't go for here unless I pay
but I want to save money anyways
[Music]
eyeball
what does it says
I will just yeah how many wow wait can
you get my dog no
it's what does it say well you'll have
to pay to find out no
and warn me where work me to the star
I'm so close to the star anyway I can't
see
[Music]
Press B Press B Ollie no okay
me
make her crispy surprise me
[Music]
with her face
okay I'll give one second B
yes
what
then no thanks okay fine yes well that's
too bad that's too bad I didn't wanna I
couldn't have gone there anyway what do
you want now welcome to Mr Mansion do
you wish to light the darkness me what
the [\h__\h] that
um
day five to light what was that what's
that do I think I think it went at night
it will help you really maybe maybe you
should invest Maybe
I mean no that guy looks promising
look at his face
and now you get rid of it Ollie
what is this I always mess this one up
can we for once not mess it up raise
hammer
oh but this is the one where I can
decide which number
I'm not bad okay
at least I didn't get the little
companion the custom guys
[Music]
let me check the warp so I'm gonna where
are you can I can go here how many do
you need you have no money yeah I hope I
hope I get money in the middle of the
road
you are shot on one coin
okay
I think it's enough
[Music]
let me go there I'm not you need money
right now anyway so just a little bit
it's actually uh you can actually if I
remember correctly if you go to boo we
can steal some Stars oh
that's another way to get a star really
maybe cheaper how much does it cost I
think it was 30 to steal a star really
oh no it's it's not nice
it's too risky oh don't unlock sorry
for now bye bye
please I need money please give me coins
[Music]
I'm
I have quite a lot
wait I was in Brush 30 yeah coins now
you got the dumbbell
just in case we never know what's going
to happen
all is out to get us hmm yeah I thought
she was nice I mean she wants to take
all of our hopes yeah
I I I read your carrot first yeah first
you give us hopes and dreams with your
tarot cards and now you want to take
them away
[Music]
another mini game mini game oh
boy
I'm sorry I think they called Sun Moon
Sun Moon they call it
oh
I'll go okay okay
it's real teamwork oh my God that looks
good job
okay okay let's go let's go let's go
let's go
easy yeah easy easy
foreign
wait why does it
oh
no
[Music]
only one
let's go we had a communication issues
you know
um
27 oh
I think you should like uh gather money
first rather than going for the star
because you're too far anyway
and you don't have the money yet so
please give me money
anything money please stop stop oh wait
yeah me too press eight
[Music]
you're here
what's that for only small numbers we
can only get one two three one two one
Brew free
one two three one one three three yes
but you know you shouldn't be the one
trying to correct me you're the one with
mine
she knows her
hahaha
she knows her I saw the Tweet yes ma'am
sorry man
um
I'm 14 away
13. somebody else I think is closer than
me oh wow wow
I mean I was saving up
okay no she has money
everybody Champs with me
[Music]
come on
let's go
[Music]
I got the Stars I got the [\h__\h] star
let's go
[Music]
do you know what tattoo means no one
now you have subtle star
[Music]
sorry sorry
[Applause]
oh oh it's so close but I think can't go
from that side
ah damn I'm so far away you have the Tom
Bell and the charm call
you gotta pay up uh
um
slides
[Music]
yeah double dice is nice
double dice is nice that rhymes
kiwama come back when if I ever gonna
have a bath
you will a custom nice block yo but you
have to throw away the kids okay I have
double key oh yeah
why
if you're 40 and what ah you're gonna
move in it's way too far for any of us
okay thank you I don't think I could
have gone there either
bye-bye maybe same position as before it
would be nice yeah that'd be
um
no I don't have any money
okay okay I don't have enough money oh
so what is this now uh it didn't come
out
because I think it's night oh he only
comes out at daytime yeah to change the
night yeah yeah
um
it's
one of my favorite
cute
yeah okay easy easy okay I'm ready I'm
ready
it's supposedly easy you have to be fast
and accurate
not apex not everything
how can I be a great
oh that Circle was hard yeah this circle
some of the circles that are interesting
okay I don't know how good was that I
couldn't look at the other me too
I don't know
oh oh
yeah
what's the worst who is the worst I am
how much percent did you have wait I'm
gonna go I think was it 18 I think it
would say
what 60 right wow okay it's your first
time yes
um
yeah yeah good for you
who was trying to tickle me or so no I'm
just starting touching
38 what's the underside 50 oh dear
health is pretty bad can we have another
whistle
Luna was really close to the store I
just known
I'm 29.
okay
well for now I'm chilling thanks for the
nine I don't have enough coins so I just
like going
um
[Music]
it's going well
okay
[Music]
maybe I should upgrade my flight back to
business Clause
no just kidding that's too expensive but
yeah it does it's crazy it's so premium
economy I think is understandable but
business never never never business
oh
it's crazy
I'm in the game again
[Music]
we're playing
um
oh no oh no whoever gets it first is
like overpowered and has to kill
everybody else wait can I try again oh
so so you have to survive basically if
anyone gets too much room like me do you
have killed yeah and end up punching ah
you can like stand up
I'm gonna ground pound Kiara
I'm not gonna win this one okay let's go
ready me too it's okay I will get it
[Music]
wasn't by survive wanna take her down
I'm a big girl yes yes you are I'm a
bigger it's ironic because you're
actually the smallest out of a sponge at
least I have money now
at least I have funny I can buy Stars I
can buy two stars if I'm lucky yeah
whatever it is
48 to the star there's someone when I
use maybe the the nobody has the Bell
right now by the car uh yeah nobody gets
the Bell what is that
what does it do how does it help if you
go if you give money to like Boo he'll
do you favor he can like steal money or
he can like steal stars for you I think
I mean I don't mind
[Music]
let's do it
yay
okay you've got to look she used lucky
yeah
still afraid I'll steal money for free
okay
oh
um you know you know who's that
[Applause]
foreign
money owner
[Music]
wow eleven that's
oh okay that's a good amount I'm not
paying for a lunch today
he's just borrowing and fighting you're
giving it back eventually surely
just renting some money
first
[Music]
yes
I'm getting closer deposit first no
[Music]
no yes
yes
wait is that thank you for your
cooperation and it says it's a Koopa
saying it's cooperation
you said that so nicely oh okay okay
you know I have the
oh can you get it I I'm busy getting one
star here
seven to
do this yes bye bye
wait why did you not use the custom one
yeah because oh it's enough okay wow if
it's not enough no I was getting so
so close yes yes no
thanks bye bye
lucky day thank you
[Applause]
Stars
[Music]
pay pay 50 coins
this star is for you later
not really
wait who's the closest this is the
closest oh God it's so far I should have
bought the chomp chomp Bell
why did I not buy it
useless
pain Phoenix
sad twerking
how good are you twerking oh not not
good at all
do you want to see me tour and I think
you're twerking it's gonna be really
fast oh my goal is going to work for us
I can't work
[Laughter]
[Music]
no that was not twerking
guys imagine just imagine imagine you
know really bad I'm dead working what is
this just trying to stay on there yeah
all right flurry easy easy
you can jump on others I see yeah
[Applause]
so lucky today
because I have a bad breakfast of the
time
let me enjoy this lucky time
the bad luck one oh so today I'm in bad
luck maybe next time next time I think
you're luckyness goes to me oh I think
she's just lucky because she works
if you want to see me twerking what is
then maybe watch my 3D reviews next week
on Saturday
will we actually do it though
I can attempt if I remember
but did you did you see it
yeah the post that you made her do that
from each of us huh
I swear to God I swear I just got my
mind
the mini oh we're fighting for the money
yeah we're fighting for the if I don't
win I'm gonna be so mad cause you took
so much money oh I was good at this when
I was a child
okay okay I'm ready okay I'm ready I'm
ready wait wait wait wait I want to try
it
fine fine fine fine I want to try it one
more time
on fire that makes sense I'm pretty hot
enough
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
[Music]
I'm gonna be silent same
oh my ass is so hot
it's getting faster
hey
hey hey hey
come on
[Applause]
I will not give up
ah
everybody
[Music]
it's down to two
it could be anyone's game everybody
jumping up and down Daisy and Rosalina
on the line on the Fireland if not
they're going for a 70 jump
almost almost as they nearly got it
oh getting close
I'm getting tired but they have the same
amount of Rhythm this is what you call
an idol everybody
[Laughter]
[Music]
let's go okay
hands in the middle we're going to beat
Google me no not you
okay come on
you're so [\h__\h] mad
[Applause]
[Laughter]
you're mad
[Music]
Onna and last minute
oh no
hold on I beat everyone I'm with
everyone everyone and Mom you gotta be
careful
I need my mom my mom she said
she she she's fuming with anger she is
looking at you with pure pure Fury
oh my God
would you like me to order you some food
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no it's about
because of the bounce face
what the [\h__\h] is that what is that
what's this
you dropped something
okay okay okay what does that do it
is it yours no what is this is that a
cake
what a mysterious thing fell off
that that's not mine oh well anyway
anyway
oh yes oh yes but I wish it was cool
come on
how's everybody like this
wow big amount of points no I'm poor
oh what the [\h__\h]
money bounce
yay oh I love this one
we get money
oh well well usually I'll grab as money
money yes we can okay
[Music]
my only position isn't so difficult up
there it's not so bad but we're a team
mom we're Team okay unfortunately
unfortunately she's
I'm back that was fast fast came on
Delivery Express
yeah
I need it
move it
okay okay
don't die don't die okay at least you
got a coin when dying
oh can you dash it
but it's again it's a win for everyone
but we have to share I think we still oh
no we got the oh
wow look at my coins
mommy look at my coins I'm a red shirt
okay so Kirsten bite
follow me
[Laughter]
shut up before I slap you
what is this
[Music]
um
events
day wow just it's so fitting to Uno yeah
yeah
[Music]
um
it's okay it's okay it's okay it's okay
are they finally gonna start selling the
good stuff now
um
wow triple dies
that is cool if someone's close to the
to the star
I can swish sweet sweet
Christmas so this is your name okay
but they're still not selling the tube
the golden tube don't they normally have
a golden field yeah yeah they they had
that before so basically you get
teleported nearby the star
let's see
oh all the way
do we have the money yes you do
let's go let's go let's go let's go
please not to Cobble okay okay okay okay
I think
is Luna somebody closest ah no I'm not
I'm I'm the floor just now you have it's
actually beneficial for Kobo
mother instinct versus competitiveness
well well well
triple dice pretty damn I mean you have
the money so like you don't even need to
think yeah literally if the money and
the Stars you have everything literally
you're gonna go that way huh huh You're
Gonna face you back to your mommy and
say
I'm gonna go different way I'm departing
from home now goodbye I'm ready to leave
mommy is right there meet up with her
yeah
well are you going to Mommy or are you
going to the store
that's reasonable
[Music]
um
what's is
wkwkwks are laughing yeah yes
Indonesian love like
oh no we're not cute like that yeah
crazy cutters
[Music]
will lose again yeah I'm probably gonna
lose again what about the chain we don't
have to trace the chain I don't think so
the mouth is actually very difficult
I know how to get around this mouth
because I know yeah
oh wait Holly disappeared
that's okay we can do that
[Music]
I pressed something
I also missed press I was gonna
it's okay Mommy
[Music]
wow
totally is the winner now Holly will
come back okay come back
[Music]
Ollie wasn't even there
she gave the control of someone else
let's make a new room again
[Music]
wow wow
oh my gosh
[Music]
I have joined online foreign
mommy mommy
she's on the different Road mom mom
what's up
[Music]
oh come on
she was making hearts pose hard pose
this is not fair pretty privilege is a
thing
it's my child it's not natural
ah we have twin tails
also how a small ball on my Twitter
and you have big balls on YouTube
and our OBS look similar no
[Music]
they don't no but at the time
[Applause]
look did you guys notice I didn't know
this until now that we both have like
twin tails that come out of balls yeah
yeah I I didn't notice the small Kiara
small box
[Music]
and you have flour and I have some
glasses
why did I just get bad don't worry I
feel you 47 to the
do this
wait so who is uh oh who's uh who's
close
uh you know you know who's close you
know who's closer is the closest one you
know you can change it you know you
can't change it you gotta change it how
far is she really oh oh yeah
yeah Warp you can watch her thank you
maybe I will can I still move after that
yeah yeah yeah
but wait with their random opponent come
on it's because you decided to leave
your parents house hey oh it's random
oh it's random oh 24 is so better than
before isn't it all right because I
think before it was 43 I went up
I'm still better than before I think
it's better behind the wheel here
okay okay somebody has to stop Kobo
though somebody stop you can buy the one
again if you can
China
[Music]
wow
custom dice block though okay how far
are you away
or whatever number you want from one to
two wait is it random or not whatever
you want it's not random it's custom you
can choose
you guys
I'm sorry this is gonna be a lie
it's a custom
is it customized vlog
or you know you might end up like you're
a senpai
it might be random we don't know
well I only only need to move nine
blocks right so
I think both is fine then do the triple
dice yeah
whoa
oh [\h__\h]
bye goodbye you could have gone with the
custom one by the way you can choose the
number
so that's why you can like steal star
you can steal munas and by star remember
19. I'm not that mean I thought you need
nine to the start not 19. I'm not that
mean it's okay
oh
no it's okay
it's okay
um
[Music]
no a charm call yes
let's go
popular you have to steal the Stars we
have five turns left we have to steal
the Stars okay so uh we just need to
gather all 50 coins from each of us and
we can get like all three stars okay
yeah yeah
Stars I have yeah yeah we're going to
steal from you yeah
don't you guys just can steal one star
no don't star each
don't start each I still once time we're
not still one star only still one star
yeah we can do that
that's what happens when you're too
successful yeah people want to bring it
down
training you for the real world so you
understand what's coming to you oh good
at this game it's not fair it's
basically bringing her back to the next
spot where the stars where's the next
star
I hope you get both no no no please
got it oh you got so lucky
I don't know let's let me enjoy
I don't think I need this
[Music]
he's no lucky lucky actually means a
male yeah
Indonesian yeah oh I'm lucky lucky we're
just lucky lucky and lucky can be yeah
yeah
can be both where are you going
where are you going I'm going to get my
scarf I'm gonna be a star star
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah
what is this we never made it game
another meaning game
this one is actually really cute so you
have to give it to him
and there's like love letters
oh it's cute thank you
will get to Love Letter yeah you believe
it okay press pause
all together
oh that guy come on okay
oh no this reminds me of a idols
[Music]
okay we're in my way why
I didn't get the love letter
yes
[Music]
okay we need we need to really only go
on low battery again oh no yeah bye oh
we don't have time
um I should have no worry maybe we can
finish this hopefully goodbye bye one
one one give a battery
we're going to the last five turns oh
okay and they're gonna like say who who
they think they uh is gonna win yes and
give some extra help I think why do we
have to prove fresh okay
okay second place follow easy
press
okay
what uh
then last place
[Music]
oh this this person
they think Bruno's gonna win
hello thank you
let's go for 40 cents oh it breaks you
to the goddamn start
oh that thing exists
[Music]
my mom
and it kind of it helps because it
actually yeah you're still gonna have a
star all right no but so do you yeah I
thought you had a star by now I really
have a shading one due to dice
nice
to the start
stop
three oh come on what kind of star is
that oh it's right there oh it's right
there
I'm gonna play safe now
I don't want
uh to mess up here so uh where's the
free
Orton I mean I don't have to land
exactly on it right right yeah
and right really really
um
[Music]
let's go yeah
we want the steel room 10 jobs
[Music]
next is dimana
dimana
[Music]
oh who's close well he's always gonna
get it anyway it's okay
this one I don't know no no no I already
wrapped I don't know I don't know what's
with this yeah oh come on British accent
please could you give me some British
accent Miss Kobo
um of course
how are you doing tonight my lovely Miss
Koba
um I didn't tonight ah yeah tonight I
would be oh how you doing I will be
doing
good good
you're doing good see
see
[Laughter]
oh oh anyway uh
everybody has to get five coins
okay
actually it didn't sound so bad Google
it's funny hearing it from you thank you
I learned much from wingardium levios
uh 15 dark um
[Music]
I swear but yeah somebody's somebody's
probably even gonna use the tube the
golden pipe or the Trump calls
I don't think this is helping me
um
[Music]
you can go to the store right in front
of it
um
[Music]
you know you're saying that if you're
poor then you can you cannot be like a
superstar
[Laughter]
well you know money certainly helps you
know but even without money you just
need lots and lots and lots of luck but
whatever
oh it's close with mine now oh no okay
okay
you can't go left right yeah
but not now oh
huh
[Music]
game
oh we have to get to the Target yeah
it's only only is shooting the balls
taking the balls no oh okay yeah we can
play this wait let him oh we need to we
need to go up
yeah we need to go up I think when we
reach the top then we win
oh [\h__\h]
okay okay
let's split up
yeah split up
stay in the middle
[Music]
[Applause]
for what
sticker
[Music]
first
[Laughter]
call me when you're first in Apex
tournament
and we'll talk she actually did one best
zombie I thought she was second oh and
first place
at everything
I know you're from Europe but damn you
got that Asian yeah
trying to you know embody the Asian
parents
[Music]
who will win Senpai okay you want the
wagon one coin yes
yes okay I'm ready I'm ready I'm ready
I want to play too I'm rooting for Muna
why not me
spikes never mind then
[Music]
what was that why were you hesitating
you're a beat oh Birdo is so close
right now
[Music]
[Laughter]
so you get two coins that's it
nice yeah was that really necessary
[Music]
thanks for the two coins
because I've doubled now okay 47
no I only have triple uh yeah triple and
double but that's still not enough so
um
I I don't think I can do anything so I
just want me do you please have a golden
tube please thank you you still don't
sell the golden tube what can we buy
food into
yeah I saw it before in shops you could
buy the golden tube yeah those are like
in the earlier games wasn't it really
yeah it was in the DS one
[Music]
where am I
oh you're behind me
[Music]
don't do anything weird
all I can do are you going to jump off
is it the remix
[Music]
time to
lose
[Music]
we all like new jeans we should do some
cover of new jeans I would love
um
[Music]
it's not that far but interfere okay
okay it's right in front of me it's
right in front of you both
what
this is what we called lucky yeah yeah
boy I'm leaving Indonesia right now
right now
[Music]
oh yeah follow me follow me and
uh
I'm saying you won't let me leave yeah
yeah
the sacred food okay lunch afterward
okay noodles
yes sorry it's okay I'll go so I'm
hungry oh
why is this okay oh
move just move okay
yeah okay okay
ready ready our money is gonna be like
collected together right and then split
um
so that we don't get it I don't think so
classical
[Music]
is this is this how we do it I don't
know
thank you where's the big money bags
why is that moving like like it's not
moving yeah I played this before as the
Bowser Rose
[Music]
thank you
ID members
thank you for your spontaneously
accepting my request to come to Muno
place and Muna thank you for hosting but
sadly you're just here only for a short
time short time but I'll come back
yes but when but when maybe this year
really
what I can do I wanted to go to the Bali
you know all right with with um
[Music]
yeah yeah I guess that's uh what's
happening we're doing a trip application
maybe I can also uh
uh uh check out again here
before I go to Bali yeah yeah
go to our houses yes yeah yeah only
house is very we're kind of close to the
beginning
and they have a really big space wait
did I just I teleported like two meters
yeah I I handed it oh but me
Runner
if the game
[Music]
we're almost at the end of this game
though so two more turns yeah
we still have a chance to steal Stars
maybe or maybe but you kind of need to
have the key to steal Stars too yeah
oh because because it's a lock the area
no but then we also get stars in the end
for winning the most games and going on
the most whatever Fields so never give
up it's not looking so bad oh sorry it's
okay I'm gonna break from us
um
you
come here come here
come near me come near me no no come
here no no where is it not that far yeah
well
good job
um nicer
[Music]
it's 17. it's pretty good for you yeah
go up go up go up bye
wouldn't jump no no because maybe it
wasn't the other Mario Party game
there's another one for a switch maybe
it was there uh you mean the Super Mario
um I brought it with me too oh I brought
quite a lot of games yes what but it
sucks anyway because once they start
selling the the tubes everybody buys
them and everybody every turn uses the
stupid tubes
I'm hungry
[Music]
what's that mean depression
um
[Music]
wait do you like durian well we'll find
out about that that's the thing oh this
one we have to work together oh okay
okay okay you have to make the white uh
light yeah yeah like that like that
so it just drive us to follow why
okay ready okay I'm ready I'm ready I'm
ready
oh no where's she where is she where is
she where is she no yo yo yo
oh yeah wait which one am I I'm green oh
[\h__\h] I thought it was red
[\h__\h]
oh
okay
it's all good it's okay Luna in jail
what's your crying
by the way Mommy thank you for visiting
me in jail
yeah you shouldn't have been in jail in
the first place because I'm saying it
was not your fault right I don't know
it's Daddy's fault no no no no no no not
necessarily yeah let's stay away from
this family okay it's kind of scary and
the kid's been in jail before I'm free
now I'm free now yeah but you know what
we are gonna sue the jail let's do the
jail
Subaru jail yes right objection
objections
here
all authority
[Music]
she never she
told me to come to ultra police
[Music]
what happened
it's for uh
um
Justice this is foreign
[Music]
can we turn this around will will
Ollie's uh tarot card reading I am true
oh Mom
you wanna fight let's fight
who are you betting on
put it put in 50 or 30 30. yeah
it's okay I'm ready to reach 30 okay
okay
it really depends on the game that we
get
um okay you can sabotage
you know right
now
oh this one it's a good job
[Music]
come on [\h__\h]
well that wasn't quite a match
[Music]
I got 60 coins
let's go
30 seconds
nine oh look at oh I don't know
I don't want to suffer anymore
well well well
just end it yeah take all my coins
and the other jumping game I was good
but this one though
again
and she get the Stars
I'm not even gonna say anything no
comment I have no commented we're loose
anyway
Carson bites bestie let it go if not
it'll eat you alive yeah you'll get used
to it
yeah that's Mark right there
this game is rigged how do I say it in
Indonesian
turn on
oh
you little
oh nice apparently
I think it's free from squares
[Laughter]
so exhausted
because on your next one the cost of
your next star is healthier
all right The Skeleton Key
but the thing is I can't get to the star
I only have three steps I'm literally
one step away from the start oh yeah so
please don't move it I screamed so much
my friends
okay we're almost done
oh no
Facebook
oh my God
easy is it like this
here we go okay
[Music]
okay we messed up I I messed up
oh
sense of rhythm
[Music]
my new career has been decided after her
life this is what I'll be doing
just give me a star game please maybe I
get mini games die final turn
final turn
five star
s
[Music]
I'm so close
please
one favor for me be nice to me no okay
well uh where is it where is it
to me I think
do you really need another star how many
Star do we need to win
[Music]
no I don't have anymore
oh I'm right here oh
I'm sorry
wow nice
[Music]
so now it's 23 I have a triple in fear
right with my triple I could get to the
star yeah okay but I will probably get
really bad luck again intro I'll try you
can go tan tan tan okay doesn't even
have to be 10 to 10. I'm not even asking
for so much
close your eyes close your eyes close
your eyes mommy close your eyes
close your eyes no this is already lost
because even if I got 10 10 that's 21.
oh you're right okay Don't Close Your
Eyes
wow
it's a big big number no 12.
sometimes
mom mom
she's dead inside well see you you
you're just in front of me wow you're
you're ahead wow
damn
cheers
it's okay it's the last turn she's
having a mental breakdown everyone
and I cannot describe it to you just how
bad she's having it right now yeah
because it's like adapted heart
game
love is just a game
she's winning against to get a star
again
did you get us out again
I can't believe I say this
is
laughs
no my stars
oh my God
[Laughter]
oh my console oh now I can't think
of what should we do come on
do payback for me now
um
you stood up and ran away uh but if you
would have kept the control you could
have said no and then still take the
start because they asked like three
times
oh really yeah
[\h__\h] everyone
I'm pretty good at this
I'm gonna change myself though sorry
okay
are you two okay
well you guys are probably not okay you
guys need therapy
baby the real stars are the friends we
made along the way
it's not fair and square it's fair and
circle was that Lena he's talking to you
okay
for a screen Circle
you're gonna start for what
Luigi
[Music]
oh all right
um do I get something too can I get
something oh that's it that's it thank
you and the winner is okay
oh no
you know oh no you know
I'm gonna lose
yeah we got like literally by the way
I'm out of the room oh yeah you need to
make yeah can you try joining again
yeah you know
you know it's a superstar
congratulations
you didn't even need to add extra star
at the end
yeah but yeah you know just more flowers
or more Flags the parser tastes okay
okay we're back to two yeah we're back
[Music]
well now that we're done with this bring
in the good stuff
I will bring you a food called
have you already bought it what's your
name yeah I bought it oh okay what's it
it's uh how to say it
we have a lot of food now we have the
Korean pancakes but we also have actual
Dory I wonder
I know I'll probably won't like it but
instead if it's at the end of the stream
then even if I throw up it won't be so
bad let's move on your free talk overlay
is this a durian durian this is the
durian durian this is
up into the cup okay
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
we are so big oh I mean yeah if it's
frozen it's okay it it likes ice cream
ice cream yeah so okay pancake Outside
Inside is
wait a minute yes yes okay and okay
prepare to you know the same really I
thought I was so the pancakes are not so
bad like it's not too bad not bad but
okay she opened it I'm scared to breathe
breathe
it's not that bad sniff
it's not that bad how's it pancake
actually for us it's it's uh really you
know it's really if you don't want to
make your we can use this one
ah because it will be on my hands the
smell yeah oh well okay yes that's a
good idea
okay gloves
okay it's when I when I purposefully try
to smell it a little bit it was a little
bit like but
if I don't try to focus on the smell
then this is still okay okay
[Music]
this one this one is not the food
yeah
I will apologize beforehand if I cannot
eat it if it's um first in your mouth
descent
huh I'll take another one
so let's eat one bite together okay
and so you girls all like durian I love
durian so much
my third favorite right now it's not
really durian season
it's not very
yeah so I can't find it so easily
okay okay
you have put one bite together you don't
want nope
you'll have to eat it only not in the
mood no okay
we already prepared a t-shirt if you
want I'm so scared I'm scared one the
plastic I have like plastic just in case
or maybe maybe uh we can picture this as
natto because mostly people yeah yeah it
don't really tend to resemble okay so if
you like method
no well do you like natto I don't know
oh yeah no
yeah okay Classics right here one
two three
laughs
you don't like it wait that's just a pet
maybe you like the real Duty and who
knows
it's delicious oh welcome to Indonesia
Garrison bye I'm not sure
it's it's
interesting it's weird it's creamy isn't
it
it's like an ice cream
but do you like the smell though I don't
know this one's not so strong
wait where's the real durian
is it just wrong let me try again I'll
try again do I really want to try again
just like it maybe hmm I think licking
would take a big bite usually a small
bite doesn't really no even though even
though I told these
um
he wants to cry would you like flowers
oh my God
oh my God can you bring me water please
okay
oh it got activated by would you like to
drink for mine throws oh thank you
this one actually looks very delicious
yeah this is really delicious I love
this yeah
I think I'm gonna repurchase this oh
I did yeah just like this just buys this
one like just now are you having fried
juice
it's okay this is kind of what I
expected and I'm happy to make this
experience
one of Arena's recommendations
pancakes I think I cannot try the real
Duty well that's okay would you like to
see the girls trying the real durian yes
yes because the real durian actually
smells a lot worse yeah can I eat yours
yeah please do okay
smell it
it smells like vanilla imagine it being
vanilla
I didn't smell anything I can't smell it
that's probably just the pancakes no no
so this is also from the freezer not
fresh durian
it's not smelly
really
it's not that smelly
what's up
you can hardly smell it right I'm gonna
try it
I'm gonna try
oh you see it yeah
no probably not this is better or worse
than this one
I think this one is better really yeah
maybe because that one's processed maybe
you don't like the process I'm gonna
feed me I wonder
what is it
not so bad maybe it's because Muna was
feeding me
I'm gonna feed me and it was okay it was
fine right maybe it's because this one
you know maybe because it's frozen it
doesn't smell so fast
and it's it's this very sweet it's okay
it's okay because the texture just now
reminded me a lot of like an orange okay
because it's a bit stringy
strings you know
um
[Music]
but I think I want to eat those noodles
oh yeah we have to cook it yeah we have
to cook it only do you have time
um my my mom's not getting me soon she
said she's still on the way okay okay
are you gonna eat this all on your own
yeah
well I still have a big durian just from
Luna
but it's interesting how I was not able
to eat the pancakes but the actual
Frozen durian was okay but probably
might be different different if it was
not frozen
and they all left the room
I'm so sorry I I spit that's fine
we can just wash it okay
after this you will get halloumi and it
will change
you won't be able to eat anything after
you eat it because it was so good it's
so good I I saw this one video once it
was a scientist he's like a noodle
expert he he saw he saw the the
packaging and he's like this is not
healthy you should not be eating this
and then he took a bite then he was like
hold up let me make one more
it was it's that tasty you love it okay
who bought the noodles I believe it's
Wednesday
thank you
but we have no egg right no egg Cooper's
going to buy it I think right now yeah
but she's moving how the [\h__\h] is she
moving wait what cool
hello did you have like a
album is that normal is it you that
would eat we put it on oh yeah that's
such a good idea how's she moving
is that her default like uh motion
no no way yeah
oh
[Laughter]
it was moving differently than you so I
was confused yeah it's because of my
Ninjutsu oh damn yeah what do you call
that like double doubling copying
yourself
[Music]
oh yeah this is pretty good it's french
fries it's like Hollow french fries
[Music]
foreign
there's like a chili sauce in there oh
yeah chili tomato don't worry it's not
it's not it's not uh just the prize
it's not that spicy the chili sauce
oh good good it's actually pretty sweet
the chili sauce see here in Indonesia we
don't really have ketchup that's not a
thing yeah yesterday I actually ordered
something
okay yesterday you know I had a lot of
um Indonesian food but then late at
night I was hungry so I wanted to order
something you know that I knew and I
ordered just some fast food but I didn't
even order sauce but it came with like a
like a Chili yeah a chili chili sauce
yeah it was good right it was a bit too
spicy I tried though I I ate the sauce
oh this moment someone's gone
[Music]
sorry sorry
it's okay I'm gonna try this
some plastic here okay if this is like
that sauce then hmm ah oh uh-huh I know
what kind of sauce is this
[Music]
Works
sorry only
sorry guess you'll eat yes you guys will
be eating it uh with the three of you
guys
[Music]
you haven't eaten at all
wait I forgot what
only can I leave this switch here keep
only hug hug without this what is this
this
person you requested oh yeah
oh thanks
so I did my favor
oh real stink
oh
[Laughter]
she um uh picked me up
so cute only
next time I'll pick you up Bridal Style
thank you for reading my my future and
so on oh my pleasure I hope in my future
I will have you too
Take Care thank you
thank you
mm-hmm
only gone yes but at least we got to
collab
so happy
I eat some more of the potato fries
which are not potato fries but they look
like potato fries
um
oh yeah no it's not so
anymore
I'm back with
food called tiller
is one of my favorite sweet food
what is it it's
I don't know how to explain it but maybe
Chad can tell me what she loves spicy uh
I ordered the not spicy one for you I
think that's a lie
no wait I think let me try this one is
it spicy or not
spicy
there's a good kind of spice and a bad
kind of splicer
um
I mean this one is spicy oh wait
um what is it
it's a Tapioca dough oh
interesting
spicy tapioca
with balado powder butter powder but I
tried Boba basically oh interesting
there's also sweet Chilla with soy sauce
oh but maybe you didn't know that I
don't eat spicy stuff I know you know
why are you trying to torture me it's
not I try okay yes
wait ah if you say this this one is not
spicy I swear I order it not spicy but I
don't know is it spicy for you or not
probably maybe they're spiciness but
because of the balado powder ah
[Music]
is it spicy not really but there's
spiciness there
um
it's it's so so so so so little
can you still eat it I think so like how
how does it taste
good
it's very much oh
what
[Laughter]
I think it's because
it came a bit delayed
you need to
um chill to eat it if I eat like
everything in three seconds
then I it will only it hits me later so
I think it's because of the boom boom
it's not so bad though like it's only
spicy in the bottom of my throat but not
in the inside of my mouth it's so spicy
here
how the tester tastes like
the texture yeah the texture is like
mm-hmm
I don't know what it tastes like though
and so this is a the tapioca dough um
and this is uh the egg
yeah egg that's egg oh
no it's good so you mix the dough
the cup
and then and then the the egg and then
you stir and then you just fry it it's
pretty good I keep on eating it that's
why it's uh it's pretty oily but just
don't consume this oftenly oh it's okay
um
good
I did this a lot
um
I want to try the sweet background that
is sweet the sweet one
wait do we have sweet Foods
I mean this one one day I'm gonna try a
sweet version oh
okay it's getting more and more spicy
yeah get them with yourself no no I
drive more
wow challenging challenging
[Music]
mmm noodles are they spicy no no are
they gonna be spicy too the noodles
no they're not no okay but you can you
can add chili powder
yeah no thank you
yeah it's okay A little spicy in my life
is okay
I want to eat what Coco eats you know
now we're gonna eat free at once
you know
I'll upload later on I will I will like
okay
[Music]
I don't like the texture
it's really Mozzy right
is this a popular Street Food
[Music]
no I don't know I
scissor
no
what's that
what's this
what the hell is this something like a
scissor
almost
no this is not Caesar a tweezer Maybe
yeah feel it feel the words
[Music]
okay
yeah I can't work so I can dance you
cannot twerk
this is much better than the durian
much better wait what what kind of what
kind of food do you prefer like sweet
salty
generally sweet
and I like salty food too yeah
but but
um mostly sweet
yeah how about Sour
I look sourdough oh just everything but
spicy
it kills me I'm not used to it
I I I have sensitive taste buds you know
sensitive butt taste buds what is taste
taste buds
in your mouth there's all kinds of
thousands of taste buds that react to
Sweet Jam sour stuff spicy stuff
everything oh yeah also you're you're
spicy butts is sensitive yeah
for the spicy just for the spicy yeah I
guess so maybe
oh
I don't taste the butt yeah it's my
taste buds it's your taste buds yeah
spicy badge try avocado juice don't
think we have avocado juice now yeah I
mean we can
I can just buy it now but
no no no it's okay all right Muna is
cooking something what is she cooking
and how is she moving
oh it's reacting to you it's reacting to
my head she's not here right now she's
cooking let her cook
okay I think I just bring this store so
you guys can see the movement of Muna
cooking stream can this be
oh
yeah she's she's moving
[Laughter]
it's working it's working okay so you
guys see Muna is moving because he she
is cooking right now yeah cooking the
hollow me and I just uh I just bought
the egg so you did yeah I bought the egg
when did you buy the egg
so
[Music]
there's food called martabak I think you
will like it you like chocolate yes
okay you're still eating Chiller so
Muna can you get mommy some more water
[Music]
I'm in the corner of the room kind of
stuck
so let Cobra do the work
hello everybody by the way I want to say
thank you for welcoming me to Indonesia
it's so nice but I don't have much time
for sightseeing maybe next time thank
you for the water
thank you
foreign
[Music]
Germany people called cat
that's it no no no no I mean I mean uh
okay in Indonesia we call the cat like
and maybe in Japan like
um
and maybe in Germany
so you're just throwing out some random
noises
no when I talk to my cat I'm like would
you
it means nothing
why is that a thing it's how you call a
cat I think you can play it because it
will play on stream I think now it's uh
is it muted only if it's music
yeah good calling in different languages
so how do you call Cat in German what is
this why have I never heard of this cat
says German and when if I say come here
I say come here
it's very similar to English uh and I
just go like
look like a baby
this is an Indonesian meme
it's worldwide meme never heard of it
ever before is that how you call
it what I don't know I thought have I
done it wrong my whole life
do I have to go to chunky wonky and be
like
yeah give it a try I don't I don't think
this works
oh
what's this
stuffed pancake
so this one is Marta back with egg is
egg Marta back but the sweet one is this
the chocolate Marta back which is do you
like cheese chocolate with cheese
chocolate with cheese what
what's wrong with it
chocolate chocolate with cheese
it's a that's a lot of cheese on that
picture too
it's like
what the [\h__\h] what kind of cheese is it
a specific cheese because
okay cheddar is kind of a sweet Swedish
Swedish Swedish cheese Swedish I guess
so
interesting yeah you never eat cheese
with chocolate people no
but that's really interesting I kind of
want to try
that's interesting that's weird okay
yeah okay if it's cheddar and maybe it
works Maybe
this is called
Manish means sweet
what is this person pouring over the
Mata back here oh it's the is um
the condensed milk oh but also Orange
I think it's the filter of the photo
I don't know what it is maybe another
cheese melt Melodies gorgeous I don't
know but this one has like banana
do they do it with banana too I haven't
tried this but this is not like the
original it looks like a pizza
but like uh yeah you can mix it with
with other things I guess but why is
this one green is it matcha no no no it
just tastes the same but it's just green
why it's because the the the dough
mixed with a pandan
leaves I think
uh-huh
we eat yesterday
we ate but so
[Music]
and we drank something green we drink I
think the tender do you like it
yeah
excuse me but I said it tastes like
breakfast cereal like milk with corn
flakes right mix yeah because the
cornflakes you know like sugary
cornflakes it tasted like that
which was good I agree but like uh no
not much people that eat corn flakes oh
Corner cereal yeah
I think if if like somebody who eats
corn flakes for breakfast sometimes yeah
frosties yeah if you come here and try
that I think you will understand what
I'm saying yeah yeah I I didn't realize
before until you say complex and then oh
okay yeah probably because they put like
sugar inside right to the coconut milk
they put sugar oh yeah yeah right right
so uh it's a brown sugar yeah yeah brown
sugar that's why I think it tastes like
that
no you can only just left her sandwich
oh
bye bye always wait but if you live
close to her can you bring her the
switch maybe yeah you're right okay
[Music]
I remember see too
and what else we will eat did we eat
some more
together what does it mean
what I forgot but
um
sometimes it's really spicy and soft
types it's not spicy it's spicy if you
if you're talking okay like it will
trigger the the boom boom the seasoning
too I don't know look I drank something
yesterday that's like pink
oh the noodles are here
this is a mukbang yeah it's a lot
[\h__\h] Shadow [\h__\h] shadow
I take with okay
really really small amount why
you're not hungry
no it's just my my tummy
I'm gonna upload the noodles
yeah oh yeah
noodles
it's like Wonder is our mommy so she's
your grandma
can I upload this yeah okay the [\h__\h] is
this mukbanging
if you guys want to see what it looks
like I just uh tweeted it out
okay
yeah oh my God
it's really a lot
um
or spoon or with your hen yes
thank you
[Music]
yeah no spicy apparently it doesn't look
spicy so it doesn't look
it's not red normally everything that's
red is expensive
or orange like orange like me spicy pop
oh come on
prepare drink for quinoa no this doesn't
look spicy it's not yeah yeah yeah yeah
this hollow me it's not spicy picture of
the food is on my Twitter it's on
Chihuahuas Twitter I can send it to uh
she can put it on the screen if she
wants to
I love the broth
hello Miss broth is really really
[\h__\h] good
[Applause]
[Music]
okay wait I want to fart
I'm polite
so polite
to love the door
House close the door then she opened
again she looks to the shark's face
holding the door handle
well at least I did fart
good for you Google thank you parting is
healthy Muna first cooks for us and now
she fixes the door for us
oh she has like um what do you call it
wow Mona is a build Builder yeah she has
like building stuff wow right at hand so
what is that
screw barrels whatever and chaos
uh
sorry we're not it's not my fault
[Music]
yeah I watch it and me too as a child
what does it sound like in Indonesian
I forgot because in German it's Bob down
my stuff yeah Bob the Builder we don't
have Indonesian version
It's English and uh in Indonesian TV
right
I forgot from what I from what I
remember I think I just watched the
English version oh because we have
German version
I forgot because I only watch it because
my brother watch it is it with subtitles
not no I don't know I forgot
I forgot what's up for the song I'm not
up for the song what's the typical
Indonesian on like children show
[Music]
is that like from Indonesia or from a
different country
[Music]
the door
support
[Music]
yeah yeah
okay I'm gonna try the noodles now but
they look very hot too it's so hard I
have I have you know what is it called
in Japanese
foreign
more
[Music]
but it's good even with even when it's
hot it was good yeah
for me
I usually
no add lime
accessorize her her noodles what do you
add nothing just the egg sometime I add
carrot
but I don't have enough carrots
and I don't like vegetables yeah but you
can add vegetables here
what is seaweed no no no no
but I didn't see you it can work
the door broke
it looks good on the picture even
yeah
oh yes
and for me and for me I'll I like to
cook this uh half
half
cooked half cooked the egg or your
noodles
the both I like half cooked eggs I want
to half cook the egg but the egg is not
omega so which is not too oh it must be
Omega yeah oh my God oh my God
I guess not omega oh my God
the vitamin
okay
that makes it so for the easy the high
quality eggs
[Music]
like like you can eat at brow in Japan
yeah but not in Indonesia
oh
see
yeah yeah so there's some eggs that you
can eat raw and some eggs you can't eat
raw
welcome to Indonesia's another thing in
Austria too I wonder I've never heard of
them
you can actually see it by the color of
the app the yellow uh the Omega one is a
little bit Orange
inside
um
salmonella entered the chat
we're doing so much in the Stream first
we did parrot card raining then we did
the game then we broke the door yeah
and now Muna was cooking and now we eat
mukbang it's a cooking stream mukbang
stream gaming stream literally
oh yeah and I usually add chili oh of
course of course yeah do you think
you're strong against spicy stuff
no no not anymore
never mind Papa
I used to I used to be strong to eat
spiciness but now I have ma
um
Now what is my stomach problem yes
ma weak stomach
good not good not good yeah not until
but it's different gastric gastric dish
yeah I have a stomach problem so I I
usually can use tree chili but now I can
only use one chili let's do plenty I
think
you're not really gonna have I have Kobo
and Kiara that's when I don't have to
talk because focus on my phone yeah
whenever
what was your first impression of
Chihuahua
[Music]
you're 165 right
I think I am
164. maybe
um
maybe yesterday I was wearing minus
heels
heels should bring me nowhere
when I actually saw Muna and me
yesterday we met shortly briefly and uh
when I was not I think when I was
nervous was when I'm nervous
I'm always nervous what was this wow
and I was nervous too
first meeting
but very cute
yeah
when I was a [\h__\h] quiet first
no I think I always quiet
especially in uh
lots of numbers
[Music]
that's okay it's overwhelming yeah
you know now she's loud and so lucky but
the first few minutes when I saw Kubo
she was like so shy she couldn't look at
me in my eyes she was looking to the
side and down
it's called first impression and it's to
be a good girl
you couldn't even look into my eye
because you were so shy
can you imagine a quiet couple
what quiet yeah a silent that's what
that exists
that's just my Human Side
[Music]
really don't believe it yeah
yeah
this is my third third Bowl we serve so
much we need to only bring only back
yeah yeah maybe
[Music]
I think she's gonna stay for like a long
time
[Music]
and we need to I don't think I can
I don't think I can eat much guys
I can still eat more yeah
diet eat more
oh yeah come on
if I touch you I feel like I can break
you so you need to eat more
and it's just
animus back
what one wash back
do you eat do you eat do you eat manual
no
webton
um
what did you do when you were on your
free time
hmm
I cuddle with my cat
and I watch Netflix and
um there's not much free time because in
my free time a lot of the time I just do
like social media and other work like I
have to catch up on deadlines
many designs
[Music]
done forget to rest
remember what Ollie said
yes
no but also well now what was that
yesterday
something with the deadlines and was it
yesterday or today I'm so confused
deadline something about
my deadline something like some
Indonesian phrase about reminding
someone of deadlines
I learned it yesterday wait foreign
[Music]
but
but it's like passive aggressively
yeah yeah you can be using do you
remember that you have some deadlines
yes yes
in Indonesia we usually type it with
that emoticon emoji with the prayer
I see
we're not
they have so many noodles but like the
soup is almost gone yeah and so what do
you think of this noodle
it's really good
very good instant noodles
yeah no the egg makes it extra good I
guess the more you add the better to
replace you should buy a lot
you can you can be uh
you can be reseller I wonder no I think
probably
um maybe they sell it in Austria but
it's a little different taste no I mean
the instrument packages are probably
imported
in Japan they also have the same one but
the taste is different oh
even they say uh it was the same taste
but it's not slightly different really
because ours is a half more a message
do you know messy
the the soccer player no no no what the
hell
yeah the what is it yeah
uh it was like like something like uh
makes the food
um tasty
yeah it's also a seasoning but listening
if you eat much MSG food that uh um
contain MSD you will be
uh here in Indonesia we called It Go
block go block yeah you can be stupid if
you eat much look at me
yeah you ate too much yeah I I even got
it I don't know you're not stupid you
can do a coding websites and stuff yeah
you're right I'm not stupid
I'm a hacker I can cook I can make
website
can you make your website what website
do you want I want um a professional
looking website that says
coming one day
[Music]
autograph biography
biography
maybe make like business KFC store
when people can order it how much do I
have to pay you to to code the website
damn
how much it's pretty much but it's for
my mom your business is my business yeah
because if you die okay you get my money
[Music]
yeah it's gonna take a long time don't
remind them
it's okay
no I cannot get the money then no
inheritance money
that is really unfortunate
you have to make your own money you have
to work strong work hard on your own
okay you got so many stars and so much
money in in Mario Party now I think you
can do it
just use all of that in real life I want
to buy new back
because you said my back is
I don't know you sounds like you're
really you really see me like very
cringe not cringe but I thought you
would have like a cute bag
much cuter with like maybe I don't know
pink color or blue color
and maybe some pearls but beautiful no
like a fanny I'm edgy it's just it's his
face did you see Muna bag
what is pretty pretty back inside also
pretty
lock my back two bags talking about
Hollow bags oh you know you sent me your
bag and Kubo also sent her back
everybody immediately even when the
picture was still blurry everybody was
like this bag but with Coco back no one
knew yeah I I I I I saw it like nobody
no nobody that's me
bruh it's such a surprise it's because
it's really practical
I guess so
I just have two things to bring
phone and wallets only that so why do I
need big back
you don't need a big bag I mean honestly
you can just keep that bag of course I'm
just saying I was surprised it wasn't
like you know cute cute bag with maybe
some frills
but if you're happy with that bag you
can keep the bag
of course it's not cringe
[Music]
cringe no
I'm just who is this
who is this person I bought a new
YouTuber
yeah maybe you can go back shopping
with Muna
with me yeah okay
mommy honey
[Music]
use your own money
ah [\h__\h] or ask go ask Kelly
okay okay that is black card let's go
uh
yes well there's still so much food yeah
I think I cannot eat anymore after this
too many noodles
oh what's that ah my
um
[Music]
you know what I mean okay
um
you guys want some
chat will you eat the noodles
eat some noodles to help help
I'm stuffing good lunch
oh they want noodles yes yes yes type
one if you want type one one one one
here I'm tired I scream so much I want
to sleep
[Music]
yeah what are you cooking I'm not
cooking anything
let her go that's her cool do you know
that Meme no no
but I know everybody always like let her
go yeah let him cook what does that mean
it's just some it's a meme when somebody
is doing something even when they're not
cooking
you know you don't want to stop them
you'd want them to do their thing
because it's gonna be great ah so let's
just say let her close
oh I could be a meme from some something
I don't even I forgot the origin I knew
it before but I forgot
Breaking Bad ah we go bang bad Breaking
Bad is that the movie it's a TV Show
Breaking Bad No but I don't know it's a
show it's a kind of like
um it's not comedy it's not romance I
don't know how to describe it though
it's kind of serious I think
yeah Breaking Bad it's the um
continuation of Malcolm in the Middle
no Malcolm in the Middle
um no no
it's a [\h__\h] it's a fun show from back in
the day it was a lie anyway it was a
joke that's also a meme that Breaking
Bad is the continuation just because one
actor is the same actor and your
favorite crime drama yeah wow but
Malcolm in the Middle is not a drama
um yeah
okay let's look it up later
we also don't really have something like
that in German
y
[Music]
I'm gonna take this can you warm it up
later
[Music]
yeah soggy very soggy
nowhere
[Music]
yesterday
I saw I saw a picture
and me we saw a picture of a horse oh
yeah and she looks at me so
many expectations
when will we ride a horse oh now I don't
have time but next time
well did you bring the coupon
you did not bring the coupon
I have it in my memory that's not enough
I need the real coupon
[Music]
um
next time
there's always a next time oh they're
snacking on the on the fries again
the fresh is the best
[Music]
cook often than home no order food
always yeah I like order oh yo you often
to cook food yeah yeah this is very Chef
mommy
challenge thank you how many food that
you can cook
so many do you know hello fresh
yeah it's a service for cooking like you
can choose a recipe and then they send
you the ingredients and you just cook it
but they send you the perfect amount of
ingredients so you don't lose anything
like that it's all over the world it's
in Europe and America it's in Japan I
think too so maybe it's exists in
Indonesia I don't know people I don't
wanna I don't wanna advertise for them
answer me Hello friends Hello friends
y'all so I cook so much from them I've
cooked like a million things yeah
sponsored no not sponsored not sponsored
but they better sponsor me like it's
about time oh hello fresh it's a brand
it's a company it's a company they send
you oh yeah they have been here they
have it they have it what's that
depending on the country they have
different recipes so some people say for
example in America it's not so good
because the recipes are not so good in
Europe they're pretty good I don't know
about Indonesia but they sent you the
ingredients the perfect amount and the
recipe and you just follow the steps
it's really good maybe you can try
[Music]
I think
it's different
Hello friends yeah that's something else
no that's different they just
took the name they stole the name
maybe they have a real one
okay can you cook stick stick yeah
[Music]
I think so I mean maybe not perfectly
well that's cooked like like like
porks pork fillet before
this
is yes
that's it I don't know if they have any
Indonesia
maybe not has anyone tried it before in
the chat any Indonesians we've tried it
before
the real thing when we cooking the prep
is 200.
the prep yeah the prep yeah
preparation on Cut vegetables and so on
yeah but it's it's
quite fun I would say hello freshman
somebody is like a long time yeah yeah
but you know I also had this phase after
joining whole life where I order food
all the time
uh and I realized first of all it costs
so much money second of all I ordered
the same food always right you don't you
always order the same food yeah yeah
right so it's not the same and also I
feel like home cooking tastes a bit
better maybe if you if you get good at
it
so this way I have so much choice and I
can eat whatever I want mostly and it's
not always the same thing and and it's
fresh why am I
helping Hello friends hello fresh
sponsors okay
[Music]
okay I'm cooking everybody needs to cook
more it's more healthy because then you
know what you put into the foods too
yeah and then after you're done you're
like proud I'm always so proud when I
look at the food I cooked I'm like I
made this and it tastes good yeah
it looks good too no thank you the
plating
the serving everything thank you but
instant noodles also very good
I can cook in some noodles that's all
you can cook
I can cook water boiling water
wow I'm so proud of you
fried egg
they don't have in here no
I don't see Japan oh maybe they don't
have a oh okay
just Europe and any and so on
oh well I guess yeah that's like I
wasn't cooking so much on my own because
I was too lazy to go to the supermarket
and buy the ingredients yeah yeah and
then I you know they don't have like so
many small servings because I live alone
and but they sell everything in more in
bigger sizes for like two people three
people also but for hellofresh they have
smaller sizes so yeah it's very nice
[Music]
what can you cook can you cook something
yeah
it's mostly Indonesian food
uh if
let's see
[Music]
it's a beef I think I saw it yeah it's a
beef right yeah it looks good
how do you make it
oh I just buy the ingredient in
traditional
chop chops
what what meat is it it's a coffee
so you're throwing the beef
uh you need you need the ingredient I
forgot what is the ingredients
yeah I'm gonna try is it easy no no no
it's like around
11 or 12 hours no oh you have to simmer
the beef so itself
yeah six hours sometimes I just uh as
long the longest the longer you leave it
like that yeah the tastier do you eat it
with rice or just like that
um
is
[Music]
Gordon Ramsay
um
idiot sandwich
you know what I mean I know
you don't know
I just got an Indian sandwich out of
Cobo I'm an idiots it's like you know
you know Gordon Ramsay right yeah he has
his TV show with cooking right yeah yeah
and he screams at the people right yeah
so he goes up to an uh like a
guy who cooks there and he's like
you're an idiot sandwich yeah that's
what I mean sandwich
I think he he even did it with like
pieces of bread like toast bread on both
sides
on the face and then your idiot sandwich
idiots
[Music]
Gordon
yeah
what are you
doing it
how about Uncle Roger yes
kind of not personally
yeah I don't know in person but you know
Uncle Roger do you know Uncle Roger
personally no no no no no no it's just
funny yeah he's a funny man
is it halal
well I don't know him at all though like
I don't watch his stuff I don't know
much about Uncle Roger you need to teach
me more more like kids
a YouTuber who will role play to be like
a chef
it's kind of funny you know
he is
and he talking like uh I don't know is
it Malaysian a Singapore accents kind of
thing
[Music]
it was so funny and I have to watch oh
they say Malaysian
Malaysian
oh I have to watch recently everybody
tells me about him
why why why why why yeah
ready ready moving in in action
[Music]
I need to understand
the memes I have to watch okay
it's three hours
finish and we do some other stuff yeah
[Music]
show me the city yes
okay then guys thank you so much
fun right now
what is thank you in your language
in our language yeah
thank you for watching thank you for
watching
[Music]
uh the song
bye
[Music]