[Music]
MALE Uh
ANA
Pa Uh
De Deep
Me
Dabon
Me Me
ME Ah, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, me, me, me, yeah yeah,
me me,
me
medee
me n
utte
me n aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Hey,
first I'll explain a little bit in English Seaside 1
Willow
hdi Antin Friars by
Sa residents Dixie Tomorrow oer
estan
Pad Siemens first in un
r 9 end line 50 os
chai 2
Usuda ideal 10 people's sounds are  Amane with
r 2 under bts
Gem Today how ha minute
dubbing
mastering 0 bobby middle moon
uncharred panties alonfinity bob
me english 3 year old barter
thin chain fade super
yea today is about the cat  I
think he only speaks Japanese and German, so I don't
think he's good at English.However, I'd like to
ask him to give me a bath, and tomorrow
I'll be in the middle of a flare.
Well, I'm going to win right away with the painting, so I'll do my best.That's a bit
late.It's
different from this uniform.So
today I went there to take a photo.What
can I say, Saa-ko?No, no, that's
usually the case in that group or in Europe, but in Chara's country, there are no
schools where uniforms are worn.
No, I don't
mean casual clothes, I don't wear civilian clothes, I wear uniforms,
so I kind of admire Japan's cute uniforms,
but I'm a kill, but I met a male,
and I'm
fine with the Japanese charts.  But now I
went to Ippudo. It
was a really strange line. No,
I'm a teacher, so that's
a bit inappropriate.
4 Like Flare Furi-chan.
It's a gorgeous flare. It's
Claire-chan.  Kacho-sensei, why don't you just flare
up?
That's smart, Mr. Edo, but
even in Edo-Kyū, stop it and stop it.
Ah, it's just a papa doll mark, at most.
Schaller: I do
n't know, I don't know, and I have an all-white legacy.
Edamoto, don't you study properly? Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
ana We're
on Net No. 5 today. That Tsuke Ria-senpai seems to
be interested in German, isn't she? It looks
like she's got a spear, so she can play.  Flare Heart
Channel Hirano Janpaku's
Legacy Which one can you talk about today?
Yes, I wanted to learn that German, but there weren't many people who could speak German when I talked to them during the hour,
so this is the 4th time.  I'm
really happy. Please take care of me.
Tetsu. It's ak 5. Thank you.
Dai. It's strange that people
call me by my first name.
Kudo
. I'll let you know. It's
been a long time since I've had a convenience sticker.  The last person I taught
was Gra-chan, right? He gave
it to me. Gra-chan was able to do a little more German-like, and it
was a little more basic. That's
great. Yeah, it's a little awkward when you look at it from the basics,
but it's okay. If you're
interested, you'll be fine.  Hmm, I'll
start with something a little easier.
Yes, I want nuts. tgn dimensions
.
In German, there
's something called "ontaru tsutsu", and in the Hai Hai school, there are two dots above the 8 or cherry blossoms, etc.
Overseas, that's also that c.
Well then, uh, the zodiac signs are the two terry birds in Boyson's store. Yeah, it's
okay to be class e, so don't
touch anything. You
don't have to write this on the back, except for today.  For example, if there are two transfers on top of a, it
's okay to call it brass, and
that's how you drive it.The star who said that it's okay to fight is the
curry that fights.This is because when we met in self-study, we
actually did Mona.  It's a bit
amazing, it has a nostalgic feel to it, and I'm glad I bought it. After a while, that person's face # ss is also there, and that b is a letter that looks like a b when it's on the big face.
What's the sound? Well,
today,
that pot I used in Photoshop. I
couldn't write that in the first place, so I'll write about it 10 minutes later. So there's some water
running along the river, but
if you don't want to use ah, you can use ss.
Yeah, that's what it is, so yeah.  From here, I'm
going to teach you a few different greetings.
Spec v Quick. I'm sure you've heard of this before.
Good morning. It's
about Gutengo.
Futenmagen. Everyone has heard this before
. This is easy. Gutenmohara.  After 2, it
's easy. Hello Guten Chako. Yes,
good center. I'm
feeling good at the clinic, and I'm already empty. Amen.
Good evening. Good day Abedi hamburger store. That means good, good, good. Good morning from the back.  It
means ``noon'' or ``good day.'
' So there are three words, ``good morning'', ``today'',
and ``good evening''.  Problem: It's
black,
huh? What's the smell? They
said it's part 4, Kyoto, etc. Well,
there's a time difference, so that's right. In that case, it's
fine. In English, it's hee
eno, but in German it's h
eeeeeeee.  But yeah, it's possible.
But you don't really have to worry about it.
By the way, if it
was that Tsunku-san, he would say good morning no matter
what time of day it was, even though it had nothing to do with the pre-war period. It's
kind of an industry thing.  Everyone said good morning,
huh? Was it 4 games? I
drank those 2 bottles and got paid, but for some reason,
greetings in the industry usually include good morning. You
might have heard that before. I went
home to Japan.  When I'm there, I
just say thank you for your hard work, thank you for your hard work, desu, just money. Kagawa, he also uses my sister, I mean, both of them are so. When I use "boso", the word "wardes" isn't particularly used.
Well, that's how it is.  That's right,
country.Unfortunately, that word doesn't exist.I've
often
thought that it's a shame, but it
doesn't exist.At times like that, it becomes Hello.
[Music]
No, at times like that, it's one of these three.
Oh, even if I paint like that, how many minutes does it take for the guests to bathe
? Well, how many minutes does it take for the guests to take a bath? General Affairs 4 no. I
don't know the palace, but I sleep a lot.
Someone who studies German is
drawing Korematsu.
Tonight, when I'm at Gar.  There are people who don't say ``gu''
but say ``good night.''
Yeah, everyone also says 4 e. ``Hey, come on.  Ah, I can't
put my dreams in there, bam, wan, wan, wan, wan, wan, wan, wan, wan, wan, wan, wan, wan, wan, wan, wan, wan, wan, wan, wan, wan, wan, wan, wan, wan, wan, wan, wan, wan, wan, wan, wan, nana, Miya
store, Naha city, I'm
feeling up, ship,
ah, I wonder if I'm weak, I'm not going to show my strength. s There were 5 of us, and we were in a mess.
Hahahaha, but Germans and
Austrians don't usually come, and
that kind woman 878 isn't gahahahaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa.
It's normal like this,
it's like this, it's like that, but it sounds like it's
perfect.
Nakane,
this is one blue chip after another. That's so fast.
Hey, I'm Koi Honkoi Ping Pong Peka Pepa Sabu Seal. As expected of
Sugar, it's
white.
Ah, waianae
Ah, that's why I'm going to tell the country,
so
after that hardware, there's cheese extraction.  I
think it's hard to pronounce when you say it in the middle spoon truth re yes chain while imagining it,
right? I'm careful about that 2010 book.I
bought more uu and moisturized it.Uuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu.  I
can't do it!
This is difficult.
Ah, I'm
using Hughes a lot. I
must be feeling it deeply right now. c Medium c 2
Spat It
's a flower shaped like a mouth. It's a burger, but
I'm
going to go ahead and cover the application a little more.  It's difficult to mix it up.
Pooh
[music] I
can explain it by saying, ``This
shape, that
tongue is at the bottom, it's amazing, and now the
character is saying ``ooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
moon.''
1 Even if I worry about it that much.  It
's okay, but
in Noguchi's a mouth f Uuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu
o 2 r Ahaha, it's too difficult Do
n't worry about it, it's okay
Nakaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Hey, that
polite way of saying it, and that
final greeting used in Kihara's broadcast is Aoni
Leaders, it's difficult, right?
90 Difficult people, aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa a little a piece a piece a piece a sssssssssssssss0000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000 type form type form type form type form type form type form type form type form type form type form
form.  It's a
very polite way of saying "I'll see you again" in the bathing and batting line.
Yes, I really like that part. I
always use this at the end of the memorized matching wave performance, so I
remember it till the end.  Okay,
this is how I got it registered in the dictionary. Let's just
write it as giving the sound of running and being placed. The
sound is like this, but it's not over yet
. This is the basic greeting of a bear. It
seems like the bear is able to hark properly, so it's
a bit more.  Let's
go to the difficult person Let's
go to one of the advanced ads on one head.
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh, I'm going to
go in German.
Yes, that's what I'm
talking about. Goods from Guten Morgen. A bouquet
of good-for-nothing goods. Well, I'm a
first-time Buddhist. Well, I'm a 2-
year-old. Well, it's
okay. Voice.
OK to the tumor ok ok ok
here Anne princess From here on the family age
Amen
ore Please tell me what the carrier means
Kennel
result
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa It's difficult to sell these words
Aaron Hey sleep through the ramen house What's the rarity of the
ship?  Hmmm, that's huge, home page. This
doesn't have to be a true knight group with Makiko Ichi, but I
thought it looked like that one in the garden now, and I clearly said that I'd like to have it all the time,
but
Kennedy Amen Were Mail, everyone. I'm sorry.
Let's get to know more deeply about the legacy of the 8th room in Osaka.From now on,
my name is in German.I
like a minor woman.  Just now, I was pronouncing it in a very English way,
but when I
pronounced it like ``don convenience'', I
licked it out of my eyes.
a 8 That's right, that's a fresh idea. ii becomes
mine mine ep 1.
Yeah, normally it's because of the good qualities of that girl.
In German, it's a. But also, the English pronunciation of love is fine in German,
but next door.  When it's in it, it's like, yeah, it's love. It's
become a bit complicated. No, it's
cyber. Ah,
that's right.
Basically, German has a lot more romantic children than Aid.
For example, I think this is very similar to how it is pronounced.  When I
try to read it in Japanese normally, I
think it's an eye,
but when I try to read it in English, it doesn't work,
but when I
read it like German, it's katakana, and when it's katakana, it's katakana,
so I'm sorry.  It's like in Middle English,
but I have no idea where the back of the bridge is, and
when I read it, I think, ``Ah, that's
not true,'' and I'm like, ``Why is she like this?'' Well, that's true,
but even if I don't really think about it, I'm like, ``I'm on a
boat.''  It sounds long since I tried to read it slowly,
but
even if I don't stretch it that much, it's a minor eye. Sweet licking.
s a Flare walk with a sad and ra.
P. Mr.
White
has 10 female friends. Is Flare Shiranui
okay?
Ah,
no, I say it.  It's a side garden, dis flare,
Shiranui, it's good, it's nice, it's so good that
Kabe-machi has a new name, and it's you who gives dark praise. It's delicious. I
turn and share it with a casual minor yes.  I
tried to say the total number of cars, and I said,
``Ah, inner stingray and flare Shiranui.''
Good fafa, ``Hey, Ino, I
want it.'' I understand the name well.
Then, when
I heard the name of ``a,'' on the other hand, ``b. Wave chair 2.
This is a tsunami.''  That's not an honorific word,
it's a tame mouth, but it's totally fine Lee Pei Sudo 3
Heiston
Ui Bridge 2 oo a minor Eyes
Rich four seasons only be
highs Michio
a
Front chair flare Shiranui
Yes
rar
Open the bread please
ranran
asai
Yukou has the same habit, hmm, 1 riddle, I'm playing various Bach songs, I
guess I'm impressed.
But this is already perfect, bab
seems to be a challenge, so I'm going to release
it. Hmm, I don't know. The
name
[music] is Minami
Tsuna.  Functions like Urbanisu, etc., that fit together in 10,000 yen inches, I'm
sure I'll wait, but I do
n't understand Japanese. I don't understand
English. I don't know what to do with the
cattle.  I wish
there was a name like No. 8 Lee, which I heard was being called. Yeah, yeah, yeah, actually. There's
no name here, so what's the name of the girl?
Honda. What do you call me?  The
book written here is really
good at home. It's a very good love. If you
look at the relationship, it's better than a teacher or something,
but I guess it's more like a summer time thing.
For example,
there's a way to say "Naaame" in the bass zone, "What's your name
?" and "What's your name?" and "What's
your name?" and "Wait, what's your name?"  I
thought it would be easy, so I decided
on this b Yes, the procedure is b Yes,
how are you? I
heard that the defense white that increases the number of chants
is this sunny Likyukyutto.
Ah,
Jude came off and started bulbs.
BAIS D An Ah
Layer
Ge Ge D4 A
Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
Sites
Dea
SEIA Good
RAN Happy
Can D.
Yeah, yeah,
esbase, how are you doing? The
answer is, I'm Gekiren-san Miyagi. s Coupon, Ha-
miya is enough on its own, but
Nagatomi-chan's 4th turn,
yeah,
Miyuki will be saved if you use a proper phrase.
I can't hear it
Flare management Shiranoe 3 a fee This is a
big festival and please listen to it
Abe Gestia Miyake's
amazing break from the mold
One hit beer ks Dia
Looking up Suasuka go to not
Bent hugger
aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
for the bee farm
Wes will eat tomorrow  Tree Ah Gee Gee Tsuki
Game Dew Yeah, yeah,
there's no number of Dohana at the end, but it
might sound a bit like that.
To the legacy of the sound and ac that the house now listens to
bk press machine your
[music]
mya mougesun
see the moon issue ah
that john sacher girl patch ro
emu get ask ba tee evan d
4 gya gya art ok then next is
ann and that  Um, excuse me, but how old are you?
Shison's
phrase is [music] birde. That
do bar, for example, is you. b
also means road, but that guy is, uh
, yeah, it's a city word.
Lee
Aichi
Rice  r one
vezel s d 2
heeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee’ys Isan
but I’m sorry to share this with you guys.
Hey, uh, that
’s it. A bird can ride on it.  I can't decide
. Ah, ha, Shiranui-san. It would
be nice if you could answer, ``Oh, that's all base.''
Wiener afe me,
no, ai. But that's what I
thought. That's what I thought.  I
smoked it for 5 times or so,
but in Japanese,
it's 20021 years old, but 221-
san
has it.If
I say
that, it's fine,
right?
Panzoider
Ah, wait a minute, I'm on discord right now. It's fictional,
but
Papa Ido, yes, I'll give you hair.
Love's Nest Banshee.
Long a. I'll
try writing it in katakana. A few times
more.
Child
ugh a I'm going to be a
role model, but 100 y I stepped on it
A I
UNDART I I have a sore throat ran
Ran
Take it and read it Wait a
minute 4 things I'll list for the kids who don't wait
a little bit by 2
Ah, I was born with a delusion for a long time,
but when I heard that it was loaded with bonders, I thought it was Kanda-san.A,
I thought it was a member, but a,
Hi Kei, it's just a pause.  I
think it's better when it's the rainy season. When it's the rainy season, it's ain't earth pressure number 9. Hmmm, I'm in two cheeks. q Past, ya, the number is, uh, I'm the only one. It's about time I was studying that time.
Yes, it's that picture of Yumeru, but it's a little bit
easy to understand.It's a bit of a number in one word.The
difficult part is in English.For example, if it's a
22 inch, you
can say it in the order of ``Aa-chan'' who becomes a pointy won by mail order.  But
if it's in German, the last one
will be after 820, and I'm
worried about the rumblings.For example,
if it was 221, it would be
201.It
was a little hard to understand at the beginning when the middle part was mixed in.  I
think, hmm, the order is strange. If that's the case, then
a
rain 1 comes first, and the inside is 1
20 Rinonop. I
know it's confusing, but once it's
explained, it all comes together.
Oh yeah, it's
okay. I have a lot of grandmothers, so I can't help it.
But my
dad asked me to give him some Schiller.
Ah, that means I
should put my own age into it.
Pence by  Nowadays, the boring and boring top dressing is expensive, but
it's a dare.Please try to say it yourself.Oh, it's a good rice tour, and it's white.Then, if you're an informant or a club, then you're below.Judge Jar Jarmen, that's a free style,
but a Germany.  It's like, ``
Oh, no, it's good.'' It's like, ``Oh
, no, it's good.'' It's like, ``Oh, no, it's real.'' It's
like, ``Oh, it's real.'' I
went to see that guy with a good idol girl.  Dainon-chan
Peyabai dozo en's wife derou phase
Shooting wine vinegar when will it be in ear
me
roo
2 wives
upaiii
ir when is it ur year
Wars club stage tae online river
to free
Hibiki papa myself  It's really hard to put it into words
.
Hey, I'm getting old.
For those of you who don't want to give in, you
're probably young. I'm
young. Don't tell me if you can't tell by looking at me. If you're young, you
're probably a high school student.  Hey, I'll wait until now.
Next time in Sentai, it'll be related to wearing clothes.
Yes, it's here. I
'm sorry, everyone. I'm sorry,
Mr. Hirano. Hurry up, Mr. Lugie. Please be firm.
Yeah, yeah,
yeah, bald, that's what I did.  White's legacy Um that
conversational English let's do it
uh um I ah
please ask me bip Sudo
Big Airway
Ware and Beth do a 1
[Music]
Oniiten Green
Mining 8 Akio I don't understand.  Until this year. So,
if you're not sure what to say,
please make up your mind before the next one. Yes, it's
different, but I'm having trouble with the mouse. It's
okay if it's because I'm angry. Yes, I'm sorry,
titanium.  As for the version, I would
like to know it in series.No,
but I'm in
trouble.It's a
problem for the students.I
don Obon and 6 ok 4th edition is ok.If I
take the mixed version, this is a blind story, so I'll
leave this aside for
a while.  Shall I ask if the next one will be poisonous sushi?
Where does Hidebo's room come from
? That means a certain room.
No hair. Now, how about Kahlo-nu-ston? Homu-spoon-ya. Nuko-nesto-zu.
How
should I pronounce this? It's cold.  Don
community 2
Yes, that's right, it's okay to feel like opening a little princess. Yes, that's
right, this is a two-word device.
Penetration wear, now,
low layer, comptoon ridge activity, and
finally, heat and hatena, while clearly stating the meaning of
cat, this, and that hate.  It's there after passing through Naachan,
but it wasn't in this font, so I vaguely
asked Situation Shiranui 3, and it said, ``
Ishibemeaiou a''
Dokosujumo 22 s down, Japan,
not ``Japan'' or ``Paso Japan''.
Yeah
then I'll
be aab Tafutami Iikomeahime
com I'm not going to have legs, I'm going to go to the outside
navigation Naaboda bar Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa with
Well, if you buy it, let's try it out. a
A's heritage
a Please
ask me if I'm from poison rather than 500
wl Come star
I'm blue,
but I'm going to have a hard time tomorrow.  The
characters in Uria and others are
soooooooooooooooooooo Stone Edia Soda's is really difficult,
but yeah, I follow the two dots on the cherry blossoms of Sky Sakinoa It's an
English letter, but I want to
do it Sound quality Mori By the way, it's important to wink
Where is it
wig help
air
Well,
after all, it's related, so it's a card,
but Chiara
is often mistaken for an Australian, so I'm going to
use this as a joke and add ashes to the rally. Are you
saying she's Jin?
Ahaha.  I'm going to take care of the rest, but hmm,
I've got the farm booster, and I've got the
iPhone's fear moon.
OK, then, let's take this to the turn play center.
Mr. White, let's have some English conversation from the top to the bottom of this.
Okay, click.
rei house
ua  If you want to
put it back, please refer to it.Let's
start with the white heritage.Listen to those two.Yes,
my name is Fufun.Your name is,
please.Heeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeoooooo
now inside me
memorize the sources and pronounce them.Open/close.
Year mine 7.  h I'm eating
Abiminor Ram Is Flare Shiranui good
a Uh eh
mi
wii Yes I'm measuring the battle Emissions v Emissions
do Gya Gya Gya
Let's paste it Minor eyes Killer was sad
A
No, Mitsuhashi and Tokoro ok I also heard the name on the contrary  I do
n't ask but yeah
yeah Depa bks Ti Ya Shiranu Iin 3
Prea-v Arthur web dea
year
peg ahhh
the answer is 4
Jess
astrale goods USR Hey,
it's a good idea to listen to it Ice cream goods yaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Ah, oh
, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
go, go to the
village 5 bs 5 bs Ah, I
want to share A,
so that's right.
Guess tomorrow true Daitaeee genealogy
du Many car art Miyagi s Ah, the book The
point is they should go to bed, what I just said Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa to to some errand,
by the way, opinion
a
Lee
That bistu
Hey  Aaaaangaa, let's cover it. I
'll decide.
A little addition that can be discovered in 8 y minutes, and a rare 5
.  Bare
India 4 I'm so
keen on trying to make a profit I really
don't like it Jaeba Heights's mirror is here A year Wow, big bones and big bones Hmmmm a rice flour wig 6 Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaiii  It's
okay if you don't ask me about it. It's just to show off your appearance. It's a ring of a carefree person. You're going to mess up your meal and your suit. I don't know everything about it, but I think it's difficult for that Japanese person, but you did a great job. Good job.  Well,
it's kind.2 In fact, if Ringo had that support, it would
be an appointment, but if it was in German, it would be up.L
Up1000 Upfell2 Ah,
yes, that's right.Participants: Let's
go for a long swim.What's next?
D Village +
Various things  I thought I'd use that senior for a moment. I
tried saying that after that.
Bach Baka Pabu The
same bus can't fly, I'll call you to read it.
Naruaa, the teacher at the push school.
Rii!
I've been trying to laugh at animals since the beginning.  It's half
-elf and star-like.
Yes, that's right. What's going to happen with that?
Bed ge
Boo Boo 8 Haru Hanyu Hanyu Harubu - It's Elfun.
Yes,
I'm a half-elf.
SFA Raging Haru Pero.
ani
Boo Boo El.  If it was Hal English, etc.
But
yeah, it was German, so it would be bb. That's right,
how will. If it
was just Elf, yeah, yeah, it could be done
in German, but by the way,
German Day. If you
count those numbers,
11 is the same number 5.
That's right, big
ran is enough.  Lying
down Pimlongin, only 31 did something properly from the inside.
Well, there's a special way to read numbers, it's a woman. I don't know what that means, from 10 to 20,
af, all 2 on the 2nd floor, tongue, tongue, throat, pants,
Edda curry.  The powder is layering on top of each other, isn't it?
Look at the numbers, Ash, I
want to give you a ring already. It's
like Mach Wow
goo. I
just want to go to sumo in my car.  I
talked about it, but I can't
sleep well because I can't sleep well because of the Seria mahjong tiles.
That's why I can't sell it.
1 Han Gwang Lunch Oh, it's so fluffy, okay? Sa
Hikari Thank you 6 minutes Aso Slider Hahn
Station  Meat Disposal Yan Ha
Ha Realistic Yummy Huh Ah Ah,
it's a transfer of the Charlie Small Blue
Oh, it
's hard, it's hard.  When
Flare-senpai suddenly contacted me almost every morning, I
had the fault of not telling him that I was going to bed two hours beforehand.Ah, do
n't say that, I promise.Hahaha, the
tweets helped me a lot, too.  I
have a tweet for 2 hours after nails,
but I'm
also doing Andy tweets. I
'm told when I'm sleeping after time. Oh,
but it's hard. Yesterday, that flare senior  I
wanted to become one, so I told him a few things.That
's lavender, which makes it easy to sleep on.I tried a lavender pillow
and told him that it was called Ra.What is
lavender called?  Ah,
telly woman handbook lavender to my sister Lavender
lame person's side and ramen and Lou Lavender Yay, I'm
sorry dinner I
mixed it up in my head but it's too much for 2 servings
Kun lavender Lavender
Mmm-chan I'm really looking at the back side of flowers in the snow
Oh
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaoh  It
's a house, but I'm
also painting patterns that are used in Germany
. I'm
sure I know about Numa So-so 6 T.
Neh, about
6 fur java and
Clair's
Yes
ana
Aaaaaaa
Overall
Well, it's the same as Japanese and English
There are various kinds of tidal flats, but it's definitely a good party, and
there's also the expression "gee", but this is
at least not in a dangerous nenbo story where you meet someone seriously.  Hanu
Atsuta's dialect and suits are
old, and his fingers and legs are c
. Well, he looks a little more like a baby. It's not a
repeat. It's
simply Aso. The more you say it, the
more you say it on the internet. 6  Later, ``
vater'' is a proper German word, but it's like
a bee swarm or a normal farmer, and I
feel like it's korma ink, manners, and pato.  I wonder
if people are used to saying things like that, so if you
teach me that from the tree I was born with, that's what happens
when you're taught that way.Mahuba of the pub
bagDepartment Babuman Bag each partman vaam vaam I
can't understand it in German, but
eh,
Harvey, what's up?  I feel sorry for Faye, who ca
n't sleep, but instead, the operator
tells me to train quickly, so I give him a ticket.  Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhy  I ca
n't do it.
Is it okay? Dear viewers, are you sure you're okay? I
'm watching Twitter from the car window, and
everyone is asking me when I'm going to sleep. It's like a metamoha. When does that guy go to sleep?
By the way, I'm
sorry for all the 5's in Bang Bang.  Kissaw
Yuzu Chau Fur is as Peter Speta I
can add beta 4 pita type Peter
jutsu tabu fader after that It's too noisy
[Music]
Enaga-kun, I think Peter's opening of the obi is perfect
ok ok So this is it.  For some reason,
yesterday I asked her what she wanted me to tell her, and she said, ``
Hey, I want to take some medicine.'' Hey, it
seems like I want a seat at work, so I
think I can put love to good use, so
I would like to share this with the viewers.  Please use it.Nemunemu Namai
name stand
medicine
Anu 6 sleepy
mediteam
Uzen This is also similar to English, it's an eye when it's aid I
chose it, but in German it's an eye d scene It's difficult to
say that's right, it's so nice
midi tune
Numuta drinking soil
abandoned
ok ok benefit
cute There are
a lot of people who want to be prescribed that medicine Doi
When do you think about it? Umm, I
love you too much, I love you too
much, and when I'm sick, ah Mr.
Flare,
white addiction
Artist of the 2000's
Hahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahaha\ha​ daddy too -- I'm
happy to hear you say things like ``I'm selling you.
'' But I need you to take some medicine, everyone.  Yeah, I'm going to
drink, yeah,
yeah,
what is JA
Gya -Gya
Mation
Rapuer Fent S If
all that Sche is next to your brother in this order, your brother will
be your older
brother.
In the Rapala era, something like this was used to
make a good husband, and it
would be good to put it in between and go bankrupt.It would be a good idea to put it in between.
Then, in 2017, I see that there was a
movement called Timan.That's
right.The words used for connection
are the same as Ando in English, but
yeah, well, it means after or after that.Yes, this
book name will be held in March next year.
Rough please
Fencer Surfer
Ah
Mach One
version r n How to
paint Bannam in 2018 made a new one
Neneun oval year pattern wool fabric September first pine
Pervia
[Music]
ana searched for
this then Caroboon It would be
better to change it together from the direction  It may have been a good idea,
but I
think that if you write in katakana, people tend to get used to Japanese, which is very similar to northern Japanese, so I thought it would be
better to have them get used to katakana or kanai.  I
think, but it's amazing. It's a great help. I'll
have to leave behind some special ways of reading, so it'll be
easier if that child supports me.
Maybe if I read all of this in Katakana Kita, I
won't be able to understand it.
- I can't say that. This is the first one. When I
read Katakana Pop, I don't think it would be easy to understand ``Delicious Delivery Nu Ainu
Harube Elf.'' Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa,
if I were you, I would
understand the song, but even with this, I don't understand Japan at all.
If it were a person, this would only sound like a strange word.Oh
yeah, I think Takanami reading is the
same in English as well.That
kind of tourist often comes to Pier Kinmae.I
used to work there, and there were Japanese people too.  I used to come here often and
the Japanese guy would try his best to change it to English for me,
but
even my co-workers at that job didn't have any at all.
But
unfortunately, it ends up sounding
like ``I see, I appreciate the effort.'' If it was a creative person, I would
understand Japanese, and if the Japanese
tried to speak English, I
would know how to pronounce it, but radish is okay.  Well,
anyway,
when everyone is buying and selling, I
feel like I want to force them to say something.
Now Mango
Chako. Thin Maa Oo Ja Bontan
Main store.
1 Turbota, oh yeah, Onta.
Erl. 1 letter.  It's
a little hard to read in some rubber There must be something
else like that,
unger, unter Honchar,
sound and romance, actually a good shower,
the moon is so calm, really,
phone, mawancha,
air in series with Asian eyes
Translated: Good evening,
come on,
Hon-chan Burn  a I said, ``
Come downstairs!'' It's
true that if I lived on the second floor with my mother in the morning, I
could eat that one time in the morning, so I said, ``Come downstairs.''
If you want to say that, you
can use it in that way as well.Ah,
that literal translation means it's amazing.Well, that's
what it means, so there are many ways to use it.
Chaananchanchichi, when did I
get it now? Hey
Imamaru Woncha,
this one didn't exist. That
little one dared to have long hair, and the result
of shooting was not good.
During that time, everyone's money was
good. I'm really lucky.  That's good, that's good, that's good. The
fried rice is also delicious. That last
one was good. Mmmmm bocha.
Oh, it's a
narrow and amazing senior place vote.
And the teacher who fights really praises me.
This is the boss type card Arthur. I
'm that kind of teacher.  Yo, I'm the
type of person who thrives when praised, so I'll
do the same for my students. Thank you so much for
making me so kind and giving you such a high rating. I'll see you
next time as a mother and son. I'm sure you're
well aware of Unhaku's legacy.  It's for the grave,
but I'm stupid to the grave. I've
written both of them, but
no one's a fool. There are many different types of [ __ ],
but I'm sure the one I chose is the one that's
better, for example.
There's
also the idea that there
's a German word that's similar to the English one, but I
think this one is the best.
The cup definitely gives me
goosebumps.Pete s No, it's like a shark. It's just
like a
cup. It's just like a cup. After the middle,
Fern. It's because it
's in command. It's amazing. It's difficult to be a
sleepy person. Sugar is also
amazing. It's amazing.
Ah
n oh
Ushihashi
Ban Burns, I'm
going to make it more and more in the shape of a shuba trend. The
Cafe Palace has come out again. Force 2
Rear
[Music]
Feeling
cool
Chinari  Yeah, Bell HIGH
BAY Let's
make a backup. Sister Ashiri Shimakkobawa
I'm the
best Bach I'm the best Campacer I'm already a coincidence.  I
couldn't do it.
Ash only learned Capella.
Even from the 5th level, it's a game called the bell. If you
go to the Ehime University soccer club and meet those Germans, it'll
be a German horse. It was in
Minami-ku. It
was Narnal Gite, that kind of thing.
When it comes to words, it's hard to reach those itchy places, right?
In everyday conversations, I
don't think I'll remember to destroy a booklet, so I don't think I'll basically use the pieces,
so
yeah, that's right. Is it useful to remember here?
So, when I was flying into those 4 breasts, I
learned about water from the good ajr day.
Hey, hey, yeah, this is no good. Hey, let's
teach this to all you idiots.
Don't play Princess Papi, Komura Oshiyama, and that.  Moon
Boat Flare
White Heritage Museum I was
told that my mother often calls her nails,
but I think she means Jell-O when she says "proposal".If you
keep that and say it in German, it
will probably be "tsu".  Dajansono
version 6 j is pattern 4 pattern
zoom Yeah, it pays, yeah, yeah, how about this too It's
hard to pronounce
haha
Chayama butter Monokeko rattan will fly away 5th
place That's
right, Ah and Tanoman
will play a lot if you put them together  Nyanbai, just a pattern
would be fine, but
if it was just worth it, I
'd probably add the word ``based on the usual'', but since it's natural
down, I guess
by adding this, it would
be natural.That's right.  The
two marks in front of the pattern are
numa-so-equivalent,
meaning that you should save up at that point,
but that's why you're merging, etc.
Bach
m is connected one by one, and each result is
based on Faddan.  Dissatisfaction with the pad
Southern Tsun's 2nd place No. 2
in that angry style
Pattern Jinon Fiber
Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa The remaining child who is ex-boyfriend
yan
Konohama eto is in it and is
the oldest in Annaka.  It sounds crazy, but
Gakken has someone close to them.So
then, I wonder if they're
doing it in 6 ways.Ayer, that's the
best way to make the heat stronger.This is
n't strong, it's just that it's strong, it doesn't hurt.Hmm.  Naru,
what's the
healing part, hmm, jal,
kuko, waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
than than than from from the from the end to the end of the words, I don’t know what to say at the end, but I don’t know what to say at the end.
Raise the number 3 in the range Dada
Groom Ah,
how many virtual links do you have
Apple cider vinegar 4th floor I'm sorry I don't have a rail tomorrow
L-shaped turn from the linker
Awesome
Autumn Danke is coming soon
Main eye herb f Oh,
everything  Are you reading this?
Aira and Mujou Janyamasho are
starting. They're
flying idols, they're flying f
8 exclusive white 3 a I have that problem, but
this one is different too, so I bought this one. The
lids of the waves and the feet are okay.  Yeah, yeah,
hmm,
who's that? 21 s Shushuban
Day measurement period Hmm
[Music]
Good,
good, so no one's right-hand man,
cloud,
but it seems like the aftermath
ha
chan to run 3
[Music]
Hmm, you can mix things up.  It's good, ah, Fal
, I don't think you're feeling this either.For
example, Sagan should lay down the ashes in the form of nuba.If you
say medicinal noodles, you're an idiot. Hey, calm
down, 9 water.  I drank Haneda 4 colors,
various connecting numbers, patterns, office pots,
picture books, etc. Nogeyama-chan, I can't see the year yet.
Ah, this is
how I did it. I wonder what the Van is. I should have attached it all to Bond.
Maybe.  [ __ ]!
Nowadays, you've been on a fa-down road without
ever leaving. Your stupidity has made him angry. You don't need a new one just yet. Hon-chan, I think it's
ok to have just the next trace of a frame just like the old one.  I
calculated the Meitetsu cherry blossoms, so I guess that's the
pattern. Luther is so
rich. He's a
German.
Well, in
that case, the master is called kope. Um, it
's between there, isn't it? Phenomenal
person. Fire, etc. Turn is also a word,
and it's grammatical, so just add it and
connect it, or in Japanese,
ah.
For example,
don't be silly, you idiot, take a calming medicine, and then work out what you're
saying.  It might be
strange to say that,
but it's true that it can't be used everywhere,
but
I took one medicine and went to sleep, and when I
tried to hook it up, I carried it in and it turned out to be
quite a mess and was barking in
German.  What I'm teaching is a little
different, isn't it?
Ah, parents and mothers are learning a lot.
Mr. Shimahana, who asked
himself, is a good student fan. It
's a job, but if you don't ask questions, you won't be able to
remember it.  I mean, no, that's because I passed
that language exam, right? It
's Dunkirk, right? I understand the way of being, and Nomi stands up. I
need a review, but
that's because I'm
not a real teacher.  Ah, it's
not the professionals who teach things like that,
but I'm
happy if you understand.The tsunami is already good.Next time, yeah, that's it.Here
's a picture in Austrian dialect that you don't have to memorize.Bach
Bedwetting
This is a German.  When I stop by, I ca
n't see the numbers. Only Austrians can understand it.
Probably
not, but most Germans can't understand it. So
this is it. How
many times have I trained this guy?
sess, dude, dude, okay a 4  Mirror
Yuminara Fitch listen 10
people spawn How is Cinder operating the Ito family?
At first there is a greeting.
There is an assassination. I want to live there.
It's crowded blue. It's
okay. 7 sems Eh?
1 It's a little strong dialect-like
a Gyuto Se
as Yeah, yeah,
Shirako, that's what I'm saying from here.
So-chan is hereditary in the village inheritance chance. I saw the game audio extract on the chance day.
To someone, it's Masataka Ichikani.
Look at me, Jas. ok
ok.  Next up is this one, I have
n't used any of the characters that specialize in it,
but yeah, it's beautiful.
Calloway, that Anne-Marie is so slow. Even though she
grew up, she didn't use a lot of
dialects. She wants to speak proper German,
but I'm the only one who's very deep.  I don't know how to speak ``dah'
' with the people who have been using it for a long time,
but I
don't know how to use it in Japan, but the way it's used is completely different. I do
n't know when to use it.  When I start, I'm
just going to start off with something.The
rest of the joy grapes are imaginary in the past.I
always use this down.For example, when I'm happy about something, or when I'm angry, I use this a little bit more.For
example, that
a, I had a lot of fun today.
If you say something like that, Oida
Fight Bumper Ai Ai and Ladder, I'm
putting it on
first.  I feel like I'm always a
pig who uses ``something'' in my
mother's stomach when I say positive,
but even when I'm 7 or older, I still use ``in my high school''.  I don't know what the
meaning
is, but when I use it, I don't know if it
's before or for the time being. There
are 3, but I ignore the meaning and
just put it anywhere.
Well,
by the way, I just put it at the beginning, and I also put it at the end.  It
's like, ah, ah, ah, ah, for example, umm, I learned a little while ago. I'm going to sow the seeds of a loop race, or I'm an oiler. But that's stupid, stupid, and I don't even talk about it often.  Idiot, you're such an idiot. In
this case, it feels like it's good. Well, I
want to try it. It's
close. I
just went home because I want to see it in chat.
Isshiki is definitely good. That's a jack,
seriously.  This might be correct, frankly, it
's a blunt usage.
Frankly a, you
're an unborder. Or, frankly, I
really had fun today. I'm
chewing on everything. 10 Oh, that
's right. It's a tower. It's a
dialect word used to express things.  Geibien,
Aoi Dai Aoi wakes up. The next one
means the best, but
Raibanrai version Love Lively 2 Raiban version 1
If you pronounce it a little more in that
dialect pack, you'll
become a king instead of ah.
No book life on
love Nice preparation bond branch This
used to be a bond to fashion etc. IE Nursery
school panelist Let's pumps 6 cases
Oh, I've been in 4 groups of free time so far, it's pretty good wow A
character-like Eho current episode 9
Speaking of the thunder version  Wow, those nice words are the best at the end. Ha,
DNA, I, 1, 2. Let's
meet up with the lightning address, Yua. I
think the words are quite childish and cute.
But
you can just say it, Fiatti. You can say it, Mouth Yaty Pepe.  It's a blue plug 2 p
8 b.
But this is the main gate, so it can
be used
as well. Ah, that's right. From today onwards, I'm going to be impressed again. It's
good because I can use it. No, it's
easy to grab. Pitti. Pitti. It's
cute.  That's what I think, but it's not good.If
you're a good person for children,
putu
putu.I
thought it was okay to use it, but it
doesn't get conveyed like this, right?It's the same thing every time.Sakura
Imazu Minami
It's like, ``Please give me a break.'' Come on,
Minnie, Despair, come on, let's get serious.
ds, san, 22, let's get on the
top day, n.
And shinhwa,
Betts, Sars, three, mm,
summer, this is umiri,
a proper German.  When you say it, it's
like, hmmm, service card.
But in dialect, it's completely different.
Even if it's not one, it doesn't sound like it's a year.
Ah, haha. Nice to meet you, yeah, yeah, yeah,
a. It's not a big deal.  Noha
a
Oisoepisobuu
What Police Whip so
Ludu boom boom
yeah
ose That's what it's like on the moon esperde Way
delicious treat e na e
Pyon-kei this How to
say it in German like German-chan
[Music]
Oi Spar Anre  S
Hoi Bar 5 Minutes
Market Ho
Nezu
Barbell
rax Orb s 4 f 4 Buu
Yeah, it's
totally different, this one is the one,
both of them seem to be good
Ah
[Laughter]
[Music] I do
n't understand, but the
fall of Makushita
Copy Car 2 Cup Pika Ear Copy Car Pack Pup
Pan
Pika Kopikatann You
can't hear the queen in the booboo sky
pou
dou
[Music] A
girl who looks like she's catching a dou Pika
Clicker Cop
to our I don't remember the point of view
Blair is on the street & hey, let's give it a little salt
Joy said that it was the day when I thought, ``
Well, just say yes.'' I
went to a memorandum store and found these words.Then, I do
n't care, I
think it would be cute if I used the last one.I said ``Good
job to the universe,'' and ``See you again, universe.''
That's right, boss, in a good year,
there are 6
in the Chocho Club, and in the bar reservoir year, it's an old hag, and the burger stars are 4
bars.
Yes, there are people who use the word "marriage"
in Austria. Well, yes,
c old woman.
Nu, I feel like I'm wearing Aso, so calm down, I'm going to call 6 more than 5. On April, I do
n't want to do it.
[Music]
Ah, that's internet slang. It
's a word that's hard to say. That's what Golden Enya Baba Enjoys Biaos Lake Ikeya
Aqua is all about.
Yukiho Carol Tasukacha Nishi Karatsu Nuts
50 Boots Ah Ha Anar Hmm what the hell is going on
with the listing Oh
well but in the end what's that touching senior A
Shiro-san I
'll teach you some long sentences but that's okay
Distribution I
won't do something like that
Genkaku Dawn  Turn
chain Wow, I'm trying hard to read it wide. It's
finally in front of me. Hobi first. A.
Those who advance to the ranking pro.
Thank you for watching A
few companies that will break up in winter n
Men's line It's not
raining, it's a bit of a shasha Ray fan Ah
Bonnie Unfair Bunya d I
wonder if it's a Chanel registration please Pi I'm
almost going to see it I wonder if it's
okay to be Abu nyan I wonder
if Artie Aya  Nya a Keep Hot
water no good a
Please give me a high rating
Ginmiya Gymedia Dinda
Omeme ada No good Daimyomine
Wait for my husband to eat, come back tomorrow Money
Safety marbles I caught a game.
Reader
Ah, this volume is also aluminum. 3 It looks like it's steamed with sand. The
main text is dog. I
know it's long, but let's read it from the beginning.
Men's festival 2 cars.
Miyata downloader, Huh,
game en, daum,
Roar, older
sister, Aokko,
raised beader,
h feeling, gyan, v $ meow
[Music]
Anarar, the
only time I'm doing this, well, it's
only when I'm reading here,
is like Nausicaa from the Valley of the Wind.  It feels
good, I had a crush on Pera and Girlfriend 4 and Ross
Barronlegdale.I
read that and there are a lot of oops on the rear.If you don't
mind doing that, I
think it would be difficult to have two of these fly out during the distribution.
By the way, I
saw that person in the chat, and they
said that the font was hard to read,
but this one is really easy to
read for someone like me,
but what I'm trying to say is that when you
use a marker, you can't use a marker.  When I first started studying Japanese, I
couldn't read Japanese at all, even though it looked like it was written in very nice handwriting.At first, I could only read that font that looked like it was on a computer.Even
now, it's still a little difficult for me, even in academic Japanese.  I
did all of these because
Kiyama-chan picked them out in advance, so
there are some things that I dreamed about,
so that's pretty much it.I'm so
thankful
for Roman masturbation.I know it's difficult for people who don't use it,
but it's still easy.
No, that girl, hey, yeah,
there's something more difficult than this,
and it's called Shurei Push. Cliff is that round.
Kazuko. I know how to write in a way that connects fluff, fluff, and fluff. Then, this writing will be Tanna. 2 Hmm,
wait.  There was something like that based on ``a'', but I wonder if
it's a thing, like going to school,
etc.
At first, you
learn how to write this normal 6, but
then you
have to write it in a way that connects it properly, or you'll
get scolded.  Well then, I've got my panties on. I
was on my way home.
Well, I guess I'm going to go crazy too. Well, I
'm going to go to the coast guard for now, but aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa's the
moon that held that thing I was
born in
German.  Yoni-san tries to sell it, but when a
certain Shoji hits him, he
doesn't cry too much, I guess, hmm, yeah, I'm
sure animals are also called one weapon, but I
did a little research on it.lives
web, ah,
uhm, hey, service car.I
want to play it, I want to hear it, and I'm looking forward to it.  I want to go, I want to go, I want to go, I want to go, I want to go, I want to go, I want to go, I want to go, I want to go, I want to go, I want to go, I want to go, I want to go, I want to go, I want to go, I want to go, I want to go, I want to go, I want to go, I want to go, I want to go, I want to go, I want to go, I want to go, I want to go, I want to go, I want to go to this country.
Well, it's mostly
in cursive, but I
think it's more difficult to read, so
it's Japanese, but I'm looking forward to the English I want to go to.  I can't write it
because I do
n't have it. Don't you know that when you write a rose or a signature
of someone who doesn't have it, you want to write it? That's right, that person can't come in and buy the signature. Wow, I
had a grudge against the elementary school students that it wasn't written in cursive. No, I'm
leaving soon.  In other words,
if we were adults, we'd be so confused that we wouldn't even be able to sign our names.There's no
one like Kawakami who
actually wrote their names together.At
first, we, the gymnastics students, wrote them in blank
notes.  I thought I'd write it down in my body,
but when I got back home with a bad hit, I thought, ``I'm
going to change my child,'' and it seems like it's a down
menu, but I've stopped thinking about how old I am.It's
okay, I don't have to worry about anything in particular.That's when I
came that day.  If you
write that block 0, it's already a perfect eating tale
. You should change it today. You were a
good student.
Gather around. By arthur Hey,
hey, there's no applause
. It's because c is amazing. e
No, not really, but I tried to do my best.Did you remember
anything about chat visits and viewer visits?Nia has a
monster elf of course, everyone.Subscribe to that Ooki Announcer's
channel.  Ga Takanashi
Player's channel registration and high evaluation Thorough
Thank you for the lift Minu's Eyu rush
Rear sports with ace sports 4-person friend piece
Disco chain cross Mitre also
Floating worm next season future
Genetic technique rice tea escort Megupo 5 Okay  Existing.
After this, someday the two of us will collaborate again.
Please let us know how you like each other by registering.
07:00
anoano It's dangerous. Ae great boots.
Fields are double.  Dogging w In a long
-established signboard with Kanagi,
this quickly healing fan
rest and that pa are a
little blurred in an instant, but it's
cold
Yellow Ah
Ah Ah Ah Ah, Ah.
Corridor
Somehow, the legacy of those kids is being streamed This is what he
said at the end Ah
Senki 4 team lead
Service addition club channel ae
burst in It & Fran
Twitter
Addedness Tomorrow is always
said twitter Well, I forgot.  Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh  I
wonder if it's too much.
Please eat all the roads with different accents.
When you finish the return, it's aaanyanpana.
There is that saying that if you eat down corn before apples, you will stay healthy. That's
right.  A word that is often used:
Difficult case.
What is the Japanese proverb?
Manipulation Pudong. I can't imagine it. It's also lava in English.
Useful app. Day.
Keep the
doctor. Cheer. There was a comment that apples don't need a doctor,
but I wonder if that's wrong.  Ah, that
's right. That's right.
That's right. That's right. It doesn't take a single employee to learn cryptography.
Winter sleeps and speaks Japanese. Yeah,
yeah, I'm
glad you taught me some amazing Japanese.
Yabu 2: Japanese is good, isn't it?  Eh, Aibatake
Claire, that Japanese proverb is fast.
Detailed
Japanese proverbs. Register ahkah.
Do you have any favorite sayings?
8For example,
Mercy is not for the good of others. It's called Ah Meguri Meguri. It's called
Noho Onna. It's
something useful.  Nah, that's nice. Um,
it's a skill that I often forget and remember, but there are quite a few
people who only remember things like, "Being
kind to others is not for the sake of others."
It's a proverb that says, ``I'm sorry,'' but I couldn't
wrap my head around the endless optometry story, so it
was difficult.  I guess I did. I
know the truth, but I know what you're saying,
but I think I've lost my concentration.
So, what's the matter with Bach? It's
probably just falling down on me.  Do you
know the legacy of anaa, thank you very much? anaa,
mira, the comedian does the standing ceremony
at the end, that's it,
archi, curie, swoosh, dress up
day, you
said it like Kim Haebu, ah, we
had a wonderful talk about Wonder Habo,
angel.  3 Voice actor, ah, the last thing before Bidar is
me.
Nah, that's
it. Yeah, yeah.
Goodbye Landmon
That's why
Gutenacht