[Music]
so
how
[Music]
[Laughter]
hello everybody
i put out a new song cover did you hear
it yes yes yes
[Music]
i was safely safely
distributed
safely um
safely
safely released after all
um
don't tell genma that i actually saw uh
one more mistake in the video but didn't
tell them because i didn't want to
re-upload it again
[Music]
no one will notice no one will know this
um
honestly i don't i don't really mind um
jackman is pretty strict um though when
she sees the mistake she's like we gotta
fix this like you know
lyric mistakes
usually it's like lyric mistakes like
when something is uh written incorrectly
or so um but i i i i kept it secret
[Laughter]
yeah it's so good this is nothing too
important
yeah so
who
i noticed the mistake it ended
i wonder if genma is watching this right
now
maybe not who knows who knows
and welcome everybody
so my new song cover was
cinderella
but
not the original normal version but the
giga first night remix
yeah
and
if you listen to the original
then you might notice then that the
original
is actually uh slower but
um
yeah so for example the the verse
i think everything is slower but
especially the verse is really
noticeable
um because and also the key is different
i think yeah
i think the key is different i don't
know if it was lower or higher now but
it was different and the the the verse
um yeah the tempo is much faster
so originally i think it was like
[Music]
maybe even slower but then in this
version it goes like
it's so fast why isn't you cover private
it's not private you got the wrong link
um i uploaded i uploaded i updated
twitter with the new link i don't know
where you got the old link is my is the
old link linked somewhere
except twitter
it's not private
i mean it's private
no it's still just the old link is uh
private because uh we had to fix
re-upload but check my channel there's a
public one now
um
yeah plea please
see people can only find
the old link for some reason even though
it's in my channel um so uh everybody
please retweet
the new link on twitter that would be
helpful
[Music]
um
yeah twitter edit button would be nice
or more a simpler fix than that but i
understand why you you can't no i mean
i think you could do it uh um switching
out videos on youtube before they are
uploaded like reusing the same slot
and just switching out the video would
have been perfect
i mean
i think you know i thought maybe they
wouldn't do it because what if it's a
completely different video but i think
it's before after uploading that would
be troublesome but before uploading
uh before releasing something before
premiere so i think it would make sense
because youtube's um automatic sensors
are gonna go through it anyway and see
if there's some different tracks there
that are copyrighted or whatever so if
it's not publicized yet i think it would
make sense
but yeah that is um
too useful to be
made into reality youtube doesn't do
things that are useful yeah
anything that is useful no throw it out
of the window
thank you guys thank you very much
[Music]
to be honest
now
i know
i know you guys know that i'm always
worried about new things like
you know when it comes to like
uh for example new outfits i'm worried
how you guys will like it
um
but to be honest i was really worried
for this one i still am um
and this time it doesn't even matter
what you guys are saying because i
personally
have to say this i have to say this
i personally i
am unhappy
um
how my voice sounds in this one
[Music]
i don't know what it is
um
i discussed it with my mixer
but the acoustics sounded so weird to me
when i first got the mix so i tried to
figure out what it was and
but
i i'm bad with words and bad with like
like i don't know i don't i don't know
how to mix
music and and [\h__\h] so i don't really
know like what it could be you know so
uh i i tried something that's right like
saying yeah maybe we can do this and
that the acoustics it sounds it sounds
like because this was the first
song cover that i recorded after
um moving my
my room layout and
at the same time removing one piece of
furniture and i noticed in general that
in this room right now it sounds more
um empty
so i thought maybe
in my recording of my voice that was
reflected by the acoustics sounding as
if i'm singing in an empty room you know
what i mean so i mentioned that but um
[Music]
it seems like i don't know nothing could
be done about it i don't know maybe it
was maybe it's just me i don't know but
i think it sounds really weird compared
to my other
song covers which i don't understand
because i use the same microphone and i
use the same mixer and i'm just not i'm
just i'm gonna be honest i'm not really
that happy about it
but i also just could not
figure out
what sounds wrong to me
i don't know what it is so i could not
fix it
um
[Music]
i don't know what it is i don't know i
don't know i just don't know
[Music]
i know
um
right it sounds a bit empty verified
some some lines at least i mean for me i
hear it
almost everywhere
um
i can hear but it doesn't sound exactly
bad just but different
and i don't like it
i don't like it but i couldn't do
anything about it and um
yeah
um i mean it's not so bad that you
couldn't listen to it i
guess
i just hope that even if i don't like it
that you guys will like it
please
[Laughter]
maybe it's more noticeable for headphone
users i tried you like listening to it
on different headphones
different like sound sources my
headphones and my laptop and my phone
and
um
it still sounded the best on my
headphones i think it sounded worse on
my phone
and and on my laptop
so
i don't know
sounds out of 10 on my headphones really
well i mean you guys i think it's
different for you guys because you
you don't
you're not the owner of the voice so you
hear it differently
yeah
um
but
on another positive note
i love the music video
uh and the art really cute i didn't uh
say who made the art until now because i
wanted to keep it a little bit of a
surprise um not for any specific reason
i just don't want to you know make
everything
so open
uh
it's by someone called goto
i linked
i i linked their twitter account on
twitter
uh
on on on on this
streams tweet but i will also um
tweet it out again properly later
when i tweet about the music video again
um
[Music]
so um you know with these
deco songs tekonina songs
um usually with like you know vampires
cinderella and all the others that are
there usually there's like a pattern of
what the music video looks like and what
the art looks like and
usually i don't quite follow it
[Music]
vampire was still kind of similar but i
didn't do the same pose you know while
um the others who cover the song usually
do the same pose like they get the same
pose in their illustration
for the thumbnail and and the same kind
of video and all that for vampire we
still kept it kind of simple um but i
did a different pose there and and for
all the other songs like uh
you know you know also for um
uh
goodbye declaration that that was not a
dick on inno song but it was also one of
those songs that
uh
everyone had like the same kind of music
video right but then i was like i want
something different and then uh united
made that whole animated video right
so stuff like that um and for cinderella
there was also like
a pattern um
not only for the normal cinderella but
also for this one even though this one
has been barely covered
uh this remix version has been barely
covered so there is not so many examples
um
but i once again did not follow the
original idea i i made something similar
but i said
i don't want the same dress so i don't
want the same pose and all that i just
want it to be like kind of similar and
then uh goto sand drew me in this cute
cute cute cute uh do i have a picture of
it downloaded i think so
in a cute but simple cinderella not from
cinderella but it's just a cute simple
dress here there it is
big
there there she is sitting
killed with twin tails
and uh
the glass shoes
gotta know
um
[Music]
yeah feet and glasses glasses is of
first
i mean i had sunglasses before but
glasses
piano with glasses i think it's all a
first
how do you make them
[Music]
i think it's the first so i'm looking
forward to fan art please please fan art
of this place
[Music]
please i want fan art of this this this
this this
cute cute dress
cute cocktail cocktail dress
yeah yeah yeah
cinderella
[Music]
um now
we're having a little chit chat i want
to talk some more about um
cinderella
um
did did that that the fast
part
[Music]
ah that one was actually really
difficult i was stumbling over my words
and
for the most part i got takes done that
are perfect but there's just one line
that i for the love of god i could
no matter how many times i try it i
could not get it perfect now you guys
maybe have not noticed but maybe
japanese
listeners have noticed
[Music]
wait it was um in the beginning
uh
let me let me see
[Music]
it's actually the first line yeah
there's a line the first line that goes
like
uh
if you listen to it
it sounds like i'm singing
uh
what does it sound like wait let me
listen in
[Music]
i could not
no matter how many times i tried i could
not get the wool in there and
i tried really hard that was one of the
best takes
[Laughter]
and i mean if it's like a slower song
then you can always cut parts and then
just put smaller words in between where
you thought that sounded better in
different takes but when it's this far
fast you cannot
do it that simply
it's uh
an incredible
tempo and amount of words in
that amount of time
[Music]
yeah that was difficult
[Laughter]
[Music]
but once i start to record like
sometimes when i don't record maybe
maybe it sounds good but then when i try
to record it i i try to you know i focus
also on
um
singing properly and when you have to
focus on all these things like singing
loud and proper and clear and in the
right key and bleeba blue and emphasize
everything properly then
then
that's when i can't i can't get that
damage
right anymore
yeah some vocaloid songs they are just
not made to be sagged by a human person
or even by a phoenix
sounds like macarena the rhythm
i guess so
i think also the combination of words
there just [\h__\h] me up even even
if like you know because i got the other
lines right it's just this one line
because of the combination of sounds
i was just like i can't
wait
[Music]
and then speed that up to cinderella's
feet
[Laughter]
[Music]
now you can't unhear it oh don't worry i
don't think you'll hear it if you try to
listen to the music
yeah so
uh
yeah so what i was saying is i love the
music video i love the art i'm not happy
with my voice i love the song originally
the instrumentals are so cool
and uh
yeah i had troubles with that one part
one more thing
uh the reason
why i chose
this
version
over the original
there's actually
um
a reason and it's not that because
everybody covers the normal one that's
not the reason
i like the normal one too
that's not that's not the reason
[Music]
i
yeah i really really like giga
[Music]
but
um
at least around the time where
i requested to sing
like i requested permission to sing the
song
um you know since the the
original stills from dickel it comes
like the permission request goes to take
on nina and not to giga um
and
um
i
i have i
let's just say i wanted to cover
uh giga songs in the in the past or even
make maybe one day make an original with
giga
um
but
[Music]
uh it just was not meant to happen
uh
ever until now like so and when i say
until now it's not like i have
this opportunity now
so when i saw there's there's a there's
a remix of dekonina
song with giga i was like
[Music]
[Laughter]
i mean that's that's a roundabout way of
singing a giga song right
i'm smart right it's a loophole exactly
it's a loophole um
i love both i love both deco and i love
giga so that was absolutely perfect for
me
um and i think giga made something
really cool out of this song
um like i love the giga sound it's kind
of like a
uh
i don't know how to describe it but
ah the the cello the [\h__\h] cello and
the instrumental did you hear that the
cello oh my god
so good
then
i wanted
[Music]
now i've seen recently um
kelly
cersei
working with giga so maybe one day
maybe one day
[Music]
yeah i can only pray and hope
maybe one day i actually actually um i
didn't think it would happen but
um yeah wicked wicked was cool um
it was pretty cool
no no no no no no no i'm not leaking
anything no it's just wishful thinking
just wishful thinking a chill yeah
there's a chew in the in this in the sun
cover
did you catch it
it's not like an obvious like choo choo
it's uh you gotta you gotta catch it be
ready for it otherwise you won't you
won't know what just happened
when i first listened to the vocaloid
version i thought she was um
not kissing but
that making this sound
you know like um being you know i don't
know what to call the sound
[Music]
not not a pec i mean yeah the
tsk sound a tongue clicking yeah i
thought she was clicking her tongue yeah
so that's also how i recorded it but
that sound is really difficult to record
like
yeah so i recorded it like that but then
uh
my mixer was like yo uh i need i need a
several several kisses recorded and i'm
like oh that was supposed to be a kiss i
guess it i guess maybe it was supposed
to be a case
so it changed from a tongue click to a
kiss
originally i recorded a tongue click
yeah
but it could quit no
release all the juice
no that's very embarrassing i was
feeling very embarrassed when i just
literally recorded five different kisses
and sent it to the mixer but you guys
get kisses all the time you guys hear
kisses all the time
but i felt like i felt the way i felt
when
um i first started to give out kisses
for my super chats
back then i was still very embarrassed
about it
so this is how i felt
[Music]
uh
no i will never
i will not no no i refuse
i refuse
ah
oh
oh yeah yeah so um this was originally
not even planned but it was possible
thanks to the artist uh goto
making
um
or sending over art data that was like
separated in layers nicely even though
even though i didn't ask for it um
but they did and therefore lina right
now who was editing the video again once
again she's my um song cover music video
creator
she saw that and she was like the layers
are actually separated so nicely i could
animate the whole thing slightly and i
was like
oh no yes please yes please and it looks
so good like the music video in general
is still kind of kept more or less
simple but i think it's it looks so cool
with the sparkles and the reflection on
the black ground
and uh the glowy white fonts
and all that
[Music]
i think it looks really cool really
elegant and it fits it fits the song i
think yeah
i told but i know and when
when she asked like what what what i
want the music video to sound like it to
look like i said to be honest um it
doesn't have to be like the original
again so
you can take inspiration from that but i
don't really mind whatever you do
so what i know is like oh i have an idea
and then she started working on it so
perfect i love the animation looks so
good it looks so good
yeah now please please praise her for
that i don't know how much time it takes
to animate something like that
in life 2d life to d ish
animation
[Music]
i did not see it
i love the video it looks so cool i was
so happy when i saw it and and she
helped me with thumbnails and all that
too she made the title font and all that
like a logo basically it's basically a
logo so cool
um
she's been helping me with uh i think
for vampire as well she made also the
thumbnail
and the logo
amanda that's got recycle you're the
best you're the best right now really
like originally i only asked for music
video but but then that i was like right
now i'm trying to make a cool thumbnail
but i suck it doesn't look good can you
help me and then she said yeah no
problem i'll throw something together
and it looks so cool i think ah the
first one that was that was not uh
she helped me with all the thumbnails
for
uh for the for the hinotoni remixes as
well i think yeah
she gave me the psd files i rearranged
it a little bit but yeah mostly it was
her her ideas and all that for vampire
and the hinotoni remixes and cinderella
just listen to the song thank you
i'm glad you like it the stars circulate
around you yeah that's that's cool isn't
it you mean the one on the bottom i
noticed that too the the the bouncy
circulation going on there i'll be
trying to from c-e-s-e-a to document
what
thank you away from from singapore is uh
sgd is that singapore
you're traveling from singapore
singapore is so fancy yeah
yeah
yes yeah right
i want to visit singapore someday
[Music]
nice
just listen to the song thank you
the one thing
the one other thing that i i
is a bit sad about this song
song cover is that it's so short
deco nina has been making so many short
songs and then i think the remix is even
shorter
wait was that shorter
the remix is two minutes 22 seconds
and cinderella
dickle
[Music]
yeah the original is 2 minutes 36
seconds while the remix is 2 minutes 23
seconds so it's even shorter
so that was that was a little bit like
i don't really
i don't know if i
i don't know it feels so so short right
not only because it's like such a fast
wrap
but also because it actually is short
so that was a bit um
uh sad i feel like there's potential for
more but maybe some people
appreciate the shortness of the song
i don't know
it maybe it makes you want to loop it
even more because just it ended so fast
right i think i can see that
now
[Music]
that's exactly it
i wonder if that's what dickon nina son
had in mind when making all these short
songs
maybe
wow maybe maybe they think it's more
loopable
[Music]
or i don't know what i wonder what it is
i would like to hear
the reason for it
but for for this song because i just
enjoyed it so much
the the giga remix i just love it so
much i wish it was longer [\h__\h] ah
release the longer cut please
i need a longer version of it
i'm for sure gonna be looping it please
do
not
know
[Music]
is like double the length
of cinderella giga remix
[Music]
choose only version no one needs to
choose only version
what all right
[Music]
choo choo only version
where did i save it um
here
all right
here it is i see uh there's definitely
gonna be people clipping this especially
putting
um
stop
that's right repeats
[Laughter]
that's what can see
well see now it's uh now it belongs to
everyone now it's for everybody
everybody gets a piece
of the truth
[Music]
it had to be fast kisses though because
like that part um it's like the music
drops for a moment
and then immediately goes into the
chorus i think so it had to be a short
short case
yeah
i had to work so
so i just watched the envy thank you
dangerous like a train with all the ah
kisses
[Music]
just to choose no that sucks i don't
want i don't want that put more of my
voice in there more
what
the 10 clicks no there was only one one
or two ton clicks originally anyway but
that wasn't part of the original
like full full recording and i'm not
gonna show you guys that one yeah that's
that's unedited
i'm dreaming of churches yeah
[Music]
and by the way
are you have you noticed on the
on the top right
here this one
it's a rhino made um
just like a
version of me sitting and chilling there
and it looping it doesn't loop
seamlessly though
doesn't look seamlessly but it looks
cool
i'm just chilling there it's like a
animated thumbnail isn't that super cool
it's so cool
now i don't know afterwards i want to
upload on twitter again like i have
released a song cover i don't know if i
should use this one or the
or
or the the preview or a cut of the
chorus again in an unblurred version
but this is cool
didn't have something like this before i
think this is the first time
that
in my
any of actually i think it is in any of
my music videos and i made a lot until
now considering originals and covers
this is the first time that i had a
like a live 2d style animation you know
we had the universe style animation but
that's not life2d style right so this is
like a first actually and i want to try
it more often but i'm not sure what to
request from the artists in order to
make that possible
i guess i just need a lot of separated
layers but i'm not sure like what
exactly
maybe maybe rhino you can tell me what
what's what's
uh helpful to animate it like that and
then i'll remember that and tell
tell artists in the future that i'm
commissioning
yeah
yeah yeah as mentioned koto-san just did
it maybe because that's just how they
work
normally
i didn't ask for it but they just made
it like this so that's really cool
[Music]
they will understand when you say to
them it will make it to laughter
i don't think every artist would
understand that because not every artist
has worked with their illustrations like
that before
like made them to be animated not
everyone did
so
it would help to have like a proper
um
explanation but i have a i think i have
a rough idea because i mean i i draw
myself too
and i think i understand like um
like
like you would want for example
in order to make the the twin tail and
the back move
the more you have
uh
like
you know of even the parts that are
hidden behind the head
the more you have of that
the more you can move it around and
swing it
yeah
you know what i mean
anyway
anyway what else would i did i want to
say oh my god
guys we're done with the cinderella
topping because today i want to tell you
something random
um i i
someone someone was ringing my doorbell
okay and i thought it was amazon because
i was waiting for an amazon package and
i opened the door
and it was not amazon it was a lady
with
a puppy
standing in front of my door
and asking me if i'm this and that
person i'm like
no
or like if she's here and i'm like no
[Music]
and
and she was like oh but she said she
lives here and i'm like
no i live i live alone here there's no
one else here i don't know what you mean
but cute puppy you have there and then
she got like all confused because i
think she was supposed to you know meet
up with someone
and um
she was trying to figure it out on her
phone trying to contact the person
and she was like because i was like and
your dog is so cute she was like you can
cut the dog
and i started petting the puppy and it
was so cute she said it was only three
months old puppy so young it still had
all the puppy fluff to it
yeah
my cat stayed away though but the puppy
was so sweet like i've met other puppies
before that are very shy but this one
was very very like sweet and didn't like
attack me or did not lick me all over i
don't i don't like when dogs do that
this one um maybe
tried to
munch my hand very slightly once but not
really
um
i won't say what breed it was because of
privacy but it was a very popular dog
breed and it was a puppy of it
i wish i was rubbing and touching and
petting the doggo all over
yeah so cute oh my god it's so so so so
friendly
[Music]
i don't
um like
uh how long she has a dog how old and so
on and i said oh i only have kitties and
she said oh i have cats too
so i got interested because hearing she
has cats and dogs uh i asked like how
old the cats are and she said oh they're
six seven eight years old or so and the
dog is just a puppy which i think is
really interesting because like i'm
considering when my cats are older and
and i have more time
to get a dog myself now i don't have the
time for it but one day i want a dog too
and i was worrying about you know
combining dogs with cats so i asked her
if they get along and she said
[Music]
not that well yet
still
but i mean it's just three months you
probably just got the puppy so gotta
give it some time
and i think if you um
if you get a dog
and you already have cats it should
definitely be
a puppy
i think
or just a really really open friendly
old dogo but i think i think i've read
that with a puppy
the cats will get used to it easier i
don't know
i don't know
it depends on the cat and the dog yeah
they all have different crazy
personalities some cats just really
don't like any dogs at all probably
my dog was grown up but it was always
nice with my cats yeah you weren't lucky
that's a territorial yeah that's why i'm
so worried but i will wait i will wait a
long time for it
uh
can someone time out that person who
keeps on
writing the same message in spanish
i think it's the same message i can't
read spanish and you keep on asking me a
question maybe put it into google
translate
don't understand
i will not learn spanish no matter how
many times uh
you read the same message i will not be
able to pick it up within that time
maybe one day i'll be fluent in spanish
but it won't happen right now
unfortunately
it's a nice message i i guess so it says
something like hermosa which i think is
pretty or so but i don't understand what
you're saying
no need to spam it
no need to spam it i'm sure it was a
compliment but don't spam
okay
thank you
gracias
yes
[Music]
[Laughter]
i see everything
so yeah that was the dog story
um
oh yeah and a gym so yesterday to be
honest i wrote on twitter that i had
uh sore muscles
but
honestly it wasn't even that bad
and i felt like i couldn't even go to
the gym again
but
somebody
wrote to me on twitter that if i have
sore muscles after the first time
working out i should i should um wait
until the snow muscles are gone not
immediately go to the gym again
so i was like okay i guess i'll wait
um
i know maybe maybe uh
maybe i'll go tomorrow
uh what am i doing tomorrow i'm not
gonna have time tomorrow i need to look
at my schedule
um
picture but i'm i'm i'm i'm i am
actually motivated
it was
wasn't that bad it was actually once you
once you get started once you get there
and once you get started
then
it's actually kind of
fun a little bit yeah i was watching uh
on something on my phone on youtube
because there was like a little
slot where i could put my phone on
as long as i have something to watch
everything's cool
yeah and the meter is going up and all
that is pretty motivating
but the roaring machine is so exhausting
like um
i mean i i i i'm proud and surprised i
made it for 10 minutes but
uh with 10 minutes i barely looking at
the meters i barely got a fire because
like with 10 minutes rowing pretty
strongly i got a thousand meters right
and then on the bike i was for what five
minutes and i didn't even put that much
into it but i got uh 2.76 kilometers
right
it actually still went on after that i
took that picture
so in much less time with much less
effort on the bike i got way further
than with rowing
rolling is
tough man
yeah it's much harder you barely get
anywhere
holy [\h__\h] i know 2.7 kilometers is also
nothing i was already exhausted but
don't i said don't roast me guys i said
fox70 did you not listen i saw a lot of
you guys roasting me um even though i
said don't roast me yes what the [\h__\h] is
wrong with you guys why are you roasting
me if you roast me like that i'm just
gonna feel embarrassed about my
accomplishments and not share them
anymore but i said this was my first
time the first time i ever went to a
[\h__\h] gym of course it was my first
time working out in a million [\h__\h]
years my first time in the gym of course
i'm not suddenly gonna go five million
kilometers
it's not logical isn't that [\h__\h]
logical
you just you're just like hahaha i can
do better than you or like even though
even those people who make fun of me
probably don't even go to the gym and
can't you don't even work out themselves
and even if you do work out yourself
then you don't have a right to
to roast a beginner like me okay okay
look i have to start somewhere i told
you guys i was so proud of myself to
share that and i said yo i know this is
not much but for me it's much and i'm
surprised i even got that far
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
what's going on i was just
yelling at my
bad bad chickens
[Music]
thank you
thank you thank you
thank you thank you i went for the for
the giga version reina i know you did
the original version you guys should
listen to dana's original version
dana the giga version is so fast
i i had a really hard time um
wrapping that part
holy [\h__\h]
then i bought really nice beach sandals
for our vacation
or that not really beach sandals but
just sandals
we need more twin tail cats yes and what
about the glasses though what about the
glasses i'm personally
someone who does not really care about
glasses and i don't it does not get me
going like other people
[Music]
but i guess some people are happy about
those glasses the reason i have glasses
in that picture is because the girl in
the original illustration also has
glasses
it seems to be a theme you know
cinderella with glasses apparently is a
thing
i don't really care about glasses unless
the sunglasses
[Music]
yeah but twin tails i can i can
understand i have a
i have a liking for twin tails as well
all kinds of twin towels low twin tails
high twin towels middle twin tails half
twin tails
and so on many twin tails
[Music]
especially half twin tails i used to
wear my hair a lot in half twin tails
you know what half twin tails are you
just have twin tails at the very top of
your head and the rest is just going
down
and i know it maybe sounds weird but
it's cute
looking shambles
no matter how many times she cites that
a paragraph to me she will not be able
to convince me about the greatness of
glasses because i just don't care for
glasses
i mean
[Music]
actually that's not true i sometimes
sometimes in the past um i would wear
fashion glasses too
um like round ones round cute ones
i liked those um but i think they didn't
look so good on me personally i like
them on other cute girls more okay those
round cute glasses i can get behind
[Music]
but the ones like like you know the girl
in cinderella is wearing is like those
those are like really nerdy glasses
those are so nerdy
aren't they nerdy
[Music]
i think that's on purpose i think this
cinderella girl is supposed to be an
otaku
that's the best part
[Music]
dirty glasses are cool too
yes
like there's
nerdy fashion glasses too right
um
that
fashionable glasses are also supposed to
look nerdy at the same time now those
look cool also on the wrap person
but i don't know
it really depends on who's wearing them
and and what the design is i think um
yeah it really changes
depending on that but you know um now uh
since reyna is here they know you're
still here and it's still here i have
something to show you
uh did you guys see
on twitter
then i said i had something terrifying
to show
[Music]
terrifying and horrifying
have you seen it
i think reyna already left she's
probably back to looping my song cover
understandable have a nice day
[Music]
what do you think it is
a dropped egg
a scale
it wasn't a puppy no this is not
terrifying what the [\h__\h] no that that is
that i told the lady that was the
highlight of my day
she like kept on apologizing because
it's awkward and then you know that she
got the wrong room number and i tried to
help her and all that but she was like
i'm so sorry i'm so sorry this is
awkward i'm sorry um i said no don't
worry about it i love puppies your puppy
is so [\h__\h] cute and you're the
highlight of my day like literally i'm
so happy that you rang my doorbell
[Laughter]
i told her
i was so happy oh my god the moment i
closed the door i jumped back into my
living room like look how cute cute cute
yeah but i did wash my hands because i
thought my my cats might not like the
dog smell
wait we'll get to we'll get to the
terrifying thing in the moment
uh
there was one more thing i just forgot
that i wanted to say what was it
[Music]
ah about the gym uh there was one thing
i wanted to say
the stream
i saw
some of you guys were worried
about it
but i purposefully made the thumbnail
so that it doesn't look like you know
one of those
sad announcements
and
would i really announce something like
that like so suddenly like without any
waiting time like in 15 minutes i'm
doing an announcement
like i don't know i thought it was
noticeable that it wasn't something too
serious
you guys just worry about anything don't
blame me for that don't blame me for
your drama
i mean the [\h__\h] that was colorful if i
had something serious to say or if i
really wanted to bait you then the phone
bill would just be in black and white
but look at the gradation look at the
happy face of me on the side
[Music]
of
it
[Music]
this was nothing
and i was just really excited to tell
you guys i couldn't wait anymore until
you know a stream i wanted to tell you
guys immediately and i thought for me
not only for me but i fought for
the cave people who know me well
that this was something big not only for
me but also for you
i fought for uk of people
for the people who know me well and love
me then you guys would be like holy [\h__\h]
this is huge
she went to the gym
what
this is huge
did you guys not think so you know me
you know i don't work out and and i have
back problems and i've always been like
and as suddenly i go to the gym and i'm
motivated about it and proud of myself
that's huge
that's huge and that deserves its own
stream
[Music]
um
yeah so it's because of my back so uh
one more thing i wanted to say there's
so much to talk about i'll i'll be
getting rid of all my talking topics
today and never talk about anything else
this week
um
uh
the sound cover with nana g
is coming up next week um there was a
little bit of a
problem with the music video i think
and
uh they're a little bit slow over there
with uh
checking and fixing apparently
gemma is freaking fast
man
when i get a video to check genma genma
checks it in
like five hours and it's ready to go
yeah
it's like so speed
japanese side very slow takes days and
days and days
um but it's actually okay because i i
wanted to
um time the two song covers
that it's at least not in the same week
so the sun covered with nanjing is
coming out next week
[Music]
um
don't know the exact date
but it will be next week maybe end of
next week or so on nenety's channel
because it's a song cover that she
um
organized and all that
yeah
finally
[Music]
and uh
we are doing
uh
a collab together the week after that as
well not in the same week because nancy
is busy
[Music]
but in a week after that we're also
doing uh
a collaboration don't know what we will
do but we were like let's just do
something
new
[Music]
what are you talking about
and considering that the energy
uh sound cover with me still needed some
time
uh and that mine was already ready
that's why i suddenly put it out today
suddenly
and she's everyone's wife no my wife
i mean okay but she will divorce all of
you one day and only have me left anyway
[Music]
energy channel both the collab and the
song cover i think cause like we did the
that horror game collab on my channel
the other day
but i do want to do an energy song cover
on my channel as well uh one day one day
in this year
i will not do it immediately though
because i have some other things i want
to do first for example sun covered with
rain
i gotta start working on that now
because um
uh we want to put that out during our
visit to the maldives
which is next month oh my god
rhino i'll be hitting you up for another
music video yoda school
yeah uh
i think we decided on what to sing but
i'm not sure do i really want to sing
that song we'll think about it
and there's actually something special
about that one because um
you know we can only really get
permission for japanese songs to cover
like that
um
but
i said
how about we translate it to english and
second in english
my idea yeah
so
we're gonna
cover japanese song with singing in
english because i know you guys are
always like me you have english english
goku it's not awful i mean you know it's
really difficult be happy that we're at
least covering anything at all
but english songs are like
if we want uh to be able to put up a
video that's archived then
we need to probably pay thousands and
thousands of dollars to get the right
song and and then you probably have
problems to even reach the producer or
whoever to begin with
um
but don't worry i'm trying to at least
have my originals be english so
so yeah
um
like japanese songs too thank you i like
them too like even even like before i
was fluent in japanese i still liked
listening to japanese songs and i think
a lot of you guys do that too
do like it too i really like the the
sound
of japanese language
[Applause]
[Music]
feeling jazzy today
okay so now
um
i will show you the thing
and then we'll probably start reading
super chats
uh
because i need to read super chats and
then go today is not gonna be a long
stream just a little chit chat a little
chit chat i don't do this often but
the terrifying thing here please um
[Music]
so
i was thinking you guys
i'm not taking
the usual room serious enough
you guys are just playing around even
though the usual room is already
terrifying enough
um i need a bgm for this though
i don't know let me go on audio stock
one second
whatever makes you say that because you
guys are like i want to go to the usual
room oh vacation vacation
kauai
kawaii gmo
um
quietup
no
[Music]
it's terrifying
[\h__\h] um maybe a bit more
oh
scary but cute
oh it's dark
[Music]
cute
how do i describe this
uh
[Music]
i need to set the mood
maybe
maybe like this
probably
wow
wow audio stock just has insane oh this
might be a good one the description
sounds good
oh stop
[Music]
yeah this is what this is what i'm
looking for
okay guys
[Music]
you ready
are you ready
okay
presented to you by the original
usual room artist
narata
a new
even better
insane user room
oopsie
take it in take it all in
what is this good question
um i mean it's maybe not so much a usual
room maybe it's just us preparing for
the future i mean see there's chickens
working in the background it's more like
you know evangelion i don't know we're
creating a chicken
chicken evangelion or gundam or
something like that
am honestly not sure
i'm honestly not sure either
um it could be the second usual room it
could be us preparing for
something big like taking over the world
um
you know we gotta be ready for the
future
who funded this
well you guys with all your super chat
dollars
get in the
get in the robot
get in the [\h__\h] robot
[Music]
i'm not sure when to use this background
i'm not sure when when i mean so there's
a laptop or pc here that i can use and
and yeah i'm not sure when to use it but
[Music]
give us a tour
well
the problem is i'm not really familiar
with this either like i don't know how
to explain this
[Music]
i don't know how to explain this
there's um there's a knob here there's
pens
[Music]
uh
got it
there we go
so there's a emergency button
and there's um
there's a big [\h__\h] robot
where's the chicken working on the robot
here are more chickens working on the
robot in the back and working on some
kind of portal or something
that where the redwoods probably can fly
through
there's a mogus
there those are also moguls
there's more more chicken working moguls
there's some path up here that you can
walk
and and and uh uh take some dramatic
evangelion scenes on the top on it and
chicken chicken this one here is
supervisor
super wet super visor uh
[Music]
jonathan
yes
uh jonathan
dualinga
uh short jd just like in scrubs
this is it this is um
something between the new usual room or
just uh my garage
maybe it's just my garage let's say it's
my garage
welcome to my garage wait is garage the
word you use in english
there's a garage door
my garage
garage
yes okay welcome to my garage
this is my car
this is my car what car what kind of car
do you drive guys this is my car this is
my car
oh the eyes see it's slightly animated
some things are glowing
so i hope you guys take me more serious
now and
um i hope no one will start a rebellion
because
this is what you're up against
if you start a rebellion
[Music]
think
can't be think
and think takodachi is fake
can you pilot this suit yes i can pilot
it
yes i can
um not the only one who can pilot it but
normally it would be me piloting
piloting it
no i took a selfie
no
allow me to be piled no
my thing
stop taking my fun play thing away from
me
yeah wouldn't it look [\h__\h] hot to
have me in a black suit people have
drawn me before in oscar langley's plug
suit
it looks really cool
[Music]
no that's
not you can't steal it you need my
permission you need my permission to
write it and my vocal permission
otherwise it won't activate
so don't don't even try
you can't move it unless you have my my
vocal permission
so and you don't have my vocal
permission so anyway
i'm i'm glad you like it
don't make an enemy out of kiara and kfp
that is the one thing you have to
remember
all right we're going back
oh girl go go get
okay we can change the bgm again
oh that's a great song though
[Music]
alrighty
right
gonna
uh proceed now with reading super chats
i think
and tomorrow by the way is sims um let
me show you a little schedule
really quickly
have you guys seen the
schedule sorry took a while i was
waiting for
fauna to reply to me
and so sims 4
tomorrow
uh and then clubhouse games of fun the
first time that we're collabing
um
uh i was like you know i was looking at
my schedule i was like wait there's no
collab here
i don't know
originally i wanted monopoly to happen
here but we had some scheduling issues
yeah i was like okay i need to need some
kind of collab so i messaged fauna is
our first one-on-one collab
and we're doing clubhouse games because
i like clubhouse games
it has nice games and uh
it's also it gives you space to talk if
you want to hmm
and then on friday we're doing starship
titanic which is a game that came out in
i think
1998 so i'm sure
a lot of you guys or most of you guys
don't know the game which is
okay but please give it a try when
watching me play it
because it's um
it's really really funny as i remember
it it has a weird humor
um it's like kind of like a puzzle game
a really old one but it is 3d
and my mom used to play it and i
remember watching her play it and i
think i tried it myself as well when i
was younger but i never got really far
and now this this time i want to um play
it on stream and it seems to be very
short i have a feeling when i was like
thinking back
to my childhood it always felt like an
endless game but
it actually is short enough to finish it
in one stream if
if i don't get stuck on any puzzles but
it should be fine
[Music]
it goes way back it does go way back but
it's on steam it has uh
thankfully it's not embed i thought it
would be abandonware too there's a lot
of old games that i was like i'm
thinking of and they're all [\h__\h] bad
and wear like the movies
um i want to play that but it's
abandoned wear it's kind of difficult
gray zone
um
yeah but this one is on steam yeah it
got um picked up by like a publisher who
publishes a lot of really old games from
the 1990s
and the first 2000s um
yeah i love the movies me too
me too
is it clg i don't [\h__\h] know
i don't know what that means stop
throwing words with me i don't know what
they mean
it should be fine though cause it's on
steam
it's on steam doesn't that mean it's
like playable
why would i need a virtual machine if i
have it on steam i will test it out but
someone already reported to me that on
windows 10 it runs fine so
it should be fine
a gold good old games version
yeah whatever whatever i don't care
i don't need it i don't need it
platform likes to ah i don't like steam
for old games only
ah
but yeah it's on steam so not necessary
then on saturday i'm with my family uh
so there will be a rebroadcast
and on sunday we have a special easter
egg painting stream the eggs arrived
today
i have plastic eggs because normally if
you decorate easter eggs if you paint
them you use plastic eggs and that's
what i'm doing so they won't break
[Music]
down
yeah
no hot glue no hot glue is necessary no
no no i will paint them with i don't
know acrylic or something
and then we'll have a members only which
could be fall guys or if you want i have
a different idea
um
but i'll let you decide and every time i
think
i have a different idea what's your idea
okay you want to know okay i'll tell you
i
a while ago i got um
from tales of a rise because of my
sponsorship i got like this huge [\h__\h]
core
thingy
um but you need to assemble it
uh and i wanna i was thinking maybe i'll
do it on stream with your help
yeah it's supposed to be assembled
properly and then it kind of moves i
think
but i don't i i
yeah
i tried opening it up and i was like oh
no dear lord please
i should not open this up yet
if i'm not ready to
uh put it together
yeah you want that
we can do that
i don't think it is as difficult as a
model kit
but looking at the
explanation there's like a guide
it's it's a little bit like it's not
just putting together like something
like an acrylic stand it's a bit more
complicated than that
um
the new background can be used for that
oh
maybe stylistically it may fit
maybe
okay
okay so
let's read
super chat shall we
also i made i made banana pancakes today
again banana blueberry pancakes again
i'm so motivated to make pancakes every
day now
yum yum yum also i just saw on twitter
when i when i updated twitter go to sun
uploaded um
like an illustration
of of of me in that cinderella dress
it makes me so happy when artists who i
work with like surprise me
after whatever we worked on this is um
published surprised me with like an
extra piece of art
that is so nice
[Music]
they may already be asleep so i don't
know if there's uh listening to this but
let me show you
cute
[Music]
i'm gonna retweet that
retweet done
right so cute oh my god i'm gonna use it
as a thumbnail
i am
i am hungry for
good fan art
go to a
style of how they draw the inside of the
eyes
and the brush they use reminds me a
little bit
of inna's style
i love it i don't know if you get it
what i mean
it reminds me a little bit of her style
same really
can you see it
i kind of see it
i i saw it even more with uh with the uh
with this one
this the eyes here the face the whole
face to me almost looks like inna drew
it to me
you know what i mean
the shape of the eyes
and the way it's colored inside
has similarities i think
with her art style
yeah
in a brain
all i think about
wait and i lost i lost it
where did it go
there it is
[Applause]
i took off the glasses i just realized
i took up the glasses in this picture a
matchkey
[Music]
glasses
wrong opinion
to each their own
yeah yeah
all right well let's uh start reading
some videos i'm caught up right i only
need to read the ones from today right
ah enter the newsflash
[Music]
you think you're caught up but then
you're not really caught up [\h__\h] well
then it's good that i'm reading super
chats
[Music]
all right
we um
with these ones
oh where do i put it
here
when i hear one one side story for this
collaboration
[Music]
so
before the stream started
[Music]
it's going to be about super decent but
before the stream started um we were all
preparing obs yeah
and i told you that i taught them how to
do the
the the glue up thingy right but this is
not about that
um
so
i sent in the garlic phone room url
into our chat and i was like this is the
room please enter
and then subaru
[Music]
asks me
and reina
her
her juniors
by a long time by years her cohan
asks us
how to
capture
garden phone which is by the way
um
in obs
uh captured just like a normal window
capture and i'm like
sweater
this is not your first time streaming
garlic phone right
and she's like yeah yeah that's right
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's
not her first time it's just a simple
window capture for a stream of streams
every [\h__\h] day she should know
but i was really amused that she asks
her juniors for that even for a game
that she has uh streamed before a
hundred percent
and i was like
survive you just gotta put in the url
into uh into a window not not the url oh
you just gotta open up a window capture
source on obs and that's all you need to
do
and she was like okay
thank you
[Music]
yeah that was a bird brain that was a
bird brain moment
[Music]
cute
i mean i have those moments too but not
that in regards to
how to capture something actually
i think i'm i'm pretty settled when it
comes to that in the beginning
uh when i started streaming with obs
uh i also had a few question marks in
the head in my head because some things
can only be captured in certain ways
like some games
um
need to be captured in in game capture
and some need to be captured in window
capture and so on
so i need to figure that out because
there's several many different ways to
capture something
the chat is captured in a browser source
and blah blah blah
[Music]
[Laughter]
three years or so
no huh
like uh courtney sent by just reached
three years anniversary was super saiyan
by before quran no after
after uh super saiyan was before
yeah right
yeah it's definitely more than three
years
yeah yeah yeah yeah so for example was
before
um
[Music]
maybe she wanted you to feel competent
and helpful no i don't think so it was
just a brain moment
all right uh yeah almost four wow
wow september 2018 oh my god
wow
testing it didn't sound like a test
okay let's start reading pepsi duncan
and trevor j duncan for two pinkies
here's my obligatory super for flying
ellie
getting all five cute chicks to feather
it seems like only yesterday that you
and silva were honking up a storm as two
obnoxious geese and now you have three
bird kohei flying alongside you mapping
hooting and calling
a special moment seeing the whole of la
collab and the super sho batter
shoe batter believe that i'm grateful we
made it happen
what
seeing the whole flat collab and shoe
batter believe that i am grateful who
made it happen she better ah you better
stretch
thanks for your worth you wait in 24 key
hours gold i leave
and appreciate all that you do now
that's enough out of me about time i
remember reyna refrain
[Music]
damn
once again what a marvelous creation
[Music]
enough thank you very much
finally finally finally and there were
quite some delays like
uh originally i think it was supposed to
be in february and then we couldn't do
it in march because super december i was
busy for like the entirety of march
[Music]
and then finally
finally the beginning of april finally
it happened
[Music]
oh
yes please do it that's cute
[Music]
hey boss it's my birthday today so
here's your present that's how it works
right
thank you
[Music]
but i hope you didn't forget you know
treating yourself as well okay
happy birthday though
stay happy and healthy and wish you all
the best
thank you for being here thank you for
thinking about me on your birthday that
is so selfless thank you
um
magazine
i appreciate it
thank you
[Music]
you got this collab scheduled my
production manager aussie
thanks to all our wonderful burps for
making this happen thank you i mean
people praised me for putting this
together and yes it was difficult to
finally find the time but all i did
really was repeatedly repeatedly asking
okay how about next week any any
ng days next week and everybody is like
oh this day just reduce it and i look at
the schedule i'm like
okay that looks bad
i i like put all the ng days together
from everybody and see what could work
and nothing works i'm like next week and
then i'm like okay i'll ask you again
next week
and then i will come back in the next
video i'm like hi guys everybody
uh how about next week any ng days and
then some people who sometimes don't
answer aka subago senpai
so i'm like uh following up all the time
i mean i gotta stay on top of it because
i'm gonna keep on reminding people doing
a little bit of like managing work there
it's like massimo
hello and no not this week okay i'll ask
you again next week
[Music]
it was basically
repeating that but yes it was sent by
very busy but that's a good thing yeah
there's a high demand for sweater senpai
[Music]
she works hard and she's a great
streamer great person fun person
hi demand for super saiyan bye
cool and but but i did make all the fab
nails and that was uh
uh
that was quite time consuming and i got
the logo for all of us
and and i was happy and everybody used
it yeah we have a logo now
[Music]
and then i also put together
all the light up thingies for
for discord for them i
prepared them all with the urls and the
pictures and
and set it all up
and then sent it over to the other so
that they can use it quickly
yeah
so
i took kind of a little role
i think
i think um
uh
like elena can also speak fluent english
and japanese
so i think us too
are the most fluent in both languages
so we're both the most capable
in like
getting all the verbs um
you know
under control you know what i mean
yeah but since i have seniority and
since i planned out the whole collab
i decided to take the lead also during
the stream
yeah actually i
i didn't discuss this with them before
the stream but the moment the stream
started i was like [\h__\h] somebody
somebody has to take the lead somebody
has to be like okay let's do it uh uh um
let's do introductions start from this
person because otherwise it's always
like awkward like
just you don't there's there's no
there's no structure and i hate that i
hate when there's no structure
and yeah i thought because there's so
many japanese people watching on uh
doing instagram side
and so many english people watching on
elena mine and mummy side i was like i
have to somebody has to like translate
like everything
at least like in the beginning of the
stream and at the end of the stream
so i was like i gotta do it like
somebody has to step up and and do it so
it's enjoyable for everyone and yeah i
i i didn't wanna like stand out that
much and talk that much but when you
have to translate everything it ends up
being like that so
i i hope it was not too obnoxious but i
just wanted everybody to enjoy it and
everybody to understand what's going on
and also because uh
not only for the audience but also
because for example mumei doesn't speak
any japanese maybe some very very basic
words like hawaii or so
but i wanted muma to understand and i
wanted somebody to understand i wanted
the audience to understand
so i felt an obligation to step up and
take the leadership role in this moment
yeah
thank you guys thank you
[Music]
thank you for the membership welcome
the super news english is very good i
think the the only one that i really
needed to worry about was mummy but
i don't want her to be left out and just
have question marks above her head so
whenever possible i tried to um explain
everything and uh double
double it
and i don't want to be like
yo yo mummy this is only for you and
just i just openly translated for
everyone
[Music]
of course as well um
yeah actually in some way i am the first
uh official verb
yeah the first real verb that joined her
alive
but now there are so many like how did
they manage to not add any burps until
he'll have english
and then after me
literally every generation had a
freaking bird
or like something that looks like a bird
or has a bird
[Music]
why maybe they saw me and they were like
yo birbs are the way to go
birds are cute and so gives so many more
ideas for concepts of characters which
is true
like i think the idea of a p file is
amazing because you can get really
beautiful colors out of that in a design
and i'll of course because
owls are just generally freaking
adorable and it just fits the whole
knowledge council thingy right
yeah
and so on and so on
the sky is the limit
you would think so but not for birds for
birds there is no limit unless you are a
penguin or so cause you can't fly
oh [\h__\h]
i think flamingo could be really cute
like a girly elegant girly pink design
but then you know then i couldn't make
fun of louie anymore
because i finally figured out i said
this in the horototi stream that
it's
it makes me angry
that me and reyna and supernu get these
like
i don't know animals that we're made fun
of
uh they have been turkey me being
chicken so better being duck
but then mommy just stays an owl mostly
i mean there's a little bit of kiwi
jokes here and there but not really
and also doing being a hawk really cool
barely anyone calls our flamingo i feel
like it came up the first time
when we um
when we talked about it uh during the
collab i don't know was that a thing
before
but i feel like mostly owl and hawk are
being
just called or owl and hawk
and me and ayn and so what are just
being made fun of what the [\h__\h]
wow
[Music]
but that's why i i wanted to point out
you know flamingo yeah yeah kiwi but
even the kiwi it's not really something
you can make fun of you can't really
call her kiwi with the intention of
making fun of her because the quick kiwi
is also [\h__\h] cute there's nothing
funny about the kiwi
bird
it's just so [\h__\h] adorable i wanna i
wanna put it in my hands and just
oh
cherish it
chickens are cute too yeah but you guys
you guys and others
make fun of me like that with the
intention of making fun of me you call
me chicken with the intention of making
fun of me
but i do have to say
ever since
kfb exists
i've been looking a lot at chickens and
they are really cute they're very fluffy
okay
they're very fluffy and
fat
they look fat they're not that fat but
they look fat
they look so chunky and
they're one of the most
if not the most popular choice of meat
all over the world
so
we could be very proud
we are very popular
meat provider and source so
[Music]
proud
you can do so much with chicken meat so
much you can make curry you make you can
make chicken wings
you can make a roast
you can make a salad you can make so
many things
wow
amazing you guys are so versatile more
versatile than glasses
she has a point yeah
but why are you saying no i i was like
no no she has a point ah
[Music]
minus 50 hp
i just say no when i say we when i speak
like that and i say we i don't mean that
i'm a chicken too i'm saying that
because i want you to feel like you know
we're we're one group you know we are we
are kfp
i always say that to strengthen our
bonds
understand
no for real though you can make fun of
me but that's really why i do that
[Music]
i say we because we
we are
we are kfp and we work hard together and
for example you know
this whole channel is way it's not only
me it's you guys too okay
our channel is our channel
speaking of i put my i put my
uh subscriber uh awards from youtube you
know the shiny ones i put them finally
up on the wall today
and i put some other things up on my
wall too um um but i'll tell you about
it another time i need some talking
topics topping talking topics for
times when i need talking topics
and i cleaned up a little bit but yeah
i'll tell them i'll tell you about that
i need some talking topics
talking topics excited for sims 1. it's
not this week but yes i am
i got the
second hand thingies the other day i
didn't install it yet i need to test it
all out and when it's ready then we're
going to play it
[Music]
okay i need to read some chats
more tangents coming soon
chat and chewy
mmm chili con carne
duck attack thank you for the rest of
the chat
first of all on the tony cory operation
let's go i'm still still listening at
work and catching up on vods when
possible buzz but i'm not going anywhere
oh
i hope we're gonna see more fun meetings
with you and your friends young lords
careful along with kiana thank you
thank you
yeah i do notice sometimes certain
certain people
like i haven't seen them in a while but
thank you for are you saying hello and
still trying to
um watch my streams catch my vods and
all that it means a lot to me
really thank you
i hope you can catch this one
it's for you
thank you very much
i love you
[Music]
thank you
thank you all all of you thank you
jacob's monkey thank you for the
audition for the red super chat
i see big fan of poro toni
understandable i'm a big fan of portal
30 as well i love our little group i
love our little group it's nice to be a
part of a group
um
i think also for like
uh maybe maybe i don't know how
reyna mummy and louis felt when they
first joined whole life and
and
i was like yo welcome to hulutoni i
don't i don't know how they felt but i
hope they felt
like happy about having a place like a
group to belong to because when you join
whole life i think maybe in the
beginning it can be a bit scary um
i definitely felt that way
um like maybe
some depending on how much confidence
you have
then you may feel
worried about
whether or not you can
make yourself at home
and find your place
and all that
yeah but immediately having a grip like
that
gives you already immediate friends
immediate connections and a place to be
in
[Music]
i definitely had those worries when i
joined her life
yeah
i
i think that
maybe
maybe that might be
um a slight a small reason
why
i really i i needed someone
in hollow myth
to
you know
get closer to like some friend that i
feel like
you know
that that i that i know that i have
someone
you know and that was uh cali cause we i
mean everything was just perfect our
our lord just fit together and we were
in the same country at that time so we
were able to meet beforehand
and yeah i didn't have as you guys
probably know since i talked about it
before i didn't have much connections
with gouda and ahmed in the beginning
um because of time zones and all that
and i was kind of feeling like good and
amber is just like you know they they're
their own little group because they seem
to get along so well and i was like i
don't fit in there and ina was like kind
of like the neutral party like she's so
sweet to everybody she's so calm and all
that
definitely
could probably make friends with her but
with cali i just felt like
i can be sure i can i can rest assured
with callie
um
so
that's
i don't know something i needed because
it was kind of scary and i i
i was always the outsider in school
um and in other situations too and at
work and so on
so
it's nice to have something you know
something to hold on to and uh i mean i
don't hold on to it i don't need to hold
on to it anymore because i think i found
my place
um
more or less
and i have one tony
and i have nana t
yeah yeah yeah
now i have um
more connections i guess
feeling like an outsider is hard yeah
it is it is
[Music]
more friends yeah
yeah
[Music]
i'm just chilling i'm just chilling
i really felt like an outside of lit
[Music]
understand that feeling when i finally
got friends oh
good for
you where was i
ah
apple did you get a kiss
[Music]
i could just play my recorded kisses if
i wanted to
but now you get the kisses fresh out of
the oven
time to thank you for the rent
[Music]
such a genius
group of people
just genius
putting horritory together who who was
that genius oh my god whoever thought
about
creating horotoli
absolute genius whoever made it happen
is just a pure genius man yeah yeah
einstein must have been einstein
[Music]
thank you thank you
oh you caught up on yakuza zero
dang i'm glad you enjoyed it thank you
for catching up el canal we have
why did burbs need a plane in the first
place
because
a duck can't fly that well maybe and i
don't know can a pea fowl fly that well
but also because you know luxury
why fly yourself when someone else can
fly you the big bird
my wings get tired the
motives are far away
fifa house can't fly
can't
really are they too big to fly maybe and
they can probably just like
um float for a short distance but
luggage yeah luggage we have luggage
oh yeah i guess yeah ducks do migrate
that's right yeah but you know
you know and i'm a phoenix not a chicken
so i could totally fly if i wanted to
but
luxury and it's just more comfortable
[Music]
it's like it's like run imagine imagine
you're a human and you have to run
a marathon
to get to your vacation but it's like
longer than normal marathon it's like it
takes you days
imagine
why would you do that when you can go on
a train or a car huh
as a human it makes no sense either you
could use your legs if you wanted to
just because you can reach it in theory
with your legs doesn't mean you should
use it
[Music]
fair right that's fair
makes so much sense i am such a genius i
must be the one who father photo tony
may believe two five zero one thank you
thank you
your grandpa's favorite thing was bird
watching
as a child i never understood fully what
was so great about that now i finally
understand him
everybody who's a fan of hulu tony is a
fan of bird watching yeah yeah i love
that that's cute
that is so cute
[Music]
i heard about that yeah that's funny
fanfictions reina is a funny person i
love her
ok
miniature
happy birthday uh
happy
hbd we've been waiting for this collab
for a long time these are wonderful
paintings that show off their own color
very well
[Music]
thank you for
waiting it was worth it right
[Music]
thank you
thank
the sun then the whole praising of that
tiny star makes a lot more sense to be
tiny
thanks for organizing this stream
tension this comedy gold all the way
through and i'm so glad i could catch
and see what doggo mean praise the sun
which is kiwawa thank you
tiny tiny
sun is tiny
tiny
[Music]
where's the sun tiny
in celestial measure the sun's pretty
tiny well i mean anything can look tiny
if you look at it at the far distance
far enough distance
i guess
wow it's like you're you're
um just undermining the sun's
accomplishments how good
you're trying to make the sun feel bad
about its size
not that it matters
[Laughter]
the sun is big okay let's just tell the
sun that is big so it's happy all right
sun is big makes us all uh feel hot
and makes us sweat
damn sun is amazing
[Music]
i'm excited to hear it from another
person telling me directly they're
coming makes it feel more real i had a
a great idea today for something for my
concert at i hope i hope i didn't make
it happen i cannot guarantee anything
but i i
i told i told
management that i want to do this and
let's see
if it works i i don't want to get your
hopes up so i'm not going to say what it
is
and also planning a bit more for my
birthday is also
uh something i've been doing
um i got permission to sing
one song
in my birthday
concert that i've been waiting to sing
for a long time
you may know what it is i'm not going to
say it either
[Music]
[\h__\h] off with ramstein
[\h__\h] off
get out of here
so sick of seeing that name
[Music]
um
that was an amazing collab kiana thank
you so much for putting it together you
guys are such a great group the
chemistry is fantastic and it's always a
fun time
number one
thank you yeah the best group thank you
it was it was a pleasure of putting it
together
and
i probably won't do it again for a long
time
i think from now on there will be mostly
a smaller group collabs
but i feel like it had to be done at
least once
so
there it is
[Music]
i especially want to do
collabs with
one-on-one with roommate
and uh
reina and subaru and me
as as free
i love i love me elena and others like
vibes
where we like you can just watch the
worms collab and you see we just get so
loud everybody's just screaming
[Laughter]
when it's us free everybody's just
screaming
i feel like mummy and and
are like
kind of like more the quiet type both of
them
so most of the volume in the horotoni
collab came from
me
[Laughter]
[Music]
um it's turned up and [\h__\h] crazy
looking crazy all right here is this one
we're gonna read the super chats from
that one
yummy mom
yeah
noisy farm animal head
a peabody is not a farm animal
[Music]
tesla arrives progress of detection
take a small conduction
[Music]
yes they were kiddies are standing by to
pounce on the emergency
pounce
that reminds me today i was sitting at a
random spot
on my floor in my apartment and the sun
was shining in
from the window so strong and it was
reflecting on my phone
to the very other side of the room on
the wall
uh you know like a like a light spot
and i didn't notice until my cat's movie
suddenly
ran away from where i was sitting
running oh ran all the way over to that
spot jumped up the cat tree and i was
like what's up what's up and i look over
there and i see oh
she's trying to catch
like a
uh yeah that light reflection from my
phone
but it was moving so much because it was
so far away and and it's such a small
reflection but on the wall it's so big
and so shaky
when i noticed i tried playing a little
bit with her but it was very fickle to
play around with that
but it worked out for a little bit she
had fun
[Music]
it does like all kinds of lights it
seems lasers and sun reflections
that's the good stuff
that's the good stuff smoothie likes
that
[Music]
i
see i will notice you and i will at the
same time also time you out because i
don't like it when you spam like that i
have do you realize i appreciate you
being here but do you realize how many
people are in the chat
how many people are in the chat it's
impossible that i read every single
comment and i read more in my brain than
i read out loud understand i can't read
every comment out loud and
i usually only read out things out loud
that are looking interesting to me or
you know are actual proper questions or
something
so
yeah
it's hard to get me to pick up your
comment if you're just like hello notice
me like i'm not just gonna read that
like hell notice me oh hello hello
i understand
if you want me to react to your comment
there's no guarantee for that
you may have to try several times but
spamming is not the way to go okay
okay
[Music]
get those gains tangel chimken power
get those gains
now now now i can learn all these uh
[Music]
gym terms gym language
i want to learn the gym language
teach me senpai
get swole yeah
i can use all of those
[Music]
oh yeah the first livestream have to be
here oh you mean have you you have
watched my archives before
thank you for coming to the live stream
just reading super chats now but
chit-chatting in between
and talked a little bit about
all kinds of other things before
that uh
will will the apple 2 be resurrect
the apple 2 resurrect to be back but not
see that this is a good question this is
a question that you can ask in the chat
that i might pick up because it's an
actual question
that i also have been thinking about so
the chances are higher for me to answer
it um yeah i've been thinking about um
hitting up crony again
uh to play it again
sometime soon sometime soon
i'm so hungry actually i'll do it now
because otherwise i'll forget
hey yeah yeah
crony
do you wanna
[Music]
oh god i'm typing it exactly like that
play
hey
uh
[Music]
play diablo 2 again sometime soon
i'm having really a hard time
thinking of
good one-on-one collab games recently i
can think of a lot of good four people
collab games but
barely any
uh one-on-one collab games and i have
not already done
but for crony i have diablo too
and that works
portal 2 yeah i was taking a portal too
i was thinking of who should i play
portal 2 with i want to play with reina
i want to play with energy i don't know
i want to play with ahmed i want to play
with a lot of people
so i still have to decide but that's why
i got i asked you guys if portal 1 is
also co-op but only
portal 2 is co-op apparently
no probably no that's not what they
we're going to play something else
i would probably do either or dana or
or almond probably
reno already played portal i think i
looked it up i didn't see it
yeah i was thinking doing portal 1 solo
first and then playing
uh
portal 2 with someone she did with iris
oh
no
did i not play it yet that's actually i
would think ahmed would have already
played it seems like something she would
like
i'm so hungry
[Music]
yeah it's short enough for a single
stream right i looked up the the length
of it
i'mma play it
two singles there
what a waste of time of opportunity
eh
uh actually
[Music]
who do i want a portal live
i think i want it to be an english
stream so it should be an
english-speaking member
[Music]
i could portal with kobo when her collab
then is over
huh
portal with kobo
maybe maybe yeah
you think a portal
cordial i was about to say corbin
combined kobo with portal and you think
portal needs two point of views i
watched a little bit of it of like a
playthrough and it felt like you're
mostly
close together but maybe you need two
point of views
okay
horrible
okay oh wow okay and we're doing on kobo
channel and my channel
if if that's what we do i can't promise
yet
don't
don't put it in stone yet
so i'm sick of this jazz now
i hate jazz now
i'm sick of it
stop it
kick that go not
[Music]
i'm hungry
have i told you i'm hungry
and i told you i'm hungry
this is
oh
hungry
round of this channel dancing celebrity
speech in motion
thank you
for the pinky
so does this mean we're gonna get ring
fit adventure streams
um if i get so fit
that
ring fit adventure
does not make me make weird sounds
you know if it's if i'm so fit that it
doesn't exhaust me anymore then maybe
maybe don't you always remember i don't
know your ring for this girl or you're
either a wrinkled stream or a horror
game
don't worry don't forget about it
forget about it
[Music]
if you don't make weird sounds what is
the point okay you have outed yourself
as the problem
that is
people like you i'm sorry but that is
the reason why i don't do it
[Music]
you are the problem you're part of the
problem
[Music]
and these are not cases
no no
bad bad bad bad chicken
i'm hungry
senior emcees at tangashan opera
for the games
get those games right um yeah am i right
am i right you even lived bro senior you
even lived i need jim lingo
who can teach me jim lingo
i need jim lingo
i want string fit for the plot
you're stupid
there is no plot
don't you make weird noises in the
regular
yeah but
not necessarily ones that can be taken
out of context
i literally saw clips
of people
cutting other whole live memories
ringfit adventure streams
to only the noises and i'm absolutely
disgusted by it
it just it just oh makes me face palm
and worry about you guys
[Laughter]
oh man
so about a ring fit at 25
is great
why
what
25 percent
[Music]
does it sound like
does it sound does it i
didn't sound like
[Music]
i'm hungry and tired
i woke up early today you guys are maybe
wondering why because i said i'll go
back to sleep
i had to because um
um
someone came by to uh fix something in
my kitchen that was missing last time
when they came and they
uh
they built that extra kitchen kitchen
pee extra extra kitchen piece
cats
[Music]
there was one card missing that they
didn't deliver at the time they built it
so
they yeah another person how did they
forget that yeah they brought everything
except like one piece
that was supposed to be a part of the
kitchen now the kitchen was already
functionable
no it's not the electricity i still
didn't figure that out
and didn't
figure that out
i don't know
there's just no electric connection but
i paid extra to have that socket on the
counter so now i want it to work
what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] was that pop up on my
screen
hmm
[Music]
no i don't think so
it has been a while since i've seen the
super chat but i i just came in to
report for duty ah good job on the
workout and please don't send me to the
usual room
[Music]
gracias
wow
well you wrote this before you even saw
the new usual room although that is
really not really a usual room it
doesn't even feel like a usual room
it's just my garage where i park my my
huge [\h__\h] mecca
yeah
it's a hangar yeah
it's just where
where uh i i experiment
experimentation room
it's a hanger
call it a hanger
kfp hanger
it's such a weird word i don't like the
word i don't like that word
i'll say garage
[Music]
you should show your face more often
yeah
roman er dancing
[Music]
i read some more from today
what
what's uh what's racist what did i say
what did i say you're joking right
edward what did i say
is it jerk it's joke
i think it's jock
probably joke i didn't say anything
it's junk
okay
[Music]
anyways
uh mr cats big so these are from today
okay these are from this stream thank
you everybody for supporting all all
your uh super chats for this stream are
going to pay off the illustrator and the
music video artist and the mixer
because i cannot monetize the uh actual
song so all of the proceeds are going to
the creators thank you very much for
making it uh worthwhile and hopefully
not go into the minus thank you very
much
[Music]
um
thank you oh you're welcome
congratulations
well you your profile picture changed
wow you're in a you're in a gym now
is that a new pose i think that's a new
pose
holy [\h__\h]
oh my god you know what like
[Music]
i mean
can i like
oh yeah yeah yeah
no sakanachi
i have a
head
a fish head right
on top of my uniform and where my
boobies are you know when i
wear my uniform those boobies just look
like big boobies but when you wear it
it looks like muscles it looks pretty
good
and those are by the way
as far as i know the real arms of that
person
damn
look at that game
look at your games
he definitely lifts bro
[Music]
he'll be lifting
that's that's me in the future
duck thank you for the red super chat oh
we're all proud of your own gym
accomplishment boss also can i dedicate
a chiara kiss to our puff fish oh
sakanashi for offering workout tips and
helping typicals become lean meat
of course
[Music]
both of you thank you and yeah um i mean
i'm not that serious about it that i'm
gonna follow like a whole meal plan or
whatever
i'm not trying to be like
like you know swole i'm just trying to
fix my back hopefully
no
maybe i'll eat more eggs still
someone said i should eat eggs
i guess i don't know i probably won't i
don't think i can follow
a daily meal plan it's like
i can't i've never i've never went i've
never been on a diet my whole life
and i don't think i can in the future
bananas i've been trying to eat more so
yeah i think bananas i can do
i try i'll try eggs i'll try
[Music]
to fight
as long as you hit your macros you
should be fine i don't know what that
means i don't understand jim lingo
sorry for all the new memories yes
i've been making a lot of actually you
know what my eggs are in my banana
pancakes i've been actually combining my
breakfast is great
i've been eating
banana pancakes that's uh
actually i've only been eating free per
morning so it was like one egg one
banana
uh some flour
and then some blueberries on top of it
and uh
then a [\h__\h] ton of nutella
okay but it's a more healthy version of
nutella
but
egg and banana
then there must be a little bit of of
nutella because otherwise it doesn't
doesn't taste so good
i need some chocolate or i don't know
some vanilla or some kind of extra taste
because the blueberries are actually
pretty weak and the banana is also very
weak in that pancake
and there's no sugar in it so
yeah
those games lost no don't say that
there's a banana in the egg what else do
you want from me
it's the best i can do
need nuts
no [\h__\h] nuts
just use maple syrup i'm not a fan of
maple syrup
yeah i don't really like maple syrup i
don't eat pancakes with maple syrup i'm
not canadian
i only ever eat pancakes and waffles and
and all that with with nutella
my beloved
or like any kind of chocolate spread
canadians triggered
i hurt my soul i was just not raised
with syrup you know whenever my mom made
um
pancakes we didn't we never had maple
syrup at home
it's just not that common
just like how also peanut butter is not
very common in austria some people like
it some people eat it but
it's just not that common um
yeah
there is
maple syrup but it's just
not many people
eat it i would say honey honey is more
common
honey is popular in austria
people like honey
and nutella and jam any kind of jam
[Music]
yeah
sorry guys that's just the way it is
you guys complaining about it and being
like oh my god will not change it
replace nutella with honey
no because i personally am not that much
of a honey fan i like to have it on my
in my tea
and wherever but just as a spread no
no
not really i mean i can eat it but no no
thank you
i could add jam on my pancakes but in
general
why the hell would i do that when i can
put chocolate spread on it
yes daichi this is exactly what i'm
saying nothing can ever replace nutella
except for another chocolate spread
no lingleberry jam does not go on
pancakes hell no
hell now
[Music]
i need to continue
i need to continue i want to go eat
pepsi
thanks for the cover attention was
amazing thank you you're amazing thank
you for listening
russell dingles that is everything also
for pinky dope cover tanger definitely
going on the top of my workout playlist
oh you work out too what a coincidence i
actually also work out
yeah and then
you want me to show me you my my muscles
oh no no
i totally have like really buff arms but
i just choose to not show it off too
much because i don't like show off
people you know
but i totally have them it's not a
problem of whether or not i have them
just don't want to show them
i think i just don't want to make you
feel bad about your arms yeah
[Music]
my fingertips
thank you
[Music]
bang of a cover
thank you
i'm glad you like it
now that i have that out i can finally
work on the next things i'm also working
on the side on my original song of
course so
let's let's hope everything goes
smoothly
hi to thank you for the red super chat
thank you
new song cover yay
thank you tarty did you like it did you
like it tai chi did you like it did you
like it i hope you liked it
i hope you liked it
[Music]
thank you my beloved tai chi
miguel duncan
uh
how the [\h__\h] do i read this
there's like a
ah
i think i can read it
no i don't know i probably um
this probably means
kiara is a
what
what are you know signs though from what
language
what is this that's not even a real
[Music]
i can't translate it google is not
like
understanding what it is
this i don't know what it is
[Music]
but i think it's probably something like
kiana is uh you know what
what is that
eldritch
[Music]
recognized it
but the profile picture of the person is
a is a chicken and the currency is ars
so i think i know who this is
and they're probably facing me
nor
ah
celtic
no guy like salty viking bronze well
google translation does not know what it
means so you failed at baiting me to
read it out loud because i literally am
incapable of it
but judging by the amount of letters
and the spaces in between
i'm sure that it's ki ada is a
she yeah i'm pretty sure
yep
i knew it i knew it
you can't fool me
i'm just that smart though
no it does not say kikitiki
[\h__\h]
[Music]
is
and thank you for blessing us with the
superb cover thank you for listening
thank you
i'm not so confident on this one for my
singing but i hope you enjoy it more
than i do
thank you
a tiny delta dancing for the pinky don't
mind me just looping the chew over and
over and over and over and over and over
and guys are misusing it
one thing i really loved were the
ad-libs they made the song so playful
and changed the tone so much eagerly
waiting for the future projects thank
you
yeah i'm not good with ad-libs those
ad-libs were in the song already
originally and i think they sound really
cool
yeah
thank you thank you very much
i wish i could come up with ad libs by
myself
like like really good ones like ariana
grande
jacob
[Music]
it's a korean one but written in
japanese
[Music]
oh damn though the filter from before it
was so long
[Music]
okay
oh
[Music]
but it makes no sense now
thank you
[Music]
cute it means sunshine
sorry today i will join kfb thank you
oh kelly
where did you see cali oh there she is
song was so good dude
yo dude kelly dude did you see i started
lifting okay not lifting but i'm gaming
i'm doing the games dude
did you see
[Music]
burmese was a good choice yeah hell yeah
yeah dude yo
i'm like
lifting bro
how to jim lingo
i admire it what
you you as far as i know you work out
too don't you
don't yeah i just started though
i just do it because of my my back pain
kinda got back into that all too busy
right
um you but callie you know what i saw
are you lift weights don't you do
maybe you need to do cardio i saw
something really cool on amazon uh
yesterday or so
like a
like a foldable
foldable
so you can put it away if you have no
space really cool really like high-tech
um uh running pad you know like a
running machine but without the the rail
to hold on to
but
i think that's really really useful if
you want to have if you want to be able
to do cardio at any time at home yeah
yeah yeah i'm sure japan amazon probably
has that too a treadmill that you can
fold
it looks so good
hate leaving home
these days always me always
yeah being able to have something at
home and not having to like go to the
gym i think
makes so much of a difference
[Music]
um
yeah yeah yeah yeah
well colleen before your gym membership
runs out
let's go lifting let's get swollen kelly
let's get swole
uh
i just i'm focusing on the on the rowing
machine kelly
because i gotta strengthen my shoulders
and and my my neck and all that so i'm
gonna only get swole in that area
[Music]
we're gonna get buff
bonita we need a um a 3d model like
ahmed a million buffs in
we're gonna get calliope
uh
buffy
and
[Music]
[Laughter]
let's go
we all need to get those buff models
collide protein oh i love that
i love that
it would look so funny if we all had
those buff models oh my god it would
look so ridiculous
like we're collecting all kinds of 3d
models that we can use for vr it's never
enough
we gotta catch them all
[Music]
cramp
i'm good though just a small crab just a
small cramp
both models doing jojo poses oh cali
would look amazing
[Music]
no egg no no no
no hydration okay hydration check
[Music]
more hydration need more hydration
ah myth buffsters and little
busters
oh funny
i'm so funny oh you guys are funny
geniuses
no the link for the new song cover did
you go for the one on twitter that's an
old tweet i already tweeted out the new
one should i delete the old
ah i need tweet delete the old one
someone in the chat once again
made a mistake
let me delete the old one
[Music]
delita
yeah i didn't want to delete it because
of the replies and retweets and all that
but it leads to a wrong url
yeah sad
sad sad wow what up
my my mommy what are you drawing does
that include me
did you guys see
i see someone on the left side
she must be drawing all of her torii is
she
in
yeah bay outfits
oh my god
i'm excited but mamaloni has been
drawing so many things at once and has
not been finished
[Music]
i know
she's been drawing so much like it's
been piling up but she's like she's
probably so inspired she's like i need
to try this i need to draw that i need
to draw this and that and this and that
oh but i also want to draw this and that
oh it must be tough oh but i'm excited
how dare she tease me with louie and
subaru but not tease me with with my i i
i'm guessing i'm part of this
why why why not teach me with my myself
i want to see me and
nothing like that
[Music]
ah wait what did you notice like um on
doing his boobie
what's leaning on louie's boobie is
another boobie i think
yeah and i see the five
yeah that's that's probably
reyna judging by the size
just judging by that one centimeter of
boobie i can say that's odena
oh but that will mean we'll get lume in
a spicy outfit too
[Music]
very observant
analysis
[Music]
[Applause]
quinine
yo
[Music]
anyway
uh
i need to read super chats
reina thank you for the pinky
congrats on the bangla crumbling was
really impressed with your rapid fire
singing rapping section at the beginning
looking forward to more copies and
especially the original songs thank you
i really liked the the rhythm of um
the song and the lyrics especially like
the part that goes like
[Music]
because it's kind of also
with the rhythm
it's like playing with the lyrics
if you know japanese because it's like
me
is uh i and i
and then
is can't stop
it that word alone means i cannot stop
it but the way it's okay this is kind of
nerdy talk
but the way it's like
uh
the rhythm you know the ribbon makes it
sound like i'm singing
eyes and eyes and eyes and eyes but no
no no no actually that's a different way
okay it's not interesting but i just i
just i don't know it was fun to sing it
like that you know
yeah
and the harmony was fun too
[Music]
yeah
you never mind ignore me ignore me
[Music]
i love the new mb i also also recently
hit the one-year membership milestone oh
although i couldn't be a day one member
like i wanted to i have been here since
debut and i'm proud of all your
accomplishments and i'm glad i'm here i
appreciate how funny interesting
hard-working and cute you are
[Music]
you're very caring compassionate and
you've built a nice community i cannot
wait to see what the future holds and
i'll be supporting you every step love
you and take care south swedes
thank you very much for the sweet words
and yeah no problem
maybe in the beginning you just weren't
sure about me and or you just didn't
have the financials or whatever that's
all good maybe just didn't feel like it
in the beginning it's all good but
you're here you've been here since the
beginning until now and that's the
amazing thing thank you so much
i appreciate it even though you know
the beginning was kind of rough and and
even though i also i feel like i changed
a little bit and and
you know you know even though the games
i choose are kind of filtering but you
still you still show up thank you so
much
[Music]
i'm not saying polito and polo anymore
because i learned my lesson out i did my
did my spanish
graciast jeffy and now i'm absolutely
nailing that spanish
pronunciation
nailing it
[Music]
smart everyday that's me that's me yes
it sounds like english it's not even
that's not even that's spanish
can you say fight me outside in spanish
again i don't know how to say that
you tell me
[Music]
i don't want to open up google right now
it'll find me outside no that's not it
nos
[Music]
because that's how i always read it in
my mind as a as a mother tongue german
speaker when you guys type
anywhere
actually for me it's
[Music]
in german mm-hmm
is like my friend or so
maybe and foreign
[Music]
are with me ah
con your corn is with
i heard that in in italian as well con
for example like for
sparkling water
[Music]
wanna fight
pierre and pelea
[Music]
try me
try me a little [\h__\h]
that's not supposed to sound cute that's
supposed to sound dangerous okay and
threatening
[Music]
a long time dude
long time do you super chat to you
cinderella thank you for the constant
efforts passion and enthusiasm you put
in everything you do you keep making our
days brighter really for this cover i
was expecting one of your cute dances
but it's okay your outfit is fire for
this song my dances
why did you expect that
i wish i wish i could dance for every
song cover and music video i wish i
could
[Music]
but it's not that easy thank you nana
thank you thank you for supporting me
and watching my content
i'm glad you're part of kfb thank you
very much
unity chat also thank you for red super
chat i love this cover you absolutely
nailed it those parts at the start
around one minute
just name two cool sections
at the start and around one minute
what's that one minute is that my kiss
or so
must listen more oh and uh the mb art is
great not that i like glasses a lot or
anything my my heart just randomly went
doki doki
uh-huh
i see
i love you dancing thank you i love
dancing i mean i haven't really been
dancing much in the
past years but yeah
it's still a precious activity to me
precious hubby
yum yum based glasses enjoyer yeah i
don't really understand that but you do
you unity chad i respect you
thank you for your glam you're so sweet
thank you she's a sweetheart i love you
[Music]
wait i think i forgot your kiss here's a
kiss you need to jack
mastiza or mrisa
thank you thank you for the red super
chat thank you
thank you
[Music]
i'm an employee who is watching from
korea i applied for military service why
would you do that then you're leaving me
but the results will come out tomorrow
thank you for always doing the show oh
[Music]
[\h__\h]
foreign
[Music]
do i have my reject button
no i don't have it
i have this one
where where the hell is it
[Music]
this is what will happen
if you leave me
there he goes
supposed to be here
oh god it's too big
[Music]
hello
i know ah the [\h__\h] layers there's too
many layers on my screen
maybe i can flip it
there we go ah there's something over
there too [\h__\h]
[Music]
it's been a while since i used that
button yeah
i have so many so many assets you know
dragon birdie danke soon the game mccree
danke soon
[Music]
with an emergency meeting i hope i'm not
fired glad that chubby charles
is finally on her way to become picture
i was never chubby i was never chubby
like legit never chubby but yes i am
becoming vigil
your cover was so lit i was already on
fire already uh i need to fix my sleep
schedule good enough wow
you're really gonna fix your zip
schedule but then how are you gonna
watch my streams you're in sea right how
are you gonna watch my streams with a
fixed sleep schedule
good luck with that but thank you
wow
welcome to the membership thank you
come samir
[Music]
this was the first of your covers that i
actually knew the original before and i
think you did very well personally thank
you every new color for me is a treat
such a great me too more glasses can i
win and the feathers on the flower were
a great touch
oh thank you thank you the
dress design is all on koto
i think i just said uh
that i want a cute dress
oh i think i maybe said i want no did i
even say i wanted to be orange i maybe
not have even said that
i don't think i gave any
any
ideas
i think it was just like
uh make it look like it's uh
a cute
dress um
yeah like a party party cocktail dress i
think that's all i said
[Music]
thank you
while listening to you so all around a
great day for me wow how long did it
take you
i think you sounded great but i've also
never met an artist who was totally
satisfied with their work either way
wait where does it continue there's a
there's a
there's a comma
where does it continue
it doesn't continue anywhere thank you
though
i'm hungry and
my air is too dry
and i'm having trouble breathing the
whole time so
[Music]
my heart back to you love back to you
thank you
222 hours what the [\h__\h]
can you finish it earlier than that
that's probably just because you did a
lot of
chilling and side stuff and all that
right
[Music]
i might stop there because i need to
refresh it's
probably still
a bunch more
[Music]
100 hours for my first run oh
speed run seven minutes no [\h__\h] way
well only if you're
a [\h__\h] pro wait do you not have to
kill all
i guess you don't have to kill um
market
because he's not one of those rings
right but you probably have to kill uh
the the other one godric
and
all the other ring people i suppose
or maybe they've used glitches yeah i
guess so
[Music]
do you you don't have to beat anyone
i don't really
see
i understand speed runs where you
actually go for the game at least a
certain amount do a certain amount of
things like bosses and all that but if
it's a speed run where you skip
literally the whole game
by not killing not doing anything
then honestly
i don't understand the meaning and i
don't want to even acknowledge it as a
speed run because like you
now ha
ha
if it's a speedrun where they kill
the bosses
or at least one of them
okay
okay yes yes impressive but not if you
just glitch through the game without
doing anything
they're called any percent sure but like
but like no it's
just like
no you know what i mean no that's
nothing you've got nothing bro you've
got nothing nothing nothing
nothing
[Music]
nothing there's nothing to work with
there
no gameplay yeah there's actually no
gameplay
[Music]
like i saw i saw any person runs for
like super mario 64 for example but that
one at least
like kills bowser imagine doing a super
mario 64 speed run without killing
bowser you basically just hacked the
game
you just hacked the game
nah i can't accept that no
no that's stupid
that's just stupid
that's just not interesting like
how is that even how is that even
interesting
you give me nothing
you're giving me nothing also i am so
sick of this music again
ah just give me
low five
[Music]
congratulations on nothing i won't even
congratulate you it's not even worth it
congratulations
[Music]
it's cool seeing delicious yeah maybe
one time
but
it's not worth
i don't know any congratulations
[Laughter]
not impressive to me
oh cram sheep thank you thank you good
luck in your job interview
did i wake up to the baby with my
singing
[Music]
that remix is so good also tensions
vocal is always perfect so don't worry
oh thank you
when you become the rap god this time i
can't find any reason for not liking
this another amazing cover kiara thank
you
[Music]
yeah i think i think i understand if to
you guys it just sounds normal
unless you really
um
you know
listen to it a million times maybe
really inspect it but for me you know as
as the one singing it um i've heard my
voice many many times and just sounded
weird to me
yeah but i'm glad that you can enjoy it
at least thank you
thank you very much
counting chicken
content chicken
looking forward to having you with
dokomi
thank you
foreign
i'm supposed to super chat the boss when
she spoils us
when you just write shoe in your super
chat aren't you cheating because i'm i
need to read it out loud because it's a
pinky or a red one but then you get an
extra kiss a free kiss basically
if you just write chew in the text box
because i'm gonna read it out loud
big brain
cheater all right don't don't take out
the knife no reason to take out the
knife
um
thank you for the pinky thank you and i
am dead thank you forever thank you too
don't die
you're just a chicken don't die
your uh revival is not ready yet you're
feather
not ready yet
new two speed run just dropped any
percent any super chat
giant mug thank you for the red super
chat doll to your attention i'm out of
the usual room and find the bang of a
song here's a ticket fiend not much but
it's from honest work
yes i reflect on my bad joke it was not
a good idea to make a joke like jim
carrey car car
after all we'll loop at the next time no
problem it's okay i already forgot thank
you very much and
uh congratulations for getting out of
the
uh
usual
[Music]
oh my god there's gonna be so many of
you
holy [\h__\h] thank you
what's up welcome to the membership
surprise she knows jim carrey i think i
know jim carrey
from
no uh i was thinking about someone else
i guess i've seen him before in some
movie
[Music]
i think um
i don't know
[Music]
i haven't watched the mask
no i haven't watched sonic grinch yes ah
grinch yeah maybe but i wasn't thinking
of that one
i think i was thinking about like a
funny movie
liar liar i think eli elaine was funny
that's the one
i think
you speak only the truth for a single
day
i think i think yeah pathologically i
think so yeah that one was funny
i think so
um
um david chris duncan
oh real gym bros are proud of you thank
you real jim are you a real jim brown
[Music]
um
[Applause]
go to the punishment room then to work
that says something about the
establishment
[Music]
i'm sad
i'm trying to offer you guys a nice
workplace
[Music]
you guys not like going to work
okay
you're just joking right it's just jerk
when you say i want to go to the usual
room
okay
no union no no no no no shut up
shut up you're ruining you're ruining it
all
yes jerk okay
okay
[Music]
set
pain tori
and striker
random chat though i've always wanted to
be a mecca pilot kiana now i want to go
to the usual room even more than last
time
[Music]
so sad but it's not the usual room so
it's a different story
[Music]
everyone wants to leave work do other
things but
you don't like being a kfp
you're losing sight of your goal and the
important things in life
which is kfp
that's my garage
you want to go to my garage i mean okay
but after after work hours okay
okay but you can't you can't use my
makeup
don't use my makeup it's mine mine
you can even work on it there are some
people working there
[Music]
they're in their free time
eh and black suit is mine
can we look at the mega yes
and right inside with you no
no no
[Music]
i mean
maybe maybe if you're a good chicken
that works hard and it's nice to me then
maybe i'll i'll put you on my lap for a
ride
in the mecca
but only if you're good thinking
as a reward
how does it sound how's that sound that
sounds good right are you motivated now
okay now work hard go back to work
[Music]
thank you
you guys are just not taking it
seriously
you're making the artist sad too if you
don't take it seriously if you're not
threatened by the looks of it
what what what will the artist think huh
like they wanted to make something
terrifying and you got you guys are like
let's go play on the playground
making them cry
oh man
jim tries to dance
allow me to be your pilot no
you have a helicopter you can't be the
pilot of everything
we need we need a helicopter pilot so
you stay in the helicopter okay
captain corncob duncan
[Music]
this is the last one i'll be reading i
ran hard to remember it
after uh korean super chat hi attention
i came here to say comrade to this past
anniversary of the 4 8 21 incident what
happened do not forget the following ah
[Music]
you mean minecraft
shush now
shush now iron heart
there's only eight super chance after
there's
felt like more came in
really okay then we got a fighter
what did you say nothing nothing it's
hard to read this in a different
language or something
okay i can't read it
now i see more there's way more than
eight super chats after that
okay not way more but quite a bunch more
definitely more than eight are you what
are you saying i didn't refresh yeah you
didn't
i mean it's not that much but
most of them are not reds are pink so
[Music]
come back
okay let's go let me close them though
okay
turning them off oh yeah black virgin is
way more than nine already
no i'm not not looking for the top
mods time time him out
time him out
[Music]
he needs a timeout
there he goes
[Music]
ah
i haven't sent mine yet you weren't
gonna send a super chat why did you wait
so long
why did you wait so
no no no no long not too late now i love
you though
keep it for tomorrow
i'm so hungry i'm so hungry i was gonna
stand one don't lie to me now you just
you know you just you only said one's
life
english speaking test
in at 4 00 am what ah 2 p.m for them uh
oh
uh-huh
like uh through like online
it was
for aim for you between uh
oh [\h__\h] that's tough man
i don't know how to say otsukasama in
korean but oscar
tattoo
[Music]
are you okay it's okay chill brandon
duncan
thank you for the pinky thank you for
another divine exquisite song cover that
i can loop forever attention the envy is
really beautiful and your singing is
just 11 out of 10. seriously love
everything about it so much my oshie
really is the absolute best thank you
just make sure to loop it because it's
so short
for someone like you that's not long
enough right you want to hear more kiwa
right i know you do i know you do it's
going to endlessly loop it forever
until the next song cover comes out
which is next week so it's actually not
that long mm-hmm
[Music]
i think you will like the one that i did
with nancy
it's very pretty
very pretty
[Music]
you know what even continue listening to
it afterwards just loop both songs okay
swan employee of the year
and maxwell the first time
crayons
[Music]
i don't know what face pulls are
speaking in gym terms again general
duncan harbor line dungeon tartarus
danish and brandon i see that i see the
light at the end of the tunnel oh my god
they're walking towards this kfp
russell [\h__\h] thank you for the pinkie
one thing to wake up to boss fangs
you're welcome it's like a good morning
song
i guess in that case
please listen to it a lot okay promise
pinky promise thank you
facelift
what no what
what
means the mamaloni art
oh wrestle bucket means the mamaloni art
where the fringe wake up tonight
don't thank me thank mama noni
and
google translate
oh
let's go thank you
i feel honored wow
we have a membership stream this weekend
so please be there or be swear
and i keep paying kiki thank you for the
pinky this is my first super chat but
i've been around since the first four
month mark oh that's still very early it
became like last year around your
birthday we found a day old kid until ah
on the same day
a day old kitten oh my gosh you're snow
your streams kept me going with energy
on her birthday of the official kfp from
me kitten and puppy
oh
you're a puppy too what the [\h__\h]
oh my god
it's so nice so jealous
it's so cute
you must be so happy so much happiness
yeah photos please please share photos i
always love to see
pictures of you guys cute pets
especially cats
thank you very much for your first
recitant i appreciate it thank you
please continue being part of kfp
douglas thank you for the red super chat
thanks for the kiss boss oh you're
welcome you're gonna get now one anyway
i guess you were
saying thank you for the pinky one why
are you saying thank you for the red one
that you're getting now
got you i got you
it's to cover the free kiss but it
doesn't cover it
but you got one for the red one too
now you're behind again
thank you and i said oh manga i can't
believe i actually made it i didn't
think about doing them all because it
looked like too much but here we are
and i really deserve some food now
[Music]
don't know what to eat maybe toast maybe
i'm just going to make toast ham and
cheese toast
easy fast
oh yeah yes it's hammy cha hun
[Music]
um
you see
i'm not even
i'm
when i wrote about what happened
yesterday
you guys used the automatic twitter
translation tool and you saw vinegar but
that's not just normal vinegar but you
all were like face palming at me like
yeah
you're making fun of me like look yeah
you should stupid why would you put
vinegar in that that's not that's not
soyuz
okay
but it's not that far off though because
when i googled there were a lot of
people who made cha han with ponzu it's
called ponzu chahan apparently i mean
it's not the
the most normal way to make john still
okay
and then um i was like
well you know what since we're not doing
cha normal challenge anymore then
whatever i mixed in tokatsu sauce
to add a little bit more
a little bit more taste you know wait i
have charm left over from yesterday i've
just remembered
i'll make toast and chat i can combine
them yeah yeah
tonkatsu not tonkotsu tonkatsu those are
two different things but yeah
no it tasted fine i mean i i originally
wanted to have the typical chaat but
it was basically fried rice
it's still fried rice
yeah
i made it with uh
some um
pork that i had in the freezer i wanted
to use it up
and egg and
leek
and uh
spring onion is a liquor spring onion
i guess it's leek
and uh rice obviously
nothing does it
and then the the ponzil and the tonkata
[Music]
the moment i realized i had no soy sauce
was when i already was like in the
middle of like i already had the
i already had the the meat grilled that
i took out of the freezer and i think my
rice was done
and i may have also already
uh
started frying the the egg and all that
yeah so it was too late
and i had to do something and i looked
in all my all my compartments but i
didn't find any soy sauce i was like
what the [\h__\h] i have no soy sauce
no way
no way what
now i will have to try it again with soy
sauce another time
[Music]
foreign
some
some uh
noodles ramen noodles usually they come
with like a packet for the ramen and
that kind of contains soy sauce
so i looked for that too i was thinking
that far yeah without even asking for
advice
and i had some noodles but they came
without the packets
[Music]
oh
that was smart i think so
it ended up being okay it was it was a
dinner at least better than throwing
everything away and ditching it and yeah
um
tomorrow sims 4 on my channel everybody
and looking forward to it uh we're going
to continue with council i think
um just felt like playing some sims
i'll put up the reservation tomorrow no
no sims one i'm not ready for that yet i
want to continue with sims 4 one more
time and then sometime soon we'll play
sims one
[Music]
soon or not so soon i don't know we'll
start with wind waker next week
so we'll see we'll see but i already got
sims ready
uh
i'm getting majima and makoto and sims
[Music]
playing with counsel and make more
more people happy
last time what did we do last time
[Music]
was christmas last time i feel like we
did something ah new years was last time
uh
so i wonder what we're gonna do next
i'm just gonna i think we're just gonna
chill play without thinking too much
about what to do this time because sims
4 streams always stress me out so much
and i think i need to learn to
just chill
chill chill the hell out
um
yeah i think easter would be coming up
but
i don't know how fast the time will pass
usually it passes by fast and seems
maybe we can get there i'm not sure
oh yeah we'll see spring
let's see spring let's just try to um
get council
some money and some skills and some jobs
and all that and uh
um
maybe maybe i don't know we can get a
pet or
uh
i don't know i don't know i don't know
we'll find something to do i could also
there are a lot of like sims 4
challenges out there
i was looking up some challenges i was
thinking maybe i could implement one in
my stream
but a lot of them don't work with the
family that i already have
yeah
i i love the racks to riches challenge
but i would have to make a new one kind
of and yeah
there was a funny challenge that's like
you start with one
uh
like character one human that has no
money and uh
four
dogs aka wolves
and one
uh raccoon
and you have to give them certain
personality traits so they actually act
a certain way and the raccoon will end
up like really trying to sabotage your
whole playthrough but you're supposed to
together with your wolf pack uh you can
send them away in some sport to get some
items for you and all that it's actually
pretty helpful gets you quite a lot of
money
um so you're just supposed to uh without
a home just earn money with your wolf
pack but the the the wasp that wash
bears the raccoon will be um
trying to sabotage you and that's the
challenge yeah
but you're also not supposed to
lose any of them nobody's supposed to
die and all that and i think it was like
about to
uh reach a certain amount of money in
the game
yeah washburn yeah and in german we say
literally wash bear to raccoons
it's so simple and so cute though
and then because they didn't wash they
watched themselves
they
they seem like a dirty animal but they
like to wash themselves
i know right it's so cute
but wait actually
in japanese it's the same
again
it's written with the same with those
kanji right
okay
yeah yeah actually you're joking you're
laughing about
it
[Music]
german and japanese instinct
and that's funny i didn't realize that i
mean i knew the word adagula but i never
thought about it so deeply that the
german language and the japanese
language both use like just the
simplicity of
wash bear as the name for the animal in
chinese as well
yeah i would i would expect that mm-hmm
in hungarian as well no no no
it's not only not only german okay
sometimes we have very
very simple obvious funny um words but
sometimes it's not only us okay
sometimes we start wearing other
other languages too
we call them trash ponders don't call
them that they're cute
ah
alana's versus pineapple
ah a pineapple is one of those words
like wash bear cause like pineapple was
a apple with like pines i guess you know
yeah yeah words words are fun
okay everybody thank you so much for and
listening to my song cover and listening
to my rambling i'll see you guys
tomorrow at sims 4 and let's have a fun
week together and please don't forget to
share uh the sun cover it had a rough
start now because of the re-upload
please please share it and care for it
sharing is caring and listen to it and
and and yeah thank you so much for your
support and your love
and making these things possible thank
you for everybody who worked on the
sound cover it turned out um mostly
great
i'm happy with
most of it
thank you everybody
[Music]
you guys very much and in germany
bye bye
[Music]
food food
i'm gonna eat some of you guys now
chicken
oh you taste so good
[Music]
thanks for the
for your wing thank you
i'll take your leg to go please
[Music]
do
you