[Music]
d
yay once again it is Super Mario Party
jorita
W and today we have some PTSD because
there's a shy guy again but this time
different people okay except me Andi do
to you uh no Shi was was super sweet but
uh we need to win orange team orange
team needs to win look to win yeah we
our team but yeah yeah we're not but
still something is dividing us
and I I hope that by the end of
today by the power of Super Mario Party
will will be divided more than
ever blue blue women blue women
wom
women so okay let's introduce ourselves
we have a another princess down below me
narissa who are you uh I am princess hi
oh I'm Princess Peach
Princess Peach can I have your autograph
of course you
may I love Peach she's my favorite she's
so fav you might remember from my purse
my Pur oh yeah oh my God I can't believe
we're in the presence of a Princess
Peach yeah a real
princess Monty are you going to look
under her skirt I will I'm
looking no yes run faster the that it
may fly
upwards be such a pervert oh my God
sorry sorry sorry should be more shy
like you yeah be careful have some
manners like crony well crony introduce
yourself
then can I to this is Oro crony from H
English promise and I am a shy
guy shy are you I know that song are you
shy really I'm super shy this is me
shaking a don't be so shy there's just
two princesses around you who are super
charming and super beautiful there's no
need to be shy at all here and those who
can execute
me we oh why would we do
that cuz you guys are
royalty
oh you guys have the power I guess even
in the Super Mario World royalty
executes oh God no no I'm going to get
sued they're going to kill you don't sue
me
Nintendo okay and then we have a
comeback somebody is here again I wonder
why G Moine I'm here to
win this time bring honor to the orange
color G please red kingom will prevail
yeah don't let everybody walk over you
this time come on I'm going to grief
everyone else so you can win what the
heck
go no don't worry we will play fair and
square then we'll be no teams don't you
want to
win I don't know my luck last time kind
of kind of terrible well that just means
your luck this time is going to be good
okay yeah let's go we're going to win we
play a win here exactly the power of
friendship speaking of winning
chat who do you think will win this time
yeah put in your votes on the
non-existent pole of my heart yeah send
in your votes on this um
crony a lot of cron number they believe
in you I think is going to win too I'm
going to be honest no I don't think so
she could she totally could but I think
last time uh it was a great indicator
that I will lose just because I I was
like winning until the end of the game
that is a sign to you that you will just
not win if you're winning that means
you're not winning so yeah always stay
losing until you win yeah yeah damn okay
yay that is I I will try to not get the
first star then because that will be my
detriment
no I will give my first star to one of
the
Blues take I'll take it oh
no it will Cur
you that's what you think I don't have
good luck when I'm winning I stay on top
oh that sounds so
confident I'm almost scared
bars all right how do we start we can uh
I think do we up here I think we all
have to run up here oh
oh should we have gyro control games gyo
control you mean motion
control yeah um
uh what will we do have to shake our
controller really fast what's going to
what going to ask does that work with a
Pro Controller cuz I only have a Pro
Controller okay Pro controllers are
built special that's true okay okay wait
I'm down for whatever do just press
Mario party cuz last time gigy I think
was controlling the room so I don't
really know what I'm doing oh I think
friends
okay and I I wanted to look at the pro
rules cuz they unlocked after the last
time what are the pro rules the ru this
rule set is for players looking to test
their skills if you're comfortable with
party rules why don't give these rules
to try
what oh they're saying that the motion
controls are joycon only so I'm using
controller too never mind okay maybe
next
time sorry why didn't they build the pro
controllers to be shaking
why that's a this is a lot instructions
yeah like yeah there's a lot of reading
should I chat should we do pro controls
the only H the pro controls Pro rules
the only thing I don't really I'm not
sure if I like it normal this is this is
too complicated I just don't know if I
like the bonus Stars being announced at
the start cuz then you can kind of aim
for it it was it was nicer when it was
like says it's fixed at 12 turns oh ly
okay let's not do it uh and then we're
going to do the shopping mall this time
I hope you girls don't okay with it gigy
wanted to do shopping mall it looks so
cute it is cute you did select Pro rules
oh yeah we got to go B oh
oopsie we don't want Pro rules we are
shitty beginners so we will Cho
something appropriate yay y okay y then
we're going to do the rainbow Galleria
which seems to be one star more
difficulty but I honestly don't think
the difficulty Stars matter at all in
this game they really oh yeah okay and
we're going to do 15 rounds do I have to
do these settings here or where where
are the 15 round settings I guess yes
and then it's next yeah there okay and
turn off motion mini games okay 15 bonus
stars on mini game help on motion mini
games off mini game selection random
okay so are you ready to fight in
It's a Mario Party up it's a Mario party
without Mario though we don't want Mario
here sorry Mario you weren't invited to
the party but we held it in your name
yeah loser Nissa you and me we're going
to do shopping and these other ladies
are going to carry our shopping bags
right
okay I I can carry everyone's shopping
bags you want to carry everybody's
shopping bags I'm I I won't make a
beautiful woman carry my shopping
Bay but what about yourself you're also
beautiful
woman anyway
Superstar it's everyone's first time
don't explain it please toad H please
please
you it's over it's so
over over because before we even started
niers
wow coins to go shopping with yipp
pocket
money I'm going to buy a
quo and then first star and then I'm
going to eat the qu
the okay what uh this map looks kind of
complicated with the elevators yeah it's
like you should have had the rules go up
that's boring that's lame I want to be
surprised let's go Shy
Guy y I'm so shy oh no a shy guy super
shy oh my God your looks kind of crazy
yeah look at these I'm amazed oh my God
there's a lot of pads you don't sound
that
amazed M wait hold on where which way
okay yeah this is confusing there's too
many ways I think it's on the second
floor so you want to go up on an
elevator
yeah oh I see
it and you get an
[Music]
item ah the random box nice that's not
good
cute Monty the fatx so
cute okay that's that's what you get out
of charging so
hard damn that was a lot of effort for
nothing I know why did I why is happen
it's starting out great isn't it yes
yeah yeah okay it's the Underdog Story
not bad not bad I'm coming for you is
that really the ah okay yeah it says on
the top left what the closest PA is no
it's not
thank you for making it so easy for me
game such a nice baby game all
right
oh oh the princess looks at the board
I'm taking it yeah I'm taking a second I
want want surpr going on I just don't
know what's
happening I don't know what's the cluess
princess stro classic do you need over
do you need to be carried up up the
stairs n n okay okay anyway you got it
time to roll a
one that would be
funny she's going far everybody well you
look you got a lucky
item
yeah
o That's that could be good that could
be very good that
is mini time our first
one come on gigy orange team one vs3
against
sh hell
no
no but I'm scared she's she's she might
be really strong she might [\h__\h] us up I
this is my first time playing the game
okay snowball fight but it's one against
three she has monkeys
ow she killed me oh
help they can aim I really we want to
not go for the monkeys but for crony
right so let's prioritize that but
okay at these these monkeys are
useless they're trying their best I'm
sure yeah leave those leave them alone I
get it I get I get the vibe this is with
it I can't
aim spatial awareness
zero monkeys are so cute is this each
other is this pickle that's [\h__\h] Mony
oh my God wait that was mine fro I think
we both we both hit
our damn that happened so fast I
couldn't even do my joke before my eyes
oh my god let's
go Kar you're you guys are tied for
first place what does that tell you we
have just
begun means nothing we're you that means
we're going to win ah as that means you
guys are tur into enemies no no no no no
no no peaceful winners Ling peace and
Harmony oh she's already on the second
floor let's go Queen but you know
I don't have money you know what they
say about the first star you don't want
it you're so close to it you just have
to win the next mini game and you can
buy it yeah but are you going to M
money what what is that 200% what is
that 200 yeah 200% off what is
that what it say are you are you it
doesn't let us look hey does she get to
look but we don't yeah we don't get to
look oh good I want to understand I want
the
knowledge are you I won't risk it I W it
yeah oh my God a stampart Col stamps I
love collecting stamps okay okay
okay go Monty go Monty go d we
go okay okay see you didn't have to
charge it too much yeah charge you don't
charge L yeah charge less l i will
charge
less wait how do I
get straight girl
straight I feel like someone is going to
buy it before I do does it
move yeah yes oh yeah after you buy it
because someone is going to buy it
before I do I want to go I want to go
all the way up am I allowed I'm going to
see oh the
elevator yes I would like
oh I mean it's golden it's got golden do
let let me add
it are you sure that's a good idea I
want to know what's up here I guess it's
a gamble yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
oh this is only for celebrities this
floor oh look how cool this floor
no
why you know Orange has to win this time
can you at least try I'm I'm try oh so
close to the star I had two
more yeah I guess I'm probably not going
to make it either right but I'm still
going to go up well prony can afford I
think you should I don't think I can
afford it
okay I don't want to make the same
mistake as I did last time where I
missed out on the star just because I
assumed someone would get there before
me oh we're going to wait I'm going to
land where you are which me hold hands
well oh buy something first but we might
have a
Dell if I buy something now and I don't
win in the mini game then I might not
have enough money
but risky
maybe something cheap at
[Music]
least I I'll get something cheap then
I'm I'm I just need one more one more
coin I'll get one coin right at the mini
game for
sure yeah I want the
pipe thank you okay let's let's dwell
crony what those who made purchases can
go to the raffle shop for drawings
it's on the second floor how fun
Goa oh oh this all right this doesn't it
only happens L later in the game okay
a I wanted to Dell
her no dueling
no duel so
disappointed thank
God I'm probably not going to have the
option to go up
anyway what if I also don't have enough
money oh wait I do have enough oh right
I got coins from the
field M oh what's happening to
youy you could have got a star there was
a chance that you would get a star
freaked me out there coins the beginning
of the
game I've never seen a hien block so
early on oh no
don't give me the monkeys
please unly flying I think we played
that last time too what was that
[Music]
again I was so bad at this I think you
might win
this
N I don't know just don't get stuck I
guess on the
sides
ow M oh OHA oh I going to say you're
good at this let's let's let's go let's
just try it
go don't get caught lock in girls lock
in everyone's locking in lock
in oh that's so high you're cutting me
off from my friends that's
so that's so Co oh no this isn't fair oh
my God what am I
this isn't
fair this isn't
fair I literally no way out me too oh my
God damn well I think Gigi is going to
win all of a sudden yeah I think so too
that so scary that's terrifying I'm not
going to be able to coins get the
star wonderful No I don't want either I
don't want the first St no because then
people will also totally like they will
hit me from the get-go everybody will
like try to get my money and my
star oh buddy I don't think I can get
him I think I'm going the complete
opposite
direction I don't want the first time oh
hey Yoshi's on the third floor
Yosi Yoshi I'm
far damn oh oh you guys can make it to
him actually really oh yeah there's a
way for you to go up the
elevator you could always use your item
block and try to switch with someone and
give you more time no it's it's it's
okay yeah yeah yeah my C Yoshi a St oh
nice oh my God cute I wonder 50 coins if
you get all four stars o
sick but you have to exchange it where
ever you're so poor get out of
here you're really close to Yoshi oh
versus I have nothing to lose extra
game hey oh three
points oh now I can afford
it let's go more fighting you want to
fight oh their coin some one with more
most money oh you choose oh no
what oh no oh no wait I might random if
I lose this I might not have enough
money to buy the
star oh no which is fine I don't want
the first star
sandwich oh God the
pressure it's the same thing again just
don't yeah don't get oh God how okay
oh these sandwiches look so
good ow okay okay I get the
vibe let's go let's go it's like crab
gam you stop try Harding yeah yeah
tasting C
around let's go yummy sand can I just
eat the sandwich yeah I really want to
eat a sandwich now yeah I'm hungry hello
guys um ah I'm so scared
I'm so scared do not be
afraid giggy lead away from me I'm so
scared sorry oh did not mean to jump on
you you totally
did I'm so scared sorry sorry sorry I'm
so scared I feeling a lot of pressure
never my
intention oh they're going faster can
can I'm I'm not trying to jump on you am
I so easy to step on or something yeah
you're so small fair play only no
jumping on each other's
heads no they're so fast oh they're so
fast did somebody die
already I died oh you did okay crony
it's
c what let's go I got
M you win yeah you can definitely buy
the star now I don't want it has a curse
on it and everybody will try to steal
things from me yeah I know oh no that's
nothing not at all right mhm go on buy
your star you earned it thank you I
would say I did
yeah oh my God I barely lost anything
this is
awesome
stons
Monty show us what you got okay was your
choice worth
it le le judge Le
okay you just you're just trying to stay
up here cuz surely the star will go on
the third floor next the st's going to
be up here can't move it yeah playing
the long
game that is so op like getting free
items this is so expensive tiet a
mushroom ticket and PayDay triple D more
money and then wow there's no telling
where I'll
go okay here I go go get your star I'll
I'll get the stamp first but who knows
maybe I'll only roll
one what why did you say that I don't
know why you say that this is the second
time today that we're calling something
like that oh my God what why what this
game is listening to us
I think so too Illuminati is it you help
I'm scared are you [\h__\h] kidding
me are you [\h__\h] joking at least
you're really
lucky I don't know if I go this lucky
we're taking it slow we're window
shopping yeah yeah we are window
shopping oh
3v1 well no when are we getting the
other mini games no no no no stop stop
landing on red spaces on again off again
what is this ah I think I know what it
is is the but press the M button yeah
yeah yeah here I flip the switch and I
but this is difficult honest oh oh it's
still difficult oh what what the
hell get good girls it's good so
scary oh what I jumped what
all right no more practicing narissa
okay okay
uh start
um we have to live or we will die yeah
oh what
oh sh what is going on we have to live
or we will die we have to live come on
GG die get C to live or we will die if I
don't if I don't live here
no
die let's go I'm
gaming so much money gaming wow gaming
amazing that felt good I'm so powerful
right now yeah give me the money make me
Rich now you're going to have a
star yeah you're going to have a star
star one step at a time
literally oh somebody pick up
Yoshi he's so L what is a FL sale we can
purchase
everything oh that'd be crazy now I
think it would be like just
discounted what what the [\h__\h] is going
on well one step on the escalator takes
you really far oh no you lose unlucky
spaceace oh I lose no matter what
[Laughter]
no wow everybody's unlucky except mostly
me there's no telling where I'll go do I
want that don't I dare you I dare you
okay let me look at the board this goes
all the way
around oh there's like a Bowser space
yeah you want to stay on the third floor
don't you yes I'm going to use a
mushroom tiet
all hey where are you going with this oo
I can't tell yes where would this
mushroom ticket take me plus five let's
go
oh looking so far where you going you
got a
Spam
stamp she going it's going to be crazy
is behind
me wow am I landing on the Bowser space
I think I'm landing on the Bowser space
oh that would be fun oh God yes oh yeah
this out
everyone all according to Kaka right
bye-bye GG all according to plan fat fox
versus fat Fox wait why is he kind of
what what
what beach beach hold in your urges
speach peaches peaches peaches peaches
peaches yes no what the
[\h__\h] look at crowny She's suffering
giggy why you
coins no what are you talking about I
love having two coins we're going to be
I love to carry
light GG don't punish everyone just
because you are
sad but I want I want us to be together
she she just want to give you you still
have enough you still have enough to buy
the coin the the star she wants to give
you some type of Bowser you know yeah I
get it yeah yeah it's very
thoughtful all right ooh are you going
to get Yoshi before CR is he so close no
she's kind of close but he's also
leaving Co yeah I
mean it is what it is oh it's 20 okay I
feel better I wouldn't have gotten it no
matter what
okay ah Kata getting the first star is a
bad sign as we know Chad so I will be
losing today let's go of course of
course it's up there of course I knew it
would be up there you shouldn't have
used that Speedy ticket damn it girl I
have no idea what you're doing you're
sabotaging
yourself
Yoshi yeah you know what no but don't
worry I'm not going to get him because
uh everybody gets a chance in a game
um to get him I just get like an
advantage in the
game thank you thank you thank you Yosi
you should get
him I think we all should get a Yoshi oh
everyone attend oh great
yes yeah yeah yeah yeah we we play a
game and the winner gets Yoshi and
honestly it's so overpowered to have a
partner so do your best
this kind of a lone wolf so no no this
could change everything for you
crony wait a race uhoh oh I need Yoshi
cuz I'm not moving anywhere I'm stuck on
the
map a long race yeah what the heck
platform [\h__\h]
terrified platform oh oh so
cute
uh is this like only Only One race or is
it like in a different uh partner game
we had like three different games is
this just one how did you eat that GG
just ran into it oh okay I see
M wait it looks so funny how Yoshi is
carrying
Monty you should be carrying Yoshi
honestly okay we
can begin I guess is the Apple we're
doing a practice run Apple's good it
gives you a boost
ow hello guys can we start no narissa
wants to practice everything until the
end I'm scared it's okay to fruit will
be do
oh in front in front of you have the boo
but people can steal it oh oh okay there
we go my God I don't think
so
fair well I got there first you know
how did you make it here
already oh
no
uh-oh faster faster go go go go go go go
go woo fly high
Yoshi what is this camera angle oh no I
know is camera angle
no oopsies I hate this camera angle yeah
I don't I don't really like the camera
either
no oh
no change angle where the [\h__\h] am I
supposed to go game okay okay okay
what what no no the jum is lagging oh my
God hello ping it is Ping
what it's over it's over I can't make
it okay why is it jumping that's
ridiculous you're [\h__\h] oh my God why
isn't it jumping anymore oh my God you
you you need to take a step back gy I
think like it's otherwise just like
rigged as
heck didn't flut flut
water okay I'm catching up but it won't
be enough for
it oh won is
serving what is she serving what am I
you
think no stop oh my God are going to get
got the body you need look at you you
got
Yoshi I'm a lone wolf though you can
help again you can
again look you wanted to play as Yoshi
now you're Yoshi and shy guy wow oh my
God budy the best of both World y
Yoshi that's great can i r
it I think he just stands by you yeah a
man you get like everything twice
it's so good if an opponent passes you
your ally what's the point of getting
this thing then yeah he just going to
[\h__\h] abandon you excuse me just stay
ahead of every no one is behind you what
a harlot oh yeah right NY what's
happening Unfaithful this is a super
shop we have items that are
super I'll take a look
bless thank you he's got some some
interesting items super swap nrow swap
spaces with an opponent of your choice
oh I'm I'm going to buy that even though
it takes all my
money thanks for shopping with us
yay powerful mirror that's that seems
too overpowered well it also costs a lot
that's why it's
super superb
can I get
anywhere
[Laughter]
[Music]
here no the answer is no the princess is
slow take it
easy princess shouldn't walk too far is
that the second second turn of the road
that you only get one yeah oh my god
well yay blame it on the crane it was
the Crane's fault always you walking so
slowly is the Crane's fault oh ah this
cute
game ah I like
it don't get
caught this one's evil BR what yeah this
one's evil I why did you guys get ones
that are like
easy wrong shy
guy oh God
let's go let's go let's
go go go go
Nissa go on I'm try I'm trying to figure
out how it works you
know you caught
twoo you got it you were in for the
win
y as long as one of us survives hey
crony
hey okay okay okay team Orange let's go
don't get
caught I have my straty
no bye no no
no Monty
survive what if she gets
me then it's over it will be so over
what if she gets
me
help what if she gets me
why did she picked me up sorry what
happened it happed it's okay she can't
move anywhere yeah it's not like it's
not like I'm getting anywhere in this
game true she deserves this for how much
she's going through yeah I'm literally
dying
like I deserve to win at the mini games
I'm never going to get a star at this
rate oh flash sale oh cool it's a Goa
like it's in balls oh my God uh during
this turn what what what what what you
guys skipped through the text too fast
skip through all of that everything is
half off including Stars okay wa too bad
I can't afford
anything oh my God what's the point of
getting all this oh you can copy her
item wait that's crazy what you just
copied her really expensive
no [\h__\h] oh my god oh y what I didn't
know they could do that bro
wow
crazy I see those are the no money
strats all well yeah you don't have
enough money to nav a
star it would not be worth it to steal M
from anybody besides narissa I'm so
sorry anywhere
you guys are so [\h__\h] mean to
me we're
not you're targeting me just cuz I win
games why would you why would you Ste
from anybody
else Yosi Pi me again I'm so
sorry Peach you're the most delicious
I'm so sorry nobody else has
coins yeah and you taste like peaches
I'm going to rage
quit this is not no I haven't moved
anywhere you are cont Co obligated to
stay in this class oh see I'm going I'm
going to lose coins anyway you're going
to lose coin coins for me just to
[\h__\h] lose that Yosi is going to make
it oh oh thank you
oh you
should what a waste of
money I'm so wasteful can't believe it
this
economy wow yeah what's
happening where are we going this time
Monty what is how many spaces is
this are you see you good Nissa
no don't worry
the underdog always wins in the
end this is true I am the underdog I'm
not moving yeah yeah so you're winning
later
on just eventually you have to be
patient damn it but actually crony was
the underdog so she's on the uprise
right now damn oh I'm still kind of the
underdog though
yeah here we go um is anybody close to
the star not that I have money but no no
one is close to the star wow you guys
are on the third floor so vly close all
right then I'll just be chilling on this
floor maybe you can steal Yoshi from
crony oh wait I think I'm landing on a
bad
field uh cuz the one after that H please
take GG's coins um take crony she has 12
see I will do random cuz most of you are
around the same okay I'll do okay okay
oh oh yeah mash the butt and mash it
mash
it
go she is
mashing oh oh what you didn't Mash very
hard did
you oh it's because I have a case over
it oh I got to take off the case oh no
wait wait I'm I haven't passed you but
if I'm on the same field does it still I
think you have to pass damn damn damn
now you're giving back
to only a y Five Points only a little
bit just a
little you're kind of close Okay this
one this one yeah if you take you take
the elevator you can go to the second
floor wait is that Shy Guy drinking from
the water from the pool he totally win
the next mini
game you're going up I don't have any
coins you're the you're a mini game
winner yeah it'll be easy you're winner
in our heart winning mini
games just get some money from Mario's
credit card
Peach yeah Mario doesn't have any money
I'm the princess in this relationship I
you don't have money either who is
Peach's daddy
anyway Bowser I don't I just give me
coins that's why she got issues with
Bowser cuz she got Daddy Issues yeah
exactly plush is
over we didn't even get to buy anything
them
leaving we're stuck here game oh let's
go money money money they realize how
poor we are oh okay GG we got to win
yeah I'm going to we have to get you
that star please Rocky rope race what is
that what are we
doing we're about to find out oh this
okay this doesn't seem like a good idea
yeah we okay okay wait GG so who who's
swinging first you let go and
swing hold on C now you okay okay hold
hold on
okay okay I'm ready wa wait try holding
on I want to see that you can do
it can you hold on crony
can you can you hold
[Music]
on you have to hold
on wa can you hold
on what what do you mean hold
on wait
do okay okay she can hold
on do okay okay wait okay wait wait I
was like oh man I was looking at the
bottom
screen okay I was like oh my God like
damn I'm really good at this
game I see it do be like that sometimes
okay now we got it now we got it okay
okay remember luck G let's do this got
this okay all right all right no
pressure no pressure C
no pressure why isn't it
grabing isn't it
grab Get Wrecked girls get
wrecked we're going to win this growny
why gra hey okay okay
okay oh yeah oh yeah don't worry Nissa
I'm worrying do not worry they're going
to win they're already there oh yeah
going to
[Applause]
yeah hey I blam the P sun dial
baby let's go steal all my money dialing
it up to 100 baby hey I lost it all it
was Karma but oh that's a lot of money
yay wow we're TI narissa new turn I
can't buy a star
just roll low and then it'll be okay I
think don't leave me crony we had such a
good time oh don't go too far you're
going to take my Yoshi I will don't go
too far don't go too far don't go one
one
one bro new stamp does Yoshi get a stamp
too a you're so
considerate a she doesn't get a stamp
that sucks it's messed up don't go down
stay with me I want your Yoshi but if I
get Yoshi now would he only be there for
me for one round yeah won oh
[Music]
Manute so is anybody closer to the star
now come on where am I
headed there is literally nothing here
CL to the star right now oh all right
everyone if you want to switch with me
you probably could get there where will
I go
ooh a
mystery why did it place oh you're right
okay why are the red one so rude oh but
you're not getting the minus okay thank
God don't overcharge she will never
learn I'm moderately charged
M what happens to go back down think
think or you can get a this way let's
get a stamp I want to buy
something
ah so I'm guessing the 200% sticker you
give it to somebody and then everything
in the item shops will be 200% for them
more expensive it's crazy that would be
so
[Music]
rude I want
to no I think this is fun oh you going
for it
okay only five coins oh oh oh the Stars
to are 20% more uh 200% more expensive I
I'm losing money
o it's okay been there I'm
broke you were once where I
[Music]
was hold up buy your bootstraps to get
to where you are now 13 only wow if I
only had a double
dice
wait you'll still probably be able to
reach it faster if you switch with
me are you are you okay are you okay I'm
good I'm good I'm
good Peach my lady you don't have the
money so you don't mind if I switch with
you do you yeah I don't I don't care
but I might I might still fail in
getting the star so we'll see we'll see
probably not well what if I roll one
what if by switching with you I get your
luck you're really really bad on the
plus side now I get the stamp and I
already got the other stamp oh I missed
the stamp a you missed two stamps oh no
I don't care about Stamps
no oh maybe he did get her look oh no no
no oh no no I'm not getting a star but
golden items how about a star give me a
star but wait the golden pipe will be us
golden pipe yeah what does the golden
pip it will bring me to the you directly
to the star oh jeez cuz I'm kind of
scared that crony will in the next turn
switch with me with her miror and get my
star that's in front of me I would never
do that would you really not do that
no are you
certain no what are your plans for the
future crony I don't
know that's a deep question I'm pressing
X on that so I'm going to get the golden
pipe so that I can get a start later
yeah so now I'm out of money I have to
save up again yeah wait wa you're not
going to switch with
me no she is that's why she's saying you
shouldn't have done that I
know all right all
right my turn if she switches with me
then that was the right choice totally
totally
Oh yay
yay I'm going to kill myself what's
going on is your game bugged or
something I have no
idea oh my god oh oh maybe swap with
someone oh you're making some moves now
into the have
no what why is my face on there oh it
can still change right yeah ah so for
example I'll Target
it Monty will give a star doesn't have a
star but okay yeah give me a star okay
okay here you looks like there's nothing
to get but if there's nothing to give at
least give me some money
like my three coins what's the
point uh oh
okay didn't we have the situation before
we can shake down time to get back my
money team you know what to do don't
lose ah how I play this whack them all
don't get whacked by Monty isn't Monty
the one who should get whacked normally
yeah
oh wait we don't get any
coins yeah we we will if we win we yeah
we get to keep all the coins that okay
let's let's start I think why are you
targeting me I just G I was only able to
hit you
[Laughter]
so wackamo let's
go no more fist much much money do you
get seven each only seven yeah you only
get to keep seven oh you get to keep 21
if you win wait oh was I thought I was
Peach oh God wrong princess wrong
princess I get one coin
everyone come here crony
oh come here right now
ow oh you're not doing very well in this
game you look at me right now
three coins two from
crony
yi yay yay we did it I'm so proud of us
that was an easy game now I have
coins G coins oh 36 so many coins wait
oh my God I got so much money again yeah
why y new oh I was broke just a moment
ago oh bye Yosi
[Music]
no oh Yi left I'll miss him he was cute
he was okay he was
delightful what are you going to do
crony you going to switch with
me I don't know if it's worth it it's
not worth it it's not worth it not wor
not worth it not worth it it's not worth
it seven you're only seven away it would
be a waste to switch of me with the
mirror you have a high chance of rolling
that
anyway honestly that is you in my luck
when I get one every single time it's a
different story with you
narissa um you need the mirror Nissa to
get anywhere I
see I don't think I'm going to wait hold
on is there at least a
stamp okay I might as well just get a
stamp what a CO stamp it's okay if I
don't get a
star yes
stamp guys I might yay
stamp second Stamped Out and I still
have the pipe for the first and the
versus oh do you want to buy a
pipe oh wait you you you didn't land on
the shop
oh oh man please leave me alone
a why is it always about money in this
game I'm
exhausted
same trampoline trampoline that sounds
like
trampoline I think that's yeah yeah
trampoline oh cute okay uhoh avoid the
horn an oh oh okay I was confused I'm
fine
okay understand
[Music]
yeah gy couldn't even give a full 10
coins I'm broke oh I can jump on you
guys life is
hard life is strange honestly what I
what I didn't see there was something
there it's cuz you all wouldn't stop
jumping on everyone's
heads gy you going to get rich now yay
money
y you guys are bad at this game me says
who what do you mean by
that don't want to hear that from you I
just rolling
one it's legendary you're going to make
history Nissa I know the most
consecutive runs ones
rolled in a in a Mario Party do
something so terrible right now as long
as you don't do it to me no no do you
have a as long as you don't do it to me
no you you could still
don't let other people guil trip you do
what you want to
do what do you want to do should I do it
it's going to be so terrible no no no no
no no orange orange orange team we're
going to come on don't don't let her
guil trip you don't let her guil trip
you there are no
teams think about it like this she has a
gold pipe so immediately after she buys
this star she could go straight to the
next one and buy
it but I won't I won't because I won
have
Advantage Advantage you should use it no
no no you should use it betrayal now CR
okay I thought you were on my side but
then you followed it up with a now no no
no no please orange what about orange
come on G what's the point of buying it
if you're not going to use it I'm not
going to if you do that if you do this
I'm not going to invite you Mario hey
hey hey a game is just a game a game is
just a game it doesn't matter after this
it's going to be
okay
no come on GG is not like that K is
together think about you're giving her
you're giving her a cute no no don't
don't let her kill Tri you don't let her
go Tri youy gy what do what you want to
do
you got this for a reason are you going
to do this every single time someone
Bargains with you are you going to do
this every single time you might as well
not use the item what's the point of
getting the item I'm going to
Yom
ROM random she's going to get two
stars and we have zero Stars come on
think about it game two stars two stars
so yelling get
me what have you done what have you
done what everyone was yelling at me I
was no why you say C I didn't even do it
you laughed you laughed so happily when
the sticker was put on me no no no funny
I was just laughing cuz it was funny
yeah well that's funny to you why is it
a joke to you that I you're my and I
think it's
funny I I I'm doubting that I'm your
now sometimes you just got to look
everyone always bullies me so sometimes
you just got to get bullied too I can't
afford it can I just maybe move
I don't
[Laughter]
want stop laughing I hate
you bro yes yes what do you mean yes
Peach you got to just roll another one
next time I curse you I shall curse you
I'm sure I will I'm already
Happ to play mini games why are you so
happy yo I'm going to Revenge
myself I I will get this star one way or
another how long do I have that
sticker G it's gone
now that is ridiculous gy I'm so
disappointed I thought we had they were
yelling at me they were screaming and
yelling you could have done random then
you then you could have like blames the
randomness of it I there would have been
no point stressed
out but it's okay you did the right
thing there would have been a point if
you put it on crony because she's right
in front of the start she's going to get
it now it wouldn't it wouldn't have
worked because it was for that turn only
I hope you roll a one
crony I probably will
actually H we'll see we'll see
Raa what are you thinking about you're
going to roll a one
anyway what the heck is wrong with you
what the heck is wrong with you mean to
me you're so mean to me you said you
were roll one anyway you know it anyway
you know your
destiny why is your block so fancy you
could probably roll a 10 too wait was it
always so fancy it's a it's a custom
dice block right why' you why' you do it
too that's Mar
better n what are your thoughts right
now why you use a custom block for yeah
isn't that one to five or no no no
that's like to 10 don't care I'm not
going to win you can win you have 41
coins you have 67 you're about to get a
start yes I have no
stars you're about to get one I'm not
about to get one
you are somehow this Mario Party is
turning out to be more dramatic than the
last I don't like this one I don't like
this one I was so bad at
this oh God go wait attack your opponent
by you don't want to get ground pounded
too much you don't want to get hit by
the wave too much so you have to balance
jumping and ground pounding cuz if you
ground pound all the time there's a high
chance that you are going to get hit by
the way
I'm
standing powerful D I standed another
day sweep GG g g is
murdering look at that
nice well moving up in the world we're
halfway through the game you girls
should start getting some stars now how
about that okay are you flaming
us no After all you've done to
me go on crony it's your time get that
star oh I don't think so it's your
time oh H it's your time a
star woo blue te you're happy for her
you're happy for her
[Applause]
[Music]
Bo
[Laughter]
woo oh Stars up there huh oh my
God
huh
well I won't that doesn't sound good oh
oh thrift store oh a thrift store oh oh
something cheap oh oh no never mind
oh he just takes it from you oh I
thought he gives it to he just took
you he
took no why did he do that that that's a
Rude Dude yay but 30 coins what a deal
what a deal you stole that item that is
pretty exactly
10 wow okay okay you're getting the
money from that take so long to oh there
we go you're going to get the money no
no no she gets only money in there so oh
what she doesn't walk that far I get to
walk
that it's crazy that is
overpowered I could take someone no it's
only 50 coins oh you could do a Goa you
could do a gotcha you can totally do
random I think random would be a good
idea if you hurt me again I think I
think you should take a star however
randomizing would be a good idea no cuz
me and I don't have a star G you have to
be balanced and fair you're not going to
you're going to get like there are two
out of three chances two out of three oh
see she's even excluded peach peach is
excluded you think I should do it I
think random random is a good idea
really no you have you bance out who
you're punishing who you hurting it
doesn't matter who
you to have star might as well take a
star I don't don't have random if I if I
take this I will have enough money for
the other star yeah so narissa you're
excluded I know and and then all this
but maybe maybe I shouldn't so I can
have a star and money yeah I mean okay
that honestly why not wait hey hey
I so [\h__\h] done with you
gy I am going to talk to management and
I will un orange you you will not be
orange anymore you lost orange
perms You Can Be You Can Be yellow you
can be
green I will un orange you at this very
I'm calling management call calling
management why would you doing aam I
wanted I wanted to take it from C you
know you know what giggy that is that is
honestly very small pee Behavior so I
will make you small accordingly small
very might as well go downstairs yeah
might I might as well go down there we
go yeah get out of here go as far as you
can away from me I'm just going
to hope you like being
small oh narissa can get a star I'm not
going to why
also let me change you why are you self
sabotaging yourself I don't get it I can
feel it cuz I've been unlucky this whole
game yeah what color oh that's me too
wait what color do you want to be anyway
wait it changes all of us why does it do
that I I I I'll change your color later
maybe I don't want to be green UNG
greenify
me I'm greenify you wait um how do we do
this how can I is it my turn no right
okay do I have time to un orange
you creepy how to un orange GG
sure all un oranges your ooshi un
oranges her takes the orange out of
her where's the stamp booth that I we
turned stuff in oh oh it's right in the
beginning yeah I see give me my stamp
coins
yay y money congratulations GG thank
you woo rich little mole hey yay now
you're basically first place yeah
yeah now I'm waddling
away from the
CR waddle waddle till the very next day
I'm going to go back upstairs no you
can't oh my God I will try to go back
upstairs yeah knowing my luck I'm I'm
not going to get anywhere
so see that guys are like you're going
to get the star I'm not going to get the
star not with that kind of
mindset I'm going to roll one I'm not
even trying to roll
one you can you can use the double
dice damn it it's too difficult to un
orange you
okay just roll just roll okay you're
taking too much time we're standing in
the bo I want to play mini games wait
wait wait where is where is everybody
right now is anybody
close oh there is
H yeah and then you get my luck yeah um
I will go right in front of you because
after how excited you were for me to
lose my stars I don't want see that's
why I said I wasn't going to get one I
knew she was going to do this of course
I was she hat me everything's too unfair
I lost two stars a ha two
stars she's a
hater a hater I'm getting Justice you're
a hater Justice you're a hater and a
gatekeeper I'm a gatekeeper okay not a
gatekeeper the gays
Tak where are I don't know man what are
you
keeping let's go
let the Gaze out kiar if anybody
especially Gigi touches my star again I
you should steal her star again I I
don't know what I can do next I have to
but wouldn't it be funny bro are you
[\h__\h] kidding me but yeah behind you
upstairs oh man at least I'm getting my
stamp
now stamp
oh
man
oh nice take something useless for you
is usess stuff no no not yetay okay yeah
I don't care about these items that much
oh you like that one I prefer the P
thank you what three coin three
coins bro W damn mine was at least 30
coins Dam the item you stole from her
I just need to go somewhere I don't know
where how about the
males look you can you can get a star
I'm not going to get I'm not going to
you're six away Double Di you're double
you steal a star you're star oh wait you
can't I don't have that kind of money
you made it you can get coins
though I could get coins do I want to
get
coins yeah want to take coin from I
think me yeah sorry sorry crony cuz I
deserve it yeah this is payback for the
time when you took my coin you're just
going to let her take
it she should still fighting she fought
back she doesn't really think she
deserves it she was fighting
back well thank you yeah of course I
appreciate that you're so sweet I know
fellow woman sharing a few coins with me
oh he he see and now you get a star yay
yay we all have is
[Music]
rewarded friendship friendship what what
is that I don't know friendship anymore
yay magic y y thank you everyone yay
well it's only moving further back yeah
watch time Why didn't it go to another
floor damn this is the superior floor
yeah well I hope everybody's happy with
their stars
now it's even now so you don't have to
Target
me you're landing on the red
space uh I'd rather be
downstairs oh okay is this Stockholm
syndrome oh and now you found oh you
knew
woo let's
go game
yay what a
comeback I don't want let go I don't
want to I don't want to be a team with
you anymore tiny
people no take me back please I'll I'm
going to grief them just
watch no you won't I don't want
you do that I'll end you give me wild
melon sort the fruit in teams of
two I
see wow melon oh I
see
okay should I secret oops should I
secretly sabotage our team no because
then you do badly too yeah that's okay
don't don't put it so close to the this
is so weird don't do anything you'll
regret takanashi you need coins
too I can't help that I picked the thing
that I was like well I guess I'm going
to be bad I guess I'm going to just take
the L so I could go downstairs melon I
got rewarded W
melon I guess that a sabotage move that
I just
did I guess I'll try oh no oh wait girl
I'm trying okay why you put that there
in my way wait why are you taking my
watermelon I have to you can do
bananas
we yay oh my
god well well
well I don't know it just so
happened she doesn't know how to play
the game name
kfp give her a break it's her second
time there's aash next turn more things
on sale
Mario oh my God you can get Mario as an
ally voiced by Chris PR no it's me
Mario oh wow Chris BR no
noisy rat
man okay let's
see I need more stickers this doesn't
convey my feelings at
all how are you feeling right now I
don't know it's very
complicated you got your revenge we lost
at the game just like you
wanted why are you here with me team
that is not an equal Revenge that is not
enough revenge for for me getting a star
star what uh
um no that's going to the third floor I
don't want to go to the third floor yeah
not from
here one three three's good
enough yeah yeah you only need 30
are you close to Mario now hey St
St St
time Mario oh you're really good at
getting at getting them huh yeah the
Buddies what well I don't know if I'm
going to get it as the thing yeah we
have to fight to the death for Mario oh
that's nice I don't F
you all right I'll steal you man Peach
okay Daisy he's all yours you can have
Chris Pratt oh it's
golf no no no no he's making us do three
mini games okay
three cuz he's a hater
yeah Mario where are you going playing
tag thank
[Laughter]
you h ah okay this game yeah yeah yeah
yeah okay
what yeah what are the other games I
want to know whoops I might not
jump how long do we have to practice
this until he shows us the other game
the other game is
race game no no no they only introduce
the game like once in the beginning from
my experience last time it was like that
oh no but I'm saying if if I'm not sure
you might be you're probably right y see
oh bumper
balls so we have to [\h__\h] kill Mario
yes we kill
Mario ah get
Mario yeah okay I I remember we had the
same thing last
time and then as let's jump off okay
stand is to raise flag game yeah okay
okay oh [\h__\h] here we
go ah this one freaking mind games of
this guy again I don't know why I did
that he gets so mean though don't trust
him cuz sometimes he changes it don't
trust him guys well do trust him trust
him okay I'm ready GG okay here we go
oh my
God okay okay okay okay
okay yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah lucky you
okay go go away okay let's go let's go
jumping we're jumping and popping we
jumping ah whoa I'm losing this one it's
so over
I'm locked
in me
too so tell me about yourself
crony there is
nothing what about you tell me about
yourself oh um so it all started when I
was a child what's your skin care
routine well myio really sucks
yeah maybe you don't want him as a
[Laughter]
teammate okay okay okay okay okay okay
all right all right all right all right
all right all right on to the next
stage okay say goodbye Mario we're
balling bye Mario goodbye Mario we get
it we get it we get it start so what's
everyone's skin care what's yours why'
you kill yourself I thought I looked at
Peach cuz orange ball I don't know not
my first time looking at Peach like that
you double cleanse at night do you
usually play as Peach when you play too
no I don't I always play Daisy but I
think two princesses is very
confusing you're just blinded by all the
princesses so many
princesses I was trying to get
Mario we need to get him off he's still
here
Mario why is he still alive Mario get
off the
edge go come on Mario B die get out are
you so good yeah he's going to beat us
why is he good all of a sudden yeah he
was so bad at the other
game bro come on he just what what did
what what
why did he do that he justed himself
what do you mean Mario got five yeah I
think it was already over and then he
just rolled off cuz he was rolling in
that
direction okay he's an idiot that was
crazy he's pretty dumb all right Shy Guy
guess I don't have to try hard this one
red right left left left right right
left left right right left right left
left right left left left left yellow
red white you guys what white white
white left right right right right right
right right left left left left left
right left right right left right left
left right left right I I
[Music]
can't Mario is literally a
computer like he can't take the
win how is that fair
nah computers are taking over robots are
taking over congratulations cron
congratulations cron yay you got a
little
buy thanks yay Mario yay
yay double fake out shouldn't be
allowed yeah that was messed up I yeah
that was pretty messed
up we should cancel shy guy yeah what I
thought it was going to be the other way
around shy guy that do shy guy says oh
oh yeah but I think that also cancels
you crony wow either one or everybody or
nothing shy guy it's
over oh yeah two
items wait there're so cheap what one
yeah only one yeah this door
everything's I mean there's also super
sale going on yeah again oh yeah
wow wow
that's so
Che oh one more you got
Mario lucky
you I want to go shopping
too now is the time to go
shopping give me that Gucci give me that
Versace so true
[Music]
that's oo Monty mold
I'm sorry
what Nissa why why me because you're
leading right now do the M princess I'm
going to get that anyway I'm sorry you
don't have to curse
me
oh is this Karma
[Laughter]
I like to go upstairs I'll take my
leave yeah you have the money you can
afford you feel awkward down there don't
you yeah I feel a little awkward down
here I feel bad vibes I'm not
vibing hey
lucky hey you're getting coins yay
coins
yay they sound tasty they yummy
chocolate coin
H well I don't have
money so
whatever
wa I didn't
know I didn't know you can speed that up
yeah oh my
god oh golden pipe as a
reward ooh I mean that's a big reward I
get three times let's go wait there's a
snake inside ah it bit me oh my God and
it gave you only one coin
that's wait give me golden pipe golden
pipe golden pip yeah you got a golden
five yeah baby y it's a sign crazy I'm
the go of gotcha hell yeah you're going
to get you're going to get another star
yes I will get back my star
that's exactly what I'm going to
do this is finally my time KF I won't
let it be taken away from
me heck yeah oh you're removing my CSE
so I see how it is do I need
to can
she
H I personally don't think it's worth it
I think you should save until the next
turn why are you saying it like that now
you're making me think I should use it
what the [\h__\h] I think she's just
genuinely concerned about your choic
scaring me yeah yeah what are you
planning to do what are you planning to
do I'm not planning to do
anything I'm getting targeted it's a
cursed
block I mean I was probably going to
roll this number anyway so stamp yay yay
almost
complete you could be the first one to
complete
it
yay mini game mini G already G completed
her stamp oh she did oh she's just going
to bring it over oh no please oh I got
it I got my
Mone it's okay you're about to get
another star with your pipe lost and
pound oh yay
what is this oh
no yeah this is so difficult is
difficult oh yeah this is
difficult my chances of winning are very
low in this
game oh have to I see how okay that's
not good let's begin Gigi
G oh no oh no oh I just want so good oh
no there's nothing I want to make sure
we're not pressing the same button it's
not about being good also it is
sometimes good to like press uh to
everybody have to have everybody press
the same because you could get me out in
one round if you hit me fre times oh
that's how it works yeah if you hit me
with the bone stick three times in one
round did you did anybody press
up yeah I
[Music]
did
goodbye please please have mercy on
[Music]
me Mind Games I chose the same you again
you again you again
round fine please Choose
Wisely or or don't think at all don't
don't choose
don't don't Bonk your
[Music]
Senpai cron need did you pick
blue
woo yeah that was a difficult game to
win yeah yeah
damn ODS aren't in your favor sometimes
those games are like that when it's one
versus three yeah they're
evil Daisy on Fourth Place huh should
not have gotten the first star cuz of
this
curse let's go
[Music]
who are you using that on oh
bar let's go plus five is it plus five
and plus five on Mario's dice
[Music]
too wait a second but I still can't
reach it I mean that was really far in
the first place you're getting there
yeah I won't get
it I will not get it believe in yourself
Frick it's okay Kiara is going to get it
oh that makes me feel a lot better if I
don't what if I don't you're going to
cuz you're going to use your golden pipe
but what if I don't want to use it now
because if I use it now you guys are
going to Target me cuz I'll be
everyone's already
Nissa I think everyone will still Target
me yeah I'm thinking you're targeting
the
well not necessarily the people still
could always go for me
too 50 look at you got all
the
rich W literally Rich holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
yay oh another oh you get to do it
again yeah why it's beneficial to go
back to the begin reward is even better
next time n probably not
mayhaps want to get another stamp
crony I'm
thinking fill up that stamp card let's
go wait where should I
go oh
God where do I go oh
God I'm terrified right now we should be
scared she can do everything twice yeah
yeah she has the money to do it too
she's going to ride the elevator
twice up and down yeah up and down she
could afford
it she can go back down yeah she wanted
to oh
oh
oash s
you could use that 200% sticker on
yourself and you would still be
fine wouldn't that be funny if you put
it on
yourself that would be pretty funny
she's going to place a bunch of star
traps she's going for it holy [\h__\h] man
she wants those stars now your pockets
are
full he he
he what which one should I get your PO
you want to replace one of your items or
she can buy she can buy two items yeah
but oh wa yeah but her items are full
yeah that's
[Laughter]
okay I
see we're getting Mario parted right now
yeah
heck yeah uh
oh she
whoa Mario's too
strong oops my
bad
[Music]
chargeless
okay what did we just
say I just get so excited
yeah she's so
happy look I get an item Yi that's
awesome what can be in
here wow star be a mini game
too go for battle battle battle battle y
yay
battle an item mini
gameo let's fight so no coins oh fun oh
oh you played the metal I wanted to play
with
you wow wow
[Music]
wo let's go let's go is G going to be
small forever yes until she's doing
something favorable
perhaps don't worry I'll I'll take from
narissa what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
don't
worry well I'm not even moving where we
not um where is
the I
see you see yeah if you golden pipe you
could go to Blue and take someone star
I'm just worried about crony soon
following up and getting to those to oh
I won't follow don't worry oh you will
I'm sure you will no
no but wait it's how much is this still
20 or is it more now it's it's still 20
so you could get one and didn't place a
thing on any yeah I think it's half off
too so it's only
10 yeah I'm just worried I'll lose the
star that I'm getting now soon but oh
well might as well go for it prony's
going to go upstairs and take two
people's Stars yeah yeah she will but it
might take her she rolls badly you know
it could take her a while
[Music]
exactly uh
okay give me the star ooh flash sale
thank you flash s only 10 coins wow you
know what that means maybe maybe boo is
also half off so 25 but I won't have
enough for that oh that would be crazy
oh that would be
crazy next star oh first floor oh my God
why is it there ooh finally somewhere
else H are you really 25
now oh no no okay he's not half off
that's lame he should be half off yeah
you have so much money oh my God yeah
Cron's got a lot of I know okay share
share
share it won't hurt you at all you
probably won't feel a difference yeah
yeah yeah that's that's barely a
difference
oh wow they still stillo a lot wow I
don't know how I did
that okay stamp you getting some stamps
oh hey my third
stamp
woo where are we Landing oh
I or should I go down now
but I'll go
down is is it a red field down there
yes uh-oh okay oh it is what it
is I'm ready I'm
prepared have my
money
yay y oh you can can you go left no no
you can't I got to go all the way around
yeah oh
man sure I'll buy some items so cheap
again oh I want to go
shopping oh wait I should have bought a
pipe oh too late creepy dice block we
have to stop
C oh I'm third place though not much
long there so much you can do with an
ally kind of
scary it's really not going to do a
lot oh I see if you get there early you
can still Exchange it uhhuh yeah yeah
how nice of them uncomplete and still
they'll take
it very
[Music]
nice yay yay y three
points flash s's over oh I wanted to
shop some more
goodbye I'm really interested in seeing
Cron's actions next
round there's so much you can do
they're so little I can do no please why
me
again I don't want to there so much
pressure cie Cutters no I'm bad with
buttons cookie cutter cookie cookie I
don't need no cookie
cutter what is this supposed to be oh
okay so each of us has a different
shaped cookie cutter so you just have to
click the button when your shape is up
oh okay [\h__\h] see I don't even know
what I'm doing this is so difficult oh I
see yeah yeah yeah okay oh my God
okay
H Square goes in the square
hole [\h__\h] ah [\h__\h] I was too fast
[Music]
oh ah ah it skips it oh I didn't realize
it sabotaging
myself finish did I do it did I do it I
messed up so many times oh that looks
really good our
cookies I'm hungry yay y
cookies cookies we're like a well oiled
machine we can start Cookie Shop
y oh my kup songs are coming
up well please never let me play a one
versus three ever again at least not on
the one
sve it's so
scary what's going to happen now stretch
she has such a nice voice she should
become a
YouTuber
yeah why
not mhm mhm okay it's serious now dwell
it's serious we're [\h__\h] their place
gets to decide
what it's not fair an
event more Bowser space that would be
fun
that' be the most fun
maybe or chance
time she's thinking she's
thinking Bowser Bowser Bowser time
[Applause]
[Music]
Bower he's not even that bad I wish he
was more
bad those are all in inconvenient places
everywhere is
inconvenient there should be some on the
third floor
H uh yeah who keeps
skipping I'm
sorry it doesn't matter it will happen
power you can't have that knowledge
um skiper
skiper so okay let's see what you going
to
do you're eight away from the
Star oh that's so close h
[Music]
h i see
you um hold
on oh God the terror what would what
would Ward people
of so sweet of you to think of the ward
people oh I
see
H lots of
thinking she's going to have five stars
by the end of this I no no no cuz nobody
go
there
oh Mario Mario Mario thank you Mario
thank you
Mario
a he's so
helpful thank
you what would I do without Mario going
to buy two
stars suddenly oh thank God she's not
going up wait what oh yeah
okay
damn leader board changes
drastically yay
and stars wait are they no they're not
half off it felt like it oh wow let's go
y you got
Stars damn they changed the line for
that
even why is it over there okay but you
can't immediately go there right you got
to go around the
corner I don't know if I want to go
there a party I mean I guess I
[Music]
could it just right in front of
me okay I will actually yeah you know
what I I will what you will what
um I no you're going to use the golden P
KY I guess I will oh no I have to get no
do it next turn do it next turn you can
do it anytime next turn will be a good
time to it just do it now yeah I'm right
in front of it so you know how small you
are right now DJ you should get it you
only have one star everyone else has two
or three you could return to normal size
if you just don't use the pipe this
round
where are I need to see where you are I
need to look at the map and look at you
I'm like uh one field in Fr
of
okay but you know what I let you have it
thank you maybe I will roll one that
will be very funny
anyway I have other things to do I want
to go to a different
place that's cool I got other I got
other plans that's exactly where you
wanted to go right hey that's what we're
talking about let's see if there's some
orange Synergy and I will also get a
one no get the start
y he I reinstating your size but not
your orangeness yet you will stay unored
for now okay she's still orange no no no
no you're just you're imagining things
yeah you're seeing things I
see okay wow this is we have so much
more stars in this game than last time
the economy is doing so well is this a
good sign the economy is
booming it is flourishing oh is it going
up no middle oh who's there nobody I can
reach it really are you on the second
floor or the third I'm the third a
uh oh finally I get to the shop
[Music]
yay and it's just for you just for me I
don't believe it y all got to shop here
I saw
it I'll take that thank
[Music]
you the Orange is a pigment of your
imagination wait what and then you took
Mario too leaving he's literally leaving
next round I'm not even going to use him
yeah but you'll get you'll get coins for
whatever thing you land on he'll give
you extra points well great oh you go
you can go upstairs and get it wait
would I go I would go down or I would go
up oh no go up the elevator you can we
go left then escalator but I I won't
have enough money
anyway oh that's true wait you won't
land on it yet and then you just have to
hope you make enough in the you win the
mini game andio Mario going to give you
extra that much money but I I guess get
six and Mario get six yeah So you you're
going to get pretty damn close if you
win the mini game yeah I don't know oh
maybe this gives me
money yeah but then again GG has a
golden pipe so I won't use it really you
state your orangeness no I have a plan
wait I didn't get the money it's
probably worthless now I'm not going to
use the star I'm not going to get it
what oh wait go twice hey oh
I'm back in the game look at that you
see look you're you're complaining for
nothing why are you laughing CR why are
you saying that what the [\h__\h] what's
your plan no nothing no nothing what's
your
plan oh you got to put the sticker on me
you got to put the stick on me what you
to put the faking stick on me no I know
it put it on put it on someone else
please this is the second time I Pats
I hate
stickers a game's just a game love is
just a game I like I playe I do the same
oh do you do you
say oh you feel the same post-traumatic
sticker disorder yeah
PTSD oh you're pretty close
too can I look at the map
yeah you still getting a turn this round
no right no but you're before me my
turns out can you please use the pipe
next
[Laughter]
round N I don't know what I'm thinking
but um can you declare now that you're
going to use the pipe oh I will use the
pipe so someone should make me more
expensive thank you yeah
Y is she going that
M someone should use the sticker on me
otherwise I might just buy the star W
that's crazy who would ever do such a
thing me what you yeah someone to stop
me with a
sticker there's no way it's okay I'm
just going to make extra money hopefully
in the next
game so that I can afford the 200% up oh
you get to visit a
shop oh I couldn't follow it at the
end Peach loves to shop I do love to
shop oh finally a different princess is
being time to get my ass kicked
[Music]
yeah what's stand off I think we had
that last time too did we
don't remember oh did this one we just
run away from
it okay run run run run
run oh yeah ah what that was
okay that was right on top of me yeah
what the I'm going try it
again please let's survive girls how
many how many attacks do I get um three
start
that's a lot that's
[Music]
plenty what
bro are you
[Music]
kidding he just went straight for
it mental should not have r
l which which way which way which way
what where do
you after a certain point I can't move
it because you guys can still
move let's go we can do this
crazy we can do this if we just stand on
each side she can't get both of us oh
[Laughter]
true I mean I might get less coins I
don't know but that's fine rigged rigged
genius that's rigged
rigged do we what we can
get y it paid off to work
together and now we are enemies again
use a sticker on me yeah yeah byebye
Mario by Mario had a short specifically
someone should use a sticker on on me on
me me oh why someone use a sticker on me
G use a sticker on
G what you if you don't do it I'll warp
to the star and buy it this is so
[\h__\h] so
[\h__\h] no none of you were believing
what you were saying at all I was trying
I was doing my
best oh she was really convincing
mhm oh exactly
six oh my God are you getting the
St well then you really didn't have to
put that on me yeah yeah true I didn't
expect to make it and does a sticker
Stay full until I make a purchase or
only for one round no no only for one
round okay then
whatever thank God yeah it doesn't
matter now so she just wasted her
sticker for nothing so it's a wi I know
she should have used it on I I should
have us use the
pipe where is it I don't have to use my
pipe after
all yeah I will surely make
this kind of if right there is if I
don't roll a
one I only need to roll a four use the
pipe use the pipe to make need to roll a
fort the game is really listening to us
oh my God I believe it it's
ecy holy macaroni y look at
that let's
go
Star I've never seen so many stars
before yeah we've all we're all kind of
built oo
uh where where is somebody
close I don't think
so a cool
cool very
lucky
right technically you're kind of close
to it if you can get far enough but it's
not like I'm going to buy anything this
round but that speeds the process up
maybe by using a mushroom
getting beat
closer oh but oh look what you get a 10
right here no look who still has a
golden pipe yeah oh
crazy and look who still has three stars
though look who has four stars what are
you going to golden pipe right
here that would be crazy I get another
try oh oh only one because I have since
only spent one thing okay golden golden
go yo oh my God what the [\h__\h] W I told
you I'm the queen of the
gacha see I got lucky landing on places
all the rest of you were lucky with
items what the
[\h__\h] the gacha rates are so high right
now
guys
wow
y all right yay all right everybody open
up your g games on your phone
now is the time to
invest roll for your favorite Banner now
braid up yes
yes I'll go buy a random shop but
there's no telling what shop I'll go byy
what if you go to the really high price
shop with bougie items I don't know I I
need to use my
items super
shop oh
that's not a
shop he'll be fine next to the one coin
shop wow one coin shop for one
more [\h__\h] yeah I mean that's all you
wanted right to get to the
shop yeah there we are hey
pie I should kill myself
I keep rolling on you move in different
ways you move by pipes and other magical
means double the
coins
coins I need double the
tumble
oo
oh ah yeah okay this was quite fun and
enjoyable don't fall off I keep looking
at the
mole I know I'm kind of intoxicating
right something about me my
fermon it's something about it your
furry Moon my furry
Moon I got to distracted huh you got to
wash that furry moon off no I but I want
to be a Musky husky a Musky husky I've
not heard that one before really I'll
send
it all
right we can do this we can all
survive that would be the most wholesome
outcome oh my God he's so fast that we
are friends together where are we going
where we don't push don't
push oh God where are we which way are
we going that way where really really oh
god oh it's so it's so
narrow y wow
wow time to find a musy husty
picture oh wow W wo wo W you got this
crony I don't got this you're the only
one left St should just ended wait
what's the point
so she still has to make it to the
end no but she'll still be first
yayn good clutch what do I get
more I think you would have gotten the
same if you even if you fell off right
there before why do my controllers keep
disconnecting did you charge it yeah
they're charged they keep
disconnecting BR they're
lame sabotage only three turn left okay
thank you for the
update so four star lady what you going
to
do she's what am I going to
do mhm mhm I see if only you could you
can probably place it where I'm standing
but if only that would work immediately
huh if only um
oh I can't look at the map oh yeah you
can only you can only do one of those
four
places
okay
mhm oh darn what
fun and
G I will be hyping oh golden P golden P
everyone okay I time everybody gets a
star will in fact be piping you get a
star and you get a star you love those
pipes yeah everyone gets a
star one second
NY NY what
is okay I hope I roll good oops did not
mean to press again I hope I roll good
yeah okay what what's with this game I
don't know happening today what's going
on I don't appreciate it they really are
trying to slow us down but we're still
getting all of the stars you can't stop
us gam what is happening to me
yeah can't hold us back we're too good
we got a star yay a
star congratulations Monty MO oh on the
bridge again down there
O
Okay well perhaps I'll be piping as
well ooh yay good catch
yay you will be piping right now I think
I will pipe
[Music]
indeed what a good idea why wouldn't I
pipe right yes why would you not I feel
like it's giving these out too much
these items I think you're just saying
that cuz now you're not
leading I Haven been bleeding for a
while what are you talking about let's
go
one sad Bowser would have been
funny yes I want the star thank
you yo you girls know we still got like
uh bonus stars coming up so you never
know you never know you never know
exactly and even in those two turns
crazy stuff could
happen like Star stealing and
Bowsers what around the corner
again all right I don't even know where
I am on the map oh right next to the
shop the one star shop one shop where
you rolled
one I'm really good at that
ah yay big spender achievement earned
ooh ah ah o yes I'll go down for stamp
rewards do I have I have I get 50 coins
yippe you have every
one yeah first time
money look at you
go economy oh H
you y
thank you I'll col I have to use my
items which one would you like to use I
don't know but I have thre so I might as
well A Min
game what if you get another golden pipe
wouldn't that be crazy that would be
crazy wait now I know how this works I
know how this works now last time I was
getting it really
wrong where do I want to go anyway uh
wait I forgot how this works why is it
all
I don't know how it works anymore are we
going down now you're going to the ah oh
that's fine the first
one oh God are you you're killing
her I'm
sorry I don't know you you you're
leading good you'll be fine oh oh I
button
mashed do we have two don't do we have
14 and 15
Okay who wants a creepy dice block I
will cancel it I have other dice that's
true I promise you
that H so does Kiara yeah sorry crony
thank
you it's okay you'll be fine oh I don't
like the way she laughs that's kind
of she kind of
evil we're all all
evil all of us as long as we're in this
game they're like get away from
us and they're like what the [\h__\h] I'm
trying
to yay coins yummy you find all
the you got a star second I'm [\h__\h]
losing why do you care what do you mean
you literally got your second hit and
block star you have four stars yeah but
you can still get four stars Prett close
you can probably get a bonus star yeah
maybe most hidden
block I think there's the I'm pretty
sure there's literally a a secret a
bonus star for finding the most secret
blocks oh this oh no can we switch
G what's going yeah I wish oh you have
to you have to you have to shoot think
is this too far or I think you can make
it you even over jumped it I'm going to
parkour
civilization oh my God how are you doing
don't wor don't worry I'm going to
parkour not good enough we should really
switch roles man just I'm just not good
oh okay now you're getting it can you
make this jump oh yeah waa n this jump
you can't make I don't believe you yeah
okay I can
parkour civilization further stop saying
parkour civilization do you not like
Park what
about a world where we can trade and
parkour you don't like let do the ideal
Society of trading and parkour no stop
it I am now going to talking
parkour
360 backflip job
stop talking just stop just keep lock in
come on I'm lock I'm locked in I
am I'm locked don't even worry I am
locked in you are doing so good what are
you doing I'm locked in
I'm I'm not going
to I'm so at least do that after we win
I don't I don't know if we're going to
win I so so lock in right now what
[Music]
isation do you hate being orange no no
don't worry once you see my plan come to
fruition you love me
again don't even worry what what color
are you going for huh you want green or
what blue is is blue what you want
don't don't worry don't worry I'm going
I understand it's all going to come
together there
[Music]
Luigi bro we don't have time for how are
we going to even reach you and make use
of you
Waluigi exactly it's too late buddy
that's why you never get a game again W
Luigi let's see
[Music]
um wait where the heck am I oh I'm here
okay what did it oh okay it's showing
me why is it showing me all the places
that I got a star
from oh reminding you your oh no those
are you're traps are they saying that
I'm going to lose soon or something is
that why
I I don't know what you're seeing so I
can't help you with
that everyone has things that can cancel
out my dice oh my God right I didn't
realize you're five to the star but you
can maximum Roll
free
oh let's
see should
I I might as well use it on me huh
yes how far am I from the
Star close I don't know but you're the
closest you're second place so but I can
cancel it out I know I might as well
just got it's not going to make a
difference is that really how it works
though can you cancel it out I I think
so I'm pretty sure you can use an item
all
right you're so close to the
star
oh oh let's go but if I can't get it my
husband then I can't get it husband what
are you going to
doio I don't like Mario wow lose one
star Bowser
Revolution oh that would be
insane okay oh that doesn't make a
difference yeah what the [\h__\h] pocket
change so rich oh man the star war would
have been
good
[Music]
wow why not a Bowser
Revolution yeah I wanted the Bowser I
want to know what that is me too oh that
everyone gets
dragged hell yeah we all lose why don't
you get the Bowser Revolution I know
right why didn't you ask Bower nicely wo
wo wo wo wo hold up hold upop girl
damn what is your I go to the star but
this is for you I'm telling you I'm
doing something for two stars wait one
star no I only I'm going to steal for
you this is all for you are you going to
steal for me from me or no no no no I I
will be doing some I this is for you
this is all for you say your prayers
wait say your prayers wow you gave up on
the other
[Music]
star I guess that's fair I am
baffled okay and then
iigi you stay orange why you get valigi
oh not necessarily though I guess yeah
someone can get him but pretty high
chance maybe if you get him you can buy
two star wait you want me to win I'm
going to cry you're so nice now you have
to win but you must beat me before it's
because you wants to be orange you will
have to beat me she doesn't want to lose
the orange perms because orange I I'm
just so happy to finally have an orange
buddy you know yeah I don't want to lose
my orange
buddy yeah you were turning turning her
to a different
color well sometimes I have no choice
you know oh that's is nostalgic pinball
yeah I love pinball oh my god oh he's so
cool Jojo I love L Waluigi he's so
cool you're not very faithful are you
you only like the villains
huh yeah maybe look at him he's getting
funky how does this work uh til lunch
ball oh oh oh my God what a great uh
uh I don't need to have it on Windows XP
anymore I have it in here we have it in
Mario Party Mario Party pinball in Mario
Party that doesn't work so well as
pinball at
home I want to play start now no
play just having so much fun playing
y oh God a the memories the pinball
memories yay
pinball yay oh my God this so
excited this could don't even know what
that means you have extra points you'll
get oh
nice thank
you what
that I want to play B
what
happened I did not have any chance it
went straight for the middle oh you can
you you can it again yeah you can still
play you can keep playing what I didn't
realize oh my
[Laughter]
God don't be such a
quitter yeah exactly oh no oh my God no
wait why is he giving you some coins
it's not fair I don't understand oh he's
giving everyone coins he's being a nice
little guy why is he being so nice stop
that why I don't know it's against his
character it's confusing me too wait we
still have oh my God we still have so
much time what on what
yeah since they're bringing him in right
at the end I guess they're like we got
to make it worth
it thank you Waluigi I love your game
this should be a stand game yeah disco
disco give me a oh what's going
on when does it end we have 100 seconds
left of the
game I love
it I kind of want to stop now my buttons
barely react I feel like I need a new
controller you're you're the highest
score right now what are you talking
about how I was literally away from the
computer for 10 seconds
that's what I'm wondering
too it's
crazy this game truly is about
pinball waa yeah Pinball's kind of
random
[Music]
who I love pinball we should have a
pinball championship in whole
life would that be fun going be all on
luck though what he doing more balls
more
the
yo
balls I am I'm not good at pinball so my
machine has you don't have to be good at
so many balls oh wow I yeah I have other
talents we're balling more
balls my machine is full of balls what
the heck I was destined for this I may
have been a pinball champion in my
previous life
everybody locked
in look we're playing pinball for 10
more
seconds get him get
him come on okay did I what I B yeah I
told you you were doing super good I was
I'm okay okay I am going to make do my
main game next week whole schedule will
be pinball thank
you just
pinball yo but I I just got him for like
what one one turn or two turns but you
can buy two stars I've only had golden
pipe
man that' be sick but you have triple
Dice and everything
[Music]
don't wor you can still get the star
going to get the star guys do not worry
your little head wait how did you get to
do all of that don't really long
thing that's crazy I will a s that's
insane she's she's having the insane
gameing and my very cool awesome Star
for me I think orange might be finally
getting a win orange
win orange winning
together and then you guys aren't on the
same team though we're we're on the same
te we are yes mentally Spirit are
ooh
e and then I end my turn randomly if I
use a triple dice pip do I get the
triple dice twice with my partner only
once I okay I don't know no I don't
think so yeah that' be
crazy what happens if I go up here
sad I could no I don't have to pipe
anymore guess I'm just going down how
far am I yeah I got to turn in your
stamp
sheet yay stamp yippe stamp ypp
yipp Waluigi I'm coming for you no no no
no
no wait what wait what wait no no wait
what can we can we come back what
happened no I that just came out of
nowhere I pressed it away but I don't
think I had a choice to stay in line
Nintendo online disconnected Nintendo
online can you
try reconnecting maybe but maybe you
girls are NPCs now yeah rejoin
rejoin
oh
oh reentering oh thank God but is it
working Nintendo online doing something
right I will wait I will we're waiting
we're waiting is this working I will
look at the
board that would be crazy if this works
well come on Nintendo come on you can do
it my internet is fine this is this
seems to be a Nintendo online thing
please bring me back in clearly your
internet's fine you're streaming right
now yeah I'm not dropping any frames
either come on let me
in hello please oh this this feels bad
ah this SC hey what are you guys seeing
right now we so we're all in the game it
does it say like you're waiting for me
or so no we can still just keep playing
am I in NPC right
no no cuz nothing's happening okay just
please please hold the line yeah I am
holding I will not complete my turn
until you are back let me in please game
please please please
please back we did to see you two wi she
turns away Nintendo yeah
seriously please it chose now of all
times we were so close to the end come
on I want that feeling of
closure
hello you have to do the min oh they're
saying you might have to do the mini
game I guess I will be taken over by uh
NPC really a are you girls at the start
of a mini game right now like is it
going to happen no I still have my my
turn to
go that's weird no is it really should
we should we just try I don't know I
guess we can try it sounds weird though
to be
back people are saying you might need to
restart your game maybe but that sounds
dangerous I don't trust it is there any
precedent for this chat you did you have
this before does it
save rejoins next
turn okay should I okay wait did I have
my turn yet in that round no oh no okay
I will I will continue my turn and then
let's see if you are let inside okay
okay that might work I'm not restarting
okay
upstairs are you getting a star what's
going on no I'm just chilling narrate
everything please Gigi went to the
second floor and while Luigi gave her
additional six coins then it was Daisy's
turn yes that was Daisy bot Daisy Daisy
bot using a mushroom girl that's not
what I would have done girl what are you
doing musroom canell the effect and now
you have plus five where is she going
with this you're going 13 places you're
31 what oh it disconnected you ending
mode no let me in please rejoin rejoin
rejoin suppos to go up the stairs wait
am might get yes Daisy is going up the
stairs
Daisy Daisy Daisy stole Waluigi
re-entering please wait a moment oh my
God this is so
broken wait is is her turnover no she's
the item item shop and you have two
customers so you'll be getting two items
she is buying she just bought a markup
sticker she's using all my
money girl and she ends her
turn yes she get six coins
good job NPC Daisy get another six
coins and now it's Peach's turn and I
don't know what I'm doing where's even
the star I'm not sure how far are you
from the Star I I'm I'm completely away
from it I I'm an agent of chaos so I'm
just are 28 as spaces away from this a
random pipe to go somewhere okay okay I
and you were now closer to the store
went to the second floor uh-huh uh-huh
oo how how much closer Are
you eight uh 14 places away yeah do you
want to like stream have double D get
the star next turn I don't really like
streaming like on on like what people
are showing on Discord it's a little bit
dangerous but I don't know do you want
to show me somebody one of you yeah wait
do I have it I can stream it okay okay
um I don't like streaming over this or
like window capturing them we'll
try yeah
we cuz I guess I'll never be re-entering
to see the finale of damn them
unbelievable let's
see screenshot picture show would be
good
too we're getting a mini game everyone
is against wait don't start it yet we're
not trying to start it it's just loading
Bruiser bash all right let's
see wait does it let me in now for the
mini game it let me in it let me
in okay oh okay was right with the mini
game thank you one guy you actually one
guy me
correctly wait okay let's
prac wait wait wait I can't I can't wait
I'm not controlling myself why oh so
you're back in but you're watching
yourself
great maybe one we have to leave it to
her bot maybe once we're
in I'm just observing for now but maybe
maybe now after the mini game okay come
on Daisy okay I'm not moving myself
that's okay oh how do I
turn I wonder when you slow when you get
kicked out do they turn the NPC into
hard mode or easy mode I will you better
be hard mod thank you run Daisy run stop
I I can't why is she just chilling at me
stop stop stop she's so smart good days
she is
smart she I got knocked
off wow good job maybe I'm glad it
wasn't me after all
she locked in
Crazy maybe she should stay and take
over my role no that doesn't sound very
fair yeah I'm not sure about her choices
before the mini game that wasn't very
convincing oh rejoined
yippee y thank you
Nintendo they gave me a second
chance yay yay
yay not so yay ooh ooh ooh last turn o
you can't buy they closed all their
shops wo wo that's [\h__\h] rude they
Clos all their shops what open
up open up what are you going to do you
have no items oh you do we're random we
are going
somewhere where will we be
going where am I heading you're going to
get so lucky you're going to get so
lucky
where
it darn
uhoh what a good last
[Music]
turn okay
okay good I've done worse hey you got a
stamp
[Music]
yay
nice oh and everyone's
closed [\h__\h] rude on
exhausted oh you have a
triple you could use your triple and
maybe get the scar 18 I might get lucky
I could make it come on don't don't
don't roll free
ones yes yes let's go 18
easy
10 no no that's just
one it's over oh oh
wait it's over wait roll something good
please please is he not rolling no he
just steals from people oh my
God no I could have gotten the last
star you're so close well let's see what
we end
up does it indicate the Nissa can get it
we'll see we know my
luck you have double
Dy yeah but I like to roll ones like a
scary amount you'll get a 10 right here
should I just go down cuz otherwise I
I'll end up on Bowser
Revolution which might steal one of my
stars I'm sorry guys I will not risk
that not for the biscuit not for this B
biscuit I don't know I don't want to
think about where I'll go I'll just go
here thanks for the
money yeah yeah yeah yeah okay thank
you nice did a cut scene yeah really
unnecessary but okay just rubbing it in
a bit more
money bang nice yeah the last things you
can do before the apocalypse
yeah yeah game's almost over so you know
might as well yeah yeah yeah yeah I
don't need your sticker shade
anymore they just you know they're about
to kick us out but they're like just in
case just in case you cannot get items
on the final wow what the wow
okay okay I just wanted to experience it
one more
time why' you use a double
dice what do you mean oh wait just in
case just in case
I was like Oh I thought K was going to
that oh she she got it she's going to
steal oh
finally she's she's going to
steal she's going to steal and
win help oh my God she's stealing from
me oh my God this is robbery this is
assault
help police
officers come to those who she'll get
the star
too look at that comeback blasted
woman I wish a plague upon
you why do you keep saying
hi TR don't know any other
words are you happy now
from last place to first I told you that
even in the last threee rounds things
can change
drastically exactly hey it's okay
there's a location of the next star
maybe if if we had another turn one you
could get
it
um go downstairs why don't you go get it
why can't I view n where I end you
always destined for number one because
you kept on rolling the ones you were
just manifesting it oh my God it was all
in the Stars yeah it was the hints were
always there wait foreshadowing sorry I
can't count one two three oh oh it'll
show me oh I don't want to go that way
okay if I go okay I'll go down I I'll be
with all of you guys you guys are so
cute oh yay
let me add it cuz it's beneficial to
you well he's going to take one of my
items and give me coins I don't want
that I need my items what if I want to
use bonus Stars we need the bonus
Stars we need some bonus Stars CH dance
you only want to be with us when it's
useful I see what kind of person you are
what you even going to get your stupid
stamp sheet exchanged
y haven't you won enough in this last
turn yeah haven't you done
enough oh wow money happy just taking
from people I should have taken the star
from you it's you I should have stolen
from yeah a new sticker sheet I should
have kept you
down you take w we go to Bowser go be
one with Bowser okay a
cow
woo even stealing my man at the very end
wow
final game should bet Our Stars we have
a we have a mini game I think that last
no no that last turn really made up for
all the ones you've thrown out there I
don't no I don't I don't want to be
alone
[Music]
again oh God how does this oh I'm being
the one okay I think I was pretty good
at this
before let's begin let's begin you're
catching lots of fish I don't want you
to have too much practice
[Music]
[Laughter]
please hey that's not how this game
works it is it is
okay start teamwork all right all right
all right all right all right
sorry get
her she's so fast at swimming I
know what are you going to get her I'm
not the one pressing the
button what who pressed oh cron is the
one you guys are having some
misunderstandings
there finish what
what why did your girls want to catch me
we tried our best was I just stinking do
I stink more than the fish then you
don't
succeed huh well it wasn't so bad then
get what you want not what
you
yay we got audience woohoo
woohoo I want direct your eyes to the
monitor okay okay okay who will be the
winner well we know that but what about
the bonus Stars my
friend it shows us throughout the game
how many stars we had yeah pretty good
shy guys Ally really stole fell
off oh okay oh that was my sudden rise
that was quite exciting like I feel like
a lot of games are stars very
onesided yeah really good this could be
anybody except oh you traveled so far
look at
you oh my
Gody bonus oh I think this one's Kiara
too no no no no no
no clap clap clap clap clap clap clap
clap clap clap clap clap clap clap clap
clap clap cl cl the
winner
Superstar no she did it she the winner
she's the
winner she's Beauty and she's Grace
Stars I I I I can't believe it I got the
first star so I was supposed to be
cursed and I [\h__\h] over so much in the
beginning what you got
lucky no no that was skill that was pure
skill loock wart I so many items oh
award I don't care about these Awards
what do they do we already lost the game
I mean the hidden block award honestly
that's so crazy that you got two stars
out of those I know that was insane I
can't believe it crazy cuz I I don't
think people say in the chat some of
some people said last time it's 50/50
other people said it's like 7030 or so
but from what I've seen from other times
this game has been played like last time
and also from other streams this is this
doesn't happen so often yeah it's not 50
right it's
not it really isn't yeah thanks for
thanks for all that stuff thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank
thank thank you thank you for all the
stuff oh yeah party Plaza party Plaza oh
is it back to GG controlling the game
huh oh I guess soz I'm just so fast yeah
it's your Lobby
now my Lobby
now that
so crazy because I feel like anybody
could have won there were so many ups
and downs if you look at the graph you
can tell like that was crazy it that
life is
unpredictable you to win Mario Party is
just like life like literally exactly
all of you in the beginning were the
underdog all of you
girls and
that translated to All The Underdogs
doing well
that was
insane that was crazy I'm I don't know
man last time it was just like like me
leading the whole time and then very
clearly losing at the very end but this
was so yeah neck and Ne diverse wow
despite me getting yelled at I had
fun yeah that was so much fun yeah that
was a like you were back in school yeah
Tiara you Rose to the top like a Phoenix
from the bottom honestly not from the
bottom but I I've played Mario Party
many times in my time in whole life and
this was apparently the second time I
won but it honestly feels like the first
time cuz
I let's go you're a wiener I'm a Wier a
Wier Winer M sausage for dinner I
see oh man well thank you girls I hope
you enjoyed this it even though you lost
[Applause]
yeah H I think in the end we all win
right it's about the friends on the way
the friends we
lost yeah wait who was who was uh Second
Place uh was it stilla that was
Lissa and what what place my an
Shenanigans what who was the last place
it was
me I really thought you were going to
win for like got so much Tak 30% of the
game I think that's how it goes
whoever's winning the first half of the
game is probably not going to win yeah
because everyone Target the middle part
I feel
like that was so un
unpredictable I thought I could predict
it but I really couldn't damn see it
life is unpredictable life is
unpredictable it is that's a beautiful
thing to learn from Mario Party is it
beautiful I don't know maybe it's
preparing us for real life life is
beautiful yeah I don't know about real
life but yeah Cal for those with eyes to
see that's how party games go yippe
yippi uh I I need to rest my throat I've
screamed too much especially at
G won orange to yeah you can stay orange
now yay redeemed yourself oh crony's fro
is also [\h__\h] we should take a a break
here oh it's always been kind of like
that for a while now this cold ain't
going away a damn get well oh no get 12
yeah oh no let's release her from her
suffering shall we we killing her
dramatic yeah all right uh thanks for
watching
Everybody enjoy when we say Al winers
because I won Al
[Applause]
winers yay Y is anybody still streaming
later today how any of you guys later no
you are G another time yeah I'm
streaming oh okay then go check out
later
guys see yall later bye bye bye bye I
will now go ahead and perhaps upload the
next uh
Mirage dance shorts with M
Senpai oh a so a keep your eyes peeled
for Dad bye-bye byebye byebye byebye
yippe
[Music]
d a