[Music]
Dan
Long emot
[Music]
feel it rash br me
it
R feel it you me
[Music]
d
oh
[Music]
honey my
feel it R
me
intoxicating DJ keep playing
[Music]
danc emot
feel it rush through me
[Music]
feel rash
me feel it me
[Music]
yay hello
hello it's us we are so
here I'm so sure like every time I like
switch like switch around my camera
around this creeper head I get like a
small heart
hello do we want to do a little uh sound
check by introducing I just want to
check the volume from everybody again
okay a let's start with
Callie hello hi check one two my game
isn't showing up hi it's your boy what's
going on everybody whole live English Cy
myy Reaper refer singer I do a bunch of
things hey everyone how are you it's 7
a.m. here I yeah she's the only one with
2.0 here Morrison
2.0 wow you're right actually hold on a
sec I am she's too advanced for us oh no
oh man the tech the tech is
unprecedented except when I'm in OBS all
right here we go I got it I fixed it we
good what what you fixed oh the the
screen yeah it's just OBS being silly
what's this iron did you do the iron
farm did you make work wait wait wait I
want to I want to explain everything
don't explore too
much say something
uh hello this is small ay piloting
Amilia Watson a oh no it's
small what's wrong with I'm here to
Ender
Dragon's
yeah yeah nice end the dragging on
those yeah block the draging on those
blocks say something go
today we're spanking the Ender Dragon SP
spank spank spank with
LA the shoe of
Doom what's L cha the
shoe I don't know what the it's AOE it's
it's a it's a sandal it means sandal
oh okay yeah let's go Spanish right yeah
yeah it's like a Spanish me kind of but
also reality oh it's is it like
Australian
thongs yeah yeah is
it oh it's like it's like a threat it's
like oh I'm going to get the chunka like
I'm going to beat you with it no not the
CH get the
Chun o sounds
a okay Anda say something hello this is
near by m English one ah okay beautiful
I think it's all relatively balanced I
think
so thing should be if it's not the case
chat please complain feel free to
complain directly to me now before y'all
I mean y'all are already running around
I got to give you a tour of some new
things for the ones who haven't been
playing that much recently I mean I also
stopped playing for a while but um Miss
uh mmm has been working just
saying mm so hard on fixing it after
Rage Quit
okay yeah which was understandable
considering everything take it out Che
it out consider it's
beautiful it has beautiful I I followed
like a video tutorial but in the video
tutorial they did it like a one block
lower I think so I had to raise the
platform so when you stood here you were
too tall but now I kind of fixed
it way it's
okay it's okay I won't blow it up if I
all the way in wait I'm coming I want to
see wow you can actually really get
attested it you can get all the way
in it doesn't
explode
wow don't jinx it it's for real you know
what you guys know what happens when all
five me member gather something we don't
have we don't have to put it test you
know it's working if you just stand back
a little bit it's good oh but I think we
might actually have to use this for
enchanting purposes perhaps enchanting
um so feel free to get your levels up
afterwards sure sounds good you wear
your outfit in
Minecraft spicy aerobics let go I like
the shiny details erotic aerobics thank
you I'm wearing the same outfit too I
did I just realized I didn't realize I
was using this kin oh you're matching
yeah nice one you're
matching okay follow follow follow
follow the
aric instructor what do we what do you
see this you're slapping their cheeks
right now he got to see the she's
practicing for the the the real deal the
this pink house uh it used to be
prettier and it used to stand next to
the pandas but I had to move it in order
to also try to get the iron farm to work
so I moved it all over here and I had a
lot of villagers with a lot of jobs in
here but walk in walk in the children
are going to leave probably that's okay
e let him run there used to be more jobs
and more people but when I logged in
today everything every single villager
despawned for no reason and I had to
start from scratch
[Music]
yay back to another
villager what what what wait how' you
wait you had to start from scratch well
the way I did it well had some problems
with the with the iron farm too I fixed
it like a million times in the past few
days there was always something wrong
with it and um sometimes the villagers
escaped or died or the zombie escaped or
died or Golems killed the zombie or so
so one of the escaped villagers I was
able to bring them over here and then I
had one spawn out of the one block and
then I have them make babies again so
thank God that was good wow big happy
family yeah took a while
W but they're not I mean I I had a one
time I had a one villager with a mending
book unfortunately he's gone no but I I
did out of that I made one mending uh
pickaxe and one mending sword so those
can be used for exp farming if need be
the sword nice especially yeah yeah a
last day so all of this is not so
important um but one could still get
armor from one of the guys cuz one has a
full diamond armor
set um and then there's fish in the
water now in the
pond is a big
Improvement and
no I'm Jing dolphins are
dead I never kill them secret we message
this not special some fair and square ah
I don't know if every did everybody
already see the Improvement on the one
block spawning thingy the chocolate bars
there's a flower on top of it oh yeah
can I kill this child H yeah what are
the improvement from running away from
home teach him a lesson there in here to
disobey your parents okay well we can
walk up here and I'll show you Callie
and me started building this iron farm
it was a lot of stupid work because we
had to find a really old version iron
farm and we built the wrong
one and some really good that you had to
do it didn't work for the longest time
Cy you can see inside I I put
some it's currently not working it's c
not working it worked before because
okay I put rails down because only with
the zombie sitting in the boat it just
didn't work um it needed a certain
amount of milliseconds of ticking for
the
villagers uh to spawn a Golem and so
with the mine cart going back and forth
back and
forth it makes it so that they don't see
it too often and not too little but the
zombie despawned even though I gave him
a name tag so [\h__\h] him wow that's off a
shame yeah um I also replaced the zombie
several times H I got like b a bunch of
iron out of it but we're already out of
iron
again why are they despawning why are
things I thank you is it the server old
version it's very buggy the server is
very buggy it's a lot of stupid things
happening well I will say Kiara thank
you for trying your best and it was fun
working on this with you anyway has been
Eide but Kelly it worked for quite a
while after I added some more things to
it and I got a lot of iron out of it so
it was useful y that's good hopefully
the iron is put to good use yes oh
please come back
up
okay I'm a St up tra Wonder all right
I've got could it happen get out of
there
where up up up let me put the block back
I could make it work again if I if I had
enough there ladder
here can you put the block there to
drown and just hop in here and end it
all thank you try me
drown me I have
gills he you can't drown there it's safe
safe for even sharks safe for drowning
yeah I don't think drowning is safe safe
for not drowning it is oh
okay uh oh yeah and I don't know uh a
yeah behind so basically check it out at
the nether portal first chest uh we have
I think we got like two more totems or
so and I made we have 14 more golden
carrots and the and here's the chest
right next to it we have five pieces of
everything except for the helmet I I
didn't have enough diamonds and emeralds
anymore for another helmet the best
player should take the iron
one everybody please take something uh
of one of each you can take something
unenchanted and with the unenchanted one
you could go to the enchanting table
first you might need to get some
levels and wait do we take now I take
now yeah take now take now just don't
lose it don't lose it don't die and the
only other problem is there's not enough
diamonds there weren't enough diamonds
for diamond swords I only have one
diamond sword that has mending which you
could use for XP farming for
now and uh the infinity bows were lost
in the past streams too due to
unfortunate things happening like circum
gling we we all get golden apples and
that was your boy that did that we have
so much food and St you're welcome I'm
the Apple man I think we'll be fine even
with no diamond swords we'll have to
make iron swords perhaps and there is
should be fine there's one bow that is
fancy make some Bows Oh yeah we can
enchant the other bows let's enchant the
other I want a bow uh yeah take take one
there's one no non enchanted bow uh
actually two I think they're not put
these in wow wow
wow yeah take it take it and see what
you can get out of it uh if you want the
the EXP uh the The Mending sword for exp
farming uh I'll put it into the middle
shulka chest that's how about feather
falling can I enchant my boots with
feather falling I think the boots most
of them already had it but if you don't
have it on then yeah if you have a
feather falling book please take it
please take it
way really
nice W the wo just so that it
Rhymes oh but and enchant it
unfortunately if you want to use one of
the books we currently don't have an
anvil and I don't know if we have enough
iron for an anvil we need that oh does
it work in the in the enchanting table
too I never did it like that before only
Enchanted without a
book can you put the book in there
book does that work can we make iron
sword we need I thought we had one the
Anvil is broken they break eventually so
yeah we need we need one to combine wait
let me see
Anvil I currently have start digging
25 we
have one block uh block I know this is
painful you just got to sit through it
uh I'll try them now we won't be able we
need more iron if we want to make an
anvil I didn't get cob we quickly we
need it we can quickly
mine 30 iron right wait wait I have two
blocks of iron now we need one more
block and I have another seven of iron
here I'll put it in the chest one
more right now too
mhm I'm going to make a two more bars so
basically we need
diamond sword and finish our
equipment kind a villager SP egg that's
cool they like eggs that would have been
nice earlier
yeah Villers are
reptiles they're not humans orals even I
have an important question I thought of
earlier does anybody have experience
with
reptiles
iards before do they smell like do
snakes yeah they do what what very
specific like like lizard pea smell kind
of O smell mus so do ferrets actually
like different animals kind of have like
I don't know if you smell horses before
and stuff like they all have different
smells M stinky imagine how the smell no
I don't want to no it's okay you don't
have
to thank you sharks are not reptiles
right that means that I don't have a
smell
okay sharks have a smell other than
probably just fish
diamond oh let's go
Diamond stack St your need an iron
pickaxe or
better okay I I I I mind it with diamond
pickaxe oh I'm picking up the blocks Mis
organizing I quit
organizing yeah I'm just putting stuff
into random chest now no no don't
destroy the the organization
[Music]
five isn't Smite the over man uh ench
yeah I think it's pretty decent I'll put
it in the we need a bunch of don't we
need a bunch of blocks like to make a
bridge across the end okay so we have
nine iron yeah a few would
be I mean yeah a few we we will
definitely need some blocks are we going
to do the bed Tech
tactic didn't we try that the first time
we killed him
together we tried it I think does
anybody you tried it works happens what
is it I don't know if you if you use a
bed in the in the end it explodes right
kind of hide but you can jump on it it's
also in the it knocked out a large
amount of remember it did that too oh it
actually made a decent difference so we
have one person who's like the sacrifice
and then the no if you block your like
like hide behind some of the Rocks you
don't take that much
damage okay from the bed explo oh by the
way one somebody has to be a tank I
changed the difficulty for today's uh
cause from easy to normal cuz we were on
easy this whole time we've been on baby
mode yeah but it wasn't so baby we died
quite often and you know had our own
issues so feel going to hear the end of
it nowes not make feel
better oh yeah
music love some
mus yeah oh beautiful what are we
listening to
everybody what's it called I didn't see
it I just put it in it's nice clue I
think it said blocks or
something oh oh no all right party time
huh I'll get my fcy
go get it go oh nice need sword I
[Music]
was it's a good working
song yeah Mining and working song they
maybe despawned because of difficulty
change no they despawned before I
changed the difficulty I checked they
were just gone
o Riptide Bane of Arthropods wow how
helpful and the B of
arthropods kill the
spiders yeah hey I have two or we can
make three potions of slow
falling cuz we have a f a single Phantom
membrane maybe I I'll work on that I'll
cook this iron cook up some potions
again wait do you know where the where
the thing is I put it uh somewhere yeah
I saw it on the on the in the Box okay
okay okay let her cook let her cook we
are
cooking cooking I'm cooking Co
oh need
coal H this was actually the first time
that uh I ever was at least involved in
building like a functional Farm like the
iron farm my whole Minecraft history in
these past four years I've always
avoided making Farms is kind of feel no
sorry what I know Fun's the right word
but accomplished you feel accomplishment
right when you finish it you're just
like yeah yeah and a lot of frustration
when it just doesn't work and when
things glitch around in this old version
of
Minecraft we got three more emerals wee
Diamond a block of diamond oh let's
go a block of diamond a block that's
good yeah that's really good we can
probably already make the last diamond
helmet that we were missing if someone
wants to make that
diamond ah sugarcane farm with my mom
yeah that was yeah that was mostly my
mom
oh
slime that's a mean dude he's spy yeah
oh kill yeah beat him
up beat him up beat him up beat him
[Music]
up did you have a nice nice
birthday I
did I slept so much after my birthday
stream a that's
nice Ked yeah after big
stream feels good mhm yeah it does MHM
love having a big
Eep oh it sounds so nice right now h no
it's 7 a.m. I'm fine I'm fine I'll I'm
caffinated right now oh oh I need
somebody to put me on a leash and run me
like a like a dog on a treadmill
something did you guys see uh the the
myth uh Ramen collaboration was
announced a few like an hour ago or so I
saw that let's go get some Ramen in LA
and in New Jersey this summer you can
get myth themed Ramen Jersey yeah Jersey
I'm so sorry there's a Ramen
there sorry my chat I have not retweeted
it yet I just woke up sorry dead be they
got some cute cards too new and
everybody's got like one
item GA has like a man I think oh I'm
slurping
here I'm slurping here Callie has a
chocolate cake dessert thingy it looks
yummy
has has a a mushroom Ramen I think yeah
with lots of mushrooms on it it looks
really good and I have an orange soda
very which is I mean you know there need
to be some nice uh basic refreshments
and I I'll take it what what's yours do
I get something you I already said you
have the Boba te
oh
pearls the
pearls they pears Watson's egg
what I like I like the idea of it being
her pearls never yeah t like like she's
a detective that found eggs just like
villagers oh
no oh no the
Lord
eggs that's why there's so many of them
so if you don't thoroughly chew them you
have the risk of a small Aly hatching in
your stomach oh no is that what the
alien movie up coming is about it's
about the no this is going taking over
the world is I support that movie's idea
I support it that's exactly what I want
to happen oh my goodness my inventory
just exploded with things
uh where did it go I'm blind you too
small Al inside of you no thanks drink
the
BBA
fine oh I think it disappeared probably
underground life's all about new
experiences right
wa
exactly if you say
so come back oh he came back oh creature
oh my God he's oh
creature careful
now
hey hey why are you buing me in
particular funny
Target he's dead it definitely did not
help in that battle it was killed by a
sword that I named named the after myth
instead of the
aftermath the
after what happens after myth uh what
does happen after this promise promise
yeah does the world just
explode gobbled into a black
hole gobble
gobble but it looks really SI the name
after myth on the sword looks really
aesthetic I have to say after dinner
myth can you imagine if D not saying Kik
Kitty but saying gobble gobble instead
gobble go you imagine I think I couldn't
isn't that a turkey
thing I feel like she would have been
called a turkey okay uh she's
a what's waya no don't what wait what
what's Way's animal what what is she uh
turkey yeah exactly
no peacocks and they go yeah she a peac
PE foul a pea foul foul which is turkey
foul
tarnished sorry she's a turkey as much
as I am a chicken really aren't they
making a new Phoenix Emoji it's already
there if only that existed four years
ago I would have taken it as my claim it
what are they going to do I don't I'm
too attached to my chicken emote at this
point add it oh that one cool though
looks really
nice looks so
cool dang it born a little too little
too early yeah fire
bird oh so how how we doing on the iron
front we have 13 singular irons and two
blocks o okay there's about to be five
more iron added onto
that with the 13 I can make another iron
block and then we
need a few more
singular uh we
need
wait wait that no we can make it we can
make the Anvil let's go let's go Anvil
time now please choose your books and
enchantments wisely and keep in mind
that you don't have to use the books you
can also just throw the piece of
Enchantment into the enchantment H the
piece of armor into the enchantment
table and see what you get there by
chance
looting on The Mending sword will we get
perhaps more items from the
mmm
perhaps some iron from the zombies what
my Ming sword already has uh some uh
other enchantments it's already full
oh I'm going to go farm some exp now is
piercing good for arrows or is that just
sword Pier
I wouldn't put that on anything tph oh
is it not that good Smite what about
Smite SM sword I think not so bad you
could put someone could put protection
on their chest or
something oh it's for Undead I see
piercing three piercing three
respiration I'm trying to figure out
what would be good for a bow and arrow
cuz I feel like I'm going to end up
using a bow and arrow oh wait aim
correction do they have that aim
correction oh if only they did a corre
winners a plus away power wow too bad we
don't have power yeah power but the bow
if you if you don't have the right book
just put the bow um well you need some
levels but I can also maybe do it for
you cuz I'm it's okay I get levels you
can put it on the enchanting table
that's behind the
Diaries
mm can I put flame on the
bow yeah
fire flame should only burn like enemy
mobs and like TNT and stuff
TNT I want your
too oh boy do we dry it
out oh maybe not oh maybe I shouldn't be
here K we might actually uh I might hurt
you because I have sweeping Edge when
we're next to each other might be a
little bit
dangerous maybe why that's why I put
thorns on
my on my armor smart wait did we confirm
we're just using iron swords my
bad we might have to we only have one
diamond sword the one that I made I
thought we were using Stone swords
honestly that's anyone going to take the
wbow uh no you can you can
use I made it use it I trust you I take
the strong sword you take the strong bow
okay
wait what should I put on this regular
bow yeah I'm also wondering but that's
what I'm power is
good if you can get infinity that was
good but
[Music]
um otherwise if we still have uh diamond
blocks if it's not we have two diamond
blocks then you can make some more
swords out of
that don't
or
ax too is Axe cheaper to
make just make what your preference if
you put this is a
preference you can only enchant it once
let me see if I get a bunch of level
cheap
yeah sword is cheaper
to they're enchanting I'm an enchantress
wow good stuff in here good is
uh level
30 wait why is there so many bookshelves
how do we make more books because I made
it so that they chat told me that if you
make more shelves then it will be
stronger free more books
better oh by the way if you're looking
for lapis Luli it's in the chest next to
the um next to the enchanting table I
took all of it there was so much in
there you can't take all of it I a stag
okay there should still be I think this
is kind of Overkill is yeah I wouldn't
mind you know I think you know we can
um we don't have to
down we asked for an enchanting table K
built the library the enchanted Library
I stop I couldn't stop anymore my God I
started and then I couldn't stop it was
fun I really got addicted
man wait so you wasted how many
materials building
extra and I was wondering how much
trouble you had building like like a you
know the usual enchanting table we see
like in a in our Minecraft server was
just like one layer of books and I just
walk over oh and see three layers I
thought if I make an enchantment table
and it's not like the full power then it
would be an embarrassment to myself so I
should go full or go nothing I thought
you were loing books you lit have
somebody in chat says we can break the
bookshelves for more books if we're low
on books no no no you can just make more
books we have enough paper and there's
cows for Lea where's the leather I don't
see it the cows the cows and I think
there's some more books in one of the CH
one of the chests uh a few more books
are in there's like a couple more in the
enchanting box yeah yeah we don't oh
wait there's both back here take some
enchant them go enchant them have fun
with my enchanting
table wait a minute they
on this one looks nice I'm going steal
that one now give me something wait
who's got mending anybody did I miss
that conversation the sword the there's
mending on my pickaxe and on my uh sword
the sword if you want to farm some
[Music]
exp what no I don't want you don't want
h no I want mending on this bow well
okay mending yeah I used to have a
villager with mending but he died he he
despawned very rude I guess we can just
get our enchant books and then
enchant yeah but think about it putting
mending on there does it even make sense
when today is the last last day and this
is like the last hour pretty much
no we want power we want to get big and
strong we don't need mending anymore do
we have a collection of uh
puppy somewhere pu paper
paperg I know that word in Spanish
pel there's a lot of paper here okay
yeah
[Music]
is that
French I don't
remember they're just making up
things CH says yes CH says
[Music]
we well guys I want to warn you we now
have a new member who speaks French
so do not with the language too much she
will sense it and she will come over and
um correct us our friend tell how to
pronounce I only care about people
correcting me if it's a language that I
I kind of know a little
bit is it is it BL
or
weage madame
you guys want to farm X yeah I want to
farm someone's sucking them all up wait
I'm almost done I need two more levels
then I'm gone one and a half line the
DMV man it's like we're lining up for
like
something yeah line up sit on Santa's
lap something like that Santa M
Santa Santa hello dried it up you guys
like the mall Santa or the mall Easter
Bunny more I'm partial to the mall
Easter bunny he looks more miserable
actually or maybe it's cuz I can't tell
cuz he wears a he wears like a like a a
a fuit so you actually can't make direct
eye contact unlik the M Santa you can
make direct eye contact and I don't like
that yeah it makes me feel uncomfortable
I prefer the big fake Bunny man right
Ian I'm going go down one
level one yeah go go down go go down the
Maly go
there in the back no go to the front go
to the front one the one socially
acceptable Kelly can you move one to the
left me yeah oh that's too far that's
too
far uh yeah yeah yeah yeah okay okay
nice I took a picture peeking peeking
fruit okay okay um what happen it's not
spawning anymore not much at least
spider up a little bit but
[Music]
a spider yeah I hear a spider up there
somewhere should I go up there I'll go
up there main time declogger oh no I
don't want to touch anything called the
plumbers yeah she's the plumers if we go
to sleep if we go to sleep everything
will
despawn yeah I don't want to touch it
cuz what happed last time no one could
blame you no one
yeah I have witnessed and I'm a rage
quit live when she fixed it for the 10th
time I
wased again yeah it was for beds it was
good I switched the beds because of
experiments you are now in the
experiment you're part of it I knew
it full hat I'm observing your sleeping
patterns depending on who are you
sleeping next to and myth who are you
sleeping more soundly next to sleep
study yeah sleep study currently I
didn't consent to that okay though I saw
I saw some of G I didn't watch it but I
it says I keep on getting it recommended
something about GDA being a test
subject yeah why are you a test subject
I don't remember I'm going to have to
watch the
clip I don't remember she was she was
the one we're all being tested
constantly wait you have a tin foil hat
emote that's yes yes cuz I always make
conspiracy theories and stuff hold on
guys let's put on our tin voil heads for
a
second it's so good oh actually yeaha
drew it Ena drew that
one encouraging cult-like Behavior yes
yeah maybe maybe you should stop that I
just need one more enemy then I'm gone
what do you mean we're not a cult we're
not okay does somebody want to use the
sword because okay um here don't don't
lose it the I won I mean unless it blows
up
again because it's me for some reason I
get the feeling that it might happen no
no no no it's very safe too close no
it's really safe you can like get really
close I'm going to take that advice and
I hear a spider
again you know maybe while you guys are
doing that I'll just fish yeah maybe
we'll get a nice bow out of it oh yeah
oh can you get bows from fishing do we
have one of the sea or something
um yeah look at the sea one kiss of the
sea okay better than nothing one of the
uh things should be enchanted one of the
fishing yeah it has luck of the fish not
luck of the fish luck of the sea luck of
the luck of the fish I Enchanted to eat
do you guys ever think about if you
threw a rock deep into the ocean you
would probably be the the the last
person to touch that rock for a very
very very long
time oh true
isn't that crazy never thought about it
that way that's crazy shall we go rock
throwing
then 2
a.m. let's do it line well go I can give
you like an equivalent take a block a
one block whatever it is go to the edge
of this of one of our platforms and just
throw it off here I have a stick if you
want to borrow that give me
there you go thank
you fine
Ste what a f just throwing the stick off
you're going to miss it Kar you're
missing this content okay okay okay okay
wait I'm coming are you at the at the
mmm name righta I'm going to do it she's
going to do it she's going to be the
last one to touch it I'm the last the
last person to touch the
stick unless you guys find
it there it goes wow how do you feel
after this emotional moment wait I don't
think that was the last one I threw it I
think it touched the bee the bee's down
there oh wow you threw it right on the
bee there there's a lot of be down there
maybe CAU it in its mouth or something
like a rose be on a stick maybe you
helped the Bee by throwing it a stick
maybe that's exactly what it needed I
couldn't throw my bone so I thrw mytic
sorry
be you're so kind oh yeah the be that's
all the way down there yeah
he in a yeah it's all the bees that
spawned from the one block but didn't
know where to go I'm so sad so they just
went to hell instead okay they went to
hell in wow they went to be hell what a
shame we should build down there and say
beine for
it okay I'm going to enchant something
now wait IA did you see my reply to what
you sent me
earlier I think so sent me a
Big Fish building and I said INF saw oh
infrastructure be so clever and
W there's literally like a big big
building that looked like you know a
shark and I was like big F need to send
up to Kura it's a building I think like
in India or something big fish building
it's pretty cute it is
hey man where's the paper do we have any
paper yes there should be paper still
somewhere where wait where's the paper
which
box
um found it okay
wa if you need more there's also sugar
cane
Farm it's a lot of sugar
cane going to buy this 17 what is this
what did I just
build maybe I don't need it I don't need
it I guess this is fine oh he hurt me
but I want to enchant one more
bow I want to ench one
more what level are you going for a c 30
I'm only 26 I'm you can get there yeah
yep then I'll
continum I got to Google what this thing
is in Minecraft oh I should
also yeah slay children wait is that not
how
I in in video
games how do you get pumpkin seeds uh we
have a few in the seed box I think you
can Harvest pumpkin and then put it like
in the crafting area and
then I thought we have more oh okay
that's good I thought I'd make more
pumpkins uh
[Music]
pie was I got
here see I knew prep would take a little
while a little more
you know what we won't have to prepare
golden app yeah there's plenty there's
plenty and we have some cool potions too
and we have we have we have freaking
totem of
undying I think I think we'll win four
of them yeah hey somebody didn't take
their diamond armor is it on purpose cuz
they don't want to lose it or did I make
too
many maybe you made an extra set no I'm
is wearing it Kelly are you wearing it
too I'm wearing mine damn where where
did that come from maybe somebody was
already wearing before we fight
okay ah not yet though can I have this
Banner ominous
Banner do it do it I want
it I don't think it does can you summon
villagers on one block
what don't think so arrows
arrows sugar egg
I'm
crafting pumpin need an empty
space yes one next to it one immediately
next to it is what I've
learned this what do you mean
doesn't I don't get H
need help
no oh you can't use this one okay a
little more
guys where's all the paper take it in my
mouth I don't take it she
ateer she ate her home P your mouth open
61 paper in the shul boxs 61 in the
Sher did you read all our Diaries Kiara
I've been reading them at least from the
ones who wrote something oh I forgot
about
it yeah I get a star you definitely get
a star you and Callie get a
star
oh you always start riding the moment we
talk about the
[Music]
doing your homework last minute before
class starts yeah literally while the
teacher is collecting the
homework
incredible you don't have to ride it now
the day didn't even end yet does anybody
have any wool there should be W should
be by the the the Sheep
yeah huh 29 wool is in there you can
it's near the farm here in the back in
the on the way to the IR farm on the way
to the iron farm in the the first floor
on the first diamond sword oh
I it's in it's in the box right here
give it to
me
okay okay I'll cut some more so thank
you than try not to uh I'm so sorry Mr
sheep oh I'm so sorry yeah it's right I
get a gold star the honest that's music
why is there a polar bear in here let
seem counter
oh don't you see the name oh I see I
pumpkin pumpkin can't grow like
this learning from scr I
see get back up to wanted the sword to
have o sharpness I'm going to make a new
iron sword we have enough iron for an
iron sword
right yeah maybe oh actually we could
should we make some more am I just that
at targeting is that what it is there's
four iron here left over but we should
probably find more everyone can get an
iron sword I don't need one I have my
diamond
sword good uh I mean oh there is a tiny
tiny HP box for this it's only two iron
I was
surprised H maybe if we get lucky we get
another diamond block from mining the
one block a little while ooh true we do
get lucky so often we do get lucky every
can't
grow see we actually we maybe we still
have some more diamonds do
we we might have enough for a diamond
sword diamond BLS and three Diamonds oh
you do okay then if you don't need it we
can make swords some more swords for
everybody who needs
one I could use a sword
I don't need one so ga needs one right
what do I need do you need a diamond
sword oh I would love one if you would
trust me with
suchit probably make make four iron
swords Whoever has diamonds they're in
the chest in the
chest now we
wait I diamonds in what good maybe you
noticed I don't know if you noticed but
I think I did this off stream when you
weren't around do you did you see in
your Atlantis gate did you see the Bell
that we previously talked about it has
now been
added it costed me 32 emeralds
oh got remove the
redock wait you have a bell
yeah
binging oh we have we have shiny melon
slices Hey where's the sword for uh XP
stuff I have it right now I need five
yeah I need five more
levels okay ding dong just tell me when
you're done okay sorry I had to show off
the Bell sharpness three ping bong ping
bong ooh and on breaking three sharpness
three knockback two looting three good
good good Prett good good I made a a
pill oh that's F the banner of it looks
like the can I change
that you can change stuff on the
medication banner I don't like it h h h
what banner I made a banner guides so
you can spell stuff make like a certain
shape like a cookie oh are you Cookie
are you trying to make your shield look
nice no you on the shield that's cute
what are you making it for if it's not
for the
shield for me a for fun yeah have you
ever heard of fun before
fun what is
fun F is for friends who do stuff
together is for you and SpongeBob right
is this another SpongeBob reference in
the myth Minecraft
stream maybe of
course fun is not
allowed why I got an
idea no
fun what's your idea
girl uh secret
secret I think I know what your idea is
impossible you cannot guess are you
making I have an idea five different
shield banners all in our
Colors oh wait my PC lagged wait is that
actually what you're
making no no genuine no okay
[Music]
that would be cool
though
no oh hello fishy time to
die okay I'm almost
done almost dang
it what oh there's the
Box you can't mine gold or with the
stone pickaxe it just disappears I know
that I just wanted to get rid of the
block at that point
yes four more iron at we're going to
show that Ender Dragon his boss oh I'm
excited should I change the difficulty
to hard
no I
could us having more diamonds then iron
is hilarious to me yeah we're so rich
iron draw that's why we made the iron
farm and I'm telling you it worked for a
while and help me with uh raising my
villagers who then despawn I cry a
little purp yeah it had
purpose oh okay I'm level
30 spawn a with they said it fun don't
worry it will not be fun yeah I'm done
I'm done wait who's done I'm done she
needs my
sword I just need some XP to finish
something enjoy thank
you wait are you sure I'm not going to
blow up it's not going to blow up I'm
going trust your own work trust it you
made it so perfectly yeah you did
good it couldn't be any better than
that by the way for food I have a a lot
of fried chicken and and uh grilled
grilled whatever 43 cooked chicken
that's kind of excessive don't you think
oh there's I think there's even more in
the chest at the never I made another
chest there so there should be
plenty yummy and of course golden apples
yes as you know what
punch
n make sure you grab your golden
[Music]
apples
again why the the gold you extra Hearts
make a
sword what extra Hearts big farts oh hey
who
there it also it just also has punch oh
oh yeah
arrows okay stick Flint feather why not
that much Flint
though yeah Flint is really little but
we have I have a lot of bows uh they
should all be in the in the weapon chest
oh wait where did they go we have them
so I have like 31 arrows I I think 31 oh
wait I have them I have a lot of arrows
if I'm going to put the arrows
into the go why is
chest around the
portal oh the nether
portal NE p is it never or never you say
never is well I say never because I
cannot pronounce
th
Li speach and no
no that is not true
no that's just how austrians and Germans
pronounce it
okay I'm actually actually actually
often they would just actually no the
really strong German accents they would
just replace the th with an
S yeah the sza is
very danger Dangerous uh no wait that's
partially Japanese accents I think but
yeah
cooler okay
okay uh yeah okay okay at least I don't
talk like
that is
quite uh what's what's another word with
th to describe the never
ah Thursday th
on on on Thursday we go to Sena
togethera what
is no threatening doesn't work because
threatening they no they wouldn't say
threatening they would say threatening
with f yeah I want heavy German accent K
to beat me up I don't know
[Laughter]
why uh what does this flag mean GAA
uh are you are you taunting me yeah I
was thinking so because just the other
day I watched the Poland Austria match
but I won so I don't know this cannot
bait me or or taunt
me a reminder of my win Poland's coming
back for
you I think they're out it's not the
last okay next year they're coming back
for you we'll see about that eventually
Poland will have their renge oh wait
that's not Poland what do you mean
what it no
it
wider wait or is
it yeah it's the other way around this
way is
Indonesia oh ID let's go ID let's
go hey show some support for ID we love
ID let's go I love ID hey I got a quick
question what's the difference between
enchanted golden apple and regular
Golden Apple oh One Enchanted Apple no
idea does nobody know you got to test it
out
Callie
Google the chat cyclop comeing Golden
Apple I'm going to be one is Enchanted
Enchanted is far better okay can I
enchant all the golden apples with lapis
lazuli oh because we have so many lapis
La sorry feele
to cool I'm going to all these loot of
course no you can't gives you extra
there a power one bow power one
Unbreaking bow o you need Gold Blocks
you can't you can probably combine some
of these bows to like get like a
fully what call it bow and then make
like a better
bow use Unbreaking one that would be
good yeah you'll have
to repair it but you can just combine
the normal bows to make like a I have an
enchanted B already so I can combine it
what's the max ench enchantments like
five or uh
three I think free for for a bow it's
free I think yeah I'm breaking three
power
five okay so we got a lot of
gunpowder oh I I already used a lot of
it iron are you making TNT I'm the demo
man oh we so going this Dragon that's my
plan I was going to I was going to
surprise you
guys okay I would be surprised I have to
stay alive until the very
end I did not hear what you just said I
am here for the
bows okay so personally I feel like I'm
fully prepared I have fully uh Enchanted
armor part no not fully actually said
demo man I thought she said devil
man devil
I'll use my singing The Devil Man theme
and everything the world may I borrow
the sword oh yeah go at the end when
you're done with it it goes back to the
WWA okay I'm the waha my my sword now
sound you don't sound like
wawaa
GOA that is not good that is not good is
[\h__\h] that's
is close enough I'm surprised you came
up with that
much thank you how are these chickens
laying eggs outside of their little zone
right they are going too
far they need to be told where their
place
is I put four enchantments on my bow I
guess you can do that
shees four can I put another one CH does
that
work does that even
work you know what hold on I almost I
have enough experience hold on that I
can get I can make another I can enchant
my other bow and maybe get a better
enchantment doesn't
work how did you get
four I don't know I just I have youant
one power punch and breaking nice Power
Punch okay I think like once you enchant
something like you have a chance to get
other enchantments on the same thing
what I remember
anyways
stretch I could Anvil
it it's okay I think we it's it's
already Overkill everything is already
Overkill so oh Chad wait Chad says
combine it on the books but I didn't do
that I just went one by one with like
four books at the Anvil ah the
enchantment table okay yeah I thought
you did the enchantment table
yeah ah o ah
ah ah
ah I'm ready me too a 20 gifts thank you
so
much yeah g is really committed to the
999 blocks you we the golden apples yes
extraordinary around the although
Callie's working on I
think fixing them hold on self-restraint
that's the word I was looking for yes
you don't feel the urge to mine you
don't yearn for the mines at
all
number you can't even see it yourself
number when I hit tab I see the number
okay
oh I suppose how is everybody
K's got like 6K oh my
lord it's not the p no it's the blocks
that I mind p i i I played a lot off
screen a little bit too much I thought
it was the Ping too in the beginning
espe super big and ours are all super
small 6K
ping oh thank God it's not that's like
an entire six seconds behind her is it
she she's is living in the past oh
no thankfully it's not
that you're sure who's uh still
preparing and what are you preparing
person who's still preparing uh I'm
preparing getting levels to enchant some
stuff I guess okay maybe we can prepare
the the portal cuz we need to like if
someone dies like to get back easily so
we can kind of make it look nicer like
put a stairs down you want to make the
the the yeah okay okay you want to go in
already no I'm just saying like prepare
it so that uh you mean on the it's
prepared in case someone dies yeah on
this side on this side on our side okay
yeah you do it yeah like a chest I'm
preparing yeah but it's directly under
the one block so I kind of have to
destroy this construction I suppose no I
think it's bigger
than so you can make it like off to the
side a little bit CU like right here
probably maybe From Below
let me
check like right here would M this is
fine like we would be able to get almost
fell
down H yeah I'll make that a little bit
bigger down
there scary scary scary scary
scary
scary should probably get the blocks out
of
here wait do I leave blocks underneath
I guess it doesn't
matter
[Music]
um good what are you doing waiting for
my turn at the PPP can you get me some
BLS thank
you wait I got to go threaten the guy
that was in front of me what I'm coming
back behind me I'm coming back from my
spot I'm coming back from my spot
what
hey I would have given it to you but now
it's going to be a blood bath I'm going
to guard your spot for just going to put
stairs here to make it easier a wait
what do you need I'm here now um slab or
stair I got slab for
you I'm going slab of meat got you some
slab of meat right
here uh I'm waiting [\h__\h] how do you make
a slab wait how many do you need you're
get this
ready yeah six is fine that's like the
default
number oh my God wait what wait what
okay where are you green light right oh
hell you dried it out in a green light
wait wait wait red
light did you get them oh my God now I
only got one I think there's too many
spiders up there it's CL here got stuck
in the water hold then darn
it wait look how behind you toilet is
clogged again toilet clogged I got it
you know you clogged
it no it wasn't me okay there we go now
we can get up and down
easily I guess I have to get rid of one
of these blocks on oh yeah now we can
jump in it's not night time we can't
sleep well of the sound that's why we'll
[Music]
wait surely Sun's going down looks like
it's kind of about to go down yeah Sun
is
setting means we can maybe sleep and
then get rid of the
spiders guess this
works I'm making the area a little bit
[Music]
safey reapy at least I'm not falling
asleep I'm
here so hopefully maybe um I'm going to
give you girls a a time limit in 30
minutes y'all y'all by the latest yall
be ready yeah I'm
ready would be nice honestly I can go
now I don't really need me I just want
to make more
arrows get out the way I me hi I need XP
I I gave you the sword what please
respond I gave you the afterm oh oh wait
I thought okay I don't get to keep
it it was not a gift
a thank you maybe we should set up an
emergency chest all right don't know
what you're doing I was just putting
stairs there yeah yeah you can put them
actually do do put them
[Music]
there my
pumpkins that's all I got okay perfect
nice
nice going make it a bit more
visible yeah damn
okay 40 arrows probably going to be
[Music]
sufficient um there's more arrows in in
the chests where the armor was if you
guys need more okay I was just making
more or uh gravel whatever
flint rocks to eat yeah snacks to have
on the
trip Kelly have you been enchanting the
apples have I been what have you been
enchanting the apples you can't it's
they're not craftable no you can only
have regular golden but we have two
Enchanted that we just found luckily so
two people can grab
those ni I don't mean to alarm anybody
but I think something just pushed me is
a server
oh what something pushed you maybe it
was maybe was maybe it was one of
us fear I don't know there where are
you
mm I mean
M here let me
see I will I will observe you think
something pushed you something pushed me
are you
sure yeah I standing here here and then
all of a sudden I was over here I saw I
move I
did don't look at me like that that's
probably just like an an was there enemy
in front of you yeah yeah yeah probably
just like him kind of pushing you to the
side but there's a block in between D
this is how all ghost stories start I
don't believe us not believing gura you
have to believe
me show me okay I believe
you I can't just make it happen I don't
know oh they're behind you nice I don't
I don't know key I'll tell you what
happened she's crazy right she's crazy I
think I mean I don't know like I said
this is how all ghost stories start okay
so what do you believe it just happened
again were you looking I wasn't
looking I was hold on I'm sure we got
the footage somebody can back the tape
I'm sure it's just like just a mob kind
of pushing you easily a little bit
you're lightweight so you know it
happens
okay it
[Music]
shimmy oh you got that at least the the
EXP Farm's working now
yeah I need three more levels and then
it'll be 30 and I'm like might as well
enchant this bow as a Backup backup
bow yeah we'll put it in the backup
chest oh maybe somebody doesn't have a
prop bow yet then they could use it oh
true we can give it to them who needs a
proper bow I just have a power three bow
I think that's you passed your yawn to
me I'm going to punch you for that sorry
about that can't be
help go you need a proper bow I'm
working on it oh okay so that's what
you're currently on okay okay okay
yeah
yeah I'm
[Music]
nothing's spawning again huh should we
sleep through
it sleep
time sleep is always nice let me quickly
for my study rearrange the bed
St okay not like
no my bed where I didn't get all of the
beds Bo give me the beds I need to do my
science stuff
sleep close oh oh who who took the
beds not me thanks it's the ghost no all
right all right
um today's
Arrangement will
be the iron sword is back of Sword hello
chicken can you get off the enchanting
table me
meow
there okay ready hey where'd you
go I'm coming I was making a backup
taking too long yeah I was buy making
potion it's
science yeah wait wait a second what
kind of science wa okay she's sleeping
in the okay sounds like sounds like a
notal science to me in their natural
habitat the F members seem to be
attracted to their own image colored bed
naturally I'm trying to sleep here shut
up real
research well we can't sleep as long as
the other members are not coming to bed
go I'm writing my journal give me a sec
oh my diary you're R already oh she's so
excited to ride in her diary
oh all right come on come on I'm coming
I'm sorry rush perfection K oh
W oh W can we just make her say anything
or right in the
chat I like this TTS
I am your
TTS Tex to speech go go to
sh that was good damn you nailed it
first
try wow wa damn girl impressive now am
is the TTS a level oh I don't think so
that was good made me
happy wait what's it mean uh uh
um uh not greetings ladies and gentlemen
but in a very I would say Austrian
way
gratifications
greetings wait back to the and the
Varian cuz cuz gr Scot is quite the
Bavarian and Austrian way to greet uh
grot yeah you don't hear that in North
[Music]
Germany M I say that when I want to
greet someone politely I say
grot hello snooze you lose you snooze
you lose gar go Squad
Gar so maybe I can put something on my
side I mean while we're still waiting go
for it yeah I just need two more levels
and then we'll be good to go but how
about we make that that uh extra ration
chest or that for example if somebody
dies passes away have a chest by the
portal okay I'll move it over because
there is already some exploration
rations rations yeah and then I have
like a couple weapons like I'm
enchanting that can be backup
weapons backup we I don't know about if
we'll even die we have the totems we
have we have so much stuff I'll move
everything over Kelly can you move the
the pearls ow yeah okay now I have a
very sturdy sword relatively stdy sword
that's all I mean teleport oh yeah that
that's that's what I meant the eyes
ofender what do they do and we need to
put them into the uh the empty Slots of
the portal there's open here no we
already have everything oh it's already
in there oh is that what the sound was
it's not in there but uh it was already
prepped and now we're moving it over
here no don't don't put it in yet though
okay I'm getting free XP let's put it in
a chest stop sucking up on my XP vacuum
get out here wait is that the
scat a I like where's where is it
parasitic Tendencies that's the
Str that's
the yeah I'm down here I made chest for
Stuff damn it okay I'm underground okay
oh
I don't know how to get back up there's
stairs on the
side
oh I promise guys I promise I'm not
stupidy
you I'm not getting any XP I thought it
was losing my
mind I got to charge my bow jump up here
and then you can get up here but yeah
it's it's kind of
weird not your parkour not your fault
okay is this the chest yeah maybe we can
put all related end the dragon fight
things can go in here I got a free level
guys I got free two
levels I would have been 30 by now what
I want free levels what a
deal no free
levels okay Lev extra food
no yes if you die you can just take some
stuff out of
here I think that's enough
[Music]
okay looking fancy what a deal
indeed okay all I need is my sword and
then I'm ready to go me too I'm just
waiting for good to finish leveling just
slow yeah I well I would have had four
extra levels of two people didn't that's
suck it all up
oh no they
didn't which kfb someone just called me
a hag in your
chat what the hell I'm going to freak
out in a sec oh I'm going to freak out
how what level are you
now expensive it could be a compliment
though depending on you think about it
how you think about it it could be I
feel like that's only supposed to be
used for like really
old time back in my day
9,000 over
9,000 will I reach the big
10K you did no but will I why am I
dying better not blow anything up now
would I do
that
[Music]
yeah where is my
donkey donkey I'm almost done I promise
I just moved again oh did you see that
you were watching you must have seen it
oh it's bub read theat sure the Clippers
will get it wait to ban no wait it is it
is I it's oh my
God what was
it it's the
ghost the ghost I just realized this
won't really work cuz I think guda has
my oh it's cuz she used the oh I saw her
footsteps
okay wait what it was me all along goba
wait what I'm
invisible what I thought I was losing my
mind I'm going to
cry well I will I will give you the I
will why am I flying why am I flying why
am I why am I flying what the [\h__\h] I
feel like I'm flying wait I'm not flying
I'm just I'm WR get down here uh uh
don't she over here look at the spiral
she's right here I'm blocking her oh I
see was it you from the beginning even
from the start of the ghost no I was
standing next to you when she said she
was moving CI fre are you guys done I'm
done so it wasn't all
me oh wait you need this wait
stin I have a sword you lose Watson
sword yeah give me I need my my waa
sword
back one more level okay I'm hungry for
levels I can't I can't help but how much
do you need still you need it for
anything I'm at 28 I was going to make
an extra weapon if I had the invisible
portion I could have sit by her and got
some free
x I want there spiders in there
the you're making me feel like I'm
crazy terminate the SP I saw Bubbles and
I thought I actually had a ghost or some
kind of I don't know curse curse on
me spooking could I chased by
ghost let me give one more level and
then I'll leave forever such a chicken
are
you no going to slurp up my let's finish
out
last it didn't work oh oh slurper X slur
I'm almost there I'm not the same person
I used to be it's okay I got some CR not
as Brave any
I'm more Brave oh
really prove it defeat the Ender Dragon
alone what don't take the Ender Dragon
alone you can take it you can take prove
your bravery still a few potions there's
a luck potion a strength potion and an
instant health potion I think luck is
maybe unnecessary but go you can have it
Watson thank you you're
welcome I'm putting it in here
too yeah yeah so we're looking
beautiful beautifully
prepared shall we go soon yes I'm ready
I'm just making a cool bow to put in the
chest
okay
enchanter on
Shante on
Shante
flame good remember you were saying some
name and then people thought that was
name of new member and you like leaked
something but you didn't what was it was
it like Mary or so in the last uh
Minecraft
stream uh maybe I don't remember what
I've said oh God what did I say Mary
mhm our new member Mary okay yeah yeah
when they when they knew that we had new
members coming but I think the names
weren't known yet they were like oh gooa
gooa surely that was one of the names
right
[Music]
Mary no are you kidding me
I
got she wouldn't slip up like that I'm
I'm I'm rock hard when it comes to that
lock down it happened it could
happen nah I would cry if I accidentally
leaked a name or so of them makes me so
nervous I'm made of iron iron nothing
comes in and nothing comes out wait no
everything can come in but it won't come
out are you constipated
no I meant with
words my Lord you
[Laughter]
are you know what I
mean I
mean we all have problems that we
struggle
with
sometimes sometimes it's something like
that it's okay it's okay we we share and
we care
care care care all
right distant Kelly Hell
Yeah Yeah the more you're going to make
me wait the more cursed things I'll say
I'm ready to go I'm sitting the Creeper
face I'm waiting okay am I ready too no
no okay I'm just enchanting something
okay oh wait are we going to do the
thing we're doing it like now now what
yeah oh the murder of the Dragon yeah
yeah okay I'm going to take a PE break
I'll be right back okay okay
byebye
okay hey what you looking at
guys what she looking
at the beautiful
flag my God
get down here spider all right I guess
I'm ready now why you looking there
girl can't believe she never stopped
after
999 this
[Music]
girl I mean I believe it we can have oh
we have a we have a high score right now
so the lowest now is
gooda she wasn't always the lowest
though and uh the second lowest is Cali
but hey we worked hard on a lot of stuff
in terms of blocks the
lowest and then there's Ena and then I'm
a really close what is it the block the
amount of blocks Luda has like 1,000
well
999 CI has
1,600 then uh second is no third is Ena
with
2,600 and then is second with 2,700 and
I am he first with a whopping
6,800
hiie middle of the pack just the way I
like
it oops oh no middle of the path oh
[Music]
yeah
uh NY what is wrong you need something
we can help
you K
we oh no I'm innocent no I said can we
not C oh
Callie call making sure to establish her
innocence in any
case TR
Fair are there any extra totems uh
there's only those four I think okay
feel free to take one I don't know I
think I think everybody already got one
I didn't take I don't have one
oh let me check but there wer not in the
chest wait
what I took all the
totems N I just got
here check your inventory empty your
pockets no you can't make
me this is a search do not resist I'm
resisting you I'll be able to see your
inventory if you
die you wouldn't you
I don't I don't have any no fighting use
your aggress against the End Dragon I
don't want that you said empty your
pocket give a junk it's not junk it's my
inventory it's my
inventory okay so who wants a totem who
wants a totem you wait maybe not me wait
yeah me take it take it take those
totems one per person one person will
not have it I'll I'll I'll be the one
who doesn't have one oh yeah you're own
die wait should I have it don't know
kind of pooo I think you want you can
you can car kill I don't think I would
no it's okay I have some apples so wait
so do the regular golden apples do
anything they give EXT extra Health okay
yeah they're good for you okay yum yum
yeah the chest is full down below just
why there's a lot of
items what
chest um just at the at the mmm oh oh
well I think we don't need it anymore
wait somebody said that povs streamers
only should have the uh totems what do
we think about
that that is part of my plan oh you can
have mine then I
you you take mine then uh no streamer is
in you right now you think I would die
Enchanted Apple cuz it's okay we take
this pretty good apparently well cuz if
I die nobody's like missing out on
anything but if car dies then what but
make sure to take a shield and have full
armor maybe you can also take K you can
take an instant health potion out of the
chest you hold the shield if you can
I'll hold a
shield potion of instant Health
healing I got Splash health potions too
so take take what you need look iron bar
oh I'll take
meat y yum yum okay yum yum Kell you got
everything too ready to go my Pock guess
I'll open it up then I can't wait wait
I'm not there yet was ready I'm not
ready I'm scared it's kind of hard to
see it uh oh well maybe we need to get
rid of those blocks there there's blocks
in the middle 15 arrows is that bad
there should be more arrows I think like
this should
work Arrow uh oh wait uh I put away my
tools can someone get rid of the these
blocks on I got it this pink one and cuz
those be careful with the slabs at the
bottom cuz those it's going to open up
don't don't don't open where I'm
standing okay I got the pink one what
else the uh the the wooden one I got 15
shots I'll just make sure they're good
water bucket what why water bucket the
stone uh in case you get blasted off
into the air
the stone Kiara oh yeah does anyone want
slow falling potion I have two extra I
it's okay yeah that's good Kelly thank
you can I what no wait streamers should
get what oh I have water bucket I'm fine
can I have the potion I have yeah I'll
have one so thank
you okay we're so overprepared probably
no this is excellent need water bucket
thank you it's just when like you need
to you know save your
fall or no for the Ender drag ender men
if you look at the ender men they'll
follow you but if you have water around
you then they can't touch
you I'm scared of water just don't look
at don't look in don't look in their
eyes don't do it don't look at them
easy easy easy I should have made them
all three oh W somebody scared of
water so shall I put the Eyes
in
okay wait I it's okay we're fine we're
fine I'll be fine oh we should bring
some blocks building blocks I have a
bunch of4 52 stacks and somebody I would
say either you know or am once we're in
should build a safe platform
please pleas maybe cuz she's
streaming okay uh I have a donation a
generous donation of
cobblestone you might have to go with
other I have endstone here I have very
pretty uh terracotta gave it to you oh
I'm
nervous I need for nervous be fine we
can do
this
okay I'm going to I'm going to put the
Eyes in I'm going to put them in we've
done this before haven't we guys we have
done it before we a lot didn't we yeah
didn't WEP times we I think we died
it'll be fine it's going to be okay I
feel like we're even more prepared than
back then possibly the eyes yes okay
finding it was harder last time uh oh no
doing you with the Apple I'm doing it oh
wait I didn't grab the apples take take
your apples take your F grab your apples
I have one apple they're in here
harvested them special oh wait where is
it by the bort are you supposed to take
one take five five ah five H
okay call made many many golden apples
yeah the enchanted ones are special
that's special loot that we found oh
wait I took one of those is that okay
the uh it's probably fine what should I
take I'll take the I'll take five of the
rular do you want to see the moment
girls is no one using the flame wa wait
wait wait wait I'm not ready hold on
there's a flamethrower you can give me
[Music]
likeing where's the
H at the other boxes section here
ah thank you yeah kfp says get out of
the ring before you put in the last one
okay I'm already out I'm already out can
you imagine if she wasn't though that
would be
pretty
no silly
no I'm scared
what's the button again to quickly put
something in your right hand do you guys
know or does chat
know Buton F yeah I thought F oh it is
actually F girl wow you did not lie to
me she wasn't pay respect
all right Sor I'm almost ready almost
done yeah what are you doing nothing
what are you doing a
surprise surprise I have a surprise too
what's your surprise oh uh don't worry
about it oh
okay I'll tell you mine if you tell me
yours wait does it involve me
dying uh wait I can't die at the end
that my surprise what's your
surprise nothing okay we will all stay
alive yeah no deaths right no death run
my question was for you right no no Des
runs Demo
Man okay I'm ready you saying I just
shouldn't enter then oops no death
allowed uh no where's my
feelings no walk off into the only one
death is allowed that's you oh me
okay I'm hyped
I'm I'm ready to put the eye in I'm
ready ready my second try at the Ender
Dragon SP I'm scared somebody else go
first yeaha Go please and make a
platform I slipped
no
you okay how does it look can someone
bring some uh Whatchamacallit blocks
uh not blocks it's
uh torches torches I have
okay know we need torches Apple it's low
Health okay is it safe to go in N hold
on give me a second I'm just making sure
it's sealed off go go go my go go my Au
AUA do we have water the bucket with
water you got a bucket always got my
bucket okay my bucket in me is it ready
o that wasti yes you can you can come in
I'm
[Music]
building I have a no glitch please no
glitch okay oh nice no
glitch wo thereon I see a wait why did I
my water the Dragon
scary already there's yeah W oh God oh
God oh God oh God but put torches down
wait are you still over there I'm sorry
I lagged out for a second I'm don't come
in yet wait okay bring ladders can you
make ladders really quick for me I have
20 how many do you need 40 oh okay no
actually 20 should be okay that should
be good if we go there attack already
wait wait wait wait let me just
I can I can make more don't die don't
die stop stop stop stop here I have 32
no no no
girls wait who got rid of the B what
happened Go Girls Girls good girls come
come let's fight I feel like it's
starting because they already
shot over prepared T
my my stuff wait Who removed the ceiling
oh no oh no oh no no no no I again no no
I'm not wa want to go in there then we
all wait wait what do we need to do wait
wait for it to go away wait for it to go
away but my stuff I'm guessing your Stu
is probably going to lie there for a
while don't worry it's going away it's
going away wait now you can come okay
and it's all like all your loot all your
stuff is in one place so you'll have to
like split it again in the back corner
the dragon is spawn camping turn it back
to
easy yeah yeah get your f again
and not mine what belong to I lost all
my stuff with all my potions easy I have
all the potions how did you how did you
lose it it's still there right T my TN
it's all there I think that's mine
here's a
bed also yours don't wor this is yours
and then a bucket of water for you I'll
but
it wait what happened to the ceiling oh
boy but
not mine okay it's not yours I don't
know whose that is then about potion of
slow falling who's that belong to wait I
I did seal off the falling or the
ceiling right it was not enough I guess
or I don't know
we that's fine I got it should I come
in yeah yeah you can come you can come
it's okay ceiling is too
low it's okay we're going to go in like
oh it wiped them t okay time to go time
to go time to go guys get out of that
spicy stuff
noad well no golden apples though all
the golden apples are
ging just just uh everybody keep on
running and uh I'm pressing W I even
though it gets removed when people spot
in but I'll I'll tell you in know when
it's safe to come back in I'll tell you
I have it in my eye okay it's
disappearing you can come in now okay
why are there so many Ender you've seen
this before GAA I don't
remember difficulty is all my stuff gone
I have I have your potions I think I
have no weapons and nothing I got 15
shot I have everything youve got youry
good thing I made some extra weapons oh
thank you naked en oh here does anyone
have my armor and
stuff uh all I had was that ah he's
coming
yep I guess I'm playing oh I could use a
bow oh thank you oh there he is I see
him can we kill him let's kill him let
go I guess I'm just support this
run what what what are you missing Ina
uh all
the where they go does anybody have in
their
inventory mm I this and then what I'm
wearing wait I have armor for some
reason you have extra armor yeah give it
to give it to oh my God I have uh 12
golden apples I must have taken your
stuff en I think you took my golden
apples oh wait I have it come take I'm
so scared right now okay no need to be
afraid
to a lot of TNT everywhere what the
where what are the Enderman doing are
they following I'm putting TNT so that
when the dragonly close you guys can't
shoot it oh
smart um sorry Hi I if it's high enough
though that's why I wanted ladders so I
could get higher he hat Mees GA did you
the the equipment to Ena no I don't know
where is right now oh I'm in the middle
of the stage kind of he doesn't care he
still hates me can we I don't want to
start this too much without Ena being uh
equipped wait wait wait can you
I have your pants he's following pants
the water I kill him yeah kill him kill
him wait here here here here here here
back
away
okay is he
gone oh boy um all right now they're all
they all hate me a lot okay die let's go
guys let's
go
okay let me make
him maybe I drank that too early
hey you guys didn't see what I did to
your buddy right okay we're good there
more where that came from buddy boy oh
you want your
apples
shot oh God take your time how do I
split a stack uh it's
a no no thank
you all right let's go kill him get
him this was a bit
anticlimactic no was kind of rough we're
fighting we
go
nice get him we need all of them right
do we yeah we need to climb up to some
of them cuz there's cages M I don't have
enough blocks to climb up on anything me
neither wait here take I have your
pants ow come on thank
you can you not shoot inside got one
my yeah I'm going to
die it's all right you
good which one it's only the cage one oh
there's one right there something
attacking me um Can can we just shot out
the dragon instead and like AG I'm
shooting at
him I'm shooting at
him shoot not
great shoot Adam yeah I'm shooting okay
we don't get rid my aim is
bad we so far have done no damage on him
hey really but I hit him several times
missing could pixes and stuff oh
dragon's getting healed I yeah oh we got
to
maybe got to go can we go someone needs
to die yeah we need blocks
I have block I have a pickaxe I can mine
for Block yeah just mine mine some
blocks if you can and then go around to
the cages I think the others are cages
need to be
destroyed I just use a pickaxe on
him yeah he's Landing get him I don't
think it matters cuz we have to get the
cages first yeah he
he I missed there is one that's falling
Hallelujah
nice are they going for
me why are they
screaming oh they dying oh wait I can
angry we're destroying their lord PE end
Pearl when I can go to up to one
cage I can go go go go and when you go
down you can mine the blocks back and
then you can go to the next one I think
I can also go up go go go go go go get
those cages if you can taking my potion
yeah try to try to the dragon away from
the whoever's climbing I'm climbing now
I'm also climbing should I not be yeah
you should you should go yeah
okay wait what do I do with this thing
do I like destroy it or
something courage I love courage help me
I got I got one I got
one I got one which one this is not one
oh was that not was that already empty
uh it was just it was a Bedrock okay
Dragon came back not going to explode
it'll be
fine okay there's one up that
one there's a lot of Ender Ang I could
fly up to one of these look it get it
gets done the job gets done there's a
really tall one that's still I saw it
while I was
flying there's one he's tether to right
now that that's uh it's so high that one
up there yeah can we climb there or no I
mean we just be to shoot but it's so
high if somebody gives me their blocks
their stack if they have them I can do
it I have I'll give it now I have 26 and
56 got 59 here you go Watson oh that
should be plenty
here the Stars
nice please don't shoot me please don't
shoot
me I got an end
they're my friends oh
oh we're having a party there they love
you oh they really like me oh what are
we going to do about this they're so
tall I'm distracting them okay come to
me you're so
sparkly all right I got it are they all
you you got it are they I think they're
all gone okay well good when you walk
away are they going to kill you yep okay
I'll stay put don't worry
no how do you unagro them a murder kill
them kill them all murder I'm
okay it's very Pur over here yeah shark
bait he's taking the TNT though I don't
know
no the
end no no why do the end hate us so
much
whyo hello boys yeah we have plenty of
pumpkins can I survive
for
my guess there's no more buckets he's
pering is he no come down he's coming
down he's coming down he's going to land
get him I cannot see have much
how does he manag to always make me f
are not I this this is not as easy as I
thought please help me standing over me
I think we're overprepared I was like
are you sure he's going
to's lands again
go maybe it's wor dying once I can pick
up your items no you having your own
little battle
here his own internal battle wait I got
to use some of these
pearls I SLI through okay wait I'm good
we need more block I don't think we need
blocks anymore cuz we don't have we got
all the
stars is it
inevitable is this working and we don't
have that many building blocks anymore
if you guys build up I'm bu the pillars
and uh end can't see me
here come here
Enderman end more
like oh
I don't have iron for iron bucket
unfortunate I think we should have an
iron bucket somewhere in the base uh in
one of the chests like where the
diamonds
are wait pause guys I got to take a
snack no not know the Ender sorry I'm
talking to the Ender boys I know it's a
joke anyway but oh okay you can't just
pause this all right I'm
ready I wish oh that's 12 golden cars I
probably don't e that much I Uso my
sword on the
end is is your sword dead um time to hit
it with your fist or make some make the
TNT
explode why am I why am I being the
Archer believe in you clappy Mo I got a
couple hits on him a couple only a
couple though calm down Dragon I think
it's oh there's
water I'm brave I'm brave I'm brave I'm
brave I'm brave Brave I'm brave I'm
brave oh you're the bravest oh [\h__\h] oh
no
no I'm alive I'm alive I'm
alive don't die is there water do you
guys have water no I don't have
water I have oh [\h__\h] what's the a today
I can't see yeah aim not very good for
me either that's kind okay I see feel
like you're not
connecting oh he's coming
down nice
oh get him I beat him up
sorry get him okay butthole
dead why does not
work what do the pearls do I thought you
can teleport when you're flying and and
bring yourself back to the ground oh you
can if you like hit the ender pearl if
the hit ender pearl hits the ground
before you do then yeah oh
[Music]
okay come on
how many shots do I have it's the P it
didn't hit in time I I threw it way okay
he's there again Landing Landing there
is no iron for the buckets for water
buckets
chat I can't reach
him more arrows pretty soon here oh no
we're good am I actually not reaching
him am I too
small we build some stairs next time he
gra all myu thank
you get in your
bus
I oh there it is get down here young man
get down this instant nice shot somebody
just got him thank
you good job
de did I this Enderman wants to beat me
up
are you still being you you're still
there I see you from afar I'm
helping in my own way you're going to be
the reason that Endermen are going to go
extinct that's that's a good thing yeah
ah
ah ah oh no he's he's cornering me get
him guys get
him I'll be with you in a moment we're
getting closer okay he's kind of low
he's less than yeah yeah oh he's
freaking leave me
alone why haven't I used dead eyee yet
yeah we should have given good a pumpkin
helmet we had some in our
base missing all my
shots I mean every time the dragon is
going up I have different entertainment
by looking
at
the oh my God all my hits are going
through these guys this is okay h oh
I
me night Comet night Comet coming right
up I cast night
Comet I don't have oh wait I have four
oh where' they come from I have arrows
if your shadows if your ping is better
come
take nice the W come on oh is he coming
almost there think he's coming coming
yeah oh I'm going to help now
okay
now come
[Music]
on we did it oh now he's a disco ball
now we can watch the
credits
yay oh the egg yay look at the egg egg
wait let's take a picture first yes yes
yes yes take a pck together where uh can
we make stairs so like a platform there
she goes there she
goes I didn't use the totem but I used
all the
apples y oh my I was here too this was
such a weird fight I died five times had
a good time is good free oh there she is
hello how have you ended the cycle of
what that was how did it end killed them
all cuz it it seemed like the more you
kill the more you
aggro they just wouldn't leave you I see
America um I'm sure kiar feels really I
feel so let's
go I mean if if I just looked at if I
just look at one snippet of it then it
is the Austrian flag yeah you red and
white in there yeah red white red some
part of that is
me let's go
nice okay let's all gather and uh take
photo oh we don't need the I okay the FL
funny I'm going to hold a golden apple
cuz that was my job you are barely
visible okay wait what's a fireworks
star I I made one but I didn't know you
had to combine it with fireworks do you
want it n i i I'll make it when we get
back you have to combine it make a
firework good take off your
armor oh y guess we don't need it
anymore cute wait what this is how we
die yay well I'll take that
death wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait why are you throwing
away stuff okay look cute like you
always
do oh girl
how you how you
back I'm okay the flag is there in my
Steed it's okay already take pictures
okay it it was a good one are you dead
no no I'm back in my
home ah such a beautiful nighty together
girl okay give me a sec let me
uh let me boys please
go fight them go fight them my sword's
going to die wait why are they not
attacking you because I didn't attack
them and I didn't I listen I I Lov
sounds at the end shoot I want to help
you but um it's nice to see you
fulfilling the side quest
alone I I'm okay all I got is a wooden
ho
now are we now take my swords
ah it's the P the
P birthday I'll go hi
call no you know of the Void the P up
into the sky with
me doesn't do remind you of Cosmos Elden
ring elen ring I'm thinking about elen
Ring again come I'm not Minecraft no I
was watching you fight Estel for a while
it's almost safe I think it's number two
okay I'm not even looking at him anymore
it's safe all right it's not safe it's
not safe it's not safe it's not safe
okay it's
safe let's
go let's watch
credit okay are we going yeah I guess so
I think I picture
together together oh
together is trying to kill us all I'm
going trying to blow us
up no no no no no I'm going to
okay guys I'm watching the credits right
now oh my
God wait spoilers tell us what do you
see it's a your special credit what it
say it says Long Live
Minecraft dude no way Long Live shall we
jump in together what about the egg um
we can take that eventually but we don't
need
it oh
another one
jump
jumping what car I thought you already
watched the smok one block it won't let
me in what have I done please help what
hey at least you guys went to a
different screen just jump up wait I'm
floating on top of it what have I done
no here it doesn't work for me there's
like glass underneath it's like a fake
floor may I see you guys sep there's no
credits in one
BL no but at least you got through I'm
not getting through I'm not I didn't get
no I'm still in the end I don't see you
me please help please help I don't see
you guys either we all got split into
different realities yeah oh is this just
how it ends I don't like this how it end
we just crashed the server we're all in
the end but we don't see each other
that's so lonely yeah if we die we turn
back to our world it's like a metap it's
like a it's like a long long dream we
had I'm not going to die here I'm going
to stay here I'm putting my flag back
down I have all my cool things so I
can't access my inventory anymore yeah I
can't access my inventory either what
beating the game broke it did you beat
the game is that it is this how it's
supposed to be I guess
so well I wish I could be standing by
your side let's try re oh I can't I
can't I can't open the E Escape screen
to disconnect neither can I it brecks
your computer when you beat the game
stuck in the game this is my bad end
no hey I'm I'm making fireworks I
thought you guys were going to come back
we were going to celebrate but guess I
want to be with am do we die oh wait oh
if you tap out of your game you can get
into the Escape screen screen the um
disconnect screen and then you can log
back in and you end up in ah I ended up
back in the house of our bed
safety nice it's pretty cool Y and we
still got inventory yay we got it I'm
alive she lives after being bullied by
Enderman
endlessly beautiful good I we found each
other again e noise the power VA tab I
can't it doesn't work when I ult
him oh say can you
computer
good the void where' she go I'm stuck in
the
void very very nice where are you
putting it up there I did full screen
but still this more on top of Atlantis
you control all the is Atlantis one of
those States now it is didn't you know
that so how many states is it now in
total 2
55 oh oh I hope that's correct GAA I
hope it
is never going to use wait there's even
a Liberty Bell bless it be off the FL it
is we should sh Fireworks off of the
Atlantis gate when it turns night time
oh do you want this I have aor star oh
yeah yeah yeah here thank you my menu
didn't work so I'm just restarting the
game
okay you where should we watch them
should we watch from the top of the PPP
or maybe from the top of here he top of
PPP would be cute because of that F art
yeah do yeah that is where we were
sitting right yeah is it safe up there
we need to build like a ladder that goes
up ladder I I have ladder okay Red
Blocks and then cross the bridge and
make
more Okie doie yeah make big ladder I I
will be
cameraman oh that's surely going to end
well nobody ever well the cameraman
doesn't die but uh I'll watch from down
here for when they
fall get a good camera angle
mhm oo just like jackass so can we open
that up is that going to be okay to open
up isn't there going to be a lot of
enemies up there no we're not going to
open it up we just go on top of go
around okay make like
a open it not open it how do you go
around it though it's shape like a giant
mushroom you can get up bu some stairs
or something yeah no problem yeah maybe
maybe not from there ga maybe from where
the other stairs were and then straight
up so we end up at the edge of it I
guess oh okay would be good probably you
do not want to crack that
open it sounds a little
spicy wait so wait wait wait wait wait
it's like opening P's box or watch wait
you're walking oh my yes you you're
going to push me off the edge what I'm
behind you what do you mean the Ping the
Ping
oh don't worry goba wait no this is how
we have to do this this is how we have
to do this okay
yeah go wait throw me the
ladders she going to throw it off the
ledge okay oh catch good
shut
up say nothing
shut caught in 4k
stop throw it throw how many myths does
it take to make a staircase shut
up okay col is clear oh if you guys hry
we catch the
sunset y okay girls you can come up it
seems I don't think we're going to catch
it though this is like holy
Holy
Ground CAU where the made along the way
sunset's dying very beautiful okay our I
can catch the fire maybe we catch the
sun right oh yeah that
works your lawn chairs out get the
barbecues popping off I was thinking I
was like this actually really put
a and now we get to hear the beautiful
sound of monsters as well right I'm
making piles everybody takes on
fireworks this is one pile this is next
C this is cute oh wait the next pile Oh
I I still have a firework star several
firework stars in in my inventory from
you me too okay do how who didn't get
fireworks there's another pile over
here thank
[Music]
you all right where should we go like
here looking over the thing yeah oh yeah
just like the thumbnail picture yeah yay
wait we just shoot them what about the
five stars do they work too yeah they're
in the fireworks I'm not sure how I
think you have to look down and then
wait I'm
bald
cool I'll shoot
some you look down blue
yeah fire
this look like
years yay happy New Year
man it's so pretty some of them are not
exploding properly are they yeah I
accidentally made like regular ones a oh
I got
[Music]
thosea
beautiful okay that's all of them I
think yeah there's like the regular one
w
pretty okay that's it
okay oh that's
finale oh it's raining
cool it's snowing wait can we take a
picture where we we have like a good
shot of like uh the little things we
built over there like oh here we fa this
let's take one together let's take off
the
armor
yeah wait what's wrong with my head ah
balls same you guys me to
me yeah it's a bug i' I'd rather wear my
helmet in that case look like you have
to confess your sins to
me wait I don't have a helmet I am a
none I can all wear helmets I bet I look
bald oh I kind of yeah I do look bald
whoa uh I want to have empty
hands there forgot what it was okay this
uh Golden Apple wait I want a better
view for Golden Apple
okay okay ah don't go I thought you were
going to fall
off because for the screenshot being on
the edge is kind of
bad oh should I should we
expose Calli let's expose the the stupid
foreheads let's do it okay take them
out okay te
Che
wow cute this is what we built in about
a week or so with F3 F6 F3 F3 for
screenshot F no f f F2 F2 and if you
want to get rid of the UI it's F1 yeah f
f f f f F1 but I mean how do I change
perspective F5 I can't believe I still
have forgot F5 there's three different
perspectives so you have to switch
around I think we should all Run and
Jump Off The Other Side together guys
wouldn't that be so
fun
okay what Cy you got you a
screenshot I think I think it took well
if it didn't it's cool okay I guess
we're going to leave all this behind
time to leave this planet behind wait
can I have a little people need
us speech before we spee speech speech w
beach beach I am happy that we were able
to give everybody some nice nostalgic
feelings not just chat but ourselves
perhaps too with these loud zombies that
I'm hearing in in the background uh I
want to say thank you to the girls for
participating in this project and and
myth is number one myth is best myth is
cute my is
love
forever let's go
down right let's JP guys let's
go with all my
homies my homies off the bridge with my
homies this is like juming but we died
it's about
time okay this I I'm going to log out
because I don't want to I want this to
beend
[Music]
we did it roll the credits
yay job guys the Diaries fun the Diaries
somebody wrote some stuff right I did I
forgot get uh I forgot to to write the
final entry I want to read what what G
wrote Oh I'll I'll give you my last
diary entry are you going to write it no
I'll just say it out loud okay say it oh
yeah I'll hard we were not
overprepared yeah seems like it that's
about the extent of my my time today it
was fun the dragon bit back yeah it
wasn't the dragon it was the end
I'm glad I'm glad it was a
challenge
yeah it's like we did it for the first
time because it seemed like we had no
idea what we were
doing I
forgot okay let me let me then check
good Ena do you want to give a vocal
diary entry for us uh I would like to
say this isai wasn't that bad had a lot
of fun thank you k for putting a lot of
work but behind the scenes I put too
much together it was so unnecessary to
make so many things I know but it was
fun it we fun yeah indeed yeah indeed
thank you thank you for thank you
everyone for you know the fun times yeah
I love it thanks for the reliability
know for building the
base when we end I kind of broke no no
no somebody needs to be brave enough to
do it and it was you exactly okay all
right uh should I read it out loud what
G wrote what yeah okay she wrote like
she wrote wait she wrote two entries for
today it seems wait we go back in oh you
want to read it read it mean like you're
reading it out loud yeah face okay I'll
read it then cuz I've been reading your
other entries
too okay H uh day five tonight we fight
tonight the Ender Dragon Falls tonight
the new Champions will will rain tonight
the spoils will be ours tonight we will
rise TBC tonight well is this a song is
a
chant say it right you didn't say it
right okay say it right say it right no
I was trying to make good voice but I
can't do good voice if it's more like
dramatic like tonight we fight tonight
the end of dragon Falls tonight the new
it's in capsw you say white
yeah forgive me goo forgive me it's okay
the next one I'll read better okay day
six no Elden ring Dragon thing yet but
the server is oh this is not as dramatic
as I thought it would be now wow while
reading the message is not dramatic no
Elden ring Dragon thing yet what does
that mean
eldering fight the Elder oh this was
four okay Dragon
no but the server is haunted it passed a
message to me
message I couldn't
spooky
spy well now I need a a a a vocal ending
uh entry please
goba the
end true beautiful
true beautiful M thank you okay then I
have one more from
Amy I shall see I prematured might the
end then I saw him riding a few times
today oh oh a I cannot even
that sorry I was pouring my tea for this
great moment I thought a left like a
peee
noise I did guys I think stain I have a
hunch might be wrong but I think I'm
right I think I'm a love
Smith
y loves she just wrote a million hearts
into the diary and wrote Love myth myth
love love am those manually
too that takes a lot of
work okay this one gets an a am an a for
am and a for I
passed this is passing with flying graay
yeah thank you for writing the
Diaries and that's it that was myth one
block Minecraft the series the season
and the season finale we all had a blast
at the end of dragon has been also
blasted um I also got
blasted yeah we all got blasted wooo
stat is wait what blast we had a blast
and we were blasted butt right oh nice
yeah thank you for watching and thank
you everyone everybody
what
byee bye everyone bye
[Music]