make me underneath the St like come Al
life move my feet to something new I
don't need no drinks tonight
baby meet me underneath the stra light
come alive move my Fe to something new I
don't need no drinks tonight
baby maybe underneath the St like come
Al life move my feet to something new I
don't need no drinks tonight
baby May me underneath the stra like
come light move my feet to something new
I don't need no drinks tonight
baby meet me underneath the St like come
light move my feet to something new I
don't need no drinks tonight
baby May me underneath the stra like
comea
move my feet to something new I don't
need no drinks tonight
baby meet me underneath the St like come
Al life move my feet to something new I
don't need no drinks toight
baby meet me underneath the St like come
light move my feet to something new I
don't need no drinks tonight baby
make me underneath the St like come
light move my feet to something new I
don't need no drinks tonight
baby make me underneath the St like come
Al light move my feet to something new I
don't need no drinks tonight
baby May underneath the St like come Al
life move my feet to something new I
don't need no drinks tonight
baby me me underneath the stra like
come move myet to something new I don't
need
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah e
[Music]
oh
honey is
[Music]
it
me
intoxicating DJ keep playing
l
dancing so emotion
[Music]
all feel it R through me
your
feel it R
me feel it me
[Music]
ah oh wait my mic was on that
means maybe you heard me making noises
to my
cats
K uh
hello did you hear me make noises
starting
to you didn't hear anything not really
oh okay
okay K I'm going to do a
tweet starting
now
action uh
no more attention please now is action
please clap yay look at my cute stuff
blue made it thank you blue oh my god
look it says kiata
film that's
kfp kiata Film Production let me film
you guys
M oh oh
oh what no I'm not filming a closeup of
your fluffy butt what do you mean no I'm
no I'm I'm I'm just filming your face
not your fluffy
butt H not all not at
all o oh yeah oh yeah yeah oh oh you
dropped something maybe check the
floor oh yeah that's it that's the good
stuff yeah no it's like behind you yeah
turn around and and try to pick up
whatever is on the
floor cute fluffy
butt I want to squeeze it it's almost
like I can squeeze it ah what you want
to check oh you don't have to check just
trust me I'm the
director no no no no
we are going to um play a game today
that I have been interested in for a
while um actually let me put up the logo
on the screen
[Music]
too might as well where did it go though
where did I save
it New Meme
template Oh you mean you mean like
cutting um this out me should I make it
like
should I put myself on the gray screen
or so this logo
[Music]
is so
long it's cute isn't
it thank you blue for putting this
together I was surprised I didn't expect
it is this like the like a normal size
like compared to me cuz the thing behind
me is a chair maybe the chair is a
little bit too too big actually and
normally they're like really low down
here it's like sad if you can't see
it but then the camera how big are these
cameras like are they the size of a
head a person's
head where where should I put it anyway
like right in front of me is like a
little bit like maybe here but I don't
want to cover the hand Maybe here's good
they're pretty damn big much bigger okay
then this will just be a small version
because if I make it too big it's going
to take up a lot like what like
this what that's
crazy now this is a small small version
for smaller
films H so I don't know if you guys
heard about this game well I have been
advertising it so you probably heard
about it from me at least Blockbuster
ink now
I I want you to remind yourself
depending on your age if you're too
young then you will not REM remember
this but there's a game that's called
the
movies from H the movies how many years
ago I oh every side is your good side
but there's one special side that I like
the most about you turn around now turn
around nice a good good good stuff
[Music]
aluda thanks for the red super chat H
the movies game
from 2005 holy
sh
that's that's 19 years
ago what no no way math is my math
accurate there's no [\h__\h] way that
that's 19 years ago no
no that means that I'm at least 19 years
old the f I mean that's not true no no
not necessarily just because you know
something that's old like you know
Mozart or whatever doesn't mean that you
were alive at the time although I was
alive when moart was alive of course as
I have told you before
um I am timeless
oof o
19 what
the 19 years
ago but then I think though I genuinely
I I did not play it when it came out I I
was I think a little bit too
young I I think I only got to know this
game a little bit
afterwards okay I mean it I'm serious I
don't think I played it right away when
it was out
but anyway that game the movies is quite
a treasure and it's abandoned wear and I
I've talked about it before and I was
like oh I want to play this I wish I
could play it but it's a band andwar and
then like some game company makes um a
spiritual successor for it which is
amazing that's exactly what I need oh my
god um like literally they say they say
they make it very clear that it's
inspired by
uh the movies so there's nothing really
to be ashamed
of um as long as you're honest about it
you know and and it's like a a positive
you know thing to revive something that
has been abandoned especially for
someone like me you know I can't really
it's like a little bit difficult and uh
grade Zone uh streaming abandoned wear
um in whole life maybe if you were a
normal streamer then it wouldn't matter
but for me it kind of matters
so what choice do I have but to wait for
companies who want to rescue like a
treasured classic of
games yeah they literally made it for
me they made this for
me sure now I have only watched uh one
or two trailers so I'm
curious how this is going to go
I'm starting it up
now ah yeah so my froat uh the last
night definitely improved it when I woke
up uh uh swallowing wasn't as bad
anymore I was uh way
more bearable but I still went to the
doctor because my ear was still clogged
um still hurts a little bit to swallow
but not as bad as before where even
eating was painful and everything um
it's
Parable yeah unclogged I went to the
doctor and I just yeah I mentioned hello
suan my ear is clogged and then he was
like okay what do you want to do do you
want me to vacuum it or do you want me
to uh shower it and I'm like EV way evil
one you want last time you did both and
then he looks at it like first he
showers it and then he realizes okay
showering it alone is not going to do
the trick this ear is really [\h__\h]
clogged up all the way to the brim and
I'm
like yeah okay feel free you know do
what you need to do so he did like
everything
um but man I it's been a long time since
I last did that I forgot
how how much I don't like
it like the water the water the water is
like like there's like so much water
going in and out and who oh wait my
screen just went black that took a long
time to load the game ah wait I'm
tanging right now um yeah uh it's it's
like the vacuuming and the watering it's
it's not painless I would say it's like
kind of weird
the one of those things I think was it
the vacuuming it gave me like a no it
must have been the water actually it was
kind of loud in my ear and pretty strong
force
so it was like really overwhelming and
felt like uh I had like a beep teeny
tiny tus teeny tiny tus in my ear for a
moment after that and then I I kind of
felt like sick a little bit and
like because I don't know somehow this
kind of stuff feels
overwhelming and uncomfortable yeah
feeling some stuff deep in your ear
it's just not not a good feeling
right
yeah
um and then he was curious even though I
said my throat is pretty much fine so no
need to really look at it he still took
a look and he was like
oh and he found some things in my
throat um and yeah found some things
wanted to give me
antibiotica
because seemingly a virus and some like
weird things in my throat
um the
shef uh no inflammation but also like
what do you call
it uh
a a uh can canker Source maybe uh like
in the throat inside um and stuff so no
wonder that swallowing was painful for
me what the
[\h__\h] um
yeah sounds like a
dinosaur but then I was like oh that's
funny that you say I have that because
haha
on my fingers fingertips right now I
also have some like tiny tiny little
bumps and like bubble thingies that I
talked about in my member stream
yesterday and then he got really like
his ears were like oh he yo what did you
just say show me show me and I'm like oh
I didn't think you would care about my
fingers um I was just like mentioning it
as a side comment um and then he got
really curious and he was thinking that
it could have
a connection there's like a certain
thing that if I have it but he wasn't
sure but he was like if I have it that
could be connected but he wasn't sure
and I was like no I don't know I don't
know it's it's fine probably it's all
connected
[Music]
W nah I don't even think it is what it
is there were like two doctors one
doctor was kind of like behind him and
like commenting on things and
like uh seemingly like learning from him
but he didn't seem unexperienced he
seemed very experienced and he did
Lima and he did say that he thinks the
thing on my finger is the thing that I
thought it was the this
hydrosis on my fingers but then the
other doctor said no I don't think so
but I think so I agree with the back
seating doctor
yeah when it comes to my fingers um my
throat I don't I don't know but yeah I
said no thank you to the meds cuz I told
him it's already so much
better uh I'm already almost healed I
think uh so he was like okay if you feel
that way then yeah if it gets worse then
come back but yeah really it got much
better yeah you were I I think you were
right I mean there's no like 100%
confirmation but I agree and that other
doctor brought it up too
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah so that's
what's going on I'm I'm I'm fine I'm
fine and oh for for the people who were
rating on Polaroids if you didn't see uh
on the community board I put up uh like
Polaroids I signed them before I went to
the doctor Rainer one there was one of
yours zipley one of yours lunchbox one
of yours I think the satify did one of
yours Z Dax Jaden yeah yeah yeah yeah
Sai one of yours you see I even remember
which ones I signed for for one of yours
yeah so check it out offer yes yours too
logical par yeah you got them you got
them nice nice nice they're up on the
community board the I I even wrote uh
the F the numbers on hyzer which ones I
did so you could even check hyzer before
downloading the whole thing you can just
check on
hyzer um if you know how to use it to
see if you're included or I guess I
guess you don't have that to do that
right because if if you open the G Giga
file link it shows all the
names you don't have to download the
whole folder
right do you do you I'm not sure anymore
do you do you you say ah you can
download them individually
okay okay yeah okay that makes
[Music]
sense yeah I'll do the rest soon it
didn't even take me that long to do the
106 didn't take me very
long so I think I can do the rest
soon but probably next week
honestly because I'm not at home for
most of the week
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah can I buy one
still oh you couldn't back
then yeah I'll open it up again cuz
you're not the only one asking funny how
it's two two Australians
asking uh I'll open it up again U maybe
next
week but feel free to remind me because
I might
forget okay okay okay okay okay now
[Music]
let's get into this this looks like Sims
doesn't it like the menu design is 100%
Sims I mean they're taking like game
play inspiration from uh
from the movies but like the the UI is
100% Sims let me make this
fit the
screen and that's what I actually really
like I like this UI I like the Sims
style
UI okay I tab in and there's loud
[Music]
bgm I I'll change it in a moment what oh
okay what is this WOW as a small team of
free core members we are doing our very
best to deliver a pleasant experience
Blockbuster ink we are aware that there
will be things to fix and
cont y I did that I supported a small
team it's kind of small to read is
it can we make the fonts bigger
actually UI
[Music]
scale oh
oh I made it bigger cool
do I want window I I guess this is okay
for now cinematic let's do
cinematic
[Music]
yeah what else Master
lower okay cool do you want it to be
even bigger guys I don't know if I
should make it even bigger
[Music]
this is simps menu I
know like the light blue and the dark
blue and the the white oh my
God here have about like this this
should be
good okay I'm excited I hope it's going
to be
good Studio name wow Ki what was it ki's
film kiata or Ki
ki's is it Ki was what do it say behind
me Film Production just going to call it
Kata Film Production okay sick choose
difficulty easy
start I want to I want to do easy so
that with more
money we can make nicer movies maybe
right away oh we can choose a decade we
have the 20s the 30s the 40s the 50s the
60s the 70s 80s the 90s the th000 I
2,000 I don't know and the 2010s is go I
don't think you're able to choose a
decade to play
in in the
movies
what I guess depending on the decade
different kind of I don't know different
genres might be more
popular and also I guess there would be
like black and white movies or still
maybe when did they start adding voices
to movies that was that before the 1920s
or after sorry if that sounds like a
stupid
question that you think I should
know oh after so possibly in the in the
1920s the movies that we would be making
would have no voice and just like
subtitles interesting but I do want I
think I do want voice maybe like
50s could be
interesting and then two starting genres
and
themes uh we have romance and action
activated right
now ooh I don't know maybe maybe mystery
because this just you guys see that and
I think of
am
I'm neurons activated and then oh
medieval okay medieval and pirate it is
because we can do an aoy movie I don't
know in medieval just because of my
personal
preference okay would you like to play
the tutorial yes teach me
please okay what is this going to be
like
w like the fact that there's like a gate
here and then we build like our building
St this is exactly like in the
movies welcome to Blockbuster Inc let's
go over the basic controls needed to
play click the continue button
below exit the tutorial at anytime press
Escape or Cho and choose exit tutorial
move the mouse while holding down the
middle Mouse button to rotate the view
woohoo move the mouse while holding the
right Mouse button to pan the view or
WD scroll the mouse to zoom in and
out that's the most essential
information is always visible in the
main view let's go over some of
it this section shows your current funds
released products I guess movies Studio
fans and employee
count this number shows your current
ranking amongst other Studios the St the
Stars indicate the studio Prestige okay
right now we have no star
but and six is like I guess the lowest
are like sixth out of six we'll describe
all these stats and depth in the
subsequent
tutorials this section shows the in-game
date and time note that one dat corresp
corresponds the uh to one month I can't
read click this button to pause unpause
the game time you can also use the space
bar mhm click this button to change the
game speed you can also use one to three
M
nice okay play next tutorial build
mode let's begin by going into build
mode click this button or press tab wow
I will not remember to press tab ever
select the wall rectangle tool okay oh
we can build our own buildings like this
like in Sims because I think
originally they were only set buildings
there was not this much
customization okay so we're going to we
want to create a room perhaps like right
away we we need to think of like you
know a
good how to
say you know hey what just happened the
room was too small you want a bigger one
five five I don't know oh that's six by
seven uhhuh
infrastructure layout Yeah Yeah Yeah
Yeah from indoors doors choose any door
uh and added to the room indoors doors o
what for
real well we kind of need like a like a
entrance looking door I don't know maybe
this doesn't really does it look like an
entrance looking
[Music]
door I don't know
sure uh let's turn this room into
producers oh a producer's office then I
should have maybe made it bigger damn it
this is my office after
all maybe maybe we got more than one
producer and then we can have several
offices for them uh objects producer
office
objects
oh okay so there's specific items for
the producer and for the rider and Canen
Etc
visual design office audio design
marketing stunt
[Music]
facility oh there's like a [\h__\h] ton of
money on that desk already now wait I
wanted to turn it kind of can I can I
not turn
it surely you can turn
it how would you turn
it oh well I don't know how
so for
now it will just be like this do do I
need all of these
things cabinet small cabinet big notice
board I'll just put this here do I need
all of
this well oh maybe I did need all of
that press simple press
r no R is not it but that's okay
okay good job let's make a Rider's
office too select the wall rectangle
tool again uh they probably want another
5x five we'll just make it like kind of
the
same or like 6X
six and then another
door and see like this is a path in
between and some in case somebody wants
to walk through pathing is very
important in the filming industry
uh objects Rider
office okay not much money on the rider
office desk what a
contrast oh but they got a little cute
green
plant isn't that
nice there we
go we will need a maintenance room too
but we'll use a pre-made room this time
ah so there are pre pre-made rooms from
indoors pre-made rooms choose
maintenance and place it on the lot
M
ahuh where this one
okay maintenance where should we put
this one H
maybe I feel like what I used to do in
the movies is like try to make one part
like the the offices and stuff and then
like the other side would be all the
movie sets and stuff you
know so maintenance however
[Music]
maintenance could be an in between thing
but still I guess I'll put
it uh here so it's not too far from
everything CU I
think the maintenance workers they will
have to go back and forth back and forth
uh when fixing something as far as I I
mean that's I think how it was in the
movies so you don't want them to have to
go too
far I'm liking this already this is like
so far it's like like back in the
day let's add a canteen too um from a
pre-made room okay ski toilet speaking
of ski I was so confused I was going for
Steam to buy this game today and I saw
you know that game only
up it has a multiplayer version or so
now and it's called only up
skibby
what
why
why why would you call it
that
like what
what what are they trying to be like
funny or what okay canteen you know what
um we're going
to I have like this awkward space
here uh let's put it like here in the
middle and it will be like the end of
this like path or so but wait ah the
door is like ah the door is only there
can I
turn there has to be a way to turn this
teach me game teach me how to turn this
maybe oh wa I'm lagging is this when I'm
choosing a a a a thing is that making oh
oh oh the moment I put it like in here
it makes me
lag what was that with the other rooms
too like when I'm in here it doesn't lag
but when I put it here it lag oh oh wait
oh yeah yeah it lags and it stops
lagging interesting it's okay okay M I
can't decide I want to put it
nicely and I don't know how to turn
it
uh at least it's not lagging when I'm
normally just in here okay canteen right
what what does it say what's that smell
I thought it said imagine the smell
delicious food served so everyone is
happy and energized for their daily
tasks I really don't want to put it here
that's an awkward space c ah thank
[Music]
you I can I not make it can I add okay
okay okay okay sorry sorry can I add
doors to pre-made
rooms no can I make my own
canteen surely I can right yes I
can okay it might look like [\h__\h] but I
want to make my own
but ah they want me to use a it does it
have to be premade
room I can't I don't think I can make my
own right now they're forcing me to use
a pre-made one
no how dare you and I can't squeeze it
in here ah gyy tiny night I it's just
just like so close to
fitting ah that pisses me off
oh okay oh
man I hope you're happy now I hope
you're happy for ruining
everything can I don't I don't think or
maybe we can move the fence later if I
buy more space cuz this looks like it
only ends
here but for now it ends
here certain room types room
types EEG the launch are currently
locked you can unlock them for research
see relevant tutorial
M the Clone tool I don't want to clone
these oh we want another producer's
office oh
Okay click on a free space to place to
copy part ah now you're telling me how
to rotate and you're you're making it
seem like you already told
me the spacing
ah okay I'll put it across from the
other one so that they can look at each
other and be like e how many pages have
you written today
huh F freaking finish Game of Thrones
already Fire and Ice
death and life
now okay uh now for the fun of it let's
turn this room into a toilet what
skiy click on all the objects inside the
copy room and delete them but not the
walls or
doors but the other producer was
supposed to sit in front of the other
but now you're making it into a [\h__\h]
toilet that's not what my plan was
no
no they're forcing me to put the toilet
across the producer they didn't tell me
that that was the
plan M M M
M oh no Skiby look at that shitty ass
toilet I wonder if the toilets are
different depending on the time as well
cuz that kind of
toilet I
mean that does seem like an old ass
toilet you will bully a pebble okay
Skiby
ski
Skiby Skiby ski
Skiby
ah
no stop it tutorial let me fix that it's
supposed to go
sideways no the tutorial won't let me do
it
what do you want choose any set and
place it in a lot oo
sets Set set set sets sets sets
[Music]
sets which one there's an default alien
set cyber Punk set fantasy set gangster
set Heist set medical set medieval set
military set pirate why is this one is
that a
bug oh yeah police set
postapocalyptic set space set slasher
set what the [\h__\h] is a slasher set
sounds like a horror movie kind of thing
Sports set superhero set vampire set
Western set zombie sets
[Music]
set they don't have like an office like
the the whole life office do they
doesn't seem like it no basic like
office set what if I want to film the
office but in whole lifestyle or the
other way around whole life but in the
office
style maybe maybe the gangster set would
be suitable I don't know or the high no
no okay it's going to be scrubs but the
office H scrubs but whole life
um okay uh but do we want everything so
close to the entrance probably
not let's start putting
things
here let's confirm our changes in exit
build mode to click the confirm button
but what about the skimy toilet it's
wrong Mama M are you forcing me
really f
f
h okay
employees oh wait did I not have to
think too deeply about any of that was
that not going to be what I'm working
with oh Mama
Mia I knew it was a tutorial I thought I
would keep the things I'm
making H okay
time to hire some employees click the
hire button okay do we have someone
famous here you can hire various types
of employees you can unlock more types
by performing research see relevant
tutorials start by hiring an actor
no um you want me to hire Randolf
Molina I don't know if that's a smart
choice I don't see much of a future in
him but you're forcing me to do that so
it's
okay uh the window that appears on the
left shows info on your new employee
let's have a quick look at it okay Rand
Molina 27 he's a
[Music]
nobody we can educate train or fire them
but he starts working tomorrow he's got
some skills athletic and Charisma he
gets 2,500 from me daily I guess
that's kind of crazy if that's
daily uh he's
happy he's been working since 1920 wait
wait well we're in the 1920s what the
[\h__\h] I chose 1950s but I guess it's just
for the
tutorial no housing requirement for this
employee but they do have a few things
to fulfill hunger social bladder
sleep reach Fame level two reward
n okay oh wait I already looked for all
of that thank
you yeah yeah I did it on my own thank
you
oopsie here you can
[Music]
see mhm mhm mhm low needs are shown as a
pop-up icon over the
employees let's continue hiring
employees hire a producer Christina pots
oh
okay producers need to be assigned to a
producer office to work if you have
already built one when you hire them
they will be Auto assigned to it mhm
let's verify that the new producer was
assigned click on the produce production
office in the employee slots info you
should see the new producer when in
build mode you can modify the assigned
employees uh okay switch to build mode
[Music]
ah let's move on okay hire a rider they
will be assigned to a rider office okay
hire director
okay hire crew person okay hire
maintenance worker okay finally hire a
staff you get a job and you get a job
and you get a job and you get a job
finally hire a staff worker for the Cen
censes and linges need the staff record
to be functional realistic
okay and hire Oh that's oh kandra magia
is the only one not getting a
job like I literally gave everybody a
job except for her poor poor girl she's
what a scientist or what a
researcher sorry Kendra it was just
first come first serve as any other
company normally treats their hiring
process right
mhm in this window you can view the
employees currently working for you can
filter by type uh using this drop down
button not a
hotel this section shows name age
happiness and salary of each
employee uh this section contains
available actions for this employee such
as fire the employee or negotiate their
salary
oh this image shows a photo and a type
icon of the employee you can hover hover
your mouse over the the type icon to see
the type's
name click the photo to Quick select
this employee you can also select an
employee by clicking on them directly
but this method allows selecting apps
and employees as well
uh-huh if this employee is currently
away from the studio a car icon will be
displayed over their photo also if the
employee is in education or
training uh such icon will be shown over
the
photo
n okay next tutorial please
cut or it's raining we'll need to set up
our daily schedule click the schedule
button
[Music]
oo what did I miss a few tutorials but
we're still in a tutorial so don't
worry in this window you can Define the
activities done per hour of the day you
can also choose the quality of the food
served in the Cen oh
High food quality is unlockable for
research let's assign the working hours
click the work
button click on at least 8 Hour slots to
turn them into work slots but wait for
whom for
who during work hours all filming and
productive work takes place uh so
everything however too many work hours
will make your employees exhausted and
unhappy What if I
if I put my work hours between like
midnight and 8:00 a.m. my whole
production studio will be working for
the
night that's uh weird that I am able to
do
that [\h__\h] fly get out of
here let set to leave hours during these
your employees return home and replenish
all their needs click the leave
button
aha probably something like this if you
have a staffed Cen your employees will
visit it during 8 hours to replenish
their hunger without having to return
home uh should that be after
work
okay set at least 1 hour of eating and
why not in in
between don't you want to have lunch
sometime in between but okay finally if
you have a staff Lounge employees will
visit it during ler
hours oh during them your employees can
hang out and restore their social need
ahuh employees will also randomly chat
with each other regardless of schedule
those little shits get back to work
which restores their social needs
slightly this usually increases their
relationship as well but not always some
people just don't get along
okay cool product
creation let's dive into the basics of
making a product click the product
creation
button here we'll need to set up all the
product details the first thing to
decide is the name or you can have a
random one picked for
you next you have various sub menus with
options the script writing menu will be
initially
selected eh
uhhuh click the product type and S it to
movie I can make TV shows
too for product size choose low this
affects the production cost and the
expected hype and
profits okay ooh
Blockbuster choose a genre the selected
genre affects the audience ages and the
ideal genre slider
values adventure for
now choose a theme your product will
turn out better if you use a filming set
that matches the selected
theme yeah makes
sense choose an age Focus this should be
appropriate for the selected
genre oh oh oh spicy
movies click on the producer field and
choose your current
producer Adele
Russell a director and the riter
you should also customize the V various
genre Sliders in a way that fits the
choosen genre but let's leave them as is
for now okay cool you should now see a
green check mark in the script writing
button this means that its required
details have been completed all the sub
menus must be checked in order to create
the product click the actors
button ooh sign sign the actor
Okay click the scenes and sets
button uh plan the scenes and set on
which they will be filmed we'll only
have one scene for this product click
choose set and select your set avoid
using the same set often it decreases
its
novelty oh no you can see the starting
expenses and expected hype for this
product in this
section uh okay okay
uh we're investing 50,000 but we also
think we'll get 50,000 or
what what what is this just our
investment so there's no uh no no like
thought of how much we might get from it
yet click the create product button to
finalize the product if there are any
issues you will see IR relevant warning
okay my employees will arrive soon you
can speed up the time until then okay o
here we
go all right we get to cooking literally
you get to cooking
your producers and writers should now
head into their offices and begin
working on the script wait until they're
done ah there there we are okay moving
on to filming oh my God oh my God your
director actors s crew should head to
the filming set and film The needed
scenes wait until they're done okay
no okay okay ooh pretty dress we're
filming Game of Thrones now but with a
really low budget the cheapest Game of
Thrones ever literally in a box with
scraps yeah talking to
nobody yeah that's because we're filming
it in Harin Hall which're is talking to
our dreams and
imaginations game of lawn chairs game of
chairs
uh okay ah ah there's like 50% progress
not at all
a but wasn't weren't we able in the
movies to like more in a more detailed
way uh plan out the
film with like actions and stuff maybe
we'll still get to do that maybe this is
like the the automatic way I don't know
thanks for the membership
[Music]
come okay they're
finished oh scene rating 37 you now have
the minimum needed scene takes let's see
how we did click the info button on the
progress
widget here you can see the total scenes
needed and the overall shooting rating
uh you can
also
okay so that's pretty bad but I mean
what are we going to
do
37% oh the first takes are usually not
the best so it's a good idea to do more
takes click the reshoot we are
re-shooting it okay better get better
from now on wait for the new T to
completed you can speed up the time
until then
okay impress me or else you're
fired come
on filming while the story is being
written no it was finished no if the
latest takes rating was better it will
be reflected on the scene's rating if
not the scene rating will stay the same
ah it did get
better finish filming okay okay your
movie is ready to be released click the
release product button releasing
tomorrow woohoo your new movie Set is
for release tomorrow is movie is set
let's wait and see how it goes you can
speed up the time until then or press
continue to skip the wait lot Rico times
the thrilling
Savage oh oh we're getting good comments
one of the year's most anticipated
titles turned out to be a complete let
down
very few good things can be said about
the thrilling Savage I love I love these
comments already and you have to search
a lot to find
them even with Kristen new man being
given such a fitting role executed
masterfully The Filling sage just can't
stir the audience's excitement
completely boring and
predictable if you want a good idea to
fail just hire Carol Perry she'll turn
any gem into pure coal oh that
hurts good for sumon nightes when
literally nothing else is going on thank
you so much [\h__\h] media of Los Ros
where the [\h__\h] is that never heard of it
I don't
care oh wait do I have to click
this you can view more detailed analysis
of your prodct score
only the last one it contains a
breakdown of the factors that determined
the result score you can click each
scene in product seemes to see its own
influence to the
result screenplay was good I guess
because it took up the most of the score
to together with
relationships technical was [\h__\h]
non-existent oh we don't even use okay
no microphones maybe because we don't
don't have voicing in the
movie it was highly anticipated probably
because it's basically the first movie
to be ever created in the world in this
world of course it's
anticipated but then they shouldn't be
so disappointed man it's the first movie
you got to be like who [\h__\h] this is
amazing this like magic how am I even
able to watch something that has been
recorded in the past it's like I time
travel production Time 1 month ooh I
lost 50,000 no no okay no I just but
yeah wait where's my income from the
[Music]
movie ah oh
oh 21,000 is profit which means already
deducted what I uh spent
right but that's not bad that's
good let's
go
uh click this button to see a list of
your products ah yeah okay I see it
mhm information sheet uhhuh the windows
overlapping this sheet displ various
information on your product you can also
use these buttons to watch the product
or view its reviews and score breakdowns
done yeah I don't want to see those
again why you got to traumatize me like
that
ah okay direct scenes and watch products
okay I think now we're getting maybe
more
detailed when creating a product you can
customize each scene to your
liking let's try that click on product
creation all righty all righty now we're
getting into it go to the scenes and
sets tab
direct
scene Christy Branch here you can
preview the scene you can navigate the
view in the same way as the normal game
view try panning The View oh oh cool
click this button to reset the view
after moving it
oh left click and hold on the actor in
the Freddy view to begin moving
them ah okay I have to wait a little
bit cancel placement Place rotate
oh hold on this section shows the
products actors that are currently in
the scene click an actor's photo to
remove them from the
scene oh no come back you're the only
one I
have let's explore more options go to
the animations tab oh here you can see
available animations first click on an
actor in the 3D view to select them then
click on an animation what do you mean
an animation oh you you mean like the
movement
ah oh yeah let's go boxing
uppercut oh Z many many zombie things
military
gangster
Western superhero
twirl superhero air Kake superhero
fly how is she doing that that's an
amazing actor how is she flying like
that what literally
how
bro walk walk for me walk for me
lady vampire
sleeping
nice
drunk pushups
planning on tables map oh yeah we're
getting game of throny
yeah I like
it kissing hand what are you doing oh
wait ah ooh booty
what getting kissed in the hand okay we
got both
sides mythology magic mythology Magic
hiya let's go
myth oh I'm disappointed I thought she
would be floating with that
one oh there's so
much there is so much okay okay okay we
got a good amount of choices maybe maybe
we'll get
more okay costumes as
well I Wonder okay this can be M Senpai
this can be subu
Senpai uh this I don't know could be Ci
or
Amy or this could be
Amy wait this could be
cell w we need more we need more
costumes later hopefully we'll get
more ooh special effects to use these
effects you must have installed to
relevant equipment on your filming set
options that are not installed will
appear right out okay
o rain fog and fire ooh the fog is
nice
see okay yeah I I clicked
it now oh now I have okay now I'm back
to fog okay oh the quality is so bad
let's
go I'm curious will it actually look
much better in the later years like
2010 while you're in this tab the
preview on the left will change the uh
to show the camera
perspective
ooh it's going to get complicated a
little
bit we're going to get so deep into it
maybe and zoom in this section lets you
C customize various parameters of the
camera movement they are different
depending on the option you've chosen
play around with them yeah o linger time
motion speed motion mention camera zoom
Focus height
Ooh shake amount
oh oh Shake speed
oh I'm the
cameraman hand to each actor oh
oh ah and then it resets but we can do
like a a shake shake shake shake shake
wow
nice
nice changes are all safe so you can
close this window oh this check mark
shows that you have customized the scene
scenes are left with the default options
uh mhm curious to see the result of your
work click the create product button
now we wait until filming completes you
can speed up the time until then oh you
guys are actually going to film what I
just made all
right cameraman a bit jittery no it's
like on
purpose it's for the drama
baby okay they're riding the
screenplay oh orc oh yeah we left her on
orc let's
go a meditating
orc with the shakiness and the fog I
feel like it it made it look like she is
making the fog
happen better do a good job on that one
I put a lot of F into it 37 reshoot no
they won't let
me are you seven is [\h__\h]
okay let's watch it my company presents
the heroic
bite staring chissy Branch
starring wa totally unrelated to the
movie title let's
go
awesome stunts and doctors where's the
bite I know
right and depending on the genres of
products that you choose to film you
will often need to film stunt scenes in
addition addition to normal scenes let's
prepare for this click the hire
button uh we're hiring a
stuntman also hire a
doctor
foreshadowing click on product
creation scenes and sets direct the
scene for stunt scenes you go to choose
what kind of stunt you want to perform
click the stunt tab oh there's even more
cool stuff
here oh
each stunt has a specific number of
involved persons and specific chance of
injury let's keep the default Choice
what what do you mean chance of injury
stunt men are not supposed to get
hurt that's why I'm hiring a
stuntman you're not doing your job right
the
[\h__\h] yeah there's no need for stunt men
when my actors already can fly too oh
but they do
about
that I guess they're just like more open
to getting her but like I mean don't I
would assume that they train to do these
stunts and they're more um like
experienced with it so they don't get
hurt because they know how to do it
that's why we hire a stunt
man like they probably have more skills
like athletically and all that
right so okay accidents still happen
makes
sense yeah H yeah of course they there's
a chance yeah here you can choose which
of the products actors will participate
in the stunt
okay you just want one using your actess
character let's use our stuntman instead
remove your ah okay
Kristen uh
Kristen Kristen will be getting hurt for
me how nice of
her okay but this time I didn't really
plan
anything they just doing it
automatically all right what stunt are
we
doing okay she just fell
down going to do that
again wait that's exactly like the in
football what we watched with the
football guy he like slid way further
than you did maybe we should hire the
football
[Music]
guy
38 wow oh she has sustained an injury
they will be unable to work until
February 1920
that's that's funny because one day is
one month they told us but that's funny
because here it just says the time but
no
day
okay
okay the stand was filmed but the stman
was injured good news is that you have a
doctor
okay the doctor will tend to the injured
employees daily and speed up their
recovery process let me
see this this could also be a movie set
honestly
okay equipment to
next mhm except for the most basic
equipment all other equipment has to be
unlocked in
research I'm like reading so much script
I need a fro candy
it's
painful especially when my throat is not
100% back
yet let me take a fro
candy
okay yap yap
yap go ahead and unlock the first camera
upgrade
oh cool oh my God right that's so cool
wa took the M
there
oh oh
oh that reminds me of something do you
want to hear a tangent a camera
tangent actually a a laden
tangent want to hear
one yeah oh damn I thought you would say
no yeah so I was at raden's place right
I visited her and we did the off collab
a few days ago like last week I think
actually and um she's not only into art
but as you guys told me she's also into
photography um but we didn't get to talk
about that at all during the stream
however after the stream like you know
she was like excitedly showing me all
kinds of things in her home like I was
looking through some some books from
Museum and stuff that she had
um and stuff like that and then one
thing she uh shows me I think I found it
myself and was curious about it I don't
know but she shows me her
camera an old really really old German
camera like a like a old classic camera
where where uh you have to develop the
pictures
M like a vintage camera
yeah and she's like really proudly
showing it off and I'm like oh this is
like pretty cool and then oh yeah she
like showed me how to use it and first I
didn't really see properly through cuz I
didn't know like you know when your eyes
are focusing on the wrong thing but only
when you start focusing on the right
thing you suddenly see something that
you didn't see
before basically there's like a mirror
or something like that inside and you
look into it and then you see what's in
front of you and it looked beautiful
like even though it's such an old camera
like it looked really really amazing and
she showed me some pictures that she
took with it that she actually also
showed her viewers before apparently and
it's just like really really pretty
really nice pictures nice sense for
that and then I noticed the thing on the
back of the camera because it's a German
camera uh I find something that she
never really understood
and she didn't even know what language
it was there's like this whole ass
huge like
explanation of all kinds of settings
that you could do but all of it in
German so it says like all kinds of
different situations like taking a
picture of one person in the bright or
in the dark and then if it's two people
or if it's group of people um if it's
outside if it's under the sun if it's
under a tree if it's uh whatever you
know like a lot of different things and
then the fitting um settings for it she
didn't know what any of that meant
before and it's like literally written
on the camera so I read it out for her
and I translate every single thing and
she was like really fascinated and and
grateful that I was able to translate
those things for her
making uh the whole thing even more
useful yeah like shutter speed and all
that kind of
stuff
yeah maybe she'll bring the camera to
Austria when she visits
me do not remove from Museum no no no no
no no no
no no no no no no she didn't steal
anything nah now no no
no so cool like her camera looks really
nice maybe she can take good pictures
like with phones too like she could take
some cute pictures of me you
[Laughter]
know got to test it out if she has a
sense for that too all right
upgrade feel free to unlock any of the
other options if you want when ready
close the research window
let's see how we can use the upgrade
that we have unlocked click the build
mode
button click on the existing film set to
open the set info
window in this window you can see the
sets size and theme the scenes of your
product get a quality bonus if the
product's theme is the same as the
filming set theme uhhuh makes
sense you can also say see the sets
Prestige and Novelty
the bottom section shows the equipment
installed on the set click on the camera
slot and upgrade to a better camera oh
oh looks like the one I
have it's my
camera Instagram boyfriend Ren
exactly adding or upgrading equipment
comes with an expense while removing or
downgrading equipment yields a refund
also note that you cannot change a set's
equipment while filming is taking place
on it upgrading set equipment boosts the
quality of the film scenes and specific
types of equipment provide other bonuses
as well for example cameras provide
better visuals and Firefall rain
machines unlock the respective options
in the direct scene
menu yeah
okay uh yeah okay
I think we're almost done with the
tutorials an actor of Fame level one has
just joined your studio famous actors
bring a hype boost to your products but
they also have more expectations from
you one expectation from famous actors
is that you must provide accommodation
for them so let's rent a flat for this
actor click the City View oh not in
here kind of outside
oh now I think this was not a thing
during the movie I think in the movies
they either had no place to sleep in the
thing at all or you were able to build
like accommodation uh within the
premises but not like you didn't have a
city like
this okay this is the overview of Los
Ricos and its various districts you can
hover your moue over each area to see
brief information about it okay
here you see the selected properties
District
rent this section shows the employes
current housing and rent as employees
gain Fame they'll require High who I
thought it was an airplane passing
through radio Los Ricos 95 FM
that
cry same goes for food quality
okay you can unlock higher food quality
through research explained in the later
tutorial and applied from the schedule
window
okay finally remember that only actors
producers and directors have Fame
levels okay
cool let's go finances yay I love
finances as long as it means that I'm
making
money my managing your finances is an
important part in keeping your studio
going let's see how you can keep track
of them click the number showing your
current funds to open the finances
window this section shows your income
and exp expenses
expenses for the current month grouped
into
categories
okay another
H
ston ston manual this field shows which
month's sta is currently displayed
mhm you can change between months using
the error
buttons
okay total income and
[Music]
expens I can't
breathe can you guys rate for
me ah
cool try clicking the yearly
button uh oh we can't can go to the bank
we can get a loan oh no I don't want to
get a loan no I hate
that here you can choose a loan amount
at the number of installments choose any
amount above a th000 and click take
loan
not okay
thanks money cing
cing you can't read oh no
oh no why did you not learn it for
me
depths not too bad though the loan and
installments will be paid automatically
every month until the loan is paid off
if you run out of money in the meantime
the payments will be paused until you
have enough money again I think I think
I used to use money cheats in this game
like in the OG
I think I
did I think there were money
cheats and I might have used it you can
have up to free active loans at any time
the credit limit shows the current
amount of your loans and the max amount
you can
get mhm
research research is a powerful feature
that lets you unlock all sorts of
upgrades let's check it out click the
research
button here you can see see all
currently available research note that
new research becomes available every few
years uh you'll see notification
whenever this happens okay yeah 1927 30
35 is this like this must be like real
years when these cameras were invented
and
released which is actually
fascinating you have to wait for that
particular year to get that camera it's
like you're learning some history while
you're playing the
game that's amazing here so that
actually means like it might be
interesting to indeed start from 1920
from as far back as you can just for the
sake of going through everything and
seeing the difference in quality and the
difference in technical limitations and
stuff it might be interesting to do
that
H here you can see all currently
available research note that new
research I wait I already read that yeah
the top row shows the available
categories click the genres and themes
button to see this
category each research slot costs
research points to unlock this number
shows your current RP let's see how we
can earn some
M it's like a skill
tree it it also helps to master the game
since things will be more simple yeah
yeah yeah I thought so too like the the
earlier you
start then that also means the longer
you can go because can you even go past
2010 I wonder how far you can
go but there might not be any more like
new stuff that you can get past
2010 possibly you may be able to go
further into like endless time
be
timeless but you might not get any more
cool new stuff yeah technology just
stopped developing in
2010 unless maybe there's like DLCs in
the future or so dlc's for technology
let's
go so we have a research office but we
also need researchers click the higher
[Music]
button click the schedule
button and give them a work time
can I do more than
necessary want to consider hiring
multiple researchers to work in
parallel you mean in the future not now
right oh okay for the sake of the
tutorial we have instantly gained some
research points click on any research
slot that you want and spend RP to
unlock
it oh we have to unlock the a PG
rating
what wait what how many do I
have 100 wait what can I
do this is 200 this is 400 this is
400 what do you mean unlock
it I
can't am I stupid
H
oh uh from
here yeah okay that's the only thing I
can do but we unlocked that in a
different tutorial already
lame okay
let's see how you can keep track of the
progress of various Stars products and
Studios shut up bus get noisy as [\h__\h]
Star Charts there's a chicken Craven has
a lower chance to perform well on
stunts
what why would you depict that as a
chicken that is disrespectful to kfb
this is literally the kfb movie
studio
insulting this window list acent
you
can details
button the UI is too big things are
overlapping I made it too big it's not
this big by default for stars employed
by other students you can click the
business deal to negotiate a job offer
this will be covered in a subsequent
tutorial
wooo okay you can click the column
titles to sort the listings by the
column wow
go charts button product chart wait I
can't click
it
ah
ah ah okay I can close it sometimes it
doesn't let me do such
things okay this window lists movies by
you or other Studios once you reach the
year where TV shows come and play you'll
be able to see them here as
well ahuh ah are you saying that in
1920 wow that's actually fascinating I
didn't think of that before they were
only movies TV shows were not even a
thing so I wonder who thought of the
first TV show and what was the first TV
show somebody must have been been like
Hey we're we're like releasing all these
like movies thingies but why not just
like release a series of TV
shows I guess yeah there was no TV TVs
first there was only like the big
screens and then TVs were
invented in the' 40s
oh not a h I'm not a h
each too much
information for your own products you'll
be able to press the reviews button to
quickly see the products reviews and
score breakdown okay cool same as with
Star Charts you can sort by specific
column by clicking on it
Title One More type of charts to see CLI
the charts
button Studio
charts okay makes sense
[Music]
M
uh-huh
uhhuh
huh
uh-huh
uh-huh uh-huh
uh-huh Skipper Skipper Skipper Skipper
too
much no more please let me play game
keep your Studio Lot in good shape is
keeping is important for your Studio's
Prestige and happiness of your employees
click on room to open the room info
window um thees every month okay
Prestige of the room okay okay low
maintenance will become obvious as the
room will become dirtier oh if
maintenance Falls below 50% the
employees working in the room will
become more and more
unhappy well then how about you clean up
your own [\h__\h] for
once don't always expect the maintenance
or the the cleaners to do it don't leave
behind a big [\h__\h] turd on the floor
thank
you sorry that it's just you know
something I feel very strong personally
about yeah we should get
roombas let's invent roombas it's my dog
sorry your
dog okay I can't be mad at your dog
oh are they cats oh yeah that reminds me
of
shii her cats just pooping everywhere
unbelievable
wait I'm doing something with my hair
okay hire a maintenance
worker but now get to work cool good for
you that's all I need to know okay cool
Education and
Training let's see how you can hone your
employees skills and get the best out of
them click the higher button oh my God I
hope this is over soon I want to play
the actual game
uh actors have two type of skills
Charisma and
athletic apart from actors all other
employee types have only one skill also
Charisma is the primary skill of actors
but other employee types have different
skill
mhm let's see how we can raise this
actor skill hire a
teacher now we have a teacher in the
classroom so we are ready to educate our
actor click manage your employees
wow shut up
stupid bus but actually really cute
bus cute
bus oh I haven't really looked at my
surroundings look at this and then
compar it to how it would look like in
40 50
years we'll make Los Ricos into
something
special okay
stop it's a good practice to educate
your employees during their idle time EG
between productions for increased
efficiency educate multiple students
simultaneously that's enough for now
click the stop button wow that did like
nothing we previously mentioned that
actors also have an athletic skills so
let's see how we can raise it train
start o o o oh
they're just practicing that stunt over
and over again
cool know that we don't need a teacher
for this type of training oh nice also
note that normally you need to unlock
stuntman and stunt facility in research
before you can build a stunt facility
ahuh why don't we why do we have to
build and research a whole [\h__\h] stunt
facility why can't we just like put a
treadmill
somewhere or maybe Tre did treadmills
exist in 1920 if not then they can just
like run around a little bit and that's
it
uh let's see how you can improve the
rating of your products with the help of
post production open the hire employees
window hire an F VX
designer this
one also hire what there's a
difference
video effects special eh what's the
difference between VFX and
sfx xx
x v visual ah sound effect oh yeah
right right that means sound effects not
special
effects sorry I knew that I just didn't
think about it just now
okay makes sense uh
become first 1927
let's see how you can make use of the
employees po product creation let's go
go to the product post production tab
not that this tab becomes available only
after you yeah shut
up oh better typography mat painting
Advanced
compositing ooh Foy sounds PRO voice
over enhanced sfx
[Music]
[Applause]
like
that I'm my own sfx person I don't need
these
people the tasks are sorted by level
from left to right higher level tasks
boost your products rating more but they
take longer to complete there's a total
of five post production levels
unlockable via research the higher a
level is okay there is two [\h__\h] flies
flying around here this whole time
because this is the only room with
lights on I'm going to get my my tennis
back
[\h__\h]
okay I have my tennis bat with me and
I'm just going
to welcome them
here come here oh oh come here come here
come here come
here where'd she
go I just I was just I was just holding
it then it just flew into it holy
[\h__\h] I didn't see that
coming get here get
here that was just one there's another
one you heard it right tap tap tap
tap where is
he it's like literally circling my
monitors cuz it's so
bright come here come here where'd you
go where'd you go I don't want to get a
heart attack again
please how are they so
good at dodging
come over here you little
[\h__\h] come
on where are you where are you
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh did I get
it feel like I got it but my screams
were louder than
zapping okay I think I killed free
flies wonderful thank you for joining in
on my fly killing session I appreciate
it very
much let me put my weapon
down next to me keeping it close in case
there's more
Challengers I'm so brave thank you
it
was definitely a scary situation but
takanashi kiar is a part-time Warrior
therefore I cannot be scared by anything
not even a
fly I fought valant
yeah I I think so too game game me that
would be good if they put that into Holo
and repeat five years later
uh there's a total of five post
production levels unlockable via resarch
cool assign
button assign
[Music]
button skipped one boost
okay okay
[Applause]
what are we
making is that the up upgraded camera or
is that the first one
still probably the first one
still okay at 86% because now they're
adding this
stuff now oh oh that's
cool maybe in the future instead of this
board they will have like a syn in front
of them a Wacom
CTI
cool why is it still the riveting
Fury the score is even worse than before
I
think scroll to the bottom to see post
production bar um
here a yeah
4% Mama Mia that was maybe not worth it
yet
uh uh
okay
marketing okay please tell me it's over
soon they didn't fix it in post I told
them to fix it in post Mama me I do have
to do everything by
myself see more Fox hire a marketer they
need a marketing office okay hire one
more okay note that marketers and
marketing available only after you 1945
okay uh product
creation no need for any specific setup
just click cre create product to proceed
marketing campaigns for a product can be
done at any point of its lifetime but
you'll benefit most by running them
before the product is released shut up
I'm reading this to my chat okay I'm
trying to
focus add IP
campaign the ramp of the
Dracula
rage choose one of the available
campaigns from the list each campaign
has a different cost required time to
complete and resulting hype boost hype
hype hype hype hype yeah okay Flyers
distribution posters billboard radio now
hold on maybe that will also be
different in the future like the
options cuz radio doesn't seem very 2010
to me
what I said CTIC tablets because in the
future it may
be cuz we are probably like in 1920 for
all of these tutorials don't low
[Music]
me create campaign okay
uh you can monitor the progress of the
campaign here uh-huh I am monitoring it
once every day the assigned marketer
will work on a campaign and increase its
progress when it has reached 100% the
campaign will complete at midnight of
that day this is the expected hype boost
that your product will get when this
campaign completes increased hype means
increased
[Music]
Revenue okay chill these are like
obvious things thank you
ah you can also run out campaigns to
boost your stars Fame levels click add
star
campaign
[Music]
okay a Gala event ooh let's go to the
Met
Gala let's go yes I'm going to wear
guci when a star campaign completes the
relevant star will gain a Fame boost use
marketing wisely and you'll see great
results
hi
okay go next go next maybe this whole
stream will just be
tutorials let's see how you can edit
your products using the video editor
click on product
[Music]
creation wow this looks like Windows
Movie
Maker I love it even that is
nostalgic well it's good that they keep
simple
uh this is the timeline that contains
the video track the subtitles track and
up to four audio tracks hover your mouse
on it and scroll the mouse to zoom in
and out
[Music]
mhm notice that the playhead moves to
show the current play oh my God thank
you oh my God I would have not known how
to use a video editor
otherwise I'm a
YouTuber I thank you I don't thank you I
don't I'm good can go go next
[Music]
it's like I'm fulfilling all these
little
quests what
like
this I already did that
differently Mama
Mia okay
waa okay that's
cool can we do like ghost spicy time
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
amazing
amazing that's how a EO sounds how do
you know it oh my god did they see a
movie and record it secretly
uh opens volume slid D click this button
to add an audio
track hold down shift scroll
what shift ah there we
go click the track to collapse expand
the oh my God leave me alone leave me
alone
[Music]
I can export it as a video find you mean
onto my computer let's go that would be
fun that's all you need to get started
uh after releasing a product you can see
the final video by pressing the watch
button in the product sheet okay oh
tutorial compete like really really I
can't believe it I actually can't
believe it I'm free
w what a [\h__\h] relief now oh my God
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait Kiana
Film Production it say it
here all right now look at those cute
toy cars oh my God I love
them all right we got to build stuff
we're going to build some offices now
Wawa knows how to do these things
because Wawa did all the tutorials
properly we can we could make some
pre-made rooms
[Music]
honestly Rider's
office research
office we got money we'll be fine right
I we got plenty of
money SK
toilet yeah can be over here and then M
yeah you know what I don't mind that
this sticks to the toilet that's fine at
least there's like an actually a nice
corner there at least it fits in
[Music]
maintenance I I wish you could change
change the door to be over there but
okay okay that's all of
those
then ooh wait I want I want paths yes I
want to do paing let's go we have
pattern tile Sandstone tile bright
Sandstone tile concrete tile
pattern no not
good
no yeah I like this
one oh well we have like is it because
then did we get two big ass Gates
because the name of our studio is so
long is that
why thank you if that's the case I
appreciate
it um
[Music]
okay let's
see I feel like I'm playing Sims right
now still very Sims
is not going to spend like a crazy
amount of time on
building hopefully
[Music]
does this make sense does this look
weird
maybe maybe just here we can have a
double path or is that weird nah it's
not weird but we'll like bring it all
the way up until the
end or we make like triples here yeah
triples could
work but then I have to extend to here
and then I have to get rid of
these
yeah makes perfect sense wow okay
already looks lovely can we have some
decoration yeah I I used to really like
making my studio look like nice I
think oh these are cute these are lovely
wow H wait isn't that on the path what
the hell here is
good
perfect
ooh a a [\h__\h] fly you want to
die come closer if you want to die come
back to
me I'll SWAT the [\h__\h] out of you you'll
think somebody called the SWAT team on
you can we have like one tiny one there
no no really can I I can't overlap them
right
no h okay that's annoying but
uh
[Music]
ah ah no
that's acceptable
[Music]
but no
no the SWAT team I am the swatting
team okay I'm going to leave this like
this because I don't know how we're
going to extend us all the way over here
what's the decorations oh trash cans and
stuff and fences and outdoor are they
going to use this kind of stuff there is
like some kind of reward for it so I
guess the more you have of the stuff
it's going to give like a a nice feeling
to the people
who uh work here
maybe nice outdoor
lights oh
oh oh my God the grid placement makes me
happy like in Sims often you you
wouldn't be able to place it like in
between the grids like this you'd have
to place it like I don't know in the
middle of the Grid or something like
that there's no like in the middle of
the grid placement
normally thank you see now we can put
this here and that will make me
happy Hallelujah
he doesn't that already look really
nice I mean the buildings look like
[\h__\h] but I'm trying my best to make them
look better
okay maybe some sets Steam Workshop what
local sets default sets
Okay so we're going to put M maybe not
too far this time maybe let's put them
over
here uh I do want to start with medical
set
maybe but yeah uh should we get a second
one right
away maybe a heist oh
no wait how expensive is
the the one the Pirates had oh it's not
more it's actually cheaper all right
with that we can do something with like
Min s or we can do like a
II kind of
movie
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay okay okay then we build some paths
to
[Music]
that wait a triple
oh no a a a
quadruple o baby a quadruple that
actually yeah that's okay it's okay that
works for now what else do we
need oh wait I can change I can change
the wall
patterns
oh oh and it has the same uh Keys like
in Sims to do it on the whole wall just
press
shift wait these are so like old looking
I wonder if they'll be different not all
of them
actually freaking
shed no this looks
okay oh they get connected like that
nice
okay some skibby
walls here we can have the
same or actually maybe this why do I
care why do I even
care oh that looks so funky is that even
cuz we're in the 19 wait no no we didn't
choose 1920s it's it's giving me 1950s
right as I chose is this
50s would you say this is accurate
I
wonder let's give this a different color
orange I kind of like
it I kind of like
it
[Music]
oo m is there something more
fitting maybe just white
[Music]
no hard to
choose wow
okay that's kind of ugly but I think it
fits
weirdly orange TI that's orange to you
is that orange or Bor you might want to
test your eyes before you decide wait
they added like funny te text just like
in Sims to
everything H mesmerizing your floor will
look like a puzzle is that good is that
bad you
decide
a I like it
I like
it yeah looking good just some more wall
patterns here oh we can add Windows too
the rooms the pre-made rooms don't come
with Windows that's so
sad I wonder if Mama to would like this
game m
I don't remember if she liked this game
back in the day she liked Sims one she
used to play
that so
possibly maybe just a a simple nice
color orange that's very orange this is
nice not too over
whelming not too bright not too
dark yeah the movies that's exactly what
the game is referencing that I also have
been mentioning several times we are
very aware of that uh let's do some
windows we're in the building phase
right now oh
cute oh cute cute
cute Windows into the toilet h well it's
stalls so it's not
even it's not even weird to put them
there if they're St no I think it's
still
weird I don't know about these maybe no
windows is
okay 300 bucks for the holy [\h__\h] wait
those windows are expensive
[Music]
don't know where I want to put these I
kind of want to pos position them
higher but it is what it
is oh I can't put it there oh no that's
not
[Music]
satisfying that's okay
Mama Mia so many windows so much
money oh I can't put them there cuz it's
out of bounds oh
no one here at least no windows back
here I don't care about that no no no no
no no but doesn't this look already so
much nicer what about like what about
the
roofs there's no like
no way of looking at the roofs right
like we can't go a floor higher like in
Sims and see the roof I
[Music]
suppose snack machine Drink Machine
W
radiator ban does that actually like
help them
[Music]
though will I use these
machines cuz then I'm going to put them
into the
Cen
yeah drink water
dispenser
nah I wonder if those devs are watching
deaths are you
here this makes me really want to play
the OG Sims same like there's just this
feeling that sometimes you want to play
Sims 1 specifically it has to be Sims 1
it can't be Sims 2 or three or four
although two Sims 2 also gives me that
feeling I don't get the feeling to ever
play like Sims 3 specifically but Sims 2
has its own very special charm that I
want to go back to especially because
Sims 2 had like the best the best
expansion packs for me ah Sims one to
Sims 1 and two both had the best
expansion packs
yeah yeah
yeah twoo games what twoo games
interesting DS Sims free oo I don't know
if I played that one but usually Sims
games on DS or like Gamecube or whatever
I like those though those are those are
good those were
fun see what I just did there I'm such a
pro
I know how to ey drop wow so
go H wait that's not going
to
work
yeah now this does bother me that
there's like two lines of bushes next to
each other but it's
okay wow wait this is so cool this is
like HD the movies it's like exactly
like okay sorry calm down calm
down okay chill chill chill chill
chill anything else we
want freaking huge ass pool are they
going to use
that well would they actually use that
amazing look at that placement a double
in the middle and singles on the side
facing the inside of course
wow deep breaths deep breaths pull at
the entrance yeah walk in and fall right
into the
pool imagine
oh this is nice cuz this one already
comes with the chairs it's not even
expensive what why is this only 2,500
when I had to pay like 300 for one
[\h__\h] window are you kidding
me Mama Mia okay we spent like
55,000
bucks but you know we want everything to
be available to our people right away
makes sense oh there's
paintings ooh
maybe you want to add no who gives a
[\h__\h] who gives a [\h__\h] certainly not the
people working
there okay beautiful
let's M hire people okay we need surely
we need an actor we need uh what is this
a
director we need a
producer we need a
riter a crew member like basically all
of this
hire staff
worker and the researcher hire all of
them yeah now we need to make a schedule
we learned how to do
that
basically how many hours just eight
right and
then uh let's work from
10 to eh uh
okay and then uh
[Music]
eat lasure if you want I don't
care yeah is this
good is this is this what I need to
do okay
begin wait how do I close that
manage your
employees wait the weather is so [\h__\h]
what the
[\h__\h] fairly unknown not at all I don't
think we need to like train any of them
yet our films are just going to be [\h__\h]
in the beginning that's okay
research
what oh if you start in a later year
they give you the points that you might
have if you play from the beginning and
then you can unlock whatever you want
huh wa does it even make sense to unlock
the old cameras shouldn't you just go
for the newest thing yeah probably 2,400
for
that o okay let's just unlock everything
that's recent the
lights a microphone
ooh oh oh it's ziser vocal bomb audio
technique
cool this is so cool fire we can learn
Fire Fire and Rain the rest is unlocking
in
1960 wait 1960 has different rain than
1950 wait that's okay do you understand
what I'm what what joke I'm making wait
holy [\h__\h] this is so expensive wait what
the [\h__\h]
need to be
careful yeah that Rangers hits
different okay we have low budget we can
do medium budget uh
production
sure post production level
one don't know if I want to if if we
should already go to this
one we probably have the money for it I
don't
know stman and sun facil we do need that
marketing office yes doctor office yes
classroom
uh yeah I
guess a lounge yes it's cheap let's go
medium quality meals let's [\h__\h] go
this is a [\h__\h]
kfp no bad quality food over
here drama PG yes drama yes Western yes
[Music]
m not a what about the pirate stuff
where's
the oh I unlocked it oh because I I I I
chose it in the beginning ah what's the
what the [\h__\h] is Regency there's a
coffee cup here what does that
mean I thought Regency means to like uh
like you know uh like a king and queen
king and queen's
Regency yeah where's the r
in it's
okay we'll get that
one ah it's like after me
oh interesting
cool now maybe no action yet
[Music]
what does that even mean NC unlock the
no children ah option as age
Focus R
rating
sure what should we what genres should
we unlock now maybe nothing in
particular maybe
action and
comedy okay
[Music]
I'll already unlock High
budget maybe I'm jumping the gun who
knows does it make sense to get like
older lights I don't think so right
surely
not okay I still have 10,000
points well sci-fi costs
10,000 while Sports just costs 400
damn I guess sci-fi in 1950 is just
really [\h__\h] popular so you really
want to get that
sci-fi what horror
12,000 okay all of this costs a
lot I'll get crime
for horror I don't have enough anymore
but we can get this rating okay okay I'm
Happy D all right I think people are
going to come in and I guess we
wait wait I I got some buildings we can
build the
buildings a visual design office audio
design office
CH we got to add these this looks
exactly like the things I would build
back in the day
uh like here all right audio
design visual
design research
office there should be two in between
like here okay ah now I have to like
decorate them
too you need to hire staff I did did I
not but we probably need even more now
even more a classroom like a this is a
legit classroom what the hell what what
are you going to learn
there
um if I put this here this thing is
huge
maybe um Behind These so we can like
Circle back
[Music]
around maybe leave enough space to put
no no let's let's connect them kind
of doctor's office can maybe be next to
this
[Music]
one stunt facility
M yeah I put that
pretty far in the
[Music]
back but this is going to mess up my
pathing
no why maybe
instead why would want to put it
like it's kind of weird I think that it
would be
there but at least that it doesn't mess
up my
[Music]
paing o I'm lagging again when I put
things in there no I'm I'm rotating
things make a recuitment
office for new Army infantry units what
are you talking about wait we got the
doctor's office we got got the we're
missing the marketing office right
uh yeah I I would like to have it around
here
[Music]
actually wow okay we've got like
everything that you could possibly wish
for except a
lounge okay let's out the lounge
[Music]
what is this
thing a water tank or
what what I have two research
offices no I don't do I I do
a how did that
happen what no not the entire lot what
the [\h__\h] I just want to get rid of
um the whole
[Music]
thing good that you noticed that and
pointed it out although I don't wait
what happened with that
oopsie
uh okay I don't want to put that Lounge
in here to be
honest but
okay is what it
is yeah yeah it could be doubling the
efficiency maybe eventually
but
[Music]
um oh look that messes up my paing
again
no what is this the school let's remove
the school move it a little bit
further so that it lines up here
otherwise I will
cry we don't want
that okay I'm just going to get the
patterns okay I'm just going to do that
I'm not going to put Windows now oh will
I can I
resist at least at least some some some
flooring is necessary
[Music]
oh my God the lag when I go in here this
is the lounge what kind of floor should
we have like a dark this one
yeah what is this again a stunt stunt
place I don't know just something boring
this is the marketing office what did we
have in here just a wood
uh sorry guys this is boring you I'm
trying to make it look nice for you
visually
pleasing don't be bored yet
please the lounge wall what if the whole
room is this I would go
[Music]
insane I would not want to be
there this is kind of cool though this
is kind of a Cool vibe though
no I kind of like it cuz it's like dark
and I don't know I don't know how to
describe it it could even work well over
here too but I'm going to make it
different are you entertained makes me
want to play The
Sims you know for me currently this just
makes me want to play
this
amazing yeah we got so many decoration
options thank you for being so
versatile you beautiful beautiful
game ah we were doing like like this I
think actually but not here
apparently it's just the the maintenance
place it can live
without
okay apparently we're going to get
school children entering our premises
okay
okay maybe some
Hedges maybe just a few
[Music]
edges just a few totally not overdoing
it I'm I'm I'm keeping it at a bare
minimum or am I
oh that's
satisfying absolute bare minimum there's
not even any anything here for the
people to go to but I'm already
preparing it for the loveliness that is
about to come upon
us oh no this is going to mess my plan
up
oh
no I wish there was like a one
tile
flower but that I can't place that there
because I placed the the light
there well I can do
this
genius
genius oh
more Hedges I [\h__\h] love
[Music]
Hedges oh no wait that's exactly across
here we can with a good Peace of Mind
put another light down here I'm
unstoppable my hedges are
unstoppable m
that's that's manageable I think I think
I can
put a light there for sure
no and then here too no no I
can't okay but that looks fine actually
for
now it's
acceptable I wonder in Sims there is a
button in Sims 4 there's a key key that
you can press so that it doesn't stick
to these tiles or half tiles but you can
just move it around freely I wonder is
there no it's at least not the same
button
oh did YouTube Die For a Moment alt no
alt is not uh doing the thing in Sims
yeah it it was probably
alt G oh
no no no G just gets rid of the grid but
it's still attaching to
it okay yeah this looks amazing I'm
happy with that let's uh get to work for
[\h__\h]
sake not my fault that the game is
making me like want to do all these
kinds of
things so um
I need to hire a teacher a stunt teacher
or something like that right a stun man
a
doctor uh and the affects people and the
marketer
[Music]
wow okay wait we need someone here too
who can I hire for
that there was there's no one to hire
maybe I need to
wait until I get
another
person hello it's work time where is
everybody wait where is
everybody oh maybe they don't come until
tomorrow I think that's that is true oh
wait my I still have that pint oh no
that's
embarrassing I unpin the message now for
the Hedge run thank you the members
messages are look they look exactly like
the hedges so beautiful look at
this
wow if only we had roofs on a rainy day
it's really not nice to not have
roofs wait it says
brolex bro give me your
Rolex come on please
sorry that
actually lowkey gave me a heart attack
it's just uh the tennis um bat fell
over
okay people please come to work tomorrow
I'm awaiting you I built all of this
just for you I'm so proud of
it please
wait we how do we have five
five my lck Prestige is
oh wa look I did all of
that okay I mean that did
something that did
something my Prestige is all the way up
there let's
go okay they're coming soon
right
about now welcome to your new job enjoy
hello hello I hope you're happy here
please don't get me in
trouble I don't want to be troubled I
just want to make
movies get in there do some stuff uh how
do we I guess wait how we we start how
do we start making a movie produ
creation product product creation okay
let's
um
make
Umi the
beginning let's make that but do don't I
only have one
actor I cannot make a movie
with h so many people yet okay uh
so something with one person let's do
something with M
only
Marin
Mar see how do
I I'm caps locked where's the a a poost
trophy okay just let's just do this
Marin's dilemma we're just going to have
Marin in the in the p
uh
set perfect perfect we have the right
set for it we should use
it
um okay actor oh wait script product
type movie product
size let's start with medium maybe I
don't know and then it will be a drama
because it's a
dilemma and pirate
what's out of these the most spicy one
is is it no
children I don't really know what the
order is of these rankings is it
R NC
17 wow 100,000 let's start cheaper
because pirate doesn't have much money
anyway in the
beginning Zachary Roy Bobby
Perry and Jeremy Vos are the team
working on this genre
sliders um what does why wouldn't I put
everything on a 10 why would I not do
that oh oh that's is this just to like
M cuz this is not happening so I'm not
going to put that high and there's no
intimacy yet and no conflict yet
probably it doesn't seem to affect the
price but I think it will affect
like production or or the ratings or so
maybe okay choose actor thank God the
one actor we have is a
woman oh can I put her in no okay just
once okay well she she's not she's not
completely unlike mine she has
boobies she's got hair so yeah she's
she's kind of
similar uh too
set okay can we only have three
scenes extra no oh no we can have more I
don't know I don't really know what I'm
going to do yet so I'm not 100% sure
oh we can start by directing one okay
okay so the story let's think of a story
basically this will be her Beginnings uh
she does have some kind of lore about uh
being a broke pirate right and wanting
to buy a
ship right was wasn't that her official
lore something like
that N7 is spicy movies should I do
R I can still change
it oh pirate
cosplayer yeah a pirate cosplayer who
wants to kind of be a real uh pirate
though right she wants to buy a big ship
she has no money though okay so her
dilemma is that she's a pirate a a
really unsuccessful pirate and she's
alone she has no crew no ship um and
she's looking for the one
piece and and maybe in the future in in
future
movies uh she will find her crew and her
ship and her one
piece sounds
familiar okay how is this how we going
to do this again um actors include yeah
animations just like an actor so it's
going to be in in the order or like is
it one one animation per scene
okay we'll see we'll
see I mean the opening should just be
her
crying right and how do I move her
again how do you
ah she should be in the front or or no
yeah that's okay in the front the
costume is already
perfect um maybe we can have it rain
because oh no I can't okay oh the
quality is still pretty bad even in
1950 let's pan to the
actor and yeah she's just going to be
crying because she's depressed depressed
pirate red let not not no shaky please
no
shake okay so that's one one scene in
the next
scene uh mining Senpai will maybe get an
idea or or think I don't
know uh
I uh
or I talk to herself I don't
know what what do we have
anything that makes
sense smoking cigar I'm alarmed and
shocked
nah I'm trying to have this make sense
you know
angry there's a lot of things that would
work with a second actor but when I'm
alone Panic anxious okay that works as a
nice
followup wow wow
sugy but this time we
will place her in a different part of
her
room nice
and you can see that time has passed
because now she's in a different part of
her room and she's freaking out in a
different
way
wonderful okay in the next
scene uh Min
Senai will
be thinking
maybe she has to change
something about her
life maybe she gets an idea of how to
turn things
around yeah yeah that's a good
closeup all right all right and that's
the whole movie no just kidding let's
add another one
I wonder if it costs more if I have more
scenes so far it didn't
increase um choose the set direct
scene her idea uh do we have like a
moment where it's like aha like an aha
moment probably not but we can do like a
surprised
happy like oh yeah that's a good idea
thanks me where's the spiciness I can't
be very spicy yet there's no nothing
kissing like she'll be kissing the
air yay she got the
idea yay everything's going to be okay
everything's going to be fine she's
going to find some friends she's going
to go out and and and find the friends
and go onto the big big ocean and get
the treasures and find the one
piece can I think of one
more one more Scene like a let's go kind
of pose
maybe M's Love Boat in the future
yeah
oh
oops
uh
ah Victory celebration sounds like good
she's like let's go
otherwise oh entering a
portal she could just like
leave
uh no that's probably fine that's
good
cut
woohoo oh
okay that is the movie Marin's
dilemma uh
one oh should I add a stunt scene but
they didn't learn how to do stunts yet I
wonder if it will work if do they have
to learn I mean we have a stunt man is
there a reason for a stunt yeah maybe
she'll roll out
motivated let's see what stunts we can
choose from
ah do you think she can do
it C can she do it let's
see solo stunts there's a
ritual what is the ritual
like or maybe she can oh
maybe basically she's going
to summon
friends
but then I would need somebody to appear
and I don't have anybody to uh appear
yet she can just jump and
fall just because um there's a meaning
to
this this is like wait I I have an idea
with the camera movement if we just
capture
uh like until this point that's where
the movie ends like but like um
like wait do that
again do it
again yeah like we would end it like
here she just the people will be like
absolutely amazed when they sit in the
movie theater because yeah yeah it'll be
almost like fredie you will get the
feeling that she's jumping out of the
like screen and entering the real world
almost but at the same time it's a
cliffhanger yeah but also at the same
time it gives you the feeling of oh
there like she she's onto something
she's going
somewhere and she's about to do
it do you see the
vision totally
oh no set the center so that works I
think I wish I could change her
expression she should be
happy
okay yeah that
works she's doing the stunt on her own I
hope she'll be fine otherwise she can go
to the
doctor I yeah post prodct ah yeah uh we
had that too we can add some sounds
do we need this
maybe what's the matte painting what do
that
even what does that
do not sure and the voice over makes me
think
that the movie is being recorded with no
voice and it's being added
afterwards but why is it why can't it
not be her
or is the pro voiceover like a narration
maybe we'll never know because that's
not what I'm
doing actually this makes no sense we
just do a general audiences because more
people will be able to see
it for now that makes more
sense
okay I feel like possibly we could go
for medium
budget we'll make money back
probably but wait there's a little bit
of suspense at the
end should we should we make
it yeah we'll get more money back in the
end oh but oh no wait I don't have the
money for that seemingly
well he what do you mean it doesn't have
a selected set
and what happened to my St Mama
M it got
reset
uh oh what
happened wait what
happened why did you me no why did you
what what did what
what this is the let's go did I do
something after the let's go or did I go
immediately to the stun
not sure
anymore stunt yeah stunt was after but
like what did I do in that other scene
whatever I'm just going to do the stunt
one more time Jump and
fall towards the
front and then we'll just zoom in
[Music]
oh she's in the
table let me fix
[Music]
that okay hopefully that
works
okay create
prod I hope everything uh was fine there
let's go
get to work baby make me some good
movies yeah riding that screenplay W
let's let's let's get a the best
screenplay we could ever have
please okay screenplay is being handed
over to oh research is doing research
for whatever reason where is what's
what's happening where are we now are
they filming already they're filming
already oo m t get into costume all
right
ah I'm oh this is like Sims what the
[\h__\h] I'm sure I found it this way and
action director Bobby pays close
attention to the monitors the actors
give the performance of a lifetime the
final shots of Marin's dilemma one are
coming together and they look very
promising when crack cut cut what was
that everyone looks around and sees crew
member Casey before a broken camera
looking what looking speechless you
can't be serious Bobby says frustrated
it's my first production and something
goes wrong
already
no it fell over by itself it wasn't me
Casey says they quickly call for your
help we can't do anything about this now
leave H Force Casey Holden to pay for
the damage I would like to do that but
he says it wasn't
him yeah 5,000 bucks is it's okay we'll
do
it I'm truly sorry boss I'll work harder
to pay you I promise I feel like I heard
that before from you
guys the repair guy arrived shortly and
quickly confirmed that it was not case's
fault oh as soon as the camera was
restored Casey out did themselves making
the overall result of the scene even
better I chose the right one I
think I did the right thing good good
good production can proceed
please M it was is not a
lie we're so
relieved the research is like are they
like
constantly ah they just keep on
researching and I get research points
automatically right that's how that
works I
think oh 48 for the scene rating that's
okay but wait there's still more so will
it go up why are you
angry what does that mean what what's
what's that mean are they on happy with
the results with the
acting oh what's happening where'd they
go are they what are they
doing why are they not filming or are
they oh they
are 11 what's happening
okay we couldn't finish the
movie remove any obstacles unable to
reach what do you mean there are other
people it's just like we have too many
staff
maybe oh oh oh oh no okay yeah we have
too many staff too little space we got
to make a new one
already that's
fine I'll add a new one
[Music]
M
uh
here yeah okay I'll leave it at that for
now and they are seated okay oh they
don't even walk over they just get
automatically
what looters and villagers
in the middle of the night the phone
starts ringing frantically it stops and
starts ringing again the caller has no
intention to stop picking up the phone
and serious voice on the other end talks
fast it's the head of the Studio's
security firm the Studio's alarm went
off we are on site but the people have
already fled what the [\h__\h]
Justice afraid for the worst you get
down there as quickly as possible
finding the police already all over the
place what the [\h__\h] an officer
approaches you
what what the [\h__\h] this is my first day
I'm playing on
easy he might have some partial eader
but nothing outstanding the burglar only
stole 20,000 only the rest were too
heavy to carry do you want us to pursue
this let's make a movie about it people
love Bas no bring them to justice for
[\h__\h] sake we are on it sir you better
be I mean I think the the other option
may have been good ah staff I need
another cook
what what what what am I supposed to
do I can make a staff to hire
them character
creator
uh for
real would be a staff worker I
think I don't
care only positive I could just make
someone with only positive traits wow
okay Kenny freaking
Kenny all right I'm I'm I'm fine is
there here
safe does he show up right
away how do I get out of here load
ah does he show up cuz I want to hire
somebody no he doesn't I probably only
get like a certain amount of people to
hire per
day
H I got no one to work in the canteen
ah
doio oh no I shouldn't have hired so
many people from the get
go wait one thing I could do oh although
I don't know if that will
help is put a snack machine into the
same
[Music]
room and
the drink machine
[Music]
is that going to
help make actors look ah yeah I can do
that for future actors
yeah are they oh they left oh yeah it's
lasure time all
right it's
interesting let's let's make a GAA and
then hopefully the next actor
recommendation will be
only that
GAA I'm caps locked
okay the youngest I can make her is
20 actor
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah very charismatic a 100 I can just
max out both you're kidding
me not going to though
oh there's so many different
traits Midas
Touch D thir devil Jim quick liner Beau
she's
beautiful h
ad him what there's an opposite wait
I've heard of minus touch before only
because of a K-Pop
song
uh so that's a thing but is sadim touch
an actual
[Music]
thing um more stats will increase oh so
probably this will also increase the
price yeah B let's put it down a little
bit
H but traits do traits also increase the
price no right probably
[Music]
not
okay
uh let's give her
Daredevil forever famous even
though I don't think I maybe this one is
okay cuz otherwise it'll be too
expensive she'll work C her way up uh
within my production
company do I have to give a negative one
I
[Music]
wonder Couch Potato I don't really think
that she like IRL would I don't think
this would like apply to her but let's
give her one negative thing
uh ah this is like gooy dea
colors that's the closest I can get
probably
no but that's nice because I think the
fashion will change accordingly to the
time month 42 at working a k me thank
you you're happy aren't you
do we have goba hair
uh ah there's no white hair there's no
blue hair
no I can't really make him look like
themselves blonde is the lightest
color okay I need people to make like
things just like they do in Sims I I
need them to make things you know for to
download I need that cuz this is not
enough for me to work with this does not
look like GAA I could make an am
though I could make an
[Music]
am but I was going to I was going to
make Umi you know Umi was going to be
like the that M
finds it's a story it's a whole
story colors other than brown have not
been invented
yet but gray hair should be a thing if
you're old can she get
ah if we make GAA 60 years old her hair
becomes go Gray
okay go I hope this doesn't affect
your like workflow in my
studio um hope you don't die soon but I
think this is
necessary gray hair light gray hair
let's
go okay goba is
saved and wait now I wanted to make an
Al but
okay let's make there's no way I can
make someone look even remotely like
Aqua
Senpai okay let's make an Amelia Watson
character and I'll I can make like a a
detective movie with
her
blonde M that looks like
am giving me am Vibes or this one maybe
that
one
yeah charismatic a little bit
sporty uh let's wait let me get rid of
those
again
h m
she's going to be a
perfectionist which means she produces
better results at
work she's going to
be
beautiful bringing more hype to
films and a quick
learner and she's going to be
ah she's going to be
alone honestly that is uh
probably pretty accurate
am uh wait where was uh glasses here
[Music]
can't see
them too accurate I'm
me
I'm oh wait a clock let's go it's
cutting through the skin though what the
hell
nice nice nice I think that's all I can
do
really aelia
Watson uh pink hair purple hair orange
hair
kiar a me a me could be somewhat
recreated with like brown or blonde
hair um but let's think of like people
with realistic hair colors although Ena
I could do with black hair it's kind of
purple close to
purple C can be a red
hair well let's try
korei uh what do we have ah yeah red it
looks more like brown to me but okay but
there's no long hair they're all just
going to have the same
haircut I don't know about that we
should maybe only make people that I can
really make look make them look like
what who they're supposed to be for now
what do you think
who who could we make who who looks like
a normal
person can you research more hair I I
doubt it but maybe with the years
they're going to add more hairstyle like
the years in
game Yago Yago the one male actor I will
get uh what's his last name yo
yo will be a little bit older I don't
know his age
but is he 50 already I
wonder he doesn't look 50 to me but he
probably is over 50 is his age
public oh
M yeah yeah
[Music]
I that's actually n the shoes
no yagle in the
50s I don't I don't think he would wear
those white pants but I don't think he
would wear any of
this maybe Yago in the' 50s would wear
something
like
this yeah maybe this this is
heagle uh he is 50 51 oh really
oh should he be an actor or like a
producer we don't need another producer
though so maybe actor is fine so we can
actually use him in the movies he's he's
very
athletic yeah like somewhere here maybe
gagles traits m
maybe the mid is
touch
and maybe he brings hype to films
because like I feel like wherever Yago
goes he brings hype just by
appearing people are happy to see him at
events more than seeing
us um gym
rat and maybe um maybe perfectionist
that's
[Music]
good yeah okay uh wait what are the
faces wait get get rid of those
glasses so I can see your face I can't
see
[\h__\h] out of those I would say this
one mhm
probably and then like this but because
he's 50 they're already giving him gray
hair
automatically even though I don't
remember him having such gray hair
already I just saw him a couple days ago
I feel like his hair was still very
black but this is all I can do does this
look like yo to
you he what the [\h__\h] Stanley who the
[\h__\h] are
you what happened
what
happened
honey why got
reset he probably would wear oh but you
can't see it he'll still get it does he
wear
glasses no maybe sometimes but not when
I see him look at
that
wa that's sick
I like it but yeah no no glasses uh
okay I I'm going to have to make him at
least somewhat famous and I I will have
to I'll have to like you know get some
money to in order to hire
him all righty all righty let's get out
of here
let's continue my
movie so this
n they're all in here but I got no one
to work here I'm sorry get go
home bye
30,000 wait I'm in the
minus it's okay I'll I'll finish filming
the next day how long can I be in the
minus yeah
where did all the money
go I got robbed too otherwise I would
still have 20,000
bucks Mama M spend money to make money
bankruptcy wait can I go bankrupt wait
let me save before I go
bankrupt
because maybe I can go back and get a
loan would they give me a loan if if I'm
already in the
minus now go to work go to work go to
work finish this
mofo can I already
set uh some wait how's this work on here
marketing yeah I can already do
[Music]
it let's do poster advertising for now
not too expensive
although we could do billboard honestly
5K per what per month that means per day
per game day did you change to the new
camera for the
stage I would think it does it
automatically I don't
know ah well I can't modify
now it's isn't it the only camera we had
anyway
I don't know got to check
afterwards okay one more Scene yeah one
more
scene and then we do stun scenes I
guess oh my God are we going to finish
this
today oh God it
okay what does that mean what happened
are we editing
it I finish
filming
oh ah okay they're working on
it oh but they left no not enough money
to provide
meals tomorrow tomorrow I release that
movie tomorrow will be another
day it'll be fine I need another throat
candy my throat feels like not good now
I've been yapping too much in this
stream the whole tutorial killed
me things are truly dire wait we just
started this is our first movie but they
like hit us with
some some bricks man some [\h__\h] bricks
cheats
doco I'm not going to use cheats we are
the sinking ship oh that means we found
the ship though that's that's that's a
good thing
ha okay
oh what the
[\h__\h] Laura Gates one of the best people
to have around doing a water cooler
discussion comes to work a bit troubled
she's not talking much keeping to
herself everyone quickly notices a sun
shift in the personality may be
good it's just a phase oh plan a
surprise party I want you to come into
the lounge later and nobody's working
there can I even do this when nobody
works in the
lounge yeah maybe yeah okay
here
it
it oh no that didn't go
well
that didn't go well
the sudden desire to isolate became
permanent is she
quitting no right oh my
God release prodct releas to ah tomorrow
I don't have money maybe I'll should I
take a
loan but tomorrow I'll get money for
sure can I I can hire people oh my god
well I don't have the money to
hire oh oh oh
is there is gooda here no what the [\h__\h]
where are my people that I
created maybe the the chances of me
getting her is really low
uh I should probably get right to the
next movie should I
not should we just make a random
one just to fill it like just to have
have like
something just one random
one I think
so just yeah a be
movie should we should we I don't wait I
don't have money to create
this I have money should I loan should I
get a
loan 100,000
sell a few
Hedges no no not my hedges don't take my
hedges monthly P holy
[\h__\h] this is okay though it's not bad
the final finale the interest is not
bad but maybe 50,000 is
okay 50,000 do we need 50,000 50,000 if
I want to make a a whole new
movie maybe
60,000 okay I hope that was not a bad
choice oopsie let's make this random ass
movie
um we
have
[Music]
uh we have two
sets maybe a drama in the the one set oh
but wait that doesn't ah doesn't fit
okay leave it to me I'm going to I'm
going
to it's an amazing title
actually that is an amazing
title let's just leave it at three
scenes so it films faster
do I have to do this or can this be
automatic too I
wonder let's just uh this is like a this
is the outakes from the mding
movie If I just don't direct it does it
just do random scenes I wonder
wait shouldn't we be
crying it's a sad movie
again and this is the blue
PR
okay
[Music]
oh I don't
know yeah play with the revolver have
fun wait she might not be on the camera
on yeah she was not on the
[Music]
camera
okay let's create that should all be
good I
think so we have a little backup and
wait now we could we could hire
someone uh what do we have we have
another
actor I just need
staff
no unpaid bills Andes from the banks
keep pting up and the word is that some
of the employees are very dissatisfied
with the delayed
payments
really no is one of the discounted
employees that decides to pay you a
visit look I don't mind the small delay
in payment but it's been days since my
last paycheck I have bills to cover I
can't keep working like that no please
wait we have a PL to pay yeah we do we
do I'm already under lot of I don't
appreciate your no let's say be a little
more patient please we have a plan to
pay back everybody tomorrow please wait
please
wait fine I'll wait but it better come
soon without an incentive to work even
the most detail oriented employees tend
to lose their motivation soon after your
discussion you noticed a gradual decline
in that's fine that's fine she just
finished her movie so this is fine she's
already done with her work so she's
making that shitty ass shitty ass a
movie
but yeah we we we we we'll be fine we'll
be fine okay I hired the staff person so
is that person going to work over there
I think
so
oh oh okay they're
filming there's no no other staff person
I can
hire yeah I could hire an
actor o clean new man but maybe not
maybe not right now I can't pay
them load the safe while it's so over no
what do you mean I have 9,000 bucks I
have a great Studio we're just got to
wait until tomorrow
it'll be fine it will be fine I'll
probably be in the minus by the end of
this day cuz that's when I pay people
[Music]
right uh-oh I'm scared
9,200 now and
oh okay we get uh critiques a good
director like Bobby Perry cannot save a
bad
if you like movies with great actor
chemistry that's all maran's dilemma one
has to offer which is great because
there's only one actor of course of
course the one actor has great chemistry
with
herself beautiful premise excellent idea
all butchered by Kiana film Productions
crew it's your guys' fault you did this
guys kfp the promising concept is buried
under so many mistakes it's barely
watchable well
we'll get better just give me my
money we need to make
147,000 bucks to get back the
money happiness what's what what does
this mean they're less happy
afterwards this is not
good this is not good
oh
okay this is the first day the first day
only we made 70 72,000 that's
good we're at 130k here how when how
does that make I don't understand that
but
okay I need to take the day off
uh you don't have to waste your money on
doctors yeah go to our
doctor even though I feel like like
she's faking it but let's tell her to
come over to uh have our doctor take a
look at her cuz she's our one single
actor I need her to come to
work um no it's fine I'll just get some
rest
wow so yeah something fishy is going
on the lot entrance is unreachable what
the what are you talking
about okay that's is she actually not
coming tomorrow I have to to film
movies I'm only 24% in fire her before
her
payday isn't payday every
day
yby very suspicious yeah I mean just
calling in after what happened with me
not being able to pay her and her being
like okay I'm going to be shitty
now it's just you know I can do the math
myself
maybe I should hire a new actor
then we definitely need to stuff okay so
now the lounge is staffed that's
good and let's get this
actor jeppi Chi
Boyer he's unpopular though what the
[\h__\h] he brings hype though this is kind
of weird
contradicting or should I should I I
don't know I don't I don't know I need
him we just have to wait because we
can't replace her anyway wait
actually wait she's
here oh I can import them oh I can okay
she's here though she's filming the
movie all is good
[Music]
then I guess she was intimidated by me
after all
do I have to do more
marketing
Oh I thought you were sick Laura Gates
comes inside the office with a troubled
face she's bringing bad news and tries
to find a way to spill it out I spoke
with producer Zachary Roy who suggested
I come talk to you Laura Gates says I
came a bit late yesterday and stopped
outside my favorite Cafe right across
the sets of tele movie ink that's where
I saw Ria Lee I think she was having an
interview there I thought you should
know she's cheating on
me as soon as real arrives at the studio
she you call for them in the office from
the way she looks and walks it's
apparent she's hiding something she's
pregnant PR let's cut to the chase they
saw one of your colleagues saw you I'm
willing to forgive you if you do
something for me in return how you
feeling are you better I just want to to
let you know that everyone was worried
about you you can read that in a passive
aggressive way or you can read it in a
kind way I wonder how we would convey it
probably in a kind way should we just be
nice or should we it would be best if
you pack your things and go we still
need her to finish the
movie we can't tell her to just go and I
don't want
to um threaten her I don't want to
blackmail her so I think I'm just going
to be I'm just going to be nice I
think I can't fire her
now I mean maybe I could and then I can
replace her in the movie I don't know
how that would
work if that
works or if we abandon filming but
there's contracts you have to finish
filming
[\h__\h] no I'll be nice oh hey that's what
I was hoping for full of guilt and
regret I'm feeling better thanks for
interest after your brief talk Ria burst
into tears I'm sorry she said I was not
sick I had a job interview a tell movie
Inc I should have told you about this
seeing her honest regret you decided to
keep her in your roster for the time
being but made sure she learned her
lesson see now it's like she was mad at
me for not paying her which was totally
legit but now it's like she feels bad
for lying and looking for a different
place and all that now now now now she
owes
me I played this game correctly The Game
of
Life now finish your [\h__\h] movie or
else please finish it to today why is
this taking so long Mama Mia Mama
Mia can we finish today
please 80% oh we could we could a yeah
oh but it needs to go into postp
production no oh wait I don't think I
did any post
production ding ding ding
ding
okay releasing tomorrow
is she going to be
there there she is 60 year old Gara wait
why is your hair blonde
here let's hire
GAA how about the crew that Mar finds is
just uh good that I don't have to make
or try to make and fail fail to make um
all the other members that will not look
remotely like them
are we filming shark NATO possibly very
possible okay laser time baby are you
done eating it's time to go into the
lounge
yeah wait should I how is the money
doing now is that 130 bucks how much of
that is my
own I don't understand
how much of that is my
own the 60,000 was
aone so I mean a good amount should be
my
own
I oh wa wait I'm number one H I'm number
one I guess the competition is just just
so shitty what why why they not saying
anything why is the film wood reporter
not saying anything what what is it
Bobby per style was the only saving
grace of Crybaby but it was me not
merely enough to save this fias of a
movie okay chill mostly shallow with
very very few exceptions okay okay shut
the [\h__\h] up shut the [\h__\h] up I'm still
making money and that's all that counts
I can make mediocre movies as long as
I'm making
money Hollywood no not even GNA say that
because Hollywood movies are generally
not bad
so there's a lot of mediocre chick
flicks
though boop boop what's what's wrong
with these
people why are they
angry but that was that was fine we made
40K on the first day oh hey we keep on
making money we made
220k in the first day of mmer and still
100K on the second day that's good also
we don't even have
um we don't have
a a marketing strategy for our filler
movie we could set one for that
too just a cheap
one she can do both
right probably
wait crybaby has way
more like reception or whatever that's
so
sad how's your fro it's okay because I'm
currently licking a fro candy again
otherwise I would be
dying thanks for asking it's another day
welcome back to kfp
Productions and
uh is GAA
here is GAA with us today yes she is
Let's Make a movie with garara and Marin
so this
is Marin's
dilemma
2 where GAA will be introduced to the
story medium budget maybe wait I don't
have the money do do I not wait I do for
sure I do it's just something else
that's missing
um maybe comedy for this
one
pirate
General lore dialogue
story uh
in no
gab will be angry at me if I do
that don't want to don't want to do
anything too spicy between those two
that's not the kind of you know
connection that they
have garuna and the modding cosplayer
literally doesn't even have her name
that's why she's a
cosplayer okay we're still in the pirate
set
uh I don't know what we're going to do
here we're going to have them get to
know each other I
guess and kiss no no
kissing Shinko was pretty spicy could
reenact Shinko if I remembered it she
has blonde hair again what is going on
there must be like some kind of hair
bug cuz she's not supposed to have that
kind of kind of hair okay they're just
like talking in this one I didn't even
give them that but makes
sense all right in this
scene how do I can I make gak walk in I
guess so
probably
walk drunk walk she shees just walking
drunk Min should be the one drunk
really sneaky walking
okay normal
walking
so good walks in O good good
no
[Music]
ah why is it this this is difficult
it keeps on resetting her to that
placement no okay I'm going to move
Marine
instead maybe we'll have her turned
around and then is there a turn
around
slasher standing turn left
uh she's carrying an axe
I mean if we if we frame it so that we
don't see the
axe okay this is how the movie
starts uh wait did we even we didn't
even we need to watch the movie the the
way it turned out I don't even know how
the movie turned out the one that we
made
previously we got to watch it don't
don't let me forget it
okay uh let's zoom
in go higher so we don't see the
axe like
this walk in money turns around in a
weird way there's nothing wrong with
this you don't see the axe nothing wrong
with
this okay next
scene they are
wait just talking to each other I guess
talking and uh
[Music]
talking oh it cuts between them that's
fine that's
good we still haven't seen Good's face
maybe we should make make her turn
around cuz apparently the camera can
only go straight
forward pretty
much in that case if a set is built like
that usually the actors also always Face
Forward don't
they yeah we need a good view now what
happens next they met each other and
madin probably explained uh her
situation that she wants to do
something
um should we KN GAA should Mar KN maybe
that should happen at the end of the
story after a
victory ah they should they should plan
they should plan
yeah let plan hey get over there
why why why not let me get over
there I can't the table is too close to
the
wall well that sucks how are we going to
plan on on tables map we got to make it
um we got to work with like
angles wait
yeah angles angles
baby
[Music]
angles we could pant to ejector oh
yeah oh yeah oh yeah that's good that's
the good stuff same animation like NPC
they're in sync it's a good thing it's a
good
thing okay so uh
they made a plan on the map to find the
one
piece and
now and
now she will stand here with a
notebook
to just you know write down the plan
[Music]
M and GAA because she's like going to be
supporting man and Z with her plan she's
going to stand there with a
sword or she's going to drink
alcohol yeah
she decided that she needs more
confidence for this plan and one way to
gain confidence
is with
alcohol yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah get drunk let's get drunk
go I wish I could choose when it does
this um
change m
oh yeah oh that's a that's a yeah that's
good and I that was that scene maybe I
don't need this many scenes it's going
to take forever to film that
too yeah 1 2 3 four
five the last
scene is so Random you think that's
random
no what would happen in the end of this
part of the
movie
they they made their plan they met each
other they made their plan good are
getting drunk Marin made the plan
H maybe Min could yell at her but maybe
she just joins in with the
[Music]
drinking good can stand drunk
drunkly oh wait Marin can let's just
this is the only set that we have so we
have to deal with it she's just already
looking for the one piece
and
cut that will
be that will be
basically
it
yeah the next is a cliffhanger again in
the next part will she find the one
piece or not will GAA be helpful or not
we will see in min's dilemma part
three Yahoo oh yeah this was also a
thing
oh oh this is
confusing
[Music]
mhm okay making a plan that takes quite
a while that's okay that's okay if it
takes a while
she found it she's like I'm 100% sure
that the one piece is
there okay I'm writing down the
information while guda is getting
drunk oh I just I just need more
confidence slowly turning into Amelia
Hixon oh oh did you see something
Central oh oh yeah I see I see the one
piece I I think or do I let me check
again oh is that just a what was it we
will never
know okay should we add some Sounds
here footsteps right make footsteps Mak
sense
here wait I need a lot of footsteps
then or can I make it
longer just one footstep I'm putting one
footstep at a
[Music]
time is there like chatting sounds no
why is this so
long I mean that's at least a woman's
voice let make it like short and then
repeat this will work trust me
[Music]
yeah yeah perfect that's like exactly
what I need
[Music]
could put that one in
[Applause]
too where are the ghost coming from from
the Ouija board trust me get rid of the
Ouija board and everything will be
okay let's add one
[Applause]
cough are you okay M zai is your fro
okay okay uh here uh
maybe another gasp once G starts
drinking yeah she's so
shocked and
disappointed wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait that's the sound of her picking up
the the thing
when maybe the squishy sound could be
while she's drinking I don't
know when does she
start I need a I need another one
then okay she opens the bottle that
could be its own
sound here spring
I want to cut
it I
can't let's align several
Springs yeah yeah yeah yeah H squishes I
mean how is this going to sound together
I'm I'm a DJ
oh yeah it's it's kind of you
know it's kind of there maybe a
splash is she done drinking at this
point no how long does she
drink
okay oh that's perfect
that's perfect oh wait wait wait wait
wait let's flush the toilets
here wait that could be the drinking
sound but okay I already put a lot of
like effort into placing
those okay no wait the placement of the
flushing toilet should be when the when
the camera is on mining Senai so that
you see her drinking and
then like
here goody in the back is like already
releasing releasing the the alcohol oh
oh oh oh you cut to her too
early that's
okay and then she sees
something and she's like a yo here and
she
whistles
yes she's whistling towards that what's
whatever she's
seeing and then as a response we hear a
zombie so that gives you this feeling
that the the maybe in the next movie the
one piece is going to be a fight between
a zombie and gur and manin interesting
that we can you know do some fighting
scenes the zombies are protecting the
one piece and they have to kill the one
the the the the zombie in order to get
the one piece Peak Cinema
[Music]
yeah or this sound is good to throwing
up yeah somebody said
vomiting oh I love
it if only we could film this in color
but maybe that's why that's why hair
colors don't matter yet
but I wish we had more hairstyles I love
the little
steps nice
conversation this is them getting to
work
yeah oh oh that's that's probably where
it is H what okay what did I think when
I put this in I don't like
it I don't like it
um but there's not
much ah when she points
maybe like Little
hits let's see if this
fits nice sound effects I'm so good at
sound
effects wait wait wait wait wait wait
she does like a triple there can we have
the boo again it's the
spring have a singular
spring how I get closer again to
this
here I love
it let's
makeer this hit a bit shorter can I can
I
not
wait this needs to be a bit earlier here
done
okay don't
it's a bit delayed but it's hard to make
it like closer
[Music]
wait how's this work where's the actual
sound
happening like
here no that's just the aftermath of
that sound
this go
work sound design is my passion if she's
slamming the table really hard she's
she's passionate about this you
know all right all right all right all
right I mean I think I put enough work
into this
movie I love the drinking
sounds sometimes you just just have to
you know use whatever you
have and try your best to work with that
uh wait no how do I save oh yeah
save okay if this is not an absolute
Banger of a movie that I don't [\h__\h]
know but I'm one thing I'm thinking
right now is
like do I still have to exchange the
camera and are they starting filming ex
no they're not they're first writing the
script so we might be
[Music]
fine now I wonder what is foley sounds
if I already did my own
sfx is this just like the own sfx that I
do maybe don't affect the sales at all I
have to add one of these things to
actually get a boost in like Revenue
yeah probably just for the
stats then I will I will assign someone
for this
stuff what I I I want to see what this
is I don't I wonder if we'll see this in
the final product or if it will not make
a
difference
okay
Kuna ah
ah ah
ah mine is dilemma too
ah perfect
title okay I think this is good to
go now
CH
oh Mama Mia we're in the 1950s and we
were filming with this shitty camera all
over
long from the
20s oh m m o this one is actually more
expensive it's even though it's 3 years
older maybe I should put that one in
there oh but I can't cuz I didn't unlock
it okay I'll put this one
in can I not put a second one of the
same in
there oh I can
okay
ah and I won my is maybe
ah I didn't do any of
this
ah okay but I didn't unlock this yet I
only unlocked uh
rain but I don't need rain
yet
so finally getting the times oh they're
probably going to give me much better
critiques for this
one
oh okay how can I
[Music]
see
my other
movies again I yeah here uh I'm scared
because I didn't do the editing but it
it should be okay let's see Kiana frame
production presents M stemma this is
hard to read staring
M ah what do I do I'm so alone and I'm
just a cosplayer but I want to be a real
pirate AO that's what I want to yell out
into the world but ah I need to practice
my AO nobody will believe me everybody
will just make up a cosplayer but I'm a
real pirate I can be a real pirate what
if what if I just go out in the world
and find someone H how do I find someone
maybe I should put it out in the in the
newspaper that I'm looking for a
companion to go out uh to get a ship and
then find the one piece yes that's right
that's a good idea surely someone will
sign up to be my companion yo let's go
such a great genius idea I will be the
best pirate all over the world and I
will be the owner of the one piece the
one and only let's
go I got a goal
wo uh
awkward ending play the credits play the
credits come on just imagine the CRS ah
no that's an outake you weren't supposed
to show that the way she's getting
up that was good that was good oh I'm
really excited for the next one though
because they will hopefully film that
with better the better stuff
so I think that's going to be
good and now we got money we can pay
people and stuff everything's going to
be better from now
on how's our re research going 2,800
okay okay we're filming go and m s by
ons set oh now she has gray
hair they're just repeating the scene
don't look this is like professionals at
work right
now I really want to see
this last silent
film there shouldn't even have been one
in the first
place if you think about it oh we should
set up a a marketing Strat for this one
right away and I'm going to go for an
expensive one because this one's going
to be worth
it this one should be worth it although
that's
actually
20 wait this is not even worth it 20 to
40%
but you pay way more while this is 25 to
50% what the [\h__\h] and it it's even
longer
huh does somebody understand the meaning
of this I
don't weird then I just go with the
Billboards I like
Billboards I I like
Billboards don't we all like
Billboards all right you better work
work work work work work work work
work work
work laser
time oh are my actors sitting
together no
[Music]
I don't know which ones of my actors
are okay they're going
home wait how do I close
this you don't have any compain so you
still need
to
what press create campaign what where
[Music]
there where is the create campaign
button wait wait wait wait wait I
here
ah thank
you let's advertise the first one a
little bit just a little bit oh oh I can
okay this one so I really can only
assign one per one per thing okay that's
fine maybe we'll get more marketers
soon retroactive no not in this case in
this case the movie didn't come out yet
so we're good we're good we're
good we're
good also look at our money we're over
200k this is
good and this new movie will sell so
much
better there making the plan in sync
perfect
team how do you call the the couple of
gura and horo
Marin like Pabon Nashi for example do
they have
a like a
name for just those
two ma
ma ma ma m I don't know wait those
cameras are
sexy
wow they look
nice
sheesh oh yeah and that fake lightning
or is that real where is the
lightning that one up there I don't know
if it's doing anything GA
Marin they need a better couple
name samin
ding ding ding
ding finish filming let's go let's go
post production
all wait we can finish today maybe
oh monkey monkey monkey monkey come on
come on come on you're almost done Matt
painting uzo a few more seconds
releasing tomorrow yay we finished it
for the deadline of today good job guys
good freaking
job
oh crybaby is making
money this is
okay I am curious about this one wait I
could already watch it
right we can watch it are you
ready okay here we go
C production birday present manma to ah
starving goba and man hello ah oh my God
it's you did you sign up to become my
companion yes I did all right then let's
become a team let's plan how to find the
one piece it must be here no it must be
here no I think it's here oh I think
it's here okay I'm pretty sure it's
there here right here you get it okay
this is where we're going to go tomorrow
for real
uh so yeah uh wait good why are you
drinking I I need some more confidence I
I I will be more helpful if I drink some
nice shark
juice I feel
funny all right let's let's uh look out
for the Sharks and the one piece I think
is it
there that's it that must be it oh my
God it's zombies the end
Oscar
incoming let's go beautiful movie Master
PE bravo bravo
bravim
okay I am proud of us for making that
beautiful piece of a
movie I think the only thing's missing
is the final
[Music]
part oh oh oh oh wait those those still
look shitty what the
[\h__\h] what what do you want from me
48 it was completely murdered by m
gara's performance reminded me of TV
commercials just because you can stand
in front of a camera it doesn't mean you
can act no GAA don't listen to them I
Believe In You Beautiful premise
excellent idea all butchered by you guys
guys again back at it again with a fair
albit very forgettable result it's a
shame to to see his talent go to
waste wait but wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait why I I used way better
like tech technical
things right wait I forgot what did it
look
like wait why is it still this shouldn't
it be in or should it be in color no it
definitely looks better quality right
than the other one
oh yeah oh yeah it does okay no color
yet in
1950 they're so harsh what can I
do what can I
do it's okay the money will come in
anyway maybe this is like something that
can't be helped when you don't have
famous actors yet in this game and like
famous everything just like a beginning
of the game kind of thing
wa oh I mean 11 isn't too bad and their
rankings are also pretty [\h__\h] what how
did this
47 quality movie make it up to number
two how
there is sequels or prequels can I set
that I didn't see any way to set
[Music]
it technical is so low what do you
mean I could I I could and maybe I
should do scene
retakes what the
hell I mean this I understand because we
didn't have practical effects but we had
a nice microphone it's only up to 1%
though what can I do add like 10
microphones or what do you want from me
why are they so angry
too how can I make them less angry when
filming
this am I missing an entire te tree Tech
Tree screen no way are you saying that
because you you know that's
true uh where was
it no
no
no I think I looked at
everything
no lights I I did get one
light which is the most recent light we
could have
gotten m
not sure I mean I I do think this might
just be like a like a training thing
like we need to train them and we need
to make them famous we need to promote
them and maybe do retakes and
stuff yeah 1% is like there is no
microphone but there is one that's the
mic maybe a second one one but I mean I
don't understand how that would impact
it that
much oh wow I do wonder how I can set it
as a sequel a
prequel oh you guys already back oh
wow uh we're not going to make a movie
right away uh we're going to
H how do I set the quality of the food
here
again how do I do that
uh I should train her maybe no yeah I
don't know maybe cuz we're not filming
today we can do
that educate sure Ed educate
sure and why not apparently it doesn't
cost
money so I'll do
it oh unable oh is the classroom full oh
Mama
Mia uh uh
can I add another of
these
[Music]
yes can I move
them just make a little bit more space
here can they reach that
just want to minmax the space
here hey that's how FR how close you
want to sit to the the front of the
classroom yes yes I want to sit this
close please thank
you all right all right all right all
right all right
[Music]
surely that will
work for the students with bad eyesight
yeah I'm so
considerate okay some are still unable
uh do I really need a second one
Mama Mama
Mia uh
classroom m
[Music]
okay that should be good enough for now
why is it so big ah go away
how are we doing
here the
first
what how did this movie make
220k with equipment from the 20s used in
the
50s what's happening here oh I need
another
teacher which can just be this
one but yeah she doesn't come until
tomorrow too bad but there's like one
space here and
here what do you want Bob where are
you can I move
you
no marketed is
retro people have Nostalgia
already didn't you advertise it no
apparently I
didn't advertise this one though oh wait
it's oh never mind I I I looked the
wrong
way 220k and then here is 241 I mean
that's a little bit better I I would
think it would do even better but
apparently this is the
best but I
mean I think we're doing fine for
ourselves our studio worth is really
high too
wow this is all looking really
nice you
know I want to hire maybe
another marketing
person so they
can Market more stuff
basically can they work in the same
room probably not can I extend it for
sure for sure
I like
this
sounds here no stop
there and then how do I get rid of this
wall
[Music]
[Applause]
on let's let's watch the paint dry M you
like that huh don't
you and then we're just going to put
these
things
maybe sideways and then we can put so
many more of these here in the
future yes oh yeah
yeah that's enough space for four
marketing
people can they walk through
probably is this like I wonder if this
is necessary like one one per marketer
but I'll at least put one more
out e looks
good h
eventually I should probably just have
made bigger ones but you know it was the
beginning so you don't think that
far but eventually if we could like put
five producers or so into one room like
this that would be
good stun but no I think I think this is
looking very good generally
okay shut the [\h__\h] up Bobby Perry just
go
home just go
home everybody just go
home
okay
[Music]
500k ah Auto assign you can work here
right uh
o might want to get more researches too
so we get more points faster I feel like
if you start from the 20s then by now by
the 50s you would already have like 20
researchers or so normally if you start
from the
beginning let's promote
gura
and with a radio
interview sounds
[Music]
good that should be
fun good I will have fun with
that whoa wait why is Bob what's wrong
with Bobby
Perry what you just
can I like reset what you're supposed to
be
doing
um stop maybe start again can you go
now I think he went yeah that's him okay
he was just bugging out would be good if
there was like a a quick way to reset
somebody like just by like like right
clicking them or something
that' be
good what version of Sims is
this no no the discs were fine it was
probably just because I was like
resetting things and rebuilding things
while they were already in there which
is
understandable okay so today is another
everybody learns something kind of
day
um I could hire one more marketer
[Music]
um it seems to be super random who you
get because I imported these
people and they're not showing
up or do I oh wait okay Yago is here
very
expensive I don't know if I'm ready
to we doing need another actor to play
the zombie
but I don't know
[Music]
or we could change the whole
thing yeah it's it wasn't a zombie it
was just Yago and then go to yo he has
the one piece they fight
him and after they fought
him the one piece is basically
cover and they joined cover after they
fought
him
because he wasn't going to let them but
cover joining cover is basically just
like cover equals the the ship the
pirate ship you know that's the name of
the pirate ship and Yago has it and they
want it so they have to fight him to
take over his ship exactly oh that makes
so much sense
I'm
cooking but he's so expensive but he's a
beister this might automatically make
the movie really
good so you're hired yo congratulations
you're going to play
yourself look at
him just look at him what a good fine
man
M okay tomorrow we'll film the final
movie and that will be the end of the
stream good free movies and a whole
studio built actually Four movies but
we're going to ignore this filmer uh the
filler
movie filler film
filmer are they just training endlessly
until I tell them to stop no right they
they have a a goal I
think why is why are you so
unhappy is it the pay how do I ask
them H they want better housing they had
they didn't have
food employees unhappy with the food how
do I change the food uh is there
somebody who
knows how to change the food in the
[Music]
canteen um
schedule ah yeah
right
here that should make them decently
happy I
hope they're actually eating right now
but I don't think they'll get
the uh
I don't think that let me what is this
what does this mean you need to go to
the toilet it's plenty of toilets
there okay wait so did that change
already oh no wait oh 5% was he less
happy
before or is this still the
same what's if Bobby Perry better
housing okay they all want better
housing so am
I how do I give you guys better
housing how do I move you into a housing
at
all and what does better mean these
[Music]
are not even this is a poorest area so
how about Green
Springs no
oh I can he probably does want uh some
place
to sleep
in
a wait so far they didn't have any place
to stay in
oopsie oh I can't put anyone in here I
can only put people here
e but I can't put like GAA for example
in this one it's like she only deserves
the one star place apparently it has a
minimum required
Fame ah this ah this is minimum required
Fame
be okay I get it now I see
it that should make them happier that
they have a place to sleep
in
right there cheaper
places maybe
not anybody else that I have that needs
to live somewhere aister no I don't have
anything like
that shees the Pinnacle Hills are going
to be where you want to
go
okay
so he
it wait what it went
up okay but that's just food
related that's also just food
related that's also just food related
okay oh
good no issues affecting
happiness what is it going up right now
wait ah wait it's going up AKA
is it going towards it's going higher
but it means not higher as in they got
more angry it's going closer to being
happier okay okay okay it's changing
right now yeah yeah yeah yeah it's
changing okay now I get it I thought
like they were increasing in in
unhappiness what are what get get happy
come
on come on okay this should this should
be really good and maybe they'll perform
better maybe they'll act better when
they're happier that makes sense
right that would make total
[Music]
sense a little campaign for her
maybe okay do we want to make a movie
yes want to make the
movie
Marin
dilemma uh from a to Y maybe because of
Yago I don't know
[Music]
or the one
piece it's a a way to write it to not uh
get any anybody angry about me copying
something no in the 1950s one piece
didn't exist yet I'm pretty
sure so this this time we do action and
pirate and
thism medium
budget
um
conflict story dialogue lore
suspense this is not there maybe maybe
some
atmosphere
okay no it's a one part finale cuz I
want to finish this whole series up
today okay oh I can uh only have maximum
free anyway that's
perfect why is she wearing stuntman
cloes also look at her shitty no wonder
my moves are shitty when the only trait
she has is
slacker
wow oh this is already a stunt scene
isn't it jump and fall 5% plus five
what is it just like when I add a stunt
scene it looks like this okay let's
see oh wow wa whoa whoa what's going on
here we're already in the middle of it
bro
um okay chill the [\h__\h] out stop shooting
uh
instead
walk
uh wait now it's probably going to be
difficult to move you
[Music]
again oh wait
okay but good I will be walking drunk of
course she's not really walking though
is
she not very
effectively maybe she'll walk normally
then they walk together looks good looks
cool oh okay yeah
oh yeah so they are on their
way yes yes yes yes they're in
sync they corra the whole thing and then
guess who
appears maybe they shouldn't even be in
this scene wait
just
him maybe what if he sneaks up to them
there's a sneak I think sneakily walking
yo is sneaking
around he like a Golem
walking ooh
squat doing the squats
okay wonderful so now it's the
confrontation
maybe oh who the [\h__\h] is that oh my
stuntman
oh oh it requires a
stuntman or actor oh yeah yeah this is
the stunt we're going to we're going to
have where where is everybody else
h ah it's because
H wait there are no triple scenes though
huh no triple
animations how am I going to do this
with three
people where's
yo maybe we should do it without it
being a
stunt but it's I think it requires say
stun
scene you always have one off camera
what you can create two separate scenes
and cut between them no but they're
supposed to fight each other all
together no that kind of sucks I don't
even see yagle here I can't even choose
I mean I guess I could get rid of one of
them and for now it would it will just
be Ming and she
fights oh
dear this actually kind of
funny but then GAA is not involved at
[Music]
all should they box it out
that's too fast like he's already going
down there maybe just
brawl oh
wow
okay okay that's pretty cool we shake a
little bit too
and then GAA will also join
for some
fighting will be yagu and
gaura
uh they're going to
do where's yagle here he'll show up
they're going to
do the pirate gunfight maybe should have
been the other way around but it's
okay and we'll cut to the actors
mhm I don't know what the linger time
does to be
honest okay thises 20% does this mean
that it's difficult for them to do I
wonder and then ah wait I want to move
them ah I I could probably move it
afterwards what's with all these scenes
No
huh wait one two wait it kind of reset
my scene again is this a
bug no reset my
scene
[Music]
no this is the
walking this is the
sneaking um
man but okay before I set up
these I guess I should add or uh wait
never mind no need to add it maybe I'll
just use
these and we'll put them in the right
order when we're editing the
movie wait this this works fine it
doesn't have to be a stunt
scene yeah this is good this is already
perfect the way it is
can you move to Yago
too they're not moving to
Yago let me move him oops
[Music]
see aato is below me
hello chunky
wonky okay how about
this
ah there we
go there we go there we go that works
okay that's that and
then they he
dies uh is is there a
die die from stabbing okay suddenly we
go from gunfight to this kind of death
that's
perfect and then do we have a
stab oh
yeah oh
yeah
wow what what can M do should choose dab
from behind or should she watch
or do a superhero air
kick wait why is she
there
ye it's a bit
fast she doesn't a bit early but that's
okay
maybe it need to be a bit more over
[Music]
here yeah and then G car I was thinking
so too at the end he's going to be
carried
out that's a good animation there
there I think
[Laughter]
it's like M's cake does nothing to
him oh yeah oh that's actually a good
pan it's
beautiful and
uh wait did it reset my
no ah wait I didn't do them
yet am I even going to do them because H
do I need
them let's finish the last normal scene
possibly last one where
Yago
um no what was it
uh maybe M cuz she seems a bit stronger
she's going to
carry wasn't there a
carry oh was that in the stunt scene
because there are there even double
[Music]
no it wasn't here I'm pretty sure what
was it called maybe something with
walking
walk sneaky walking with money
bag I mean the money could represent
the
treasure but wasn't there the body
thing CPR
uh
body yeah it was probably in the stunt
scenes H wait this maybe unnecessary cuz
you already kind of died but oh okay
this is just a yeah he falls
down this is
chaotic good just won't stop
shooting what should we do in this
[Music]
scene examine with stos
scope he's already dead GAA you shot him
like 300 times
oh let's go Victory
celebration and M carries the the bag of
cash let's
go okay she carries the cash out and
then in the last scene as a stunt scene
will have GAA carry yle out on her body
[Laughter]
[Music]
nice
okay
um
y was it carry yeah carrying
body oh I didn't even have to choose who
carries who they got it right
immediately I wouldn't have known how to
choose it
anyway Kaa what have you done what have
you
done
spooky threatening
Aura she looks happy yeah she did that
I'm proud of
her um did we want to add we should add
them right the fighting scenes
those two were
brawling as I
remember and then one more this is not
in the right order now
obviously GAA and yo what were they
doing were they having a sword fight or
no I think I made them do the Western
Duell at first
maybe she's the one who stabs him right
so sword fight would make somewhat
sense
maybe
maybe let's do the
cut too bad she's like as tall as him
that's not really
fitting okay I think I got all the SE I
can't edit wait why what's the problem
ah because probably
this extra
scene if I remove this it doesn't remove
anything else
right it
one one two three four and two
St didn't I
have didn't I have free Stone
scenes huh what what is
this what is
this it says free sty SC but I
don't it may have wiped one huh wa wait
we
have yeah I I guess I did that many
fighting SE we don't even need that one
to be honest that's another fighting
scene was the walking
scene and that's the sneaky
scene yeah what what is gone ah the
victory scene of them like walking away
is gone bro I was just going to get rid
of
the the one like empty scene because I
think it wouldn't let me move
on how do I when I remove something it
removes more than I want and then it
resets [\h__\h] what am I supposed to
do I don't know if I'm using it wrong
but I don't think so
oh extra scenes do not affect the
filming time or quality of the product
what I'm putting so much effort into
this but it's just for my own
satisfaction H Okay I uh what did I do
let's see
uh I just want
to okay maybe we'll just try to make it
work like this without the extra stuff
I'll just set this
let's just do the the victory scene cuz
that one disappeared and that one's
[Music]
important requires one oh ah right this
one only cuz it's a it's a it's a scene
that has to have a stunt so I can kind
of only do two people maximum in that
[Music]
scene which is sad
what if I
add I don't want two
normals okay okay we'll make this work
we'll make it
work H I thought this was a stunt scene
what I'm so
confused okay now it's Ming carrying him
that's fine
[Music]
what do I need to
redo gooda walks away with the money
Yago dead
Mar
uh Victory
celebration uh it's it's changing
again
okay I don't care anymore it's making me
redo it too many
times okay how about this
he dies she celebrates She carries the
money for mine because in the end she's
you know the helper so that that makes
sense in its own
way did I always have this ex scene
still I'll fill this up and then it
should be nothing
left there shouldn't be anything else
otherwise it's bugged for sure what can
we do in this one scene what else do we
we
[Music]
need ah maybe a Yago scene did we
already do this or did it disappear did
we have a scene where he just
dies I think not
[Applause]
maybe or did
we I no how about a kissing
scene they made another W yeah they did
it's a spiritual successor
I don't know if if we don't have it then
now we have it if we did have it then I
can just not use it I think in the
editor or it's just another another
cut perfect okay now we can edit it
hooray I'm not going to put sound
effects this
time too much work but the order the
order is important let's get rid of this
and start from scratch
H so what's the first scene them walking
in right although I I love my walking
sound effects but we'll have to deal
without um wait we got we we need
jle did we not have a yo sneaking scene
I guess that was was that in the second
movie let's just start shooting I
guess should we just he dies I think
several
times okay let's just start shooting
him and
then Ah Ah that's the scene where he's
sneaking but I forgot to remove the
shooting of GAA like GAA
shooting ah
[Music]
and he sneaks for quite a while it's
like
whatever can
I let's fix this which one is
it not this one is it this one oh yeah
if I remove
her and then maybe this makes a a bit of
sense I don't know does it make
sense they're walking in he's sneaking
in but this scene is way too
[Music]
long and then and then we start shooting
anyway and we started
[Music]
blasting PE PE and
then on
next he dies so many
times okay I think this one should be
next and in that scene he does
die but he also dies in this
scene
and and then you will also die in the
I mean I think that's uh a common thing
like several Death Scenes to make it
more
dramatic and
then he shall be carried out by Min
Senai I think that's all the scenes
one two 3 4 5 6
7 okay this is a real action
movie Yago sneaking in he doesn't want
to be seen but we have found him and we
start shooting and kicking and
stabbing die
die and he dies but he dies again more
dramatically this is like the different
angle
totally oh no oh I will have to give
them my one piece which is cover and
there we go celebrating once again the
death and the the accession of um cover
and the ship the imaginary ship and one
piece and we'll take his body at least
[Music]
to just just put it on our ship if
anybody asks like hey this ship belongs
to Yago no what where is Yago oh he's
just sleeping look he's in his bed ah
okay everything is fine
then
yeah sound is there gun sound effects
there's
[Music]
explosions no
guns wait I think this is the one sound
effect that I need
[Music]
[Laughter]
a
yep here
wait some foot
steppies oh that's a that's actually
working pretty well like
that more foot
steppies all right
here right right
here Steppy
steppies I wish I could wait I think I
can copy but I can't copy like several
ones that would be good if you can
select several
ones and copy and paste all of them at
once I said I was not going to do sound
effects but here I am
[Music]
there might be too many footsteps
actually let's
see H not well timed
[Laughter]
okay uh ooh explosions should fit well
in here no
maybe oh I didn't expect
that how how do I get like a
quick
uh maybe
some that that fits the rifle or the
shot shotgun the shotgun matches
[Music]
that
[Laughter]
wait do you need anything else here
oh this is
good I should I should become a movie
director and
sfx person
[Laughter]
oh
wow this is amazing
actually that sound effect but we don't
need it that's good I wish it was like a
woohoo let's
go oh there's oh there's blood sounds ah
man ah my sounds my sounds are funnier
[Music]
is there a good moment where I could
Implement that
it's perfect wait one more
[Music]
maybe wait wait
here Yo's body is so [\h__\h] heavy
damn those muscles are made out of
steel wait what's going on here she's
just celebrating is there anything I
could do
[Music]
here ah
maybe maybe she's like whistling out of
Happiness
yeah it
matches it kind of matches
good good good
good I think I don't even need to voice
over this one this is perfect with sound
effects
[Laughter]
yeah okay oh all
right I could not be happier with
this we don't need a voice over the
special effects are making this the best
thing I've ever seen and heard and
witnessed but there's a lot of shooting
maybe it shouldn't be General audiences
what would this be in like normal
reality
pg14 it's so goofy right look like a
meme video it is a meme the whole movie
is a [\h__\h] meme it should be a comedy
movie no it's as serious I as I can make
it PG for
okay it better be5
billion it better be I mean we have a be
Lister in here now among our ranks so
here we go the one PC by the way means
the One You're supposed to read it as
the one
piece
yeah all right get to work that's going
to be worth my time I would hope uh wait
do I have to uh stop them
[Music]
from I think I have to stop them from
training who are you or wait wait where
are my
people who are you guys
wait where are my where are my
actors where are you oh you are you're
training right now okay
stop okay what about everybody
else
stop stop
M are you guys doing something are you
guys doing something no are you doing
something are you doing something
stop is that all the people I need I
hope oh W that was fast what the [\h__\h]
okay we're
filming okay now I might want to retake
some scenes when they don't look so good
but generally I think this will already
be better because the actors are also in
a better mood
are you guys wait what are you waiting
for waiting for crew oh [\h__\h] where's the
crew what everybody just stop what are
you
doing what are
you crew where is this crew person how
do I know you are you're a
crew stop and you are another crew
okay now you can start right
okay
okay let's
go is this Phoenix then this is this is
way better than phoenixon I must
say good good doing interviews no
seemingly not I think that's just like
they kind of do that behind the scenes
maybe oh no what is this let them eat
bread
MMA the one piece became to be one of
the most anticipated titles and the
appearance of Yago motaki is one of its
selling points there's a lot of
anticipation and the marketers seem
satisfied with the audience's pulse
while the atmosphere is light and jolly
there's more than the usual commotion on
set
uhoh actors are nagging staff is
displeased the director is always
mad hiding in scream for hours on end
the source of trouble quickly becomes
apparent
Yago do you call it acting Yago shouts
to one of the of
course no I think this scene is meant to
portray the futility of existence yeah
oh that was the other one okay Yago
disagrees with the director why don't we
do a closeup to my face here Yago
instructs the camera crew everyone is
obviously he's a
diva ah displeased by this Behavior an
action needs to be taken immediately oh
no let's choose the right thing you need
to learn to cooperate uh if you want to
be part of this movie otherwise I need
to I'm glad someone's taking initiative
keep up the good work I trust your
judgment everyone seems displeased can
you turn it down and not we can arrange
a bigger salary that matches your talent
and status if it will secure your
coroporation raise
salary uh I mean that would certainly
work but not sure if that's the best you
saying
to but then that's just like I'm
pleasing the diva and that's like maybe
can do that
behind like like kind of like
lying just to please the diva but in
reality I'm going to go to the others to
the crew and be like sorry about his
attitude but but but he's just going to
continue doing that and they're going to
be displeased and it's not going to be
good right it's going to hurt the others
yeah I think I'll just pay him I got the
money
yeah okay good yo just wanted the money
I'm fine with that okay how do you do
scene retakes again oh wait what's
happening now waiting for
actors
what oh there he is okay 59 ah here okay
59 is not bad is
it okay we won't even finish this next
scene I can look at all the scenes in
the end and we'll decide if we have to
reshoot some of them
okay what do you mean what's
wrong
what unable to reach the canteen table
this
one what about the other canteen oh it's
full CH I'll make it bigger I'll make it
bigger
[Music]
cuz we have space all the way over
here
yeah like this
maybe oh
yeah
spacious are we in outer space or what
let's give it the
same
colors it's getting cute yeah the Sims
yeah people honestly they come in here
and think this is the
Sims I get
it I get
it it's not though it is not
[Music]
okay now we can get these further apart
I don't know why you would not get to
that honestly that annoys me that you're
not able to do that
anyway but
okay you do
[Music]
you all right I'm not going to touch it
anymore I don't want to [\h__\h] it up while
the people are
eating
okay people should be fine now I think
what was
that this one will have to be like not
extended because I think I think
extending is difficult here but I can
make a second one in the
future oh yielding plus free hype oh
good eyes a
beister oh that means she's moving into
here here I
think yeah good you've made what a do I
have to like kick her out of her current
place okay don't worry I'm terminating
your lease just because I'm moving you
right over to a better place don't you
worry Gooby B only the best house for
you mhm she's making
it she is becoming big in the industry
as expected I knew she would be a star I
knew it I want all the
credit oh yeah she became a beister
during the movie shooting so I would
hope it would affect it because they
didn't even finish filming
it I also want to see how this movie
does hell
yeah okay welcome back oh now Marine is
doing the radio interview but she
finished it really fast
okay and we're back
filming very
nice ooh scene rating 62 is that because
she got
better oh what is it now illegal
poaching M walks in with an envelope in
hand the logo nin of locomotion films is
visible on the upper left Cor that can
only mean one thing they made me an
offer after watching me and min's
dilemma too ah yeah says I'm afraid I
have to take their offer unless there's
a way to match your
salary yeah okay I need you obviously
you know exactly the right timing to hit
me with something like
this no it's okay we have money I think
this is
fine a
yeah but yeah she pisses me off she's
extorting
me look at them walking like
supermodels 53 that's a shitty one I
want to retake that
one what where are they oh there ah it's
just him
now come on Yago you're a beister you're
going to nail the scene
55% why was this one so
[Music]
good what
what she's sparkling now what do you
mean
functional yeah why are people not in
here what what's going on
huh door
[Music]
broken oh well it dis
oh N I think they're just bugging around
I can't help them
honestly why are they not just okay now
it's Laser Time
is your cook
training um
ah is my cook still
training okay I'll pay attention next
time because that one in the bottom was
not training
anymore where's
my
ah hey but I don't know wouldn't you
automatically go to the kitchen when
it's time I would hope
so oh well plus 54 oh Min became a
beister too 54% that's pretty that's
pretty amazing that's impressive wow
that radio deal did
wonders
sheesh wait where is SCA ah in here okay
damn I'm made making them famous now we
have free be listers on this
movie these next scenes better be
looking
good I need to finish this
movie
okay just one more Scene
final scene with free B listers how is
this going to look in
[Music]
percentage
oh
57 what the [\h__\h] okay we're reshooting
this one cuz we have
time let's see how much better it
gets oh film wood award ceremony is
about to
begin uh don't you won't lose your
Awards if you don't go okay I I don't
have time right now
bro I think it did not get better what
the hell
huh
okay
uh
whatever I think if it reshoots there's
still a chance as we learned in the in
the tutorial that it will not be better
and in that case they go for the better
scene Yahoo we finished it we can watch
it now what's with the [\h__\h] Cen
huh what why would you not be able to
use
this you were able to enter before just
fine I mean there's no cook yeah but you
still they should still be able to to
walk
in why are these like lit up by the way
I
wonder what does that
[Music]
mean what the is it I don't
know what does this
mean should I get rid of these
[Music]
wait what's over
here these are not shiny does that mean
something when they're shiny like
they're not
[Music]
usable this stuff is shiny too okay
wait what if I remove that wall
[Music]
no oh no I think it
no why is it like this the room is oh
why why is it set to a
lounge uh how do I set it to something
else it used to be a Cen
no can I change that I mean it has the
kitchen
how does it how does it how does it
become
a is it because I put I put these like I
copy pasted these particular
ones ah I thought it wouldn't matter I
thought these were the same don't they
look the same no maybe not this
particular set of chair and
tables were only for the lounge
Mama
Mia Mama
Mia okay no more complaints please
please
H oh where's
my where's my chef
I thought I had another
cook
a I
have these two chefs no and then this
person is the lounge
person yeah yeah yeah but both chefs are
here this one Chef instead of cooking is
about to be eating
bro get to work
Randol may you could you
please what is wrong with
[Music]
you
why but even if I hire someone now yeah
he will only arrive
tomorrow oh my God can I move these
like can I move a
person no I don't think
so it is what it is I need to assign him
again
how
ah random
ah ah
is she going to okay at least he
teleports over
there sometimes Min Al what do you mean
when did she become a [\h__\h] aist or
what what
what what when that when did that happen
what
what I have to move her already shees
wait alist just down here
bro whatever she's doing is working so
well for her what the hell teach me one
of the ways that I'm using on on my
stars I don't even know how am I doing
this what is this
radio sheesh I guess because the radio
thing is like a free day
thing so the effects from that continue
for a
while oh my mov
[Music]
critics
oh oh my God wait wait hold
W oh my
God I finally get what I deserve relying
on Marin's talent to turn a half done
job into a blogbuster might have worked
in the past but audiences need okay [\h__\h]
you like a Thanksgiving dinner warm and
conforting but never surprising a tried
and test okay he what Bobby Perry
finally makes his long awaited
directorial debut eh really a perfectly
executed idea despite the man okay this
one sounds good for the fans of action
Min dilemma the one piece is as good as
it
gets all [\h__\h] right guys we have
taken over the
movies
y woo
I'm not going to look at this and think
too much about it I want to watch my
movie now thank you do you guys want to
watch it in
order all right this is the first one
where
minin our pirate is
devastated she wants to find a new
purpose in life she's failing as a
pirate because she's just a cosplayer
and she's like ah what do I
I need to um I need to practice my AO I
need to find a crew where am I going to
find a crew and with the crew that I
will find I need to find the one piece
oh yeah that's right the one piece what
is that even I don't know but I'm going
to go find it all right time to find the
crew that's the first step let's
[Music]
go I'm so ready for this oh
Shak yeah she's celebrating a lot oh
now I'm on my way to post an article on
the newspaper looking for a
companion uh cut please cut cut why you
guys not cutting what the [\h__\h] the end
yo amazing and then second
one this was already a big step up min's
dilemma too
ah starring M and Gaa Gaa walks in oh my
God are you signing up for being my
companion yes I am ah oh my God I'm in
love with you let's make a plan the one
piece is here and cover is here Yago is
here that bastard he has the ship that I
want I want it give it to me let's go
are you ready for
this first let me hydrate and get some
confidence out of this alcohol out of
this nice little booze shark
juice Dam I don't know if I made the
right choice with this
companion but okay let's go let's look
out oh sorry I just had to go to the
toilet really quickly
ski okay I think I found him I found the
one
piece or is it a
zombie no it's not don't worry guys it's
Yago let's watch my hit movie K
Production presents M's dilemma the one
piece staring M Guna and
Y no voice over
[Music]
necessary dies threee
times dramatically
yo are you
[Music]
okay let's
go we got the money we got the ship we
got the one
piece we got
Yago the
[Music]
end amazing
what a that's the best trilogy trilogy
trilogy trilogy that I have ever
witnessed in my whole life Mama Mia that
is going to get me some good
money life
changing Honestly though we have a story
line an actual story line what else
could you be asking for we got action we
got drama we got suspense we got
T of course it's better than Lord of the
Rings
M the first was lacking well that was
because shitty cameras and
stuff oh oh the first day it made
429,000
sales let's
go so wait the first day that means
yesterday at the end of the day cuz I I
released it at the end of the day
I guess it doesn't matter oh look at
that
sparkly mding hor mdy hor
[Music]
mdy she is sparkly as [\h__\h] G also pretty
damn sparkly holy
[\h__\h] okay I
think everybody's just chilling
everybody's just vibing I'm good with
that let's save holy [\h__\h]
besides the long tutorial session I
think I mean that's kind of necessary
you know but I want a little bit too in
detail of
something
yeah I am a Movie
Maker those were some nice works best
works of my
life I I feel more accomplished than
ever
wait did I save proper let's save
again Windows Movie
Maker I am the Windows Movie
Maker
exactly no I love this this is like
legit this is the
movies I haven't played the OG in a
million years so I can't
really compare
properly but it feels the same it looks
the
same I think like the movie making is
probably a little bit more intricate I
don't remember sound effects and
stuff um but maybe there's certain
features that I just didn't even know
about in the
OG uh but yeah this is uh incredible it
feels the same right hard to beat the
original I don't know I feel like this
is the same like to me like playing this
a million years later it just feels the
same
kind of kind of I
[Music]
mean actually I mean maybe not the same
but like definitely very similar and it
it it uh fixes that
urge of wanting to play the movies on a
stream I'm looking at pictures of the
game right now of the
OG yeah that was that some good stuff
that was
fun it was so dorky everything was so
dorky back
then
maybe I I think we reached a a similar
level of dorkiness today at kata's film
Productions scratching the it
pycho might pick it up for myself
really by the way I know you sent like a
rainbow but I can't read it
today um it's already really late I'm
going to stream again tomorrow tomorrow
will be that like uh part-time working
game or something like
that I'll set up the stream tomorrow
when I wake up I
think the wild already on the game ah
there's like the the the whole thing
with the
scenes messes me up a little bit like
that annoys me a little bit I feel like
that must be a bug it's a bit confusing
how that's going on but besides that you
know like some things are a little bit
weird like just now it got it really
confused me with like the canteen but I
guess that was my fault but it it was
just like a different set of tables that
look so similar
uh they should just let me use any kind
of table in
there but yeah once once you guys helped
me out then it was pretty understandable
um since the sign was the signed for the
lounge so it makes sense it makes
sense a little bit fiddly but yeah it's
often easier to work in an actual editor
than in some of those simplified game
editors not sure what you mean
you still need to make a movie of yeah
yeah yeah yeah today we focused on the
Marin GAA
mon you like the stream really I'm glad
I'm glad this is like basically like me
playing
Sims
basically oh smovie what's
[Music]
wrong kind of chill kind of
chill but also nice uh Productions came
out of
it the sound effects were
great I wish there were more there needs
to be like just some like talking sounds
like just mixed talking over one
another thank you for watching today
everybody I had a good time ohow that is
5 and a half hours didn't expect it to
be that long hope you guys had fun and
German and I'll see you
tomorrow and
cut bye my merch by my merch here
[Music]
honey night is
my go