Yes, yes, yes, yes, that's a piece of tiki, yes, yes.
Yes yes Oyori's food one name yes yes
Yes, yes, help, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, help.
Kiyo, yes, yes, yes, why are you crying?
Yes, yes, making cute games, yes, yes
Yes, it's okay.
Yay Maria had mayonnaise is a drink
By the way, Fushi is air, so Osa Tenma Frozen
I hear you always have udon on hand?
Lighting complete 9 Yes, yes, it's the cook.
It was a [ __ ], but it was better than a [ __ ].
Coby
Yes, I can make it, is it okay?
Yes yes yes yes no
No, yes, yes, yes, yes, I have it.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, Khufu's lo is yes
Yes yes yes amo
Oh yes yes yes yes
Sayata Maria Mayonnaise is a drink
By the way, I'm a face, ok big brother
I always have frozen udon on hand.What do you think?Yes.
My combat power is 540,000. Yes, yes, next.
It's Nohato, yes, yes, it's Ichimi-cho, yes.
Yes, it's bamboo. Yes, yes, yes, it's there.
Wow
5050 iiiiiifi jump is not a vehicle
No, it's Fufuifukoramen.
Can I rain your tail too?
Yes, yes, yes.
Everyone, come and support OroLive 6th Generation
This is Koyori from Phlox's Zuno White Coat.
Yo Everyone 6 Generation of Hara
Live Enbrain of Phlox My
White coat from name Izuku here
Sorry for having to rush an hour earlier.
Hey, today I was at work and had to go home.
I didn't know if I would make it in time though.
Go home in time for 6pm.
Now that I'm here, there are a lot of things I want to prepare.
It took about an hour.
I want to start early
Thank you, thank you, and thank you.
I haven't been home yet, so here's the archive.
So thank you to everyone who's watching.
Right after the cat, from 7pm.
A lot of things will happen until then.
I want to make various preparations, so let's start right away.
Let's start streaming today.
Participate in the battle with the strongest weapons and armor from the opening of the Nether.
It's probably 6pm to get ready.
I just posted a post that started distribution, so I reposted it.
Thank you very much Honde
enter
Puppuaah, I was just drinking soup.
But I haven't finished drinking it yet because of my cat tongue.
I want to keep doing it while drinking soup every now and then.
I think so.
Actually, it's raining a lot
It's raining ominously in this town.
I've never seen it rain this much
do not have
Oh yeah, I put it on mute while I was working yesterday.
It's been a while since I put this in.
No, I'm not looking at the rain. The Nether opens today.
But what does that mean?
Monsters are coming, so wait, what do you think?
What's wrong with this? It's dangerous if I don't sleep.
It's Lului, I'm gone.
I'm just wondering what's going on.
Neoishokore
Well, first of all, let's check various things to make sure it's not a storm.
Diamond 5 to defeat the ghast you want to go to
I want about 10 souls in the Nether
I'm going to get the sand. I'll go to the Nether.
I think I can find it. I think I can go to Glowstone.
Isn't it nice? Today's story is about frogs.
egg
frog's
Eggs seem to be a bit difficult.10 This is true.
10 I actually want a nether boat
I'm waiting for you to become the first discoverer of the Nether Fortress.
Naru Diamond 30 is too bad.
That's right, everyone went to Hobo and discovered it.
He's the one aiming for number one, wait.
5 diamonds to create a potion
I'm thinking of opening a potion shop today.
You know, the three skeletons were yesterday.
I killed it but it probably won't fit
No, I just went to see the rewards from yesterday.
I would like to
Jan 21
What's better than getting 21 of them?
What did you do yesterday?
Difficult to use full body equipment
3 clouds catch about 23 enchanted books.
The dose of 10 types is about 5.
It's about 15 oh and I brought ice and it's about 7.
That's 21 now, wait, it's pretty diamonds
Okay, just wait and go to sleep. Why are you here?
Gone
It's scary, but my fear is ominously disappearing.
Drink some soup and wait.
Let's
Yoisho pet no count pet write
Because there is no
I haven't asked my wife if she wants to change her sleep.
I don't know
And now it's probably in the nether
thinking that he might go and die.
Like, if I die, please use this.
It might be a good idea to write it down.
house
Can killer whales be pets? Buy now
I've completed it, so I'll write it down as a mission.
There was something written there, so I'm sure that's it.
I didn't write it until now, since the mission is over.
I didn't write anything
It's gone, it's over
That's open and left behind. Maybe this is it.
Rami was working on something during the day, so
There is an infinite possibility
I'm the wife of a military man, so it's a little more
The legacy of the heritage store
Well,
[music]
Good job
My chest and small items are packed full.
Can you notice this?
dead
Use Darakore
Use it to turn back
Turn back
Wow, I'm scared today. I feel like someone's going to die.
I'm saying that
Sakoyo is about to die, there are 49 of them.
Well, it's not so good, but it's true
I want to make it for Rami-tan.
diamond
equipment
Oishonto
I want to put away things I don't need for now.
But my luggage is already full.
It's so busy it's hard
Neoisho
Chin Chin This is my important thing today.
It's what I want to do. I can't do what I want to do.
Doesn't it open here?
Nako's house is small
Na
I wonder what I should put in here.
I don't need it, but if you're going to the Nether, take it with you.
Is that okay? I don't need flowers.
This is not the time to do something like that.
I don't need scissors either. After this, I'll go to the Nether.
I think TTT is possible because I'm going there.
That's what I was working on this afternoon today.
I wanted to go to TTT to have my bow repaired.
That's what I want to do.
Also, a little something to everyone about last night off-stream.
I think it might not be until tomorrow
Show me what you have prepared.
It's been completed with great effort, but now there are casualties.
I know it was
Apparently the trial will start at 7pm after Yokono.
What's wrong with Twitter?
I saw something that looked like a cutout, but from here
At the trial yesterday, there were 5 people.
Please make TTT.
Wow, someone said that to themselves.
It's so small that it was cut out along with it.
It's like I predicted that Yori would die by herself.
It is written there.
That's what I mean
picture
How many below?
There's something bubbling up underneath the bottom, though.
I saw this and made this yay
This is the automatic color potion making machine.
I wonder what that is, I'm making lots of them and distributing them.
Although I wish I could
It's hardcore after all, so these materials are
It can be quite difficult, so that's who I am.
I think I might not be able to do it all.
The base of a manufacturing machine that can be easily made automatically
I made it and this is it, one button.
It's a pain to make a device with
I'll do it on a portrait stand, so I'll make it for you.
Is it convenient that everyone can make it just by pressing the button?
That's what I thought, so I made this.
So that even first-time users can understand
If you add redstone, it's better than this.
What's left of the one I happened to have here
It was 54, but I got a small redstone
Put it in here potion etc. and magma
Self-made maki to put cream etc. I'm sure
It's like that kind of rice that you often find in the countryside.
It seems like you can have it as you like.
Also, this is nether wart, nether wart.
I can only get this in the Nether, so I haven't yet.
I don't have it, so write it down, Oh Kiro-senpai.
Ah, this is my senior, not my senior, not my senior.
Hello, here we are today. What is the beginning of today?
I saw that 10 that's what I'm doing right now
I'm already streaming it right now.
Thank you for your tiredness
So I'm going to build a house for a while, maybe I'll do my best here.
It's a free world, so maybe, but around there
I think everyone should take advantage of the white space in
I think you can make it from here, thank you
Thank you. Let's cross this bridge.
Pol Pol will make Pol Pol for the person who received it.
Lunapolunapoluna's release date
I saw it tomorrow morning, it's free over there.
There are potatoes and that bed.
I think it would be convenient to get it.Okay.
Thank you, yeah
It's good again, so that's it.
Glass bottle filled with water and netherwoot
It seems like it's already included, just a little bit.
I've got everything ready for you here.
The statue stand and blaze powder This is also blaze
You can't get it unless you go to that Nether.
I wonder if there is one? If I put it there, it will come out with a click.
I made a little English version called Kuru.
I'm sorry that I wasn't able to do that.
These are probably the only ingredients I use for potions.
It's not like magma cream and slow falling.
I wonder what it is, but what do you think?
I can think of a few other things.
I don't think it's transparent, but anyway.
I got the golden carrot that I wrote about.
I thought it might come in, but there was some kind of recovery.
But the ingredients seem a bit difficult to make.
I can't make it
Hey, it's dark.Will it be dark this time?Will it be dark this time?
Tokochi also seems to be very difficult.
None
What is darkness?
Recovery, wait a minute, what?
Are you going to the underwater temple?
For now, I'll just write the calligraphy, or I'll write the experience already.
magma
Nether stuff even if it's useful in Cream Nether
Now it is not possible to make it because of the material
cloud fermentation
It would be faster if you looked into the fermentation clouds yourself.
Well, this is it.
Ah, the darkness is in the eyes of the clouds that were issued.
Um, no.
It's dark, but it's transparent, and it's a cloud issued by transparency.
My eyes are wrong, they're right, no, they're not right.
It's dark here
Transparency
That's good, don't you realize that?
It's hard to remember the ska song
Where did you get such thin slices?
I can't go in, Tsuyune.
What do you mean?
of
I've never seen it sliced.
But that's right, it's mostly that thing.
Right, it's not Endora, it's not Endora.
of the end
Come out from there
It doesn't come out of the chest, so it doesn't come out.
Okay, now TTT Where is TTT?
It was before Yahoo distribution.
I'm singing
[music]
I'm tired
Where is it?
I wonder where it's far away, so tell me where
Tetete
Where is it?
Wait, where is it written?
Na
If you know the coordinates of TTTTTT, please let me know.
I want TTT
I would appreciate it if you could give me the coordinates.
[music]
Hey, it's far away, so take a minecart and go through the Nether.
go
Well, this is what I have to play in the Nether.
Tennoyo
I'll do something else with this.
or something else
Let's get some experience points, then let's have brunch.
I think we'll get 63 if we have brunch.
I was thinking of trying to recover with TT.
I haven't heard from you for a while now.
It's that far away
Hey wait this
difference
Is there an infinite infinity? If infinity is added
I'm even happier
3661600 is really far away
Is it really far away?
silk
[music]
Touch it and you can get a diamond sword etc.
It's like that now
Isn't there a real book?Silk Touch
Other than that
It seems like you can only attach it here.
Well, it's impossible to go infinite, so get an arrow.
It means I need flint, so I need flint.
stone
Wait, I'll sell the iron I have, or I'll go home.
But I can't use it forever, so I'll have to repair it anyway.
Looks better, it has a bow repair.
hey
Okay, let's erase it a bit. I found the coordinates.
from
Good iron
of
All sold out
Oh wait.
There's more
[music]
Left hand elbow
Let's go to the left elbow, and while we're at it, we'll treat you to squid.
hand
Return hitch
It's easy to get
Lucke
Shishi's left hand is sad because the left hand is just adding it.
That's what I was looking at.I've gained a bit of experience points now.
It might be a little bit better, but it's recovering a little bit.
I might be doing it like crazy
Good
Okay, that's right. Let's dig gravel. Let's dig gravel.
That's it, Aoku.
I'm going to need gravel in the future, so I'll put it near gravel.
I think he said something like, ``I made this.''
That means there is gravel near your mouth.
So
in
Okay, this feels kind of convenient.
Teru
I'm sure I'll be able to fail.
Let's have a chat
Yoshiohana
Okay, fire stone from here.
go get it
And the stick is my own
I can't make it.The wings are from PorPor.
By the way, you can get
from it
I'll see you there.I'm on news.
In the news
All right, Ramy Ramy senior did it.
That sorting
Helpful
My wife who is a type A is helpful.
is a wonderful wife
Hey, I'm more senior than you.
Do you have it? Oh, I made a mistake again, that demon.
Because chan loves me, it's a diamond
Wow, I have that question.
What's wrong with that iron farm?
I heard that there is iron.
Please go to the farm over there.
It stinks, it's right next door. You made a mistake again, Senpai.
I thought you said that on purpose.
I did, but it's usually wrong.
Yeah now
I thought he was being messed with on purpose.
Oishio Oishioyo senpai
That connection is so cute
I did Idol Connect Abaki before.
Monne Kia-senpai is also happy, Barnebarco friends
There's a chest here where I got off.
It's there, so it's here too.
That or the equipment? Nice, nice, nice, pass.
Thank you very much for doing this
Please, won't I die? I won't die.
It's okay
It's natural after the elementary school
I guess seniors are starting to show up.
The mouth is not gravel now.
I got a big family that wasn't sand or gravel.
I'm glad I got it safely.
It just so happens that Anesakkin is better than Koko.
About 30 pieces of paper that were left behind
be
It's probably okay from
If I feel like I'm missing something, I'll give it to you now.
Is it made when no one is logged in?
I wonder if it's already become a very popular content.
year
Delicious Koushi
What should I do?
sword
Kenke
[music]
Wow, I've recovered a lot. I did it for this.
I was
Well, I can get Rami-tan with this.
N
What would you all do?
this
Even if it's luck, there are diamonds
That's why I like the diamond sword
or silk touch
I don't need a qua
Kura
For now, Diamond will be revived, so that's right.
Maybe it's better to leave it for revival.
Nede equipment is just available here.
Is there a shortage of iron now?
It seems a little difficult
Looks like it has good durability and good falling resistance.
Isn't falling position damage reduction good?
Looks like the rules have changed so what's going on?
Ta
This is cheap because it only reduces damage.
Dogutsu force
3 This looks good I want to play Blaze
And this is it
Yeah, just this
Once per person
Resurrection Yes, each person can be revived once.
What happened, I was revived once without a trial Anaho
Hey, this place where the golem is walking is a town.
Wait, you've fully recovered, then wait.
Let's get hitishhihichi and make arrows
Koyori has lived to play Blaze.
Is it scorching?
[music]
I could also use the familiar Kanama court.
I'm satisfied, this is gravel, that's gravel
Iwa, maybe this is it?
Gravel Ah, it looks like gravel. There's gravel in this place.
Well, it's better to sleep.
What a one-shot, the one who attacks at night.
You can also get a lot of arrows from
Yes, but it's better to make it.
Nane
Zuzu Ichi-chan was attacked while sleeping here.
I'm scared
Pecola-senpai, I can't sleep.
I'll go 75%, so it's okay.
It's delicious, it's hot, it's hot, it's magma!
It's scary but yeah
What should I do? If I die from magma, my eyes will also be destroyed.
guessed
Creeper that is scary even if there is no creeper
It's not spawning yet. Wait a minute. I'm scared.
But I'm scared
But it's scary up here. I'm really scared to climb up here.
There is gravel over here, and it is more dangerous over there.
There were a lot of flags, I guess not a lot.
I got this that I can't get at all right now.
As you can see,
Tokoto
Tototototo here
Flint 1
1 piece of stone
individual
[music]
This means you can crush a bucket and make it into iron.
There isn't.
You can't do it, right?
Iron!
iron and stone
You can make it with a stone that doesn't exist.
But I feel like I left it at home.
Look, the iron trama is probably gone.
Karate
Chan, that golem, come on, but the golem is different.
Let the water boil freely
What are you doing with that golem?
I wonder if I can't use another iron tiger?
Ta
But the golem is burned, so it's dead.
It's here, it's here
is
Tototototo
Ruto, kill that golem.
It's only about 4 iron.
Chane was able to repair this too.
It's huge
instructor
Tekoko
Yo
Totle Ejasa
I don't need it anymore
If
I don't need diamonds either.
thing
A little bit about Eba-san
Well, I can make it for Rami-tan.
is
But I have all the energy
Let's break up a bit
I also ate octopus
Well, what are you trying to do now?
[music]
It's a Mugen Yumiko repair bow, isn't it?
A bow would be fine too
Hmm, I took the trouble to plant bamboo and this bamboo.
Bamboo planting
Tende
no
13 pieces
Desu Now 13
Do you need real gravel?
Nome-san, that's right. My wife came to pick up the iron.
I want Gakoyo to take a lot of iron and use it.
Where did you go and save up your iron?
Anyway, do you have your own iron now?
Na
It's a waste to make it like this.
make your own iron
Wow
talk talk talk
Okay, tell me you want me to use your iron.
I haven't written anything so I don't know if it's true or not.
Because there is no
If there was a difference, we would just become a married couple.
Relationships may become strained
I'm so scared Good evening, Senpai
Good eveningGood eveningGood evening
What do you do?
ah
What is Fumabo?
Yuyuyumiyumiun
Yumi Ayubo
Yu
you want
Yumi Yeah yeah yeah IHaveIhave
Uncle almostIhaveto fix it
Fix it yeah yeah yeah
Good luck!
Chichi chichi
Ayu you ah
You are no longer sorry
Janari
Chichi
Later yes bye bye bye
Ahhh
Ah, I became a mistaken woman.
[music]
Hey, it's different now. Yokoyori cheated on me.
No, no, no, that's not it.
I thought it was a greeting.
After I said "I heard you"
I noticed that I seemed to be reacting a little differently.
I noticed it right away, I noticed it right away
That you are better than a small child who has backed down.
Let's do it
Let's sleep
It's different, it's different, it's different in the end
I'm not, it's okay. Wait a minute.
I want to use this bow as soon as possible.
The civil court of that marital quarrel
Don't try to use it for cyber
It's okay, Yoichi won't fight over something like that.
from
If you like, get more and more fire stones.
get to do
do
Does anyone need Totonjari?
I didn't use much concrete.
I don't remember anything, so I feel like I can use it for something.
I don't do it much, but...
This, this, that, the gravel, this tonkoku here.
If you put the gravel you took and dig, you will hear hiss.
Kurun
I know it's easy to get it from pine trees.
[music]
I'm absolutely scared of what's going on
Accumulate all this and more
Dae
I'll try a little bit of a dangerous one.
But at the water fountain
At the waterhole
Press shift like this
hand
Woo
wahoo
Holding the hatchet rope
More flint
The fire that has increased now
stone
scary overwhelming fear
difference
There will be no destruction of the sleeping pine tree.
No, that's no good. I had a scary experience.
You can't use Nijamatsu
In that case, it's faster to do it here.
I'm glad I didn't die.
If I died, I would never be the same again.
Wow, I also know that destroying the pine tree won't do it.
Thank you
If you do it like this even under the calluses
Hey, this will come out.
A crazy race with no courage
Only one person even played Toritama.
It feels so good and I can see 15 of them coming out.
It's okay, it comes out a lot, it comes out a lot.
It's definitely a good idea to pile it on top and dig it up yourself.
Well that's for sure
But it was really scary. I was in the water just now.
When I jump into it, it's like that missing ball
It became
I felt it
I feel like there's a little too much risk involved.
Don't do that, just stay here for now.
There's gravel, so if there's gravel there, that's it.
Why don't you just do it?
Diamond equipment
If you have a strong bow and arrows, you also have a shield.
Why not do Blaze?
I wonder what it's like
Collect up to 4 flints in one stack
No way
44 stacks is enough, right?
When I went there, I only had about 3 stacks.
I just feel like it didn't happen.
Stack is fine
a
It's fine, it's fine, it's fine
If you have a 4, you can hit it fairly freely with a small arm.
I wonder if she can survive.M is weaker than Koko.
If I say so myself, my aim is weak.
That's it, isn't it?
If you don't have that many, you won't win.
That's right
It seems like it is
It's better to carry as much as you can from
Is it okay?
I don't feel well
I wonder if I'll be able to meet that Blaze?
Even if it's a fortress, you can meet it if you go to the fortress.
No, no, I want to go to TTTTT.
That's what I thought, but TTT is so far away and in the Nether.
It seems to be such a work that I have to go through it.
So, is that so? So the Nether came first?
I think TTT comes first or Nether comes first.
I'm thinking about making arrows myself right now.
That is to say
The gold is the one I dug up the other day and I'm just burning it now.
There are 4 of them, so you can use them somewhere.
Even if it's just a leg, it'll turn into a leg.
I got a leg with a hat on too
If you walk on the ground, you'll probably be back at 7pm.
Apparently there's going to be a trial starting at 7pm.
I went there from there.
I don't have any reason to go to TTT other than Shinaya.
If you can earn today's amount, you can get it at TTT.
Can use arrows
There is
I wonder if this is too much for Karakana today.
50 pieces means 200
200 books
book
Ebu
I almost got hit by the falling gravel.
Taane
For now, let's go home with 51 pieces. Amazing.
It looks like it was placed correctly
Teru Jiri sales girl
Yoriko Yori-chan wanted flint
So it was.
The teacher
You can't get it without digging, so it's small.
There's a lot of gravel on hand.
How can I use octopus gravel?
Maybe someone wants gravel.
Shire
do not have
Akoyori-chan came up with the idea of Gravel One.
The stack and stuff are increasing
I wonder if the mustard has increased, with gravel one stack
All you have to do is exchange one diamond.
I think sand is the material for TNT.
Was it?
Maybe it's Ede Kori, I collect a lot of gravel.
I remember going there because I wanted TNT.
in
too
If TNT is made in this world, it will be used in crimes.
It's better not to make it because there is a possibility
I wonder if there is one, and that's it.
It seems like feathers and trees are missing a bit too.
Let's do woodcutter too
Hahaha is waiting
mosquito
a
Oh yeah, Pol Pol is free to take
Even if you say you have money, you can make one at home.
So, sand and gunpowder gravel? Sand, sand?
Don't mix gravel and gravel.
There are four of them, so here are the four.
I'm making legs because they're the cheapest.
I see
Well then, let's make some legs or something else 567
Ma
Take-head Ah, if there is one more head, I can make one.
I feel like I want to have a head like that
But there are falling bodies
[music]
You know, money can't be changed by an old man, right?
Let's collect feathers for now.Feathers
Collect
Ah, the power is too powerful, the power is too strong
It's too much to collect eggs
hand
Where did it say "delicious area attack"?
I was born that way
I haven't really been born yet.
It's different now, this isn't being born, it's hitting me
Terueeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeey
[music]
Maybe I killed too many eggs.
A certain force is too strong
I'm in trouble because my right hand is too strong
There's no little one, there's a little one
A child may or may not be born.
40 teru feathers were saved, so the feathers fell off.
I just killed you, I'm sorry.
Don't make it a stick
[music]
I'll use this to make an arrow.
make
Shushin
oh
2.5 Stacks What's missing Feathers and Feathers and Trees
Or rather, I forgot to say Takegami.
Bamboo grows in Takore
[music]
You can line them up
You can line them up.
There's nothing wrong with that, but you're such a great senpai.
It's good that you have a good head.
Let's cut a white birch tree
[music]
Bamboo can be slanted, idiot.
This is probably what Lami-tan used.
I feel like Ramita is always cutting trees here.
do
grow like a monster
Stop calling me a monster. Bamboo is also alive.
Looks cute
Right? The bamboo is densely packed.
Is it okay to make sticks out of bamboo?
If that's the case, I'll cut it off from here.
Ta
Ok, Mi-tan's cloudy weather was also cold.
It might have been a little cold.
[music]
There are some white birches that are not growing.
What happened to this, this and that was planted now?
[music]
Why is it this high?
I guess I'll make this much.
Apple
I should have cut that white birch, but there was a lot of shyness.
Falling down
Why?
[music]
Is it just a matter of time?
I wonder if it was stopped?
The rest of someone else will grow up big
I'm trying not to go too far
I guess it's because it's a hassle to cut.
It came, it came, it came. I have to plant it.
[music]
Nekuno
It's around here Naegi
If it gets this big, you can place it on a pedestal when cutting it.
It's a bit of a hassle because I can't cut it without it.
More Nayoshi Arrows
Make about 3 stacks
The stone that I should have left in the weak gravel house is still there.
I have it, so please let me do it a little more.
[music]
Let's fall down
Sorry I don't have one
a
Ah, this and that is right, right click is right.
Hey
Born, born, born, born, sometimes
Born
Nether after the resurrection trial from 19:00
Gate results take regularity
Yes feather
Zero The children who died now have zero feathers.
I feel like I killed too many eggs just now.
Do you have eggs?
I'll plant it, I'll plant it, no.
The wings of the free chest are gone.
After all, we all think the same thing now.
I guess they are making it
Hey, you can multiply by seeds, so let's feed them some seeds.
It's okay then it's okay
[music]
I feel so sorry for you, Gravel.
move it over here
Okay then.
Okay, put the rest on Rigo.
It's easier to go to the Nether if you have stones, so stones.
have
Tekuuu
Emerald Ira
You can't use water in a bucket without one.
I'm sure there's chishi too
Damn it, I can't get any diamonds anymore.
Nehona
[music]
Good job
Up with this
Use it as you like
I earned money on the internet
I like part time
use it for
I hope I don't have to use it
Koyori wore it once
boots
Okay, maybe I'll make an axe.
Shinekikori
Okay okay from
Okay
Okay, now let's put the bed somewhere else.
I need it, so I'll take it once.
Wait, you'll need this one.
There's no athlete's foot. What's reflected is not athlete's foot.
Don't show it
It doesn't show up
There's going to be a trial right now, so let's all do it all at once.
There's a chance you'll feel like you need to sleep.
I'll bring my bed, but I don't have any money.
1 gold block gold gold block gold plate
Is there one stick?
[music]
I'm going to bring some chicken, but I don't have much.
Maybe this
Red nether to make rice nether gate
Because we were talking about making it from the gate.
That's it
Materials that can be used to make rice
It might be nice to have one too, like cherry blossoms.
I'm afraid
This golem is scary
I hope they won't replace it.
If I melt it, it will turn into gold, but I'm wrong.
Ta
[music]
Too
I didn't have any money.
I want one gold.
[music]
I want to do something good with my feet but it's true
teeth
Nkou
I highly recommend it
I wish I had one1
I'll probably go to private court, but they'll probably tell me to gather.
Until then, prepare
No, I'm just afraid of dropping it.
This is fine
I think it's okay to attack if it's in cat form.
does
But rice
I have a fish that I caught myself yesterday before dinner.
from
Did you eat fish?
I'll bring some grilled salmon, and some yakitori.
Chicken grilled cousin
ToriKona uses amazing magma
It uses magma and replenishes magma.
What a great wife she is.
[music]
Use it as a material
I was thinking of bringing something like that.
Thank you for accepting it
I'm happy, that's all there is to it
If you are able to participate in the Namo trial, please contact the court.
Yes
Starts in 1 minute
I thought he was just writing a poem.
Let's go
Let's go, I want to sleep
Who isn't going to sleep?
also court
Let's go inside the courthouse. It's probably dark and the night is blowing.
It looks like Kaa Peco Lapa isn't streaming.
I thought I'd take it
[music]
circle
Okay, it's about to start so I can give you a ride.
Mr. Miss.
Okay, so just open the Nether.
I wonder if it's time to end it.
There are quite a few people behind the scenes.
I wonder if it's time to close the deadline.
If you like, please go ahead and make Ririka-chan this
Licca-chan's as the one who died in the middle
The person who will defend you is on the right side or right here.
Yes, yes, finally the presiding judge and others have not won.
I see that the presiding judge is Judge Pecola.
That's right, I'm careful not to become a slave to God Pecola.
Sorry, that's not what happened just now.
Please cut it with
Hamechan who followed Masukachan
It's supposed to be left
I haven't done anything with Beko yet.
Log wondering if Hajime-chan killed him.
So I decided to stay on the left side for a while.
I hope you can hear my story too.
So, there are two cases in this trial, and the first one is
The second case with Ririka-chan is Akutan.
The second half of each lesson can be completed in under 10 minutes.
I'm thinking of doing it, so please help me
And when speaking, the person in the inflatable seat
Please do it in chat suddenly
If I talk, it becomes a mess.
Because I think, I speak, so I raise my hand and do it.
I would like to, please. Yes, one more.
I'll start in a minute, okay, please, come on.
I wonder if Lyrica-chan can be revived?
Ah, how can I do it this time?
So the resurrection trial will end with these two cases.
I understand that you can enjoy it to your heart's content.
Tako's sword of justice once again hits Ririka-chan.
There is a possibility that
Maiiya is being killed
Maybe it's possible, maybe
Thai deception
In just one minute, it's up to you all.
Is that so? Please.
What happened? Just watch that video.
I was allowed to do so.
However, there is a cheerful child named Feldspar.
Sorry
This side is having fun and I can see it yesterday.
The scenery is different now that it's 1:05am.
I would like to hold an Article 1 Lyrica revival trial.
I think, what should I do first?
Ririka-chan will explain the situation to you.
Can I ask you to tell me? Yes, I understand.
Yes, it was last night, late at night, same as the beginning.
I went to cut that tree, my senior.
Because of the uncle manufacturing machine that he was trying to make.
In order to hunt the tree that was necessary for
Next to Lyrica's house is a large one called Momori.
There was a forest, so I went there to borrow something.
But it was just the day before that.
I thought I could use it for something, so I tried automatic fishing.
I tried making it myself, it's amazing
Yes, yes, yes, yes, but a little bit
How to use it as a beginner
Even without understanding, I just looked at myself
Leave the things you made behind.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, thats it.
I took the opportunity to use it at the right time.
I was just about to say "Yo" and try to use it.
I didn't know how to use it, so I made it myself.
Caught up in the equipment and unable to get out, submerged in water
There have been three incidents where
I play around with it a lot, but I don't use it, and it's an accident that I can't use it.
It's like I can't use it and I can't use it.
I ended up not being able to leave.
This is completely true.
Lyrica is 500% just me and my neck
Just by closing the door, the bee will try to help
Self-respect is amazing
As a very strict double, this is my own merit.
Yona
Yes, there is a relatively realistic execution video in reality
It seems like it's just a coincidence
It's not
Kateteitan
At first, Mecha was laughing so hard and I was so nervous.
I feel like Licca-chan is dead.
What I was doing was saying, Where should I go?
I was allowed to see it, but I can't open it.
Did you do it for the sake of it?
Were you trying to help? Yes.
I tried to help, I tried to help, but what should I do?
He seemed like he had no idea. It was fun.
Ta
I feel a little guilty since he died.
Yes, we are talking
I probably said something about A-chan, the best lawyer.
Is there anything you would like to do? Ah, lawyer Azuki.
Yes, I will watch the resurrection of the accused.Yes.
Is it because of a malfunction at work?
That's right, as I was watching it just now.
The color is just like that.
Mako's team at the beginning of Lyrica is in action.
Especially when you are crawling and crawling in the middle of the day.
One more thing that could be called an accident.
A little while
It's too dark to be a lawyer.
I will keep it for you, so click here.
I would also like to read it out loud.
Although there is a defense and defense, it is being distributed on May 15th
Ririka-chan died
1 square of the automatic fishing machine at Ririka's house
He accidentally swam into the water and suffocated and died.
It seems that I have done this at the beginning.
Chan tried to break down the iron door to help.
As a result of the punch, the log started from Hajime-chan.
Ririka-chan died while trying to escape.
It was a log, but it was definitely Hajime-chan.
This is an accident that did not kill Ririka-chan.
generous
I'm glad I can get the treatment done as I'm standing here.
It looks like Gahame-chan so there's no sound
I would be happy if you could
Masu means
Well, I was curious so I started with one.
Can I confirm with you? Yes, please feel free to do so.
I was able to get along with you, but I guess I abandoned you.
No, I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm really trying to help you, aren't you?
I think that reminds me a little bit of that.
I mean, I can't play Lyrica.
I thought I'd check just in case.
Hey, are you okay, Azuki-san?
I'm a little suspicious at home, but it's a lie.
I can't follow you, so let me make it clear here.
There's no Mashohai, right Bancho?
Thank you very much I believe in you
Well then, all you expansionists, please listen to this story and listen to Lyrica.
Please make a decision on whether or not to reinstate him.
I wish I could come back.
If you agree, please raise your hand for chat.
I would like to ask you a few questions. More than half of them are
I would like to make a comeback.
Please, what should I do?
After this, I will work like a ba.
It was making a lot of noise, it was making a lot of noise
do not have
Ugh, please, that shield and that sword.
I'm going to become a lot of things this time.
If you let me eat my limit, I'll give it a no.
Of course, it's cheap and delicious, and I can make endless amounts of food.
Thank you very much. I made a mistake.
brain like jesus
People who have died twice have brains.
You're really helping me out with this.
Ririka-chan will be revived in Manjo 1.
Looks like it's okay, so see you, Ririka-chan.
Congratulations on your resurrection today
Thank you, congratulations, try your best, no more accidents
Don't wake me up, please don't wake me up again, shield
use as
Please give it to that owner later.
Please stay with me, the house of beginnings.
I'll leave the chisto there because it's there.
Thank you very much. Yes, thank you.
Thank you very much
Masu
Thank you very much and welcome back
[music]
return
Ten you
Good luck clothes
Is there anyone who can defend me?
Like, it's a bit like a lose-lose trial.
I don't want to. I don't know what happened.
I just don't understand
Isn't that what these people saw?
Well, as a witness, then as a witness, then as a defense.
No, just a witness, ask me a few questions.
I wish I could have it for my back and legs.
Some people have suffered some damage or other things.
Some of the things I've seen so far
In this life, I can no longer feel no, no, no, no.
Thank you so much everyone, together with everyone
It's really easy with Minecraft
I'm a fun senpai. I'm the most senpai in this group.
nice to meet you
It seems like it's not bad, but then everyone dies.
I want to check what happened, so I'll check what happened.
Is it okay if I ask you to tell me?
Well, the prison work for that incident from yesterday.
That fall from the TT Tower inside.
What's more, I slipped and fell.
I see, that's a fact, so it's a defect.
Does it feel like an accident? Yes, it seems so.
A witness's foot slipped in an accident caused by a delinquent.
Is that true, folks?Actually, we
There were no witnesses.
It's true that this is all about work.
That's right, the three of us were having lunch together.
It's true that I was working in prison at a high altitude today.
But yeah, when I realized that...
Aqua's voice suddenly disappears and the conversation begins.
He disappeared in the middle of the process, so I checked the log.
Aqua has just fallen from a high place.
When I looked, I saw some of Aqua's belongings scattered around.
Oh, we died too, like Aqua.
That's why I didn't see that moment.
Hey, I see.
There's something I'd like to ask you.
But it was just a slip and fall accident.
I was doing that and I didn't look behind me
Yes, yes, that's okay.
All you have to do is do it, bro.
We're friends, the atmosphere is tense.
It's because I died twice.
Thank you, thank you, I died.
I'm sorry, but Mr. Takaa was a bit like yesterday.
Pecola says it's a bit of an elephant sin
Partly because I was forced to wear
The fact that it was lost in an accident means that
It's a bit sad though
I want him to be bad, but
How much is it for the guard seat once?
Aqua-senpai did that little naughty thing to me.
You can count the number of people for a while.
Someone who has been wronged by Attar in some way.
I'm glad I left it alone. Surprisingly, there aren't any.
Maybe there is no victim now.
More glittery
Rakiwa, do your best, do your best, sorry tomorrow
What did each of those three people do?
Can I just check, what's your name?
Did you go to the baby's house?
I'm going to go and bother you a little.
Just a little bit closer
If you feel that way, I want to talk to you.
That's what I thought, but magma was poured on me.
[music]
I couldn't say anything because I was burned.
Ah, burn it, burn it, I forgot that.
Sorry, it's not me, but my wife and family.
However, there is a family called Ramy-chan.
But that Lamy-tan is on that leg.
From behind in a very deep hole in the house
She was crying because she was pushed off and dropped.
My wife was heartbroken.
has been dropped
I've done the same thing twice, haven't I?
It's been known that this fruit is running twice.
Be quiet, be quiet
[laughter]
Who are you? There are so many things about you.
I'm feeling a little guilty about this.
Yes, that's right. Is it just a trial?
That's right, that's what I'm waiting for.
Can you tell me that from Subaru?
Please, please, no, just one word
Let me just say that it's just a term.
It's not, but that TTT Tower is
It really wouldn't have been completed without Aqua's power.
I see, that's all there is to it.
I hope you keep this in mind.
You've been working really hard. Well then, there's the bar seat.
Is it still available? It's totally fine.
No, Captain, I'd like to say a few words.
You know, after all, it's the bond of Noe Tire.
I just wanted to say something.
Yes, that's right, we have a bond on the first day.
Two diamonds were stolen from me by leader Kanete-chan.
It was.
At that time, when the leader said that he had been deceived,
I'm like that without any hesitation.
I started burning Kin-chan with flint.
My heart
It's hot and a little noisy, but in the midst of that, friendship
I'm a shy kid, so it's a bit like that.
Please give me a chance, just for a moment
picture
But that's right, there is humanity.
Thank you very much for your help.
After hearing what Kiddie has said so far, the audience members come back to life.
If you don't mind, please hold your hand.
Please please please really
I would like that please, dada entra.
If you're going to go, I'd like all your wishes.
I want it.
You idiot, you don't have the right to vote.
Subaru's bottom name is already wrong.
So what's this about?
Wow, this is such an important item.
I said, ``But,'' and gave me some cod.
I see, he has a kind side too.
That's right, that's right, I have to give it to you.
It was said that I would be cursed
It seems like he has no feelings about being cursed to death.
hey
I've given it to everyone, I'll give it to you, it's coming, wait.
Hey, who's who, who's not doing it 12345 who's doing it
No one is raising their hand at this gig.
Well then, I can't help it, why should I raise it?
On the contrary, there is a possibility that it will break.
Then, more than half of the hands were taken.
So this time I will go with the resurrection, but I will go.
Ka-chan is so close that it's a bit of a pain for you.
of
[music]
It's a little new
It's not nothing, it's yesterday's problem after all.
I guess so. Yesterday's problem also exists.
Just a little bit of guilt
I thought it would be nice to receive it.
From now on, you will forever be my little servant in that operation.
I started asking for help, and
You also have the hell project organized by Pecola.
I hope you will participate, and
In order to turn on the people around you,
Behave well and live a good life.
I can't do anything today either, it's already too late
That guy was really bad, I'm so glad
Say goodbye
Thank you for your hard work.Thank you for your hard work.Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for coming to the court.
Thank you very much
It's a party, so people who want to go to the Nether, that Nether.
Let's make that gate
Thank you for your hard work. Good luck with your recovery.
It was just barely, thank goodness I was able to get the temperature right.
I want everyone to make that.
Where is Licca-chan's greetings?
Make
I know where the Red Nether is, I know.
I understand, but I have to make Peko-chan first.
Nanko-chan is a little busy.
It seems so, so I'll leave the stupid place to you.
Anything is fine as long as it's that close.
I'm telling everyone today that there will be divine punishment.
Good luck with all your equipment. God's punishment, punishment, punishment, punishment.
What what?
Let's go to sleep, let's go to sleep. Take care of your throat.
Let's all do it together.
Let's go to bed. You talk really fast.
Yay Rena, you're talking so fast, what's that?
I didn't know what to say. It was definitely a punishment.
The punishment is too scary, I guess, at what timing?
You can't really listen to it, can you?
Become a rose
It's going to be nice. Something good happened.
I don't even use the guard station here.
I'm sure in the future
It's really well made, let's make it
What is the nether gate?
Um, Youseki, um, Magma, Magma, water is fine.
It's not like magma and water is obsidian.
It was in a dead place, but it was a diamond.
I can go with an ice ax, but I don't have a diamond ice ax.
Yes, everyone has a daya ice ax.
I'll go get it. How many? It's 9.
23459 99 is all you need 9
Okay, yes, I can go with 9. That's 10 or 10.
10The bottom of the foundation is about 15cm.
Knead a little, about 15 minutes
What we want to do is equip Ririka-chan once.
I'll comb it
2456 We can't do that.
Is it something like diamond equipment?
That's right, let's go back one step at a time.
I'll be back again, I'll be equipped again.
Masuhai
12345678910E10Minimum10
Because it's at least 10 if you're going to do this.
Looks like it'll take about 14. Well then, about 14.
Yakane
It's better to keep a little more.
This might be a good diamond 15 glass
So I made a base, poured magma into it, and poured water into it.
Or something
impossible 20
I don't think I can do it if it's below me, but still
It's totally fine.If water is fine, it's fine.
There is water, but it is soil and there are stones.
I'll bring that fire.
Masu
Looks like it would be dangerous to spill magma on something like that.
So it seems better to just take the one that already exists.
There's still magma down there, so it's a bit
It might be dangerous, are you okay?
[music]
Yeah, I'm afraid of accidents with mugs.
That's because I took a lot earlier.
Let's make some water, just pour some water on it right away.
scared
You know, if you die three times in two days, you can't come back to life.
Probably
Hey there
Taanenechi is doing it properly
Yeah, 15 pieces. In the end, I'm actually fine with 10 pieces.
But I was wondering if I should make it that big?
Oh, I might be happy if there are a lot of them.
Somehow, all the entrances to the courthouse were made into gates.
It feels like I'm trying to make it. Ah, that's nice.
Thank you very much
Masuuchi stone
I'm glad I waited for Shiuchishi.
Just right
No, if I die soon, I won't be able to go home.
Not this
All you have to do is make it with
Woo
Okay, just put your foot down
Anyway, I've already given up.
It's a little difficult to get one piece of gold from now on
I thought it was far away so I put it on my feet, but actually I put it on my head.
I wanted
[music]
But 15
Okay, if I can still get it, I'll take it from here.
Maybe it's not enough, but I got 105.
I think it's because the soil here is magma.
Okay, let's stop, stop, this is enough.
If not, let's do it at that time.
It's quite spacious.
ton ton ton
If your head drops, then your feet will drop.
Maybe I should have brought it
I proposed a place over there in the Nether.
Yeah, it seems like it happened in an outrageous place.
Even if I do, I have to go very far
It won't change, so I'll bring it Noel.
Senpai, that should be it
That's right
Ta
Thank you so much
There's Yoishi, so there's already a frame.
It's so hot today Subaru is so diamond
I found this super obsidian while digging.
Just fold it into a square shape inside here.
123 That's 891 There are also 12 pieces.
It's better to go 3 This is the one below.
Maybe it's not good here. It's not good here.
If that increases, it will be 14, so it's probably enough.
So you need fire, right? I brought some. Damn.
You're on top too, so take this seriously.
Senkyu, this is good too, please break it down.
a
Okay, look, hey hey hey hey
Ooi oi oi oi oi
Oh, it's okay to go away. It's okay. Be careful.
only
I love you
Ta
For those of you who went there, let's make the first trip.
Let's join in!
Don't be in danger
Yeah, wait a minute, what if?
It's a waste to make this sometimes
There are so many cobblestones that you should take from there.
Maybe it would be better to make one.
It would probably be better to have one.
Be careful not to put the bed there.
By the way, it's a bed.
But when you come out, there's a cliff-like thing on the left.
I have one, but I can't compete with it. I think it's good.
First, the gate was surrounded by that gate.
I'll definitely go for a bit so it doesn't break.
I think I'll go even if I get a gift.
Is this okay? The gate has already been completed.
I should have made a certain head. That looks good.
It's totally fine, it's safe, the gust's cry is
It looks good what you're doing
I'll leave the place for now.
Yoisho Gas and Teyabe Gast
Anyway, I don't have enough stones.
Come on
Good job
Oho
I surrounded it with stones and it's already destroyed.
I hope it's not there
Yo
Now it's time to work in a scary place
Be careful, don't be like Ooyone.
legs
I won't leave you like Nahane Aka-senpai.
Good job
[music]
Yeah and Tonoko, like that sister and that one.
There are people who seriously think that if they die, there will be no next step.
Enchantment recommended Enchantment
That's what I'm talking about
I'm wearing a falling body.That's better than that falling body.
It's true that the flame system may be
I'll wear both, but it might be better to wear both.
Please wear it if you are in danger.
Please enchant it before you go.
please
Let me just say something
Nether ghast's voice is scary, let's go.
If you are
picture
I recommend starting with enchantment.
Masu court entrance
The eyes
Well then, leave this to me for a while.
Oi to Peko-san's operation
Called
Shall I bring you a wooden chest?
I don't know if it's better to use it with a serious eye.
It's gone
It's well maintained, it's dangerous, dangerous, dangerous.
Dangerous, dangerous, dangerous
You're dangerous, you drink a lot, dangerous.
Can I ask you to put it on the wall? Please do it on top.
Do it
Is there a stone?
Nakyapyo
oh
Hey, just connect this like this.
That's how it is
dark
There's nothing good about it
Because you're going to fall down there, it's like this
thing
I'm sorry I can't save you
Look, this is going to turn into gold nuggets.
This is it
of
I just made this.
a little bit
I wonder if I can get diamonds with the new update?
Do you have 5 gold now?
Is this what you want?
All right, Subaru's Subaru Diamond
Even if I receive it
Hurry up
Hey, okay, I thought I'd put on that armor.
That's right, wait a minute
Is this okay?
Good protection
[music]
I don't know where it's coming from.
I don't have it, but I'll open it or protect it here.
It's there, isn't it?
For now
I went to pick up Nami-tan from Kakoyori.
It hasn't been streamed yet, it's from 8pm.
Tandayo Nami
After that, wait a minute and get this now.
Takinkai will become gold block 5
Good luck
Hey
[music]
Hey, there aren't enough monster positions again.
But wait a minute, there wasn't anything else.
It wasn't there.
[music]
Why do I have to make a new umbrella?
That's good, there's money in the Nether.
I shouldn't have made it. Let's go home once.
Let's take that fall system with us for now.
If you find one, go to the site
Let's make one, we can't take apart the legs.
It was in the upper left corner.
Well, it's a little scary, but it's already over.
Then I went home once and Rami was there.
I guess it's not streaming anymore
still
tantara tattantan
[music]
There is a gap between
What's with the big belly at the end?
I thought Tenno was amazing and laughed when I saw it.
Oh, I'm writing a love letter from Rami right now.
Thank you for giving it again
It's not a love letter, it's too positive
Receive a receipt
It looks like someone is hurting, so I'm glad.
Thinking
It's so cool, Suinamitan is such a disgusting girl.
There is
By
[music]
Get a pine tree
Falling down for the time being
Let's go home, your home is so positive
I just wrote it because I thought it was a love letter.
seems to be
Well, you should take this with you.
Okay, this is the stone now.
But there is more
Is the industry in danger? We don't need any more soldiers.
I don't need a bucket anymore
The cherry blossoms are gone
do not have
So it's like this
That's right, the industry shore is fragile, isn't it?
You don't need a rack, just one stack is enough
Kabone is always ready to catch the dog.
is
But the bucket can't be used in a pinch.
in
There's some eggs
It's a waste, so I'll just take it and die.
I don't know what the Nether is, what should I do?
I'm preparing to go separately.
Nenami-tan, are you scared to go to the Nether?
If there is dirt or sand, the ship
That's right, I see.
Even so, I'm waiting for the diamond equipment.
now
That's it, but it's not bad, Koyori Yanami-tan
I just saw the presentation.
I saw the presentation.I saw the presentation.I saw the presentation.
thank you
I won after yesterday
It's amazing that there is enough equipment for the entire body.
now
You can go, Nether, you can go now.
I'll think about it later, why is it still being streamed?
It hasn't started yet 20 minutes later
It's a bit of a struggle from now on
You'll be surprised too.
The work starts from
I understand, thank you very much
Thank you, I guess I'll wait.
I guess I'll have to go alone.
Ah-chan, that's okay, it's okay, wait.
Even if you don't have it, I'll just talk a little while I go.
Yeah, it's okay, don't worry, it's okay.
Even if I'm alone, I still have plenty of time.
Koyokoyo will go too, and later Rummy will go.
Thank you for coming back and understanding.
thank you
yes
If I can go on a date, I'll go. I usually don't go. Wait.
There's even a possibility that it won't come. Just wait, it's still eggs.
I haven't given birth yet
That's what happened today
There are a lot of people in groups right now.
trying to go
From this to that, I'm so lonely
Don't be alone, okay?
Even the "yoisho yoisho yoisho" is available
It hasn't started yet, so I'm not sure if I'll go.
Very
I get it, I'm getting more food. I'll get some food.
Get a stack
yeah
What is it?
Kea
It's scarier than being on a ship, getting off on a ship, on a ship.
When I got off, I said "Sue" and said "Par".
What should I do if it happens?
No, isn't it too much? Yakoyori's aim licking
Wait, please don't give me more torches
[music]
There is
You should bring more wood.
Kamatsu That's right.
signpost
from
I'll get Onami-tan.
The stacks will be made on-site.
After all, we need trees
Even if you don't choose, you have too much pine 3
stack 3 stack
Kurisui-chan doesn't have any mods installed
I can't do VC, so I can't install this mod.
It's a bit troublesome
hey
It's going to be Oisho Nemo Bread, that's right.
is really
Yeah, really, yeah, it's a little white, but it's the same now.
Prevent stacks from increasing when turned into trees
Be careful
I want to plant trees
[music]
Afforestation
Should I just keep the tank?
[music]
Sleeping
The door opens and closes.
[music]
I'm sleeping, I'm not cuckolding, I'm sleeping, it's not NTR
I mean, it's like
It's a normal word, right?
It would be a sin if I didn't plant some necho there.
Because it leaves a feeling
Where should I plant another one?
Keasoko
Okay, plant it, just 3 stacks.
I'll bring a pine tree
Is it okay if I wait here?
Hello, who are you waiting for, Subaru-senpai?
I'll ask you to show me around the trap tower.
Yeah, that's right, Trap Tower
You said it was very far away, but I guess that's true.
It seems far away
I'll give you some diamonds
I have decided to ask for guidance from
I see, come on then.
Yes, I wish I could go to the Nether.
Well, the Nether will open from now on, but TT
I just learned about it, so I thought I'd go.
I can go
But that's not it. Thank you for your hard work.
Either that or TTT.
Eh, if you make a design with TTTT, I'll connect it.
I can do it, but I wonder if I'll do it?
If you're going to the trouble of going, bring obsidian with you.
That's it!
I'm already doing that
That's good, that's good, that's good
It's okay if you can do it for me.
I'm already full, but what about my luggage?
For now, let's go look around the Nether.
mosquito
I guess everyone hasn't been to the Nether Fortress yet.
Aim to be the first discoverer of 30 diamonds 30
However, the era of diamonds is pretty much over.
I feel like it's coming here
As long as you have enough stones to go, that's fine.
It's more troublesome when you don't need anything anymore.
Let's go, let's go, let's go
Let's go this way where there were people. Should we go this way?
My sister, Noel-senpai, is also in the trap tower.
Thank you very much.
Thank you
Even better saltiness
Let's look for something wide here after someone went there.
Hey, there's a wall over there. I was going to go there but I gave up.
The wall looks so good
Then let's go to the other side
Because it's a big deal
It's scary to hear this, but it's better to do it this way.
Okay, it's dark.
Newo
Oh, it's not the Red Forest.
yeah
dangerous in short
danger
in the forest
Come on, there's nothing good about it, glowstone.
It's dangerous, it's dangerous, so just stay here.
I did this to reduce other people's fat too.
He said there was a wall.
It's scary, I'll die in an instant
What about that side?
Probably
[music]
That side
Ongust makes me cry so much
can be remembered with this
takes out the workbench
It's so scary, it's a mistake, it's wrong.
Take a deep breath, let's go to the Nether, say something like "ha"
I used to do it, but it's really scary, but I decided to make it a gold medal.
I don't need any gold nuggets.
Deyoishokoshi
head
[music]
Okay, I feel like this place was also a hole earlier.
I'll do it
It would be nice if they were connected, but like this
come to the left
Because I brought a lot of torches.
Even if you leave it carelessly
Okay, put it in the chest.
I'm sure it will come
I put it everywhere. Wow, what is this?
Very kind
Kindly, is this okay? I'll leave it here.
Hingod will exchange it for you, so bring it with you.
But if that's the case, I'd have some gold nuggets too.
Enough is enough
Or this?
Na
Okay, I have a boat too, which helps. I can take it with me.
Ta
But if there are piglins, it's a bit gacha.
When I look at Taionekin
a
Oh how?
[music]
Do this one
Chang Wan Ching
Will the fortress come down?
descend diagonally
I feel like I can get down if I dig from here.
[music]
No, it's dangerous to go by boat.
scared
It's scary
I feel like something like this
How much to dig?
It's like the aura of this red forest.
Is Nano coming out?
It's about time to get scared
Go for a while
Let's see
oh
Ueoh my moga
Ah, I see. If only I knew about it.
That's not what I meant when I said it was falling.
Yeah, let's go a little lower than this.
You can cross that bridge. You can cross that bridge.
I'll do something
or bridging
Oh yeah, there's Gust
This way
[music]
Yeah, I don't have a destination
Although I no longer hear Gust's voice
Hey, hoglin
[music]
Teru
Omoobo
[music]
too
Ah, this is where Nene gave up earlier.
I guess it's okay to go if it's about that amount.
Even if you don't have Gusto, it's okay
Yeah okay
[music]
Even if it's better than never letting go of the shift shift
Wow this is the end
What I failed at with the scary ending
be
scary [ __ ] pushing finger
But my fingers are jiggling all the time Okay, so thick
let's
Okay scary
I made a mistake
I'm scared
[music]
Yo
Okay, but there's a hole.
Ah, the red forest is creeping in a little bit.
is
It's a cat, so it's called Red Forest.
Maybe it's not connected? Just dig once.
see
I came to the hairy fruit.
Tomorrow
Do you want to go here? Pass this here? Do you want to shift here?
I'm afraid of the hand that pushes me
[music]
Yokoko
The map isn't that bad, really.
[music]
I want to die
Not scary
[music]
Yoma Nether is
lifetime
My whole life is in danger, no matter what I do
No matter what I do, it's dangerous so I can't help it
here or somewhere here
Okay
I don't need oke quartz.
Cat Hole Dark
dark okay
Okay don't guess
I don't need coats, I feel a little better
only
Tips and tricks
There's no more scars
Or go left.
If you go to the left, it seems like they will be connected.
Shall I dig this?
Something
My eyes widen as if I could go on an adventure like this
It's okay though
I want to make the most aggressive potion.
from
neo piglin
Piglin Piglinglin but around there
Yes, it doesn't have to be a piglin fortress.
I guess it's a little too expensive
Just go
Let's see the diamond
Should I have made an ice ax?
Na
What?
It says sound buin
a
Get down there!
Ta
I met the scary Beguelin
Gacha
play gacha
hello hello this
Hold it and right click, it's red.
Red too
It's okay to be on the right. It's okay to be on the right.
Throw it9
Anecho Piglin, please make this a good one.
please
Yeah, they're fighting, they're fighting, it's dangerous
Now
Piglins that may be born
Piglin's what what what appraise
What did you give me? It's gravel now. It's better than gravel.
I didn't bring it.
Hey, I don't need gravel. It's better.
Please give me something better. Something better.
This is different from before. You're different.
You're a good piglin, aren't you?
Show me the difference in horns from piglins.
what
Yeah
Well, Nemopan will be Nemo
Pangomi Makoto doesn't even have an ice ax anymore.
It's so-so-so-so.
But the forest is scary
[music]
Let's just take a look
It's red
red
It's also a red forest
It seems a bit expensive.
I might be able to go somewhere by digging here.
do not have
I only have courage from
I remember it now, and as expected, it's early days.
I should have memorized that sponge thing.
Hey, it's open
Pi
[music]
cormorant
Hmm, nothing
Neon
Yeah nothing
[music]
No gravel
Shall I try to get on top of it?
[music]
scared
hey
Scary Piglin Seen by Piglin
Try not to look like that
hand
There's no sound of magma, right? Wait a minute.
As expected
I will collect money for
I can't date this 6. Maybe this is it.
I came to a place where I could open up and explore.
The Nether is a place to go on a date unless
No love
It's okay for everyone to dig into this.
It's not like it would be if we met somewhere
What the hell don't you just say boom?
of energy
The footprints are on the right, right? What is this?
footsteps
Eb is Mr. Ender or Mr. Ender
Ender's
I played the role of bringing home Ender's bullets.
Looks like it will stand up
But should I go this way?
There's no place
Is this still expensive?
Hey, 52 might be expensive.
It's not expensive though
This is red
It's a red forest, so there are hoglins where you dig.
There is a possibility that something like that will happen.
Normal Normal 52 Normal
Which one is more expensive?
Which stone should be unified?
Which one?
Oh my goodness
Red and red are scary too.Why is it red over there in Akamori?
But not only that
Nodou
It's dangerous, Akamori has a small fighting ability.
I shouldn't go
When I was walking on a tree
[music]
I can go there and there.
It's this, this and that.
Yomori
Wait here
If you want dangerous magma, then magma
If you want cream, you should try slime too.
What is it?
Let's go up a little bit.
Take these safety measures
While
[music]
bread
If you see something, please tell me.
Drop what you don't have
Oh, yeah
[music]
What to fill in
Especially that's just gravel
Kamori is listening to the story from the elementary school.
[music]
Also on top
I don't know much about telescopes than Amethyst.
No, I just know where it is.
But Kara-chan wrote something for me.
There is amethyst
Location hmm
[music]
It feels like I'll be red for the rest of my life.
The cat is blowing through the air, so get out.
It doesn't seem like there is, so go a little higher on the left.
Or go back to the gate and find another location.
Okay, sure
[music]
Opposition
side opposite side
It's over there, isn't it? It's over there, so let's aim at the gust.
It's a matter of whether you can cross it without
Hey, let's move a little bit there.
Tara
Maybe
There is a possibility that they are connected.
Where is it?
Dan
Kokanakoko
[music]
Dakoko
mosquito
Uh, this one is red too
Do you want to see this one more time?
[music]
a
The connection is not connected
Ah legs
I don't hear Gusto's voice as I go.
[music]
connect
Gust's
Quie yes
[music]
Gust isn't there, but that's over there.
It doesn't seem to be connected anywhere though
I want to cut that wall over there
Naho
same as ne
I haven't seen the other side yet, but in the end
After wandering around, I found myself in the same direction.
I'm on my way
A hoglin is roaring
Edoko
Please stop growling at Hog.
[music]
It's scary, it's really flowing
Ta
The red one was also no good.
It's not bad
Kayamori is really dangerous
I'm glad you responded quickly.
If it's on that side, it's connected.
[music]
Yeah, that's what it means
oh
I think everyone is probably prepared.
I don't think so.
Uaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
[music]
Toko
oh
Ok, let's try not to fall for now.
What is it?
I'm just connecting this to the place I just mentioned.
snack
Tara de
Should I go here?
I want a red demon cut
Right now this is it
teeth
What is Waste Waste?
[music]
Lava bursts on the left
If lava comes, just put it there.
That's right, this block on the left
circle
Is it possible to use water because of the sound of footsteps?Is there any first aid?
can't do it
There are so many. What kind of feet are these?
Surprised
[music]
do
Okay
I thought it was open, but it wasn't.
But I'm making a lot of progress on this, so it's red.
It will be done
No, I'm trying to pull you over here.
That's if this is the right path.
I wonder if it can be used as a way to connect with that TTT.
Looks like you're not digging right now.
[music]
I really wanted to come to Heaven and Earth, and I opened it.
When I opened the door, I felt like [ __ ].
place
Gusto cries.
[music]
Terumori As expected, Gust has already passed.
crying
[music]
Defeat Terugust to get 5 diamonds
It's Ewasu
biome
Waste Kokohie
yeah
That disappeared
I was thinking of saying it right now.
But it disappeared
Ai cousin
Good place
[music]
Other than the Jan drawing team
Okay, it's going to go down once more.
I've been liking this for a while now I want to go down
It's scary, but there's a gust here.
Maybe from the side
I don't think it was that expensive
Then Ghast comes out of the hole.
Please take a look at Yarukoyori
This shot damage increases by 4.
I wish I could escape with a bow
Oh, I was wrong.
I caught this one yesterday. It was here, in Etchbo.
Wait a minute, that's the correct answer
Look, this is all you need.
Let's see, I guess it's still too early.
[music]
Money
No, wait a minute
Wait, wait, wait too much
Ta
It's dangerous, it's gone too far, it's gone too far
Kokokokoto
Kotoko
A mass of risks
Hmmm, that's good, you have a great ability to step back.
Okay
1 mass magma
I see.
Is it a lag?
Anko, things to say, things to say
I suddenly became scared of
Chankori-chan is in a state of cowardice right now.
Are you okay
It doesn't seem to work.
[music]
scared
hey
I don't think you can see what it's firing.
I want to kill that guy.
is also on the left
Open it up
I can't see it open.
I guess they noticed it.
No one's coming, no one's coming
No, it's dangerous
terrible
bean paste
disappear
[music]
It's still quite expensive though. There's a bit of a fire over there.
It's spread out, so I should hold it there.
It was
Looks like I'll be able to get off
But what about there?
[music]
If it's Thomas Magma
Detour
[music]
cormorant
Scary gust turns right
It might come up again, so stop it.
Well, we need pine trees after all.
4 stacks are needed.
Good luck stacking
Thank you, I'll watch over you so you don't die.
I haven't even gone on a date with my wife yet. We're holding hands.
Not
zombie piglin
I'm sure I groaned
here in here
And when this place opens, it's date one
Chan comes
height
The answer to the highest height is very correct.
But first, let's deal with the gusts.
I would like to process it through this hole if possible.
But where did you go?
I want you to stop, I have no intention of fighting you.
No, I don't even want to kiss you
Let's put a torch at the entrance to this hole.
Crying
If it doesn't scream, go.
I'll take home some glow stones.
That kind of thing
I'm hungry
mosquito
Mushrooms You won't get mad if I take mushrooms from you.
[music]
I can't pick up piglin mushrooms
what
This here and there
What's this tension?
[music]
Don't take money. If you take money.
Fieglin will get angry.
Hey, I'm doing hardcore.
There's a place where you can walk
It's just that there's nothing. Everyone just put something on.
Tene
I'll stop here
Hey, what should I do? Just walk while this is open.
It would be better if
Ah, magma cream
is not magma cream
magma cream
I'll go somewhere that's open.
Or scary
[music]
Can you see anything? Its amazing over there.
I can see it burning
Masue Gust
Irie attack event
what
Denan
But I'm safe here.
However, the latest information is complete.
Completely through
Well, that's what happened after all, so it's an event.
It was
That place is magma
[music]
I'll ask my senior to pick me up.
Wakoko
dead end
No, please wait.
Please wait.
Where are you crying?
[music]
of
Above?
Na
I don't know, I want to cross here, but right now.
It looks better than that.
cross by
stop
Quitting is a little dangerous
buy
[music]
Looks like it's gone
The magma over there is really scary.
I came here a while ago, so I'm going up there.
I guess there's a gust after typing this.
Yes
Hmmm
[music]
On top
So where should I go?
everyone
Can you walk on that side?
I also feel like getting a glow stone.
But it's a little out of reach
Hey, let's connect this too.
Not
Hey
Stop Acho Gusto
Oh wait, I can get Glostone.
That's Glow Stone Sill Touch.
Is it okay, Stone?
It's okay because it's stone
[music]
mosquito
I turned it into Throne Stone Dust and brought it home.
That's it
A cute glow that just sticks together
It's Stone, what if you say that?
It's just a feeling
Let's solidify it with a bang
Okay, this is it
That's better than that
What should I do next?
What will everyone do? Cross over there. Cross over there.
Maybe I'll try digging a little deeper inside.
I feel like it's better not to change the direction I'm going.
stomach
Teka or
It's on this side
Let's find Neu Wait, where's the nether boat?
Nianda
It might be a good idea to start digging from here.
[music]
Wart is a fortress. Wart is a fortress.
It's only available here
for now
O
I don't see the pine tree
I don't see it in
Well, I have to find a fortress after all.
Same goes for Blaze, Blaze is also a fortress.
There are, right?
Once you find the fortress, just call everyone together.
There's only one road, so I can come to the fortress all by myself.
We're probably going to a very dangerous fortress.
He said he found it and 30 diamonds.
of
Let's take everyone
[music]
But it's the same as before, so wait a minute.
lever
Clear it and it's fine. It's fine.
Maybe we'll find a fortress down the road.
maybe
I will make it an easy path for you to follow.
I'll make it up to Gust.
Well, like this, like this
I feel like I'll be able to find something with a great amount.
hand
Kio glow stone is very popular
easy
There was someone who was lighting a fire.
What's going on in this narrow place?
The culprit who set this on fire was not the culprit.
Why was it burning in such a thin place?
yeah
That's not the path of a gust.
I thought this was Gust
Wow, they are responding to emergencies.
Helpful
Rascal hasn't come yet. He said it was around 9 o'clock.
But it's spontaneous combustion.
Hey, let's walk
Kakocchi is no good
What is this?
Thin Ui
road ceiling
but
Yeah, it's connected, but what should I do?
Look, this isn't connected.
n/a
If you try to believe, you will arrive at a land that is easy to explore again.
possibility
Find a fortress, find it today
Defeat Blaze, make a potion, and enter the Nether.
I got Mort and had a little experience.
I feel like it's the other way around
I have a feeling I'll find it
I have a feeling that
I don't feel like going
I don't feel like having a fortress date.
Only Namikoyo
A fortress to go to
[music]
Wait, there's not much here.
It wasn't there
Kegebu
Ga was not a good place.
I feel like it
hey
Hmm, let's go this way, wait, from here to here.
What were you planning to do if magma came out?
eyes
PreviousMagma Slime Lots of Magma
slime is everywhere
apart from
There is a fortress in Nienankasa Gemga Delta.
It didn't feel like there wasn't much.
The gusts are screaming like they're losing.
I have an image of it being like that.
I seriously don't want to die
Sakoko's bow is strong
Nako's bow is strong
Maybe at least once
Maybe I can come back to life
This bow and Osabi stylish Osharaba
Because I don't want to have a salad
[music]
I definitely want to die
do not have
Nothing says ok anymore
Octopus
Well, if you go to the right, you'll end up in a mess.
Go back to the previous direction
Gusto was also crying on Tarako's side earlier.
Is there space?
let's pray
I wish I had kept digging like this.
Oh what?
Gust
low
[music]
There are a lot of low ceilings.
Oh nothing
[music]
I'll go without it
Kao TTtone entrance
crackle crackle
I wasn't looking for a quick fortress.
It was connected
That's helpful, this seems to be progressing quite a bit
It's probably crowded.
perhaps
Maybe it's already surpassed
One stack of pine marks that were still blue
I wish I had brought 4 stacks.
I'm scared when it's dark
I'm going to put a lot of pine
Scary, scary
[music]
Until the numbers of stones and torches were reversed.
I can't open it.
I'm afraid I'll hit the wall of that fortress.
That particular red Legacy one.
Yeah, I guess it won't hit hard.
You can just go in from there.
Look, even if I find you, I'll be floating in the air
How do I get there?
Something like that could happen, so please come to me
I'll go to the tub
It's easy to do though, Minecraft
Listen to Minecraft
Minecraft
[music]
This is such a wasteful, pointless hole.
No, yesterday with this ball, more diamonds came out than cats.
I feel like I'm almost getting a diamond
I'll do it
It was out on
Since yesterday and today, Koyori's luck is also yesterday's luck.
Maybe it's true, but that's not true.
There's no such thing, keep doing this, it's a fortress
I found it in about 5 minutes.
A lava cliff that people who have dived will probably tell you about.
point
The lava is rising on the left.
Hide it well
It means to be able to play
That means
possibility of success
It looks like a pachinko or something like that
I sat there for about 5 hours
a
[music]
[ __ ]
back one
Changwanchan
Back Gusto is crying Ah Gusto is crying
Terun
Lava
Hardcore difficulty, maximum wave 7
go
I'll go anyway
I guess the game has a lot of lava so be careful.
Maybe Dayonako is a little too low.
[music]
upper-class
Not here
From further away than this guy who's about to die
I want to climb onto the roof somewhere
But I don't have time for that.
Soooo
They come so much
is hardcore
The attack is dangerous.
Nene from a distance with a bow
Let's do our best with this bow
is more than anything
It's strong here, it's not okay, it's okay
Where are you waiting?
There are only strong enemies here in Wave 7.
What's coming out? Warden is coming out.
If it's Warden Warden, even a bow won't work.
That's right
But stacking blocks to gain height is a scary thing
I'll tell you, it's definitely going to fall.
Only the same person who doesn't remember the way home
Because it's hardly bent
Hey, I'm trying not to carry it. Oh, I'm back.
It's so great that if we come, we'll be wiped out today.
It's over, hardcore, it's over today
I see, it's okay to pack your luggage for now.
hey
[music]
Is everyone gathered together?
Na
Do your best, everyone, do your best, everyone is desperate, please help me
Can Noel-senpai help me? Help me.
Let's all work together to see if we can do it.
Let's go
Even though I'm a lazy woman, now
I want to tell everyone, no, no, no
That kind of thing
I don't have any diamond clothes, but I want to make one too
wait a minute
Yo
That's right, I have some left over to keep here.
I wish there was a shop.
friend, I guess that's it.
A dashed line kacha
[music]
I had it in hand
Tatemoto, what is this?
etc.
Dakorobe Ochan's head is that bread
Make it a hollow movement
Will you come?
Isn't this or maybe that? Let's fight
for
I have old Shanghai Taiyumi, so where is Eori?
Karasasadoko
It's piled up everywhere
Thank you, I'll just pile it up myself and go.
I'm going to ride there and say yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, that's it.
break this
Break it down so everyone can ride it easily.
I won't make it impossible for the enemy to get on board.
There's no way I can help you, there's a really dangerous enemy
I heard that there will be a lot of them.
Yes, 7 waves, right? The potion is weird.
I can't throw a potion, so I think I'll go back.
Hey, you're a magician, can you reach me here?
do not have
It looks like it's going to be a mess with the octopus. Let's do it properly.
place to hide
Hey, oh, but I have the strongest bow with me.
What is the strongest bow? Increased shooting damage that I caught yesterday.
4 Repairs that are not strong enough
It's not worth it because it looks like the last train will be gone.
I just made it
Oh, milk, maybe I won't bring milk.
Yes, I can divide it into 2 pieces, but 1 piece.
That's fine. One piece is enough. When I go home,
I'll probably give you one back if you don't drink it.
Thank you very much, that's helpful
It's efficient, but it doesn't have any empowerment.
But there's a lake here, so when I'm crossing the sea
It would be easy if you could defeat it
Or maybe one of them will come from behind?
No, I made a mistake and hit an old man.
If you do that, you'll be attacked by a golem, that's for sure.
It's dangerous, dangerous, dangerous for me.
It's different from that, the golem is climbing here.
Because there is no
Na
Wow, I'm looking forward to about 2 more minutes.
event
It's an event
It seems difficult for people who haven't arrived here to climb up.
But are you okay? I'm sure I'm risking my life to climb up
I have no choice but to get it, I have no choice but to come while being attacked.
While being attacked
Chan-chan
do not have
pounding pounding pounding
Doki Doki-chan dies when he tries to fight a real battle.
No matter how many axes you have, you'll die.
That roll
The game is a meat group, a group, but it's all about foot money.
I don't feel like I'm being protected, I feel like this
Is it bad if I don't connect here?
There will be a battle and some pretty strong enemies will appear.
Where do the enemies come from? How do they come?
I don't know what it is. Even we don't know. Wow.
If you climb up and fight against it
I'm thinking it's okay, but this
I feel like I'm going to be burned, but I'm going to run away.
Certainly, stone is better. Once you die, it's over.
But it should be much better then.
But my family guessed and I was the only one surviving.
Isn't it fine if you have the spirit of being able to do what you want?
What do you think?
Chana
It's true that the boat owner helped me.
I've already shown how cool the ship is.
I'm in trouble, I'm in trouble, I think I'm in trouble, but I'm still in trouble.
I didn't see it, so what's the punishment for beating me up?
is
This is probably the final one.
more and more coming
How did you manage to get up there?
Do this on your own
Do your best and use your power and understanding to rise to the top, bow.
The bow that goes on the bow also the bow body the bow body is the bow
Is it better to go above the torso? That's the only way.
It's a bow moving body, but especially with this sword.
Please, I'll go on a suicide mission. Hello, let me in.
Please give me a special attack or something like a golem.
Come on, you're the bancho.He's really 100 rich.
But the Kyudo bow
or
Thank you, thank you, yes, ao
Thank you, senior, I also have arrows for my bow and arrow.
Is it really warm?
Let's have 57 books, there are so many.
There were so many people who were already kitako.
If I happen to finish it and have some left over, I can put it back for myself.
I have it.Here it is.Here comes the leader.
If the leader is in a hurry and falls down, that's true.
Hey, the leader hasn't come. You can try it.
It's okay if you don't eat for a long time.
I'd like to leave it to you for a little while, please.
I may be able to do this, but I can't do anything else.
I might be able to do this
That's great, do it there too
I'm not making a scarecrow.
Oh wait
I'm making a golem.
Golem Block Iron Block Kee Genius
What is pumpkin?
I'm riding a golem.
Where are you, where are you, where are you?
Where does it say that there was an attack?
This is where I'm heading from somewhere.
As soon as it accumulates, it will come.
I can hear it from the other side, it's coming, it's coming, it's coming
Pirijipiri
Then I'll shoot Pija.
I'll use it remotely too.
I need a bow.
It's too tough here, and I have to act like a man.
Even if it's tough, there's only one left, wait, wait, wait.
Golem
I hit it and guessed it, but where is it?
Karane cow is like a cow, oh cow is a dangerous cow
He's coming, he's like a cow.
The bows are coming from the same direction.
When you get off after it's gone
Kadoko
I wonder if I should change it to something like, ``I haven't come yet.''
This way
Now that the BGM has changed, where is it coming from next?
I don't know, where is it coming?
Terubi
I'm scared of the attack. I'm scared of the attack.
Are you in trouble? Are you too strong?
Is everyone too strong? Let's take a look.
That's too fat
Will you look at the flag? That's the line of a dying person.
Are you okay
Kayone Aki-chan is excited and swimming
swimming swimming swimming
It's true, there's a group over there.
Is this a shadow under that bridge?
It looks like a shadow when viewed from
Naia book
I'm here, I'm here, I'll never get it right
He probably won't come, but the book will only be in the back where he won't come.
It's a big hit
Or the front line bring me
It's true, the Golem is doing it.
asked the golem
Something like that
It's good and reliable
Too many people left in the opposite direction.
I guess I'll go to bed then, but I guess this is it.
It's coming, it's coming, the sleeping person is starting to become a person.
I'm going to lose it, please come any night. More will come.
Maybe I should just sleep like this
Should I just do it? I should sleep. Really sleep.
Sleep well
I'm going to sleep first, this is good
I'm sorry that we are working hard.
That one
[music]
The trident on the back is a bit rare.
I can't see the trident, it's a trident zombie.
Even if you're dead, you're still dead.
Amazing backside wave that's about 4 now
Meirume is coming, coming, Gorm is doing something
I made this because Golem-kun is working and working.
Oh, there's Uchi, too. It's a win. It's a win.
It's good, it's good, do your best, it's perfect
I want it, I want a bow. I don't have a bow.
Dangerous enemy, this is poisonous, please move forward.
Some people are poisoned, some people are poisoned.
I should have brought some milk.
It's milk, the poison is milk behind milk behind milk behind
milk back milk white milk thrown away
I have some milk
Ushite Rem is nice, that guy.
I'm also going to Ushiumai.
[music]
It's fine without a bow.
Don't make dangerous moves that will cause an accident.
There's something flying around.
I don't know about that scary guy
Ota
I think he bought a chair.
Thank you very much
This is a great hero.
I'm watching it so much
Dae por por por por por por por por por por por por por por por por por por por por por por por por por por por por por por lie ah to Bex
Vex being murdered
Oruoru
It's open, it's open
Teruun
Oh what a world it is, bye bye pol?
myself
Pol Pol is so simple.
Chan
It's not a Polpo product, but maybe this
The bucket is a polka, right? A polka.
Maybe he was drinking this or that.
Making a grave for Pol-chan
Let's make it here and get it for me.
Please leave me alone, how can I come back to life?
Did it become like that? It's just a normal zombie.
Is this something I can sleep in?
I was writing a will.
No, I'm sure someone will cook the food.
I remember writing about the costume on that day.
It's too early to write in the diary
I said, ``Go to sleep, it's time to write in my diary.''
770% said it was a lie and it was a little more
It says in the Horosa that 30% goes to Princess Luna.
Tae won't come back to life
Yeah, I'm still watching it for the first time.
why
Let's all buy Pol-chan's grave at the grave.
Let's make it bigger here here here here
Aunado Polka senpai died here
Polpe that I want to make
[laughter]
The one who doesn't come back to life has long limbs.
Like Sopra
My stomach is wobbling
Is it true that it's so long? It's true. It's 9pm.
I don't have a long arm to touch it
Tokoyanajanbe has become a murder
I have to make an offering
Something amazing happened.
Because it was so dark after all.
I want a face. There's no trial anymore, so I won't be revived.
It's okay if you take a punishment game.
You can do it at least once. I love this.
Oh Pol Pol, you liked this hat.
Yo Pol Pol, everyone, take a photo!
Let's say peace in front of the grave of
Peace I'm not lonely
Okay, we're together.
[laughter]
It's right
But this is what I'm told
unscrupulous and unscrupulous
Please be careful
dynamic
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Thank you very much everyone
Thank you for your help.
Thank you very much for your help.
It's sad, sad, sad.
Pol or Pol Pol this is over, let's end it.
I have used it up
Who was that person who said something? Maybe it was just my imagination.
mosquito
Well then
I want Polpo to come back to life
Hey, this guy came as a result of divine punishment, but it's trembling.
I haven't done anything to deserve divine punishment.
Somehow, somehow, I'll play the punishment game once.
1. If you accept it, you will be able to live a new life.
There are only times
Apparently, it seemed like an easy win.
In the future, an attack event may occur without prior notice.
I have sex, no, no, I'm ready for now.
That's why it was an easy win, one person at a time.
He's dead.
What do you think about Polpol's life?
It's easy to win
Measles
[music]
Everyone's feelings are on whether he will make a strong comeback.
I want you to come back
Yo Pol Pol
Everyone is too quick to accept Polka's death.
Isn't it because Pol Pol accepted death?
Na Pol Pol and
Pol Pol Pol which one is better?
Pol Pol Pol and
Poloporo accepted salt, so I read it a bit.
I want to play with Pol Pol Pol Pol
Let's keep it simple. Rami-tan isn't here.
Ta
Hey Lami-tan
I'll take care of you
Honey please reply
It seems like you can buy it.
circle
The killer whale was near the bride.The killer whale was near the wife.
But you can't do anything and leave, Ramy.
That's what I'm saying
Enami
What do you mean, a misplaced universe?
We passed each other too much.
Of course, I don't need this much cobblestone.
put the cobblestone here
Ah, I wanted to go to TTT.
I know how you feel, it's okay
Occasionally
Well, I'll mark it with a circle, just in case.
Have
I need a nether in this way
do not have
I'll leave my head alone
Is it okay?
I'm sure it won't be a diamond ice ax
diamond ice ax
Let's make it, wait, make a diamond ice ax
Those who exchanged for more emeralds
Garuoke, maybe this isn't enough, a little iron
Bring it too
Good luck and efficiency
Are you going to dig? If you dig in the future, good luck digging.
If not
It's efficient, it's cheaper now that we have a hero.
Seriously
It's so cheap. It's like a god. It's like a god.
Becoming a being
"Huh, being a hero makes me feel good. A brave hero."
I couldn't get it
I guess he's watching over Namin, Polpol.
Definitely go to Polpol
Ta
Right, I'll do my best for everyone.
Kara Pol Pol
I'm sure there are benefits, I did my best.
I'll come back for just a minute
Good luck too, it's really cheap.
I'm lucky that I don't have the fuel to use it.
Just give me some raw meat over there.
Let's strengthen the efficiency of
Enhanced exchange efficiency
[music]
Okay, the Nether one is that hard.
do not have
It doesn't matter if efficiency is improved or not.
I don't think it'll change though
Well, the durability value changes after using iron.
Let's use this, put away the things we don't need.
Even Tanrami and Tan went to TTT.
That's right
It's scary that the nether efficiency is faster.
It's coming out with great force, Magma Bear.
My feet are instantly taken away by magma
I don't have a pine tree, I'm always here with Nenechi
I want 4 stacks of pine trees that pass each other
[music]
I wonder if there is one, but it was there too.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Lamita
I brought too much of this, so I made it to 4 stacks.
Mashonami
Tansasu
Wife manufacturing
The first thing I got when I got it was this iron crane.
Let's use it
Hey, do you have any milk?
What did you say about mushrooms in red?
If you plant a mushroom, it will go there.
from
I don't really understand that part.
Nako
Is this better?
Well, I'm sleeping. I'll come in the morning now.
Mushrooms are effective against wizards.
Blue-blue mushrooms or those normal mushrooms are no good.
what
Or okay okay
The attack event has ended.
I will be at peace
Thank you very much thank you very much thank you very much
It was so small that it had just been born.
Please give me some meat, I want some meat now.
Did you hit me? That's right. You just punched me.
Also hardcore and capons are really dangerous
Well, it can't be helped, but fish are also
The nourishing DH is coming.
DHADH Fish was also caught by Kyukyu Uoko.
It's a fish, good boy, good boy, good boy, good boy.
Please don't forget this.Forget this.
Maybe not, I'll load it with food first.
I started fishing because I thought I was going to fish.
Not slapped, slapped, slapped, dripped, dripped
Tanitaretaru
I was hit.
So please do your best and be grateful.
Once the leader, there are about two things.
I can't seem to get the words across right now, Yumi.
I forgot to give it to you.
It probably wasn't communicated.
And DHA was not communicated either.
I was told D.
I definitely didn't understand it, so I'll explain it to you.
I thought it wasn't necessary so I left it as is.
I have this so much
Tekuakokone
TT this is amazing, it's already connected
The road I took earlier
Back for now
Oh, it looks like there are customers here now.
What happened to this? I was surprised.
There's a hole here.
Continuation of what happened earlier
What is Sagen?
right
Let's go this
[music]
The right Gemga is
I really want to go to a place where I can die and have a nice view.
I can't go out to places with great views.
It seems like it's going up, it's going up, it's going up.
There are a lot of gusts, but no matter how you look at it, it's here.
It's a bit like 2 years old.
It feels like you're in a sandwich.
Very
[music]
Defeat the Wow Ghast
I can't do it either
It's hard to go right here
Wow, Polpol is alive!
[music]
Everyone is in the Nether God Army.
I'm glad you brought it back
I can move even as a spirit.
So maybe he's still alive?
Isn't he still alive?
[music]
Moe, what should I do? I'm going alone.
I don't know if it's the right answer, but even if someone comes
There's no point in not opening it up.
Let's try climbing the cat once
close
Karami-tan is in the Nether and is being called out to.
Isn't there something you want to do because you don't have it?
Oishokoshi
He probably leveled up in TTT.
kana
[music]
Wait a minute, as soon as I left that stone behind.
Small stone user
twist
Okay.
Hello above from here
[music]
a
yeah
Nhoyori is crying
Yo
yeah
Looks like it's superior
Kogami-like
[music]
Looks like a good person
Climb up Nakoko
[music]
It's not like opening it.
Oh wait, please tell me.
[music]
Teru
This is Pol Pol Pol Pol Pol Pol Pol Pol Pol Pol Pol Pol Pol Pol Pol Pol Por Pol
But that's different, I can still dig, different.
It's dangerous for people, I want to do it, but wait a minute.
These guys are scary here
Everything I did was gone.
It's gone a lot
I was saying hello, but now I'm a pig.
Scary
Ta
That's scary
It's so bad, it's so bad, it's so bad once
Hit here and collect it
[music]
Hey
Stop it, be scared here, be scared here, right away
I need to be able to escape, so wait.
Techi here
This is not your path, you guys.
What should I do, what should I do, what should I do?
Let's go on the road 3
It's too much. Let's do this once.
Gone
disappeared
I'm back to my original plan for a moment.
I was talking about wanting to get to the top.
That's right. Piglin too, please reply.
It's scary to take
Stop here, what's the gas, what's the point?
There's a lot of people in here, but wait a minute.
a little bit
picture
Oh no, stop it for a second.
Please, wait, let's get to the endermen.
I'm here, but what is this?
I'm going to shut myself away
What
Explosion with Endermen taking damage
What the heck is Gad firing? What's wrong?
This is dangerous, wait, what should we do about this?
Disguise yourself as the sender and defeat Gust.
I defeated Tanegust, right? Wait a minute.
Wait a moment and hit back
Hey, what is this?
It's a festival, and it starts from here.
I feel like something is going to come out.
Yo, it's not over. This red senior is another gust.
It's different
Gust
Echo wait this is magma is magma
It's over when it comes out, isn't it?
This is dangerous
Chatting with Aro-chan support is bad.
[music]
Apparently, it's scary to look up, so I'm running away
I can't do it
You can't run away
Hey, it looks scary being scolded by God.
But what is that? I'm looking at your hair.
too
What should I do?
What should I do? What should I do?
Let's try, scary, scary
I feel like if you're that scared, just stop.
[music]
Nemo can't come out for a while
I want to come out on top
I want to put the seaweed on top
I really need to make an escape route.
I'll open it then.
Kaukowacho, the pig isn't coming, what's going on with this pig?
point
Wait a minute, things are looking weird.
Something is wrong with me. Koyori is confused right now.
There is
What happened to that guy? He's seriously a pig.
If you get it wrong, you'll end up with a needle.
above
Even if you don't have to move up, it's not necessary to move up.
The only place you can find it is if you go to the Delta.
Mon
Put it away
Kashimaou goodbye
Where did you go earlier?
Dakoko
No, even if we go here at the same height
On this side, this one went earlier.
do not have
Maybe Gusto is gone, Gusto is gone too.
Endermen are gone too.
Okay, it looks safe. It's red or it's safe.
do not have
I know it's not safe.
That I'm scared of the woods outside
Now I'm sure it's only heading to this side.
Because it's not
[music]
It's not over there, it's a gust.
Teru
This is true
Quite a lot
upper layer
[music]
Let's go from here to there
Kako went from here to this side.
Karane
Tantan is so hot
take
What if we hit Gebugan Delta?
Monna
Game
I'll give you a drink
It's too fast, too scary, too fast
It's too scary, too fast, this is the sound of magma
[music]
No, no, no
The sound of magma
[music]
Yoko-chan, let's move on before we leave.
Gust is crying, Gust is crying
That means there is space.
I'm crying on the left
Look at the left
Look at this to the left
I see MMR crying very close to me.
Gusto ASMR now.
I'll listen to your ears
What are you doing? I'm looking for a fortress.
Ankore Himasu
Is this magma a good thing?
[music]
3 times
My eyes are open
I believe there is no lava chamber at this height.
I'm wondering if this exists
I've been digging this a lot and what I've come up with is
There aren't that many
But from here it's like that
The image of the lava bursting was just the free time.
Is it the remains of magma?
No no, there's magma breath on top of this
[music]
Is there magma fluid dripping?
This is magma
The amount of accumulated magma is about the same.
That's why there's this and that.
It's not above ground
There is a space above this, and it hangs from above.
I feel like I want to be better than you.
But Gust was crying too, so just now on the left
I got ASMR, so let's go a little further.
see
It's so different, I dug it too fast.
[music]
When you go to the top, magma starts dripping
Maybe Koyori can't handle death.
There are also footsteps
The sound of a cat purring
[music]
What I thought was that once it goes down, it goes up.
No, it's easy to go down, but it's easy to go up.
It's crazy, so maybe it went down too much at the beginning?
Nadone, it's a little scary to surpass it.
But it's not enough anymore
It's popping
Here I come
[music]
sound like gas
It's really small
But it's a little off.
I'm so scared that I put it down a little.
So, what was that magma from earlier?
Looks like it's open a little bit
feel
wait
I wonder if I'll have enough cobblestones.
I should have written a will before going to the Nether.
From smile
too
Oh, who's there?
Something you can ride with your friends
[music]
Let's go for a while
mosquito
yeah
Hmm, what's standing there? What's new?
conger blue flame
[music]
This is the same color as the one next to the conger eel.
Tana
Gusto dangerous gust
Waiting for you
2 animals
There are two of them. Wait, they're surrounded.
Try not to fall down
Those are bone blocks of dead people.
corpse
what
Chocho
I'm not used to waiting like this.
[music]
Ok, this is it.
No, no, no, no, no, I lost the gas.
Everyone is so excited!
Well done, I completed the quest to defeat the Ghast.
That guy was so strong that he fell down after one hit.
Not now nice nice
nice onyaon
And the blue flame is solemnized by the earth
Sandwich kaarejichokocchi
Let's go, coming out of the blue flame is sole sand
Wasn't it true, it's a bone?
Soul piglin, soul sand, soul
Picked up a sandwich
Tekou
There are so many sole sandwiches out there.
Oh wait, it's expanding, the world is expanding
Wait a minute
I'm making a landmark water elevator so I don't need one.
There is a possibility of dying in between, but this is Haratake.
What is it?
That guy always hits me when he's there.
There you are, there you are!
Turn your back on me
Looks more like a match
Scary soul sand is a little dangerous. It looks dangerous.
But
Yoshiko is here too
take
Yes, don't make eye contact
It's a sleeper
Everything over there is light blue, that thing is not depicted.
[music]
Only Nemopan
I need a bone
Nothing, nothing.
[music]
Hey, wait, Gust is crying.
enderman scary
Let's wait a moment there
Oh no, until I meet the endermen
What is this?
Oh, it's nothing, right?
It's just a stick. There's nothing on it.
anything
Just a pillar
[music]
Yes, what's the deal with gas?
Next
The drawing was
It was launched
[music]
fight here
It might be scary, but there are two Garths.
There is no more land here now.
from
go home go home
[music]
go right
Kaya
What are you doing in your hands?
I'm playing psyllium in Nembachabacha Nether.
I don't have time to spare
It's a little bigger here, but it's not that big.
Because of this, it's hard to walk here.
Is Gusto Gusto there or not?
Kone who is in trouble won't show me, so please show me your face.
You don't have to give it to me
But there is something
Is it expanding above this?
I really want to go
I have a child with me.
Can't you go up?
[music]
Ghast is scary
Oh, it's enchanted
All my feet and hands are slipping
I'll leave it alone
This is it from before
[music]
Do this for now
It was too close
lava bald
Naurutai urutai you
you
It's a hindrance, I can't dig it, it's a hindrance, money is a hindrance.
If I don't do it, I won't be able to do it, I'll die.
I'll say it's bad if I make him angry.
It's not coming soon
[music]
If you side with
Okay, okay, don't come, don't come, don't come
Please come back soon, go there, go there
Go here, come here, why are you my friend?
I'll call you, so don't be afraid. Just wait and go.
I want to go there and make it a little wider.
Yeah, there might be magma next.
is before
If you can hear me, come here!
O
Oh wait
I'm scared of everything.
Nezura
Okay, it's not close.
If magma doesn't come out this soon
believe
Okay, I like holes too much, right?
It suddenly became just land.
[music]
That's right, on your left hand
I see a block
play cat
Then you can fill it up right away.
Cat here
Hey, when magma comes out, don't go down, dig the floor.
That's right.
I'm sure you're panicking.
Because I'm panicking
For now, stepping back is not dead.
So that's a mistake
I put it there by mistake.
I have no choice but to do what I can at the moment.
Yo
Suddenly, everything was gone.
Ta
The lava is bald
Lava pops on the left
Is this it or not?
Lava
is an open possibility
but
Are you looking for a certain fortress?
in
I've been searching for it for quite some time now.
But I feel like someone other than Neko will probably find it.
But I don't like it, so I say it out loud
Better without it
There aren't many good open spaces.
Even if I open it, it immediately comes to a dead end.
The lava is pouring out
[music]
No, this isn't just one square, it's lava.
It's blooming
Shie
But even if it's not a solo
Isn't that what we're all digging?
Even if we all dig together
that
Looks like it won't be too soon
But
That
picture
yeah
Yeah
Nkoreko
twist
Ah, the current part
is
Hmm this is that
It's that last place from earlier.
[music]
oh
Something like this happened on my way home
It's a hole from Ekoyori.I recognize it.
Well, I'm going to be attacked, so I'm going home.
I went home
Here's what happened
Well, that hole was big over there.
Better than a cat who has already lost his bearings
Even if I go to Gebuga
Face to face with a good game
It's time to face Gemga
This is where you can go the furthest
Yo
On the contrary, it's amazing how we meet each other like this.
Affirm yourself and
Let's go the furthest we can go
teeth
This place is straight
straight
Gemga is hard
Hmm
here blackstone
It's really mixed up somehow.
Hey lava bald
It's here that I'm back on the path to where I started.
Okay, let's go back to the beginning
is scary
That's so low
Try to finish it
It's only in very small places.
Hey, but there's land over there
Wait a minute
Is it land?
just
The cut magma cube is bouncing magma
The cube is bouncing
[music]
Let's take a look above here.
Tekouya
This is how it is here
[music]
Ta
This doesn't seem to make sense
Or magma cubes were bouncing
But
Let's stop, what's going on?
come
Hmm amomo kibu jumps
Seriously where?
where are you jumping
noakoko
change
How do I climb?
What's going on?
hand
high school
like this
I'm in the nether
Yochi
message from my wife
ah
opened a little
But it's harsh
It's a tough road here.
Here
There's no voice of Gust though.
good
I'll be back
or where
In this world where I say hello, I don't say hello too much
There's no one there
Neyappy
Now
Okay, just go straight from here.
I should be able to go home soon.
But what should I do?
Still yes
still
I don't have a good date.
etc.
The nether is a place to go on a date
[music]
No, I'll do glowstone for now.
Bakake doesn't mean anything, no matter what, it's meaningless
No, you can't use it on magma in the Nether.
in
There isn't.
[music]
sleepy
click
You're free to enter as much as you like.
I don't think we should do it, since it's just two people doing it.
Hmm, why is it soil there?
There is soil that I don't know about.
Two people who love each other
So I decided to do something with a lot of people.It was yesterday.
It looks like it's going to be something like this, but it's just the two of us.
To do it
Yes
Looks good, love, love, love
You might feel empty with no profit or loss.
Know
[music]
I don't know if I want to go to the Nether or not.
I'm seriously going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going
I can't do anything about you, where are you waiting?
Where is this? Sorry for the wait. I'm here.
What's up with that amazing diamond with 3 stacked on it?
This is the diamond you gave me, it's really useful.
Stand up
Hey, what were you doing all this time in the Nether?
I left it alone, but it turned out to be a good thing.
It's a skeleton. It's better to protect than to protect.
I don't think Rami will be protected.
Please give me money Please give me money
Okay, how many pieces? I want to make golden head gear.
I don't like it, but I have it.
Please wait for a picture of Ashikane.
It's good that there are just 5 of them.
It's tatada
Yes please
Thank you, you did it! I'm off to the Nether.
Maybe someone sucked my poop off?
That's a lie, do you have Rami-tan? I'm sorry.
Rami has it
Warami-tan has an arrow stuck in it
Thank you for being gone
I did it, I'm glad I did it, I'm glad I did it, thank you
Is there anything I can do to help?
Thank you very much Nether is serious
I can't find anything good so I'm making a mess right now.
What is the Nether?
I'm looking for a fortress. I guess I can find a fortress.
I went so hard I went so hard
I was able to defeat some gusts just by digging.
A nice bow came with a bow.
I have it. That's right. Enchantment.
While I was fishing for this and that, I did some repairs and shooting 4.
Come out, I'll protect you seriously, but if you hit me, you'll die.
It's too strong that it might end up
Awesome, if you two are going to the nether, then yeah now.
So I guess I'll go. I'll go.
It's okay to be angry, it's finally here
I think I'll have good luck, so I'm going to go to the fortress.
I feel like I'll be found. I wonder if it's okay.
Let's go, let's go
Do you all have something to bring? Marue
What do you need? Give me a round stone.
Oh, I'll bring the Maruishi Necho.
And maybe that's one boat in the Nether.
There are a lot of boats parked there.
Can I have it?
Also cobblestone
Maybe it's a deep-water granite stone or something.
If it doesn't happen, it's okay. Koyori has it.
Tekunde
I have as much as I can, or rather I have as much as I can.
Thank you very much
It's okay, it's like this, it's okay to use soil.
Even the soil of
Is it okay if I sleep on the ground? If I go to bed after that, I'll die.
So please be careful. It's better to leave it there.
I'm going to die if I sleep in a bed in the Nether
If I sleep in it, I die, so why do I really die?
I don't know why, but it's going to explode.
It looks like it's going to explode
Be careful leaving it in that scary place
please
There's an orchestra that you can leave behind.
By the way, you can't use water either, so use water.
Apparently the water evaporated and turned into lava.
I can't do it, so I have to be careful about that too.
Theron said earlier that it would be better if I brought milk.
Look, I got milk, but I'm using milk.
I don't know if it is, but I have one too.
Ah, I have some milk.
So what color is this? What is the milk used for?
When I feel like I'm in a bad situation
If you drink milk and see it at Asoka Withasuke
Definitely
Thank you so much!
Shall we go? Shall we go?
Yes, if you meet Wizasuke, you will find a fortress.
It's no exaggeration to say that I've been beaten.
Skeletons in the fortress, wizard skeletons
What is a Wither Skeleton?
This color is a bit like the color of this bridge.
It's a skeleton. A skeleton like this bridge.
Yes, this slightly dark colored skeleton outside
There's a fortress there, and that's where he lives.
It's a fortress, I see.
By the way, if you find a fortress, you will get 30 diamonds.
Yes, I can get it
Yes, only the first one can get 30 pieces.
It seems like it hasn't been found yet.
Everyone is struggling.
I guess that's why everyone went today.
That's right, I was there, but I saw it.
Right, where is everyone looking?
I guess there's no point in searching for the same place now.
What is it?
hey
Yoshiitata
After all this, please give me some pneumothorax here.
It looks like I have a boat.
If you don't have a boat pine tree, bring it with you.
I'll give you an egg, a boat.
I was on a boat wondering what I would use it for specifically.
If you fall from a high place, you won't take any damage.
That's right. I want to go down there.
I sometimes use it when something happens to me.
After that, I have to climb anyway.
I don't know how to use it better than Anmako.
I'll keep it until I run out of it.
That's about right.
That's Ender Enderman
It's so nice to have an enderman on board.
I see that you will be able to attack.
let's
I wish I could go to Toto, but not here.
I'm sorry, but not here.
Is it better to go on the road than in Koyoriko? Girls?
There's a place you've been digging for a long time.
Well, there were no results. There are people there.
There are people on the road
Who is there?
I wonder who it is
invisible name
1 person solo solo hunter yes solo hunter
From the elementary school to the road, ah, it's Aka-senpai.
What on earth is this? It's better to load than this.
Lord I was digging to find that fortress.
It's a load that doesn't find anything. I see.
Where is that?
After digging, I got lost. After digging, I got lost.
This way
Koyori got quite angry because she didn't know what to do.
There's a road there, let's go, let's go
I look and see and see that it's open once.
Yes there is.
There's a place in the Nether where you can pick things up easily.
I think Toru Gas is amazing, everywhere is spacious.
I'll do a Gusto that has an image like that.
Gusto ah, I did it, nice and quick
It's early, the gas is almost here. Something is wrong here.
I thought I could go, but there's nowhere to go.
Hey magma cream, magma cream is different.
I thought it was Nodoya Ten, so I right-clicked.
If you stretch it out and hit it,
There are mushrooms growing in magma.
cream
This looks good as a sword.
Hey, why are you going so hard?
I'm not strong, it's okay, it's okay, Rami
I want to do it too. I have something on hand.
It's okay to come from left, left, left, and right.
Well, those piglin pigs don't attack me.
If you attack that pig, you'll be in trouble.
That's right, we're going to attack.
It's obvious that they're going to attack me. That's scary.
She's cute and proactive.
I've been in this space for about 2 hours now.
I'm getting used to it.It's strong.
That doesn't seem to be the case, so from here on out
I was digging straight, but it was a bit dangerous.
I ended up going somewhere.
Then I'll come to Lucky Luna, right or left?
I want you to decide, right?
left
From there, it's a little dangerous to go left, right, right, right.
But let's go, it's dangerous, right?
I have to cross, but this way
Is it connected? Is it okay?
Eh, let's go here. Ah, it's okay. It's okay. I'm scared.
It's scary, it's scary, please don't step on it.
Let's do this, this, this one over there.
Over there over there over there so what's up
Rami-chan, youre not strong, youre not strong, youre strong.
I love you so much
Eh, you're cute, you're cute, it's okay, it's okay
So why are you going to such a dangerous place?
I'm going on the road, I'll make it, I see.
It's like it's hard to fall down
The shift is good. It falls when you press the shift button.
It's going to be difficult so I'm going to shift, oh yeah, that's right, I'm going to shift
while pressing the button
Yes, it might be a good idea to go from there.1
1 piece each
That's why Nami-chan has so much time.
I'm not that good at Minecraft though.
It's too cute, hold that glow stone
When I go back, I'll get those diamonds.
That's because I get it, see this.
I made this with a little scaffolding.
Oh yeah, earth, stones, whatever.
Soil, earth, stones, this, this, this.
Take this or that shiny thing.
I'll take one pen and take four. I'll take four.
4 in 1
It has to be those guys who have been released.
I'm glad there are 4 exceptions, but it's better than that.
I decorated it so even the gross was really
It's going to be exciting, it's going to be exciting
Hey, let's stare at that light at night and have fun
Hey, I started laughing like I hated it.
I got it, now I can get diamonds.
Thank you, this place is so big. Wait, I have something to do.
This is so harsh, this is what I'm going to do
Even if I cross, it's red.
It's a red forest. It's not good here. It's not good here.
The forest is so dangerous. It's so dangerous.
Now I'm being told a lot to stop it.
comment
Isn't that good if it's not good?
On the contrary, go left
The left is the left, so which one is it?
Then I'll go backwards, then I'll go backwards and go left.
Koyori will join you where you just went.
comment
The one on the right is the one on the right.
Okay, the one on the right is stronger.
Open it
Yeah, pounding, this is straight across from here.
That's right, there's a pig on the right side.
Irresistible pigs are noisy
Let's go over there. Shall we go over there?
Turn around and dig a little.
I wonder if I can go there?
How many gusts have I traced?
Everyone there, be careful, oh be careful, be careful
Turn it on, wait a minute, wait a minute, oh
terrible
Oh no, wait, what about this rice, rice, this?
What should I do? What should I do?
My voice is burning, this is terrible, what should I do?
How can I make this good little kid disappear?
What should I do? It's food that disappears. It's food.
Ah, I couldn't eat rice.
I'm scared
The shadow of Aomaporu is distracted by Gust.
appear
I can't talk about that.
mosquito
I thought I was going to do a gust, but my legs ended up in magma.
Aim your aim and shoot your bow
Koyon's luggage is being taken over by me.
Request
Masu
I really did it
So ghosts can see each other.
I can't hear the voice
I can't cry, please keep me waiting, oh
What did you do to Na-tan and Rami-tan?
I'll take you to the Nether and the next day you'll see a ghast.
I thought I had to come and do that.
Let's go to Ramin for a while.
There are quite a lot of cases where I press 1 to go and then press 1 and vice versa.
It's true that there are many people who say Karasa is seriously the highest.
There are so many people, everyone, someone is going to die.
I don't know if it happened, but my ears were on fire
or
Hey, what's going on?
It burned, it burned, it burned
Thank you for your hard work on the fire.The bow is on fire here in the grave.
It seems like it would be difficult to visit the fake grave. Let's bring it back.
Oh, it's back, but it's a small bow.
I lost my partner because of my burning [ __ ].
That's true Poluna and Rami
Thank you for your hard work, Yono One no Jutsu is gone.
How can I turn it off?
If it's bad, then it will definitely cause damage.
Even though I was thinking about it, I was trying to eat.
I did, but I didn't make it in time.
It's true, milk, milk, milk
What do you mean by pouring milk over milk? Milk?
Looks like I should have drank it, it's really disgusting
I don't have it, but I have it.
You said that it's really impossible.
I can't put out the fire with milk.
I didn't know about drinking milk.
That didn't seem possible.
This milk cannot be cured by milk.
It won't heal, it feels like water.
I wonder if
It's such a command to pour milk over there.
well
It's dangerous to pour milk that isn't long enough.
I noticed something different.I noticed it.I wonder if this is the one who noticed it.
I'm so full right now that I can't eat.
I hope Chanpeko-chan will take care of it.
Pol Pol please respond to Pol Pol as well.
Is this that or that?
Yes, I'm the one who refused the request from here.
Why did you decline with two people?
So why did you refuse at all from Pol Pol?
I don't remember, I had no intention of remembering the way, oh, I'm back
My child, I'm sorry, but my bow caught fire.
Sorry for burning up
died near
There's nothing amazing about it, Polpol.
This all matches here.
It's true, it's not true, it's the opposite.
Nakochi is the opposite, right? Wait, this is smaller.
It felt like I heard your voice, but it wasn't.
I don't know
I declined because I thought that would be more interesting.
Tamaji
Wow, I didn't know if God was enjoying it.
Pecora-senpai, uh, pekora, pekora-senpai
Thank you very much.
Apparently not, I don't know.
I don't know, it's over to the right.
This one
Thank you for your response.
Kaaaa
I feel like I can't go home anymore.
I'm going
I'm regretting this. How am I going to do this?
How do I get there? What are these 8 different tabs?
Let's get on with it, the two of us go home.
How do you teleport?
Wait for this, how is this going to happen?
Ah, I made him my senior.
I don't know what this means
do not have
What's the report? What's the fishing?
Um 1 to the player
Even though I'm teleported, I'm here for now.
I have no choice but to go, who is Peko-senpai now?
Just go
There is a stone here.
Now
It's so hot right now
Masu
I'm so excited right now
Kunka-sniff (sniff-sniff) you before I can hear you
I want to come back
Yes, I have to make my dream a widow.
teeth
Yes, please go to Buddhahood. That's terrible.
He's doing something for me
No, no, go home
Give me octopus
That's so kind
Pekopeko-senpai, I wonder how you feel now.
Oh, I heard how to revive it.
Please come and enjoy it.
Aka-senpai, I'm still not feeling well.
There's still a ceremony in front of me.
In the middle is the resurrection ceremony
Please do the ritual in silence.
I wonder if I'll be born here, thank you
Oh Sensei, you're using black magic, wait!
It's not that similar, but if it's just a little bit, then yeah
I have to give you a cross.
What is "ba"? "Batsu" has become "Batsu"
What is a cross? What is a cross? What is a cross?
Kotoro and Rosa 1
This is a solo that has been collected from
Quite a loss
If you play solo with this, let's revive Peko.
From 1st to 1st solo in solo mackerel
What you just said was
So I got about 2 pieces of solo.
I finished creating my own server if possible.
That's about 3 of those.
Or touch it
Make a chib world
It's a big mistake from now on
Does this mean everyone is going to be like this?
Pecola's diamond, diamond, that's right, diamond
That's what happens to everyone who dies from now on.
It's not a diamond block called Diamond 7.
Neko runs side by side, and Popo runs side by side too.
Is it the same punishment? It doesn't have to be Bu after all.
I wonder if someone is doing it.
It's okay but it's normal
Sorry, this is hard, so please wait.
Oh, wait for 7 diamonds, if it's 7.
Well, I think I can do it with 7 pieces, or paper perspective.
It seems like you just gave up. Oh yeah, give up.
No, any time, any time
You guys who can do it and run side by side
I cut it too quickly so it might be Pol.
Break through, I feel like Pol Pol is accepting death.
That's probably why everyone felt that way.
Is it okay? I will write that I will run parallel to Polpol.
Let's do it tomorrow or today or now.
From now on, from now on
Do you know? What should I do?
Sorry for a little bit of everything.
And now, 7, wait a minute.
I wonder if you heard that I'm going to pack it up now?
If it's 7, it's okay.
But iron is easily available
I understand.
I'll be back in 30 minutes.
I don't want to be in the middle of the day
I don't know how to run parallel to Nohira, but I'll try it a little.
I might be a little tired or busy.
I don't know, so you can start a little earlier.
I'm busy, so increase it by 6 times. Over 30, that's crazy.
It's so bad, it's so bad, it's being dropped
I'm being dropped, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Keep the fortress alive
Damn the fortress Achan
Youkaikan
Seriously, how many generations has it been?
I wonder if it's a piglin or a nether.
It's a nether fortress.
First discovery of a Nether fortress that's not true
It's true
I went
Masu going
go
Thank you Masukora Senpai Daioh
Masu
That's a punishment game
Nico
The penalty for disconnecting is no longer a thing.
Hmm?
Is it better if you disappear?
Don't live alone, it's time to get 7 mackerel diamonds
found
[music]
There is a server
No, no, I'm soloing the server.
Not a multiplayer world
Well, I got 7 diamonds right away in Slo Slo Solo.
found
server creative
What is this?
I'm not going to get angry at Peaceful or anything.
I wasn't told that.
what
Nothing was said either
this
creative creative ecocchimo
It's not called hardcore, it's called hardcore
No, just make it 6 times more.
Tonene is with me somehow.
But this is nothing, Nechi also died.
Nene suddenly felt like talking.
It's just that Sanenemo is starting now.
Let's die for a moment, then we'll be three.
The third time you dig a diamond, you die for the third time.
You might want to run parallel to the diamond yourself.
Or because we're lonely, let's go together
I can help you even if you can't hear the call.
Sue, I don't know, maybe it's just that
Maybe you're lukewarm, maybe you'll get angry
Maybe I'll play around with you, but there's someone else there.
I might get [ __ ] raw, but I really want to go solo.
Kotosou solo mackerel in single player
Create, distribute and watch
Why is it so lonely? Why is it you?
Isn't it strange that you're still alive?
You were a little too cute, what's that, what's that
It's a shabby attack, and this one is that shabby one.
This is what an attack is, I thought, Nekoyo-chan.
Tayone was attacked a little more than I expected.
It was shabby, it was shabby
That's what killed me.
Yes, but Poroporo doesn't move forward too much.
I probably wouldn't have died without it
You should listen to it before going to the polka.
I guess he was brave enough to attack.
He's a good guy, Pol Pol says.
While I was doing it, I said it was amazing.
It was
Well, no one is doing that job right now.
Everyone said they wanted you to come back to life.
Wakananka Plaka accepts it rather reluctantly.
There was one thing that happened, but after that everyone's
When I looked at the grave, I felt like I was truly grateful.
It felt like the grave was completed, so that's it.
That's it!
Look, a nice grave has already been built.
But there are also graves, so there are also graves.
That's right, we have that exposed neck.
The grave is the biggest and coolest, but this is the most laborious
A grave that looks like a grave has been completed, but this is what it looks like.
Where are you going to make a grave? Please make a grave for me.
You're in the nether, you're in the nether
Nene is like this in front of the entrance to the Nether.
Thank you for standing there, I'm so happy right now
I'm about to find these 7 diamonds in mackerel.
Tell me which server you want
I was saying that it's not good to be creative.
If that's okay with you, then that's fine.
I was told, what should I do?
You think it's a lie, Card Core.
After all survival hardcore which is normal
It's the usual one, survival is fine.
Yarusairu Survival Normal is fine.
This is good, I won't say it's bad.
Why is the comment section so hard?
They say it's core, but it's a bit
Wait, let's ask for a polka, shall we ask for a polka too?
What should I do?
Well then, can I just submit an application?
It's snowing so much for the first time
I want the key, I've already started it now.
Still go in and put that explanation on the screen.
I just died
Well, Utan and Lami-tan died.
We, the widows, were the ones who left behind
What should we do even if it's just the two of us, Lamy, leave it like this?
Looks like I'm going back to being a woodcutter again.
I can't go, I'm wondering if it's just the two of us.
I was home
Since I died, I'm collecting 7 diamonds from Sabah.
Well, then that's it, because I'm dead.
Change the text and try again on Twitter
I have to say it
I have to do it as if a new frame has started.
Why are you like a dead senior?
Unfortunately, he was revived without doing this.
Hmmm, the precision was still high back when it was that affair.
So when the good students were still groggy,
Because it is determined
Then I'll make a cherry blossom sign for you.
That's true, bye bye
Like, "Hey, come back again."
Okay, okay, take a photo of this.
Thank you. It's snowing, but there are trees.
Well, it's snowing at the eclipse point.It's snowing.
There are a lot of trees
A rabbit is crying.Can I kill it?
Usagi Kaun
I have a grudge now
Hey, in the possession
Alright, I'm going to go to mackerel soon.
There are also mackerel and ice mountains.
Let's play gacha. I've been asked to call you.
I'm writing now
Tokoe Diamond
Taki
[music]
For now, I made an ice ax and started digging.
Should I start?
It's a lot harder, man, it's really hard.
It's heavy, that's what it was when we started this time.
It's the first one.It's been 3 days since I got it.
You know, there was iron, right, from iron wood to stone.
Well, the game mode is
Survival difficulty is normal.
You can decide on the world name.
People in the world who have strict rules
to
evening
Hmm, I can't think of anything. Don't think of anything.
There doesn't seem to be any benefit.
I think I'll stop by after I hit the air.
I guess you're right.
Looks like it's from the side
sense of schedule
In the jungle
I responded, is that okay?
Well, I'd say it hasn't changed much.
From an unchanging biological perspective
Photo of Nana Nana Koi Koi's grave on Twitter
posted
Since then, everyone has seen the grave of Kori-san.
Apparently it's popular so please check it out.
Please, I can't go see it right now.
We, we, we're going to call out the diamonds from now on.
bye bye
Hey, this is fine. First, gather some wood.
That's right, I made a workbench using a wooden ice ax.
You make it and then turn it into stone, right?
It's a good pace, Umaru is a jungle
It's the start, so suddenly there's a tree.
That's really nice. I'm scared of the night.
There are people who feel the same way, so there's no need to worry
Suddenly, it's true that Mamo Despo is also there.
If you think about it, it might be a good idea
Apparently not, but now they are dying one by one.
Hey, it doesn't matter if a lot of people die from now on.
I don't really care about that, it's 6059.
Not this block
Well
child
I don't dig about 531
What has become of this?
It's okay, it's pitch black, but there's no pine tree.
There's no such thing as diving underwater.
Mae, this is water, this is water, water, water, coal.
discovered coal found coal here die die
I'll die once. I'll either die or not.
It's just bad luck. Yeah, I guess it was bad.
Everything was so bad over there.
Did you finish that one more time?
My life has become lighter, even if it's hardcore.
It seems like all I have to do is start the world over again
There's something about you
Raaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
I'm breathing at the very limit
breathe
It hurts so much
Ah, I hope next time is a good place
It's not hardcore, it's the same world.
Yo
Isn't there a time limit or something?
I just said I'd do it in 30 minutes.
Because I'll ask you.
If it's stupid, 30 minutes, if it doesn't work, don't do it.
I was told it was fine
I thought it was a bit simple.
Pekoro is not sweet to Nene.
Senpai, no matter what happens, Nene probably
Don't you think this is good?
You've already died once or twice, so your life is
He seems to be taking it lightly, probably a game breaker.
I'm enjoying it so I'll die again anyway
Yes, there are places where it seems like it would be.
That's right, that's right, it seems
I think I'm one of those in the lucky dog position.
Right?
Isn't your voice nice too? No, not yet.
There are only trees, right?
If you find wool, it's not a win, it's a bed
No way
It seems like he doesn't know how to draw a bed. That's bad.
It's snowing after all. It's just a rabbit.
I see, it's snowing, wait a minute.
It's snowing as far as the eye can see, snowmen, nothing but snow and ice.
Hey.
Please tell me Wanami-tan is waiting for me.
I'm so happy. It was tougher than I thought.
By the way, please throw away Luna quickly. It's quite a polka.
That's a good lie, but I think it's possible to do it.
I didn't abandon her, but it was quite like that.
It's so dry, wait Ramin
It's over, but I'm still waiting
But what should I do today?
I ended up feeling like I didn't understand.
I'm sorry, but there are so many things I want to do
I'm sure I did, so I'll be back by tomorrow.
I was so lost when the attack happened.
Lammy was there and something came close to me.
Apparently, he wasn't there so I couldn't make it in time.
Yaka
Na
Haa 64
mosquito
64 height ah 5054 minus 54 current
It's high now, go deeper and deeper
Please climb the stairs.
But I don't have any coal or stone.
is
But it's Ishishiro, it's Shirokine, the white fox is amazing.
Is it really cute? It's the first time I've seen it.
There was also a Kacha search, that's right.
There's a lot of ice, so there's no ice at all.
I tried to pick mushrooms but I couldn't.
Is that Taga? Kirihara Taga or Rare Baomu?
Okay, I don't need those right now.
That's nothing, seriously, just make this into this.
I made a stick and made a workbench.
Make an ax
Great
Hey, let's make an ice ax too.
Teaomaru can now go up to the ground.
Just a little bit of wood that I'm going to dive into now.
I took the torch because I wanted it.
It's not too soon, I was lost, oh right now
I think I'll be able to go back faster if I use the potty after all.
It will be the same when the earth returns
After all, diamonds are good, right?
Apparently it's not a victory if you can go underground.
Looks like it's going to be a long time until I can dive, right?
Go Rock
There were rocks, rocks, rocks, and stones.
It's not just one piece, it's many, many.
There are a lot of idiots, but it's okay.
It's so deep, it's definitely here from the beginning.
It would be nice if you could go from
There are only icebergs and things like that, but I can't find any rocks.
It wasn't there
Are you looking at me too much?
It's a bit of a man's fault.
Wait, I don't have any food, what should I do?
It's okay, this is normal, let's make some rice.
Pol Pol, where do you think this is?
There is only one letter difference between mackerel and mackerel, but it's mackerel.
Yakoko
Ah, the new phase has arrived.
Waarenke
There's no DoriDori here or Abune logs.
It's too good, it's finally here
But if you do this, Mr. Creeper
Hello, there's no stone, there's no money, there's no money
Jan
You can do infinite moms, what are you idiots doing?
say
In this situation, you can't call me Infinite Mama.
I can't get the down, but there's no light.
The zombies are already swarming
Infinite magma formation here
I'll die from this
I want to die, I'm going to die, I'm going to die
But it's true
I can't even be calm once, I'm writing too much calmness.
What does it mean to be calm? Along with you
of
Hey
What is the most efficient way to do this?
At a time like this when all there is to do is money
That's fine
I don't need it, I don't need it
What I want is diamonds, diamonds, diamonds
diamond
Diamonds
The pine tree that Matsunamitan made for me is a valuable item.
It was
That's right. Everyone had pom poms.
It looks like that, but that was also a valuable item. Valuable.
It's a pain to make something that looks good.
This is how I can truly appreciate it
Maybe it's a good thing
Thank you you
Now, when I was number one in having the right to be completely unconcerned,
Thank you thank you
Okay.
Iron, iron is good, 1 piece, I'm licking it, 2 more pieces.
Oh, I'm glad there are two of them.
Is there still food?
No, let's calm down or we won't be able to farm 1
Don't kid yourself because it's an individual species.
Why don't you farm here? Just bring the trees home.
farming anywhere
It's night everywhere
I guess it's better to block this coming.
I wonder what it would be like to do it from above.
I don't have an image of Pshidoga coming in.
But when you say that, it's true.
The cool polka was also plugging Koyorinchi's hole.
right in front of me
You're really kind. I didn't know that. No, no.
Mr. and Mrs. Tae are playing after getting a different sex.
What
There are times when Kotori was blocked.
That was Pol Pol
I didn't know that, that was a polka
You're so sad, you're so mean, I'm running out of food
What should I do when I run out of food?
There is no food. People who are lazy look at it.
I made a mistake, but just a little.
I heard this because I was a little hungry. That's right.
Hane, I just ate warm rice and cod roe.
Good thing this is always a horo mackerel
I can't go back, it's so disgusting that I'm here.
Moreover, I feel like my debt has gone up.
Yesterday's layer of debt is still there.
After all, I don't know, so I guess the truth is
You did it, no, Peko-chan senpai
That's what I'm talking about.
I did it with the resurrection, is that okay?
Sananaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa can go up to 54 in one go
You'll die if you get off like this.
I'm going to die. I'm glad I came out deep inside.
Yeah, there was a hole. No, it wasn't good at all.
I feel like there's no water in this cavity.
come in
It's a bucket
Hey, don't make a bucket, iron.
Do you think there is an iron trap?
Sorry, Kokosoro-sama.
Is it better? Lucky water, water, nature
There is a natural generation elevator.
Hold on, who's bringing this water?
I can't stop thinking about the water elevator. It's sad.
It's going to happen, but ah ah ah ah ah
It's okay, lucky lucky lucky
I can go anywhere just by flowing.
Chikore
When I open it in the morning, I open one bottle from a small corner.
No, it's a stupid thing to do, it's a lie, absolutely.
No, it's really a natural elevator.
Natural manual elevator was really possible
It's too bad, it's too bad, this is it
Is there a dangerous enemy? It's iron again, I can't resist iron.
Na
I don't have anything to burn for a while, I understand.
I don't know what
Dodekoyori-san, I don't know if I understand or not.
Should I reuse it?
I thought to myself and lit a torch.
I've already used up all the logs, but that's okay.
It will spring up behind me
Oh, if I block it, I'll never go back, I'll go back
It's not like there's no way back.
Maybe it's not, I took a screenshot of this.
Is it okay to just submit it? I don't think so.
Polo has reached 54, yes he is a genius.
Wait, it's bright
Cree Park super bright axolotl
It's true that there are loopers
Wow, what's this? It looks like it's a natural light field.
It's the best, even the beautiful flowers are blooming
But it glows like moss
Something like this and this
The place where broberries and the like are growing.
Poison falling from the flower is nice, but
It's not like it's not all magma, but I noticed it
I wonder if I just realized what is this?
Pick up the cannon you found.
Let's make a stylish base, that's fine.
No, the zombies are looking at me.
This is where the zombies and magma are watching.
I guess you can just avoid those zombies.
get off here
If you turn against me, I won't come. Where should I block you?
The screen is so dark it's noisy and it's brighter.
No matter what
There's something about that one that doesn't even matter.
It just looks like fun, but it's dark again.
Became
Oh my goodness, there was a diamond, yeah seriously
Where was Amokoyo exposed?
Then it seems like there's one chance, right?
It seems possible. I'll use an ax for now.
I also found a polka from where I played zombies.
It's amazing. I also have a polka, but from here.
I haven't discovered it, but is it a lie or is it true?
No, no, no, no, no, there are 7 lies.
I still don't know if it's coming out or not.
No, but there are probably 4 of them, the bottom one is Magma.
It's below here.
5 of them have been confirmed, so now I can go to 7 of them.
Otherwise, it will disappear.
Polpol, sorry, I might go home first.
Volka, it's so bad, it's so bad.
It was good, but the camera and the cameraman
That diamond was fun
Where should I give it?
Groven is more food than food.
Strong or not, it's overwhelmingly weaker than what's currently weak.
Thank you very much for winning the 5th edition.
BACK BACK BACK
[music]
Back back back a different phlox came out
Yesterday, I brought that lucky ice ax with me.
I was only diving, but only 6 in an hour.
It's not lucky to be in the middle of a crowd. It's too funny.
Luck and luck ice ax minute meaning meaning no luck
It's good, but I don't want it a little more
As expected, the guy who died twice is here.
Teruaaaarekaaenanenenechi is that energetic.
But it seems like my luck is being sucked away.
There was something a little far away, so please expose it properly.
It's exposed, but I still don't have any iron on it.
I didn't put it in
Damn, this is so bad I don't want to lose
Pook giggle and it's a target next to magma
It's impossible, I'm a little disappointed
It's not the time to eat glow berries
Moro first
Okay, let's dig a little.
I have no choice but to dig. The coordinates are great.
It often appears. Something is filled with various ores.
After all, all 54 people are hired.
Oh yeah, it's easy for everyone to remember.
Remember, do you want to brag with a cat?
It's true that I'm under the blessing of Shita's voice.
Find out for yourself what you want to eat Mosarobe.
I hope Robbery is over.
Polpol No, no, no, I can do it myself
Iron, iron, iron, iron, iron, iron, wait, iron.
Is it troublesome?
Stones that I didn't bring with me because I had to make them.
A nice stone to have
in
There are probably two more procos.
If I could find a normal one, it would be over.
At first I thought it was 7 blocks.
In fact, with just 7 pieces, you can return fairly quickly.
I thought, sure, you're in the second half.
Once you become that guy from Endra, everyone will
I thought it was time to go and took 7 pieces.
Maybe someday there will come a time when people need it.
Even if it's just a polka from outside, there will be a day when I can become a shield.
I think it's coming, no, but it seems like it's coming.
It seems like that's what I live for.
Well, today it was just polka.
It just so happened that the role
Actually, my role today is that I was a proka.
Pol Pol where everyone can play that role at any time.
was supposed to be the role, but Koyori
Somehow I printed it myself.
It must have been difficult. Yes, Gust came.
The two people after that are really cute and cute.
It was so cute, I didn't even realize it a long time ago
I got carried away.
I'm not that good, but I don't like it
No, no, I tried to fight, it looks like I'm going to fight
It's not like I just went to Takaso or this place.
I guess it's not there.Wait a minute.
It's dangerous, stop your pine lingering energy, have you found out?
I've found out now, I'm looking at you, Matsu doesn't have any left.
What should I do if I don't have any remaining torches?
Collect it while rolling back
Tei no ya going going my ui
Not good for distribution
[music]
I wish it would come out. It's too deep.
I guess it probably won't come out, but coal will come out.
I wish I could give it to you, but I'm sure it's coal.
Well, first of all, dig a shallow place and put the coal back in.
By the way, that will come back.
That's right
The screen is dark, no, I still don't understand.
But as far as I can see from the front, there is still one
Well, there's not much I can do, so here we go.
Even Aiya got one, hardcore
In the world of Poloka, one is really rare.
Even though they say that, I'm going to go there anyway.
One or one everyone
I'm so tired, D is so tired
Diamonds that are not diamond blocks are average
So what are you guys going to do?
What are you doing? What are you talking about?
Naru-chan is in a bit of a place.
I think I'll end up with about 2 pieces.
If you use Nideko and the iron breaks, get the diamond.
Can't you add it up because it's gone?
I have no choice but to do it
I haven't reached minus 54 yet 9
I guess I got a 9 in less than 30 minutes.
I think it's pretty obvious that it's not there.
Shiyoye, there are only 16 torches.
What else should I do?
It's amazing, isn't it? I just applied and it's really
I want to see if it will come back to life
I want to go home to Sena Elementary School, so let's wait for Elementary School.
I wonder if this is still 1
When I couldn't find a single one, I said,
Please do something for me when I come back to life again.
It's true, but it's a little diamond
There's no point in looking for it, it's almost time for mackerel.
Why is that?
I feel lonely too.
I'm starting to miss the stream. Let's take a bath now.
mosquito
Na
It's a bath for strong people who survive very well.
That's right
Yo, there's no one else like that yet.
It looks like only two people are dead.
Looks like some people are dead. It looks like some people are dead.
I guess that's the case
Yes, I found it at Minus 38.
1 diamond is 38 and there are many people around.
No, 12, it's amazing, amazing, amazing, yeah
Yeah, there are 77 blocks, 7 blocks.
1 Wait a minute, 7 Wait a minute.
I'm starting to slump.
It's been a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time
A little bit of iron, a little bit of salt, a little mackerel
I don't want a Tokonisamigi call room.
It's not good for everyone to eat miso miso.
hand
1. There is a lot of rain.
There are 3, 4 and 4.
Wow, that's the best 9 What's this? Wait, wait.
You're next to me, you're so strong
As expected, wait, how many of these are there?
There are more than 13 good ones.
The 13 weird things I found are just as expected.
What do you mean, 8 and 7? 8 and 7
So 8 and 7 match, 8 and 7 are 15.
It is hopeless
So, maybe it's 7.
Or 6 or something.
I feel like it's amazing, it's over
I didn't have to make you wait for 27 minutes.
After all, it took less than 30 minutes.
Awesome, should I submit this or that?
This is Peko-chan, isn't it?
I think it's going to be tough, Kobo, it's okay.
I wonder if it's true that the dog is unlucky.
Suck it or run it so dogs can do it too
I wonder if it happened now.But yeah, it's true.
I just took a look. I'll go back and report this.
hand
Now back to hardcore, there are 22 people 27 let's go back
I am doing
But it's better to close this than this.
You can start again from here
We can meet up elsewhere, but we can't all meet up.
Nene, take a bath. It's just right.
Yoenene is resurrected and everyone sees the grave of the employee.
I see. Thank you very much.
I'll disconnect it for now, then plug in.
Where is it?
Well, the calls are going down, the calls are going down, now I have a body.
That body already exists, that body that exists
My body
Early
When I got home, it just brought me back to life.
I wonder if that person was the one who became the subject of debate.
I thought it was coming, so please just stay there.
Congratulations, you're such a lazy senior.
I thought, ``I did it, Senpai, I came back to life.''
He died before I was old.
I'm thinking of you right now, I'm thinking of you.
You're deader than me. Yeah, that's a lie. You don't know.
Do you not know about the same thing?
When I saw it during a break, there was a polo teri.
Iroha-chan was in the moment she died.
I see, I see. It was hectic.
I can't help it, I didn't know it was Kagami.
Why did he die when he tried to play Gust?
It crashed into a dripping tarag and caught fire.
You said something like that, right? You died after saying that.
Dandho is home right now.
I died saying, ``What should I do now?''
[laughter]
[music]
Thank you, thank you God
Thank you, I'm going to mass produce emeralds.
I gathered the equipment so that I could
Thank you Tara
Thank you for your support, Colla God
Tayaa
Where can I find some good stuff?
More than
There are no leftover units, so it's confusing that it can't be revived anymore.
It's nice
That increase
Teretette
It's a little boring
Why don't you make it more properly?
There is a nether boat.
I've done horrible things that I wanted to do.
Even if it takes me to come back to life, I hope I can come back to life.
What are you going to do? Tell me this isn't okay.
I can't give it to you. I was watching it earlier. Good luck.
It's really tough right now.
What were you doing? You were so lazy that you turned to diamonds.
I found 7
There are no pine trees, no rice, and no iron.
It's a scary world, where the world may never come.
I'm glad it was difficult, thank you
Thank you
It's okay
I wonder if this is different or that.
Didn't there ever exist a daily?
Find the fortress where all the things you didn't do are still there
There is no stage yet.
It's still the Piglin Fortress from earlier, so it's still there.
I found a move I like
But it is
Well then, I'll collect all of them.
Please write down the part.
I guess there's some kind of employment available.
Rami-senpai and Luna-senpai, please take everything except the bow.
The strongest bow ever burned out
Yooisho
swimming
It's Deruhie's chest. Thank you.
I almost cried when I received a DM from Nami-senpai.
Hey!
Tatenoko, if you have free time tomorrow, come with me.
Let's do daily
Neyashi
Right, Rami's favorite to play with Rami.
I got it but what?
nether quartz ah nether quartz ah
I have it better than Nether Quartz.
The one I left there is good, isn't it?
I'm excited to see how much of this dish is left.
I'm so excited, this is all I can do
Ah, there are quite a few swords and Tsuruha left.
Wait, who's saying "Shasha"? Who is this? Loki
well
No, I don't know who Loki is. I don't know who Loki is.
I don't know the name
No, no sleep
And I have quite a lot of diamond equipment left, so it's just the bow.
It was on fire, so only the bow was on fire.
Yes, I put it there myself.
I have the courage to go see Loki for the third time.
Maybe I'll visit
Nini
It's morning morning
Yeah, I had it, so I had it on hand, so I burnt it.
It was easy
is
Nether quartz chair
Teru La told me it was true.
I still haven't raised my voice a few times, so hit me
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's so painful, I don't want to kill him with this.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay equipment
Why is my stomach so stiff?
I want to like it, I see, hey cake
You're about to eat now, right?
Please, please, please, to this little lame-san.
Are you trying to eat the cake I gave you?
Just about five shots.
this
Dome
Ah, not yet, ah, not yet. What if I die?
No, don't be afraid. Thank you.
I'm hungry to eat this too
It's full I ran out of money
I got it from Janra-tan
Don't leave your bed at Lami's house.
Don't leave it there and throw it away later.
Tokimasu
There is also magma cream
Wow wow there are so many
Bet, everything is fine.
Hmm, everything is left, even the soul sand is left
There's no point in having arrows.
No, here it is. I'm going to take a bath.
Thank you for your help.
I was happy
No, I'll play with you again. I'm alive.
please each other each other
I can't die anymore
And there's money too
After all, one person is more careful and dies.
It's hard, my lame-tan voice is dead and I'm depressed.
Let's get in touch Let's DM DM Welcome back
I looked at it and licked it.
Come back
Ta
Sorry for leaving you alone
Thank you very much Nehimohimo
I'm not going to die anymore, I'm going to make a real dent.
Sorry, I got carried away.
Ta
Send me an amazing pienga and a lot of hearts
No kisses, no kissing faces
kiss face kiss kiss kiss
I want to find the Piglin Fortress
What should I do? It's not a piglin.
how many copies
Sorry for bringing you down
Nename
Ta
Chioke Nether Fortress Nether
I wonder if everyone went to the nether fortress.
I was looking for one, but it wasn't just one item.
come back
What should I do? I'm already tired
That
ask someone to help
Or if I dig up 30 diamonds...
I think I'll find 13 of them right now.
Ta
The shield is burning. The shield is burning.
Iron is running out
The one who is strong is the one who is strong
Didn't you give me something, Rami-tan?
I wonder if that was it. I stopped buying it because it was second-hand.
Hmm?
iron can be obtained quickly
I just put it all together.
I see, I understand that.
I really put
That's right, it's probably a good idea.
It was a mistake because I was the one who put money on it.
You probably already have diamonds.
Honestly, honestly
Let's leave the pure white bed dirty
Or leave it black
Even better than Kaedousun Kanako, Samou is the strongest.
I lost my bow, the strongest.
I want the strongest bow
I'm going to get some iron now. I need a shield.
A strong person is a certain existence.
[music]
I'm going to go fishing. Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you for your hard work. I went to the nether.
Yes, I'm back. How was the Nether now?
The fortress was fun. The fortress is back again.
I found the place, yeah yeah yeah yeah
Yeah, nothing happened at all.Oh yeah.
Shobonshoboa
I found some mushrooms here and there.
Is this where you found it?
Akinoko mushroom
Senkyu Berry Match
Yes, thank you very much, keep up the good work
Thank you very much, I won't die.
be careful as
Hate please note
Dead, now we can go to the red forest.
Hold down the shift key and slowly leave
Thank you for coming
This is so daily
That's right.
Don't just fall to your death.
I'm holding down shift so I don't fall down, it's the stairs.
I was surprised that it was a little slanted.
But there's no price for this equipment, it's really necessary.
Yes, I have a falling body.
But that Nether one for now.
Well, today from Ane Minakoko, skeleton 3
How did you collapse?
Maybe there are two of them.
In the Nether
There are two of them in the Nether, right? There's one more.
I want to defeat Gust. Wait a minute.
hand
Let's get Glowstone together.
I'm glad I was able to do it, but Rami-tan is already here.
I found it myself
Quick attack with TTT, what are you doing with the bow?
I'll go or lose it now, May 16th.
Well, I'm going to die while raising the flag.
Live already
As if many people were already dead, the next one was dead.
It's so bad I'm probably going to die soon
Isn't that so? Then what's the point of life?
Start using it now. Get stronger with experience points.
I think that's how you earn experience points.TTT
I was thinking of going to TTT with you.
I thought, let's go, the kids want to go too.
Is that so? I want to read it somewhere.
Same thing, I wanted a bow, but only the bow burned out.
Yes, actually, it's sad, it's really sad.
Then let's be together
Let's go. How long are there in the Nether?
I went there a lot.
There's a lot more food than I imagined.
Kona-chan is back alive!
It was great, Rami met Ramirami-tan.
I guess that's because I'm already sleeping today.
I almost cried when you sent me a DM.
I'm glad you were kind, I'm glad you're so bad.
I died because I died, I died because I died.
That Rami-tan, Una-tan, and the three of us in the Nether
I was there and a ghast came, so I guess I'll protect you.
When I was fighting a gust, it turned into magma.
I thrust into it, oh my, so come somewhere.
It burns out and burns out
It's called Taeso solo mackerel.
It seems like it starts from the point where you make the sauce yourself.
Thank you for your hard work, Matsumonashi, nothing.
Thank you for your hard work, I hope you'll be back soon.
It was a bit amazing, thank you for your hard work.
The 7 diamond one and the 6 diamond one are fused together.
I found 13 things that do that, that's amazing
Apparently there was a cluster of diamonds nearby.
He came across a cluster of diamonds and returned.
It's like, come back.
Oh no, I can't die anymore
I can't die anymore. It's okay. It's already twice.
Keep your eyes safe for the next 4 days until the 20th.
I really need to live safely.
Please, I thought you weren't going to die.
Everyone, please be careful because you will die suddenly.
Please, no, no, but it's still in the Nether.
This is scary, and really, when did it happen?
Everyone is asleep because they are dying.
that's right
I just came back and want to survive.
I'm back with Polpol.
Yay, I'm in bed with Sone.
Place
It's getting further and further away, this is all there is to Polpol.
If you sleep, at night
Open ah come 7 adake ah 7 okay ah
Okay.
Nyaaajame, are you going? I'm sorry.
Miko-nee-san says let's go because we're going somewhere.
I was invited to this group
Kaun Amiko-senpai, are you going to church?
Let's go to church. Let's go to church. Let's go to church.
I'll go get it. Let's meet here.
Hey brother, I went to get a bed, okay.
Who asked my brother to go with me?
I did
In the end, it was different, Rani-senpai, but what do you think?
went
Where did you go?
Can I get some iron now?
I see, I took the bed.
Anyway, there's no iron right now, so I'm going to get some iron.
go
hand
Ah, those two were also looking for their sister.
It's so dull
It makes me sleepy
I understand, there is iron.
It's a little sold out, Ramy-tan.
Everything has been sorted out by
It's gone
Right now
I wish I could pay for this a little more than going there.
Should I buy the price?
Looks like this team
It's definitely cool
If you destroy the grave of Jan Hut, you will be able to get an iron hand.
What are you talking about, Punch?
Or rather, the village hero has disappeared.
It's sad, even though I tried my best to defeat it.
Oh, the experience value is huge.
increase
The Great Explosion
It seems like it disappeared a long time ago.
It'll disappear
That's perfect, I'm sorry, thank you
Thank you Mikone-san
I wish I could be with my seniors everywhere.
I'm glad I got it.
I'm not sure.
go
Let's go
Only my sister
Seriously though, both Chiara and Iya were confused.
Weren't you there just now in the grave?
It's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here, it's here.
Is there a lot of people here?
It's a great team
fruit
Hey, good job, did you come out?
I went back and forth and collected diamonds.
Thank you so much Negiyu
I don't want to know anymore, Negiyu's friends are dead.
It's already my second time so I can't help it
Give up, it's sad because it's the second time.
What are you all going to do when you get back?
I wrote the mission before I remembered to come back.
Is that better? What should I do when I get home?
Isn't this a nether fortress?
My name is but
Let's go with the group leader that I created.
Thank you very much for the day. Wait for this.
This is the first time I've seen someone defeat Gust.
That's right
Is that the item mission?
I have to take a picture of that bed.
There's a commemorative photo spot, so I guess it's likely.
Please sleep in bed so I can take pictures.
Mochia was a great trap
I was scared of the way you said it, it was like, go to sleep.
It's a little scary, I want to die already
It's too small here.
Senior is on his way, please go with him.
Is it okay? I want to go with you. I want to go.
i wanna go
I'm coming home
Now
Come on or flag flag come on Miko
Senpai Miko-senpai, that will be a flag.
A flag that is definitely a flag
Yes, go home
Chan let's go let's go
let's go
Let's go this way
First time testing through
[music]
I'm going. I'm going for the first time.
As long as there's someone coming home, it's okay no matter what happens.
Oh yeah
I saw you caught, I was coming, I was on my way.
Are you okay?
How much does it cost?
I guess they said it was around 1600.
It's on the ground
[music]
I don't have a senior from here.
Eko's senior is there, right? That's right.
that kind of thing that kind of thing
Koto finally called me as a cat now.
Well, if I concentrate on something, I can say it without my senior.
If you call me casually, I'll probably be answered by a senior.
Should I close the door at the end?
It's better to fight
good
Niamou everyone took the glow stone
Glowstone Yes, I took it, I took it, I took it.
Oh, 1 Oh, it's already early here.
Very close
oh
Oh
circle
Wow turtle
It's here, it's over there
It's coming, it's coming
It's nice to have Mo Jungle too. That Jungle.
I was on my way home, so I wasn't on my way.
Sure, but maybe we can proceed from there.
[music]
Well, open up there and find the fortress.
Yasu
Yes, you're going to find it, right? Yes, you're going to find it. Open it.
It wasn't even there at all, right?
It's been a red forest forever, that red forest is so scary
When I went to another place, there was always a wall
Ta
scared
When I get home, I'm not netherite yet.
Ta
[music]
I'm afraid I'm going to leave now.
The graves of all the actors were burning too much
Right?
Seniors
Please give me something
I died here. When I did the PT, wow, here.
iron to
There are a lot of swords.The eyes of the cloud are fermented.
I don't have it, I have a bow, I have a bow, I have a bow, I have an infinity
I want to make a bow. I want an infinite bow.
Me too, it's too early.
Infinite is in my house. Infinite is like that.
[music]
with infinity
There are many other free
Free Kaela-chan House
Karaha
So it changed
[music]
Nene
Corde
Aldi blew away
Blow me away with a sword
Oh wait, I chose this.
I defeated this and that skeleton.
Because it becomes
Yes, I'm sure
[music]
to
It's easy to take a nap
It can't be helped if you just take it.
I already took it. I want to give it to Nico too.
I want to take it, take it, take it, monster
I can't sleep because I'm so close
Take it, take it
Send it
Okay, wait, something is playing.
Wait a minute
It's not showing up.
I was so surprised that if I slept here, something would turn into water.
It felt like I was washed away
Jiji, where are you going to sleep? Let's sleep on the edge. On the edge.
It's a spot. I was surprised.
It's a spot, send me a photo of your sister
Where will I send my warm sister?
The cat is also
yes
Yes, I want to make good photos and pictures.
I also made
Clouds don't come up here.
I'm sure it is, but it's special.
Bows and arrows are not clouds, but if they change
That's a good arrow
It's pretty easy to make, you don't even need clouds.
Masu
It's so weird, isn't it?
Ane it's okay bow
Bare
[music]
I also buy a bow
Can I buy a bow?
If we struggle, the village will not last.
I wonder if there are no palms or not.
do not have
But it looks like I'll definitely need a bow.
Yes, that's right. I'm about to learn bowing.
I'm so tired. My bow is burning.
And
[music]
Oh, I might have a bow, so I might as well make one.
certain
Ninanda Yashie was able to make it quite quickly.
I might be able to create memories now.That block of palms
easy
It's easy
No mice come out, more than cats.
Maybe not.
Yes, it can be made with fire and wood.
I'll probably have some leftover while I can.
Let's make something. Shall we make something together?
I don't know what to do just a little bit
It's a money grabber
[laughter]
But how much bones are gold?
I don't have money, I don't have money
Let's name it
think
I want a daddy
You can get it by asking.
I'm not using it
I'm going back to Dara.
Where is the infinity?
Apparently there is
Yeah, there's no such thing as a house.
Is this it now?
place
O
let's go let's go
You can do it for me
Helpful
Have this
change
I hear some kind of scream
What happens after Tatsumomo's dream?
is
mosquito
It's okay, I want to do something, I can hear the dream
But it's okay
Ehaha
Ao is it okay? It's okay, it's okay, it's okay
Are you okay
GoodAll
good a good maybe miko
This is cute today too, teacher.
You did it
There's something wrong with that
Something is wrong with Sui-chan being a little silly.
Takana is still a cute Sui-chan, Ponkosi.
I do, but it's a bit clumsy today.
It's No-chan, I can't seem to count.
I don't think I can do it, but I don't know.
Chan can't do it either.
It's tough
Bye bye bye go to Baccarat's house
Give it to me bye bye bye
by
Nokuru-chan, bye-bye-chan and the camera
I took it, no infinity reading, no infinity.
Reading too
I wonder if Uncle Nau has any left?
House Ototle House Spospo Heart
of
House Heart's House Nana Heart House
I feel like I'm just trapped
I feel sorry for the turtle.I feel sorry for the turtle.
Let's go let's go I'll send Taro Urashima
This is Ore Go Let's Go Let's Go Let's
Where is Goka's house?Love
Nai gust gust eh
Run away, you died because of Lugust.
It's scary, it's scary, it's scary, it's trauma
[music]
Trauma is scary
Gusto
I got the bow and arrow that I'm definitely going to get.
Even if you can do gust as a bow raiser
You're going to die, man.
There is no salvation in this world anymore
No way, but there is salvation
I'm sure you survived, but now you're done.
It's okay, it's not there anymore
[music]
Maybe that's what makes people strong
Yo almost died once
I won't die. Clear the episode without dying.
that goal
From now until it enters the magma
[music]
die here
I might need some emeralds.
Emerald Emerald I went to the house to get it.
I'm coming too
Was there something?
I left 8 of them at home.
Is it a prediction again? A little more than this
I rarely say things because my predictions come true.
Maybe it's better not to have it though
I never said anything about my death.
I did it
Na
Damn it, I predicted Kua-senpai's death.
I didn't say it was limited to Nema-senpai, but who is that?
I thought it looked like it was me, but it turned out to be true.
Because I did it myself
People can't see the minutes, so it feels real.
The dog that came
Seriously, the Grim Reaper will come just when you forget.
There were 8 of them, I really let my guard down.
I don't need it
Hold on to these bones, they'll burn too.
32 pieces
A little iron
If it was just a certain book, I think Karashi would have it.
say something like that
In the first place, Yumi-ah waits and makes a big vegetable.
From Kurunjananakatako
That's how Toane Diamond's prophecy came true.
If you said you were going to come out right now, come out.
I also have some liquid so I can make some delicious vegetables.
Let's go
Well, maybe all the trees burned down.
There was no
Let's go, even though I still have it in my hand
Why is only the bow burning?
is
I came back in 30 minutes, but I'm sure I won.
I never thought I could get 13 from there.
I didn't think so
I was facing the archer, so I was already with my body.
It was on fire. Where is everyone? What?
bean paste
I'm here, Pekoro-senpai
Yakaji-chan
What are you doing?
I guess it happened once before when I was so frozen.
That's about it
Ota
Thank you very much.
I don't know anymore, what about that guy?
In this world, I can become a senior who gave me something.
This is how I express that it's not sweet.
It seems like this is self-destruction
Shiro, that boss is smoking.
A woman was given gunpowder and was given dangerous powder.
I'll be taken away
It's like telling me to self-destruct at any time.
I guess if I commit a crime, I'll self-destruct.
This is probably what it is, right? It's garbage.
Teru
But different, different cloud eyes, cloud eyes, solder clouds
There is a thread of
I guess it means that you should do your best.
That's right, I'll go ahead and put up the mat.
It's garbage after all.
But these are valuable and heavy items.
Well, I lost my catch. I was fishing.
I wonder if he was telling me that.
Even though it's different, it's different from that oga shell.
like
The princess told me to live by firmly protecting myself.
I want Loki
Everyone, come on, Loki is coming, run away.
I can sleep if I don't sleep I have a bed where I can sleep here
Hey, take a bed
Hey, Pecora-senpai, I was attacked.
But I guess I wasn't sleeping.
Hey
Kiroki is here
It's a bed.
Is that okay? Abecho, please wait.
a
Why does he look like Becho Banchou?
Pecola-chan sleeps in the first room
Thank you for taking it away and taking it away for nothing.
It's the first time
Hey, what do you have? This looks like ammolite.
Loki, are you okay? Loki, Pecola-senpai
Isn't it Loki who's attacking? Are you okay?
I can only hear
good morning good morning good morning
I'm here
The chief has also started to say
Hey Kara-chan, Ata Miko-senpai
And everyone gets separated
Where is it?
Something like that
Flower
Wait for me, Senpai. The name of this flower is not cute. Yamagi.
not at all
cute
I'm waiting for it after all, so it's not trash.
delivery
Let's go, let's go which one.
I got 17 emeralds, 17 pieces.
Is it enough? Is it enough? I wonder if it's enough?
Is it enough?
Na