[Music]
so
you
[Music]
do
foreign
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
hi welcome again
to another
takanashikiyada stream
hello hello
still i still have the chicken in my
hands
always always chicken
[Music]
today um
we will play a game
that is uh
it should be easy
[Music]
first of all i must apologize
these past streams of mine have been
filled
with a lot of fangirling a lot of
stimping
today's challenge is to not
mention a certain sense
[Music]
yeah i will try actually it's not that
hard
i have to say like yesterday in the q a
it was just it just came up in the
questions and stuff and uh
it just happens you know it's natural
and also i'm so so excited about
everything
uh so it's just hard to
to keep myself from from not talking
about this
certain person but today i shall not
speak about it
today um i'll play
[Music]
today i'll play a game that is called
what
egg is broken heart is too now
people have told me
have been talking again about something
what what did i say that i that i'm like
killing my my babies or whatever
ah i don't lay eggs
i don't lay eggs guys this is a
misunderstanding i don't lay eggs
i don't lay eggs no no
no no no no no i am not a chicken so i
don't lay eggs
phoenix's how do they procreate um
basically when a phoenix
loves another phoenix very much
they you know they get very hot
together and then it gets hotter and
hotter and they start
going up in flames together and then
all that's left over is some ashes
but instead of both of them
coming back to life it's not only them
it's free phoenixes
so that's how they procreate yeah
no eggs only ashes
[Music]
yeah i personally have not um
experienced this
hot act before
i i hope that one day i can
but i've never found never phoenix
before that
i found a liking in um
i wonder if it works with other
beings as well though i wonder if it
only works with phoenix's
ah how will i procreate with cali that's
a good question
that's difficult we'll have to try it
out you know
try it with other chickens it will not
work it will not work i'm a i'm a
mythical
being it i can only procreate
with other phoenixes and in this world
i'm the only phoenix
okay anyway let's get started with the
game i would say uh today
today game is a broken heart too
i have to say i'm a gamer who doesn't
really get aggressive
i stay positive maybe i get a little bit
loud but
i don't get aggressive so i will show
you
my calm spirit in this game
mm-hmm
does this game have bgm does anyone know
does this game have btml where's the
chat
[Music]
because now i'm playing my own video no
it doesn't
oh yeah then i guess i'll play my own
btm
i don't think so okay let's play this
i've seen some people play it it
shouldn't be too hard
right is this without mouse right new
game let's go ah
ooh
that was noisy what the hell was that
what the hell was that oh wait the time
is
oh okay
but 80 or hours to move space easy
i can handle that i can handle it okay
slowly calmly um
first try next try will work
um again i will i have to state
this is very important i'm not a chicken
but i
my my fat my plant fast food restaurant
will mostly be
selling chicken so
i have to learn how to deal
with uh i have to learn how to deal with
these ingredients you know
easy easy easy easy calm calm come come
okay no problem
oh
this will take a while i see
oh are you counting is there no counter
on the street on the screen that's sad
you'll be counting guys i'll leave it to
you me
no
okay okay okay let's go let's go let's
go actually there's another um chicken
related game that i kind of want to play
soon oh come on
another game that i want to play is
related to chicken
it says a certain how do you say that
call now carl now kernel
a certain colonel is in that game
oh we've never been this far
come on come on yeah but we still have
to get the
permission what
[Music]
no
yeah yeah yeah i still wanted to play it
already but
we'll get there friends
is there any other good game that is
related to chicken i need to study the
chicken if i want to cook the chicken
slowly slowly slowly okay okay
[Laughter]
okay here we need to take care right
on josie okay
how close can i get these clothes
is this better with like running over it
or should i get closer and then jump
run you're liars you just want me to die
i want to protect the chicken
add the egg yeah
oh
i can start here nice nice eyeshadow
well that actually that broke my heart
indeed
seeing that chicken turned into wings
man that really hurt
come on
it's all good it's all good
i said by the way how do you how do you
guys like your eggs uh
cooked i i want them to be cooked
really really really well really hard
ah no i don't mean that way i mean like
how oh
i mean like
i should have kept on running
oh
i see we have some communication
problems guys i mean
how how how oh
how oh
how hard how hard how hard
[Applause]
we did it i thought i was gonna die
there
nice safe and now how do we get down
will the act just fly away when i jump
up should i just let myself fall
out you know that's impossible what the
hell no
not here no that's not fair run run run
run
that was not fair how are how did the
plates
kill the egg eggs
sorry sorry little baby egg
no no why you go there
okay oh this chicken looks so fluffy i
wanna hug it
you know my my phoenix mom my phoenix
mom
she's in a different dimension at the
moment
i haven't seen my phoenix mom in a while
but she actually
has a yard with a chicken
yeah what the hell she she has chicken
but the last time i saw her she had
chicken but she said something like
she's gonna eat them eventually and i
was like
mom no don't eat
the chicken it's like when you actually
see them
it just breaks your heart man
[Music]
it
my mom is uh
i don't know why oh okay i need to focus
ah oh yeah okay okay calm calm down calm
down calm down
you're literally holding chicken legs
while you say that
i i never killed a chicken i have never
killed a chicken i always protect the
chicken
i'm not the one who's killing them i'm
not the one that's killing them
no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no
no
i was so good at the beginning i need to
[Music]
uh 23 already
god damn it no no
[Music]
please please let me pass
don't cook me okay we have a lot of eggs
in stock so you can break the eggs but
don't cook me
it's not me it's not me never mind dad
never mind
no no no no no i just mean because i'm
playing the chicken i'm not the chicken
i'm playing the chicken
so i said don't don't kill me that's
what i meant because i'm playing the
chicken
but it's not like i am the chicken
nice
maybe maybe run again
[Music]
this this scares me okay go
no oh we start here nice nice okay okay
oh yeah let's try to let's try to run
my heart hurts
[Music]
you go first egg
have a good life egg
oh my god
oh yeah what was first the chicken or
the egg
place your pets now
no no no no
uh
question of life the phoenix came first
jump no no no oh
this hurts this hurts i i'm killing so
many chicken
i'm killing so many bright futures
watashi
wait weren't we already further than
this why did they bring me back or was
did i not see this is what you call
a big brain don't remember where you
came from don't remember who you are
where you are we raise chickens they
don't have a lot going on in terms of
career
excuse me
how rude of you to say that
35 already where is babysitter
i'm i'm not oh i'm not babysitting i'm
trying to do my job here okay
we are opening
we are opening a worldwide fast food
chain
i really like chicken burgers i really
like chicken burgers more than
normal beef burgers what about you guys
i just suicided myself
i wanna go
suicide beef
beef better i like
ah keanu burger shut up and there's
never gonna be a kiana burger
oh god
beef
[Music]
no i mean you know what i like
a beef burger with pineapple in it
with a slice of pineapple that's like
you probably have noticed by now i have
a liking for pineapple
what are you guys angry about again
just try it guys you need to try new
things in your life
why do you all hate pineapple pineapple
on pizza pineapple on burger
there's nothing bad about that by the
way no bgm
what i hear bjm
oh what is it too quiet
what about these
well noticed that pretty early is that
too loud
i like pineapple nice
pineapple pizza
oh my god come on
i hate this game sorry i love it i love
it i love it
i love it um
pineapple pizza yeah i was playing the
museum all along
you know pineapple pizza is just so
refreshing
hmm
getting over it i shall never play
getting over it
oh my god what phuket papa made
made a sword
on twitter i just saw
hookah papa is making my sword
oh guys check out the twitter of my papa
he's like making my sword
oh yeah i think he's making it in 3d
3d debut coming soon just kidding just
kidding just kidding
will i ever get past this point though
please coco coin
okay come on come on we gotta be strong
together
yes no
put those blades away who put those
blades there
where are my employees you know there's
a bunch of
bunch of people on twitter who are
acting as my employees
which is hella funny
i haven't even opened the restaurant yet
how do
come on okay okay okay let's
let's focus for a little moment
did i when i made it through here first
did i run or did i go slowly
yes oh why you go so bad
it's this actually you know what that
this proves this egg must be empty
because otherwise it wouldn't fly that
like
nicely that smoothly that
that
so it's okay if it breaks because
there's no life inside
okay okay
okay okay now stay calm
stay calm
[Music]
calm wait why am i back here again i
don't want to be here anymore
no fox egg is empty yeah actually like
oh you can do it kiara
thank you i shall i shall i shall
save the egg no put those plates away
who put those blades there i have to
fire the guy who put those plates there
could be i always go back
yes
stop stay calm you could
okay okay we can do this guys we can do
it
we can't do it okay ju run
run or slowly
oh
here we go yes yes yes yes yes yes
keep running keep running chicken
how long is this where's the goal
i need to see my goal
go lugamia
come on come on oh
nice safe nice safe
okay
calm
by the way guys do you do you ever have
weird weird dreams i heard there's some
people that have
no dreams but i have a lot of weird
dreams
and i had a really really really weird
dream when i took a nap today i'm taking
way too many naps to be honest
[Music]
i don't know if i can tell you about the
gym it's kind of disgusting
but
do you want to know what i what i dreamt
in my nap
talk about dreams and then you'll reach
your goal
it's really weird it's really weird
you'll judge me for having that dream
that dream
[Music]
i
i needed to
pee and then
and um i
i i quickly
went to the place where you do that
oh my god no i thought this story was
gonna
bring me closer to my dreams
don't judge me okay don't judge me
and then well
i didn't make it i
i didn't make it i was there i was right
in front of it
but it was too late it was too late
and now i looked up the meaning of that
because um i feel like that
dreams can have lots of meaning and it
says
if you had this dream it must have been
very uncomfortable for you
indeed this dream is associated with
your emotions in real life
hmm actually it is possible that you
have been hiding your emotions for a
long time and now you're ready to
express them
interesting isn't it which emotions have
i been hiding
[Applause]
have you ever had such a dream when i
woke up i noticed oh yeah
i need to pee
but idols don't the idols don't pee so
it's all yeah it's all just a joke
idols don't pee so i was just kidding
all of this was made up all of this was
just a joke
oh no
oh no oh no no
i wonder how much english my papa even
understands
i actually don't know because i've been
talking to him in japanese
i actually don't know how much english
he understands
[Music]
okay he says he can't speak english at
all he doesn't understand english
perfect wonderful
let's talk more of these things in
english i'm just kidding
are you guys even still counting
he says he went to america a lot of
times so
he kind of gets it like from
the sing each single word he kind of
understands it so he might have
understood
ah
should have never talked about this no
it was not a joke anyway it was all a
joke
okay i need to get my chicken together
concentration come on
i want to touch the butt of this chicken
looks so fluffy
fly high chicken no
you go so far you cannot you're not a
real egg
no egg flies that far and that lightly
this is all fake this is all a dream too
simple
maybe i should try this game with the
chicken of my mom
one of the chickens she has not eaten
yet
maybe those are doing a better job maybe
this chicken is just not good enough
oh
one of the japanese comments who said if
he keeps on watching
our streams for the rest of the year he
might be able to learn english and i
agree
everyone watch our streams everyone all
over the world
even if your english is not so good we
shall teach you because
we all we all are not good with this
language ourselves so we only use simple
english
especially
i am not an aggressive player i'm not
not an aggressive gamer at all
i stay calm i stay happy
i'm sweating
[Music]
put those plates away for frick's
stick see i said something i didn't say
the word
i don't
oh
[Music]
i think i have to stop in between
i have to no why you go there what the
hell this was not what we talked about
are you stupid stupid egg
stupid egg stupid
how do we do this guys
coca-cola
slowly jump super slow
how do you slowly jump
no
who put butter on those plates i'm
slippery slipping
believe in myself yes yes
i protect the egg
okay okay
okay
okay how do we do this i'm scared
i was so close i saw the end i saw the
light in the tunnel
do we both have to go through or only
one of us because
i think i can handle to send the egg
over over there
but myself i don't know i'm just happy
if the egg makes it
okay
let's go let's go egg you and i we can
do this together
stop
not
[Laughter]
no no this is not how you do it this is
not how you do it kiara
jump
jump but this is too high i can't fly
that high chickens don't fly
did you not know
[Music]
foreign
papa
[Music]
wanna win
oh
[Music]
um
i'm not winning not yet this stupid
spots
need new keyboard soon
okay sure we can do this
well we can do this we are strong
you know how everyone calls you a
chicken
i know how that feels but you don't have
to be scared
don't be scared fly high
chicken attack chicken
don't be scared no don't run away
don't run away
it looks like we could do it before
i think the egg needs a needs a fight
call tell the egg to fight
oh
i think i think we won
we did it end of game
those eggshells are from all the
previously broken eggs
but the last egg made it through
uh
[Music]
oh
this is the bird language that was
talking about
we don't have much time left
we only have eight minutes left
come on believe believe in yourself
chicken
oh
we went so close with the fight call i
need it again
where are you
oh
i want to see myself win
[Music]
i don't wanna oh this anymore
i don't wanna
oh yeah okay
come on if you want to open a fast food
business
all over the world you have to be able
to protect your eggs
right yes no
why
[Music]
ugh
oh
i have to clear this in five minutes
okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay
run run for your life no not so fast
okay come on
this was a bad idea i thought i could
protect my chicken
but i can't
yo
huh oh how am i going to open a fast
food restaurant if i cannot protect my
angst
but that's why i'm just i'm just gonna
be the boss and
other people will work for me so as long
as they can protect the eggs
as long as they can protect it huh
okay this this has to be it
is
that didn't happen no that also didn't
happen
i'll show you my pro gameplay come on
come on where are you
i don't have time for this we don't have
time for this
stop yes okay
now now now is the time
the time has come fly high little birdie
yes no no no no no no no
pain
it
we'll do it until the last second
we'll do it until the end i will
i will fight until the end i will fight
for you little egg for your future for
your dreams
yeah that is me
i'm a warrior i will fight for you
i will never give up i'm never gonna let
you
down never gonna
never mind out
what do i do
thank everyone for coming today please
subscribe to the channel
[Music]
[Applause]
mm-hmm
[Music]
um
you