[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
no
oh what a soft sweet guy that was
so cute
the life has changed forever
go
everybody sounds so tired
[Music]
where are we where we go
we are back back back oh my god just
kidding there we are i knew i'd find us
i knew i'd find us
i was gonna say i was i was about to get
all smug and be like ha a scene where we
enter in and all of us are here
but then it wasn't so i had to leave and
then come back obs you sure are a
strange beast but thank you for not
betraying me i guess
oh my god
[Music]
[Laughter]
look at you moving with excitement um i
felt like i was a little bit too tall
today kelly do you not mind my tallness
i don't care
it's whatever
get you moving with all that energy
um
i'm shivering i'm so scared of what's to
come today you know because i don't know
what spins along it's been a while since
uh sorry it's been a while
okay
are you okay
you need some honey in your fruit
i had a musical karaoke um about five
hours ago and um
yeah i had and i also recorded uh like a
four song project as well so uh
i'm announcing it at the dress reveal so
be there
oh yeah
um i hope you guys i hope you guys will
like it it's kind of semi-related to the
outfit sort of
ah
it's got like a similar vibe
the project does so i'm excited for you
guys
to hear about it but yeah that's what i
did the other day and i have not slept
um but i am here and i'm alive and
that's what matters and i want to have
fun with you guys
it's been a while huh since we all
collabed together
yeah no problem alive it's been a while
yeah
indeed
[Music]
cali voice is almost gone i mean
i do kind of need to save it a little
bit but the good news is all i have to
do today is dance lessons
after this
i'm learning the jerky dance i don't
know i'm just learning i'm learning how
to dance
that's all style charlie yeah um dangle
with me break this that's not gonna you
yeah
so that's not gonna use my voice too
much but the good news is i think you
guys might be doing quite a bit of the
talking today interestingly enough
um oh yeah so
maybe it'll be fine
um but yeah i'm gonna save my voice for
yeah we gotta save it for dress reveal
and um and also small cali concerts so
um i'll do my best not to over strain it
but
yeah
yeah oh my god ian is looking a bit
ghostly
yeah
nina's existence is fading away
i'll save you i'll save you god help me
i'm a muted by the way
uh
yeah there is a hilarity chat again
hilarity
it's happening it's been like a year
already come on guys
come up with a new joke
let's let's get a new joke going let's
get a new one
can you it can be anything
um
yeah yeah i'm it looks like sponge
that's all so old uh but that was what i
thought today looks like spongebob
[Music]
family is spongebob color-wise are you
patriots yes i was actually just about
to say that you know
i'm patrick starr also same intelligence
level which is genius
um
yes
i'm definitely patrick and i definitely
live under a rock too
the territorial
what's good squid
are you sensitive are you sensitive oh
yeah that's right you're you're not
you're an octopus right
now it's crotchety though
i'm human
oh
no that's okay you're definitely a human
what about um well see there aren't any
birds under the sea but i think chiara
gives me sandy cheeks vibes
no birds
but not alive it might be in the crowd
what
what maybe i don't remember them ever
cooking with chicken meat dough it's
only a normal patties i think
yeah
isn't tuna the chicken of the sea oh
that's right is there a tuna
yeah they call it they like to call it
sea chicken yeah yeah
chicken
cute i see chicken yet i eat chicken
oh
you're literally right now in the middle
a monk of millions of uh kfps
so
we don't want to offend so don't please
don't scare them you're going to scare
them away i'm going to cry my babies
it's okay babies
i know they enjoy it really they're
enjoying it look at that blushing faces
in the chat they love it
uh
they seem freaked out
oh no they're not yeah
a few ones are playing along so that you
won't eat them your wish is their
command
but that being said i guess i guess um
that's our intro to today's session
um it's been a while since we all
collaborated together but let me just
refresh you guys on where we are in the
story um
so last time that we left off you guys
returned from a ghostly realm
revolving around a beach carnival where
you met doppelgangers of yourselves
that's right and um
and granny b led the way
she knew the proper rituals to bring you
guys back but unfortunately it looks
like many folks were lost along the way
in a sense you were able to steer the
ship
back to reality passing through time and
space and dimensions
yeah
ghosts are gone now they went away
what about the granny granny's still
making mm-hmm everything go back to
normal yeah you guys ended up um
steering the ship right back into where
the uh the beach carnival was before and
reality began to slowly shift and put
itself back together and the ghosts
slowly were sucked away into the eternal
machine
no idea how we did that yeah it was some
spooky magic
poopy magic look good yeah
maybe maybe there are some things that
you don't need to understand
i think you really
want to tell us that emma's voice is low
actually
yes and i
really like that
she sounds fine to me i can turn her up
on my end
leave it to me
yes there we go i fixed it okay okay
okay all good good okay
okay
just gotta open our ears yeah open those
holes
so
where things kind of wound up is you
guys all on a beach
and um
flash cut
to a beach surrounded by police cars
missing persons reports being written
left and right
people being arrested left and right
uh under suspicion of murder for example
those two
what were they rappers musicians
clowns oh you guys are fine arrests
aren't being made for you intriguingly
enough um while ambulances are pulling
up and taking care of the injured and
whatnot you guys are all just kind of
chilling out together along with granny
b
and when the police kind of start
sniffing around and asking you questions
another officer comes up to them and
says no no
we have orders to let these guys go free
oh oh
special orders
what special order the conspiracy
yeah
who could
um
in the end the police just end up
looking at each other shrugging and
leaving you guys to your own devices and
it is quite the scene you guys are kind
of sitting there and watching on the
beach as many people are either arrested
being questioned thrown into an
ambulance
or simply just getting in their cars and
trying to drive away and continue into
reality after seeing what they saw
oh
scary
pretty wild stuff right
yeah they're what else up on the news
says
well the news kind of just reports it as
an extremely mysterious incident um that
may have been a result of
perhaps
possibly possibly uh the spiking of a
mysterious soda drink that was drank and
mass by the members of this carnival
it's assumed that many of them drowned
ran off into the water and went crazy
after drinking this spiked soda
at least that's how it's painted
what was it called again
lingonberry spray
no estrego yeah
is that real
um
there's something
there's something like it that's similar
something something tells me that kelly
might have seen it while she was
writing some stuff but okay i don't know
i don't know
you never know it's a hundred percent
real soda um
but essentially that's kind of what the
news has chalked it up to be this
incident
and um after that you guys return and of
course are greeted um
by the bars manager who actually
um pays you guys really well for this
mission um because in a sense um nobody
really
found out about the existence of
supernaturals which is a mission that
you guys strive for
actually
um
you hope that people don't exactly and
so because you guys did a good job
you're awarded handsomely with a
thousand dollars each
oh
that was the big bucks
those are the biggest paid last time
though you did you only got 500 for that
mission though
oh i thought i got paid before
i thought i paid a live stream for this
don't worry about it
good morning
yeah
exactly
before uh
i can imagine that there's some ttrpg
enthusiasts in here who count uh like
how we roll and have our our
sheets somewhere to check if we're doing
it correct i just want to say that i got
plus one dexterity i bought it okay yeah
tttrpg
enthusiasts um
at the end of the day can i make another
casual reminder um that this is an rp
heavy focused game and story and i know
that there are some folks that like to
play ttrpgs that are very heavy on the
rules very strict about the rules
because it is a game right but the way
that the myth breakers goes is that it's
story first and if we mess up with any
of the rules we roll with it because it
takes too long and breaks the immersion
of the story if we get too caught up on
rules
um and role-playing is number one in the
way that we do things here um so please
understand that and uh if it makes you
mad and see then i hope that you will
not watch it anymore or uh like keep it
like under control i guess
um
and otherwise one is the first rule here
exactly
so now that one family okay yeah and
it's not fun when we're stressing about
rules and and that kind of thing all the
time yeah we're friends
[Music]
are we just the cast of spongebob
squarepants guys
that the japanese anime adaptation of
spongebob looks different right
did spongebob have a shark character i
swear to god they did
if they didn't like
[Music]
yeah what is she smelling
oh i can see that she's just pink
evil
maybe a little bit
my leg
[Music]
i'm the the chocolate grandma that's who
i want to be
sweet why do you all remember spongebob
so well i don't remember a thing
that's okay not everyone grew up with a
ton of spongebob
yeah
anyway um
after that little
after that old tangent which is fun i
love a spongebob tangent um
i it's all good because we actually have
a time skip you guys
um oh my god
a good spongebob that's right you
watched a lot together how much older
are we
only three months
three months
you're three months older oh goodness
but for kiara for that moment you're a
couple years younger i see
a couple decades younger
oh my god it's only two months old yeah
oh gosh
uh three months do pass and you guys
basically do a lot of what hunter
society has kind of like taught you to
do but this
this crew of of hunters this this little
society here this little sinked um
that operates underground from the
homestead bar
um
is really just
they're kind of
how shall i say
you get the feeling they're not exactly
a very
high level luxury syndicate or anything
like that you guys take on a lot of you
know whatever missions banish a ghost
from a house
stuff like that
yeah but you guys make you guys make a
little money on the side um a lot of
times it just barely covers enough for
you know your your food expenses and
maybe buying something that you want
every once in a while but it's a living
and you guys are kept safe
that's the number one thing that the the
master of the bar um
or rather the the mother of the bar um
madame m
mommy um that's kind of stressed to you
all
that you're rather safe here
um
apparently and you've been living pretty
well underground yeah thanks
mom thank you bournemouth thank you
thanks mom
so for a long time you guys kind of
continue on this way and gradually
sometimes you take on jobs with each
other like two at a time occasionally
there will be the three of you together
or all of you together um and it kind of
it fluctuates every once in a while but
sometimes you'll do a solo mission but
you're starting to get the hang of
this sort of hunter life it's slowly
settling in this is the common room by
the way big old light up sign that says
cigars
why
boss likes cigars
he's like
yes it does seem like the cigar type
yeah occasionally um kid will try and
jump up on the seat and try to start
smoking one and uh
and um
she'll snatch it away from him either
that or vic will come up and just
punt it out of his hand
yeah that kind of place
but you guys are all kind of chilling
out here relaxing one day
um
after a long mission
where madame m
the event decides to come down and have
a little chat with you guys
um
and she sits down in the chair
and um lights up a cigar
pours herself a quick
whiskey drink
takes a sip
and she looks at you guys and says
so
we've been doing this a while
but um right
i still feel like
i don't really know what you guys want
you know
money
fame glory
maybe a little bit
oh it's about the money eh
i get it i get it but like
that's so surface level you know i want
to know like
your dreams
you know
i want to know my dreams is to be
free of student
student loan debt
okay now we're just a compound
a compound a compound what kind of
compound you're thinking you got
we have some of that here we are
underground i wouldn't say that your
room is exactly built to be
a compound or anything like that but
it's something that we could work on in
the future
if we wanted
that keep you happy water
yes
yeah thank you
how about you um
smart looking one
points to um points to you
[Laughter]
her hand kind of like wavers over scout
and then points to yule
the bait
what do you see yourself doing in like
what five ten years
uh
i never thought about it
just been
worried about the present
and my student loans
all the assignments
i didn't really think about it
understandable now you've got a
part-time job being a hunter as well and
it may very well end up becoming a
full-time job
what if we could help you someday if we
got big enough we could help pay off
your student loans oh
that'll be great
no long life i can't sleep
it's a dream yeah
well if that helps you focus on the
present
uh then maybe you'll have a little more
time to focus on the future as well if
we got that out of the way
you know
fun sounds good
how about you
pay raise oh well i'm getting to i'm
getting to my point but uh okay i'm
gonna keep you on the edge of your seat
there
um let's see how about you
you
one that always takes off your pants um
in really strange moments
yes yeah what do you want
money
i was not joking
okay that's my mom my partner
i presume they are dead to me and i have
a sister i need to take care of all i'm
here for is the money
ma'am
okay
you know what that's a realistic answer
you're pretty goofy
i'm gonna tell you but you're also
realistic you're goofy but you're
realistic
i'll show you oh
put my goofy where the sun doesn't oh no
please don't show me anything extra
goofy today i beg you i'm not showing
you
whatever
all i'm saying is goofy but realistic i
like that you know what you want you've
got your eyes on the prize and that's
good but then what are you expecting
what are you expecting me to say there's
just well i mean i kind of expected you
to beat around the bush i'm here i'm
here i'm here to make a world a better
place and to save the world from all the
vampires by saving our our lovely
bar maiden mother with all of her lovely
quest thank you ma'am no i'm here for
funny do you have a complaint would you
like to file a complaint to me
not with that tone
[Laughter]
would you like to buy a local play to me
[Music]
would you like to fight a complaint
would you like to file a complaint to me
whatever
all i'm saying is my ears are open if
you have if you have something that you
want to say about the way i've done
business here
well mine are closed for business right
now ma'am have a good
uh a good day wow a goo gaga day she's
really feisty
she's a she's a feisty one
what about girl
would you would you like to have a
little battle with me here oh
do you want to be rolling strength for
arm wrestle already uh if you'd like to
do a little brawl with me i'm down
let's bro
all right let's brawl
i still like
spicy
all right she had she stands up and puts
on her gloves
oh grubs now pulls up your pants
all right
scout what's your defense
defense
yeah
wait do we have wait
yeah how do i know yeah gotta go to your
shoes in a street of country wonder
flops
yeah
then they're
flaws below two
what the heck's yours
oh
overpowered i close my eyes and choose
eight no what is your defense i told you
mine it's yours the secret
what are we rolling all right it's just
strength plus brawl minus the opponent's
defense ah so i guess it's not a secret
jk
my defense is two
uh oh
even
wait wait so
strength and brawl minus defense yes
okay
that's it too
look
you can get her
i can do this get her
one success what's your defense you said
it was two also
oh yeah all right
roll bar mother all right
all right
oh yikeys
no
wait why is it better
than greater than one oh just kidding
ignore that that's not that's not a
success
i put it as a great one no it's only two
successes uh she just gives you a thwack
you give her a thwack
her throat is a little is a little
harder than yours and it makes you fall
back in your seat scout but it doesn't
hurt you very much
you take like one bashing damage
ow
you two what the hell are you fighting
for adam what she looked like she wanted
to fight someone wants to fight i'm here
i'm here to fight if you guys want to
like kindergarten
[Music]
what about you what do you want bird
lady bird lady from a distant land what
is your
aspiration i had a i had a plan but
partially because of you it's totally uh
totally um forgotten i suppose but i
came to this land to find more different
kinds of birds on and also i would like
to see my brother again eventually i
suppose but
these these weird missions that you keep
on giving us
oh you mean we're interrupting my yes
they keep on interrupting my actual goal
adam okay well sometimes when you have a
job it interrupts the things that you
like doing on the side like hobbies not
like we had much of a choice but to take
it out
this is what i say to everyone like you
because there have been others like all
of you that have come here and leave
after a month you hear about them the
next day in the newspaper torn to shreds
in the alleyway by a werewolf drained
completely dry by a vampire why because
they left because they left and thought
they were badass enough to get away with
it to get away with experiencing the
supernatural and just walking away
pretending like everything was normal
so that's why i say to you
i understand
my life
me it was it was normal before adam
am i the one that introduced
supernaturals into your life
you crazy people out of all of you
the whole bunch of them now who sounds
like a kindergartner
you kind of snares
excuse me what an attitude you have
goodness gracious four versus one right
now ma'am mm-hmm just as a reminder what
are you being first asked for our help
i'm not here to do anything i'm not even
here to really fight you except for that
when i punched her that was fun
fun
i'm not here to be versus anyone
goodness gracious that kind of attitude
is going to get you nowhere fast in life
i promise you
oh you know that too well yeah i'm a mom
you learn to eventually just stop
struggling and kicking and fighting and
screaming and just do your
best so yeah i've been through this kind
of situation before
i've i've dealt with this
okay
and i see where you're coming from
i actually just wanted to tell you about
something today
i told you that it would be really
important if you guys got to know each
other a little bit
because you guys need to learn to stick
together
[Music]
are you firing us
no
i'm not firing you i'm just um i'm
giving a bit of a warning because
something
something bad is happening
um
recently
it's uh it's not really
it's not really news that you find out
on the streets
it's more um
under the table hunter stuff
essentially
um
there is another well i'll start off
with this there are many other groups
like us
other hunter groups that are
operating in business some of them are
doing better than us some of them are
doing worse
a hunter group is basically any group of
people that get together and decide they
want to hunt supernaturals together
that is essentially all that you require
to create a group of hunters a hunter
cell for the most part like what we have
here not all of them have the same kind
of funding that we do which is well
admittedly pretty [\h__\h]
but also not the worst some of them are
large syndicates as well
but in this case
there is a group of hunters that have
all
gone off the hinges
they have gone completely slasher shall
we say and begun annihilating
other hunter groups
[Music]
wiping them out fun completely intense
dangerous
yes extremely dangerous because they are
all extremely
well-trained individuals
almost as if overnight they became
incredibly powerful due to some kind of
freak accident or something like that
[Music]
yes and they're out roaming roaming
about
taking out hunter groups one by one
and that's why i needed to tell you
about this because everyone here will
also die
if we do not learn to stick together get
to know each other a little bit better
you don't have to be best friends i'm
just saying earn each other's trust for
god's sake
oh
that was
awesome
heck yeah
nice one nice one wants it
okay
all right i'll take that
there is one other thing that i wanted
to mention very quickly as well just as
an aside
but
you know
granny b has been working here longer
than me
she was working here actually when my
mother ran this place
um
i may have told you some things about my
mother
um
but i actually was attempting to hide a
bit of the truth
a long time
ago
she and um
there were others like you
was it four of them there may have been
five of them i'm not exactly sure but
this was back in the
40s 50s or so
many like you four or five of them
different members of this society um
were doing a similar thing to you as
well
but all of them went
a little crazy
a little a little mental
a little slasher and they went on an
investigation yeah hey wait a minute
why would you telling us this has
nothing before
oh right yeah that makes sense it has
it's almost like history is repeating
itself but for them
they ended up
going on a mission into the underworld
and they surpassed the sea
which you aren't supposed to be able to
do
and they entered the deepest part of the
underworld that you can enter that no
one returns from
and so the underworld you say
correct that's where you guys were
oh that on the world
[Music]
fragments um and the way that that place
works is that once you go deeper and
deeper into the sea parts of you just
start leaving parts of your identity
things that you like
things that make you special
one by one
begin to part from you as you go deeper
and deeper
but
there is apparently an island there
where it is possible to go even deeper
and no human has ever returned from
there
which is why i'm i'm
can't help but think
perhaps this could be them
by some
by some crazy twist of fate
possibly potentially
that these five people could be them
returned for whatever reason
from the past
but in the past
if it is them
they may want to come here and make all
of you a target
[Music]
um
it's not so much what you did it might
just be that they've gone insane
i can't really give an exact reason why
hunters go insane for various different
reasons sometimes what we do is a bit
mind-breaking i suppose for some average
folk you guys all took it surprisingly
well i was
shocked
that nobody really got
too freaked out but hey i'll take it
many of the others before you
got very scared and left and well you
saw what happened to them but
understandable
you guys have stayed the longest though
out of anyone in the past what
60 years
or so
it's quite admirable really
yeah
a long time power of friendship anna
was that sarcasm i wonder
money motivates all
yeah i suppose so money is the universal
motivator
i just wanted to let you guys know to be
on your guard because anything could
happen from here on out
okay
we're gonna die
guard just three on god
yes everyone just have friends
be on your guard
and what i was thinking is that it might
be a good idea um
if you guys lay low for a little while
because where would we do that
well just around here i would say might
be good to just hang out around here um
we're fairly safe underground but if you
guys go out on any missions above
um
then they can very easily track you
potentially with these with this
ridiculous power that they apparently
have i've only heard the rumors and the
news that's been passed around in the
through the grapevine of hunter society
but that's about the best i can give you
so just be careful is what i'm trying to
say and also like i said wouldn't kill
you to get to know each other a little
better
okay okay mom i'm just we have to
life
yeah what hotel and everybody
we're already friends we're comrades
yes as you could say we're something
like that yes
something like that yeah definitely not
rangers anymore
right yeah i i believe you 100
here's what i'm gonna do she stands up
and she walks out the door
closes the door
and locks the door
and says
figure out how to get out together
have fun
but wait we're the only ones here
where's the shopkin
oh kid
a kid is not there kid is restocking
guns because you guys don't have any in
stock anymore
i have something i do
yeah you guys have your own personal
stuff but it's not oh
there's nothing for sale right now
you just shoot the lock
oh let's
perception check to look around the room
sure what's up i'll build us a doohickey
we could use a credit card
oh my god she's screaming
all right i see
goodaleo start out
[Music]
all right oh how do i see
with your with your special eyes um
let's see which i see with your special
eyes here
um
that it's just it's the same common room
that you've always been used to as per
the usual just the difference is now i
guess all the doors are locked to
everything and you guys are alone in
this room but uh inside the room are
cabinets with
various things inside of them
memorabilia it really is quite like a
cigar bar um quite a few cigars things
to light them with the traditional bar
setting lots of drinks lots of glasses
um highly flammable highly flammable
everywhere
um
places to relax and chill a nice tv you
guys could hang out here for like a long
time
and like
she might just be like dang where are
they we're out of money you guys could
be just chilling watching movies and
stuff like that honestly just raiding
the fridge what would she what would she
do let's make a bomb yeah
we'll use parts from the tv
and we'll make a lot of money
exactly we'll ignite it with the alcohol
yeah i could always i could always work
the door open i do feel like a man out
of
uh the door is made out of titanium this
guy is just wood you think that do you
think the room is like airtight if you
like the fire it's gonna get rid of all
the auction gonna die
maybe maybe like it
laying fire is not a good idea because
we're underground
and usually
underground
no windows
they would just go to sleep and then not
wake up
oh that's an option just another way to
escape
because you want to get paid
i mean you all need money where you're
going
[Music]
but
is there is there any kind of like locks
or anything
on the doors
no all the locks are on the other side
what's on this classic riddle
what's on the tv today
yes there is you've got 5 000 channels
just too many
spongebob reruns
all right let's watch spike pop
spongebob reruns playing
as well
maybe spongebob will give us ideas
yeah well how does that riddle go this
is a riddle
it's like a yeah there's like a common
riddle where it's like oh you're in a
room with no windows and no doors how do
you escape isn't it isn't there
i thought we'll crawl through the vents
um is there a fence
it has to be ventilated somehow because
otherwise we'd suffocate right yeah
exactly with your specialized uh you i
will give it to you that you spot two
different vents
oh they're pretty small
might be able to fit in there but he'd
have to do quite a bit of
quite a bit of wiggling around in there
what was the last thing you ate
is there any butter
grease would you like to check the
bridge water
okay
all right roll uh no i'll give it to you
watertow you walk over to the fridge and
you open it and you look inside
and uh it's a bunch of takeout leftovers
um you got like
some
what is that there's like some lo mein
there's like some fried rice oh
there's like a
if somebody took like one bite out of an
apple and put it back it was probably
vic
um
there's some half drank out of soda
and
you've got
what is this there's olive oil
no butter though
oh
olive oil in the fridge yeah in the
fridge
if if we can't think of any other way
water will
go through the vents
okay
don't use too much of all of that olive
oil i was gonna make some pasta tonight
oh you better pull it out so it has time
to uncoagulate
yeah i could just cook for everyone
yeah
i mean you can't escape an escape room
well an empty stomach
that's right
so is the lock like it's it's like a
like a vault or something on the outside
yeah it's like a vault kinda has to be
this kind of secret underground hunter
society
right
[Music]
oh
but if we all pretend we're dying
and she has to open the door no no
that's what we do we do we do make a
molotov and we do release harmful
chemicals
and then when she hears all the ruckus
and then silence then she'll get worried
and open the door oh wait but then we
might actually be dead you know what
never mind
we just pretend
cause a ruckus
there's lots of screaming
well
there's no windows or i like underground
exactly
oh
what are the walls made out of
would you like to check and see
yeah all right roll a perception check
from your scout
this place is not really safe if the
lock is outside yeah i have to say it's
like usually
underground vaults are made too maybe
there's a hidden button somewhere
oh that is true
i feel like
i feel like with my special eyes i would
see something suspicious
there must be a button
somewhere maybe under the bar
or order some speakers listening to us
say a specific special keyword password
and then they will let us out
oh
oh it could be anything else
maybe you can unlock it with a
smartphone
[Laughter]
alexa open the door
hey alexa
open the door
let us out
okay
let us sound
okay google
you do hear a little
oh
hi i'm cortana
[Laughter]
well we're dead it's hard to understand
hi i'm corontana
hi i'm cortana
hi i'm cortana hi i'm cortana hi i'm
cortana i'm cortana hi i'm siri
[Music]
hi i'm siri
[Laughter]
[Music]
the girl i forgot who forgets but they
like forget every single day yeah 50
first dates
without him
for you
forget every like two seconds so you
have to introduce yourself
oh yeah
at least you guys do seem to have a
little
a little smart smart friend down there
okay
um
wait there is a siri
yeah i think it's cool except it's
called
okay it's called um
it's called archibald
your personal butler i've been kidnapped
call 911.
you got it we're calling 911
you got it calling the swat team this
building
no got it calling the bomb squad help
calling the bomb squad
send in the bomb squad boys
hello hey art art archbold
huh this is the this is the mythton
police department
hello
can we get two
large
uh no
number nines no
and
no uh
you focus
do you kids ever learn to stop calling
us god damn
they hang out i was gonna call the dog
why you always gonna eat burgers it's
not good for you you
well mcdonald's
i was gonna cook healthy pasta all right
what total will grease up now
do it
i'll help you
let me let me grease you up
my total has to be shirtless
short what
[Music]
[Laughter]
takes off his shirt
and gets all oiled up
with the pot with the
um
olive oil
hello archibald here would you like me
to call
that's 911 thank you though
not a problem yes play baywatch
you got it
but now playing baywatch theme
archibald plays the baywatch theme
would you like to would you like
anything else
no archibald thank you you can change my
settings anytime
shut up
you guys all knows how to get out
hey
how do you ask it i don't speak my
archbold change language thanks to
italian
no
that's grazie
no problemo
riverdale
uh yes go ahead and roll your athletics
and let's go with strength because it's
it's very tight so you need to brute
force yourself through there
oh
okay okay
[Music]
um
dear successes yeah you can roll again
uh
with zero successes however once until
you're a little stuck you may need some
help
oh
hey push or pull
what the toes is hanging out your
shoulders oh one success
oh nice
all right
you're able to wiggle
back out wait wiggle okay back out yeah
back out
damn it
would you like to roll again
maybe someone can help you somebody can
give you a push okay i can i can talk
you have a push all right so he's strong
strong
who has the highest brood strength i
wonder
strength huh strength is free free for
me strength nice that's pretty nice i
have three oh cool you guys could both
help if you want i have two okay you
guys you guys can push everyone can help
if they would like what will happen is
i'll push one butt cheek you'll push one
butt keeps that
[Music]
right foot or whatever yeah nice
so both of you guys both scout and tiara
roll your brute strength roll just three
dice each okay and wait watson you'll
roll next
oh nice
oh i don't know
and you push watch it through the vent
all right nice okay nice nice this is
good because with these two successes
that you guys got that adds two dice to
wattatos rules to try and squeeze
through again
oh
yeah so now you have to die
okay
oh my god
oh geez
what do you have for lunch i have an
idea then
okay
um
by now since it's there has been a time
skip i am assuming that with us is my
bird
yeah who's with you oh true i can't
stand my bird for the vent
oh ooh
that's a good idea
right yeah i thought i was stuck
you wasted all that ollie boy mama
[Laughter]
you guys
pull lothato with all your might and
thankfully he pops right out
oh thank goodness yes like a baby yeah
you guys did a good assisted roll so
working together you're able to try that
watertow did his best indeed with my
animal can may i speak to my boob
sure
okay um
is it only animal ken
uh let's see
animal can and go ahead and use um your
presents as well
[Music]
maybe you can go for the vents and see
if you find something interesting and
anything that could help us get outside
i'll let ina do it i like inna's
interpretation that's good
okay
um
[Laughter]
can we put a gopro on
is there a gopro in this thing here and
somewhere in here would you like to roll
protection
yes
look for a gopro
uh sorry it's been a while the
perception was uh
uh
it's it's wits plus uh
composure
okay
uh
and put the camera on
uh who has the best skills in wrapping
something to a bird
well with that
kills
uh five crafts i have four
do not strangle my bird please no i
can't make any promises
all right scout you can't rule your
crafts plus uh dexterity
or wits either one i'll let you choose
[Music]
also i roll the perception to see what
the wall was made of what did you get
[Music]
one i think it's one more d10 okay nice
all right with that you can tell that
the wall is made of um it's a very thick
material that is also sound proof
as well
used commonly with soundproofing and
also titanium probably behind it from
what you can
assume but that's only those first two
layers
um
i cannot hear you when you're screaming
yeah
all right roll one more time scout for
your tent right
[Music]
give me that burst all right roll again
for that ten
oh
no yakitori tonight it looks like if i
roll another success then i eat the bird
no
let's spice things up
will eat you if you try to do that
owls are very dangerous i think you uh
don't know we have to come to that if we
run our food here
that's right true facts
you will have to eat me before you eat
my burp i don't know get your stuff
together and be serious now
[Music]
scout you're actually able with uh your
crafting prowess to make a little helmet
that fits perfectly on ooh who's head
that can hold the phone oh well that
looks like you're good
good job
yeah you crafted the perfect little
helmet for for ooh that now holds an
iphone you don't know when you'll ever
use this again but it's very durable
is that not heavy for you who are you
all right
oh
yes sure you guys can be in a discord
call if
you link up your discord accounts with
the phone with ooh what's your card uh
id guys
you guys all exchange discord ids now
you're real friends
and um
after that um
since you got um a pretty good animal
can rule woohoo
goes ahead and plops down into the vent
and just kind of starts waddling in
there
doing some little owl steps doesn't
really need to fly or anything just
doing the little owl walk
yes like the way ina is walking
that's that's exactly what ooh looks
like um
and eventually um
you guys see in the discord call i'm
assuming video is on correct
kind of a point yeah video is on it's
basically a standard air vent
um and it's pretty dark in here but you
guys turned on the flashlight so you can
see mostly what's ahead of you um
and
who kind of like continues forward
waddling around it's pretty much a
one-way vent
um
and it does look like there is
very decently far deep in there
um
a way to escape um and it looks like it
leads out into the bar
um
but it's like a very small rectangle
and in front of that small rectangle
is a button
a big red button
[Music]
whose leg hovers over the button
slowly approaching
girls do you think we should push the
button or not
um
yeah
do it okay okay
go go go ahead
all right
step on the button
yes who steps on the button
there's a click
and then no sound
and then nothing
suddenly
there's a sound similar to an alarm
and all of a sudden the lights turn red
and you hear metal doors slamming all
around you
especially from the outside
oh
from the event you hear someone say what
the [\h__\h]
that happened in the bar or it happened
where we are what happened in the bar
happened in the whole complex
the entire place has been completely
sealed in
well we're safe then we've been safe
you are safe
but um you are not free unfortunately
the door is not unlocked however you do
hear someone banging on the other end
and it sounds like madame m
is banging on the other side
[Music]
what did you do why did you trigger the
emergency alarm
why not you tried you told us to figure
out something we tried to figure out
something i don't know
don't give us a hint what were you
supposed to do adam what dotto blames
i blame the lady
ah it takes so long to reset
wait
what wait what no no no no
you hear a gunshot
what teams here is boys
is that really one shot though
uh ma'am are you are you good out there
is our sniper boy back
silence
okay
uh uh well with my animal can i tell who
to come back outside of the event by the
way
all right
you relate to
come back out
from the table
good job
who returns looks a little bit ruffled
feathers just
a little bit roughly from this
experiment
who uh seems to be very shocked
and uh worried about what is going on
how long are you it's gonna be fine i
don't probably
i'll be fine
okay you know who says
in a human voice
you're the big brain among us so do you
have any idea what we should do adam
mean we could try to see if there is
like a secret
passageway of sorts
just it before
should do another perception check well
to look for it or if there is any
let's all look sure
[Music]
new music by the way oh
for once my luck has run out what's
going on with you today
you're not yourself
nice
[Music]
it's our wild card today all right type
your successes ladies
a little sad
[Music]
all right um yule
and tiara are a little
uh preoccupied um
with just
the general surroundings not really
looking the nooks and crannies etc
um
scout you for one are also
scouting
the area
and there are quite a quite a few doors
obviously the doors that you're familiar
with that lead to all of your bedrooms
and you realize these are actually
unlocked now
oh
yup trap scout you figure out all the
doors to your bedrooms have been
unlocked
um
and as for you
is my panty drawer open who's been in
the bedrooms okay
you do actually manage to find um
an interesting pattern in the floor
beneath the bar
[Music]
it looks like it might be some kind of
little trapdoor
bunker
[Music]
okay i'll go inside do i still need the
oil
oh no it's uh this is a very it's a
large trapdoor when you pull it upward
you realize that humans could could fit
here and there's um a stairwell that
goes deep down somewhere dark
oh
do we still have our belongings this is
in their room
yet
whether we already have it they are in
your rooms
your cell phones are with you but your
equipment is in your rooms
my total is shirtless
yeah
stay that way otto
it's what the toe with the shirts and
scout with the
pants they always gotta be off
all right just in case go back to my
room and grab my stuff
is it is it safe outside isn't there a
gunshot
there was better
the situation
whatever it was but the doors are
unlocked now so we can check it out yeah
the doors to your bedrooms but not the
main door yeah
oh okay
let's go to our rooms and grab our stuff
you don't know what to do we'll
take a quick shower
very important
that is true you're a little a little
oily right now a little funky just just
a little funky
so
um
i take my thing to two all right can we
is is there oil left over though can we
take some hey no
hey you don't know
if it'll be useful or not
[Music]
a few drops perhaps
just leave something for the cooking
later
please all of a sudden
well if
if we need all the oil to stay alive
then we won't have enough oil to to cook
afterwards and then we'll die anyway out
of starvation
we can buy more oil later
we can order it with arch bubble water
and my piano apocalypse out there though
it
actually sounds like it means you can go
raid the supermarkets for more
more oil all right if you want then take
it i guess
yeah bless you bless me bless you thank
you
all right so now that you guys are all
prepared
yeah take the olive oil it's very
important item you need to have equipped
um
now that you have um
now that you have all of your things uh
do you proceed
into the darkness do i need to get very
acceptable of what i'm taking with me
because i also want to take my cyanide
poison that's okay we have the we have
the document that lists the things that
you have so
yeah it's okay yeah you can bring up
also stuff
okay
gotcha
okey dokey so everyone's got their stuff
now and you guys proceed deep into the
darkness below
and it's it's got a very musty smell to
it the stairs themselves are made of
very old wood
kind of reminds you guys of a seller to
be honest but it's hard to see because
it's very very dark down there
i'm making wooden don't we have no we
have flashlights can't we use them you
do
yeah
[Music]
you switch them on
this place is very old and musty it's a
cellar actually
is it a dead wine
it looks like there are many wine
barrels and it's it's rather large so
it's hard to tell right off the bat if
it is a dead end or not you might need
to proceed a bit further
[Music]
proceed
okay
now uh as you guys proceed further into
the cellar
um
suddenly you hear from above the trap
door shuts
[Music]
and you hear someone giggling
from above the trapdoor
an odd distorted strange voice you've
never heard before
oh
no
it was a trap
it's the siri guy it's a trap door
it's archibald
[Music]
hello it is i archibald you fell into my
trap ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
ha for real i knew no i knew we should
have uh placed it all
[Laughter]
yeah
with google
with your flashlights though you are
able to kind of navigate around so it
seems like it should be
okay
maybe
but it's a very tense situation you guys
are down here in this musty cellar
and it smells
the smell is getting
worse and worse
more and more disgusting
methane uh maybe not so much
but something else that
it makes you feel you're feeling really
oh no don't breathe
you're really sleepy
can i pull my bandana over my nose or is
it too late
would you like to try to quickly pull it
out
it's around my neck it should be
religious
sweetie swappity all right whoop i'm
gonna need you to try and be fast scout
so i want you to roll your dexterity use
those dexterous hands uh and let's see
dexterity and wits together it's two
attributes but i think uh that's fine
for this rule
all right
now with one success scout
um
you see your friends
kind of fall down
um unconscious everyone goes to sleep
and scout you
are also very close to going to sleep
however the difference is
you see everything that happens
um you can't really have any control of
of your body
but
you're still your eyes are open and you
are
observing what's going on
um excellent you see your friends fall
down
and go to sleep and then suddenly uh the
trap door opens again
and you hear
five sets of footsteps
come down the stairs
they sound like heavy boots
through your bleary vision you can see
five different members in hoods with gas
masks
coming up to you guys
and dragging your bodies away
game over
they drag you up the stairs with no care
at all for your personal well-being
all the while kind of giggling and
making weird noises
um
and just being overall rather creepy and
suspicious
um can i load my save file from before
[Laughter]
um
and they pull
they pull you guys out um into the
common room
and then things start to get a little
bit fuzzy um but they actually uh are
able to open the main door now it
appears almost as though they may have
come from that side
um
as the door is the door is open so they
take you through there and scout it
starts to get a bit
fuzzy here however you can tell they are
dragging you guys out
to what looks to be what is that
the garage
it looks like they're taking you to the
garage
that you guys saw we stopped uh we
solved the mission of going of getting
outside
yay
i mean
it worked
it did you guys did you guys did solve a
mission i will say
um but the hooded members what you can
kind of observe about them scout um is
that each of them looks like they have a
different colored gas mask
um
there's a red one there's an orange one
there's a yellow there's a green and a
blue and all of them are wearing black
hoods
and they pull all of you guys out
into this dusty dirty garage
and they start tying you guys up
together no in pairs
oh
yeah
kinky
who are you tied with
let's see
now watso is together with uh tiara and
yule is tied together with scout
okay
those two are tied together um and you
guys are back to back you guys are back
to back with your hands tied behind
uh everyone except scout who can see
what's going on
essentially
um but very slowly over time
you guys kind of come to
and these five are just kind of like
lazily
circling you
with this
sick and weird curious fascination
it's clear that they're using voice
changers or something something odd
built into their masks
they look like a bunch of hooligans the
way that they move is very
jerky and strange it's definitely the
way that someone would move after
they've gone absolutely insane
they look feral
oh
yeah
interesting
at this point everyone else you guys
begin to come to
and you guys start to see all of this
but uh scout you're now able to like
speak
like wiggle around and [\h__\h]
awesome
oh are they waking up now
sure it looks like it
like can i roll a perception chick
sure
just real quick that would be really
awesome
i think it's 40 and i don't remember
yeah oh nice successes we roll those
uh
can i just do two d10
uh sure yeah 2d 10 is fine
okay two
nice
okay so a total of three successes
okay and this is to do a perception
check scott
yeah okay
um so you now have completely clear
vision
um on these
these people these dudes and you see
that they're all armed
with really intimidating looking guns
like dang intimidating
and everyone seems to kind of be like
crowding around and asking um for the
opinion of the red one who appears to be
their leader
some kind of leader of sorts who's also
the tallest one
um
and everyone is using voice changers
like this can you hear me hear me there
we go it works
they're all using voice changers is what
you perceive
um
there's something
bothering you though scout you can't put
your finger on it
you can't put your finger on why
but it's like the way that they're
walking is like it's like odd to you
it's like you can't put your finger on
why it unsettles you
but it just does
it's all like they're actually
little little little people on stilts in
big coats
um i mean it could be
oh
it's just
weird tickles me
oh
didn't you say there was like a
it oh
wait what
it tickles me if i okay yeah
it tickles me
i'll keep that in mind a little bit
i'm i'm going insane right now at 7 00
am sorry
[Laughter]
um
anyway um so they kind of continue
ha looks like they've woken up now
finally
after all
why else would they use a voice changer
people that use voice changers don't
like their voice so clearly
clearly they were trying to cover up
something that they're not so confident
about that you watch yourself little
lady
hey you
yeah
turn the voice changer off
watch my voice is deeper than yours
no no
no i can make my voice sound like this
what you're gonna do now huh what you're
gonna do now i can go lower
okay wow all right flexing a little bit
on me there yeah
um
no i don't quite feel like it we're
actually not a lo we're not allowed to
turn them off but bosses we can't turn
these off sorry oh they're scaredy cats
getting
yeah getting scared about getting in
trouble i see all right who's the one
with the big gun huh
it's me obviously you
say
something in this sir
um the one that you're heckling here is
the is the yellow one um who is kind of
like a tall like well-built dude um
and uh he he does not like your comments
um and it makes it makes him really
angry and he kind of storms towards you
but then the orange one kind of holds
him back
all right all right now dear come back
come back
we don't need to deal with the likes of
them the boss is gonna is gonna play a
little game with them ooh game
game
okay i like games
yes i like games too
uh the red and blue the red and blue
ones have the higher voices
oh
yeah the red and the not the red and
blue and sorry the blue and green ones
the blue and green ones have the higher
voices
and they seem to be very wild and frisky
they're doing all kinds of wacky [\h__\h]
and creepy moves like there's something
there's something something definitely
not right oh
freaking out doing some break dances
the only one that seems to like not
really
do any of the theatrics is the one in
red who stands up very tall and straight
and just walks slowly towards you
with the gun
and just
points the barrel to your head just a
little bit
it's like
how does this make you feel
we
we aren't hearing anything
oh
how does how does this make you feel
safe
or anything god it's the megaphone i
can't use the megaphone
discord on discord it's like oh this is
too loud i'm gonna cut it out
how does this make you feel
um
every one of you
is he actually yelling at us with a
megaphone
no he has a voice changer okay
you can use your imagination this time
well i gotta see i haven't slept this
well in
a long time
ah so you is recharged can we all talk
no
oh yes everyone can
okay
oh
yeah where are you taking my total
oh we are not taking you
anywhere i um just wanted to have a a
bit of fun with you
um trying to sort of weed out the week
you see
considering we have
bigger plans
for um
all of you
you're our favorite fight club hunter
cell
oh you could call it something like a
fight club just a little game that i
thought i'd come up
first rule fight club
you forgot about it
ah
i never saw the
you movie reference it
okay i'll remember to not do that
anymore anyway i wish to continue with
the game
you can't like tell what accent it is
it's like it's like it's me not being
good at accents
is it italian the majors maybe i don't
know
something like that and french italian
friends
[Music]
[Applause]
um
he says i have uh i put you two together
in uh in groups with each other
um we we all have we we had made little
bets before to see uh how our our little
game would turn out but i'm so curious
um
have you ever have you heard of the
prisoner's dilemma before
no
you don't you don't know what that is
oh no i guess i i have to explain what
the explaining okay i i explained to you
now
i explained to you now essentially
it's it's like it's like the game
it was a game show a long time ago a
friend or foe
now the way you played it is that there
was a lot of money but this time we
don't have
any money do you guys have do you guys
have money
oh i i got nothing
i got i got nothing served me neither oh
you mean your friends
nope not not a dollar except for what we
wagered before
who are you
that is right we wagered something but i
forgot
but you're so cute interesting of that
voice
oh man
darden so much for our intimidating
villains
can you say some cute stuff
that's the wrong one
this is how voice sounds now how do you
like ha ha
[Music]
something like that
you have to decide who your friends are
today
if you all want to listen to these
weirdos
get the opponents you are you are a
feisty one i will say you are a feisty
one
i kind of like that about you
i don't need you liking me
ew don't make it weird yuck yucky
yucky
i just gave you a little compliment i'm
not it's not like the goodness oh my god
what did i say
it's the question of
of uh will you save your friends lives
um in exchange for
okay i lied there's a lot of money
there's a lot of money
behind door number one apparently and
you guys turn around you're turning your
heads a little bit to see where he's
like
walking back towards we don't have any
money because we're pretty poor
but
we do see you guys have this vault down
here in the garage you can't see it now
but
it's behind this wall
and they all go to move the wall
and they move it and there's a vault
behind one of the garage walls
somehow they knew about it being there
oh
i know how many employees did mother
have in the bar
ooh that's a good question
i think it was three yeah
[Laughter]
all right
there's a theory
how do i how do i say this without them
hearing me
you do you want to whisper i mean
they're pretty far away from you guys
now trying to get the vault open they've
turned into a bunch of hooligans now at
this point
excited about the money
yeah cause i was
can i just whisper i will scout whispers
to yule
oh if
if it is the employees then one of them
has to be a kid and then he's definitely
on stilts so i think
i'll take the risks here if we just
continuously kick their legs out
eventually one of them's going to be
yeah how we tied up is it like our arms
are tied like our torsos to each other
or like your hands behind each other are
tied up together and even though your
ankles are tied at the ankles you still
might be able to manage a kick if you
really wanted to
all right let's time our kicks or trip
to move
short legs what if i miss
don't miss just don't miss no focus
you can do it
you're just going to piss them off
just don't miss hey future future
problems future
solutions
well
wait did one of you did somebody ask
where kid was in-game or was that just
like general
yeah i think i think we asked earlier
yeah i'd say yeah you guys made a
basting game
just didn't didn't mother say that he
was off getting guns
uh-huh
but they seem too excited about the
vault to be i
mean
if they were employees then
if mom's the ones paying and she's
holding onto all of the cash
and they aren't satisfied with the
amount me i don't
they're good theories you guys have some
good theories
um
all thoughts for sure to keep in mind
um but as they turn the
the wheel to the vault and open it
they uh reveal to you
that this place is actually loaded
even though it looks kind of shitty up
there
madame m has a [\h__\h] ton of money
a lot i've been lying
yup
a whole lot
and they all kind of start hooting and
hollering and getting very excited
pulling out some bags and getting ready
to fill them but then they remember you
guys are here
and then kind of like mosey their way
back and they say oh yeah by the way um
the one in red explains i forgot to
explain yeah the rules of this little
game to you because we are we are
recruiting actually um but we will also
let you we will let you go free if if
you'd like if we can maybe make
a deal
if you want
here are the rules
there are two of you together
um
you can't see
your friend's hand right they're behind
they're behind your back your hands are
behind your back
now
if both of you
give a thumbs up
you both get to live
isn't that great
you don't get any money though
yeah no money for you
um if both of you give a thumbs down
you both uh die
we shoot you in the head ha ha
um
if one of you gives a thumbs up
and one of you gives the thumbs down
the person who gave a thumbs up will get
let's say one fourth of this money which
is a couple million
uh the person who did
rather the thumbs uh sorry the thumbs
down the person who did the thumbs down
after write this [\h__\h] out the person who
did the thumbs down essentially betrayed
their partner
gets half the money
the person who did a thumbs up who in
very much good faith was hoping that
their partner would also do a thumbs up
for them so they could both leave
unharmed will be killed isn't that fun
oh
i see it's a game of friend or foe well
that's easy then lada
how much do you trust your friends
what is really important to you
friendship or is it uh i mean
becoming a millionaire instantly
you will get this you have my absolute
promise
blood promise
i know it's very hard to build a
compound
that's right
you could
you could get out of here you could
ditch everyone and just
we'll be free
never have to worry about a thing you
won't have to worry about us either this
particular hunter group is very special
to us for various reasons and so we
decided to let you guys have a chance to
get some of this money
but uh not everyone not everyone can get
away oh you know
we have our reasons
this is a very close to our heart
conspiracy of sorts
good old madame m
we've been uh watching her movements
recently
and uh she is
doing a great job uh raising fine
hunters
uh-huh yeah but some of you have to go
so
we do have a reputation to uphold after
all
go away
away forever
why there's a big
hunter rainbow in the sky you'll
we can't have four of you running around
that's too many why the two is fine
oh why i told you why
i told i told you that i told you the
reason i
because too many of you
them your reasons make no sense at all
silence
i make the rules
i heard that i'm standing right here now
oh
okay
so what do you say
let's go ahead and get it started then
how about you first
little one
little one little one here
well yes
what yes watoto
there she is
that's my name watato
and also
tiara
i trust you'll make a good decision
of course i only make good decisions and
one of my decisions is that
i will get out of here safely
that's very wise
all right now before you guys tell me
what you want to do i need you to
message it to me privately
what your decision is
uh
privately on discord
oh come on you
[Laughter]
i'll explain it to you again i'll
explain it to you again all right
think of it as this way it's
ally
or betray
okay let's use those mario party
minigame
um
maybe possibly
ally or betray works like this thumbs up
is ally
thumbs down is betray
okay
you don't get to see your partner's
answer at all
um
a thumbs up
ally thumbs down betray got it so if
both
players decide to ally with each other
then you get basically an equal prize
which is getting to be alive
both are good friends and don't need the
money and just want to escape with their
lives
and that's it you don't get the money
two thumbs down
means that both of them were probably a
little greedy hoping to get you know
that 10 million
and they both get shot in the head
so both players die
okay
this is with the hope that you think
that your partner is going to give a
thumbs up so you're hoping that
they will give a thumbs up you give a
thumbs down and they may die shot in the
head but you escape with the money
finally
there is um
the ally betray situation where one
player gives a thumbs up to ally
thinking in good faith their partner
will also give a thumbs up but they
don't
their other partner their partner gives
them a thumbs down which means the
person who chose to betray and gave the
thumbs down
gets 10 million dollars from that vault
and the person who chose to put their
trust in them the ally gets shot in the
head and loses their life
okay it's a test of how close friends
you are or
you can have the money that's fine too
10 million is a lot of dollars it's
quite a few dollars
i mean at the end of the day i think
they just want to kill us some of us off
so i don't know if i trust them all the
way
hmm i hope you might just say
[Music]
all right
on the counts of three you guys put your
decision
[Music]
um i've received them okay great
now everyone
oh no just these two so okay the the one
with the red mask says
alright three
two one what are we thinking
kind of puts out
hands side to side and looks at your
answer
huh how boring
you put around two people together in
thai's buddy aya
my name is friend
we have friends
what about the compound
watoto will work hard for the compound
whatever you say wattato whatever you
say
that's fine how about you two
looks over at yule and scout
uh-huh
your turn
how about some of this prize there's too
much money here
we gotta get rid of some of it
i see
i could tell you weren't raised on a
farm sir
uh yes don't know the value of hard work
clearly
i mean
we worked very hard to get this this
money out of this vault
and we're working very hard to steal it
oh yes working very hard
okay
sounds like a you problem
i say so right
all right i
alright how about you you'll
oh what's your choice
okay
on the count of three
three
two
one
ooh
how interesting
oh i was so excited to get to shoot
someone today
cox gun
points it out
nobody ahaha psych losers ah
you're also very boring
i hear that a lot extremely boring
all of you
the only one we don't trust is you guys
here
that make that would make sense and i
agree uh we're not extremely trustworthy
that is for sure
um
well we're going to take this money and
leave then um if that's cool with you
probably fake money anyway adam
okay
have a nice day
have a nice day bye
i really wanted to kill some of them
can we kill some of them
please
can we just choose
yeah
i ought to whoop you you're the one
you're the one that i want to give a
piece of my mind
is that why is that why is that cause
you're looking at me funny
yeah cause you're ugly i can see
underneath that bag
i'll go come here
oh yeah you oh yeah is that
[Music]
the one in the red mask says all right
don't be so quick to anger out of
uh i don't
know
hmm
no more clones
uh
clone apple gangers
yeah they did they
were they still alive from
last
week they escaped the mirror
[Music]
bro
a look on kelly's face
there's new music now i'll link it to
you
[Music]
at this point uh you asking that
kind of just
causes uh
the figure with the red mask to like
just kind of stand there motionless
um and like not really
not really say anything
but just kind of size a little bit
and i was like of course that would be
the thing to slip me up
ah
what are you doing here
uh
i um
in truth i uh
i came to this country
looking for you
after egypt
and then decided to open my own
uh hunter conspiracy and
well things have been
they didn't really go according to plan
we were not treated very nicely by other
hunter groups here as well as
supernaturals and so we are just living
the only way that we know how now uh
which is to take and to kill which is
fine by me at this point in time because
i've had enough
but but there are other ways to live
like why why won't you just why didn't
you try looking for me if you came here
i don't i did but i could not find you
and then i met these others so you found
me now
right which is why i want to say
tiara how about
you leave them and join us
instead
how about you leave them and join us
then
how about just you and me go somewhere
then i i
i was trying to i came here and you know
why i came here and i was i was trying
to get my stuff done but i never could
but if if you are with me then i i'm
sure that we would do so much better on
a
but aren't you just so
tired of being treated different here
different
yes
they can never understand what it's like
to be from where we are somewhere far
away in this new place
and all of the issues that we face it's
difficult
and
i'm just tired of it
but then i think
to be honest i
in the beginning i felt similar but
now that i've come to get to know these
people with me better i
i must admit that
maybe
i was too stubborn in the beginning and
to be honest maybe
it's the same problem with you
you need to see the world in a different
light i know
i think you
[Music]
you
kind of
faded to the dark side
i have to admit but it's not it's not
too late
do you really think so
it's never too late
i do have to admit that i missed seeing
your face
sister i missed you too arnold
i see you still kept the pendant that i
gave you
of course i did anna
i'm glad i tried to take it away from me
but
i
kept it safe
i'm glad you did
thank you
that means a lot to me
i don't
i don't think i can join you i have to
figure out some things myself
i have to go figure out some things
ah
just what what be with me anna we've
grown up together
uh i can't give you a straight answer
now i'm so confused i didn't expect to
feel this way but when i took off my
mask then i saw
i saw what you really look like in front
of me
it just
it
i don't know i'm feeling complicated
right now i can't take this anymore
i'm leaving
do you wait is your phone number still
the same bro
we should exchange your numbers at least
i got a new phone once i came over here
i will come for you when it's time
but i have to be on my own will that be
how long will i have to wait again to
see you on a
goodbye tiara
you gonna leave me hanging here at least
i'm tying my freaking ropes
he walks uh
he walks away and then he quickly walks
back to the uh the vault and takes like
a like just a lot of cash and leaves
what happened to you
does that mean you're from belt buckle
what
that's um
that's when you kind of start to
realize there's something funny
something was tickling you guys funny
especially you scout
in the way that those two were moving
it made you feel strange
well so you are from belt buckle
i knew i smelt horseshit
damn right
and you still got a mouth on your scalp
i can't believe that you wouldn't even
recognize your own dear old dad
oh
at this point scout's papa takes off the
mask and so does scout's mama
[Music]
you bunch of idiots
it's been a while lucky i'm tied up here
otherwise i would have turned that gun
on you 30 seconds ago and
these walls with your brains yeah well i
i ain't as sentimental as uh this fool
who just left over here so um i can see
why you'd do that you're truly one of my
own at this point i'd probably do the
same to you but i'm also feeling a
little a little sentimental after that
speech so i guess i'll hold on to it for
now
you cold bastard i'm telling you what
can i say thank you by the way kindest
thing you ever said to me scout
huh oh i raised you well didn't i
i wish i had my belt with me
i wish i had my belt with me oh man
i give you a right whooping
do you have any idea what you've done to
this family you left me you left me and
your love sister all alone just so you
could go off and do what what exactly
get real rich and commit lots of murder
sure did
a country brain couldn't get you out of
bell buckle this was your only chance
how pathetic
what can i say after i learned about the
supernatural world i just couldn't help
myself but when i happy
what was that
smashed it before what did you do to the
ford
smashed it i swear i'm gonna go get my
belt i'm gonna go back upstairs and get
my belt
i can swear i'm an idiot out of the
country but you can't take the country
out of the idiot look at you going back
for your belt no i swear i'm gonna no no
dear no no no don't stop we still love
scout and we we still support her
come back here dear
he storms off to go look for his belt
um
and then that leaves
only the blue and green left
oh
there's someone white toto nose too
finally the secret is revealed
oh my god
he isn't still stuck
he's gotta be sorry
the secret is revealed
[Music]
our son our son
we missed you but we found we found
government secrets
yes we are on a mission
a mission to take down the government
with this group of new friends new
friends
is it both of the last people
yeah
yep it's mother and father watato
oh i'm no one for you
[Music]
i didn't expect much though
it's probably the leader or something oh
nita's
oh yeah that's right
it's it's mother and father
you're alive
you died
oh so sorry leave son alone
we love you but great mission and
and big government secret and big enemy
this mask is oh [\h__\h] my music changed
[\h__\h]
this is not all what other fault
it's the it is this mask
this mask from our boss
when we wear this we become powerful but
the things become so strange and hard to
think straight
oh so sorry i don't think you should not
wear the mask
oh but watoto we need this for strength
become powerful defeat defeat lizard
president
we have to
need something
just wants you to stay safe
what dodo can't pay the bills
really but look this safe so much money
these these stupid idiots bye-bye
wa-to-toe take all this for water family
now it's for us
no problem no worry about bills
we want hotel we steal from the
government not from
the people
[Laughter]
mother what oto starts crying
um and just is weeping absolutely
weeping on the ground at this point
and father watato strokes her head and
says there there
it's okay
don't cry don't cry
we figure something out
[Music]
oh a total wants to work with you
oh
but where we go you cannot follow son
i don't want this future for you points
to the mask
okay what does it
will watch over you somehow
[Music]
okay thank you wattoto
that makes us happy
you are very lucky son
not stupid like us
thank you for being so smart son
always make sure to not make bad deals
with extraterrestrial deities
stay safe okay
okay
[Music]
our smart son
i know you will keep being smart
[Music]
can you untie me first
all of us
oh
after this whatever the hell this one
they may be your parents
they're still super evil they killed
literally
hundreds of people old lady
oh
they're still evil they have a soft spot
for you guys when they take off the
masks but they're still evil as [\h__\h]
they've been corrupted don't become
corrupt by by spooky
uh space insects what was the name
space insect space bug
ah
space what was it plankton worm
oh
yeah
[Music]
you mean worm total yes
no worm
it's okay our smart son is smart
a friend
with that being said
it's time to end today's session
oh yeah what about you
[Music]
i think hillary's probably gonna be the
the boss boss he's gonna be like
somebody you will
you'll be alone
uh you'll see we have like an after
party we'll see
i need to do some
i need to i need to keep myself awake
come on oh sure yeah we can do an after
party i know it was a bit of a shorter
session but i accomplished everything
that was set up for the session so
we're making good pace
you sure are
but
but like wazoto family says
self
build character
so i'm sure
listen if you guys you guys managed to
put your heads together and figure out
uh how to do
something in the bar trigger an alarm
that was pretty sick uh trap yourselves
in with the enemy that was fun
um
but still you did something you worked
together and you showed that you trusted
each other if you can do that surely you
can untie yourselves
wait we still have our stuff right
uh
it might be in the cellar
was it in your i mean if it was in your
pocket
i know everyone carries a kitchen knife
in their pocket oh yeah like those
butter knives that you like use to
spread like butter and like cream cheese
on bagels and [\h__\h] like that yeah i
carry one of those
just because i want to kill someone with
a dough blade yeah sure
yeah of course
that's a good idea use your animal ken
last rule of the sentence
yes okay uh
uh
with the other thing i guess that i
wrote before that was i think eight
okay
all right i think
i think he understood
two successes
so with that um
who understands and starts chewing away
at um
the ties
that are binding your hands
um is the mvp today adam yes
definitely um however the safe is now
empty they did take all the money
they didn't take without it yeah how did
they think with their heads ten million
dollars yeah they they took a lot maybe
they had bags it's like um
like so many endless fit into one pocket
huge bags
they took the money wow but they could
still be in the complex it's not totally
out of the woods you know scout's dad
said that he was coming back with the
belt
so
he'll be back
for him
oh you could have changed it too
you could if you wanted to make a trap
yeah couch
yeah
to make a make a doppelganger scout or
something like that
how do you catch a wild pigs
oh god
oh no not not scout's papa oh no not
your old man
the the
the lady that was shot outside the door
what happened
um you don't know yet
you don't know yet
oh
you will
play again next we gotta untie and get
over there yeah that's right and check
out assess the assist the situation um
yeah we are nearing like the kind of uh
big conclusion of this story um we'll
finish it in the next two sessions the
next one's gonna be on iana's channel i
believe and then um the finale will be
on on my channel um
yeah the whole
the whole like little myth story um i
hope you guys enjoy what i have in store
this is just kind of like the little
opening act to the final act i guess
um
and uh yeah
i had i had a good time despite
oh man i can't believe evans
[Music]
but my voice kind of came back it came
back
i took a 20-minute nap which is why it
maybe it sounded kind of groggy but it
came back after using it a bit so yeah
yeah yeah yeah get some rest
i will hey outfit reveals guys you
excited
oh my dumb question of course you are
i'm hiding outfit
yeah
um
[Music]
and the final collab whoever's channel
maybe
some girls yeah
yeah yeah i'll be on girl's channel
yeah girl's channel
look forward to it i'm very excited
about revealing to the world so
beautiful
and like we've known for like a long
long time we've been sitting on these
for so freaking long you guys we
announced it in like september so
yeah
we announced it for our one year
anniversary oh god it feels like ages
ago but you know what it's gonna be
worth it because these rule
i think
i think actually
i mean they already on reddit
it was written there so i guess it's
okay to say that their party dresses it
was written there so yeah you're right
kind of
yeah yeah anniversary it would have been
nice to have party dresses yeah but also
for this holiday season it's also very
suitable so yeah
yeah
for the new year's eve we got some party
choices
yeah i'd love to do like a little collab
countdown like sit in vc if you guys are
like around for any of that
yeah i'm gonna be around i know there's
something you were doing yeah
uh countdown though yeah i feel like i
choose a time zone what if we did a
countdown relay and just an idea but
like that would be kind of fun if you
just chose a time zone and did like a
countdown for it i think that would be
fun
yeah i was gonna
count down stream anyway but i wasn't
sure which time zone yet oh
wasn't someone gonna do one for all of
them i think there was a mad lad who was
going to
oh
yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah i did it for nine hours last year i
was thinking about doing something
similar this year too oh my gosh that is
nutty yeah
goodness
well if you guys wanted to do something
like that i'd be down but i'm also just
down
yeah yeah yeah sitting in vc also i'll
wish you guys a happy new year do some
new year's calls
yeah we have fire we can put the fire in
the fireplace
nice and cozy
yeah
it sounds so bubbly yeah i think a
little a little bubbly together i mean
after all i mentioned this before but
my holiday plans got scrapped and
the family that i wanted to go and see
for many years i don't get to see and i
had made all these plans and
reservations and last minute it all had
to be canceled so um at least at least i
have uh those of you guys that are like
around as well it's maybe like chill as
well it would be nice to hang if you
guys are down yes please yeah
i just had an idea but i can't remember
what it's called no
i i feel that
frustration thank god i think
use those big what's the name
just explain it explain it yeah what's
the name of that card game that was
popular
cards against humanity
it might have been that one it's
definitely too inappropriate for us to
play but i feel you i wish oh man that
would be so fun they have it online yeah
yeah yeah
that's yeah that's definitely it yeah
that's my failure
yeah
yeah yeah man unfortunately i wish we
could um for the reason it's called cars
um yes it's an abomination so apple
staples is a fun one though
though oh this is a baby yeah apples to
apples is the baby version of the
barbecue
what if we made a custom whole live deck
for cards against hood
that would be really funny custom decks
yeah we should do that if we made like a
custom like hololive but also just like
us like the five of us make our own
custom deck together
um and send like all the way
together we're gonna have like our
viewers also like pitch in and we can
pick like some good ideas yeah
definitely not all of them oh my god oh
no
that's gonna be too much but
oh
oh gosh
i mean i'm sure it exists but we we need
to make our our special deck
you know
yeah that'd be cool yeah yeah myths
against jago
it sounds like we're like
the end so that uh yeah it's all over
[Music]
yeah nah make our own yeah make our own
deck just play our own game yeah and al
all coded i don't know how to code never
mind
but me and my big ambitious ideas
sometimes take it too dang far let's
have a musical karaoke to ttrpg and also
dance lessons oh and also record uh a
project
all within 48 hours you idiot
you're almost at the end right it's true
at the end and hanging out with you guys
made it a million dollars on your people
oh my god
it ended up being um like more uh
more fun than i thought though because i
feel like um whenever i like i'm about
to like start a session i'm like at 100
mental stress for whatever reason
because there are a million things going
on in my mind but as we like eased into
it and it was cool seeing you guys like
like chatting as well like your
characters like role-playing with each
other and like having like funny quips
and conversations and then also coming
up with good ideas and stuff um it was a
joy to see it made me smile
yeah
i was like yay they're getting closer
thank you again
thank you for all the hard work
it's my pleasure thank you i'm happy to
thank you for being in my game yeah um
i appreciate you guys just being in the
game to be honest
um
yeah i'm glad that it's a way for it's
just a way for us to like get together
and hang out and also make like
shitty dumb jokes together and just fool
around that's why i don't i don't cut
off the derailments very often because
they're part of the fun in my opinion
because this is all just kind of
a way for us to like
hang more and collab more i guess
we'll hard to gather everyone together
with the time
i love all the rainbow hearts that are
all our colors
ah
can we talk about uh
yeah can we talk about the omo cat merch
drop oh yeah yeah
yeah wasn't that
insane goodness
yeah i'm so happy you can finally show
everyone
yes all the designs are so good and
don't worry we all got like we got to
order the merch that we wanted um that
we're gonna get so but don't you guys
worry and it's counted separate from
from y'alls so it's not like we were
there refreshing the website over and
over again you guys to try and buy it
yeah we buy out the whole stock before
you guys get it
can you imagine oh my cat buyers
shop.com omoketminusshop.com
everybody go there
yeah yeah i believe the sold out stuff
will be restocked yes yes in the near
future so please look forward to it it
is not a limited sale yes
it's not limited yeah so you guys have
time
you have time to save up your allowance
um you have time to get that winter job
it is winter huh i mean maybe it could
be summer if you're in australia get
that break time job save up those
dollars
hold back on that supa
and uh and buy a
buy shirt something nice yeah yeah
yourself a nice piece of clothing my
favorite personally though um is the
long sleeve holo myth shirt i requested
that actually oh yeah
because i love elmo's omo's long-sleeve
shirts so much she doesn't have enough
of them i think on on her side
personally in my opinion because i love
them so much and so i'm like hey long
sleeve please i'm gonna wear it so much
that is that is kind of you indeed yeah
yeah i got a small though i like fluffy
though
i like small get everything large so
they're like super big yeah
yeah
i probably shouldn't get a small but i
think they run a like a teeny tiny bit
large but yeah like like i mentioned i
like tighter under clothing but like
huge jackets so i'll be wearing it under
my huge jacket come home from a long day
of
going outside standing in front of the
convenience store
wondering if i should buy something
wondering if i should go somewhere
deciding eh it's not worth the effort
going back inside and then i throw off
my code and then i'm in the holomet long
sleeve t-shirt that's basically what
happens when i go outside
these days he represents yeah
walks outside my house hmm never mind
goes back inside
going outside now
yeah
i mean also though because it's winter
and honestly
fall did not last long enough for me
guys
it was bad yeah
yeah yes it already snowed a lot here at
my place a while ago
oh snow
no
jealous i want to see snow
i'm sure
have you ever seen snow before
yeah it's just been a very long time
um
what happened did my
what
yeah you are like a little i'm surprised
that you've gone this long that you guys
have been here this morning honestly oh
you're back i think your internet was
weird because you disappeared for one
second it was gone oh there she goes
okay i can't believe that that you
laughed
the horse disappears
oh is it not
[Music]
um
i can't see it
yeah i hear you it's still streaming
it's still streaming because it's my
internet
yeah yeah i just mean uh like like i
don't see you guys yeah you disappeared
i see guru
but i don't see
you yeah
whereas in a state of zen
um like a pile of ashes underneath the
desk there oh yeah she just has to rise
from there
actually
that is kind of fitting because um
on the day of my new outfit reveal which
is
this week anyway uh it is also the one
year anniversary of the first phoenix
down
here
was completely deleted and heated and
sent into the void you remember i guess
you ever remember that one yeah yes
that was like the the whole life members
channels have been banned or like the
the streams or whatever have been banned
a couple times at that point but that
was the first time someone's channel got
actually completely terminated so
that was fun
goodness gracious anyway i can't really
find my way back so um i'm just gonna be
a ghost now that's okay pile of ashes
guys chiara's just a pile of ashes but
she's still here with us don't worry i'm
ashes
[Laughter]
beautiful
nice voice effect
i love the voice effects were really fun
this this session
oh that yeah those are really good the
female
high voice was really uh nice to listen
to kelly do it again
yeah it's
why aren't you giving us what we want
why do you do this to us you're scared
of the power you contain isn't it you're
scared of it
holy [\h__\h] it's kawaii
i gave them what they want
i want you to do it
[Music]
wasn't really technically my voice so it
was like fine to do it yeah
yeah it was it was calliope not calliope
yeah why do you fear the cute so much no
i don't fear
i don't know
it's whatever
yep i'm gonna
okay i shadow what is it called shadow
uh record thank you okay
okay
here i am here's my testament i will
say the mo the moe lines seriously when
i hit 2 million subs
oh man
everyone in chat hits unsubscribe at the
same time no
more like
like five more accounts to subscribe
with
jose super rain
oh geez
oh yeah we got to do exp don't it
oh yeah
we got to do experience you guys ready
for experience sorry hold on
experience
yeah you want to put up a picture of me
sure i think i have your cardboard one
second okay
i might i think i do hold on
otherwise i'll send you one
what is this
i think this is it
[Music]
i got it there you are you're with us
okay no worries
of course
she never left
she never left rising from the action
cute
those cute eyes staring into yours
staring at the snacks on the table like
she's looking straight at the macaroons
if you look at it
no her gaze is going straight to the
macaroon
all right now let's do some exp
uh beets beets let's give you guys some
beats first of all we got you will be
all right in the left corner
let's see
okay let's see
let's see anytime you fail a roll you
didn't take a dramatic failure okay
um if your character takes lethal damage
nope at the end of the session take a
beat one beat for you anytime you risk a
breaking point none this time but it
could have been bad if if uh you guys
weren't such good friends with each
other um
good role playing i'm going to give you
one for good role-playing today you will
woo
good teamwork yes i would say that um
you were extremely uh helpful with your
perception as well um and you did come
up with some ideas for the team to like
use and look around so yeah i'll give
you another point for that
um take an action influenced by your
vice
i would say no you gotta declare stuff
like that um take an action influenced
by your virtue nope remember your flaw
use it in session nope complete the
mission yes you did you did get out of
the room so that's four four beats for
you
be all right and now uh i'll give you an
extra one you'll i'll give you an extra
beat if you can tell me something you
learned today
[Music]
uh
what did i learn today
[Music]
you
you'll be further
you will be forever alone you learns
that you'll have no friends
don't worry about it that doesn't remind
me you i never mentioned yule's family
so yeah
you didn't yeah you never know which
means it's left up to me
it is
it's left up to me
uh
just say the power of friendship
oh yes
maybe maybe the beats we gained today
were the friends we made along the hour
i'll take it i'll take it
all right so that takes your current
beats from one
to six not 67 hold on uh six oh no you
have sex you have six beats which
transfers to one exp
um with two left over so that's
currently six exp and two beats left
over
all right
next up oh we're gonna go by the beats
bank so let's actually do uh tiara tiara
for you
let's see
okay um
i'm going down the list um a lot of
these like conditions and like you fail
a roll opting to make a dramatic failure
didn't do anything like that but end of
the game session take a beat um didn't
risk any breaking points but for good
role playing i'm giving you two points
cause
you had some awesome role play with your
brother dearest at the end there that
was sick
yeah that was awesome so you get two for
that and then good teamwork yes
absolutely uh one for that and then vice
virtue flaw nope complete the mission
five that's five beats and i'll give you
one more beat if you can tell me
something you learned today
i will tell you okay
i learned that in the event there is a
red button that makes the bar
go into safe wood
and i also learned that there's a trap
door in the main room
that lets you go to a bunker with a safe
a lot of wine
yeah yeah yes correct learn more about
our our headquarters i guess yes exactly
that is a very that is very
straightforward and true 100
you're correct so that's six beats total
which gives you
nine total beats which if you transfer
that into exp it's two points of exp
nice and then one beat left over
thank you very much
no problem next we've got scout
scout hi scale audi howdy howdy scouter
all right let's see what we got here
um for scout
um let's see at the end of the session
take a beat yes this one beat for you
uh next um let's see good role playing
i'm going to give you two
that was uh
dang there's some really good role play
in there
yeah
good teamwork yes i will give you that
one as well um
vice virtue flaw nope was not called
completed the mission yes five and
finally
i'll give you an extra beat if you can
tell me something you learned today
not everybody's on stilts no matter how
much i might want it to be true
[Music]
that is uh something you learned it's a
very important thing for everyone to
know so you now have a total of eight
beats which transfers to two exp
so now you have seven total exp that you
can spend and no beats left over yeah
no problem
and last but certainly not least
certainly not least um we've got
to tell
um let's see what we got here so uh end
of the game session take a beat yes good
role playing um
i would say
it's like right in between a one and a
two but we're gonna round up um
because what's that's a family now given
we have to take into account that um
scout tiara and wataso all had
connections to the characters that
appeared so they had more opportunity to
like
role play in that sense
surely you will will get a chance to
make up that point in the future perhaps
i mean what the uh also had the uh
situation was also
really good
so uh yeah
oil depth
that can never be an
easy
thing to do um
next up good teamwork i'll give you a
yeah a point for that for sure you
definitely had some friends
behind you
at your backside
helping you get through the vent really
uh no not really but you tried um you
tried you still did everything you could
water and at the end of the day you
chose ally and that's what i constitute
as being a show of
you are becoming one with your friends
that's good
and then after that uh complete the
mission yes five and now finally uh with
one more extra point you can learn uh
learn earn what did you learn today
what did you learn i learned that
papa toto mama tattoo were alive you did
you sure did that's a big important
thing to learn
um
yes with that being said seven beats
total which transfers to one point of
exp and three leftover beats oh i can do
math
yeah
so um yeah you guys are all exp'd up
that just sounds odd um feel free to use
your points whenever you want there's
like an experience cost thing um and if
you go online you can just search up
world of darkness merits skills
attributes you kind of want to try and
see if you can get the ones that are new
world of darkness but
i don't stress too much about the
differences in the editions because
while we like use the rules as a
framework um and also the world and such
again we aren't really big sticklers for
the rules here because it just in in my
honest opinion it bogs down the game
when we're just yelling about rules the
whole time but there is a balance and we
also need to pay attention to them as
well so
to make it a game so anyway rp though is
what we focus on because i don't know i
just kind of like goofing around with my
friends to be honest and i think at the
end of the day a lot of that is what
this is about yeah so um
anyway this has been really fun guys
thank you yeah yeah
thank you
so tired thank you yeah
but you guys make it easier to to bear
so all good
in the neighborhood
don't you even worry about it because
because we're neighbors hello neighbor
oh get it
yeah hello neighbors
there's a game actually with that name
that has nothing to do with what
happened this this game
uh this session
yeah they're not our neighbors
no but they are like a neighboring
faction i guess kind of um
i mean it doesn't make sense kind of
yeah
you guys played the hello neighbor game
we played secret you know we played it
yeah the house halloween
yeah we played this yeah yeah i haven't
played the original though
yeah yeah i didn't play tuition though
just randomly thought of that
um my tummy is growling and then i need
to get two hours of sleep
i go down
so um there's a little save checkpoint
for you guys thank you everyone for
coming to watch us play this fun game
it's always a blast with these guys
um
i hope that we'll see you soon i mean
we'll get to collab soon again anyway um
you got some other fun collabs planned
this month and lots of stuff is
happening you guys um a lot of really
wonderful stuff myth is still going
strong you guys
um
iris and council are working hard too so
please uh
if you'd continue supporting us we'd be
happy
oh soon yes thank you
oh smith breakers
hello
[Music]
thanks for watching
do
[Music]
so
you