[Music]
do
oh my gosh are we good
wow that was a loud one that was a loud
one
hello everyone hello
[Music]
let me kind of crank that down just
we're good shall we start out with the
introduction and audio test everyone say
their name one by one and we test each
other's audio in each other's streams
you can't
am i loud am i quiet what do you think
guys on the other streams
i think you're good looks fine to me
next up who wants to go next
uh hello testing test test guest amelia
watson
hello everybody whoa oh thank you thank
you
thank you
hello one two three hello all good
okay
next up howdy
check once oh wow that was loud for me
hi hello let me turn that down goodness
gracious me
i did not realize excuse me hi my name
is uh clappy maury first
apprentice grim reaper you guys know the
deal hey what's good
please die that's all oh wow
i already died once today i don't want
to die a second time today
okay well you've already filled your
quota then so never mind thank you
you're good
[Music]
somewhere i don't know baby yeah
okay okay okay good good
nice i'm very loud in my own ears though
guru is muted of course google streams
is that not just the way i'm going to
throw
my mouse oh no not the mouse
why did my settings
hello all right obs decided to set all
my audio settings to default for some
reason
all right i didn't start her story oh
yeah
oh yeah don't worry i'm done i'm just
setting up the
discord thingy stuff almond will be live
in a moment
yeah live in a moment please
wait love you look
the moon's pretty today
[Music]
the server is coming together so nicely
it's so pretty we're gonna go to the
game now i think so
yeah well i think uh we should all
bring uh the stuff that we need and the
chest or two chests so that we can put
it all down safely
uh in the in the stronghold
everyone yeah all inside so we we have a
lot of armor
like in in case we lose it uh we want
some of them
some of that in the in the yeah over
there
uh-huh if you girls planned on doing the
bad strategy but in any
so bring your beds okay
you want me to make a chest uh yeah just
bring
one chest i guess for you safe to keep
your your belongings safe once we get
there
okay let me make an 18. never mind i
just remember the word right
yeah and whoa what am i relaxed
give me more i can make more
money i'm not going to chop someone's
tree down
not this time no other people's trees
okay what else i got
i didn't tell them to sleep in the end
i'm telling them to bring
a bed to me before going into the portal
so that we
if we die we don't go all the way back
to our
it's the ultimate payback yeah in the
end
i got a tip that we should bring bottles
to like capture the ender breath or
something yeah
you can use it capture the stinky dragon
bread okay
bottles bottles do we have that
yeah you can just bring some glass and
you can just make a whole bunch of
bottles too
oh gloss in the forest it's really dark
on my eyes
i didn't make a bun okay not like that i
forgot where i put my glass i
forget where i put everything no this is
a very beautiful area it might belong to
someone
i don't know they have the the
the hands free to be capturing breath i
mean
one person can be hitting the dragon
and oh my god capture the breath
i think you just put you just use the
glass where it's like doing the breath
attack
[Music]
let me tell you all right so if you go
uh if you're on the way to my house yes
all the way to my house you will see two
chests i am standing there as well
the left chest has armor everyone may
take
uh two sets i guess
for themselves okay i don't have many i
didn't get many weapons but
um
we need to bring food or this shouldn't
be like uh yeah we should bring food i
mean
which probably i have some steak i can
get people too
oh yeah and um after you guys are done
prepping come to my
come to my house i can give you guys
some uh slow falling potions so you
don't die
oh yeah i need i need some shoes
two golden apples from the chest where
the armor is in as well everyone gets
two golden apples
okay and i will tell you how to use them
and cut the apple and
[Music]
have an end chest before going you just
need them
you just need like a chest and like
under i'm getting it oh
watch me call it yeah yes if you make
two you can just store like stuff in
there yeah
[Music]
total i think okay and then a golden
apple stack right
yeah with two two golden apples yep yep
what is super thanks
okay it's fine i'm just uh i'm just
going on a little
journey access access work uh
if you like the sword is better if you
do like quick
uh hits but the axe does more damage if
you do like
shorter slower hits i guess doesn't
matter basically
a sword is quick damage light damage
in these chests
okay yeah you guys got food
got cookies cookies i want cookies
[Music]
and i wonder if we want to bring like
something like scaffolding
you guys definitely want some um water
dirty
i'll bring sand all right forget this
guys i gotta look at the um
i have a boogie maybe not saying what is
it the
coordinates the coordinates
nothing you buy puffs up right no
no no always your graphics card i'm just
kidding
was it f3 i've played this game in so
long
sir yes hey are you
lost yeah callie yup i'm lost
where'd you go first fuel went to go get
nope went to go get some wood so i could
make a chest but everything around our
areas is owned so i had to kind of go
outside the area the trees are not oh
i'll give you a tree i
live your chest if you want yeah i just
can't touch anything anymore okay
[Music]
what is it they go can someone tell me
where they are
[Music]
someone please tell me can someone
please tell me where they are
um please give me the coordinates
please of where we are you mean where
does this
uh yes uh x
uh 326 okay
why 79 y doesn't really matter and set
minus eighty-one wait i'll i can minus
four hundred and eighty-one gotcha
wait okay
[Music]
it's out oh thank you i didn't hit
anything
uh hello cat yeah they're afraid of cats
so they weren't
attacking us
so yeah that's how i got a lot of the
membranes for the potions
so by the way i brag i'm bringing sand
in case we want to
go up to the towers with sand instead of
shooting them
and and i'm bringing dirt because we
probably have to build like a bridge
from our portal to
the actual main island and what did i
say the coordinates wrong
330 and that is x and z is minus
wait sorry it was not 400 it was wait
what is that no
no minus 480 470 something like that
how did i get this far away i was just
trying to retrace your steps and i was
like
where did you go i mean i was walking in
the darkness
sorry for yet another delay you guys i
have to contribute
to being useless at least once it's just
basically like getting ready for the
family trip you know
everyone everyone gets ready at
different different
[Music]
i'm telling her to
i am correct you guys are incorrect
idiots
i'll just start it in chat
you know what is it this week
[Music]
[Laughter]
this is turning out to be a bad morning
this is a bad morning baby i'm already
enjoying this
and where was cali or where is cali
we all don't know where she is
wait i thought the last time you played
you were like uh doing the ferris wheel
or no
oh i know i i was um a couple minutes
ago
i went to go make a chest um so i went
into the darkness and i went looking for
wood
and i made sure to go far away
far away
where you like shoot it up into the air
yeah
a flare uh
do you see some of our monuments or like
the
oh the coordinates we're giving her this
is nothing i'm thinking about just dying
guys
like at this point i think i think the
problem is that we're giving her
our base coordinate when she's all the
way in phoenix town
ish no no no no no no are you okay i'm i
left from
no i left from the base town guys okay
okay okay
you left somebody did you go through
ame's
ah where the house i fell
uh oh uh i i just want to die guys i i
honestly i just want to die like reset
kelly gotta find the third darkness
oh god what is this sheep
stay where you are kelly where are you
tell me your coordinates
okay yeah yeah it's just telling us 99
299 219 77 which doesn't matter
and then this is the one that's effing
me up that i can't see
negative 692. oh she's real is it down
oh not really again i think i i kind of
know where you are maybe
i don't know draw my way coming to i
actually don't know where you guys are
so as you know if you're already going
then i'll stay yeah i'm i'm already on
my way
you're better with coordinates can you
write the coordinates in chat
kelly second look one sec
hang on uh sorry okay let's see
are you on snow or grass right now
i'm on grass uh-huh
six nine two grass
wasp she couldn't have gotten far
yeah and there's only once
only one place we can go where there's
trees
pressing on this way
[Music]
is somebody bringing a leash
please oh sorry i don't have to leave
anyone just bring a leash
what is like those baby ones that strap
around your chest
oh yeah there's three of them and yeah
people like to walk their children
one person with three children and
they're like all over the place
mommy's trying to put me on one of those
oh what color
oh it was like green
tartan print plaid
okay what are the coordinates callie uh
305 for x and negative six nine two for
z
neo5 negative what six
movie i'm thinking like callie
it's like something if i was
callie okay like i go to
negative x negative wow
where did you go five negative six nine
two i just walked into the kindness
really just tried to go somewhere away
from the camp turned around and couldn't
find the camp anymore
riku too
i'm gonna get up on a pillar
yeah that about figures that checks out
uh you you got lost really quickly that
might be a wreck
that really probably was a world record
okay it was definitely a world record
yeah he's on a different side
honestly you would not be surprised
would not be surprised if i was
okay getting closer um
[Music]
smell cali and it's negative six nine
two by the way i'm on a tall pillar
i see it i see um kiara
and uh i said i was about to say kiara
and kusatori
kiara and okay okay
i think it's kind of hard to miss the um
what's it
kinda hard to miss the giant stairway
yeah there is a giant stairway right
above me too you should you should
follow that
i guess i should okay please just signs
of civilization
follow the moss-covered rocks oh
i came all the way here for this
freaking wood i will sit here and i will
hit it with my hand
until i get it even though my axe has
now just broken
i will hit it with my hand because i got
lost for this wood
determination hey who was that are you
guys all ready to go by the way remember
this
oh no literally holy
pretty much do i have news i knew it was
gonna happen
i feel like i need flint yet i didn't
listen
to myself
[Music]
they seem useless and ugly pink
it's a stress ball
oyster arrows just tasting i need to
practice not a few misties
[Music]
buckets did i hit you
all right i found my way back oh i
thought i thought
okay i guess you're back in base cali
okay good i got a bucket do you need a
bucket
i have a lot of buckets oh i also have
some
some drinks for everyone thank you god
please rendezvous
at taco bell do you guys think we can
play some of those
those minecraft minigames have you seen
like the minecraft
mini game servers oh yeah yeah
i want to play that yeah that we could
mod our own
i could do it probably i found the cali
it seems like it'd be a lot of fun
you know i want to do it
[Music]
hi
we deliver everything from humans to
dudes
[Music]
put i can give you one oh it's okay i
have one i made one it's okay i went out
of my way to make one don't worry
everyone okay come over here to my
my lab yes open up the right chest and
take some slow falling potions
okay you'll need it you got it this time
i got it now i got it
i'll give you something thanks for the
clap clap clap chat
always clap clap in a rough morning
how many can we take i'm sorry enough
four or five i forget
oh five okay i already just took a
portable inventory
yeah i mean i'll take the leftovers
myself so don't worry yeah
okay you can't yeah can i have a bucket
five each five minutes oh yeah buckets
you can open up
uh there's seven in this chest over here
and there's like four on the outside one
i got something yeah so feel free to
take
okay thank you for all the preparation
you guys did this is really helpful
you guys are amazing sasuka
wow yeah do you have any extra ender
pearls on you
okay that's not it i have one yeah if
you guys have any extras could you
maybe carry some yeah because i'll i'll
bring some blaze ross just in case you
know our eye breaks before we find
um okay i have like
a couple extra
[Music]
uh as for diamond armor is that in front
of kiara's place
yes yes okay
did everyone else already take their
sets of armor you should like take
probably two
but what if we die and burn and then
they all burn but if we die then we'll
just spawn back and spawn and then we
can
try to meet back up in the yeah wait i
forgot
yeah did you take the under just where
they put the under chest
i didn't take the end of the chest
from my phone wait wait yeah go back
uh okay
yes i see you i'm here okay
first floor oh yeah just have me
just help me follow you i never use um
left chest
here it is two two full sets of armor
yes ma'am okay thank you honey
wood one you shall
wait like 50 something would okay you
need more and the
other one in case you died
okay how do you say shield in japanese
what the hell happened here okay uh
please take one of the diamond axes all
right
one of those balls one of them uh maybe
the
the second the first row second one oh
yeah okay
i'll see i guess you can
[Music]
okay one stack of arrows golden
no the normal ones the golden ones are
not really not really useful
yes did you take an axe as well no i'm
thinking about the diamond one the
diamond one
kiara asking oh axing all the questions
[Music]
which one should i take any of them uh
it doesn't matter oh
okay strong all right
all right and one stack of arrows okay
yeah um i am also bringing
some snowballs but i don't have many uh
all right i was gonna
get snowballs are you bringing them too
oh yeah i was gonna make some
snowman oh i gotta go get a shield guys
oh boats we're gonna make those showers
what do we need snowballs for to shoot
the towers
uh like there's towers then you gotta
shoot the top and the snowballs are
really good for that i think
oh okay you guys want to build the
snowman
what do you guys thought might be fine
wait kelly did you get the gold uh you
have to take sorry one more thing the
two golden apples from the chest oh yes
yes ma'am i'll go ahead and do that
nice crossbow
i know dirt in my house i had one one
helmet
damn it i didn't resource something
precious
no waste of questions resource oh
okay feeling better guys
[Music]
is somebody more responsible want to
hold the scaffolding because i do not
trust me
trust in you trust in me
believe in the you that believes in me
should i have a pickaxe you guys cool oh
actually
using that
i have a cape and i don't have a cape
are you using optifine
or maybe somebody was saying it might be
your shaders i don't think cali is using
optifine so i don't know i am
oh you are okay it must be optifine then
yeah it turns off
i i should bring some shovels and stuff
too i forgot
it's freezing
[Music]
can i give you um the free enterprise
that i have oh yeah sure
i just gotta make sure i don't die so i
don't lose everything
we're safe shoot them down
you can get their membranes come give me
your brains
where are you why are they the wrong
kind of membranes
but men before that's like when
when the membrane wall of a cyst
have you ever seen cyst removals you
have to remove the membrane wall
otherwise the cyst will grow back oh
whoa that's nice
[Music]
shots absolutely yeah beautiful shots
i at least put it in the corner i can't
see anything
all right so are we ready
can we start the car so yeah we can
start the car
everyone got their snacks you got food
snacks
[Music]
are we sleeping that's horrifying
yeah i guess so i guess let's go sleep
i'm
there's another bed over here i think
i'll have to go inside the hospital
okay please stop that please stop
sleeping through this night oh
oh there we go all right good morning
everyone
it's time oh callie in front of your
house there's a dummy i will destroy it
okay oh ball tosser ouch
it's very kind of yeah yeah there's a
lot of enemies out here oh my oh my god
okay i'm not moving or scaly
there's no more no more explosion
waiting for you
okay okay that was horrifying uh you
know
come with me quickly can you take the
ender pearls out of the chest i have a
full inventory
okay not this chest is inside my house
thank you
you're going to be here pearl tosser am
i the
chosen picture that's what they're
called right oh thank you
that's what they're talking about yeah
let's just keep our eyes on
all right all right you guys guys i have
to
i have to grab a chip i'm sorry my
stomach hurts so bad with that
one chip one just enough to not
hurt my stomach hold on i have a sausage
that's supposed to be spicy but ever
since i ate those spicy noodles nothing
has ever been in spicy
oh thank you for this assassin's creed
okay
i'm guessing we're not doing the bad
strategy
i mean i'm bringing i'm bringing wood
and wool so if you if you need to make
more bets then
that is i have one two three four five
six seven eight beds
maybe nine i don't know a lot of bits
really i think i can do it
hopefully two but yeah
checklist everyone has armor yes
everyone has weapons yes everyone has
arrows
yes yes everyone has slow falling
potions
yes yes everyone has two golden apples
yes yes everyone has a food
some kind of food yes yes i have some
leftover in case
everyone has uh one chest at least oh
no um no i can make more chests
i i mean we probably have enough yeah
okay
everyone has maybe one or more but more
than one water buckets they could be
i mean i don't know if you if you were
if all of us are that skilled i'm
probably not skilled enough but i
brought a
couple of water buckets uh because if
you fall down
then you can do a swoosh
water uh-huh please use that too i guess
that was cool
yeah probably i don't know all good okay
put it on the floor
yeah get into it at the right time i
guess now
and i have some building material i
don't think we all need
a little building material because yeah
just one
yeah as long as we don't push each other
off
okay cross fingers okay are we good
i'll put some water buckets back or do i
i'll just bring him along whatever okay
let's go let's go
let's go all right let's go to i just i
just gotta toss this right and i'll go
towards it yes
yes keep your eyes on it though because
i think you can collect it again yeah
oh yeah how did i toss it no i didn't
right where did it go
i think it went that way right
yeah they go behind this
[Music]
it didn't even like usually it travels
and then everything is that pinged right
away are we
like what
uh i mean just just wait here let me see
if it works
at the ground it kind of throw like
horizontally yeah okay
uh i said chad says it went the opposite
way maybe
opposite way he went behind oh there's
no way
yeah how far does it go
i have fifteen left and one go truck
okay i'll go see the slit see if it
what you're getting really quick um i'm
just following her
with the extra ones because i will get
lost
michael
make one of those was that not supposed
to stay polo uh you need blaze words and
jingle bells
has all that stuff yeah i have more eyes
it's
wow you're supposed to masturbate you're
supposed to do it in the
other for some reason and it's in
another i don't know i don't know
that's what i thought i didn't know oh
no you can do it anyway i'm just gonna
turn off shading okay
it doesn't it doesn't go that far okay i
don't think we'll find it
[Music]
does it d d spawn in like five minutes
probably
is there a radius like if we know a
block radius then we can do like a
you know a circular sweep yeah i think
there is a limit to how far it goes but
maybe it didn't go the other way blocks
we can calculate from where enos through
it and then we can okay
i'm gonna maybe maybe throw another one
it didn't go that far because it pinged
really quickly
[Music]
that's 10 to 15 blocks okay so let's go
back to the original one and then
10 to start blocks away from the corner
that you know threw it
okay so close yeah that is pretty close
must be a heck i'm sure we're just
missing it
it could have broken apparently oh yeah
that's true they break
sometimes right away i say they probably
this is probably broken
okay i'm gonna group up and throw
another one everyone be on the lookout
wait wait wait why are you we can see
[Music]
i'll sit up that's what judd's saying
she'll just throw up
oh oh no i i i look
a lot all right two
one
what
i was in third person so i was looking
at i didn't see anything
yeah it actually literally went behind
in midair are we all using shaders
yeah because it went down
but i i checked in the kfp though i mean
the kiara's house is not
i wonder if it is a shader's thing dig
down
no i turned off shaders
are we right above it no way
there's no way there's no way and we
then we would have probably like
dug into it with uh amelia's
underground subway turns way further
that way
like to the left but maybe we should dig
straight down from where you're throwing
it in kiara's house
kiara your house is livia under
construction you're forbidden to use it
from now on what
[Music]
i mean we can try dig down but
somebody says oh it's not a good idea
it's not a good idea
i'd probably waste all the pearls though
should we there's no way that it's here
all right i have one wait throw it
somewhere else where we should try
it okay let's go let's try throwing it
somewhere else
let's go into a flat field like uh is
there any of yeah
my cabin i forget what about what about
like near the ocean oh okay
like the flowers go back to the cave
yeah i like stuff like behind my
house-ish
yeah like it was gonna make atlanta then
we went to this don't worry guys i
definitely know where my cabin is it's
just not optimal
don't let your dreams be me we'll finish
the cabinet memes
don't be dreams and memes boys and girls
is it
so we already wasted two of those and uh
i have one i think i'm happy to offer it
wait is it under pearl
under yeah me too no i have enough rods
but you know
i have enough place rods so as long as
there's pearls
that's all we need okay okay
it is underneath his house then
the pearl will travel towards her
is not very house are you sure you're it
is this what you consider flat ena
what do i do throw it on top of my chest
huh yeah
[Music]
still alive we're gonna test at her
house over there we can
do that that looks flat okay
i understand anyone kidding
okay and you want a ride
i would like a ride actually i have a
boat we can use
all right i'll ride with you girls
stand them with me cali
nice where are we going the girl's new
house pretty flat
nice cape it's getting dark
it's got a triton on it wait wait
i tried it right yeah this is quite fun
you're welcome
have you seen your cape pretty cool all
right
we got it we gotta do it before we get
started i gotta throw it that's fine
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait
there you go oh my gosh
[Music]
look towards inna's shrine i guess one
person i'm throwing it towards the
shrine
you want to throw it towards like shrine
like some people are saying
this guy throws the ground like what
should we say third person okay i have
five
beds if we need to sleep yeah ladies and
gentlemen
yeah let's see first before monsters
slumber party ladies outdoors camping
yeah you have a bed it's all stones yeah
i got you i got you okay
[Music]
yes
okay oh maybe if we go maybe enough you
go really high up like on a on some
blocks
oh okay and then throw it all right oh
easy block okay
dirt
i think that's good all right i'm gonna
throw it towards
towards the tory gate okay everyone
ready okay
watching
[Music]
is
oh there it goes it's working
is it there no i got it oh thank you
should we throw again uh let's do it
from the toy gate
yeah yeah good idea you wanna throw that
one
uh you do it you know this is fine you
mess it up
okay
[Music]
oh wow really far oh
so maybe the last two times just broke
that would be pretty unlucky i mean
we we still have like three spare ones
what should we do here like should we
make a bridge or should we just go
in that direction and then do it again i
feel like bridge is just gonna be
wasting blocks possibly we have other
boats because if we have the other
other boats we could just go in this
direction a little bit yeah yeah yeah
try again
let's go
[Music]
yeah there should be one more that we
rode on the way here
[Music]
it again oh god all right
oh okay okay keep going this way catch
it get it broke again
i think we can go a bit further yeah for
the next one
okay because yeah we're wasting them do
you still have enough you think yeah
twelve
three pearls twelve plus three pearls
and five blaze rose and that makes like
a couple of powders so it should be fine
let's go until we get to land and then
uh
we can do it again we have like a
perimeter
to check this feels so cool you guys
could be underwater
it could be unlucky though
he's walking on water damn what
[Music]
i'll go until atlantis let's go there
on that hill the big hill in this round
okay
[Music]
we're taking pictures of us
beautiful
epic minecraft music all right copyright
rta let's go
there's a minecraft playlist that i'll
put on like a 10 hour playlist okay
when everyone gets here we'll see
hold
[Music]
i'm gonna on all the nether tracks oh
yeah a good idea
oh hello sorry it's okay
i'm ready
epic minecraft track no that that'll
give you remixes from
from other music producers okay yeah use
the nether ones
minecraft soundtrack all another tracks
20 20.
yeah i mean i'm listening to girls ease
yeah cause i'm just 500 sounds
trustworthy
[Music]
everyone here
okay
[Music]
yeah it didn't break it fell
like this
let's keep going for like a couple
minutes
yeah how many blocks maybe like 500
blocks
is there like only one or is there like
oh we're back at water maybe we should
go to where those trees
yeah until the tree let's go on to the
tree wait i lost you girls me and kelly
are
too far away from you girls i'm not the
only one yet wait where'd you go i'm not
the only one that's lost anymore
oh no okay i'm so close you go uh i'll
come i see
i see some names i found found you kelly
you're following me
yeah go to the top of the hill and you
oh wait wait
i see them i don't know the boat
yes all right let's go ride together
father we
right got i have someone's bed
uh all right here we go not mine
[Music]
thank you thank you all right
yeah yeah maybe yeah yeah let's see
is there only one or is there multiple
welcome to the mountain top i'm gonna
is there multiple yeah that's the one
it's the one it's gotta have to get out
of the there we
there's tons okay okay so i guess it's
just the one we're closest to uh-huh
okay cool
we should have roller blades that'd
yeah or another another real nice smell
though
i also saw like a like a oh that is
really close
relatively close i guess what's what's
close
wait for everybody to go a little
further
uh sure okay just a little fur
[Music]
maybe like on top of the the hill right
in front of the tree
yeah oh yeah i was thinking that to you
all an unexplored territory
would have been good to bring a map oh
true fill in the map we would have
needed a really big map though if he
went real far
yeah that's true i want to make a map
room exclusion
what is that this one
how is that naturally possible pumpkins
all right guys
i saw some on my head but i went
straight
oh there you are okay okay okay
there you go okay three two one please
wait oh it went the other way okay it's
somewhere here then oh oh
oh oh so now we turn back around
yeah steps
and then we break minecraft's number one
rule don't dig down
[Music]
on the way it's getting dark
okay let's do that one more time before
before it gets dark
yes yes no sex actually helps
oh beautiful
[Music]
did someone pick up the pearl or i
yeah i have 11. i used to have 12. it
broke okay it broke
okay sleeping
[Music]
oh it's real dark sleep over time sleep
sleep sleep
oh there's a bed over there well thank
you
okay
hurry did it break really it is on the
tree but i thought it still hit the
ground
it's on the tree i mean
we can check hold on oh i have your bed
you know oh it's right there i see it
there it is so much for hearing it for
you
yeah you're on my bed ah oh i see you
that's my bed okay tall okay that was
your heart breaking we're going this way
right
you're wrong okay
let's go it's okay
right here oh this is nice and open i
don't
[Music]
okay i kfp worker we do it like at the
edge of this cliff here yeah
um watermelons
oh oh oh oh okay we're here
okay hold on someone stand here someone
stand here that's it
oh okay and stay stay put sit
i can stay
[Music]
i'm really good at standing still and
not doing anything
[Music]
somewhere here okay me me i'll stand
getting close i am standing
[Music]
i can smell you i'm glad some of you can
relate
yes ma'am okay so it has to be someone
there has to be like someone here yeah
can i move i already moved hold on
yeah let's stick where where am is ish
okay
okay how far down is it yeah
i don't know until we see it pretty far
down i think
we totally see it yes
all right ladies i can help oh no she's
digging straight down
[Music]
she'll be fine okay i'll dig somewhere
around here
you'll know that because the stones will
change it'll look like brick stones
i should probably stay with someone i
don't have a i realize that they're
bringing any torches i opened up a cave
here
there's a cave down here oh
[Music]
come on build some stairs we can mosey
our way dance
oh yeah good idea shut up there's a cave
here and then you guys i have torches
[Music]
you know you have an arrow in your head
there you go don't worry about it
welcome
wait nice like uh oh but i guess it'll
go through the wall huh
i have i have no space in my door well
if there's a cave though then there's a
there's a good
chance it's okay they'll find it
okay i'm going to stay with you uh i
have no clue
okay i don't know how far we have to go
so i'm gonna
start digging down again just to see i
didn't bring it
oh oh oh oh
[Music]
it's kind of a long way down you might
wanna
[Music]
whoa hello hi where's oh there's a
button
[Music]
whoa this is cool and can you open the
door for me
yay yeah
there we go oh there you go okay
okay nothing here nothing
it's a maze oh wow so it's like that huh
okay so exciting this is so cool
there's like stairs here
spawner is that possible i think so
might as well get rid of there's oh
there's god everybody
there's oh my god there's a lot of
people here i don't have any more uh
torches
right now don't look
[Music]
oh
there's uh it can be behind a false wall
as well i know there's like
cheeky uh uh uh joke walls
you buy this is anybody doing watson huh
uh throwing away blocks
that was scary this library is so cool
yeah i probably shouldn't try and hit
this spiderwebs
we can take them yeah if you hit the
spider webs with a sword they go down
really fast
oh cool thanks oh i think i found it
nice there's a ladder i don't have a
torch to get rid of the spawner though
oh that was there was actually a spanner
that was really yeah
again i'm gonna borrow a torch
here i can give you some
i didn't look at you i did not look at
you i just thought of space yeah that
enderman's really scary
uh oh you did find it the other yeah
that was fast wait there's like
literally no eyes
[Music]
wait you know what i have exactly enough
oh my god you want me to go get the one
i have i have one no i have exactly 15.
under your gosh oh my gosh okay everyone
everyone
[Music]
wait 12. oh never mind i get it
i can't math i have exactly twelve
no we're gonna everyone running here
you're good
everyone here my god okay yeah someone
marked down the
coordinates for this oh yeah good idea
screenshot yeah okay got it i got the
screenshot
it's good right here um let me make sure
i'm absolutely prepared
chest should we put on the chest guys
just in case oh yeah
put the bed bed and chest on your chest
ladies
yeah bed and chest stupid door uh
ouch oh you gotta get
they come out of the the walls and stuff
what are we starting in the chest
like your second set of armor and uh
silver fish maybe some embryos
that was not me i did not do that oh my
goodness
i'd probably just get rid of them
[Music]
what the hell the bed is about to burn
is there is this underneath the portal
if there's no lab on the portal will we
break it for some reason or can we
break the spawner can we break the
spotter i think so hold on
no we're lava or water in the lava
yes we don't need the lava all right
yeah it does we don't need the lava
[Music]
and okay oh let me put tonight
i don't know they don't look edible how
about
the potions you guys the potions yeah
yeah maybe bring in one one only for now
i think
oh maybe two's in here because it's
pretty dark yeah two
i don't have any one i have one toy
leave it to me leave it to me
okay i'm gonna start putting the eyes in
all right we can do it
i'm putting two books into the chest but
those are those are
mine i already set the spot okay
what's in bed is
[Music]
everyone ready
can we take a group picture can everyone
get on the stairs okay
i want to take a picture nice idea
[Music]
okay well i have a really cool cape too
to go yeah i guess we could no yeah
everyone look
to the front and
cheese i want one too
[Music]
okay i got it thank you okay me too yay
different people use the under chest
does that mean
they have their own storage
i opened yours earlier and i didn't see
anything in it oh that means you guys
can use it too
just throw your stuff in oh my god
we do oh well
okay well i'll put
wha it looks like
[Music]
okay okay not mine okay are you in
i think i think
[Music]
maybe not all at once because we don't
know how big the
platform is when we land we might push
each other's going in
from where we stand i'm nervous oh she
said
watson all right how is it is it is it
very nice
i can't see wait you guys oh
i have torches it's a small platform um
you guys can oh god
do we have building machines right here
building material can we go ahead i'll
make it bigger
then yeah
yeah everyone ready yeah should i be
holding something
specific you guys are holding blocks oh
yeah to build yeah to build yeah i'll
help
uh do we use the you know do you think
we should use the
falling potion right away i think when
we when we go in we can
use it when we start the dragon when we
start fighting okay also
uh cali don't there's a lot of endermans
down there
like a ton when you go up to the
dragon
try to look down because there's really
an army of and the dragons don't look at
them they will
kill you once you look at water
yeah and if you do if you do anger them
pour water
and get in it because they can't go in
the water
but kelly remember we're not fighting
the ender men
okay okay all right i got it i'm waiting
i i'm ready
morning ready
one one i'm loading look just wait
it's just loading yeah okay that was
anti-climactic
climatic
[Music]
i think we should probably make a bridge
over to the bigger platform before we
all die that was too much the portal is
so powerful
what is this place this is cool okay
it's dark in here
i think i don't know who wants to
it felt wrong who wants to you know the
bridge
over here yeah to the platform i don't
have a lot more building materials oh
here i can
i 52 dirt i also have a lot
thank you okay that should be enough oh
my god which one should i build because
there's one close to our left or should
we just build upwards because we could
build stairs here oh and
i got one i think we should go to the
main main uh platform over there where
the dragon is
yeah okay i am
in the end just let almond do her
her thing okay don't go push her
what the hell you won't get anything
back
is that normal what is does the sky look
like
noise to you as well guys this is itchy
it doesn't look like that in uh
air for me
we need to put walls up yeah okay okay
you question do you know when you're
going to the nether and that thing that
goes
can you and you can like hit him hit the
fireballs back at it can you do that
with the ender dragon
i don't think what is this what is this
smoke can i walk into it no that's
there's fire on the ground that's the
ender dragonfly oh okay
okay watch wait can you build a puppet
oh god
[Music]
oh wow i'm in bad shape right oh this is
bad
this is bad i need to build fast okay
still there yeah yeah yeah yeah
how do we make the fire
yeah that's a good idea turning off
shader is my vehicle oh man it collects
more materials
please collect my items please oh
um wait oh nice oh my
gosh does it break walls also
i don't know
get your stinky breath out of here you
big scaly thing
there by chance you guys your stuff is
all still here
you just gotta get here okay i'm coming
well actually maybe not for cali
i think yeah um stuff is there yeah
fire's done you can come in
okay that's fine i'm not going to start
over the game
i want my things all right i got a bunch
of stuff oh god the diamond armor is
already so low we really should have
brought all of it yeah
this is a great start okay don't don't
walk
towards the the platform yet this stuff
is here
what does that mean hello mr dwayne
whoa thank you wait watson this is what
is that noise i turned them off i turned
them off what is that
oh huh oh it's a enderman
[Music]
it my game doesn't work anymore without
shaders
buildings bridge they're brief souls
i'm in danger all right what
is what whoa we need to build stairs
you really want me to step out there i
chose 1.171.1 the
most recent release
well this isn't great guys oh
sure my bow and arrows are gone um so
i'm thinking
maybe i leave my stuff here for you guys
and then i am
using that one yeah
thank you watson you don't have to all
right okay
you sure there's there's more outside
i'll just say
how how do you go outside wouldn't i
catch the
fire i'll go in
oh yeah oh yeah when you die okay okay
well turn off the shaders
like uh manually
maybe i'll be your eyes in the sky
what's home
watch out behind you with fire fire fire
fire fire fire fire firefighters you're
off
okay it's gone it's gone it's kind of
set are you are you guys already
fighting the dragon no
no yeah building the bridge he's coming
[Music]
i mean the others can't see it i mean
this one's already angry so
does anyone have a pickaxe so i can you
can't you can't use uh arrows or
range attack for enderman yeah can't
i don't know i think some stuff might
have been upstairs ladies and gentlemen
nice
to meet you but yeah that works too uh
give me a mean pocket i die i died
exactly where kelly died so whoever
picked up kelly's stuff
might have my stuff i cannot don't know
who has
okay should i turn off shaders did you
guys turn them off
i turned it off you have to like reload
the game if you turn them off
because here is a bit safer to give me
my stuff thank you
i built
one side of armor and like some dirt
blocks
some arrows armor i only have
i only have one set
oh but you're wearing one first and you
have one extra
all right no i'm i'm only wearing the
one that i have hey
where are you by the way this is your
this is definitely
we have tiarax here you go
yeah wait can somebody kill me so i can
go back and then no no no no no
okay you know what let's keep the armor
i wear how the
word okay
[Music]
no pants uh okay do you like arrows
wait i don't want all your stuff though
no it's fine it's fine there's more
stuff
here she asked me to tear stream heart
challenger
yeah can you bring me one
uh yeah we need one full set of armor
because we're sharing right now yeah
there's two full sets here so i'll bring
i don't have one either and then um
oh do you have a oh damn it the
the golden apples uh yeah i have two
here
a dutch i just need one one
uh no i don't have any it's fine okay
it's cool i'll just try not to die oh do
you guys have bows how many bows do we
have yeah
i got a bottle one two please one bowl
uh a few more arrows please scary
that's fine okay looks like a big
overgrown chicken there's an extra scent
i'm missing armor right now me me and
camilla
yeah i'm missing pants and boots and i'm
yes
you guys are amazing your dreams your
dreams
give me one too please the homie house
see though cause i don't wanna
i die i can make some but they won't be
enchanted
but i'll be right back can you bring
some building blocks just in case
yeah how do we leave do we just leave
the game
and then come back all right
can i leave these things here and then
come back you guys
[Music]
yeah yeah would you be able to hold my
things real quick
yeah my my thanksgiving oh yeah i guess
technically
they are yeah oh wow that's loud all
right
i'm going to go play some sudoku i'll be
right back
okay and good luck oh my glass bottles
i'm holding a shield god i'm such an
idiot
all right well i got regular bows wait
kylie wait what what about what ending
potions the top the top armor god
damn it look you could have just
asked us to kill you
that way you know it's good we have that
three armor tops here three pants okay
three hours one full one all right what
i missed
nothing much
don't make anything else for me please
just keep it you guys
i'll survive i prepared for everyone so
there should be a
one more set for you and one more set
for me it is missing
but no i have everything sorry i have it
in right now
i was gonna go back with it hold on i'm
gonna be right back
yeah because we could store everything i
mean i guess maybe we can't start
yeah can i shoot this thing or is it
gonna come after us
depends on what the thing is yeah
oh i think that's why i mean it's gonna
heal itself because
we still have the crystals to kill or
get rid of
oh okay jarrah you have pants already
i have shoes and pants
okay thank you mint ice cream anyone
destroy the crystals all right chet
they're at the top of the tower right um
oh yeah i never watched speed running of
this so i won't i barely know what
happens plus i always
speed runners always have like the uh
the like the program
outlines turned on and stuff it's really
weird oh hi
i mean we just gotta get good okay and
shoot it
[Music]
good girl i gotta get good guys
i gotta get into this ice cream first
though crystals are the things making
the beans they hate yeah
okay i can't get into my ice cream
nice nice weather here today don't you
think how's the weather up there you
know
no it's a little bit cloudy with a
chance of dragging fireballs
what material is this is it like sponge
i think it's ender stone or whatever
yeah ender sponge
oh i got it i don't know
how would i do this glass bottle to
capture something oh yeah
yeah yeah and phase two of energy and
it'll come down and do like a
breath attack oh okay uh-huh is it okay
to eat the apple now
probably yeah yeah wait okay
right wait where's callie cause callie
said she uh oh
i think she's going through the game i
can't re-enter the game
now it says the server is outdated yeah
that's because i turned up new shaders
uh
um i have the same thing just now you
have to you gotta be download
or update no no no no no use use the
option that it says optifine the normal
one that you used
up until now then once the screen is
open uh you click into options
and turn it off manually um before
logging into the minecraft server
okay uh you know where you can choose
the minecraft service before you click
that you go on options and then turn off
uh at graphics settings you go to uh
shaders and then turn off the shader
manually
okay it's threatening
actually i feel like i feel like i
should give this
when she gets no please don't give her
oh
please no stop it no i'm
not here
[Music]
don't don't touch my stuff i'm not my
way
you heard her don't touch it i'm not
touching it
all right she's back in the yukata for
revenge
we need him i got some uh dragon's
breath
ooh
[Music]
sensory overload captain hold on i need
a what's up
this is nice pink pink step
[Music]
is okay
video settings and then
let's see shaders graph graphic settings
yes graphics graphic settings oh my god
damn
sorry keep keep focusing on the game
sorry once uh i need food i need food i
need food
yeah i gave you chickens hey i think you
picked it up again i didn't oh my god
how do we do this
okay is pigstep part of the game
or is this a remix hello do you have
food please
that sounds copyrighted
[Music]
it's literally from the game but we'll
take a risk
i'm standing right next to y'all anyone
who has food
dmca part of the game
all right get it back goddammit you
think i am getting way too many
yeah mixed got it thank you all right
we're good we're gonna do it
yeah yeah graphics
this is not going well uh are you
running around that's not cara
[Music]
we can start trying to destroy the
towers
we have to destroy them we do yeah can i
even shoot that farm
destroyed one it takes only one hit yeah
what the hell
one hit and as always right into the
bullet
oh yeah did someone look at me don't
attack me guys don't attack me
oh my god and a bullet bull's eye not
bull's-eye bullets eye i don't know
boom okay let's go nice
it's shot
the second time first try
uh okay i got a problem i got one
did you get enderman
use water use water use water oh hi
there
uh hi fellas
thanks guys all right what about them
it's generating health back yeah i'm
following you
okay hold on where are you guys oh yeah
we got to do the towels
okay all right
all right hours first oh okay
what am i shooting at i need i need more
arrows so
uh at the top of the towers you're gonna
there's uh
what did i put a bed up here
i'm feeling dangerous it's our only dose
with the cages right
yeah oh yeah almost without the cages we
can do
we're just shooting here
okay come on do it again kiara you've
done it before
[Music]
can you can you not drag oh no
drink the potion how do you drink a
potion you eat it like food this one
yeah i destroyed the third one
how many more do we have yeah okay
how do i destroy that one are you going
up that way okay
oh wait there's one here how do you blow
these beds up
maybe one more yeah why is that one so
low
i'm back hey check okay got one
okay i don't have an axe
it's much better i can actually see okay
oh i'm gonna go right click roger
[Music]
i have no more arrows unfortunately
thanks chet oh slow falling
appreciate you guys i'm good it's it's
gonna be okay
i need building blocks
i'll find you guys don't worry wait a
minute how many left you'll never mind
um i can does anyone have arrows
i have some uh uh i have infinity so i
can spare
14 for you i think oh wait
i think it's free or something i'm i'm
in front of you one piece
in front of me oh
[Music]
thank you yep got it i don't have a
pickaxe i can't have a name
looks
oh that would be a good idea did i
destroy that one or not i don't even
know anymore did we
wait i'm a lot of slow falling potions
oh i'm happy to just it's almost chewy
i think someone echoed the enderman use
some water
oh oh just on
it now let's just use a potato
oh yeah oh oh no
yeah someone wait did we get all these
crystals
they seem pretty angry
i think they're all done okay
[Music]
well we'll see i guess i'm missing all
my shots
regenerates
taking any energy from any of the
tallies anymore
okay but is that one not worse
does this mean
oh nice i hit him i hit him yay
i want to use the bed it's coming down
uh-oh oh face two ah oh boy
oh wow am i doing anything to it i don't
know
i can't see i don't think my arrows are
doing anything
i'm kind of far oh not it's doing
something
let's go girls yeah let's go guys
i got the race before
i think we're supposed to attack it with
a sword right now
attack with sword or bags beds where the
beds get on how's your child
oh no bad bad bad dad
i have i have one more chicken thank you
kfb
i have my arrows i think that was
hitting for a little bit but it's too
late
and that's flying again now maybe it
actually isn't good
all right let's see how to do it now i
remember never hold on
don't die really there is okay
i'll pick it up oh no you fell it's okay
we're good
to remember careful of the fire
oh that's a fireball
i tried
i have water
it's really awkward you guys slenderman
[Music]
aim higher closers
excuse me
i'm still gonna win enderman get lost
yeah bye nerd
where's my stuff where's my stuff
where's my stuff
where did i land oh it's climbing back
to the middle i think
what did you see my stuff it's raining
i'm really not happy at us it's bad
[Music]
okay you know what
anything i'm taking back some of my
water did he regenerate or not
nope someone's gonna i don't know
oh are you guys good
fire on top of the water wait it's not
taking any time where's my water yeah
it's not taking any damage i wish i had
all right i have to go down here don't i
until oh wait there's water
cause somebody hit the bed the
ah golden would be too easy huh yeah
all right no no no don't kill me no i
gotta get rid of this enemy
first oh the fire
why can't i hit him i hit the bed
they're really excited to see us they
really are
stay in the water seeing the water stay
in the water okay okay yeah that's right
that's right i love it
give me whoa okay oh wait what the hell
uh where are you where are you buddy why
are you slow
this is not good
[Music]
yeah sorry i would have grabbed one
like i need to blow this lizard up with
this bed that's my life journey
please
i prefer to die i guess i think i prefer
to die at this point
yeah you can get a sword oh yeah yeah
all right all right
all right all right not clean not clean
no no no no no no no no
wait use me no dude do it
hey oh he didn't take my stuff
no way he did i don't think under my way
can the new men take myself i don't
think so okay hold on
we're here i got it excuse me really
really
oh don't don't don't
don't stop it hey oh
okay i'm on my way
[Music]
oh
no no okay
do you guys have is my stuff i'm still
there dying
or did someone take it where you died
i'm still in the center
i'm gonna leave my diamond armor
i know i had a sword or something like
that i hear an angry
man i don't know okay
lord no sword oh okay i have an armor on
the floor okay i think we're okay
are we did you pick up my stuff when you
said you were taking my sword
nope was that a yes or no
no no no no man
there's a creeper okay just kidding time
to go back to you guys
near the edge
what have um
guys
[Music]
the water kills me
well that is a powerful portal it did so
we also
appeared when i died right okay
is there a way we can put out this fire
no i don't think we just have to dodge
it that you know where kiara died
[Music]
i think i don't like a sword it's a
bottle
oh no i got a bottle i'll fill it
that's the fire wait it's gone
again okay let's go uh as long as i have
oh shoot i should be fine
my things my helmet and my chest plate i
wonder if my bow is here
are we still doing the the bend strategy
i don't know i have yet to get it to
work
okay it might be a pipe dream
shoot him shoot that down
yeah i get him it's an experience just
i've only got a shovel but
i'm missing all my shots this is bad
[Music]
i can definitely debate nice shot who
shot that nice
but i can't do it again and you have
some food
i have a little bit food yes yes he's
coming
i got him again
[Music]
i don't have a sword so can i hit him
with a bucket
i don't know can i hit him with a shovel
i can't i can't get it let me get him
let me just hit him with that
uh yeah take that you jerk i'll just hit
it with the phone like this
get him get him get him get him get him
yeah hit him with the shovel
[Music]
i'm definitely not hoping but it's well
it's nice to feel like maybe
are you guys seeing credits audio
software not seeing credits
oh she was oh she went through the
portal already
oh we have to go yeah okay
okay all right pc
goodbye minecraft it's the end of
minecraft it's over
is it over
bye it was fun
i hear someone dying they're standing on
[Music]
yes take care it has reached a higher
level now
it can read in oh
that's like meta gao guru
wait they're talking to us whoa
that does minecraft lore wall breakings
we are part of the game
wow i like this player it played well
it did not give up it is reading our
thoughts
as though they were words on the screen
who wants to read next
what about the egg what egg i think
we're at different parts
i think we left something important to
imagine
many things when it is deep in the dream
of a game
that's confusing we go back
maybe i don't know
can we re-enter the portal oh yes you
can because
now in that end the world there are
treasures and galleys so
from now
[Music]
my mission is to get an elytra as soon
as possible because of an electron you
can fly
uh yeah as long as you have fireworks
you might want to yes
who eventually yeah super flying kids
let's go let's go
it took us so long but we finally did it
you guys did so much amazing prep work
thank you so much so
proud of you all you guys already
stopped in the beginning
[Laughter]
hey it was so great guys oh when is the
win
winner is a freaking win i'm just
privileged to have been able to come
along to watch the journey
the guy that you guys prepared so hard i
hope that my few arrows could be as hell
yes of course our power together as
five is stronger than anything stronger
than that
the dragon yeah yeah flush him down the
toilet
player is going restless so glad we did
it together
you guys are so nice zero dance club
hello
can anybody else say the same that is
pretty dope
that is kind of awesome pretty good with
the bed that did uh
yeah that was so cool i did one i think
i did one
that was like something out of like a
crazy action movie
that was just unbelievable speed
i think i got a lot of uh tower shots
first try shots were quite quite a lot
of them
i would definitely give kiara the
sharpshooter award yeah
that was really only luck
with the um
skip credit oh how do i skip them can i
scroll up i want to get a screenshot out
of gal guru player of games that's going
to be my gamer title now
i'm changing my oh i just spread escape
and the credit
[Music]
can i just go jump real quick back
inside i just want to um
give me a minute
phoenix there we go whatever
in the morning
that'd be a lot of fun to uh explain oh
the endermen are still here
yeah they live here oh this is their
home huh
yes cool i see the i see the portal
thing
wait wait where is it how do you go
there's the egg i don't know my picture
the stronghold you get spawned back
there's the portal thing a woman inhaled
on me
it what what inhale the meat a woman
gathered the atoms and she inhaled
the player in her body we got bored
what are you reading oh here's the
portal
everybody else named it wow yeah
i don't need it you're missing the good
stuff here
where the treasure is made from milk and
love
the player is made from nothing but milk
and love wait what do we do with the egg
the end is basically
like insanely endlessly huge
so when you ask for this
so you might not find it right away but
you got to travel from like islands
there's like
all kinds of towns separated like
bridges and uh-huh to get to
another island
hmm are there more dragons maybe we can
go on a treasure hunt
only one dragon oh
i'm gonna go with millions of enemies
is that the egg inna yes but
what does it do you need a question to
move the egg and let it land on a torch
you can respawn the dragon with the just
leave it for now i guess
don't touch it
[Music]
do i want to go there
we're being spoken to encode you guys
zeros and ones
it's the mark of a true gamer when you
read it for us girl
universe said they love you by the way
oh
that's nice to know um that was very
kind also the universe is inside you
oh that's true that makes me feel
violated
no i'm not skipping the credits i gotta
know more the universe says you're not
alone
this is not a scuffed stairwell egg
there's the egg there
and then you never said and my mommy
said that you are the knight and my
mommy said
the darkness you fight is within you and
my mommy said the light you seek is
within you
am i you can't get out
there are not always reading the credits
wake up
i know i know where from that horrible
dream what the hell is that
what is that wake up wow did this take
us less than two hours you guys
oh wow i thought it would take us three
it's like it's only 20 minutes or
something
[Music]
i thought it'd take longer to uh find
the place
yeah only almost 2 a.m here i thought it
would be much later
uh-huh yeah oh ow don't hurt me
oh callie minecraft kelly you're gonna
die
yeah water or jump into the portal
portal would have been a better choice
here
oh that's okay i can go i'm gonna yeah
we did it
for fun okay let's take another picture
like outside yeah
outside still in there yeah outside
we'll we'll make our way back
anybody have a pickaxe you are the gamer
i have pickaxe where are you
uh i'll come in okay oh they in
uh just uh read the title if you want to
use it that's important
okay oh stream heart challenger and
sparks
i'm collecting materials
[Music]
was that a creeper yes
i don't know
sorry are you okay
eat you moved in my line of fire down mr
president
he'll leave for the rail railroad back
here
well whale world i don't want me a whale
i want some books now what do we do be a
party
do you guys see this letter oh nice
secondly because i lost so many items
what did you guys see this just a backup
oh my chest there's books in it there's
not much
oh
um um i i have something to confess um
i went i i might have been the
uh first one to open the chest and i
might have been the one
who took something out of the chest oh
what was in the chest yeah
two to two books uh that were in
enchanted nothing super special
oh yeah well i'm level 68.
68 wow wow it almost gets a nice
i was over 30 earlier hey how do we get
an electric
can we get that now the what i thought
no you had to look for treasures in the
in the world
yeah oh one do up
you guys you take care of me i know i
thought it was going to take longer to
be honest
i wonder how many elections ours
like there aren't enough for japan
members to keep on getting new ones
even though they lose them all of the
time
how many lives there is no limit it will
take a while
yeah it might take a while to explore
because you have to find the place
where they have it and then you gotta
like clear out
the stuff you gotta kill stuff
oh we wanted to take a picture
yeah yeah yeah should we not take that
like
in the end that would wouldn't that be
cool
again in the end and then we'll just
take a picture and quickly go
outside again sure if you want to do
where the hell is it is it here yes
okay there you go yes this iron shell
helped achieve victory
i'm going in did we get the egg
hey i think you have to leave it there
let's leave it there until we know how
to take it safely
yeah let's let's get to the egg and take
a picture in front of it
yeah let's do it wait does anyone have
my
um silk touch pickaxe
one percent
[Music]
i'm here to reunite you here oh uh
someone's mine
corner please not look at them
oh one percent is my other pickaxe thank
you for keeping it
no no yes
[Music]
uh why don't we take the picture make
sure you don't stare at the
inner man
[Music]
if i switch views will it make me look
at them just don't touch it
um not necessarily
okay ladies oh i'm ready whenever you
want to take a picture
okay is this how you really feel
i'll go i just spit everywhere like you
know it's going to get it with a little
touch
i don't know i don't know if that's nice
you guys you can't mine it
don't touch it no touchy
yeah just don't touch it right now we'll
deal with it later
[Music]
get close like maybe in front here
oh we could build like our own pillars
right behind the egg and it'll look
really cool
a pillar yeah some building material
in the portal i have thumbed up
oh i'll i'll take him callie here you go
oh you sure oh it might be like oh no i
got it okay
oh then okay just one touch it won't
hurt will it
[Music]
oh sorry i i panicked i left
destructive this shovel helped achieve
victory
lay down yeah where are you
[Music]
wow they're real quick they like to move
with the blocks
mm-hmm oh yeah they're real mad yeah
yeah i'm watching i don't have a sword
zoom
zoom zoom i'll sit here for a million
years until i get this
i just run it
is there a way that i can help you okay
[Music]
oh
they're angry this is going to be run
run play with this block
love it stop it they really don't like
us in their homes
[Music]
thumbs up this place is a lot less scary
without the uh dragon search how to get
the yeah
without the dragon sorry about the
shaders but yeah it was about the dragon
as well
yeah the sky is pretty uh without the
shade but it's not yeah it's much easier
to see without it
yeah pitch black but i mean yeah it
wasn't much better when it was noise
you can get his head they don't share
anchor
you can mount it to the wall that's not
all
use any tool or even your bare hands hit
the ender dragon egg until it breaks
oh yeah remember remember mikko senpai
and suicide stand by
uh wearing those ender dragon heads yeah
it was really creepy all right this is
good
[Music]
i guess for every picture we can look
into a different direction
okay okay i think this angle works for
me okay
oh yeah this one works for me too here
oh wait this is confusing to the right
look look i'll just switch right you
stand i guess that means
am i looking in the right side of it
yeah yeah yeah good eyes
look at them too okay i'm just gonna
leave this to you a little
i can't see oh potion
hey buddy the picture get the picture
i'm feeling it so it's a girl they're
about to push me in photo bomb us huh
get out of here it's nice my puppy back
in the portal we got one right
i think so oh wait i didn't get one yeah
[Music]
one cheese
um i'm let's see uh yeah sure
[Music]
and then i should be looking in the
right direction all right everyone look
at this way
[Music]
all right i'm jumping in the portal all
right let's go all right here we go
yay
[Music]
does anyone want to like go back home or
like
is everyone ending now or because i feel
like i've got
lost yeah i want to go charge your
hunting later
okay oh yeah you know we're not doing
that how do we do that
we'll look at it later
[Music]
i'm playing minecraft later today guys
so i'll just remember
here i guess
[Music]
yup me too hey thanks so much everyone
for the fun time
thank you this is quite an experience
thank you for everything you guys do yes
thank you it would not have been easy
mode without all of your preparation
yes thank you so much guys he's always
cooperating
whenever you needed help
thanks for the fun time
[Music]
goodbye bye bye
bye
you