so
[Music]
hello
hey guys what'd it do how are you guys
what do they do how do they do
great question county howdy
howdy deadbeats howdy kfp employees
welcome one and all
we're doing it finally we're doing it
for real this time no problems hopefully
no no yeah i got got to knock on that
gotta knock on that wood hopefully it'll
be fine
we have a plan b but yeah for those of
you that don't know we're gonna be
playing it takes two
and um we wanted to do it last week uh
but we could not
so now this time we finally got
everything figured out and we're gonna
we're gonna do it
it's super exciting this is such a a
pretty new game right but
we played a way out before which is from
the same creators
and they recently released another co-op
game oh my god cats don't go crazy
they released this other co-op game and
then then
it's perfect for us i was waiting for
more like this
me too me too i guess they're like
they're like the the best
at creating these types of games i have
um a
favorite streamer who really um enjoyed
this game
and so i'm looking i'm anticipating it
i've been waiting for so long and now we
finally get to so
so you kind of know what it's about or
i know that it's about um a couple
that's having some
issues and then you you go on an
adventure together so that seems cool
i basically only saw like two minutes of
game
of game footage and that's it so i know
it's about some puzzles and stuff
yeah yeah they got puzzles and whatnot
popping off i think
i'm pretty sure but we have two smart
cookies right we should be able to do
yeah we're great we're great at puzzles
i that they're my specialty i love
puzzles i'm real good at them
around yeah they're zooming around
they'll come down
in a few minutes and hopefully don't rip
out my cables
cute i want a cat i'm i'm actually
probably going to get one right now i'm
currently trying to figure out
a while yeah i know but i'm finally like
actually looking at
um the possibility because before
i wanted to get a rabbit um but then i
did some research
into raising a rabbit i just have i have
too many cords in my house so i think
what i'm gonna do is get an adult cat
that doesn't chew cords that's kind of
enough to make sure
oh that would be so nice if you get an
adult one because they barely get
adopted
yeah yeah that's what i was thinking too
to get um an adult cat
uh to just give them a nice rest of of
their existence
so i think i mean yeah then it's also
not like such a long commitment but a
rather short one i guess
yeah exactly exactly so i think i'd like
to do that but
all right good you're sending not humans
anymore
off to the underworld but cats often
don't know no it's not my
it's not my responsibility that's the
only reason that i can do it it's not my
responsibility
it's not up to me i don't handle animals
but um
let's see yeah i'm very excited i'm
looking forward to it
yeah all right so here here we are
we're gonna play the game now yata
i think the volume might be a bit low so
in the options i'll probably turn it up
once we start the game um but for now
this is all we got and i'm actually
using every single time i move my mouse
it thinks
okay you're using mouse and keyboard
right yeah
no controllers my hands are
a bit big can you make me either
bigger or the hand smaller yes i can
make the hand smaller the problem is
i tried this i tried to center them
perfectly for you
um and and i can't because your body
just moves around so much
okay i'll try i know that i know that's
struggling i i don't
notice myself but i'll try to say i'll
stay calm after after we're done
talking here well i'll say i'll say
you can it's okay move around as much as
you would like
it's no problem move around according to
how you feel comfortable i'm also going
to magically change the size of my hands
okay
yeah whatever your vibe is my dog okay
now we're ready to play the game maybe
let me go ahead and move this actually
move my stream up here
okay and then game is here in front of
my eyeballs wait
no stop i don't want you to be hang up
what the
stop no no i don't want full screen stop
it
no it gets small hang on guys this is
gonna be a wild ride
it's okay it's all right i just have to
change this
my my below monitor is smaller than my
above monitor here
i'm gonna fix it we're fine we're fine
everyone don't panic don't panic we're
good i did it
yes okay
perfect now we can start playing the
game but i may need to change the volume
so hang in there with me on that one
let's get started i'm nervous oh god
i hope we can do well on this it'll be
fine it'll be fine
i'm certain it'll be a-okay we're gonna
we're gonna
kill it so what do we got here we got a
trap we got a trash
a trash dad how was your day great
toaster broken rose refused to eat her
vegetables
how did it go at the dentist the dentist
hmm
don't tell me i've got about the dentist
appointment you forgot about the dentist
i thought you were thinking well hey
listen maybe
today he seems like he's busy you know
but it's saturday
i know i've got to work overtime you
have to do that every week oh cody i'm
not in the mood for this oh my god is he
british and he's american
yeah that's what it sounds like that was
a great accent using her
oh i'm just standing in fact
why don't we just go ahead and tell her
that we're divorcing
no that's a bad way to hear that hey i'm
gonna turn up the game fail
let's stay friends forever oh i love you
cody this is already sad it's already
cue the sound
shadow oh
those are so cute
oh oh okay we're choosing now
well i mean
well i think it's pretty obvious what
everyone
who who's what you guys think
kelly dad kelly dad kelly dad there are
people saying that the mom's workaholic
personality fits me but i think it's
just not enough of a justification it's
just it's just not enough
i already know what has to be done why
you wouldn't waste time
i guess so yeah
i am i'm ready to be i'm
a mom i'm gonna be a good mom i'm
already a good mom of all my chickens
out there
yo chickens what up yeah you guys can
testify
i mean and even look at us on the screen
how we're situated right now it's like
it was destiny
oh that's right no although on the
thumbnail it was the other way around it
seems oh yeah you're right
oh [\h__\h] i was dead okay i guess it just
fits color wise yeah yeah yeah exactly
no problem
hey guys what it do have a great day
today
you guys want some of this wait this
morning huh you guys gonna have a great
day today
take elephant a sec oh it's serious talk
time
uh rose honey
you know we love you right oh they're
having that conversation
sometimes that means that uh
we have to do stuff that isn't always
very
fun what we're trying to say darling is
that well
mum and dad we've decided to go our
separate ways
[Music]
okay can i come play in my room
uh yeah yeah of course
she's not okay with it no it's not okay
ah and
she doesn't quite like realize it's
really happening
yeah so she'll try to disappear in her
in her own world yeah it's like a coping
mechanism you know
[Music]
no baby please don't leave the house
please don't leave the house
what are you doing
she's got a little secret hidey hole
oh that's cute actually
doctor hakeem you have to help me now
booker we have to stay together
what's written in a book it says here
love is work see
wow their daughter is magical
i wish you could be friends again
don't cry no please sad child
oh the tears they fuel the magic it's
always as they always do
sounds about right
the puppets are so cute
oh wow check it out
you're kind of fat callie hey listen
homie
might need to hit hit the gym every once
in a while but i think he's looking good
hey
listen maybe that's just the way he
wants to be that's fine
he's got huge hands though yeah that's
what i'm more that's what i'm more
concerned
about the huge hands shut up
what's up homie looking good
going they're going crazy
what have you done what what why do you
always
oh it's not homie's fault yeah
you always blame him oh hey what's up
it's the book it's enchanted
oh yeah that's the master of love right
there i was the last copy because i was
selling the best
oh my god millions of couples and now i
will help you
to get together again this is actually
my sleep paralysis
to be honest this is no love book
okay i already have to agree that dad is
more like me
you can't wake up here exactly
okay um mr um book
so uh how do you wake up his name is
hakeem meh yeah it's like you're here to
fix
your relationship stress the book
properly fixed it yeah yeah
we're uh divorcing now we're gonna make
it spicy
[Music]
mix between donkey and the cat yeah
yeah yeah yeah and yeah put some boots
yeah the donkey if donkey
talks like puss in boots oh perfect it's
separated perfectly check it out check
it out so first thing i'm going to do is
go to the
um options now hold on just a moment
let me make sure just in case there's
anything i buy hide this
i'm going to go to the options and make
the game louder so that i can turn down
the filter
okay oh my god
gotta figure out all the controls
because i have no idea what
uh they are mapped to and i'm always bad
with running out of controls
it's okay me too i'm gonna take a little
a little look there's a dash
interact cancel jump camera rope grapple
movement press the sprint i see nothing
okay um got it
i see okay apply
now i'm going to leave and now i'm going
to turn off this god awful filter
on the desktop so that we don't blow out
everyone's ears because nobody enjoys
that
nobody we are not divorcing we are
fixing our relationship
i don't know what you're talking about
when you say that but okay
oh my god my cat hello kitty
in case we are divorcing i'm going to
take both of the cats okay
do it do what you want do you want well
let's find one hang on
i need to pull it down just a bit more
okay perfect
all right let's find another way off we
go
dash if the game is going to teach us
how to oh this feels good actually
you look like a darko yeah
oh we look dope heck yeah i'm already
feeling good about
about about this my dog maybe this is
what we needed
in our relationship to just dash around
and like okay can we get big now
fixed relationship fixed can we get big
now again
oh yeah it's like jumping into a pile of
uh
leafs in the in autumn yeah
is fun this feels good to play all right
and we can do oh we need to do a grab
oh amelia's special
i'd like to see the uh the manager
please nice can we break the glass
oh let's try okay oh nice my turn my
turn oh
yeah that felt good no she definitely no
shards of glass in my ass on that one
no dangerous at all oh great it's called
ground clown
oh god
fun oh that feels nice okay cool i'm
feeling good about this
oh he's the first thing we gotta work
together with okay
i don't even know what y is what's why
i'm like i mean i saw actual like
playstation control okay here we go uh
whoa
they're alive what is going on here do
we ground pound them
but whatever's going on maybe maybe you
won't lower that staircase without those
fuses
but those fuses they just
they just ran away i mean you see them
on their little
okay all right let's do it uh
ah that's okay the opponent okay feels
weird because you're made of clay
yeah i was going to say homie okay
all right grab them there's one up there
too
oh stiff nice good eye dab i got you
and now we have to jump to either side
all right
okay nine there we go i wonder if
there's like no hp so you can die
however often you want
oh yeah maybe it might be i'm not sure
i mean we may we might get hp later so
you could say because this is kind of
the tutorial
oh you can sprint oh oh
nice look my legs going before my body
check it out
like a chicken without my head oh don't
let the kfp employees hear that
we shall oh wait that was how come you
don't even know what that looks like oh
my god
nice i like the game let me do that
i love that the game let me do that i
don't like that you should be more
careful callie
no that's fine it's fun don't die
there's nothing wrong with dying man
jump and slide on surface oh jump and
slide okay
like this
oh i just continuously i guess okay yeah
pretty much we have to try and find a
way to get up there though
you can you can actually hold on to oh
wow you're having a fun time there if
you just hold on to it maybe
and that's how we can get up there yeah
so just grab on
okay it's trial and error
oh wow nice i bet i could have air dash
wait what good night
that looks painful that was fun
and jumping
oh that's okay i didn't i didn't realize
until now
oh okay actually it is this way i'm
gonna keep shifting the weight to be on
this side maybe i can post it though
oh yeah that's actually a way better
idea or i can just run inside
oh oh no here we go yeah
just have to run on the inside oh yes
come here
oh the inside
oh wait we're not even supposed to do
that
ah we use this
what oh yeah you can jump on it and then
there's a hole over here
oh i didn't realize oh yeah
[\h__\h] stupid think go away go away
you got this homie i'm cheering for you
over here
just ground pounding oh sorry i'm sorry
for the weight i'm here oh you're good
don't even worry we're just going on
here uh
problems how do i get up there let's
give me a ground pound both of us
okay we can both do it oh wait i better
have something to do with these wires
um stuck in there probably
yeah oh cool okay get out let's go
good job
did you see my foot let's do it again oh
that's so cute
the flips are fun can we do it again
this is so funny because because the
personalities really are switched
it's funny i kind of like it
though it's a nice gap i can can i jump
with that
oh yeah again i think yeah i think the
last one
goes here
what
[Music]
yeah very good cool
all right let's party
nice oh perfect let's go okay
oh no that freaking book is here no
i don't know i don't like that book man
real big donkey energy just like you
said
dumb fuses oh may there she is
gross oh hey daughter can you see us
like this
your daughter oh you talk like you own
her
ask yourself can you really own the
people you love
you just let it go through come on
that's a good point but
but first there's someone i want you to
meet
cha-cha-cha-cha
oh my gosh they're all alive why do i
recognize your
voice why am i getting these brave
little toaster vibes i don't like it i
want to flee this place
please take me away from here the vacuum
cleaner oh yeah
because it is your vacuum cleaner oh
[\h__\h]
yo vacuum
[Laughter]
it's like a movie show
sorry sorry it's the cat hair i can't
help it
hold on
oh there's a battery in there don't know
how that worked out and i feel really
bad now for all the times i've cleaned
my house and
used the vacuum cleaner to suck up
things that maybe shouldn't have sucked
up like a hair bag
instead you put me away from life in
here
sorry hey book why did you introduce us
to this dude
what was the quiz we both kind of
uh he's the reason why we had a fight
because you broke it and i promised that
i would fix it but i didn't
so we both did a mistake there oh i
guess that's it
and didn't talk about it so we have to
talk about it
yeah yeah it's true but i still i prefer
not to meet
the spirit of the vacuum cleaner it just
makes me feel very strange
oh my gosh the dude is lost lost lost
the vacuum cleaner it's lost its mind
collaboration
yeah that's what we're doing
collaborations yeah yeah we're collabing
but
i guess they have some issues so we can
skip it right
yeah we already we're doing that right
now yes i heard you
hakeem that's what we're doing right now
what crazy book i like him i like the
way he talks
if you hadn't broken it oh yeah well
this would
it like you okay well i didn't know we'd
end up in a place where our vacuum
cleaner's alive
yeah it's pretty messed up
[Music]
maybe we're stuck here forever forever
no way
we're getting a divorce yeah i know
we're getting a divorce
do that unless we get back into it yeah
we can't we can't do that when we're
like little
dolls like this and then like what are
we gonna do i'm vacuum cleaner
okay it's climate time let's go
where's that annoying that reminds me of
those water slides
in one of the parks yeah that's oh
there i go i love that we both did that
like we didn't even think
[Music]
here we go here we go
i just said what's happening i just
described what's happening
i didn't hear that there you go
what is this am i gonna give me like
goku vibes i don't like that
should we have that suckers in too
inside the house yeah okay
oh try not to drop me all right i'm
gonna put you on that thing
you gotta try and get in there oh it's
okay i'm i'm gonna be hating
it's okay uh yes i'm i'm aiming what you
want to try
why oh i see i see i get it now
but that was good that was good that was
good
okay again sorry that was my fault
here i'm just going to aim
i don't know i'll figure it out here oh
well that's fine
uh maybe i have to whoa oh okay
i don't know it's up to you now i did
something
oh cool okay now it's extra strong nice
you did it
very good that wasn't bad does it suck
us in again
did you die nope i'm good i'm chilling
okay i really don't like all the bugs in
here though
really not a great feeling
oh it's okay happens to the best of us
ew it's so many goku booties yeah i
had really bad feeling with that i don't
like i don't like it
mm-hmm let's see now we gotta oh
yeah do something over here no doubt um
i think one of us has to control this
again so i'll control this
no worries leave it to me there we go
what does it do now great question
i'm not sure it's very very thing yeah
oh i see so maybe
tonight's there down yeah yeah come down
and then
do it again or anyone yeah oh [\h__\h]
you're good you're good ah i'm from the
other side now okay
yeah i don't really i don't enjoy that
part but you know
okay reversed again or oh no no what's
happening though no
there's a new one i can join you oh just
kidding whoa
whoa whoa okay okay wow
i am really oh i'm really going around
everywhere
i guess i'm going there too maybe
regardless
i shall hold the door open for you
kusatori thank you
what if i did just let go that would be
kind of i'll
get in here i guess that oh wait
you got to help me out i do something
here
how can you pull them together
oh it wants me to ah
or to to lead the the the the
electricity later on just because i'm
just like
connecting it with my own hands but
first we start
ah first it starts here
okay and then oh [\h__\h] i'm not that fast
yeah i'd like to come and help you but i
just i don't know how to get in there is
there a way you can open the door from
your side i wonder
i will see well something's up with that
too
uh now you should be able to come
through i'm saying
all right here i go perfect okay
oh
wow very good wow all right i'll start
up the circuit then and we just have to
be fast
okay you can press the button and then
it'll go through me and then you gotta
go you gotta run
okay i'm gonna run to the one that comes
right after you and you're gonna run to
the one that comes then after that one
okay sounds good all right
okay holding it why am i let me go
that was painful oh wow
uh you gotta aim oh no no
i guess there is some level of aiming we
gotta do oh please please please please
please okay nice
okay oh my god
[Music]
then we can crouch crawl
very nice very nice a little bit of a
side
side slider slightly slightly yeah
when you call in yeah a side scroller
a science girl that's yeah that's it
come on okay
i'm getting i'm coming in i'm coming in
yeah
i'm in there too my my ass is right in
front of you kind of i see
it yep cause it's so big how can i not
see
it it's funny but that's dad's ass
you're looking at it
no no i bit this dash i did a ground
pound damn it
nothing beats a ground pound
nothing beasts are ground
okay oh
yeah wait okay
nice we're doing quite
well i would say but i haven't seen
really much puzzle difficult puzzles yet
i think now it's like like uh
uh uh what do you what platformer
puzzle yeah this is definitely uh this
tutorial
so what uh what i'll do is i'll grab on
to this
wow keep okay oh oh no
no problem okay wait no i meant it
wow that was lucky okay you can do it
dad thanks
dad we'll try did they actually have
names in the game yet
um i think i wonder if it's just mom and
dad they probably do
maybe we just didn't pay attention
probably done right
so something must be on your side i
guess yeah
i'm gonna check it out oh it's it's me
and cody
okay i was gonna say we can name them
just you know kiara and and
cali but no i guess not what
made it oh it's hoping automatically i'm
scared how did you do that
oh i pressed a button oh [\h__\h] um
i panicked but i know okay it's okay
take your time
take it oh [\h__\h] thank god this game is
so forgiving
right i was gonna say oh my e
why does dad pose like that when jumping
that's very strange all right there we
go
this is an interesting little mechanism
right here we made it over
nice yeah
that is pretty fun this game feels good
to play just the controls feel very nice
to play
yeah okay so i think we can what's up
pass maybe
oh no we can't get through there i think
we go this way
so what i need you to do is switch it
right as i'm in the middle okay
oh okay okay okay
here we go i think i can all right i'm
i'm putting my faith in you here we go
all right here we go well [\h__\h] okay
let's do it
it's okay you're doing your best all
right let's get another shot
and here we go nice and here we go
nice very good now it's my turn
all right leave it to me cause it's
sorry i got your back
okay okay okay ready three two one
i go and go nice oh nice okay
okay nice oh
okay
it's all good in the neighborhood
it's okay you got you got it you got it
this time i'm sure you got it
and dumb okay
very good well done yeah baby all right
now uh maybe here i wonder
uh if we jump over here
it's making it making the cute glitter
nice yeah like amelia's emilia makes
those sounds
yeah except they're more high pitched
[Applause]
can you not make it
oh there we go there we go i did it
actually um i i had like vocal voice
voice training before training
and this was one of the exercises to get
loose you know
yeah yeah yeah nice
oh we gotta stick something in there
again it looks like it
what shall we stick in no maybe not oh
yeah or maybe it's just decoration
oh maybe okay what do we do here oh okay
uh oopsies it's a shortcut
oh i guess we can't go this way huh no i
found nothing
yeah maybe we are supposed to go this
way
okay we're just going back though down
here are we
all right and i'll aim this for up oh oh
it's kind of it's a wild one
oh [\h__\h] wait huh ah
fun yeah i will activate the red button
[Music]
that emma recently does a lot activating
big buttons and letting everything
explode oh really that's kind of cool
yeah he's playing a lot around
like obs and stuff oh really
that sounds like amelia
so inspiring indeed i must say
i i kind of wanted to open my obs game
too who is in here
yeah hey grandpa oh yeah oh
they didn't like that i did that huh we
both got
oh wow this is a big jerk so if you
ground pound this thing it'll ground
pound you right back
so what we have to do is what if we jump
from like up here maybe
okay oh no that didn't work no
no i got rejected okay at the same time
yeah uh
maybe we're not supposed to ground pound
it let's just maybe maybe we just ignore
it
yeah for the time being we shall try
that
it was fun playing around with it yeah
yeah that was pretty fun
oh shall we press the button oh okay
nice you see you can jump dash i don't
know where i'm going
i don't know yeah
[Music]
here we go
oh that's true that would be pretty neat
i gotta say
let's see which way shall i go i would
go this way we can go this way
maybe only one has to go to switch it
again you know because that
one over there is red so you want to go
yeah all right get ready to help me
okay okay ready go
thank you perfect oh good timing nothing
after that okay
is there one over there as well uh let's
see i'm about to figure out how to get
you over to me
maybe i'm supposed to jump i think i'm
supposed to jump on this hold on
okay oh just kidding i guess maybe i'm
not
um oh i'm supposed to use this here i
use this to move this
on i'll get it a little closer to you
all right can you hop on there from
there oh i think that's too far okay now
okay i understand okay
all right it's coming your way that's
the right one
oh [\h__\h] oh close it's okay i'll just
leave it right i'll leave it right there
for you
all right here we go make sure you
crouch okay
granting okay yo here we go
oh wow that worked nice okay
welcome welcome back to the land of
living this is the best couples therapy
i've ever seen
yeah i mean if if this could actually
happen in the real world i think that
positive results would be off the charts
yeah
it makes you work together and grow a
special bond
yeah oh i see so you ground
okay a ground pound and then you do a
jump okay so you're ready to jump into
that
wind
hi
i don't know what i did code but i i did
something
yeah i think so too let me go look
uh maybe if you let yourself get sucked
in
oh yeah you get shot out
ah yeah you get let yourself get sucked
in from the other side yeah i guess
or not but where should i wait this is
right here but
then except can you get in right there
where i see out i see hold on i see it
if i can switch oh i think so yes it did
so i just need to go inside all right
got it
and then jump over to the other little
thing
and then i go with it there we go now
we're cooking
[Music]
oh i'm sure i'm going to shoot something
into that that mouth nice okay go cool
oh shoot here how do i
wait
that works too oh no it doesn't work
here i'd like to pick this up please can
i
i can't actually move oh wait i'm
supposed to direct this at them
all right right now it's coming up
you got this oh yeah i've been making it
heavier
whoa this is fine
endless oh wait we're done okay we're
done that's good i don't think so oh i
guess we are
dang it i wanted to keep going
okay moving on very well done
what is that uh maybe we're supposed to
push this together
and push and push
nice here we go oh automatic gameplay
yeah oh okay time to fight let's let's
kick this
vacuums word
this looks exactly like the new automata
tutorial
oh yeah you're right actually i did play
that oh you did
yeah i've played a little bit of it but
i just i couldn't finish it because i
was too busy that's the story how it
goes for everything
fun game they're very beautiful right
she's an engineer i just finished a
whole playbook
automata very recently on my channel
this last week actually yeah i saw you
were playing that film
it was very don't listen to emotional
check it out get my real body back i can
fix you
with that song
hey expensive x turbo thousand come save
us
that's what i want is the turbo x2000 to
just bust through
the wall be like yeah mother f word i'm
the new sheriff in town that's what i
want
brave little toaster number three oh he
showed me he was the best sucker
um no thank you i'm out of here he wants
to show us though
no thanks okay so now it's a boss
oh
i guess so here i got the balls they're
going in and now you got to shoot them
oh
my god that's cool yeah that's pretty
dope
all right so we actually we have a
health we have a health bar for this for
these boss battles it looks like we have
a healthy yeah
yep oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah this is fun
i'm up there again all right here we go
next step maybe
you can do it shoot shoot
shoot
oh man you can go really far
we're gonna do this no damage callie
yeah no actually i got hit
but then it gave me my life back so
can't be no damage sorry
okay i'm going to be down here now okay
and do it i'm going to do your
shooting leave it to me i'm a good
shooter
i think you're the better shooter oh my
gosh
well that's really painful
i died once i guess oh so much for none
no damage oh my god he's
[\h__\h] me now okay i kind of figured
that wasn't gonna happen anyway
not necessarily just because of you but
because i'm attracted to death naturally
so i wasn't ready
okay let's shoot him again
oh my god not again not again
not again not again oh [\h__\h]
oh yeah the falling rocks are really
tight
all right let's
oh i mean to your eyes
yeah make him suck his own eyes out
[Music]
i can't let the hell demons see this
play through i don't want to give them
any new ideas
that's horrifying i made these dolls she
made these
yeah they're pretty sick right you guys
were just insulting the heck out of them
you jerks
why didn't you tell me about them well
why would i she's a kid she plays with
all kinds of stuff
yeah well come on let's find her
all right here we go you should oh crush
you use this place i haven't been in
here for ages oh
everything looks different yeah but
where is this
is it their background in that happy
place oh oh
whoopsie-doodle yeah it seems so it's
probably kind of near the child's hidey
hole we gotta get back to the house
maybe i hope we get to like ride some
dogs and cats and [\h__\h]
i wonder if they have a pet it didn't
look like it
oh that's a shame i want to write
otherwise probably the vacuum cleaner i
would have spit out a lot of cats
that is a great point that you bring up
now i'm glad that i just went into this
lunch why didn't i do that
it's cool do they automatically hold on
to the surfaces
or do you always have to press cell why
um no you automatically i just tested it
you automatically can cling on to what
else
oh but not every wall i think some walls
you can't
okay okay
hey over here i'm trying okay
i'm just chilling i'm hanging out i'm
hanging out
oh there we go now it worked it depends
on the wall i think
um
oh my god hello daughter why have you
done this to us
rose why have you done this to us you
can't hear us
no sweet child of mine you have doomed
us forever
i'm gonna get over there now i think
it'll look pretty cute like this and
we're having fun
like this i'm just i'm just trying to
think of ways that we can convince rose
to burn the book
i think that if we get rose to burn
hakeem then everything how we know
no we need the book i'm just trying to
no we got a talking hammer i'm just
trying to think practically of how we
can get out of the situation but that
human locked us up
we're not ready to get out of the
situation what do you mean i'm ready
i mean it's a fun game that's the only
that's the only reason i think we need
it no
he doesn't because it's a fun game
anyway i heard that heartless woman got
a new job in town and doesn't have time
for our hobbies anymore
who cares about hobbies do you know how
painful it is to die from rush
it's like burning alive oh i know how
burning alive feels like yeah you're
you're familiar with that but at this
point do you even feel it chiara is it
painful every time you die
only not really it's like a
hot stone massage that sounds amazing
actually
i love hot stone massages pull that nail
up gonna need it
okay here it goes whoa oh
where'd it go just whistle what really
oh is my weapon now oh cool we got a
flying nail and a talking hammer
oh let's go
it's hammer time stop hammer time
every time you see me i forget the rest
of the song all right
where are we going where do we put the
nails
hey why are you doing that to me now i'm
gonna pull my nail out
why are you doing this to me
okay i will hurt you
you can't shoot stop nail time yes i can
yes i can yes i can
no you can't yes i can
stop i want the hammer this isn't fair
yeah i stuck it in you huh i stuck it in
you
this is fun what okay let's focus
no it's not you oh let's poke us okay
gotcha i'll poke this look focus
i'll poke you right now
yeah i kind of agree with dad on that
[Music]
oh yeah hey
why am i the only one that truly suffers
when you when you
throw around the hammer but when i hit
you with the nail like nothing happens
because you can't hurt me yes i can
wow it's like a metaphor for real life i
kind of hate it ah
wait i got
but then i died too there's gotta be so
many
oh [\h__\h]
only one because we did at the same time
maybe that was
too much power oh no i guess it was not
enough fowler
holy oh yeah you have to use the hammer
oh so maybe i go over to the other side
and jump from here okay
oh wait there we go just barely
you made
i actually can't grow and pound these
that's a shame i'm stuck okay
let's see let's see let's see let's see
let's see
i think this is a job for you if it has
a blue thing then it's a job for you
oh the stream cut out for seconded
themes welcome back everyone
stream cutout just for a second that's
weird stupid dude blue
yeah that sounds about right here i'm
going to hit this thing again with the
knit oh that didn't work
harley
hold on what am i missing here
[Music]
yeah that seems like it would work hang
on
oh but what would that do
i know right that's the question
we gotta use our big we need to put on
our big brain
oh hold on
uh oh i can do it here oh
you can uh fixate it
got it oh oh nice okay
oh oh oh
wow very nice gymnastics excusatory
thank you i'm here we can swing off that
nail
oh swing off you have to do it because
you have the hammer
okay that sounds a little dangerous
oh you want to recall it oh no i can't i
mean i can't recall that but did i just
jump again yeah jump again
okay sweet moves [\h__\h] yourself
the dad is so cute in this game the dad
is so freaking cute
wow you're going nuts over there all
right here you go i threw another nail
for you oh
thank you jump jump
oh this is fun yeah is there another one
that we do like that
here find cody what do you mean find
cody
i'm over it it's so that you can see
where i am i just threw another video
for you
okay [\h__\h] oh
i failed it's okay you got it this time
that's quite far away
it is a bit far here let me see it maybe
oh
i was gonna say let me go ahead and put
it a bit closer to you
there we go okay okay oh [\h__\h] wait wait
wait
maybe i need to dash
wait you can because you can dash yep
[\h__\h]
oh maybe you can dash with a hammer
it kind of no it does seem like i'm
dashing yeah
what's up hammerstein okay
there we go oh wait sorry i
saw the other one
i saw the other yellow thing and i got
excited
sorry i have a very scrambled reaper
brain excuse me
[Laughter]
okay and yeah and we
i got you a nail nice did you receive it
i did i got a new nail so now we can do
two more ammunition
so maybe now you can do both reach
oh sick thank you
yeah did it
aggressive hammering indeed
[Music]
i'm very nice all right i gotta go to
that side and hammer again
yeah it would appear so ah you gotta get
on there i think
yes ma'am sorry it's okay impact
me all good i'm here all right next and
then the next one
oh what happened oh okay you're fine
all right let me see what i can do here
uh i actually can't uh i need you up
here so we need to figure out how to get
you up here from here
let me see how what if i
no that's not it maybe if i
uh let it go up again maybe you see
something where you can
hang it onto oh nice idea ah
you have to fix fix it again maybe no
maybe not
hmm i feel like that would make the most
sense but
because we did that before i think i
know how on the yellow uh
do it again okay
uh i see i kind of see how here so for
example do this one do this one
closest to me first okay
[Music]
oh wait that's where okay see there's a
hole in the on the bottom
try it again oh
nice this is something we ought to do
from down here anyway
all right do this one again
okay
now at a height that we can get up to
nice
wow the puzzles are really happening now
yeah they sure
are
[Music]
wow feeling very smart fitting that you
smash everything
i will say
oh this is this is perfect for you
this is how i let out my aggression go
we're all done hang on i'm missing a
nail okay was that okay
uh yeah i need to get a nail back hold
on
can i recall my nails there we go
cool all right here we go
what's behind let's find out
oh my gosh this [\h__\h] again i mean
this a word
challenges make you grow what is it can
you just leave us alone
when you're willing to face you always
learn something new it's a tumblr ring
when you hear this sound
follow it keep following it and you will
find
the challenge you seek
you're so motivated i love it to your
purse
yeah it's very sweet win or lose
you must do it together
well i guess we're gonna have to all
right you want to give it a try
we haven't got time for this oh are you
afraid of losing
me no way
bring it on oh i'm gonna bring it i'm
gonna
[Music]
this game has mini games too by the way
is
[Music]
hi
peekaboo
[Laughter]
honestly this works better for you and
me but i mean for you and me switched
but
you know
oh you're the winner that's cute
here i challenge you one more time i
didn't realize that i'm supposed to try
and stay up for a while
let's do it one more time how about that
double or nothing
doubler okay i mean i'm threading but
okay let's do it here we go
for this
two one that's it
there we go
nice yay how did you win
um because i stood up for a long time
that was pretty short
but it's cool we both have one win under
our belt so i'm fine i'm just fine
leaving it at that
i'll leave it that was fun that was a
good time indeed i wonder if we have
these weapons for the whole game or
only for like this part and later we get
other weapons i think there are probably
various various mini games but it was
interesting because the uh the
the tables were turned usually it's the
other way around for me it's me trying
to whack you
hmm so that was fun
oh [\h__\h] i don't know what i'm doing i'm
over the other side okay
oh you too hello
oh maybe you're supposed to swing
maybe i can hammer something here oh no
you sure can
what is that what does that do nothing i
think this is tony maybe you might be
able to swing over here
check it out oh
you are smart very smart dad
no no thank you okay i'll i'm on it
we
very well very well done i timed it
perfectly so i knew i knew that you'd be
fine because it's okay
it's just
oh look at that nice i think you have to
get up on that platform
oh the yellow one i see i see okay
and three two one oh sorry i
i don't think i can pass here actually
yeah i think i need you to pass uh-huh
i need your i need your nail yes i need
you i'm right here
oh you're stuck on this side oh just
kidding yeah
there you go wait no not that one
oopsies
all right i'll be awaiting your
hammering oh
okay okay where though where do i go oh
good oh good
that is good fair okay yes ma'am leave
it to me
hold on here we go
well there's a car sound oh my god
what's happening oh there's all these
moving metals
okay big puzzle here big
oh man this is a big puzzle all right
oh you need to help me there oh okay
oh okay but and now
oh okay oh thank you oh
oh no no worries no worries i got you
interesting
all right okay okay safe safe
all right now this one's coming don't
make a run
i think um it needs to be stopped uh
a bit later i see okay damn it sure
let's give it a try then
okay oh wow you're able to just do that
on your own
okay so what's gonna happen is you're
gonna get on there you need to time it
well
uh and then i'm gonna stop it when it's
on the edge here okay
yup
ah i see so i should pull the yellow up
here in a minute okay
can you
[Music]
nice all right oh
oyster oh oh oh
oh wrong side ah
well done all right now let's see what's
going on up here
oh my god this is so interesting i'm
gonna stick a nail right here for you
i don't want to mess up um okay okay
um wait it's coming soon
i'm on it and i guess i'm taking another
nail right up here
wait hold on there you go oh
i retracted the other one too oopsie
doodle
good enough can i wait for that one to
come around
and i'm just gonna shoot it as soon as
you get close there
okay okay
yeah those gears are pretty tight yeah
don't you don't have to retract those i
guess i guess i can just reuse them
sure just hanging just hanging
yeah just be careful of the gears
because they will just they will destroy
you
oh what the [\h__\h] i have to probably
jump when it's up high not when it's low
yeah maybe i don't know
i think i guess
it has to be
there's a way to stop the gears
um all right
but like if i jump over there now it
would kill me there yeah why do i get
both back that's so strange okay let me
try something
can you nail it like to the like closer
to the gear
okay did it roll to the middle sure
i'll try that thanks dad
ah nothing
hang on that's like oh
oh wow that's that's what was that
something up i don't know
all right oh [\h__\h] what
side uh but the second one you can nail
that one
oh [\h__\h] at the at the middle like a gear
right i see i see yeah let me try that
okay nice
okay i'm ready so i'm gonna do
get ready i am gonna go for the next
round
okay that should work
nice very well done
that one okay there should be some
platform somewhere
again oh no that one's first okay
heads up cody oh
i i i don't know oh you got a new name
nice that makes three huh
wow you're pretty far back here i'm
gonna go find you wait i don't think i
can i'm actually stuck here
[Music]
oh what is that
i'm not sure but there's some stuff
going on over here
let me try and let me try and jump on it
discover it flip the switch what's this
is this a game this might be a game
oh a mini game yeah
i guess then that's because i can't
reach that right now
oh really yeah i just have like a lot of
weird other options
like it starts with some small platform
like dude
there i am okay oh okay then i have
another one
where it does the same thing what is
this
oh yeah that one but i'm not sure what
it what
it doesn't stop it when i do that it
doesn't maybe i just need to run
right now get ready
but okay i get it
it's okay let's do it again hold it
ready
go yeah very good
now i need yeah now i just need you to
break these i'll be good to go
oh uh can you me shoot going on
i got you i got you my dog
yeah next one okay get ready
thank you no wait no what what
oh i can do three at a time hold on i
can do three at a time hang on
all right here we go
god damn it
all right oh wait wait uh hey
what uh let me see one sec
oh i can do one at a time wait
maybe not i mean i can but all right
that that's very helpful i can do it one
at a time
now that i know i think i have to i have
and the last platform i have to go up
but like i'm having issues with that i
see oh hold on
sorry sorry all right let's try this
okay i got you leave it to me this time
okay
i'm always leaving it to you that was
the wrong one i think
oh wait what um the
the the there's the left one first eddie
the long one though i don't know what i
want
that's open now all right hold on a sec
okay now i'm gonna gently remove this
wait wait wait it's fine one at a time i
can't
climb i can't [\h__\h] oh
how about the other one that's strange
um i think it's just like sometimes it
works and sometimes it doesn't so it
should work
eventually okay like it worked before
and then it didn't work before i don't
know
let me try again
i know what it is okay so look there are
two
parallel ones next to each other right
uh-huh so
what i'm gonna do hang on is i'm gonna
make it these two hold on
all right get ready let's jump to that
one first oh
okay oh that's how you do it yeah
and now oh my god okay okay uh i need to
make one of them go away
ready okay oh [\h__\h]
it's okay it happens to the best of us
no worries if we got it this time we
know what to do now
yeah we figured it out okay
[Music]
we are in sync yes we are
okay you're ready jump oh i
i can't jump that high the last one
again
yeah oh [\h__\h] wait
but i can't jump that high oh no oh
can you bounce off the wall by chance
it seems like just barely
then the right one all right now let me
grab this one real quick hang on
mm-hmm all right go ahead the other one
first maybe yeah oh i see i see
okay okay
oh we got that speed now
true it's a true fact all right
go ahead
okay okay nope nope
you're so well organized yeah i'm i'm
trying to
i'm i've put my mind to it
okay so here okay there we go
oh
[Music]
yeah i would i would do it if your why
do you have three hands
i was just trying to high five don't
don't expose my free hand it's fine
nobody noticed nobody noticed
okay um wait let me drink a little bit
everyone hydrate yes hydration check
everyone
ah i never knew i could use my hand for
a high five like that
yeah that was pretty crazy you have the
high five you don't have a high five
hand do you i don't i don't
damn it okay i jump down here
we don't typically do high fives in my
culture
if it's a high five aimed at your face
it's assumed that i'm trying to kill you
so it's like a deadly high five to the
face
that's a slap we call that a slap a slab
correct that's what it is
no we can't you you could do that also
like not only in the face it's a
friendly way to say hello if you do that
slap on my booty
it's out and that's an owl culture
nice try if you could please don't break
open the glass bottles
come on help me break it open okay okay
okay rio oh
[Music]
oh wow this one has a face tube
all right let's go don't don't go away
last time oh we're just fine okay
hang in there buddies we're coming to
save you i'm gonna save the tool buddies
all right and that's the end of me
are you dying don't die we both died i
guess if we both die that's the end huh
uh the final boss and big bad evil
character of this game to be the book
i just feel like that'll be fine
it's fine i shall live for the both of
us oh [\h__\h]
oh just kidding i need you with this you
stupid toolbox
oh
i gotta wait for you my homie it's fine
i would come revive you i can't
unfortunately oh
don't get nailed all right i won't let
anyone nail me don't worry
i mean i won't let any of the nails
nailed me because that's what males do
oh my gosh
i'm really digging my own grave here huh
yeah man he must be like 5 million
meters away though
all right okay okay
i'm focusing now yeah i'm just waiting
on you i'm here
okay just trying not to get it here
you got this because tori watch out okay
now now's your time to shine what is
that oh
oh wow i oh okay all right keep doing it
here we go
oh you did let me see i only like it
when you do that
what i don't know what you're talking
about there must be a way i can stop
this
and that was so [\h__\h] close all right
i think if i dash i can do it though
it's okay actually i can just pull it
back up and i can
i can nail it down
i have to aim perfectly though
[Music]
oh getting nailed again oh no no this
time
i think i can if i dash i can do it on
my own are you sure okay
yep oh [\h__\h]
all right i'm here just you know
avoiding the nails
you got this
okay
all right now this one's my turn to
shine okay
and uh i'm dead you did not shine on
fire i didn't
i didn't i really didn't all right here
we go
faster yeah faster may go go go may
go fast there's something to happen here
again
for you to jump on i think i'm gonna be
sick
that's fine homie you're joking oh dad
go dad
go dad go get go dad what is that oh
okay i'm supposed to nail this stuff
here
right go midway okay oh
[Music]
all right can we even get oh yes we can
oh how did you get there oh you got a
pot yes
okay
okay let's go
in the air it's fine i'll i'll confuse
him
i don't know how i'm gonna do that but
i'm coming
nice okay oh my god okay do it again
got it oh all right i have an idea
all right i need to hear it one more
time i have no nails left
yes okay okay
don't die
okay so how do we do this fight
um my man yeah i think we both need to
be here okay
let's freaking go yeah party time are
you gonna turn into a mecca
sick this is this is like that that oh
my gosh i'm getting flashbacks to metal
gear rising or vengeance where there's
like a big
oh i'm supposed to pull out the nail i
see i see
i see we'll figure out how this works
no no no no no no no no
no no no okay ah
okay i'm supposed to nail him here yeah
we nailed him
and then hit him hit him beat him up
beat him up beat the beat the crap out
of him
beat him while i have them nailed yeah
uh wait no oh i see i see i have to put
the nails in and then you
and then you swing up to his face i see
you okay
got it got it got it next time
it's fine i don't know how that happens
whatever and
you got this oh do i have to hit the
lock
i see all right i hit the lock okay nice
get him yeah beat the crap out yeah um
beat him up
nice very good
oh how dare you no no no
he spatulates me back no it's business
now
guessing that back to reality up there
goes gravity oh boy
oh oh oh oh what's that oh
yeah so we're in big trouble if this
goes on for too long
we're in a lot of trouble oh yummy yeah
oh hey no
[Music]
okay that's only four holes we can deal
with that how do you
because i was in front of you oh my god
no [\h__\h] it's fun it's just fun
what oh boy it's cool nah we'll we'll
live we will survive this
no problem at least i don't have to do
this thing
oh my god
okay it's done i guess i can't do more
than four holes anyway
yeah maybe not okay now this time
it's coming oh [\h__\h] now i got this
because it's okay because you went too
far in the back and then the hands
uh if you like more in the front then it
uh works yeah you got this
and jump and down and
oh [\h__\h]
it's cool i won't die
you're good you're good you're good
you're good
you're good you're good with the hand
again yep we got it
we got it this time yeah perfect ace
timing here we go
we shall
[Music]
nice well done that's one hand down
whoa oh oh matrix oh he's amazing nice
whoa life is so cool
characters are very lovable in this game
dad is just very goofy and
mom is just very very
i'm not referring to
you're not saying that you aren't cool
or anything i'm just what's that
i understand i understand everything you
say yep
uh everything what what what is it oh my
gosh
that's one hit do not
and you know what maybe i have to get up
on that thing oh that's
there yeah you're supposed to hammer it
yeah try oh
maybe can i hook it down somehow uh okay
oh no yeah get on get him get him oh me
oh yeah hit the spray bottle
almost okay i see nice nice one dad
okay got it guys this is such a cute and
fun game
the mechanic is very adorable
[Music]
oh boy that's not great oh bye-bye
please don't die
come back to me i'm here i can't live
without you
oh gosh
oh it's getting really cozy really cozy
in here
oh oh oh oh my god can we get this
paper crane hello
[Music]
very good another one really we have no
space here
yeah i think are you gonna take more
space oh no
[Applause]
[Music]
okay it's happening it's happening it's
happening
this isn't the fun one yet okay oh my
god
okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay
oh thank god you're back we may just
need to like
okay and oh [\h__\h]
okay he's gonna do it again
okay we missed the timing [\h__\h] okay
oh no mom
there we go boom goes the dynamite
that was pretty sick
nice a high five on that one
[Laughter]
i was gonna say the hammer like there's
something about the hammer's eyes being
like human eyes that really makes me
feel strange
yeah from that rust and toolbox yeah you
guys are welcome
you may you are a true hero
hey dad do some work to hate hey what
about me
huh yeah i did i helped where's my hero
low did you see that explosion
that's pretty dope you'll have to get to
rose of course of course
sebastian can you help him out they have
to get to the other side
yeah sea bass would do help us
saw bastion huh step on board
you sure come on it's safe it's like a
dog someone says about the hammer i was
thinking the same thing but
okay yeah it does remind me of the dog
dog's eyes
we're here child now our child what have
you done to us
you're voodoo magic you're a witch
rose you're a witcher host oh play
around
clara oh that book i tell you what the
book is
is evil i love the book
i love the music that comes with the
book
somehow that fits there's something
about the uh
the hot pink eyebrows and mustache that
really just ruins it for me i'm sorry
got style i don't know if you'd call
that style though
the color palette is just it's not
i mean he's got a [\h__\h] mustache you
call that not having style
i mean the the intent is there but
listen man oh ooh
heck yeah we're on some
kingdom hearts tarzan here oh wait what
okay
oh my god we're on some crash
bandicoot oh my gosh
uh wake up
very cool [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
that is so cute i am i feel stupid for
that
yeah very cool but just don't fall off
don't worry
i'm pretty good at this me too
you're all right
some people are saying sonic riders yes
oh [\h__\h]
i'm just stupid no you're fun hey um
i'm help me yeah there we go okay i'll
go okay
now i'm doing this button there i wonder
i guess it doesn't really matter
[Music]
oh yeah electricity watch out
okay thank you yeah
thanks for the warning yeah
very thoughtful of you see we already
are improving our relationship
what in the game obviously oh my god
i mean our friendship yeah relationship
as far as i learned in english
relationship can
uh means uh friendship too you are
correct
however i'm sorry i i know your ways
listen i have to be a little careful
with you
use that word a lot okay that's good
sometimes we got one of them
now we need to hit this together that's
another lesson that we need to learn
in this game is trust you have to trust
me callie okay
looking forward to it oh i
have to get on the other one we have to
time it so we have to hit the buttons at
the same time oh really oh my god
what's wide oh i don't know all right
see my buttons are not the buttons that
it says
that the game tells me what's why which
one is it
here let's just get on the i'll just
smash buttons
yeah oh it must be ah oh it's that it's
that one it's the okay so
triangle yeah so maybe you get on the um
get on the wire a little bit after me
because i go first all right ready here
we go and then wait
oh [\h__\h] i went too early i guess oh wait
no i meant
sorry i mean a little bit before me
sorry okay
you go first and then i go okay ready
and ago
mostly the same you did the thinking
this time i
did not know what i was doing oh my god
nice
what the heck nice
that's awesome holy moly
only macaroni holy macaroni indeed
oh we can go oh yeah
oh cool wait what
what
i'm stuck i don't even know really what
i'm supposed to do here beyonce
over to the other i side even know what
i'm supposed to do on here
try and get on the other wheel i can't
r1
try jumping i am jumping it doesn't it
only does there's another one
what nice i didn't know that that one's
a thing
yeah no no
pyou
oh i should have expected yeah yeah we
uh we
need to find her oh yes i know we look
like dolls but we're actually her
parents
i know who you are nothing escapes my
lenses
baby stalker in here
yeah that's a little uh creepy see
i look dead they're just dozing off dad
you're
not dead you're just sleeping what's
going on oh
where's mom we're sleeping oh we're
taking a little nap
with us all i know
was that rose sat down there with her
dolls
and then you two came alive
just like that you didn't see anything
else
well there was one unusual thing why
what happened she was crying
i know quite unusual for rose but i am a
hundred percent sure
because i could see her tears falling
onto the dolls
no tears were falling onto the dolls
it's magic oh wait a minute i know what
happened
magic our daughter is magic yeah it's a
spell dick it is cody we've got to apply
logic
okay we are having a lot of binoculars
there is no logic in that i don't even i
agree with that
yeah you could be turned into a wooden
doll huh
exactly it had to be the tears
it's always the tears magic
so the gathering is a spell
how do we break it okay i got this yeah
me and rose
we read all about the spell stuff i'm a
virtual wizard right now
just give me some space i need to think
virtual vision virtual wizardry we're
telling you
yeah yeah if the spell we are
technically virtual wizards
then in order to break it oh
in order to break it virtual machine
reverse it yeah tears
so put water in her eyes yeah so we need
to force the tears back into her tear
duct
that sounds impossible again really
okay we need to find our daughter and
make our daughter cry again
let's make our daughter cry like what
years of happiness
oh that's cute that would be a cute plot
twist
she's in her room
go on okay thanks uh come on mate
oh but how do you get a room from here
easy we just climbed the tree
we just run across the yard oh we're
outside now
nice yeah we did it
what you're never gonna make that jump
ah watch me
dad that's not respawn
no
throw us the rope it's too far good
that's the only book i'll ever read
oh yeah oh
we got it okay you can't kelly
i'm great all right all right let's see
yeah
i guess whoa that tree is
don't worry about it the ropes will take
us
open the ropes we'll take a stand
the rope oh
you can do it
how did you do it you just press r1
arm which one remember the same button
you used to get on the other tire
oh i thought it was a different one
it's okay it's
not the ants the other ones the ladybugs
oh ladybugs
yeah yeah cute cute cute
i don't like accents up here
you're fine oh i thought you were saying
again at me
oh no no you're good so you're the
guilty one
okay run through it anyway
got it you still got it
as it sails to nowhere
was that supposed to reach uh rose
i don't know what it was supposed to do
actually
i i have no idea oh well
this is fun i like this outside area
more than the inside
it has a nice feeling refreshing
although the inside one was cool too
oh yeah oh good about the area's pretty
oh oh you can get in here
skydiving
ah the graphics also really nice in this
game i got really really good
pretty game very beautiful and the call
up for now is working well because i
i was worried about some connectivity
issues but hey it's working well it
seems to be okay
yeah oh here's our swing finally a use
for that thing
let's get across oh yeah
hey here's another one oh
now this time you can't do it well i
can't choose actually which way i throw
it
the game doesn't let me choose okay
on it on it i don't
see a way to get to rose's room yet
let's get higher
okay i'm having a stupid moment again
you're good
stop it stop it stop me
[Applause]
meanwhile dad's just having fun
guys gonna say it really does seem like
hi
go for the swing and there we go i was
like wow i might actually live just
kidding
dad isn't much like me at all but i do i
love
dad actually that's the lie i see i do
see some similarities in myself and dad
they exist
okay i'm on it now and now how do i
not [\h__\h] up here
oh there we go okay i have arrived
the phoenix has arrived where are you
oh all right over there you know hanging
out
can we just stay small life is a small
uh
doll is kind of more fun right where are
you
i'm hanging out
oh that's close you're all good
oh yeah oh yeah
oh
here we go very nice well i'm surprised
your own weight couldn't already pull
that down
hey quick quit saying that about dad
we like that here but can't you see how
far away it is yes i can see how far
away it is that's why we got to keep
moving
yeah maybe there's someone inside who
can help us really
like an owl i want an owl please give
them a wise old owl
there's got to be a wife to the house
what if it's not yours
you're
what's your business there casper's
voice doesn't sound like that is this a
shortcut or not
oh is it actually a squirrel not a mouse
i guess it must be a squirrel
that would make sense this is not a
dirty ride
and we also can do a lot of voices so
we are imprisoned in improvising
in police have you heard of this book
by um dr hakim oh no he doesn't answer
it's important to forgive each other he
just ignores her
damn it you can't become friends again
no
dad's not wake up he's like out there
dad oh [\h__\h]
okay no no it's not okay
it's not like that he's sleeping
no no
cody are you okay oh no please dar
the squirrels have trapped us
are you working for the wasp oh my gosh
the wasps
don't play dumb
[Music]
kill you what is casper and casper's
squirrel friends doing it
oh my god pull a switch
you dumb stupid rodents hahaha we
regenerate
we keep coming back to life ah boss it
doesn't look like they're on the wasps
team
and why don't they die maybe they have
super powers
you stupid rodents
a boot a boot just about a boot terrible
isn't that um
isn't that canada yeah
that was the best you could come up with
dad get to the house
yes this is like a war to a war-torn uh
squirrel
he's been for a lot of [\h__\h] you know
he's seen all kinds of things
what do you mean follow me you want some
nuts huh
we have some nuts at home we have a
whole jar of nuts that we can give you
let's trade come on oh red carpet
do they have a king this is oddly
familiar
they stole it oh my gosh it's the
squirrel apocalypse it's the great
squirrel war
and we just stumbled in that's our
remote control
those sneaky rodents
[Music]
oh that's perverted yeah that's pretty
messed up
oh my god he doesn't get heart underwear
i like that
can we get it back can we get it back
yo what squirrel made this graphic like
i don't
can squirrels even do it i mean the
wasps have invaded our tree
wiped out most of our tribe
huh you must kill them
what you can't kill those crazy
creatures you nuts
no no offense ah you said nuts that's
funny because they're squirrels
you're going to need these wait that one
that one squirrel has one blind eye oh
well yeah they're war-torn squirrels
damn oh well what the [\h__\h] is that
honey maybe
it's a pen oh
i just feel like that would be kind of
weird a squirrel like chilling in the
wasp yeah
that seems kind of strange i don't think
you really see things like that
oh oh wait we're on our way i guess so
giant now well you wouldn't have to if
you've cleaned out the hive
what ah remember
in the real world in our tree i asked
you so many times and you promised to
get rid of it yeah yeah
fine why didn't she get rid of it mom
and be here if you
hadn't knocked on the squirrel's door
knock knock knocking on squirrel's door
you believe that i don't trust those
squirrels they stole my underwear
yeah that was a blessing oh
really i like those hearts my underwear
is now yeah
i mean it wasn't a bad looking flying
machine
it could fly of course you do i bet that
it'll fly later on in the game
and we'll all be surprised i can't wait
to get back to my real body
so that we can get the forest oh me too
oh this
seems like the opposite of the intended
effect okay
and we gotta we were doing so well now
we're in the fight
worry we've got weapons you mean these
homemade squirrel
diy drill passer i think it's really
funny that dad has like the kind of
support role and you get the like
weapons that really assault and hurt
now both of us are really important
though
yeah no i mean i like it i think it's
neat it's like we both have oh now i'm
shooting i wish we could i don't want to
even show
i want to give you the bazooka that's
cool i'm fine with you having it you're
you're i mean you're a warrior too
you explode things and things and and
and
swing around your sources this is
me uh testing my fp fps so
interest again we both kind of get to do
that huh
this is gonna be uh difficult yeah i can
sense that as well
nice i opened up the passageway
how do i open up mine oh make it burn
like that
[Music]
yeah we can do that try up here though
wow that seems a bit uh aggressive but
okay
nice we hit it all right
squirrels we're kidding yeah this
is a war zone
cool so basically i can just kind of
like
put zap on things and you can just
choose if you want to like hit it or not
yeah and blow it up like i'm not
smoothing it out your
strap in order to make things go boom
yeah
oh oh
does that do anything oh there's
squirrel training ground
wow and that's a ground pound
ground pound oh sorry oh my god
i survived nice
check it out i think it's a shooting
range let's try it out
nice oh nice oh nice
uh
i guess so now we get to go kill some
wasps this is pretty sick pretty metal
i mean i feel bad if they're just
chilling in their home but you know
we got to get out of here we got to do
what we got to do
okay wow this is impressive
i'm getting spooked by this boys
[Music]
okay sounds good yeah
it's kind of oh nice i can go now oh
nice cool let's see oh never mind we
need that so they can talk to us maybe
let's not blow it um
one's ready oh oh
[Music]
okay i fell down while i was aiming
okay gotta be careful where i'm looking
oh it's okay
maybe the bridge no oh there we go
is that what what is that anyway is that
honey or what is sap what is that in
german
um it comes out of trees it's like gold
and it comes out of trees
sometimes not like i've tasted it just
saying that i think i
i think i know that from somewhere i get
it i get it
i'm supposed to weigh this down what's
up oh reveal the
target
oh was that okay
yeah i shot the target
um i think it's i guess again
oh now i see it
what do you want from us i think we got
it down the oh
now it's moving oh now it goes down ah i
went down on this own a bit more than
before possibly i don't know
did it oh wait we should maybe not
oh okay okay yeah oh yeah
i thought we shoot maybe the
okay maybe you put some more sap on it
and we just make it extremely heavy
until it really comes down will it ever
come down
no it seems like that's the maximum
bridge
nice oh didn't even look at that should
have died
because now oh no that's bad what if i
die now
because i landed on the wrong side oh
there we go i respond here very good
i was gonna yeah that would be bad
mm-hmm
so here i guess now i have to shoot it
maybe yeah
no nice yeah okay okay
explosions progress
too fast get up again get up get up get
up
no no no no get up get up get up get up
yeah okay
hey ooh spooky it's poopy
where are the bees we're gonna find them
did you ever watch the bee movie i did a
long time ago i prefer to tuck it with
actually i've have it tucked away in my
memory so i don't have to think of it
anymore but now you've gone
back to life and i don't appreciate that
here it tries now
i never watched it good i mean i just
know that it's not like the whole
meme movie yeah the jazz and the really
long uh yeah
the script yeah and that they mentioned
a lot of bees
in the movie jokes
sorry for bringing that memory back oh
it's fine
it's fine i'll i'll recover
oh i shouldn't shoot it sorry
i need to hold back my shooting that's
all right
so it goes back up okay and now we
continue here
and all right next i think they'll have
to add the hanging thing
um that's a great question i'm not sure
maybe we get maybe we hop on top of the
oh
okay the oh get on top of here
ah whoa
now blow up that step
oh you're yelling
[Music]
thanks i'm glad you think so i was
is that your cat no that was me just
zooming oh okay i see i got it i can't
hit somewhere because uh i was being too
loud i guess
oh yes that makes sense oh
oh we still have the hangy thingy yeah
because it shows us design for it okay
what about this shirt
from here let me see maybe we can pull
this down
darn the sap isn't sticking yeah
squirrel attack isn't foolproof
oh how about we want to
do maybe another surface will work
better
i guess we'll go there first huh yeah i
guess sir
and where are they yeah that's the only
thing is where
maybe we got to hit these targets first
ah
oh okay okay i'm coming back late and
okay we're gonna hit the target sure
is something moving besides the
something happening i wonder
i feel like something should be
happening but it's not
um let's see maybe there's another way
we can activate
here maybe we can pull up this
damn it um nah
the gear maybe maybe you try hanging
on to the thing once oh yeah
okay oh oh oh
all right the void okay and now maybe
i don't know oh maybe there is some kind
of way i can stick on to them
oh huh okay you are
up higher now and now you can jump over
there nice
okay awesome thank you yee
okay i've got the grippy surface
paint primer i'm gripped on to it
now maybe you can oh i have to turn it
around oh quick quick quick
very nice all right now i'll just i will
simply use my weight
oh see that's uh impressive that that is
enough
ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha hey listen
daddy is doing dad's best and i'm proud
of dad no matter what
interesting they're experimenting on an
acorn
they really are nuts look at those tabs
oh yeah it's like it's a nut joke
because they're squirrels
oh maybe we can turn them like this
and let me get up here can you do the
the first one again the honey one the
first one because i exploded that
sure oh [\h__\h] oh
i died one wow it was on the platform
and
killed me once it moved it we started
over there
that's a good idea let me try moving
this
one
does that move no no
it doesn't it must be the other way then
here my okay let me try again though
chad says i walked off off
but then uh i got it first it's exploded
again so i can get on it
okay now you make it heavy again
there we go okay now it's working now
we've got and
and the angle changed too
yeah the other one that looks that legs
okay come on dad a little more
there we go
[Music]
dad i thought you were good at aiming
come on
i'm not bad i'm having a heart you know
what this is what you get that's what
you get that's what you get is what you
get
wrong wrong way wrong way
it went the wrong way
oh okay nice nice
i can shoot again what does that do oh
that did the right thing
okay noise welcome
up here guess he's back
okay
nice that's fun very sad time
we're destroying this this tree from the
inside
coming up move right along okay
push the red button that's
no i think what's behind oh can we push
it then
yeah i guess so the start one we can
probably push
the start button hey do you have to
ground pound that i want oh there you go
oh let's go uh-oh
i wonder what these buttons do
[Music]
[Applause]
hello
[Music]
nice how about acorn
cool oh grind up the acorn until i make
a little acorn stew yeah
nice that's very you think that's fun
huh you think that's funny uh this is
great because we can keep coming back
and whatever but they they can't
so this is like a squirrel like torture
chamber and usually people perish in
here but you get to
you get to live anyway i'll stop now
i've had enough
sorry just one moment you let me out
there we go
kelly i love the birds
i am not going to let you forget that
one
it was fine you look fine kinda
whoa whoa they're acoustitory well over
there
oh there whoa
i don't think either of us are my dog
this one can't hurt you like then like
the hammer can i guess
yeah i guess not oh well
i'm very unfortunate too bad without
continuing
that was fun we already came this way
right
oh wait yeah i was very focused on
getting my revenge i'll get it one day
so it's cool we're supposed to go this
way i believe
okay left everything you want in a box
to the left
hold on we're going to do here hey
this is lit looks loose
reacting okay
we know about that lamp oh
hey maybe we can blow it up nah
oh right i can't zap that
what if we can stop this other stuff
though these latches for example
my dog okay just shoot to your heart's
content as soon as i'm done sapping
everything up
so that they all open up at once i guess
exactly hang on let's move
on a sweet chain reaction all right do
your best because it's already wait hold
on
oh nice that worked what now
we just fall down oh
yeah something big this looks like a
whole different game
yeah it kind of does huh no i'm dead
yeah you want me dad yeah i just kind of
oh i don't even know where i am now it's
responding to me somewhere unfamiliar
anyway
bad very long
okay ah up here fans do i
shoot too oh no i don't
what is good at these races brings these
over
mm-hmm i have to shoot that oh
no oh no i'm not you're not coming with
me
i want to i would like to can you shoot
those really quick so i can come back
thanks oh here you go oh it's going the
other way though
okay okay okay okay all right leave it
to you
oh close nice i'm over on that side now
but when shouldn't you i thought we were
supposed to get like uh
we were able to get on that together oh
yeah i guess we are huh
just a moment i'll pull it back
hmm oh but let's see where i end up when
i die
now i want to spawn on your side damn it
okay wait let me get over to my shot
i'll come i'll come back to you
what it's not coming to me why why
come back to me thought we can ride it
together
yeah that's weird now it's just kind of
chilling in the middle and i'm dead
not yet oh not dead oh no dead
why is it not coming back to me when i
shoot everything
hold on
[Music]
i shouldn't ah yeah okay put all the
weight on it so it the the thing gets
super close to you so you can jump on it
and i'll just shoot it from here oh i
died okay i died but yeah just
uh because i can shoot them even from
here yeah me too
okay so now you should is it close
enough to you
i think oh no not yet i'll get it i just
need to hit this one over here
yeah okay okay still not close enough
here i just need to maybe hit it a
little bit more let's close this one
oh no oh yeah i moved a little bit more
maybe the the closest one to you a bit
more i think
okay hold on
the one closest to me is that four i
think but maybe the other ones okay
that one went down and then that one
went down oh okay
okay it's not moving an inch though yeah
it really isn't moving at all
huh ah i light i like that one
what happens
it didn't move either huh
let me try let me try what happens when
i shoot them again
oh it comes back oh now it's going away
no get go to him yes
we took some time to figure that one out
yeah no wait
i'm still here again
i don't understand that mechanism it
gives you power maybe
it like powers it up oh oh oh
oh so bad no
yeah okay okay oh no
there we go oh welcome back dad
thank goodness hi miss yeah yeah
me too oh next level
what's up oh my god oh
we have a wrap there's like onions and
nuts no it's only nuts
okay
who was it was who who was in uh b-movie
again was it
jerry seinfeld
i do not know i know that chat knows i
was i was going to say
no jerry please but i actually don't
know
it already down here yeah it's oh it's
good old jerry it was adam a nice try
all right let's see
um what are these these acorn like
mutant acorns i don't like that
they want to make the biggest nuts on
earth i mean i i understand them
huh i guess i'm a fan of eating those
the the nuts no but i can relate to the
scare square wheels
can you relate to them because i
had a collab with lisa senpai before oh
reese's all about those nuts right
yeah she loves those nuts yeah she loves
sheila oh we count them
what's going on here one of us has to
get up there
yeah i think it might be me because you
shoot it right and it goes
boom okay oh this
is like maybe this one too
possibly see this one is the same ah oh
yeah
i'll get it ready to be shot and then
you shoot it when i'm on it and get on
the other one
fill it all up okay yeah my sap okay go
right next oh yeah i actually don't know
which way to go
okay oh okay
okay we're fine now uh darn it i really
need to
shoot this i think there's a bridge here
let's knock it down then
okay hold on let's knock it down again
all right well yeah but i need you
is the thing so let me see
[Music]
maybe there must be something i can do
from here
um i can't get a good shot from here
cody
i can't get a good shot from here cool
day all right well uh
no hold on a minute there's something
i'm missing and i'm gonna find it
interesting what oh wait let me
something must be here there's some more
nuts
what if i blow up those nuts
yeah no no it's just roasted nuts now
very yummy oh
oh is there something um there oh
no yeah so there's this look where the
bridge is um
there's something holding it kind of oh
i can lay a trap
oh i can lay a line of
oh smart yeah so let me just
yeah it works nice
happy new year you saw that worked okay
now
go down like redstone in minecraft yeah
yeah you think you can hit that
yeah of course i can but oh i guess when
you go maybe through here
you can probably head through the gate
hell yeah
that was not enough um here let's try
multiple shots
oh wow it worked nice just more
more power indeed don't get too power
hungry because
be careful i don't i don't i don't
necessarily trust you with that
what what what is that football doing
here you mean the soccer ball
yeah sorry about that ground pound
rose and i used to play with it all the
time just another thing the squirrels
have taken from us
the squirrels are feeling so much oh
wait there's the tambourines
discover tug of war it's a mini game
that sounds fun oh no i'm interested in
playing this i think you're the blue one
okay that goes on me
okay okay pull cody into the hole
into the hole oh that'll be it is made
for you
ah
okay that wasn't fair that that wasn't
fair we can do it again we can do it
again
we can do it again i'm not worried we've
done this before
but you're so strong look at your belly
armor that's all the muscles
you're right that's all that's in there
or you'll miss me winning
oh ow dad dad's face
oh no
did you did you let me win oh no i
didn't no
fair yeah yeah i mean i totally did that
okay let's do it again let's do this
yeah three two
one
[Music]
this was mine
that's right
wow i guess if it's a controller i just
can't
i can't uh i can't win
[Music]
because last time when we were using a
keyboard
it was your boy
i'm good with pushing those buttons
that's the true fact i can uh i can
attest to that
let's go what's up here
oh no my legs hurt
my feet hurt get out of this mess
i'm having a cold beer you drunk i do
stuck here you're stuck like this
you don't know that we'll get to rose
and break the spell
what if we never get to her please stop
talking and keep running
okay we will get there no worries oh my
god it's all good
yeah i mean if anything she finds us
when we're in a coma and then we go to
the hospital and then we wake up so
maybe
oh wait are we on the slide oh yeah it's
tarzan time again here we go
i'll probably fail oh [\h__\h] yep i did
fail
oh it's okay that's the best of all i
guess i think
you are the one of the best of us huh
who's riding those mine carts it's
amazing
yeah it's pretty cool
this is such a good game i'm absolutely
[Music]
amazed
[Applause]
damn waiter
come on get past that point
and then we good
oh my gosh is that are you a mine car oh
okay [\h__\h] it came from behind
it you did it sure didn't come from the
hell
i didn't see that probably hit you again
actually it's very close oh
nice
okay okay okay okay i got those moves
you can do it
meanwhile hydration check not you
how are you already at the end this
whole time you did well
wow oh i just i really like the tarzan
party kingdom hearts that's all
i'm like i'm like decent that's
yeah it's nostalgic nostalgic
it looks like it's time for a boss
battle i know right this is definitely
boss arena material
upside you will
um
here i think maybe we turn it this way
oh i think uh you have to do one at a
time
uh-huh that's how you correctly here
oh maybe how about this one this one's
maybe is the first one that you do
oh ah okay no you make it heavy sorry
oh okay i understand first the left one
and then it goes down and then i break
that when it goes a bit lower
and oh yeah okay it wasn't even
necessary one opened
yeah they want to harm us
yeah it's uh jerry and pals jerry and
the gang are here uh
for a sunday night barbecue no problem
he got that left i'm not ready for it i
i don't care
he's actually invited
boom boom are we supposed to still do
that that part
yeah the upper upper left one yeah and
i'm gonna shoot that one
oops yeah now you can shoot that one
okay ah
and once that opens there's gonna be
more beams
[Music]
oh my god yeah i coded this dude but uh
really
not slowing down okay okay i got him
once
really not ooh this one's uh really
angry
zoom uh dash dash is
[Music]
a death and the phoenix will not be
destroyed by a freaking
bee grim reaper so ultimately it is kind
of up to me my dog uh which one of us
i hate to burst and make you even
angrier than you already are
there we a big go
oh i ran into it you will not fast
okay i need to get behind him
my turn for a beating i got for a
beating huh
we made nut jokes now we're making
videos got it got him
more
oh oh where is he
yeah i think that yeah it's like
squashing a bug irl
oh gruesome this game oh [\h__\h] that
reminds me of the ant
movie thingy
yeah cause it has like a inside system
oh yeah yeah i know what you're talking
about there's an interview with that
bring them to me
oh dude that would be crazy if risu was
if risu was the queen
uh
i watched a bug's life recently actually
that wasn't even ants
no it wasn't
call those chickens yeah right
preparation we are not [\h__\h] chickens
but remember collaboration is also key
we know that that's what we're doing
here thanks for reminding us
[Music]
yeah i was going to say i think the book
is why is the book cursing at us kiara
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] friendship with
there we go there we go that's that's
one way to get
the book not in kiara's favor
i will never forgive
the unbelievable [\h__\h] room yeah that
was pretty rude huh i learned my lesson
i learned it's a long way to just run
here
oh oh there we go there's something
oh
if we kill the spawn point then we can
stop i am
i guess so yeah nice
we got that one down oh there's more
coming
there's more coffee
yeah i got a little c close my fault
here let's aim for the right spawn point
first
and swing around make a circle
in the meantime they don't really look
like they could hurt us though i don't
know they look kind of harmless don't
die
but they're definitely still gonna hurt
us
i think actually your gun is powerful
enough to just take them out
yourself i wonder
okay we took out all the nests i think
nice
now just get rid of those yeah
they're glowing cute kind of cute oh
there's another spawn point over there
so they actually they explode yeah they
explode
if you get close to him i'm back that's
his back back again
dad is back until he's still friends
they're all coming after you but don't
worry i'm on the way
oh yeah
nothing can hold us down swinging time
oh
as expected the first time we will fail
you oh [\h__\h]
oh
jam from your grandma yeah from grandma
i don't have i don't have a grandma in
the same sense as you so
i fell into the hole i have an advice
for you kelly don't fall into that hole
yeah it looks kind of friendly and like
blue and we fill it up
i wonder when there's a hole
you can always fill it up oh we actually
it looks like we can
oh [\h__\h] ah i guess that was probably not
the
actual mission yeah probably not i mean
there's definitely some sap in there but
i just i don't think it's quite
yeah it's not gonna do anyone that's a
great idea though
it must be something like this with
these bottles yeah we gotta do
hey are they actually full of stuff
already okay
yeah can you uh uh from the sides though
because it looks like i can burn it
it looks like i can burn it if you put
some sap on it sure
that's a good idea yeah yep it's wrapped
in
a flammable ah it filled the hole oh
these guys can't hurt us
you would think so oh no they're mad
they're stuck they're knocking on the
glass wall
oh more towers more pink he got armor
that's a pretty sick armor i gotta say
oh i'm a very good position here
from something i've seen before oh [\h__\h]
wait not squirrels what the hell yeah
did you see us
okay i was not
thinking oh yeah i really should be
diary
i got him again
i got him again oh we're doing well
we're doing well
i got him again okay nice
[Music]
it's a shame we're not even really
involved in this this war that's going
on it's very strange
yeah but all right i mean we're humans
so like
in the end
he's almost dead i like i like um the
fat ones what do you call them in
english
oh yeah bumblebees have a purpose
they're so cute
wasps uh they just hurt people yeah
yeah kinda kind of thick
must be a british wasp oh [\h__\h]
they do anything for the for their queen
don't they you sure do
it's almost there it is kind of sweet
[\h__\h] again it's cool i'll steal it
okay okay now i will get you
aiming at me
he's dead she's dead lots of dangerous
weapons of the road
yeah they definitely do not hear at
least
hey you're pretty good with that match
gun
with his pests and her pollinators i
rather that's incorrect somewhere
i heard that wasn't it but if you say so
i believe you know
yours i'm say so if you say so
i want that you can pull down that
basket
somehow to make it into a bridge oh nice
idea let's see
i don't know there's another bottle oh i
didn't see that oops
never mind the basket it must be the
bottle or maybe not
on it maybe it is the basket can you
shoot on that thing
yeah sure hold on which thing here yeah
oh here we go
now we got a bridge and those wasps i'm
very sorry for them but they're going to
stay in here for a while until they die
that's that destiny yeah i guess
if wasps are helpful then cool i'll let
them do your thing if they're not then
there you go but they stole a freaking
camera's running away from something
how quick we can't position it we can
take a photo
oh that's so cute oh it saved it i think
yes oh no maybe not it did not got it
was an achievement just
do another one oh someone has to think
yeah all right i got it i'm hanging onto
it
come to the middle
oh we can hang it up on the wall nice
okay oh cool
come on oh i can take a picture of just
you
no i want it with you
[Laughter]
what are you doing come and join me on
the photo i just wanted
the time is going down go
go now you should go to the middle
dad
this is why we can't have nice pictures
in our photo album
all right that way i'm taking it out
look into the lens
okay cute
oh just kidding that's my fault whoopsie
doodle i zoomed in too far
you want to take one more one more and
if we can do it oh you can
oh you can move it here oh
[Applause]
oh my god that's so cute that's pretty
adorable i gotta say can we get it well
i'm sure it looks great yeah that's
perfect
good good good good that one will be
framed on my wall
okay you know it oh there's so many
people oh my god what they did they were
really stalking us
huh that's a pretty kimoshi
i like it oh what's here
a boss fight it would seem uh uh
oh my god look over there oh yeah
there's sure
there are many looking out the big guns
now okay
okay well we just hit the hammer oh it's
a hammer
they call me the exterminator
i really don't
they call you the reaper the reaper rap
but not the exterminator
yes it's a little bit off but you know
they don't want that fire that phoenix
fire
yeah i guess not huh i'm terrified of it
oh yeah you get no chance here
oh [\h__\h] whoa
oh oh wow there are so many
yeah you big jerks away with you
oh what is that a hammer again no
hello oh could you oh that was really
strange
i guess okay we're going down
oh we can still shoot them liver on the
[Music]
oh my god oh my god are you behind the
door
i am hiding okay oh no
i can't do this about you okay
can i i'm not
okay let's see what they're gonna do
next okay here we go
nice just in time
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] okay
we got through that one somehow nice
okay oh this is so good
i love it it is a really fun game i'm
really enjoying it
you know despite despite the tight hand
bits we're having
yeah i think we're doing fine even when
we have to use a brain a little bit more
sometimes
yeah well true the puzzles aren't
impossible
and i'm dead i was pressing but
it didn't shoot because i was out of
munition
[Laughter]
okay you got it
oh i guess uh the explosion was too big
ammunition is also the word oh it is
wait are we redoing it
oh we aren't oh we shouldn't die from
that it seems i thought that
we had no choice okay
[Music]
okay this time we'll do it chad give us
some power give us your power give us
your b
give us e no no no more beastly
oh these aren't bees these are wasps i
guess they could spam
out yeah
okay i didn't i didn't i didn't get us
okay
good bees all dead now there we go
we're just fitting because they're
spamming bees and they're dead beets
dead beets yeah they're dead bees
nice rest in peace
oh
[Music]
all right
we've got an engine we do where uh it's
in your hand
what
ah oh yeah i guess so huh
nice
okay
[Applause]
okay what do i do i just shoot i guess
defend
we do you make the boat move
sally oh i see other way i think
i'll steer the boat
as for the usual i am the driver
i am i am yes oh okay
okay
nice
are we going in the right direction dad
um i don't know man i'm just steering us
uh where i feel like fun
oh there's more coming oh
i like that in the same there aren't
items so i don't feel like i
need to go look for every single item in
every area
that's nice yep it's relaxing
okay okay okay popping off over here
okay oh wait we have arrived i think
yeah unless you open that up you gotta
hit the target
hello nice
ready to move on bring it on so this
gives me a lot of the
uh the hobbits have it all right as well
when there were the barrels and like
going down that river yeah
yeah i can see that did you watch the
comments long time ago
i watched with my members just recently
yeah i saw that i saw that
yeah we watched the lord of the rings
and then the hobbit all together
that was a nice marathon yeah
i mean we didn't watch it as a marathon
but oh
[Music]
what are they doing they're leading us
to their queenies
perhaps yeah maybe
this is like a huge ocean what the hell
oh boy
thank you
i'm just going to shoot the stuff on the
oh we have it on the ground
okay that goes in the way that the
that goes in the way that was a very
german way of thinking
[Music]
the stuff that goes in the way yeah
that's fine hey whatever way you gotta
say it's
to get the thought across
this is uh before they were after this
drum this is the
life is strange continuation oh yeah
yeah i guess so uh did you ever play
life is strange
yeah but i forget how it ended oh i
think it and it's dead i never played it
though
yeah i think i watched a playthrough me
tell me too
thanks i'll stick to my boomstick
wow we fell and we land
nice oh oh ew there's a jellyfish
oh that's kind of cool actually deadly
it's fake jellyfish can be lethal we
better
it's real jellyfish let's go
i love jellyfish i shoot them
no no don't hurt them they're beautiful
of course of course
of course but they're also deadly yeah
we have really dope jellyfish in the
underworld actually
steer straight ahead aye aye captain and
the river stage
oh we have arrived oh we did it nice
okay
when is a good spot to end today's
stream by the way i wonder wherever you
would like
to because satori i don't know maybe
does anyone in the in the audience know
there's like a good spot coming
where we could take like a break or
is it let's always continue endlessly
almost done with the with the bee stuff
boss fight is soon okay
the jellyfish they're coming up to the
surface
i thought they were deadly we were
actually going to jump on them oh my god
that's cute
so beautiful it always continues
but almost done with the bees okay i
guess when the bees the bee chapter is
done we can
sure [\h__\h] uh up there yeah sounds
good i gotta
i got a little stream uh coming up in
like
two hours actually not two and a half
hours okay
no problem okay
i'm mogu's oh nice i'm not
you i'm i'm monkeys i'm oh among us okay
that took me a minute that what the h
word you were talking about i see i see
have fun it actually has a a new level
now we
um i was thinking we can do another like
big collab on that level
oh sure you know you know how we did a
mogul's collab before
why it's so pretty wow beautiful
beautiful quinoa
wow what are those cave drawings
look at those these snow
and the squirrel warriors oh my god why
are they using like
neon colors though pretty dope they
probably got him oh my god oh
there's an evil squirrel that there was
a cat i got excited at first
i got excited maybe there was a cat
could be a cat
yeah oh
that's because we tried to drive them
away i guess
well of course oh what's going on here
supposed to be us
the baby here's the baby
and the baby is like the chosen one i
bet it looks like a rave party
yeah i do i do kind of enjoy it toilet
paper what's up the toilet paper
we used uh these glue they used our
child's uh glowing highlighters
ah damn that's cool i didn't know there
was such a thing
look at those stars there why is there
stars that's freaking beautiful
i love it whoa let there be light
that's the scene where they steal all
kinds of things from us why because we
got a baby you think you can steal
things from us what the hell
yeah i guess we're working hard working
hard to afford those toys for our
children for our child and they steal it
oh yeah we just have a big old grudge
you can jump really far with it wow
oh what is that high-tech stuff man
how do the squirrels do that technology
oh my god oh they're so advanced
oh i love this idea that the squirrels
are way more advanced than humans
like we all need to be watching out you
know because like
this could be a reflection of the real
world and you'd never know they're just
pretending to not be very smart
i don't know any secret information or
anything by the way
you don't trust the squirrel guys
[Music]
can we stop dying now yeah i was gonna
say fish that could fly yeah it looks
like uh
looks like some kind of catfish it's
like an orca
well well shark dolphin
yes
it could vibe
no he's giving us a toy enjoy it that's
what fish do
yeah i'm the fisherman dad's the
fisherman okay
just keep swimming don't pull up keep
swimming
oh yeah i guess
reminds me a little bit of that super
mario 64 level on the sand
bird but that one i nailed so i'm gonna
nail this one too
yeah i'm sure that you will it also has
this magical music
oh and it's really giving us a nice tour
i love these trees i just love red trees
in general we've got a lot of them in
the underworld
did it just flip over nice one actually
it looks a lot like the underworld
it's cozy it feels like home wow
[Music]
there's more of him hey nice
hey friends oh
stay on top of him dead right through
that wall
oh that's not gonna work oh bye-bye
oh no
[Music]
so that tour costs everyone in the
audience uh
five dollars thank you yep yeah limited
time only and it'll never happen again
pay up five minutes no just kidding
don't do it just don't no no no no no
you're saying oh i didn't say that
hey i am made of clay could you run jump
and fall like this in your real body
no oh sit there doing it well it lasts
yeah okay
it's a freight door guys plan oh we have
a minigame again
plunging dungeons what they do
sorry i i kind of knew like after i said
it i was like [\h__\h]
it's okay it's all right
i still treasure them i will read all of
these
later
let's see it's by dory
it's all right
how do we do this hey cody do i go over
here hold on i don't know
i'm on my way hey i'm on my way
oh oh oh
oh no okay what is this game oh it's all
in the party
oh you're going to win this one you were
so good with the shooting range and
and the in the uh oh so careful you're
okay
shooting game in the other one yeah i
still don't quite get how this works
though but let's see what happens
so am i
wasting plunders oops oh i see
i know how to handle a plunger oh [\h__\h]
smoking gun ah
wait how do you charge it can you try it
you have to hold it
will you hold it back
ah okay and now i get it yes
[\h__\h] quite a few of them now huh
oh no oh no
[Music]
oh you don't want to do it again just
doesn't require pressure okay
next one no problem where where did we
come from
i think we're just going this way okay
[Music]
yeah but that's a deep
it looks like we can jump over it yeah i
mean it doesn't seem
yeah no easy easy enough
oh we're having that fun time again oh
you died yeah
i sure did oh i understand okay we have
to go to the middle one
on the middle platform no oh i see i see
it looks like it
hello nice okay probably boss time where
are we going
only one way out
okay i'm eating pizza after this
actually i was really planning to
oh wow really that sounds awesome no i
want pizza
just throw some pizza but yeah oh okay
man i wish i had even a frozen pizza you
know actually at the inconvenience store
they have a really good
takoyaki that you can just warm up in
the microwave and it tastes pretty good
oh
no no no okay start
starting over it's kind of confusing
though because it's hard to say who is
who
one way you gotta put your um your
bullet health skills to the top
oh [\h__\h] yep i've had enough of that in
your automata
yeah i bet i guess we can also dash too
can't forget the dash the dash oh
i fell down don't don't die now don't
die no don't die now
i'm good okay i'm back i'm not okay okay
dashing kind of scares me because i
think i'd fall and fall
over the edge yeah
you have it oh my god oh my god
oh okay yeah with two hits
yeah it's one of those two hits you hit
nothing
i see i see okay no problem no problem
only one way out we're good we're gonna
get
back with your crazy sauce
but they're crazy sauce just though
gotta use that dashboard can't forget it
don't use it when you don't need it or
else you can end up yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah we got this
you say that now but we can't taunt them
we shouldn't have poked the hornet's
nest we're making jokes
because we have a checkpoint here
you don't have to start from the
beginning anymore what's coming
oh okay teamwork again
okay wow
wow oh my god
yeah the bees are great we want the bees
we always kill them
yeah yeah yeah yeah we traded it these
are dope
oh oh it's like pretty dope too if
they actually do good things i don't
think they do but
it's a death arena okay it sure is it's
my favorite kind of place
i don't know but yeah i'm pretty angry
you're really sadistic aren't you huh me
no this is normal where i'm from
[Music]
oh yep
i'm not sure no you are dad it's cool
okay giant beans here's the bonus
isn't sticking to it yeah it's not too
strong
maybe we can break off the shell somehow
oh hey check it out i can get him to
stick here oh [\h__\h]
oh okay over here over here huh
oh i see i get it can we get him from
behind when he collapses wings like that
[\h__\h] that would be nice but i think we
just need to lay these traps and then
lead him over at them and then that's
when you kind of
bring out the set
ah okay i got the sap laid up over here
okay
you ready okay he's gonna come this way
again come over here it's still there
the sap is still there
we're springing this is
that was my idea my dog i came up with
okay i didn't come up with it but i
realized it
yeah are we doing that one okay yeah
let's do this one okay
are you coming coming right here
very good well done i've already got
another one laid up over here
oh [\h__\h]
uh oh hello friend
i'm over here big dumb no okay you're a
coward
on me oh it's okay he's standing right
on top of the uh oh
good thing you're there yep i'm staying
alive
staying alive staying alive oh oh oh oh
oh my gosh no now
you also have weird eyes like the hammer
so why are you on their side it's
getting forced to do this
i fight for anyone who pays me the food
worms slugs larvae
have a wasp
well uh you know the queen she has all
the nectar oh
actually oh yeah i guess the sap and
nectar aren't the same thing you can
have
okay okay this reminds me of the car
ride that we didn't know way out
oh my god oh the people just damn it's
just like the car
yeah this beetle's pretty dead uh
usually vincent was the driver
so this is perfect yeah man
uh i think we're probably gonna fail
this one but yeah i don't think we can
make this but hey
we're already so low oh yeah okay it's
cool now we know
now we know what the deal is the deal
yeah so
no worries
he looks like he can fly come on beetles
he really wants that necktie
yeah right there i'll try to avoid them
but you try
and shoot them at my house
there he goes the next year
yeah cause then then you'll be dead so
you can't eat it except maybe in the
underworld but in
the world it's not great
my name is
not available
okay okay we probably have a checkpoint
anyway so we should be fine if we die
now okay
okay
[Music]
i believe i'm a beetle and i can't fly
really that well
oh they don't like it they're not
excited about us
approaching their home
he built
[Music]
wow right into the hornet's nest we're
in oh no we lost the beach
oh that's sad that's actually kind of oh
why is there a mechanical huh i bet the
squirrel is controlling
the the squirrel imposter is controlling
the
mechanic um it's the squirrel
controlling the robot like wizard of oz
uh okay so the squirrels and the
blacks are actually in it together i
mean
there was like a there's like a double
crossings
apparently
we're
we can ride the ride the lightning hold
on
oh here i'm gonna r1 oh oh [\h__\h] okay
there's a spot on the back that you can
shoot just so you know okay
okay let's see oh but he turns
with us he turns with us
uh i'll stay here so i will stay here
okay okay and i'll make all the strength
maybe he'll focus
nice well done okay and you can lay some
more sap on him yes i'm doing it
give it to me and those last right
into the void okay all right i'm gonna
distract him then
i'm on my way
we've also got some spots on the front
as well of the wasp
okay i didn't get him but i'll take
another ride [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] those wads yeah i think uh putting
staff on the wasps is pretty like uh
useless
oh what the [\h__\h]
oh bye bye
nice fire fl flavor while you got there
yay all right so the sap is on the the
the
[Music]
i'm too stupid to shoot right now we
gotta shoot the shield i guess
all right now okay i'll give it another
try i am
all right now it's it's on the uh the a
word
again the app okay the
don't worry i'll say it for you in case
you can't say it i'll say it
yeah oh wow
oh wow oh what the [\h__\h] you didn't tell
me that that was coming
wow that's not great ah shield
swords and now this
this is a very intricate intricate
is that a word yes that is a word
oh man hello baby we love to see it
oh my gosh right on
oh no come back come back okay good
timing to come back where are we going
right now i'm gonna put oh
i'm gonna put some sap on the front of
the b again first we need to break down
this shield
then now now we've got um some on the
front
done so we got the back part but we
didn't get the front part of this oh
okay
kind of took out the hardest to get part
first actually
so well done
shield bye-bye
[Applause]
again
there's some stuff on the heart
traps have been laid i'll try and put
some on the bees oh my god
so just so you can okay i got the heart
i got the hard ones
nice now we just have the heart it's
left over okay
okay oh gosh okay not good not good
no scissors please no scissors
they're really fast the scissors are
really fast yes
dash and run
uh shoot okay i'll die
oh no we both died damn it bad did we
start the whole battle over yeah we
might have to no
no no no we come so far
yeah we do no it already has some hp
oh it's only the front card okay
i think it's only the front part yeah
i'll go check let me go confirm there
might be one
yeah you're right it is only the front
thankfully but security is definitely
ramping up
so uh here i got some in the front
guys you can take your pick easy easy
okay all right here we go
it's fine i will live
here we go awesome
okay okay okay getting close
no air strike please none of that please
scissors
this is definitely like a squirrel using
a voice changer
yeah yeah 100 probably
oh god it's it is sent by gone crazy
oh senpai what have you done
snape snap snake
bees beans yes we did it okay
finals are okay oh they're really
relentless they're
angry all right you got some on the
heart
sorry i'm fine in the beginning i
thought i was on your screen for some
reason oh to the wrong side
you're good you're good i got some more
on the heart i'm gonna go
i'm gonna run okay i'm trying to stretch
them make them follow got the height
all right i'll put a little more on the
heart again
let's see what's inside your body
[Music]
maybe we gotta hit the head
this is so cute though this game i love
this oh
how am i supposed to shoot when i need
to keep on jumping over these things
okay
no no no no no okay
okay okay
okay then all these guys done for the
queen's
is he actually getting any damage right
now uh
i think um
maybe we should be aiming somewhere
let me else where else i can aim
i mean i feel like the wire system we
can't ah
yep that does damage it does okay yep
push the wire the wires above yep
when i shoot it after you zap it then
it does but i guess we also always have
to take care that he has
uh no shield and all that as well i see
i see
okay okay oh you put some sap okay let's
go
okay it's just only a little damaged but
step by step
we will get this it's damaged i guess
it is what it is it's the final
boss
yeah yeah
this is so much fun i know right what a
good bonding experience for them
i'm very happy yeah
oh oh the sword is happening again okay
oh i gotta get ready to jump
[Music]
up
what is love baby don't hurt me
don't hurt me no more
yeah or something like that
maybe on the back no that doesn't do
that much ah there is some sap on there
okay
yep okay system no on the
on the i didn't see that you had some
step on the chain yeah
i'll keep laying it on the chain
okay
little by little
man so many wasps are biting the dust
today
it's like we're eliminating literally
every wasp on earth oh my god yeah i
know i mean at some point there are
going to be no more wasps left so like
bad unfortunately yeah
oh my god the queen should probably uh
look out
for that we're going to run out of wasps
eventually
[Music]
yes here we go i get the shield's up
closes
oh it's difficult i still fall away from
me
no swords please
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh that was a lot of damage nice
all right i'll put a little chain yeah
that's that's that's a good amount there
we go
[Applause]
oh my god
[Music]
oh my god it's so cute oh no i
am the wasp queen
[Music]
oh
oh no not great
[Music]
nice get them live nice
well what about the nectar for the
beetle yeah that sucks
the beetle is gone no more
no more beetle that's sad
hi i have nothing to do
for now oh no longer a wasp queen
what's the point if you can't be special
you are special special one of the
noblest pollinators
in nature yeah these are awesome we love
bees of course
bees pollinate crops that feed 90
percent how did you get into that mecca
though is what i wanted to know
that's what i'm curious about really
so i am special you're super
yeah and all the wasps have gone i mean
we don't need to kill her do we
huh oh so you're on the same team now no
wait squirrels
squirrels what
okay the bumblebees so fast how did they
shoot bumblebees yeah i mean the
squirrels also got to know that we
are immortal so it's kind of just it's
not a good idea to not have us
on their side but you know
oh oh it's flying away just without us
now it's okay
could have
[Music]
we're taking my little ripper rest in
peace and the cannons
i want air coverage no no cut them down
go go look at that little squirrel knife
oh man oh hello
[Music]
oh my gosh once we get on the ground oh
nice
i think you can probably end it there
all right you're shooting and i'm
driving again
[Music]
no i can i have a boost but i can't use
it all the time
everyone check your trees after this
because you never know what kind of
weird [\h__\h] your squirrels have been up
to yeah open up your trees look what's
inside
just open them up
[Music]
oh what was that okay the squirrels are
the squirrels have brought their planes
get them okay i'm gonna try
i'm trying all right
it's so wobbly
[Music]
oh no we're fine we're good huh it's got
one hb
nah it's perfect
yeah that was a lot
okay yeah all right it's fine we got
this
what am i supposed to shoot there's so
much coming uh everything
shoot everything and open
[Music]
okay i really don't have to aim when i
aim at this those squirrels it's so
forgiving ah
thank god it seems so can i do like a
barrel roll
i it appears i can't oh i just need to
keep moving okay
please do not do a barrel roll i just
i'm trying to see if i can avoid the
gunfire somehow
i need it to be straight alright
uh hey kiara yeah oh [\h__\h]
good keep shooting away sheriff
[Music]
oh my god all right beat him up maybe
oh that was my fault whoops i didn't i
thought it was actually really just up
to you guys and not
me i thought so too yeah i really am
actually driving your stage
where you're fighting so good luck
oh my god
don't forget don't forget your uh don't
forget your combos
don't
[Music]
okay i think we have to do this one more
time he's been in the fighting game
community for years
oh my god okay nice dodge oh my god
well done finish him
that that is the move that you called oh
that's so bad
[Music]
oh my god
oh
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] thanks cody dead
sweet moment they look into each other's
eyes thanks cody no problem mate
dead i love it
nice and balanced we don't need to go
too crazy on the controller
it's a nice balance you know although
okay doing well doing well
oh smooves move
it could just be that easy yeah
yeah definitely can we go up
[Music]
oh i think it's just a side to side
thing
is up
[Music]
i mean their leader is dead again
sorry um phoenix airlines still needs a
little bit of training
it would appear so our pilots are not
fully trained because we got a
belt from our papa that's holding us
back from flying properly
oh really i see ourselves yeah my belt
my papa belt oh that's cute
you would think so i'm mad
they're just i mean they're just looking
out for you you know
[Applause]
[Music]
oh yeah yeah yeah
oh okay okay okay all right now we're
speeding up we're speeding up
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh yeah yeah that was
close
[Music]
i am really getting a bug's life
flashbacks here it's kind of awesome
i'm getting dizzy now there we go
oh okay oh this is not correct
[Laughter]
ah it was not correct it's fine i don't
know where her room is either
i guess all right where where's our
daughter's room
[Music]
because i have no clue let's go right i
guess oh no
no okay well yeah
all right right let's go right okay okay
i wonder but maybe there is no wrong way
we just need to start
trying to not bonk against something oh
[\h__\h]
it's right here okay right here right
yeah wait no not
here okay yeah here yep yep
[Music]
okay smoove yes the house
up
[Music]
clara oh she's asking mom now
oh no look who i found
man
but at least she sees i'm obviously
sleeping yeah that's true
okay it was very confusing with dad
yeah yeah dad was just like not maybe
can
say it again yeah oh and all the other
space tweets you got from me
i'll play it as long as you want clara
for a long time
so cute
[Music]
she's got that british accent from me
yeah from from you takes after me
[Music]
do you like my british accent does it
turn your own
yeah i don't know but i don't know about
the last one that asked the ask the dead
beasts how
they feel how did the british
the british kfp employees
i'm the real brit in hell live english
yeah
amelia what one yeah
[Music]
god that is so adorable i can't take how
adorable it is here we come
daughter okay well
we made it last time i'm flying by the
seat of your pants
ah i get it real comedian you know that
hey
look comedie henry oh i'm missing
comedienne
she looks fine i mean she's playing like
nothing happened
my goodness she's upset she's sad
be careful we don't want to scare her
are you saying i'm too harsh with her
no no i meant she might get scared when
she sees us
look at us we've turned into a couple of
dolls remember of course i remember
wear her dolls oh my god do you see that
that frame lag
[Music]
oh no he spawned in like two frames
because his magic power was too much
you are ready wait is he trying to stop
us i think that he is
wait what if we can't make rose cry
we have to or we'll be smiling
or stay together for god's sake
we have a dog after all but does it save
now can we yep it's saving okay
cool we can finish then yeah this is
where we couldn't
yeah so this was very fun i had a great
time
oh well it was actually been three hours
three and a half hours wow
yeah wow that was a way longer time
that's one of the longer collabs that
we've done actually
yeah well next i will be on my channel
right
next time is on uh kiara's channel so
check it out guys
uh go over there for the part two yeah
we're gonna try to have it next week but
i'm not sure because i'm actually moving
next week so we're not sure but we'll
try
yeah we want to do it once a week but
we'll see we'll see
yeah it's uh and lots of fun good
therapy
yeah i would say so i mean we didn't
disagree
as as much as i thought we would but
that's probably a good thing i think
that's because i i feel like um
a way out kind of sealed our um
i guess cooperation abilities with each
other
um and rather it was just a lot of fun
so but who knows that could change in
the future when as the puzzles get more
difficult
so now we're going to do a great job
from now on today i'm sure
yeah it was a great thing
that's good i am so i'm gonna go take a
break and uh
stream among us in two hours yeah that
sounds good
i'm gonna i'm gonna drink some coffee
and go watch one of my favorite
youtubers play this game up until
the point where we are so okay yeah now
you don't you don't get spoiled anymore
exactly exactly all right
that being said i'm your more i hope
you'll remember me what
and in in kiara in australia they say
avid
thank you guys for watching see you guys
[Music]
bye
you