[Music]
so
good day good night
[Music]
good day mate hello everybody and
welcome
me and they are having a pretty
australian day today oh yeah you are
don't you have an australian day every
day
that's true oh wait wait wait
and that's true
yourself as a fake
[Music]
let's talk about this later
oh you guys did an australian quiz at
smash
yeah yeah we did the australian quiz
oh well me and hantam i would have
obviously gotten all questions right oh
my
do god think
no
no well well well well then today shall
be the battle where the real australians
will show themselves and proof
themselves uh
[Music]
is
please introduce yourself let's do left
to right or so bales you go first
it's me is baby
chaos from holy council what's up
what makes you australian bales
well i don't know may you just came back
from macca's grabbed a few burger
burgers yeah i'm ready to win mine all
right it sounds sucks to me but
we'll see about that mate
okay well then
well introduce yourself and tell me what
makes you australian
hello
[Music]
english council um i am the speaker of
space and
[Music]
what makes the australian this voice
yeah okay no doubt this voice
no doubt yeah i mean she might be faking
it but
this one
[Laughter]
sounds legit good argument but we still
need you to prove it properly
i think between us the most australian
is right next to me huh
[Music]
my head
i'm not sure australians eat eat
tarantulas i think that's just you well
that's what it's not an australian would
say because you're not
so you eat try this too huh so you eat
spiders and they're like yeah yeah i'm
in australia because i eat spiders
uh spiders while we sleep sometimes so
it might have happened
although i think i've heard that that's
just a
crap
that's just lies oh there's a lot of
baloney mate
sorry
uh okay uh and then uh
hello this is me i am of course
australian um as you can see uh with the
with the very australian
traditional outfit that i'm wearing
[Music]
up above
so today
even though there might be some
suspicious australians among us we will
prove who's the real australian with the
game of australian crikey mario party
let's go we were telling you before
[Applause]
we were telling her before it didn't
make sense
it makes sense
no it doesn't what it doesn't i realize
brilliant was going like what do you
mean because like because like crack
economy is like what the what the hell
yeah like wow like something like that
they're having a what the hell buddy
it's a positive word crikey crackers
positive word
very positive cried you mate right
going to the silo
to go to the other side of the world
australia
croaky
backroad the pipe yes the pot wow that's
very australian that's a very australian
animal yeah yeah i know
um do you know that australian easter
bunny you know what it's called
yeah yeah there's an australian easter
bunny that goes down um the hole like
that whoa
[Music]
is very fitting for you sana
i think
everybody ready
and yoshi very teddy
i have a feeling they're gonna
win
yoshi power too strong all right what do
we want to go for okay
oh
isn't this one really hard i hate this
spaceland i hate it i can write it
before but i remember um the other
members told me this map is quite hard
even though it says too difficult yeah
have you played this map
i never played anything oh
[Music]
okay
yeah i will accept it one last time we
will go to space australia okay
so
according uh
i don't know i've been told that or from
experience the timing is kind of wrong
so this time it's kind of long
15 turns it's quite good
time okay 45 minutes it's like um they
must have sped up time like they must
have time travelling towers also in
granny that's fine that's nice okay the
rest seems fine um
pick up my game pack all types yeah
let's go let's go
wow
let's go to the land down
under oh two princesses and two dinos
yoshi's a dinosaur right
this is it we made it to space
[Music]
oh god that bowser i already have
ah
i'm scared
he'll destroy me uh
superstar vanquished an evil king and
restored peace to the galaxy
well
[Music]
like the laser coming out of his mouth i
kind of want one um
i'm sorry
no
we're not going there all right
uh okay okay bye bye koopa troopa
toast and challenge let's
[Music]
[Applause]
uh no not the first time i don't bow
down
crap i wish i was first in monopoly
though that's where it really matters
[Laughter]
[Music]
would be first and that would be last
right
oh that makes sense
oh okay where is that it looks like very
far away it probably is very far away
[Music]
okay
okay where where are you even believe in
this
with this map i feel like i always got
pushed away from the bowser and i never
got to the top
no no maybe one or two times though
my turn let's go daisy
okay
starting
daisu for a red
that's
not too bad
mm-hmm i always say dices but then i
need to remember it's not dices let's
die right it's that
dices is like um
dai says is like cutting something up
maybe oh
[Music]
no what is it like nice thing
she dices something you know
lucky
[Music]
[Laughter]
yes this is how you use kraki
yeah yes
you're you're passing us in australia
and i think
oh so far
[Music]
oh yeah maybe i'm always so bad at
don'ts
get something good oh i gotta
[Music]
not bad not bad oh
my god
[Music]
that's why i hate
oh man okay well then we're monkey
raceway hatchiman's low number it
doesn't matter anymore she brought us
all to him fine reset already
little horse lr
are you alternating lr
[Music]
are you pushing the right buttons not
the big ones the small ones
a small one oh
[Music]
okay i was just i was just waiting you
know for two
but this is crazy
[Music]
oh
what's going on here
[Music]
uh
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
okay if you're ready then
press the plus or minus
i'm ready
[Music]
maybe we can give sana a head start
no no every time i feel like there's a
rhythm and i don't change the rhythm it
doesn't
i'm not changing my rhythm at all oh no
yeah it might be
something might be possible it's either
my controller or
i'm sorry just just do it just do it
okay then you're gonna do it right let's
go
yeah all right
okay okay you're gonna rock in the other
games i'm sure
[Music]
nice going to sleep
i'm just waiting for you now i guess
okay maybe if you're a real australian
little experienced australian pig
[Applause]
no no no no no no
there's no such thing as
[Music]
okay
yeah oh i have a good feeling today oh
my god i can't believe it okay can you
believe it oh it's going good ah don't
change it don't jinx it
it's going good because that is
controller bro
no even without that i would have won
that it's freaked kiara you did
something didn't you no no no
no no no
[Music]
patrol will chase down speeders with
just five coins um
[Music]
i guess
what do you mean speeding
what does that mean
anyway
i lost no money with that noise
okay um let's just go let's just roll
yeah yeah let's roll no oh
oh
[Music]
get a good one
okay okay
give me the best one oh where's that
ghost spell that's cute
okay i feel like oh
[Music]
oh
it's gold and sparkly it has a bow on it
must be good
yeah skeleton key open the gate
useful
that's going to be useful later
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
yes
[Music]
um
oh
[Music]
oh my god
well there it goes there goes all my
chances
it's like a game show
[Music]
it's like hatchimals are just here to
create chaos
yes
i wouldn't hurt anything
i don't know i'm sweet
um i'm sweet and fluffy like bread i
wouldn't hurt anything
not even using largo can you just move
this uh like i don't
what what even what is straight yeah
i don't know you just need to shoot i
guess
move and shoot yeah
time to get a new controller mate bloody
helmet
actually just control it like um if for
some reason
it just vibrated
for a week no it just wouldn't turn off
oh is that all done
okay let's go let's go
sound like you survived until the end i
think you're gonna be fine
[Music]
oh
yes
[Applause]
[Music]
the thing is the star is right behind me
but i can't go that way
that's okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
i thought you guys are teaming up but
you're just sabotaging each other
[Music]
oh
will be given to you
okay
but it's on the line okay oh how many
coins do we know you know we should just
put all of them in oh lead is it random
oh it's red it's random oh okay oh wow i
was kind of jewish 15 some of you guys
don't even have 15 coins
zero
coins
[Music]
oh
yeah okay well i don't think we need to
practice this really
i can't count in this situation
let's cry let's try okay okay
one two three four five six seven
oh
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
just got a copy twice homework what
happened
one
more night what happens
everybody just gets their money back
oh my god everybody gets 12 plus one
okay
[Laughter]
well i guess hatsuma has more money than
before now
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh
okay good good good good okay
[Music]
faster faster faster faster
oh
[Music]
well you've never been in one route i
wonder what it takes you to
yeah that's that looks like a safer
route than the other one
[Music]
oh
i think she deserves a star now
i see i see countdown uh-huh
[Music]
unless you're in space and then you're
just gonna go up and up and up and up
[Music]
oh
oh i see i see
[Applause]
i already hate this bloody helmet i hate
this so much
who's doing good is there anyone who's
doing good
no [\h__\h] hell helmet
okay
let's go
oh no i like the window to move and jump
is like so little yeah
okay jumping let's go
let's
go
help help
okay okay
no why is it so hard
i got 24 meters
[Music]
and that's good all right let's go give
me a good one
mama mama
let's go
we're getting closer oh the countdown
[Music]
oh red a red one that's okay i'll take
it i'll land on the red thing but that's
okay
[Music]
i like taking these steps oh oh wait
that's pretty good again this ghost is
so busy oh
go random oh wait beast has a lot of
coins they're 45.
one month
[Music]
this is your chance
are you are you going
you will keep you'll keep that thing a
secret right yes
that thing okay you won me open
[Music]
she's already dead
so much has been lost
so sad friendships are friendships are
okay so far right tonight
[Music]
um
and that might be good maybe in some
cases that might be good that's true
that's true
um
oh wait do i have to do it alone then
push pump pull pump up
oh wait huh
what what wait um get it oh like this do
you have this oh you
oh
[Music]
it doesn't make sense because like
because like in the mario world it's
like bouncer is a bad guy so what the
violin is
don't see him
okay okay
let's go
[Music]
puppet
okay i'm trying this
[Music]
what's this
oh
[Music]
okay
you know normally when i play any of
these kind of games like like mario
party or monopoly on my channel i always
lose even though it's my channel
[Laughter]
mama
aim for the shoe hello
oh [\h__\h]
oh no
uh-huh
yeah yeah
didn't want anything anyway it would
make the game too easy but i see i see
yeah let's use an item
um
is this custom ice block but how do you
do the map again
what um
i know chat i know
no arms i know
i'm wrestling straight
wow oh
oh what a surprise it
[Music]
is in like constant when it goes to zero
right
yeah i think so
but then i think only people if you're
at the top of the map are you still
affected i think only if you're like in
the middle
maybe that's what you got bae
that's what you [\h__\h] get baby
[Laughter]
[Music]
how do you feel about
using your australian part of your mouth
oh oh
i'm good
i believe you're an australian party
mouth
you're having
[Music]
no problem
take all your needs fruity free coins
okay
[Music]
oh there's one all right
let the change we're gonna get it as
quick as possible
okay
oh i see i see i see okay
yeah but then like um
sometimes it runs yeah
so that perception is quite hard
[Applause]
let's go
[Music]
duckles
come on come on little boys
[Music]
[Applause]
give me the money
[Laughter]
thank you
yeah
okay
we just need to make it really blue
oh they look so cute in those colors i
like it they should keep it
i'm gonna mix it kind of makes it look
like icing
hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi
hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi hi
hi hi hi hi nice to meet you nice to
meet you
she's the other characters
[Music]
oh
i can't really do anything here anyway
that's just automatically
oh
[Music]
are not looking very australian to me
sauce just won a game together and
you're still wishing bad things right
why
one
one one one
[Music]
you don't wish bad things about you wow
what lady kiwawa please
i'll get this door duncan yeah nobody
steal that from me nobody nobody
it's illegal
next time
[Music]
i feel like bowser is going to visit us
soon no no
just don't don't go to the middle
platform
ah okay oh shortcut shortcuts
maybe
not really not really because i can't go
backwards again you'll push back right
yeah let's go
so unlucky what the hell
why are you
sanana
[Music]
going further away uh-oh
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
so what are you oh to do
okay
you're trying to cream
i hope you like coconuts sana
i don't like coconuts i do not like them
either i like it
round pal let's go
let's go
oh [\h__\h] i can't do this
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah you like coconuts i i don't like
pickles
i'm not really hoping for that but
everybody's fall away i think
unless
can she go straight to it or does she
have to go over patrol
oh yeah jesus meet us with just five
coins chase them it's cheap but will he
also chase me down like i wonder
i think they'll stop that's what i don't
know hmm
ah i see now if i had a a key that would
be nice
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
that's okay i see my my pockets
something that's gonna be possibly
received
[Music]
come on be nice to me please oh
ah that direction uh but then down oh
wait
this is dangerous because everyone's
going to
um
[Music]
all the way to the left i think so i
think you would still be close to the
star even if he pushes you all the way
to the back
probably
[Music]
thank you
and decide on how many toys do we hold
[Music]
how many how many you want
how many one
seven
yes four times seven
[Music]
hmm
honestly i just mess around with this
randomly
i never know
like is there is there really like a
system with this
can you ever i think
it's like you're
i think
okay
it's just so fast i know it's timing but
it's so fast it's like what yeah and
then the others turn two and you have to
get their backs
no
are you aiming for me bills
no no yep
[Music]
[Laughter]
i got two hits from bay i will never
forget that
okay babe this is uh
take her down
[Music]
thank you very much thank you thank you
very much
[Music]
[Applause]
because when you leave this spot now
aha okay
i go this way yeah okay
[Music]
oh
ah
31 points
oh he's all it's coming up
[Music]
[Laughter]
that's pretty cool
well yeah that would have been nice
those mini games i always suck at them
guess i'm not the only one
[Music]
winner got this we got this
let's get one with explosions
oh
[Music]
yeah okay
right
left okay right
okay
[Music]
oh
hi
[Music]
hey
um
[Music]
28 to the okay
i can't do anything anyway okay
okay let's go
oh you guys gonna get yourself something
in the situation
you have a key you at least have a key
that's the truth you guys have created a
bank to deposit your coins
should go it's safer to deposit them
don't carry around so much cash bails
no yeah
no one but myself
[Music]
i can't believe how unlucky i am in
every single mario party
just this time
oh my god
how many
[\h__\h] hurts mate bloody help me
[Music]
[Laughter]
if you're real australians then teach me
the real australians and how to make
some
some australian please
okay oh
a [\h__\h] [\h__\h] is too much for me
i rather just say bloody
[Music]
oh
rotate rotate
rotate rotate rotate
[Music]
before he pushes you only to help you
now wow
no change moving up let's go
for me again
big win
okay
25 to the star i'm not getting there
anytime soon
what oh yeah
lucky
[Music]
okay what does this take me
hey you're pretty close
oh
ow
i'm sorry but i must last deposit three
times but i don't have no coins right
now to buy a star anyway
oh if a miracle happens
yeah look at his face
now you could buy one if you get to it
first
you could
oh
yes i also have noticed you only wish me
to roll one nobody else you wish that
for
what's what that what's up with that
nothing you only wish that uh
me to roll one
the other ones you don't wish it for
what's up what's up what's up with that
bae bro hi
lucky it just it was just timing
[Music]
it was just time
what what what oh too bad
oh no again
oh my god
[Music]
ah
puzzle game
what's up mario best buddy
oh texas
[Music]
can you make it go down
uh you go up quick drop get up it down
and i instant a quick and instant oh
yeah yeah yeah
ah
that [\h__\h]
uh crocky mate all right
let's go
i see
oh
oh oh whoa
[Music]
i literally haven't pressed any buttons
and i got 31
hats and we're gonna win this one
yeah i'm gonna win you're gonna win
okay
we're gonna use our brain wait so fast
come on come on come on come on come on
come on now
i press the wrong button
[Music]
nice
okay okay okay squish this down
[Music]
push harder
the controls man
okay
oh
yep
[Music]
oh
keep forgetting
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
[Music]
okay we have we have five rounds left
guys five rounds
[Music]
why is that nothing
oh
because you can't go straight to the
star from here you gotta go around it
would you expect me to get this done
next turn that's the thing
true true so you might as well just go
somewhere else
where is it we're a team fan i'm rooting
for your
you're like our team your winter
from smash team you know this this is
how this is how we you always get the
one roll
can we hear some like experience about
smash from you guys how was it you just
came from smash like directly
what's up
how was it no
no we did like like an australian panel
oh um i don't know how much we can talk
about the panel but it was a lot of fun
i think you can talk about the way you
can talk you can talk about it yeah okay
um
basically the bike reading is
hoodoo
[Music]
is that an australian thing
apparently it is we don't know it uh no
it's heroes
it was like we did a quiz we did an
australian quiz and then um
yeah apparently uhuru means goodbye
oh
it sounds like an owl
it's like an elk
[Music]
your brains are small it was at a
conclusion or what
it was like the queen's the chris is
like um the questions are kind of
left field
oh you can even push yourself there
bales be careful
oh
[Music]
wow she's so close to the stars she
needs the coins
there's gonna be a game there's gonna be
a game maybe you can get coins there
[Music]
it wasn't me it was chant
can you get 18 coins from a mini game it
must be a coin game then i suppose
because i don't think you can get so
many from winning a
coin a normal game
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
i think i fall in love
[Music]
like
weird
whoosh
whatever
get the
[Music]
the princesses are gonna win
go princess team go princess
five turns left
we're down to the last five times let's
look at the current standings
[Music]
please stop jinxing me thank you you're
so close nothing can go wrong now
okay so really
prediction ah these predictors are
always [\h__\h]
nami
oh
what mom
oh that would be nice he has not much
faith in me that's so much pressure that
would be nice no
you heard that right come
on get like a buff now don't you
yeah
oh we're gonna save my parents
of course if you help her there's of
course the chance is higher that she
will win obviously
[Music]
um
oh
but you know
start the star will be gone soon so
where should i go
um
[Music]
you got a one and one and six one in
three channels i'm gonna see what uh
what i wanna land on
down that would be nice for an item here
i'm going to go down
i i would have to go down anyway i guess
okay go go
one it's gonna come again soon wait a
minute is it is it going to land on me
once i get the star
if i don't know
maybe but nobody's nobody's going to
step on there before you
thank you
okay pop the balloon
i don't i didn't want that one i wanted
the dice the dye
i know
should i use it no you don't need
anything
i guess
oh now you just need to run
okay oh but wait you will you will pass
the middle which means welcome
before the past like wrong that's right
okay okay okay right
i think you should yeah you go somewhere
else then no one no one will be in the
middle room
[Music]
finally the second star
nice
nice can we reach another one in the
last four rounds
come on come on where you going where
you going where are you going where are
you going
come on
wait a second wait a second
i can just go around the corner
i don't have tiny coins
if you just go around the corner without
passing it now you have too many too
many
oh you can't just stop right in front of
it right oh down yeah
[Music]
okay if i'm passing it then i might as
well get that this way
okay
maybe you'll reach it soon enough again
no sign of life percent he remembered
he's mad he's mad
okay
i guess we'll do a circle around
[Music]
let's go 12.
whales is close but uh
not much luck with the dice
guys over all according to kay kaku
ah let's see if you can do better
you probably will
[Music]
okay i see how it is oh
pretty good really good
oh the golden there was a golden tube
that you have got would have been
not in austria not that i would know
anything about austria because i'm from
australia but in austria the like a very
polite greeting is giving each other
like kisses on the cheek
how about in australia of course i know
i'm just asking to check that you guys
are australian
oh what's the great thing
um
a good
giving someone a beer sorry hi
now what's a normal greeting a beer
you understand what that means you're
right
yes you're right yes you know what right
means yes mate
this is right
yes
i'm right i'm right whoa i'm all right
yeah yeah yeah
wait
[Applause]
[Laughter]
what if it's a child still give it a
beer
[Music]
minigame
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
ah
wait i i thought it was a okay
ah big flaps big flops big flap big flap
[Music]
flap
i can do that well
[Music]
sorry oh
i'm losing the rhythm
[Music]
okay we can
keep flipping keep flipping
yeah
[Music]
oh
that's a fun game though
that is a fun game
wow okay
[Music]
i have an item
okay
17 oh man
okay good start good start not bad not
bad now i wonder who's closest
okay goodbye 69 it was nice seeing you
[Music]
good number
good number good number
oh are you getting the money no you have
to give you have to keep
got a key to the door
no
you can get the item game on the right
okay let's do it
and maybe those will turn things around
if you get a golden tube i'm gonna mold
or more or both
oh
focus
okay although it would be pretty nice if
sana wins it would just be lame you know
perfect yeah
santa needs the
win yeah
yeah this is a happy ending what are you
going for
attack
me yeah
what no
[Music]
i would go for that too
then maybe i can get the stall
maybe
if i get there first also if you if you
just roll one one one then you're still
too far
but the thing is you'll be you'll be
rolling one-on-one
right
oh back what about veils oh she's 10 10
away from the star
so close two
of you
yep
all right
she's getting the star
okay
[Music]
just don't go the wrong way bales
play dice
nicer
can you come back
listen monopoly you could come back i
don't know about mario party
do you know chad
come try to come and come
it's okay it saves the game
ah i think should i
join yes you can
let's wait a little bit
i'm waiting i'm waiting
um
veils
take it i'm just waiting oh she said i
need feedback
i need food
i need full audience to be here before i
buy it
where are you
well
we're looking at you i'll
[Music]
next one
left oh
[Music]
oh you can buy it
uh it probably has the golden pipe now
[Music]
i'm going to mold
goddammit
she's gotta get the second star
morbing wait him can hanzo come back
oh
[Music]
okay it's not akahato it's hachiman
oh no i hate this one
is there a wrong and the right path or
is it just a shorter and a longer
oh my god yes
okay ready okay it's better to go you
could you could eat
everyone get a star
nah huh yes
oh
[Music]
balance is zero
where should i go
i like the music it's so godly
[Music]
makeup
i don't know what you're talking about
the golden tube tool
what if what if you do it like it right
at the end just to uh seal the coffin
nail in the coffin one
[Laughter]
[Music]
i need some money at least
not the australian one oh wait sorry
they still want me to okay
oh i decided oh for you okay yeah
oh three coins are collected the winner
will take it off
i hope it's a game with with eleanor
[Laughter]
come on l our game
oh no it's a german game
[Music]
um
shall we go
the timing on this is weird
it's because some sway differently
okay
[Music]
thank you
yeah you are oh
no i got it i got
it whoa
i got it i got it
oh this one's
good
this is so cold oh my god [\h__\h]
it's so close
[Laughter]
what the [\h__\h] mate
we were so insane the whole time but
that last jump is like what the [\h__\h]
that was so close oh man
[Music]
ah yeah this is this is when you say
crikey
cry
crappy mate bloody hell mate
oh oh for me
where's the golden wheel man
no way
i'm not gonna get no i knew it
no one
i didn't know it would stop that fast i
thought it would go longer like
[Music]
let's go
but it stopped so fast after pushing the
button
or should i go there should i use my
hand
blimey
that's a blimey
where there's no blind man that's a
blind baby
should i use it okay let's see how far i
can get her
oh please if you don't get
eight with these with these dice i don't
know what to tell you
oh come on come on
[Music]
star and then bay gets another one with
the golden tube which means on three
one two three
one two
ah three well you should tell you should
tell you
oh cause you can only go ah okay okay
yeah but uh you you're fine
no oh yeah oh no go go to the other side
don't unlock
because otherwise you'll go that way
yeah
even the gate lock for now
yeah yeah
what's in the skeleton placer
you'll never know oh no it's just you
unlock the other part that's it
ah that's it
boring
yeah
sometimes sometimes that's that makes
you uh that gives you a shortcut to the
star so sometimes
[Music]
let's go
another one coming too
[Music]
um
47 16 21 okay let's go
ah
yeah
but i'm on that path too
i think you need to land on the other
one
[Music]
you have to land on the other one
where you go
going left i guess
that's really
[Music]
please please please please please
please please please please
i just need one more to earn all the
hearts
three one one two one one two three one
two
[Music]
at least i i had the feeling of winning
for a while
yeah
you don't need to win in the end
the fake australians are first and
second we gotta
[Music]
it that star is quite close to where
places
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
it's fine
wait she doesn't have okay
[Music]
i don't have money though oh
currently
strategically missing one no
wow
well at least uh hata might get an extra
star for having the most coins
maybe um
[Music]
i have
no money now
[Music]
but if somebody like everyone else drops
it early it's not like i can get that
much more
but the golden boom
golden goombang
[Music]
that one was never gonna come over here
anyway so how does it look lucky
one
wow
oh okay
[Music]
i was thinking yeah that looks good even
without a golden one yeah okay
[Music]
could turn things around if i land on a
ghost block in a ghost ghost field and
still
still a star
oh in theory but there's only one ghost
field right
so that would be very far
i shouldn't have bought that pipe guys
no
oh almost stepped on it oh my god
oh wait wait one two three i could i
could land on the bowser i don't have
any items do i no
oh god
i i just oh no oh no oh
[Music]
oh oh oh you almost stand on the bowser
field so close
[Music]
wow dangerous danger zone
you can get something good here ah no
pipe
no pipe disney
[Music]
yeah you jumped when it was pretty high
yeah these games are so unpredictable
magical
much
[Music]
she doesn't need any moist dyes
oh no you're going pretty far oh
hi there oh
australians titty
karma i know but it's okay i'm still
is
[Music]
you didn't realize
oh
[Music]
in my heart you are a winner
start
[Laughter]
[Music]
hello
so quiet everybody's so focused
we're strong
let's go
oh my god i still don't have enough
money this is crazy
i shouldn't have bought it i shouldn't
have bought it greatly empowered
oh [\h__\h]
really
lesson learned
well i don't wanna
land on
on the route route of bowser but there's
nothing really interesting to land on
[Music]
i guess oops i'll go here
that should be safe zido is anyone here
is anyone in the in the line i don't
remember i don't remember
okay
[Laughter]
sorry i'm laughing
not for sanana
i feel sorry for you
[Laughter]
i think she's been playing a different
game
she was maybe watching and thought she
was doing it um
i'm watching but npc chama is strong
but why npc
didn't buy the freaking items into item
shop
because it's mpc stupid nbc
strong in mini games but
in the whole other game
i'm gonna use this i guess
we got split into different games
maybe interesting
npc let's go abby
she's here in spain
right in front of it mate
oh but i didn't have any money either
that's fine
that hurts oh
oh man oh
man this is why i don't like this
this bat map
it's so annoying you know still moving
your back um
i might as well just use one
just look at the lows take a look
at it just take a look at it let's take
a look at it no i start you got there
mate
yeah
it's fine
it's not like a hurts at night
but you both have two two stars and zero
coins this is uh really the face is
going to get some coins off to this
right yeah but it's still a mini game
i hate you oh
i thought you were going to get the
money
oh
yes
again
what is it this time
you can look at it again
look at
[Music]
i didn't get it yeah okay so you mash a
to paddle and then i'll steer
okay so i'll oh oh mash and then you
steal we both have to match yeah yeah
because then that makes it go faster
yeah yeah yeah and you're the one
staring okay
wait what
i'm not scary now
oh okay i'm am i staring what you're
steering let's go
okay we got this okay actually npc
jammer not so bad in minigames
[Music]
oh that's a lot of money man
thank you
so
much on
give me the coins
drop the coins
[Music]
i can't tell who
and you guys won i saw the coins
in general oh yeah
that's goodness sightseeing bonus
lightning bonus intrepid
[Music]
nobody went on the bowser space
unfortunately
no one
no one went on it oh do you mean the
middle one yeah no no nobody
[Music]
okay
what does that mean i wonder
you are the australian
thank you very much
thank you very much thank you very much
thank you
they have a picture of this from last
time where i was
busted by bowser
oh
oh yeah a lot of spaceships got you
that was an amazing effort sana is also
australian i would say because she got
second
thank you i don't know how to feel about
that from coming from you
yeah
ladies and gentlemen that's that is how
you play dice
oh
i suppose so wait can you press a no
oh sorry yes i can place a you collected
more chords than anyone else
goes to me but
i'm i'm still australian totally um
but it wins it yeah
for most of the game so i'm quite happy
yeah better than usual and the mini
games yeah it looks like i won more mini
games than anyone else
dare you guys
um
[Music]
you're helping the banks make money
investing
yay
final results
well that's the most corns in the end
she should have gotten a star too 2
that's true
that's next seven point that's like
seven stars
huh
yeah true oh man well me and hakuma with
all that money we're gonna go travel to
to some secluded secret island now
let's
yeah go about you come to a little
island called
australia
already in australia i don't know what
you mean
already damn
i'm waving at you from my window right
there
[Music]
[Laughter]
is
[Music]
but i'm glad we finally got together and
uh at the last opportunity the
australian group whole live australia
mate
that's us
australia man australia
hello
[Music]
is
well i won so it's great
i am one true aussie man
also how do you like the the quokka that
i put on your head
uh it's a bit heavy compared to mr
squeaks but
are you gonna adopt it you should adopt
it nobody's gonna notice nobody didn't
know this right chad did you know
did you know i think i saw people
calling it a wombat it's a it's a love
hat
i can't even take a wombata clocker that
that person is not australian they
should be kicked out yeah
yeah
you say you noticed a chat i don't
believe it huh oh well congratulations
bails well what about you
[Music]
oh it was fun i'm so happy we could
finally play a game all together
yeah
before
you're so busy with all those collabs
but you still made time for everybody
thank you so much
this is what i make time for also are
those those sensations the other two
have australian animals on their heads
i'm assuming that those on your your
your twin tail balls are also australian
i guess yes this is holy slug it can
kill and this isn't um
a crab it can kill
i recognize them because i'm from
australia
yeah yeah
yes i know
you were actually uh not doing someone
in the beginning but look at the
comeback noise noise sasuke i don't know
what's happening
universe has no idea what it's doing
yeah oh it happens this is mario party
for you
yeah so i hope you guys enjoyed this uh
mario party even with one round gets
really really long so this is the one
game that we're playing today uh i'll
see you guys later i have another stream
with a secret surprise so check it out
and the other members channels that's
participated today are in the
description if you want to check him out
check him check it mate
and oh if you're in australia like us
obviously tomorrow is another day of
smash so the two girls
will be there again right
yeah yeah
yeah
for the rest before then
get some rest yeah
tomorrow yeah tomorrow
night tomorrow enjoy tomorrow everybody
[Music]
you're an an australian we say huru
um
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
oh i made chat in in the game that
hatchimal played santa was the winner
just telling you
[Music]
i would like to report that hajima lost
in the other game as well that she was
playing
[Music]
you