first
album point of
view
pineapple 2 2 three it tastes so so so
sweet when you the around kiss me I'm
taking a perfect
picture you're stuck to me like
ack you
got love
[Music]
Rush never let
go you're in my heart you'll always stay
right here won't fade
away the great
Wanderer
[Applause]
I I'm walking by the Liv FL before my
eyes the silence still I'm reaching out
to you Conn sacrifice
life so
I
retrospective calls me to Tru and every
part of my being
that's the best feeling tell me what am
I to
you sleep
[Music]
talking you got me oh baby don't you
know got
me I'm brething you and I just foret but
you got me stressed just baby that's
what
you
[Music]
for I will to keep oning till
the heart
Challenger
[Music]
Sparks life is only what you make it
you're going to be
okay so go ahead and do it do it
youbody favor
[Music]
night move my through something new I
don't need no drinks tonight give me
that do
you if you know play that
game know I can fight the feeling and I
want love hate all the same if you know
play that game maybe you decide if you
me shout it out right
[Music]
now
K
[Music]
ah okay loud very
loud in my ear
[Music]
okay
hello I am here on this
joyful
Nicolas day is the day I think I think
it is right the 6th of December
is uh uh a day where a fin fake uh Santa
Claus makes his way around
towns
in probably most of European
cities yeah yeah yeah and he is
being um
paraded by or joined by an evil
evil gremlin on his
side he gives is extra presents I don't
really know if you can say it's extra
presents
because I think he just gives you
nuts and T maybe tangerines I don't know
um not
really present no
what and if yeah if you're not so good I
don't know then you get whipped by the
gremlin I don't know maybe I don't
really remember so well haven't seen him
in a
while
mhm my throat is a little bit oh tired
already it seems I haven't had tea today
it's okay though I I aired today also
look I've been in a
crazy
cleaning
uh craze
ha yeah I cleaned out I I cleaned my
kitchen again I wagon cleaned my
apartment I contined to clean all the MF
infested coats and scarves and uh
cleaned even more and more and more and
the threw away the trash and I flattened
the the
dumb and this and that and I aired out
the apartment so that's a bit it's a bit
cold but fresh air y yum cardboard yeah
daily chores no they're for me they're
maybe once every two weeks
chores but like no like I'm pretty
pretty much doing um New Year's cleaning
early
on meow yes I'm a cat waah wow w wow
kitty
cat H shout out to the Hat why what
nobody cares we don't need a shout out
to my hat [\h__\h] my
hat what is your favorite hairstyle from
the ones I already
have M my kimon twin Tails I love them
so much even though I can barely use
them and I'm digging this shorter one a
lot
too I do love I do love my default hair
a
lot um but it only exists in a default
outfit so that's also um
yeah yeah well anyway so this is a fan
game and Holo parades that you can get
on Steam this one is actually not free
but it's pretty cheap but it's part of
this new
program uh of that cover I don't know
what exactly I don't know how to
describe it but now there's like if you
bring out a fan game you can do so in
cooperation with cover I guess you could
say uh I don't really know the details
of what that entails but uh it seems to
be a positive thing because you are with
that for the first time ever allowed to
indeed take money for your fan game
which before you weren't allowed
to but you need permission and you need
everything confirmed and all that by by
cover you know but that's not bad like
you know yeah now you can make profits
from the hard work you put into creating
a fan game yeah yeah yeah just don't
don't charge 60 bucks for it okay don't
charge 60 bucks for a game we don't we
don't need any more of
[Music]
that H yeah so we're going to have fun
with this I I have only seen a few clips
of the
game night I don't really know much
about it so let's get into
it SE 70 is the new 60 no [\h__\h]
way
what
no are they already selling games for 70
bucks no
[Music]
way oh my
God and welcome to Holo parade please
enter your player
name
Ki KI I like this font oh I like all the
fonts very futuristic at the top oh oh
there's a voice over
by a world without
[Music]
Idols oh she's so
emotional
what the [\h__\h] why what
[Music]
happened oh
man why you why why you got to do this
now in the
[Music]
beginning
I don't want to start from the beginning
[Music]
again no I hate
that
[Music]
I feel like I feel like they said the
same thing three
times this is a world without Idols
let's do it start from the beginning
let's start from zero the world is
without Idols but let's just do it come
on let's start from the beginning yeah
we start now again without Idols in a
world without
idols
H nice to meet you a it I know her
personally I I met her in person several
times you know are you jealous weird
flex but
okay hey hey hey oh I love this music oh
my God it has this uh Picola vibe that I
uh I found a my own bgm ages ago that
resembled that I something about this
kind of bgm I don't know what it is
about it but you just want to listen to
it endlessly especially while playing
Minecraft no it's not hers but it has
like very
similar uh
instrumentals nice to meet you I'm
friend a a staff member I'm really happy
to have been chosen as as a founding
member of whole life's parade division
o I'm hak NOA also staff member I'm also
looking forward to the
parade let's work together to grow Holo
parade into a great parade troop and
increase the number of whole life
fans together we've conducted all
research necessary to uh to so that we
can support you to the best of our
ability this is whole life's office this
is where you can prepare for the parade
such as forming troops and scouting
talents it's a peaceful and fun place
where many people visit on the whim as a
start let's go to the parade oh already
okay parade par par
[Music]
par I love that song so much it is such
a b and so
emotional
too I want to listen to it now
ah ah so good right hey hey he hey let's
go begin the hold the parade completion
rewards we get a
PO not hold there's 11 stages 11
trophies okay let's go
prologue cleared okay uh tutorial number
one let's
go oh oh oh we play itan and she's
fighting against a wall so wall versus
wall let me explain briefly about the
parade I believe you're watching the
side through a stream right
now I I are you guys I'll first explain
how you can command the parade
remotely at the bottom of the screen
icons of the parade team are lined up
mhm the parade formation okay
interesting place for an office E I feel
like that would be really refreshing to
work outside yeah when you press the
talent icon the talent will be summoned
from our base and will March towards the
left side of the screen okay okay yeah
I've seen i' I've played a game like
that before I think as you can see
there's a wall at the other end that is
the people's mental wall against the
virtual
world okay okay so everybody who hates
like YouTubers and all that has a wall
like that and we want to break it down H
Parade's role is to gradually break down
that wall and improve the public opinion
of the virtual world
[Music]
oh kind very deep the parade is a
success that we can bring down the
barriers by having the talent parade
around while promoting a alive next I'll
talk about motivation
oh to summon a talent you need enough
motivation oh that's like the the cost
of every body at the top right of the
screen this is gradually accumulated
over time the required motivation can be
checked from the number one H number on
the top right of the talent icon in
addition you can activate support cards
from the bottom left of the screen
giving you various helpful effects okay
I like these ones okay these can be used
only once during a certain period of
time but will not consume motivation
about camera controls you can scroll
horizontally by dragging the mouse or
using the left and right arrow keys the
screen can be Zoomed In and Out using
the mouse wheel or the up and down arrow
keys might be faster if you have a try
let's go into the paride field super
refresh once you have enough of
motivation in the top right yeah yeah
yeah yeah I get it I get it yeah okay
okay okay this is all you need to start
okay let's go start the
parade okay and no Sagi we start with a
no Sagi and they attack automatically or
what oh [\h__\h] maybe I should have
summoned the other thing let's go
what what the [\h__\h] is this
stalker what is he doing there
on little cat in the
back M M M it already feels Overkill but
I guess let's let's uh save for the
flare B the L
friend
yeah maybe another
one maybe never oh wait what what is
this the support card what does that do
ah a it's just like an attack that
doesn't come with a a character okay oh
maybe another one another one another
one oh that's it okay this music is way
over the top ah yeah I wonder if they'll
play this all the
time ah scouting digs ah I wonder if I
can today get myself because I don't
know do I even have any scouting tickets
from the beginning or can I choose one
character like it would be nice to have
one choice like one free choice of a
character at least per account start
would be
nice Ki is my strongest unit oh takes a
while until he summoned me
what I had to pity pull you what I don't
want your
pity you have to play a while to get Mo
what the hell no okay we'll see if we
can get get there that was a good parade
I was watching you on stream the viewers
were all really excited I can't believe
this was your first time you must be
naturally talented let's proceed to the
next level for the parade menu okay yeah
I get it yeah thank you number
two tutorial
two we spoiled by H having my one of
GetGo for real for real
yeah
but you know like for for other I don't
know like a a certain g game that I have
experienced I think uh when you start
your
account in I feel like there was like uh
I mean from a
certain roster ro roster you were able
to
choose uh one of one of the more nicer
characters I think isn't that a thing in
a lot of g games yeah like a star
selector I don't know this time we'll
teach you some useful tips for a
successful parade uh first up we'll
learn about attacking the attacking
range as well as front rear units listen
up as the section is very important the
attacking distance differs depending on
the talent each Talent will move
automatically until they are in range to
attack the
enemies talents with a short range
attack will approach uh closer to the
enemies thus becoming tanks to Shield
allies from enemy attacks for an example
Knight M mhm I thought so this thing
looked like a knight Knights uh have
very short range attack and will
approach very close to the enemies enemy
attacks will hit Knight and will not
reach allies that are located behind it
the so cute Knight is very weak as an
attacker but with high health and low
cost it becomes a valuable Shield to
guard rear allies let's now look at ALR
elfr has a long range attack so it can
attack from a far distance although it
has a high attack power it's low HP
makes it very vulnerable you should
summon it along with Knight so you can
attack safely from the RAR
rear R exy let's try summoning Knight
along with the other talents wait so
wait just
realized n senpai's fandom is called
Knight that's that's such such a simple
name I just realized like there's no
Sagi there's alred and then there's
Knight oh it's just translated it was
kishidan right I I knew that it was
something weird about that cuz I don't
remember oh then they should maybe they
shouldn't have translated kishidan
tonight oh well I'm sure you will
understand the importance of kishidan as
a tank
not
okay so
we save up a little bit well how much
can we there we
go afford to
wait push back push back oh wait we were
saving for alri no
there isn't this basically the same
scenario I'm just like I also summoned
all of this before but I guess now
they're
explaining the importance but this is
same same kind of same
scenario oh my God my tank died wao wo W
wo okay if pleas not present in this
game only C is
oh oh I want to see some
chickens that's okay Ki is fine
too okay y we to
[Music]
how did it go were you able to feel the
importance of the front and rear talents
some extra advice attacks that Target
single enemies will hit the closest
opponents be careful when facing talents
with area attacks as their attacks could
reach rear allies as well as the front
line area attacks are powerful so make
sure to form them into your parade if
you obtain them for
Scouts next I will explain about forming
the parade Squad and upgrading talents
first let's go to the parade formation
screen this can be open for the botom
menu
okay oh on the screen you can select
which talents to take along your parade
currently we don't have a wide variety
of talents to choose from so make sure
to form up any new talents you obtain
the same goes for support cards you can
press the talent icon to display more
details on the bottom right of the
screen let me show
you uhhuh now weak but can be summoned
in large numbers M from here you can
check the skills and stats in order blah
blah blah now on to upgrading the
talents oh first off press the upgrade
button displayed in the detail section
upgrade oh on this screen you can spend
holoc coins to upgrade the level of your
talents you can check the holoc coins
required for the upgrade as well as the
increase in
stats oh do I have
to is this play at the top right of the
screen mhm
420 upgrading talents is very important
for successful parade so make sure to
upgrade whenever you have enough holoc
coins as you may have noticed there's a
few typos here and there all right in
our previous parade the tank and attacko
roles are the most important so I would
recommend upgrading Knight and elfr
first M Talent will also obtain H skills
when upgraded enough oh upgrading to
level
[Music]
10 I'm looking for to seeing what kind
of skills they learn whether they
increase attack power or block enemy
attacks skills are first chosen at
random but you can roll skills later on
choose carefully whether to strengthen
strong points or make up for weaknesses
that's all for now let's proceed to the
next parade once you have completed
upgrading your talents talents you call
these talents these are the fan mascots
but okay guess you guys are Talent now
too okay level level up I guess
and level up the this how I
yeah maybe two level UPS maybe one level
up for
you okay I'm I'm satisfied with
that you talented you are talented to
sure
sure my talent is being head empty
same oh wait I can can I I can't upgrade
support cards can
I oh no
okay all right uh I guess we
[Music]
continue let us live the dream too all
right just you guys though only KP I
only call you guys talents
today no but you guys understand right
the talent is used in a different kind
of way in Japanese talento s some like a
like a like a Disney uh uh what's it
called Disney's uh what do you call the
the the people who work at
Disney not a Disney
princess I mean uh yeah the cast member
so it's used kind of in the same way
everybody who's like so to say a
streamer or performer and life is a
talent tental
song
not sta I mean the cast members yeah for
this tutorial I will explain about the
symphony effect this can be a little
complicated but please bear with me we
can scout Talent after this is done oh
she knows that's what I want to do
Symphony effects are strong Buffs that
are cast depending on the instruments
played by your parade let's take a look
at the icons on the bottom right uhuh
yeah yeah each Talent has their own
musical instrument which is oh oh what
musical instruments do you guys have so
far they're all pretty do doot
machines oh it's the same in in in
English language
too a chicken leg
n Mayon a hunting horn hunting horn
trombone a has a trombone wow okay is
this a trombone this thing
and you also check instruments from the
parade formation screen uh-huh oh yeah
true okay when you summon a talent the
symphony effect of the corresponding
instrument will be activated effects
vary depending on the instrument and you
can check the effects by pressing the
icon let's take a look for an example
when you deploy no Sagi the flute
Symphony level one will activate which
increases movement speed for for
everybody uh character movement I don't
know if that says for everybody in
addition if Al friend is deployed not
only will trumpet Symphony increase
damage of single target attacks be
activated but the
symphony
yes yes for everyone okay Symphony
effect for of both flute and troid
effects will increase to level
two oh it Buffs the
other
effects play piercing tones to increase
damage of single attacks
oh oh no that's just like whatever I
play second increases everything to the
second level or
so is this fanmade or official fan-made
but officially
approved on top of that if you deploy
Knight a total of free Symphony effects
will be activated each upgrading to
level okay so it's really just if I have
three out they will all be at level
three if I have one out they'll be at
level one if if I have five out they'll
be at level five I
guess I suppose so the more the
merrier as more variety of instruments
deployed each Symphony effect will
become more
powerful okay when all talents of a
certain instrument leave the field the
effect of that instrument will disappear
and the overall level will
decrease let's say I have four no sagis
so it's at level four but one dies so it
goes back to level
three Symphony effects will buff all
deployed perade talents so make sure to
activate them whenever possible uh
that's all there is to learn okay
voltage is displayed at the top right of
the screen the higher the voltage level
the faster your motivation will
accumulate oh no for no only level one
okay so what if I
have one of each but then four no sagis
one
dies does the level go down just by one
of the four dying let's say I have all
of them on the field with more
no oh okay so it's still level three
okay and yeah the voltage level the
voltage level will also increase
depending on the number of active
Symphony effects increased voltage level
will not decrease during the
parade even if the symphony effects are
disabled thus the rate of the motivation
will remain high okay to summarize make
sure to form a v variety of different
musical instruments to try to keep at
least one Talent of each friend on P
okay
okay so do I have to click on them to
activate it no right it just happens on
its own
right
why are we weaker why are we so much
weak oh yeah nice
[Music]
bounce another
tank strong team let's go push forward
push push
push we need more
power e do I have to use what do you me
mean I don't have to use it right it's
just working on its own because it's not
grayed out
[Music]
right cute cute they're all so cute I
love the
mascots I love all life mascots they're
also
adorable I got a scouting tiet
nice uh what is what is she doing here
welcome back that was an even better
parade than last time in order to make H
parade bigger we need to scout more
talents so let's go
scouting all
right you can scout talents to add your
whole braate from the screen usually you
will Scout mascots but if you're lucky
enough you might get to meet H life
members aan will randomly select or for
looks so
nice oh she looks so pretty she fits so
well into the game
two Scout cands from a stack uh of
application forms okay okay oh random
random doesn't sound right I would
rather say I use my instincts when
deciding oh only one Talent can be
scouted from two candidates so choose
carefully oh I can choose okay okay to
scout you need Scout tickets the number
of tickets owned is displayed at the top
right of the screen one only one Scout
tickets can be obtained as firsttime
rewards for claiming stages or random
rewards once you conduct a certain
number of Scouts you can obtain you are
usual
room Scout tickets and talent selection
tickets so over time you'll definitely
be able to scout your favorite talents
don't forget to add the newly scouted
talents into the parade uh yeah
okay
then we're getting oh I could choose
from other wait you guys said I have to
wait can I not go for myth
[Music]
it looks like I
can ah maybe it's like an update wasn't
possible
before yeah that was an
update let's
go my it go out
e
uh e
[Music]
why was I so convinced I would get a my
[Laughter]
member and
then so disappointed but that's that's
okay that's okay what do we have this
looks like uh like a like it could be a
tank but what is it close range single
attacker a very fast move and attack
speed oh maybe not a tank strong enough
offense and
defense long range attacker oh we don't
have a long range attacker yet so maybe
we go for
Shield oh you know I know obviously all
the whole life members names and I know
some of the um a lot a lot a lsh of the
um mascot names
but this way I can learn all the ones I
don't know I didn't know that sh
senpai's mascots are called shoko for
example I didn't know that
wow wow a free mail ticket
oh thank you for downloading h y give
give give give give oh I just received
it like that one more chance one more
chance go please please wa or or anybody
please uh but we got a taco
Dai Taco Dai I have to choose a taco
Dai oh I can make an army of
tacis just like Ena does in her free
time just like at home with
plushies it's a
spy close range attacker low stats but
shows full potential of his strong
offense and defense against blue red
black or enemies okay so kind of weak
but no offense it says low stats but it
still says strong offense and
defense
okay man I
want no oh the Goa feeling is already
getting me [\h__\h] wait I need to uh put it
into my formation okay get in there how
do
I how do I do I double you how do I put
you in there what I'm too stupid I'll
just replace
okay I was like oh it's not replaced
because I'm not replacing anything okay
okay okay go go go I want more tickets I
need more tickets go go go
go free tickets for
c for real I got to try after oh my God
look at these yummy
carrots there what a scouting ticket do
I get a scouting ticket if I do
that yeah bu Faster come
on wa w
w they're strong why are they so
strong Bo I need I'm waiting for some
here stronger
ones I don't know if they're really
stronger but you
know no saki don't
die okay oh that must be the last one
surely oh aqu he can get those Ena
tentacles out of its body
interesting there's the wall there it is
should I wait for the shield goal I want
to see it in
action G
G oh this so
cute wait we're missing this one no no
we're not oh oh this
one go go go go
magic friendship is
Magic
wow
there we go oh they're so
cute and we got a scy ticket wasn't this
random this one me getting this here
isn't that kind of
random or was that
scripted wait so where do I put in the
co okay here col
press can they make a code that's only
for talents so I can get more scouting
tickets
is there any more
codes
P
[Music]
oh H
life
[Music]
no oh there's like three different
voices
of is it n or E I think it's
n
she's commentating my choices she's like
why why why myth because I am part of
myth we have two tickets one of them
will give me what I want right right
right one myth member
please one more one more come on please
please please please please please a
please don't disappoint
me okay something new uh cheers allies
oh it's a like a supportive one
increasing attack power for a few
seconds
oh a buff or close range single attacker
with very fast movement and attack
speed Mei is good okay nice buff we'll
get all of them
eventually oh
oopsie what was this one long distance
foreign strikes that Target single
enemies deals double damage to red Aura
uh enemies okay well by the way I think
I can uh level up
some yeah
upgrade who should I
upgrade K is also
good I'm just I'll just I guess I'll do
everybody
Maybe so that we're on the same
[Music]
level M I can do a few more
actually they should make a button that
I can uh switch while like to the next
one while on this
[Music]
screen just mentioning
Improvement choices
some decid to say Holo
gift Holo
gift no it's
fake so young ah I want more let's go
let's
go this will certainly bring us more
tickets oh yeah it does give us ah for
ah every maybe every first clear always
gives you Scout
indid hey hey hey hey it there's a
strange flag on the field oh yeah what
the [\h__\h] is it like Capture the Flag
let's now talk about the flags that have
appeared on some stages there will be a
flag place for both you and your enemy
in order to reach the opponent's base
each parade will need to destroy the
opponent's flag here's where things get
tricky when you destroy the enemy flag
powerful enemies and bosses will appear
if not prepared they could push back
your whole parade in comparison when
your flag is destroyed nothing will
happen you will accumulate a large
amount amount of motivation and your
voltage level will increase by one
giving you a chance to fight back okay
okay so as you can see flags are a vital
component in changing the situation of
the field so is it okay to just destroy
enemy Flags without thinking not
entirely if you destroy the enemy's flag
without enough preparation you could be
pushed back by the enemy
forces not all but I should destroy it
anyway as a basic strategy you should
build up motivation and prepare to
parade before taking down the enemy FL
yeah
okay if you're still struggling another
powerful strategy is to intentionally
let your flag be taken so that you can
gain motivation and voltage to quickly
take out the enemy base
[Music]
M now hold the flag levels are really
difficult ideal for hold member oh yeah
I can I can see how yeah because you
need to like throw out something really
strong to counter whatever they throw
out when the flag is taken
down but by doing so the chances you
will obtain the trophy will decrease so
it's best to win without having your
flag taken out it's best to keep both
flags up so maintain the front line
accumulate
motivation but I can't win the game
without taking their flag down right
that is the ideal situation it could be
difficult at first so until you get used
to it uh you should let your flag be
destroyed on purpose and then push okay
but can I stop them from attacking
it can I
[Music]
I can't right okay so I'll just hold the
enemies so even in this kind of beginner
level I should not aim for the
[Music]
flag
we're attacking it though for now I can
okay because
like I I I as as a try hard I can oh no
ah I'm
scared
Yahoo but my motivation Rises fast and I
think I can take these
down let's
go
what what are we missing
[Music]
this yeah easy easy
easy we can do
it don't give
up F oh their base is there we made it
easy they've got nothing nothing
nothing that was too
easy oh
[Music]
okay there was no reason to be scared
okay Scout oh money if you're here then
why don't you join why don't you show up
in my scouting oh because I'm going for
myth well yeah for example that could be
a
reason oh oh yeah
[Music]
but it's also pretty good but
I'm I couldn't be any more happy than
this wow wow this
feeling get in there Amy you cutie
patootie what does she do debuffs
debuffs enemies by analyzing their
weaknesses decreasing their blocking
rate by 30% effect will increase when
upgraded n but is she like a close
range does she not
attack she doesn't does she not
attack oh
[Music]
MAA that doesn't seem so good uh
why is she not doing the Pew PE Pew why
does she not attack with a
[Music]
gun now you guys also say she's not so
great that's that's fine I I I I'm happy
to have her anyway I don't
care I don't care oh I don't get a
ticket for this do
I it's just nice to have her down here
as a picture I just like seeing her
face she's so cute look at
her it's just nice it's like having
someone's someone who is dear to you
someone's picture in your
wallet that's really all that that is
you know yeah bad
[Music]
y oh maybe what are we missing we're
missing nothing right now I think
besides
oh
spam
should we safe for I don't know if I can
make it if they're bringing new
[Music]
enemies can we make it without
yes she's
here as cute as
ever let's have her be
uh joined by by takti for safety she
can't go
alone tell me the weakness that's right
all right now she's so
[Music]
smart is not really doing
anything we saw Elma in
action ah yeah she's doing so
great now I wonder
if Amy could analyze herself and tell me
what her weakness
is I want to know her weakness I'm as a
cheerleader yeah she's doing her best
and that's that's all that's all I
really need from
her she doesn't even have to do anything
and I I would I would still love her and
support her yeah
yeah next though go
[Music]
next
they're sending that enemy out already
now but it's like probably not as strong
as the like they don't have the same
stats right as if they're sent out when
taking the flag right I would
assume
[Music]
okay can we save for the shield
c
ah
mukashi yes let's go
oh maybe never know s now we have all
the Symphonies
[Music]
activated Bonk with the what's it called
not frying
[Music]
pan the lad
Le one more come on yeah
bunk it's this is a a bit
funner and a bit
funny sorry I mean I don't even I don't
even really need you in terms of like
power like cuz you're not even doing
anything anyway but I just want to see
you thank you for walking around a
little bit we got two we got
[Music]
two stream
pleas back welcome back hey
[Music]
hey okay we're back that was just for a
moment um no problem I was wondering I
was going to say before we crashed this
is man senpai's fanom right did she
actually like I I don't think I saw them
like this before is this really the
official
design I don't I don't recall seeing
them like this like an actual human
being close range anchor attacks that
Target single enemies sheesh attacking
with an anchor that that's [\h__\h] scary
they'll probably knock you out
immediately very strong in offense and
defense against red Ora enemies n n one
more one
more
woohoo they're actual buff men oh it's
in her starting screen oh I never look
ah bu sorry I have have to go for Bubba
Bubba is Sr close range attacker
moderately High Firepower he's standing
on his back feet Bubba Bubba is evolving
oh my God he looks like a bunny almost
oh not no he looks like a kangaroo
standing on his Petes increases the
motivation recovery speed by playing the
symbols Sim symbols a is
like M oh strong sounds pretty strong
wrong yeah we have am and Baba we got to
bring them both on the
field can well we should probably
replace the same
instruments oh but that is difficult
so I think I'll replace
this and this is our is this our only
like
tank he HP 300 is that what tells me
like is there defense or only HP 223 oh
this one's but she's not a tank cuz she
stays
back this I guess this one's also very I
guess this is a
tank this could be a tank now too
right oh but yeah I should keep
something that's low cost for the
beginning okay
then let me replace these just because
whatever is fine I would assume
okay ah oops see uh then let's go
[Music]
next yeah I know Taco Pirate say but I
want to keep the taco doy and and and
and and I I did want to also bring the
pirate in just for the sake of showing
them we've now covered all blah blah
recap the most basic and most what is
most important information this means
deploy your tank so that okay okay um
yeah um okay keep the neck
position one is to raise the Volus level
and Symphony effect they only require
one motivation so you can quickly
increase the voltage level by deploying
night with Nagi for stronger bosses you
can deploy an army of Nagi along with
the Knight to fortify the front line
they are also useful as they can
increase the parade movement with the
fluts effect mhm mhm mhm okay okay okay
okay okay okay
okay easy don't worry about it yeah
pirate is strong
right this is uh Pirates of the
Caribbean
number what was how high did they
go what's what would be a newer movie
which number would it
[Music]
be okay so this is pirat of the
Caribbean number five Yeah by we have no
[Music]
tank I want I want the
pirate okay okay okay we got the pirate
to be pretty strong should be pretty
damn
strong let's go let's go show me what
you
got oh yeah kill him assassinate them oh
why did I why did I go for that one oh
well we already had one we don't need
two
buffers I
guess could get uh
baa baa are you like just tired of
walking on four legs you found it more
efficient this
way the Dapper lad looking Dapper she
does look
dapper he
does oh
[\h__\h] Are we going to be that I think
we're going to be that right right right
right right bring another one of the
Pirates out
there we'll be fine we'll be
fine
probably maybe we
can
um wait we need
flute wow more magic yeah yeah yeah ooh
another p would be good also we need
this uh oh he's they're dead they're
dead the stronger ones are dead
okay all
right Boss music still playing but they
have no chance
anymore I've destroyed the
wave uh maybe we can get El now yay El
ba ah we got the perfect combination
here I'll send another Bubba oh you like
to see it you love to see
it and there may be another
one yeah more Bubbas it's almost
paradise as many Bubbas is
possible micke well if only they had
more than
Bubba ah sweet sweet sweet let's Scout
another one come on come on it's time
for another myth member I need to
complete the
team no okay
ooh Sr
poo highly mobile
and
uh uh
hello I think we're back probably sorry
this is weird OBS is kind of acting up
today it's actually not YouTube
[Music]
really question which one should I take
because this one's cheaper but this
one's way
stronger
M don't I going to which one which
one we blame both that's fine it's
probably got to do with both
yeah okay fine fine with me we'll get
them all
eventually they they definitely got me
hooked because I want like I want all
all the characters I want all the
mascots a [\h__\h] I forgot to switch out my
team oh well that's
fine also I need to uh probably upgrade
again again
soon the G is real
yeah let's get the the Knight out there
wonderful
wonderful throw the
Ladle down there maybe a shield call
uh are are we missing yeah we're missing
our
tank and no Sagi would be
nice a taco would be
nice and a
[Music]
b those aren't comboing well I know but
I just uh put them together like that
because I thought I want to show
y I want to show the pirate but I also I
don't want to let go of the taco
Nai it's just me
being me being uh supportive of myth
anything that has to do with
myth all right now we got everything we
have every oh never
mind Bubba is dead no
oh Bubba died not let's
go y b pirate
[Music]
down uh there we go and this how about
that this and
that I want another support card how you
how can you get
more do they Al so come out in the Gata
or what is she
singing what is she
[Music]
singing
Bubba M it's so nice to see you recently
I don't see much of you because you're
if you stream you stream at night for me
man going to go to the American lands
and kidnap her yeah that's what I'll do
that's what I will
do she's so
cute she's so cute I love her so
much damn this fight is kind of long wow
it's actually worth getting Amit out
here cuz the the defense is pretty
[Music]
strong well another wave of my parade is
upcoming hit him with the
little just Spam
spam why won't you die there we go oh so
if you take down the the wall even if
there's still enemies there it also
kills them ends the fight
noise the actual voice lines did they
recorded for the game or are they I mean
no got definitely Rec recorded the intro
right now I didn't get a scouting ticket
from now
[Music]
my de
formation I guess we'll do something
like this for now
[Music]
and H can you look at the trophy yeah
okay uh this looks like this is
confusing to me just shows me what I did
and I
guess
oh I have so many
[Music]
points okay we got to upgrade
everybody everybody everybody every and
you get an upgrade and you get an
upgrade and you get an upgrade yeah
let's go and you maybe too tle do it of
course Bubba Bubba needs upgrades free
of them
um oh and you too you bit was about to
forget you okay now they're like three
four three four four 4 three three three
four four okay everybody's like somewhat
around the same
level last one of the first
[Music]
chapter too expensive yeah it might be W
it's another flag like
one this might be a tough
cookie well we can always spam no
saggies no
problem guess that's what we're
doing
sh well now we got a pirate that's
pretty good
now waiting
for uh our buffer I think my chat
died well we're streaming
right ooh this is O this is quite quite
your
buy you're pretty strong oh that didn't
hit anything come
on let me wait a little bit now now that
I spam so much oh there you are hi guys
welcome back the flag is going down what
will they have but I got a pretty strong
one oh my God hat
terrifying the
damage oh my oh oh
[\h__\h] oh my
God yum send another a pirate
fast she's so stuck I only have her down
halfway
oh Bubba Bubba Bubba to the
rescue I think I think I can survive
she's pushing back hard but I can do it
let me get let me get up to 12 maybe or
now let's get this
one her defense is strong too pirate
time okay okay go faster go faster push
push push don't give up Papa please walk
on four legs you would be so much
faster okay okay she's almost
dead easy easy easy oh that that did
look pretty
critical definitely not too
easy
[Music]
she but we good now wow that was that
was
strong
the rock and roll music
too we need the mcnuggies Bubba oh I
would love some
mcnuggies oh who should I bring out
huh now I got a [\h__\h] ton of
motivation there we go a I got two
tickets and what a story clear reward
let's go 3,000 coins and another
scouting ticket so I have free now is
that what you're saying a secret town
been unlocked is it MAA because I know
that MAA is also kind of like has to be
unlocked
oh let's go oh I got a free poil wait
what what do what what happens when you
get like the same thing again the same
something you already
have
t oh
really
[Music]
where where I can scout her where would
I scal
her they upgrade the star
rank it Powers it up okay okay it's not
a level up it's a flat stat increase M
okay or could it be any of them
no let's go free got a ticket
give me another myth
member why but we got two fluffy cutie
patooties this oh they're both pretty
low cost low attack power reasonably
sturdy has fast movement speed reduces
damage from black or enemies close range
attacker low attack fluffy durable oh
durable really oh yeah yeah yeah reduces
damage from blue aura enemies oh and
this one's area attack maybe I'll go for
the Yuki
me
M please please please please s s SSR no
oh my
God 16 cost crazy movement and stomping
with area effect strong in offense and
defense we immediately got
her I got lucky I
guess of course I have to take
her mama
mia you
good oh
cute close Str single attack that
ignores enemy blocks with high
probability oh slightly strong in
offense and defense against black Aura
enemies let's upgrade our new
talents 1 2 3
4 1 2 3 four five fine why
not 1 2 three four m let's bring the
freeze up to
four free up to four bring up to four
three up to
four up to
four I don't know what I'm
singing yeah 16 is uh really powerful
but I guess maybe in a flag uh map you
could use her when they break your flag
and then bring her out as the counter
maybe that would be a good scenario
maybe maybe
maybe do I have anything else that's one
cost no but we have the yukim Min maybe
maybe we can you know switch everything
out get like a a new looking
team play place these
ones this
creature oh my [\h__\h]
god
oh and then for wait this is the same
instrument as oh no I switched it out
so
okay do I have something else
double
flute nothing nothing's double right now
[Music]
M now maybe I'll wait for later to use
obake or I no wait these are double
these are double I just realized sorry
I'm blind there we go now we have a full
set of symphony
attacks okay
interesting uh okay then oh non-stop
story what is
[Music]
this select
and uh let's
go glasses aren't
helping they're fake yeah they don't
have any prescription because I don't
need
it cute wait is this what is
this this from
n oh my God the the yukim me is getting
drunk in the back
so yeah because I thought the color is
wrong
interesting but the movement is like a
otaku cheering movement
[Music]
so this one has AOE attack right so I
think the the ghosts are pretty
good maybe a
Bubba
throw down the
little oh good team good team got we got
space for the a
mascot yeah yeah yeah looking good maybe
maybe we can get yeah
yeah now all we're missing is the
hatama I don't know we can get to
her H come on now there's no no one
fighting back there we
go she's so
fast she's so fast wow
hay oh my
God she was there for only a moment but
still she oh
[Music]
game there's game game
streaming hurry up me COI is it a side
game
what
oh little mini
game oh money oh I got actual coins for
this ah okay I I thought I could maybe
jump over
that oh over this I can
jump oh oh
oh this this is a bit difficult a
[\h__\h] can you only play this every once
in a
while no way I should have gone
down oh but never mind actually the top
row also has coins but the yeah the
bottom one would have been better
unless oh it's like maybe almost endless
but yeah you die eventually now hold on
my score is 19 my first time
score you can move when you jump I can
jump over oh I see I see can I do it
again do I get the coins even if I
retry but if you can reach any time then
you can get like endless coins
no 100 for
ticket
[Music]
oh
my is the the road always the same I
think no because it didn't start with
the bells right away I
[Music]
think okay okay okay ah okay
okay well war war Warf
okay oh she's running so much she's
running she's running a [\h__\h]
Marathon what the [\h__\h] no so
close wait score 100 for
a more more more more more more more
more
more run M
run why is she so
slow
a
OBS
why get
[Music]
why
on the prompts at the top were
funny oh come
on why why why a [\h__\h]
hell I can't do it I can't do it or
maybe I
can ah OBS please please be nice
[Music]
OBS but it's like literally endless
coins no or is there a catch that I
can't keep the coins
unless I get I don't
know there's no catch what you was run
into the moving cats yeah I'm trying to
maybe I shouldn't be so greedy then for
those coins those are difficult to get
[Music]
anyway I sure okay this time I didn't
fall
down here I
did why I'm trying to jump
[Music]
over
okay okay hey what why
why why why but I got 100
I got the 100
yay at least the 100
oh can I click on them no they're just
hanging out there in the back getting
drunk okay let's
Scout
[Music]
IG oh
n dangerous cat with very fast movement
and attack speed close range single
attacker strong in offense and defense
against blue aura
enemies not hold
door let's
upgrade because now we can have
[Music]
endless endless level
UPS
let's keep them all do you guys also do
this do you also try to keep
everybody around the same level even if
you may not use
[Music]
them not always yes no only the ones I'm
using okay but I'm not sure which one I
want to use everybody
so for now I'm doing
these okay other of points and what what
what what element are you the flute
oh oh I feel like we can get rid of
haima for now as long as there's not a
huge challenge
upcoming
and yeah that's uh that's fine that's
fine that's
fine let's go to the
pade guys join me let's go
[Music]
together
she just came back
a I can go thata again oh well we'll go
after go go fight go go
fight [\h__\h] I kind of was hoping to wait
but there's uh a lot of enemies so all
right all right all right that looks
good that looks pretty good look at the
cute what's it called Poco b or
something like that a it's so
cute
uh yeah bye they're pushing they're
pushing come on I need more more
damage the yukim dies so
fast not they're actually strong oh the
cat is so fast and strong though holy
[\h__\h] so
fast bring me yeah that's what I
want that's what I
need I'm actually not doing so well
right now maybe I should not level
everybody because now we're lacking the
strength BB is super
strong oh yeah
Bo oh yeah
y y
actually let's keep it low cost I guess
holy
[\h__\h] they spawn Endy right unless I
reach the wall and kill the wall or do
they ever stop
spawning
oh
oh it this does not look so
good I think we have to fix
something I don't know if it's my level
or my
formation maybe we need a bit more low
cost with the noag is I don't
know what do you think why did you die
again on my side ticket yeah okay okay
[Music]
okay there I'm refreshing my
chat you think the
formation need a strong tank but I have
I have my the the two strong tanks I
have like the the basic one and the the
pirate
maybe we need more more gold because I
ran out of money so I couldn't upgrade
more but maybe we have to play the mini
game for a while BB closer into attacker
sometimes knocks back enemies of blue
Ora
okay okay okay I think I have to play
this a bit
more they gave me this mini game at a at
a good
timing I do require
it
okay we have
to
we just have to we have no
choice play the previous stages for gold
eh can I I get more gold than usual or
what oh look at me look at me
girl
good good
[Music]
job yep yep yep yep y yo the stone the
stone it looks like it's the the the top
row is empty it fools me every time I
think I'm pretty sure now that it's not
empty oh my God [\h__\h] off
ah go
[Music]
away
oh oh I can't see why does it not go
away I got 150
woohoo and 248 coins
y one more one more it will never go
[Music]
awayy getting any higher than 150 seems
very difficult to me right now
try to get 200 well ideally I want to
get like at
[Music]
500 but I was I was doing better than
before that's for
[Music]
sure nice jumped a little bit earlier
and it worked yeah bye
yeah no I'm
stupid you managed to do it before
where's the problem
now oh no not
again but yeah when you go up and commit
to go to the top there in the zig dag
then going back down is
actually quite difficult oh [\h__\h] hell
whatever one more one more one more
I just need the money it doesn't matter
if we die
early your best is 433
sheesh that's also pretty impressive Zen
Lo
[Music]
Deni you know they could do like a
burger memorization and serving
restaurant Min game with
me just
saying just just just saying just an
idea you know I feel like I would be the
perfect character for that just
[Music]
saying Stone up coming let's stay
down [\h__\h] what
n
why
[Music]
oh my my pretty good H I got out of the
zigzag oh middle what the
[\h__\h] a what the
[Music]
[\h__\h] oh what the [\h__\h] ah no I almost had
it a
see okay I got to do it again cuz I got
so
close oh but yeah I dodged the
Stone Face tank CH the Rocks take two
lanes where where the [\h__\h] am I supposed
to
go even on its own this game
has like enough to become its own
game this mini
[Music]
game
nice yeah n that's the diagonal jump I
have to get better at it [\h__\h] too
early okay okay I get
it
[Music]
okay chill this area is pretty easy to
comprehend my eyes are getting dizzy
it's it gets too fast fast my eyes are
like what the
[\h__\h]
w at least the course is like always the
same so you can definitely get really
good at this just remember the the
course was a good run
right the coins look so
good coins look so nicely animated and
Drawn to me so
shiny
[Music]
sorry and my eyes are already getting
tired of
this ah I'm trying to diagonal jump but
I'm yeah no
[Music]
[\h__\h] H
so reach I want to
[Music]
retry
diagonal jump is
[Music]
difficult or something like
that do you guys know that weird word
that they came up with on the Japanese
side
or and it's very uh
[Music]
mysterious they coined a new word yeah I
I don't even know how to explain it to
you I I only heard about
it it means like mikoi I am embarrassed
so I guess somebody wrote that in her
chat and then she uh made it short or
somebody made it short in into something
like me I am kind of like
that
can't yeah I don't I don't really
understand it
either I'm dizzy
I'm
dizzy dizzy I'm dizy oh the close range
area tackle great damage to Red Aura
enemies
OH Close Range seven cost M kind of
expensive Tak I don't know yet if I want
to use
it don't know yet just scouted
kiaha give me give me give me give me
I should I should do
uh how much gold do I get
[Music]
380 wait uh we got some money so I
should upgrade to okay we should we
should create a team basically at least
like decide which ones will stay in for
sure I think the pirate can stay for a
while so let's get him to six the Bubba
I want to keep too I think Bubba is
worth keeping Poyo also right pretty
strong Nick
is I haven't seen much of it yet but it
seemed pretty
[Music]
convincing yeah low cost should I should
I get well they're the same instrument
so that's the
thing two one cost and two tanks I don't
I only have one one cost
anyway
getting to level 10 gives them a skill
need some cheaper ones okay then until I
have like more levels and all that more
money in there thing I guess we continue
with noag
is as
my flute
[Music]
option what else was pretty good
don't upgrade too expensive what no is a
staple opener I guess so let's see
[Music]
uh oh yeah we got BB Too Close sometimes
knocks back that sounds so good but it's
just a level one it will take me a bit
more money to get it
higher m
M should I go for obak or the
karasu uh five cost four cost
308 attack
a this one's cheaper a bit more buff but
less damage and this one's bit more
expensive less buff but more
damage
[Music]
let's go for the cheaper one oh but I
have okay that's already too much I'm
just missing one coin for real for
real
so uh let's switch
these
um the rest
looks okay oh but yeah we were going to
replace the cat
because
of the
overlapping uh overlaps which one
doesn't overlap I guess this one does
not overlap we could get a yukim Min
too attack 12
area upgraded Niel can solo some early
straight really but I don't have the
possibility for that right
now am doesn't overlap yeah but like 18
cost when can
I if I'm already being pushed back that
hard you
[Music]
know I'll I'll I'll try this combination
for now T
[Music]
aimos I still feel like that that stage
that we just did where I kind of failed
will still not be possible but let's
give it a
[Music]
try she overlapped anyway H
what hi I love you love you
too yeah let's just Spam
it we can do it we can do
it so far so
good yeah
don't get
overwhelmed let's wait
for something else now maybe maybe we
can afford
it
okay y now they're pushing back
okay
yeah it's fine it's fine I can fix it
waiting for the pirate maybe it wasn't
worth it but I can fix it I can fix it I
can fix
it okay okay we're we're getting some
balance back in there and we got
[Music]
this
no f it simply fre babies you're done
yeah [\h__\h]
me no and they don't stop coming and
they don't stop coming and they don't
stop coming and they don't stop coming
please no have
mercy it's not going to get better is it
they're just slowly but surely pushing
back
Dam let's play the previous stage
again that was a suddenly such an
increase in like difficulty because the
this one was no problem at
all anything up up until that point was
[Music]
fine weird
spaming low cost is how you lose you
need range I do have a ranged one but
it's really high
cost
m
oh let's get the ghost back come on give
me give me the
[Music]
symphony how high can we get can we get
much
higher I mean this level is really no
problem
it's no no
problemo is it yeah it's a bit more
difficult than the others but see we
already reached the wall so this one's
fine can't even get Bubba
[Music]
out oh
okay we got a little bit more money
so
H the problem is like I don't even get
the the yyu the the chance to get any
higher units in there so I feel like I
have to upgrade the weaker ones that I
send
in H
that's what you call a noob
filter should we should we get the T
that
back close R area tack but shows
full it's like they T is pretty
[Music]
versatile that would be the
trumpet did I have any thing I had the
the pirate M yeah we can try replacing
those but then that's my only other
really
buff
uh character that I
have time to
what it helps you get your costly units
out what you need to focus on getting
voltage and Buffs
up what helps me get my costly units
out
oh send the Higher One in
[Music]
first I think a problem with your team
is that it cost so much you need that's
what I'm
[Music]
trying let's upgrade the Knight one
more
and
[Music]
then I guess we're
switching uh
this yeah for now for now for now just
for
now volage to four then save up for high
cost like
hot that that will be a while until I
get there let me try again then let me
try let me try let me
try
yeah as many as F okay let's wait a
little bit to get something else out
first if we
can let's get to four and
then how sturdy is the Taco DOI
huh T is still alive let's go
now my symphon is looking better
now oh get the taco thaty back and my
[Music]
tank they pushed back a little bit I was
waiting for more but uh oh we got Bubba
we got
Bubba OBS why why
[\h__\h] I sent the wrong
one oh wait guys I'm doing it come back
to
me uh keyboard
keyboard and almost at 12 I'm doing it
I'm doing it
guys yo the variety I didn't even use
the
ladle you guys are back at a good moment
cuz I'm
winning now hold up
N I
understand yeah okay okay okay before
good eyes here what the [\h__\h] good eyes
in a kitty pool in a kitty
swimsuit drinking something
blue oh my God what the hell
[Music]
GA
m kka
this this might be the
way okay I will not Scout yet I will
instead go to the next map uh oh maybe a
level up actually it seems like they
keep on making everything stronger
faster and faster so let's look at my
usual team I would be nice to have like
um another like maybe like a grouping so
that I can find the talents that I
really want to upgrade easier I guess I
guess I can do it for the formation
screen too though I guess
so six five five five okay upgrade the
Yuki
me
and anyone at four no but upgrade
obon okay cuz those ones I also get out
pretty
[Music]
early
a okay why do you miss her if you have
me
huh U number three let's see if this
will also be a big surprise and
difficulty hopefully
not hey hey hey hey in this stage I'll
explain about auras oh okay oh no it's a
flag
level
okay be careful against enemies
surrounded by a glowing aura they have
much higher stats than normal
enemies you love both okay always come
in different colors they're stronger in
the order of blue red black gold oh blue
red black gold blue Ora enemies have
twice normal Health whereas red oras in
addition will deal twice the damage
black or gold enemies are even stronger
you're saying red Ora enemies will have
double Health as well as double attack
power is there any way to counter them
yes there's something called anti yeah I
already saw that yeah yeah yeah
yeah po the red icon displayed in the
upper right corner is the anti or
building yeah 30% mhm you'll see a red
shield icon along with the percentage
number dis ability reduces damage
received from red or enemies there are
also other icons such as the sword which
increases the damage
dealt sword what this one what and fist
which causes the knockback the color of
the icon corresponds to the color of the
aura that these are what we call blah
blah blah blah so we should leave po to
deal with the red or
okay
fine oh yeah okay it looks like this
stage we have powerful Aura enemies
let's try the stat strategy of building
motivation before taking the enemy flag
yeah yeah yeah okay so building enough
motivation to prefer your parade when
than taking the flag okay so but like
does that mean that I just don't create
as many units yet
because if I do then I'll push too hard
and I go to the
flag why is first if I have to Cho
a nice
answer yeah okay so we'll save up I'll
I'll try I'll try start the
parade I'm
scared so do I just spawn nothing until
till they destroy it or I guess so cuz
otherwise I'm just wasting It
[Music]
Anyway ah they got the cheap ones out
for
voltage okay okay how until what point
do you say it's
cheap but then they stop attacking the
flag I guess that's fine for a while we
can defend motivation still goes
up mhm
uh what just died uh this thing how
about the
takachi okay
uh is this the way to do
it we're already at 17 18 but if I knew
it was a flag level like this I would
have uh brought in maybe a
hatcham
we're actually pushing
sheesh start sending stuff out now but
then I destroy the flag or is that fine
just to
[Music]
counter
okay okay okay we're coming in strong
very
strong all
right I guess we're doing it
y
[Laughter]
y over over oh we're pretty strong we're
pretty strong I got another another
Shield all right all right and then you
can in I
Easy E
easy
easy ah it's quite the stalling
technique
yeah
easy oh we did it y let's Scout a little
bit you are
Scout I am Scout
please yes character
[Music]
character
man
[Music]
um but I guess I'll still take her
because like even though I don't have
this character this mascot
this one's still more valuable
so wait the fact that it said you are
does that mean I was guaranteed to get
like is it like a Pity thing was this a
pity pull and the one I get is the one I
already
have yeah might as well upgrade Amit
that's what I was thinking it was a Pity
one it was a Pity
[Music]
one
that's
ridiculous I don't want your pity then
like this phrase actually applies I in
that
case oh
man oh man a man I love you but that's
yeah
unfortunate very
unfortunate 6 75 okay upgrade
[Music]
yeah okay you know it's a bit
unfortunate that uh the talents are just
the the the actual stream us we the URS
actually that's expensive because then
you rarely get them out on the
field cuz really mostly you only get at
least for now I don't know if it's later
different but for now all I'm getting
out is these
M the low cost mascots that's a bit more
D because I want to see the idols too
right I want to see them in
[Music]
action
all right I waited a little bit in the
beginning takachi already dead Mama Mia
takachi since when were you so
sensitive okay all right all right all
right uh you me
bonked yeah bye
it's okay I'll I'll get there see I got
Bubba I got Bubba everything's fine as
long as I got
Bubba I almost had I am there we go go
go she's so fast too like sorry to keep
you waiting I'm here
now
yeah already reached the wall okay
okay
easy full
[Music]
Symphony next see that one was
easy go next go
[Music]
next
I wish there was a button after you
clear a stage oh oh no oh no that says
uh go to like the next story stage level
thingy that would be cool then I don't
have to go back to the starting
screen tle that you please survive as
long as you
can okay okay good Symphony oh wait oh
wait I'm doing low cost low cost wait
wait wait okay don't push too much right
don't push too
much saving money here but they're so
strong I'm so strong stay back guys you
don't have
to way too strong why why why why am I
so strong stay
back stay
back I'm building voltage though I'm
building motivation building everything
I'm just too
strong in let go if I'm that strong and
I guess I'll just I'll just go for it
just go for
it no yeah yeah that's fine that's
fine gold is level
five 20 W wo wo 22 23 my motivation is
so
high
ah why why I didn't even realize
goodbye wait we need a
takachi okay okay oh no we can do
it uh yeah Tak back we need a Iron Man
po
faster what they're dead they're dying I
wasn't even looking at their HP but
we're fine we're
fine keep the defenses up keep them
coming easy Bubba is back we're on the
rise
again kfp unbeatable cannot be destroyed
can I get a 12 can I get a uh a number
12 and a
number
H and number two and then number four
and then number four and then number two
and then number one just spamming
now
punk po po is really good to have on
your
team
okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay well let's
do some upgrading I like this
team I like
[Music]
it if we're going to upgrade let's
upgrade the ones first that go out there
on the battlefield
[Music]
early okay I try Amit over
sh could do could do just so that we ALS
to see more
arm maybe maybe may maybe next time I'll
go into next stage
[Music]
now got to go to work okay have fun or
good luck I hope it will be a good day
at work
today enjoy didn't you guys say the
stage that I just did was like like well
known to be difficult but I first tried
it like come
on
oh no this level you said that about the
previous level
too so I think we'll be
fine uh what am I what am I looking for
everyone's still alive even the takachi
all right Bubba is
coming
nice oh my God Tak the first takachi
still
alive still and we got I out Bo
nice if smug will bite you back surely
well so far look at this easy I'm
dominating the
[Laughter]
battlefield
BK yukim Min die really fast I wouldn't
mind like replacing yukim Min eventually
if I get another like two cost or one
cost character
talent that was
easy it's not this one but the next
level oh I see okay you guys keep on
confusing
oh dog wait does Chloe Senpai Senpai
chlo call her because this is from Chloe
right does she call her fans Inu dogs
and they look however like orgas but she
calls them like kind of like insultingly
[Music]
dogs her masc my mascot's called Eno so
she like she addresses her fans as
dogs like that would maybe make sense if
it wasn't visually an
orca
that's so funny wait I didn't read the
stats
actually o eight cost M 500 HP oh that's
that's pretty buff close range tackles
that Target single
enemies are sturdy and very strong in
offense and defense against blue or no
looks pretty strong if I want to switch
something out for a high cost
tank and mascot not the fense oh okay so
some some for some uh talents it's the
same thing
I'm I don't have the same thing noaki is
like mascot and fan right but Kotori is
mascot and kfp is the fan for
example all right true yeah yeah that's
the actual name
[Music]
for yeah tacos are both as well
yeah and
Chums no Chums and shrimps are chots are
depicted as shrimps
right
right and she would probably oh she
would probably see it as her mascot too
right look cuz she doesn't acknowledge
bloop doy like in fan games also they
officially they would acknowledge blue
but
personally she
wouldn't corn
bloop
[Music]
oh I almost choked ah oh pretty low cost
coton Kon just does not have feet so it
just like whips back and
forth cute or rocks Rippon is German it
rocks back and forth I and I I feel like
we could give it feet we could just say
like in in this like normal
sitting it's just a sitting form but it
hides its feet so well if it wants to
walk and stand up like it can show its
feet that are normally tucked in but I
guess now it's uh now it's um
lore that it moves while rocking back
and forth that's pretty adorable
actually not very efficient but
adorable you use kotoni a lot or just
fly right yeah low cost long range and
oh long range highly offensive but
offensive but very vulnerable yeah just
stay in the back then okay we have to
use it obviously it's a trump o
[Music]
Maga that's like my most valuable unit
right now I'm not sure if I want to
switch it out then maybe if we switch
something else out that it's like as oh
wait this one's also trumpet
[\h__\h]
maybe later maybe we make the switch
later when I have other options uh to
switch something that is as valuable as
a
PUO COI better you think
so we can try and see if we can live
[Music]
without
there you
go we'll try make a second team no no
it's fine it's fine this is fine this is
fine apparently this is a difficult
stage though so if it doesn't work then
we'll go back to our normal
team H I don't want to go double trumpet
unless I have
to slap whip with the tentacle
sheesh all right volage level
four ah could have brought a c next next
next here we go here we go coton is out
how far does it stay back back it's
still pretty
close and Bubba is here guys you said
this stage is difficult no look at the
fire whirlwinds to go and a taco that
still lives and we have the shield out a
this is a pretty valid team oh my
God I'm I'm I'm I'm
Invincible the only thing that always
dies is the yukim
min
is behind the tank so that's all
good look a couple ones died now but
that's the first time they died so I
think that's
acceptable
SK
wow wow easy that was like you so
easy yeah I got got the order down I I
my my thing is now to always wait for
the Taki and then send out the tank and
then no Sagi like I have an order in my
head now that seems to work I know I had
so much motivation but there was no need
to send out anymore but I guess I I
could bring in am but am is like not so
useful unless I need like more defense
or or need to break their
defense
I'm
motivated they'll BFF for next I hope
so I'm tell I don't know if the if the
creator of the game will watch this but
I'm giving a lot of uh advice on how to
improve
this it all oh no another
flag
ah flag game MAA
uh okay so we try to
stall while getting the Sy the voltage
up okay don't get too strong wa wa this
is all I'll do this is maximum okay ooh
new new Little
mascot or should I do more oh don't know
I can't help it I don't quite understand
the stalling uh balance yet like what
exactly I should should
[Music]
I no I guess I'm doing it right am I
doing it right I you going
to I could I could bring out this one is
that too much like the more units I
bring out the stronger I am obviously
so I don't want to be too
strong that's the
problem
but this this is pretty good we're
standing in the middle I have uh a good
amount of symphony uh
voltage I guess that's pretty good right
now need to be stronger on the
opposition get Bubba
out
read chat for one moment and fall back a
little
bit wait motivation is so low
[\h__\h] I'm I'm bringing out too much why
did I why did you tell me to bring
bubble out I need to get my motivation
higher okay now now it's good oh now
it's good oh now it's really good never
mind never mind it's fine
M
no okay maybe maybe now we can
go all
in BK another Shield there it goes
y I got bonked really hard
already oh
[\h__\h] is this the difficult State I think
it is look I need am I think I need amo
in this stage
because the it would be great to have
the defense down of that enemy
now yeah that might be dumb that might
be D up until that point it was easy
easy easy oh
no
D I won't give up but it's
quite
yeah brute forcing it
uhuh domino
domino red anti red
Aura
[Music]
oo
I
man yum can I just Frey this is too
painful oh my
God didn't know this was Dark
Soul spam
takes
oh I don't know if I can at this point
oh oh no oh
no I
don't
[Laughter]
die okay okay okay red
Aura ahuh it's time to switch these out
again for a strong
comeback
uh could bring the pirate in
too no
red maybe instead of Bubba we can bring
in the pirate what do you think
or cuz they're similar
cost C fire
no keep Bubba
okay
maybe maybe H wait I also got to look at
the instruments I
guess we could switch the taco Dodges
but the taco Dodges are fine too but
just in terms of like the
instrument what else is red the crow is
red oh we could switch these
two and
uh yeah maybe that will look
better
give it a level up
uh maybe one
more okay I'll try like
this this is now with my new team right
so bring am if it still doesn't work
like this I might bring am but for now
I'm hoping that I brought enough
red Aura uh
tackle wait this no this is the red team
okay okay
okay all
right but and now we
[Music]
wait am it won't really help much
yeah 13 14 oh [\h__\h] ah wrong ones oopsy
ah he died anyway so that's fine in that
very moment he died 16 18 19 20
21 they're starting to attack the base
now
so getting everything up is very
important
now oh oh it's about to happen so I'm
sending them out I'm sending the strong
ones out let's
go yeah yeah we're
pushing
IGA stay
strong oh yeah holy [\h__\h] the difference
is
incredible oh it's like night and day
poo
strong go
y
c yeah
beautiful that was
powerful strongest army I've ever seen
in my
life M very satisfying to see the
difference nice nice nice
nice
hey Bo cute
indeed okay okay I'll I'll
go I'll go next already
but I'll switch
back maybe no I'm not switching never
mind this is our Capture the Flag
team maybe unnecessarily
strong scouting time no if I only have
one ticket I felt like oh wait that one
has a blue aura though and I've ah have
nothing for blue
aura actually the taco dases are strong
and the yukim mees too against the blue
aura
enemies maybe maybe we're
fine so I'll bring a couple more of
those oh and more
wow
ooh take him down take him
down well I want to go for 10 oh but
Bubba first maybe Bubba Bubba has no
particular Aura strengthes
huh yo the blue ones have higher HP or
what was
it I can tell because they just won't
die okay I am a time I am
time hit him with the PO y
yo hey let's go
Sho well the game definitely makes good
use of uh like or forces me to make good
use of all my units because depending on
the
aura again you want to use different
units but even though I was like using a
more red
team I was able to deal with the blue
ones anyway so that's fine
look at my motivation
Mama
nice maybe some upgrading can be
[Music]
done I don't know what to upgrade I
don't know what's
what's I use the same unit all the time
yeah I I did I did do fine with this
team as well
surprisingly
[Music]
but the Knight and Bubba for example
don't have
any Aura
specialty so it would be good to maybe
eventually switch them out so that I
just cover all my bases you
[Music]
know currently like we don't
have the purple one for
example this uh my ghost obakan would be
covering that for
[Music]
example buba Symphony really good too
good to replace yeah it seems pretty
rare to have the
c i uh I could switch out these if I
don't need so much red anymore I could
switch out these
again this this way I would have some
purple just in case
let's do some leveling
776 but did you notice like the blue
ones they stayed alive for so long but
the moment pooo comes out even though it
doesn't have any like blue aura strength
immediately it cleans up the field crazy
po you kind of
overpowered
sheesh
po you might get Ora skill at level 10
on well getting
there one slowly one
step slowly but surely one step at a
time another flag one it's like every
second level is a flag
level okay let's go stage
210 bring it
on what do we
get
[Music]
nice spooky Halloween
music
buk Halloween is over guys where's the
Christmas
music volage level
[Music]
six yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah I like Halloween music though we we
should know more ize Halloween music
even outside of
Halloween this dope it's kind of a waste
to not have music like this outside of
[Music]
Halloween I wonder what kind of strong
enemy they've got for me now cuz we're
destroying the
base what Aura is this rent red very
obviously red okay okay I still got my
red team no
problemo send them all out po never
po I see no HP all I all I see is these
timers and my
motivation rock and
roll but never Boy oil can never have
enough boil oh easy easy we're killing
them
Yo to strong what was so strong
strong it's not really a thing in Europe
I mean I think it kind of is but if if
you guys say it's not then I wonder how
crazy it is in other countries like
America or other continents a secret
Talent has been unlocked and now
available the gcha stats can be checked
from the gallery
nice Crow carried I wasn't sure what was
carrying I was just sending out
units yes what is it I heard that the
preparations are not complete n
absolutely H parade public relations
department is now
ready hooray let's go check out the PR
department office oh what is this can I
make a room oh cute oh what is this oh
like a little like a little Factory to
farm coins and stuff behind the
scenes I'll take it from here this is
the Hol parade public relations
department this division will post
information about Hol parade for social
media making people more aware about us
so that we can obtain holoc coins yeah
money money money it's all about the
money more money more coins if you
successfully create buzz and hype with
clickbait d thumbnails and titles we
will get more followers as well as whole
coins we can use these upgrades uh to
upgrade our talent by the way guys
subscribe like and leave a comment
uh maybe join the membership because I
do weekly members only streams just
saying which're is grateful as we're
always in need of extra coins I'll first
briefly explain the analytics
section here you can check information
such as number followers total earnings
Etc stonks oh yeah hit the bell I
guess too late already a member
nice oh zly with the memberships thank
you uh next is public relations ability
column we need to create videos to post
onto social media the quality of of the
videos depends on the scores displayed
for each of the four steps right below
are the members of the public relations
department above the members you can
check the assigned task and score the
overall total is displayed at the very
top the higher the level of the talents
the higher the score sometimes the score
will be higher if the talent is
motivated talents who were in the
previous parade will be less effective
as they would be too tired to work it is
important to separate parade members oh
that oh that's fine that's fine
currently you can only have up to two
members a time but by meeting the
requirements you will be able uh to
upgrade the equipment increase the
number of
members next is the SNS demand
survey survey when conducting PR
activities on social media it is very
important to invest get the public
Trends so we need to pick up on the
trends
oh girls playing instruments are cute
true uhhuh then choose the pr strategy
on and focused areas for the PR's policy
section a membership thank you guys
thank
you for example if the public shows
interest in a cute parade costume the pr
stry would be pop and cute and the focus
would be videos or thumbnails how do I
know sounds like a plan posts with high
ratings and a large number of shares
means it's gaining a lot of attention if
things go well will go viral and will be
riging holoc since when was hon so
greedy finally this number is the uh
Public Relation points necessary for
executing public relations
activities
uhuh
[Music]
thank you more memberships thank you
thank you you can earn one point each
time you go to parade accumulating up to
Five Points ex executing public
relations activities will consume all
accumulated points uhhuh you can consume
your points frequently or save points
until you have conducted enough research
and then use it all at once when you
have the right chance okay that is all
to know
okay okay uh so let's switch
what if we have hat hat
and this is exactly the kind of people
you want to take care of your
[Music]
PR the blonde power is strong what I
still have what I didn't know I had
Super Chat still disabled ah what the
hell let me turn them
on let me turn on didn't realize somehow
it didn't seem absent to me at
all
oopsy okay they're on now do with this
information what you
please I didn't even notice people were
telling me when where I didn't see
it why dis sa in the first place because
I played a game where I wasn't able to
or Allowed by policies to monetize
[Music]
it
Maga
yeah super Chata
time okay uh what what what are we is
this fine I don't really know what I'm
doing here uh let's do poping cute
because they said something about that
but I can't execute the pr activities
yet anyway I guess
[Music]
oh Focus content what up oh yeah right
uh this
ah
go overall 20 no
30 30 four
oh
60 W that's pretty good no thank you for
the super
chats this doesn't match too much with
the SNS strength what you told me to do
that didn't
[Music]
you I'm so excited it did pretty well
anyway yeah it keeps on going keeps on
Rising it looks like the post has been
shared by many people
yeah do I have to look at this
[Music]
forever cut cutting cutting
cutting oh okay I got uh almost 1,000
coins and what what what do I get from
having these followers more coins in the
future I
guess like for the next PR activity I
get more coins probably isn't fully
working I heard stuff got Lost in
Translation oh that's fine I feel like I
understand
[Music]
mostly there's a chance that you get
like a really really uh viral post and
then you get like 10,000 points uh coins
10,000
coins M scouting time I guess yeah if I
get another am I swear I feel like we're
close to the the pity pool again aren't
[Music]
we oh corisi a new one cost six short
ranged area attacka with very high
Firepower great damage towards red or
enemies unblock
unblockable all
right
okay oh that's pretty good
maybe oh an
cuz we don't have anim yet medium range
area attacker as usual is stuck in the
ground reduces damage from Blue Area
enemies medium range 12
cost it's kind of
[Music]
expensive oh wait wish should maybe um
upgrade 7 seven okay everybody's seven
now so let's start going up higher to
eight
[Music]
eight okay let's go
parade it's parade time we're I think
wait how many stages 10 out 20 oh we're
still only halfway through this
one I also got two am on my first one
what same with
me no
[Music]
way
have you guys noticed my skin is like
shinier than
usual I finally used one of my beauty
masks that I had lying around for a
while since actually this one I had
lying around since I went to Korea it
was one of the masks that uh Nai Mama
recommended me when we went shopping for
like beauty products she was like this
one's good this one's
good but like I actually I don't even do
that much skin care and I I I never
really take the time to use my my beauty
products all the
masks especially the sheet masks because
I don't really like sheet masks I have
one um I I think I showed it before
maybe I have this like powder uh clay
powder whatever that you mix with water
and then you apply it with a brush to
your face and that one that one I like
to do every once in a while but the
reason why I don't like uh the sheet
masks is because often they don't fit my
face so well and I have to like position
it well sometimes they're too small
sometimes they're way too big and I
don't like the all the overlap is like
super super
uh like so much liquid is soaked in
there I don't like it I don't like it
they're stupid they're not uncomfortable
but also when you put them on your face
they're like cold as
[\h__\h] I like brushing the the powder
stuff on my face more is that blue or
what is
that I guess it's blue
right m
so I I barely use them but today was
like with me cleaning my apartment so
much these days it's kind of like a
self-care thing I guess and honestly
every once in a while it does feel nice
to do a self-care
thing instead of like bathing in your
depression and your
dirt and disgusting
environment dirty kitchen dirty
apartment dirty face dirty body dirty
mind clean your dirty
mind like not only like you know doing
something for yourself mentally but also
doing something for your own
body and your surroundings everything
everything
combined just is a good way way to do
selfcare and improve your
overall how to
say
happiness Breaking the Chain is tough
but worth yeah I totally get that like I
also have this problem but since I live
alone I eventually get forced to clean
up my [\h__\h] but yeah I I also often like
especially the kitchen after cooking
something but then first of all going
getting to the point of like being
motivated enough to cook something is
really hard it's even harder when the
kitchen is dirty so then I cook
something for once and then it's dirty
as [\h__\h] especially cuz I have a pretty
small
kitchen and uh like everything
accumulates so fast
immediately it's just everything is such
a motivation problem man
right and motivation when being kind of
the presso is presso is a is a rare
resource but I try my best I am keeping
up and recently really like my right now
my apartment is so clean and I'm so
proud like looking at how clean it is
I'm cleaning things that I never cleaned
before things that I always neglected
and ignored and now now I'm cleaning
them
up wow and I'm proud of
myself yeah it feels good so if anyone
is in the situation that I was in uh
right now where like everything's a
[\h__\h]
mess maybe me talking about how it
really positively affects me right now
by actually getting my ass up and and
taking care of my apartment and myself
may maybe that motivate someone else in
here
why wait I didn't realize it's a flag oh
[\h__\h] I oh [\h__\h] I was just mindlessly
playing I didn't realize [\h__\h] it's a
black Aura oh I'm so [\h__\h] oh I'm so
[\h__\h] oh I'm so [\h__\h] oh I'm so
[\h__\h] oh oh I'm so [\h__\h] but what even
what even is good against black Aura
enemy is black the same thing as the
purple one in it's like I only saw
purple blue
red in my characters that's all I
saw uh we're barely surviving we we
didn't get pushed back yet
but they're dying though I can actually
do
it pretty on par I mean considering the
fact that I was not looking at the
flag oh so purple is black okay okay
okay okay okay not hold don't I'm I
actually doing it I'm impressed I am
surprised and impressed they did clear
all my front line for a moment but no
problemo
h
easy
easy easy all right no ticket for that I
was doing so well and you don't give me
a ticket
why I think Bubba deserves a head
pet and maybe Bo oil wait I should go to
formation
screen I like my team right now I'm
pretty happy with this team so obak Chan
was pretty good against black Ora
huh nice to have
[Music]
her okay okay okay B is a good boy who's
a good boy oh who's a good
[Music]
boy
yeah built a strong team first I was
like I don't know who the hell oh thank
you zly yeah I feel like like for really
well how to say well put together
like people who just win in life all the
time who maybe like Workaholics um for
those maybe it it it might come easier
to complete all these like daily life
tasks
cuz they always got to be doing
something but I I need to balance it out
with just like chill me
time with my cats and and with my
TV I really need that you know it's I
know it can be seen as lazy and yeah I
am lazy and to some
extent but if I don't have that cool
down
time like the TV is for cool down time
to just like
get down from all the work related stuff
and then the cats are for like basically
social interaction like cuddling and all
that because I don't have anything else
anyone else that gives me that so I need
my cats you know they they are the
only ones that keep me company here on a
daily
basis and honestly I like it that way
like I I wouldn't want a roommate or
anything like that cuz that's like like
would that would disturb my my workflow
and my daily life
flow and I don't want to give a human
too much
attention oh M by cute she's peing she's
looking at what they're
[Music]
doing I just like living
alone like I I I
honestly could not imagine having a
partner a life
partner
because I'm sure they would be extremely
either jealous or
like complaining about me not having
enough time for them and I don't want to
sacrifice this like momentum that I have
right now and it's okay I don't really
have a a need
for such a person in my life even though
it would be helpful because they could
probably take care of the
chores
yeah more restrictive yeah that's what
I'm feeling it's more restrictive to me
than beneficial for real for
real I'm paying attention now I know
there's a flag so this is all I to put
out for
now
M just take your
time but they're already killing
it stalling stalling
stalling
and let's
go what is it blue ah easy blue and red
no
problem yukim Min is
blue let's bring out a Bubba let's bring
out a dead pan let's go let's go let's
go another IR man easy easy another one
yeah
y let's
go kill them
all similar needs and expectations that
I don't even I don't even like go out
like and have time to meet people so
it's not
happening it's not
happening until I'm done with this job
basically and that's fine like I don't I
don't have the the craving for it so
it's all good all good it's not the not
thing that makes me unhappier
so I have I have other
problems sometimes I feel
maybe like I I I crave a little bit of
human
interaction like a hug or so but that
can
be resolved by meeting one of my close
friends maybe once a
month PR think it's
a wait what what she what what are they
first open the parade team formation
screen what what what what are we
doing here by pressing the details
button at the top of the
screen you can have an overview of your
parades team abilities you can not only
check the abilities of each town but
also the trophy bonus
[Music]
okay wait is this real share your parade
team on social media like do they
actually is that like cuz it's confusing
is this fourth wall breaking do they
want me to do that on my real social
media or in-game social
media true friends can take care of that
as well yeah that part I can cover with
my
[Music]
friends it's a Cy paste I think is
real real social post your teams do I I
want I want something from that like if
you post your team wants on social media
you get a free scouting ticket or so
that's what I
want please come on that's like the nice
a nice way of
[Music]
um please reward me I mean my tweet
would really boost H parade you know I
got over million
followers gotcha 101 exactly exactly you
can compare skills and the ability side
by side which helps you understand the
strengths and the
weaknesses showus par team yeah yeah
yeah you want you want the
clout yeah no no no not that easily
you're already getting a
stream this game is all about Cloud this
game is literally about Cloud chasing is
it
[Music]
not about money making and Cloud chasing
and becoming famous on the
Internet it's a
[Music]
simulator this woman of Holo Yen for
real for
real that crack was small okay so we
currently have what
it
really that doesn't seem right think we
have 50 why is that on zero shouldn't we
have 100% cuz we have fifth or just 50 I
don't know but what is that how does
that
work cuz 11 that's also where's the
where's the blue where's the blue one I
don't understand how this is being
calculate lat click the trophy icon on
the home screen oh is it from the troph
ah this is extra Buffs from
trophies ah I thought it was like a
calculation of what's up here oh okay
okay okay okay copy not doing anything
with it
though how to take a screen I didn't
even tell you how to take a screenshot
ah
cusa
okay we got to go back in here
uh what to do this weekend maybe go to
music event the parade I saw today was
cool I love parades because how am I
supposed to know what that is supposed
to
be for my
[Music]
strategy how do you
know what's the
ideal you
don't ah the most liked one first of all
maybe looking for the one with the most
likes okay but but then what does this
tell me the cute maybe something popping
cute because parades and cute I don't
know who did the
n and then like here what would
[Music]
I maybe thumnail because visuals I don't
know or
audio who knows really who knows video M
video
[Music]
planning how do you know it's a lot of
guess work we need eventually I guess
maybe there will be some guides popping
up but I guess it's still too early to
really
know me you want
[Music]
a maybe it's like a translation thing
like in Japanese maybe it's pretty
obvious is but in English it's really
[Music]
not maybe I can change the talents why
why aren't they fine I think they're
fine is is their motivation the
21 then they're like one of the highest
so I would say that's
fine video oh I need a video ah video
focused oh maybe this one
19 maybe I can do both focused on video
huh okay
okay strong video
[Music]
team it better be the right thing to
do turn out good okay 67 yeah it matches
the SNS trends
[Music]
oh waku waku doie
doie is this the new
Twitter that will kill X this this how
how whole lives Twitter looks like that
I can't use
yet the Japanese members can already use
but Ian members can't
yet skip
that
10,800 oh not as good as last
time in terms of coins but oh we got a
higher bonus on the followers I think it
wasn't
[Music]
bad and apparently we matched what they
wanted
[Music]
so yeah let's kill
X all right go
next you got way more than before did I
huh I only got e really okay then I
remember it wrong well that's a fast
sheep uh okay oh my God speed
hay kill the Sheep oh my God it's buff
and fast what the hell and the red ones
the red ones are coming ah they're right
at my at my line but I got I got the
Yuki wait yimin are blue [\h__\h] uh-oh
bring more tachis bring more tachis and
well holy [\h__\h] the
spam the spam
though it's okay we're we we're catching
up we're catching up I got the Poo all
everything is fine everybody calm down
we have the
PO and we got the okay okay okay okay
okay yeah I think this stage is kind of
like this is just bound to happen
because the Sheep are so fast and then
they send so many of the red buffed ones
out so it's like kind of bound to happen
that you get like stuck in in this area
but then once you have everything out
everything is fine
easy they're all barking no bite exactly
they now it's more like they're all and
no
bite easy easy
easy that was fast we're really
overpowered right now so I feel like we
don't need to worry too much about level
UPS although I already have 3,000 coins
[Music]
sheesh oh another another Speedy sheep
let's bring out the tank
early yukim mean is strong against Blue
so we can tackle the Sheep
[Music]
takachi also takachi is strong against
anything actually like totally
op
she her the Buffs are like
crazy mama mia Bubba Let's Go
Bubba good coverage yeah
okay I'm waiting for the poo or not
wait got to fix this situation here we
go here we go the moment you bring out
poo you know everything is going to be
fine wait holy [\h__\h] I just noticed the
animation for the yukimen cuz it carries
the alcohol bottle right but I just
noticed it blows fire through the the
the the
bottle it sets the the the bottle on
fire and then she
sh
crazy calm down
[Music]
M to you
too maybe it's fine to save a little a
little bit of money because level ups
are so expensive now and also who knows
maybe I I suddenly get a unit that's
something I want to replace and they're
level one so I have to upgrade them from
from the getg okay we can scout a little
bit
actually I
have uh counter you are five
okay oh wait there's a obtain selection
SC oh if I if I pull 10 more times I get
a uh a ticket where I can actually
choose which one I
want it seems
like get po to level 10 I mean I
understand I get a skill done but so far
do we really did we really need it yet
everything's
[Music]
fine
okay I have a good
feeling no never mind a the DU yay a I
was so sad when I couldn't choose a duck
before but now I can cost
free highly
moai okay good against
[Music]
Blue huh maybe maybe no Sagi cuz I'm
actually using
them oh oh n n
ni
n
[Music]
n close range single attacker cost one
ooh weak foot can be summoned in large
numbers for low cost reduces damage from
Red ores this could be a replacement for
the
noag if we wanted to I want to um
compare
them so no saki has already I I upgraded
like I already had like a second no saki
so their base stats are higher I think a
little
bit has 180 HP 22
attack ah hey how much does a a second
one improve the
[Music]
stats
DPS 8 DPS
11 red ah the thing is the noag doesn't
have any anti- AA
ability while the Neo at least comes
with
something let's at least get it leveled
up oh you're right cuz it wasn't leveled
up so of course it couldn't compare
let's get it to seven or is it
eight okay wait let's get it up to eight
and then we can
compare uh yeah okay so
now 15 153 and
29 oh okay stronger attack than the
noag but a little still a little bit
below in on HP DPS 11 DPS 14 okay now we
have a stronger
one
h ah oh yeah that's the thing they have
different instruments
so but what if we if we get rid of that
flute ah if we get rid of the noaki
flute we have the choice to bring by H
back hatama or we can do a nick nickel
combination which seems to be really
powerful also a strong against
Blue we could replace the noi with low
cost
Kato for example I like that idea wait
wait wait why did I wait it's already
why was it already so highly leveled
what the [\h__\h] I didn't
realize give me back my
money okay so that
means we
replace let's say we replace these that
[Music]
means I it
which oh it's still not double actually
and nickel replac
with how many instruments are there
[Music]
po I do hear good things about the ne it
could
[Music]
work replace yukim Min yeah yeah yukim
Min so weak
man I think I'll I'll try to
dangerous cat with very fast movement
such a dangerous
[Music]
cat it's for support cards and you're
not using them that much The
Shield my that's just true I don't even
get out the sh that
often but and this one's not about
buffing is it or do you mean the the
instrument it
has lead the lead the
Le the Le the Rhythm with sharp tones
while the increasing recovery speed of
support cards while increasing
recovery oh oh not even that
[Music]
good help about help about we do
something crazy here and replace it with
Amame yeah they have the same
instrument maybe we can do this because
the shoko never really seems to be that
vital anyway so
but then I'm going need a little bit Ah
upgrades I can only do one that's
fine drum isn't very good yeah it's okay
I mean we're already so powerful we can
play around a little bit then then you
get your y oh no it's a it's a flag game
but that actually might be good to have
am who
knows where are they they're so
slow
so
slow Taki probably going to die soon
no can't this so fast holy [\h__\h] and it's
so low cost this is
insane stop come down oh my
God it's like a eating anything
oh my God it's too strong I'm I'm I'm
scared I'm scared I'm scared of the cat
it's all okay I I can't it's maybe
better to not bring out the cat because
it's too fast and it does too much
damage she so
violent rabbit
cat uh-oh uh-oh holy [\h__\h] it's
filla
uhoh
uhoh I want to get to am but
uh oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] okay go cat go go cat
[Music]
go how will this one go uh so far it's
okay it doesn't have an aura
right doesn't seem to have an aura
and damage is pretty good pretty
good I'm keeping up oh yeah we're
pushing
back no fine fine easy
easy just wait for No we don't even need
her we can save forit I'm kind of scared
honestly cuz that like with my units are
uh they they're they're like
dying so pretty fast
so I would be kind of terrified to do
that not going to
lie maybe we need yeah I need her I need
her
but I got to keep the symphony up
too wait so the voltage level actually
doesn't go down even if the symphony is
not like kept
stable [\h__\h] the front line behind filla
in front of villa is actually like
really [\h__\h]
strong this is an
issue okay I'll I'll try to wait a
little bit if I
can yeah almost there there almost there
come go please I don't know if you can
really help me in this situation but I
hope you can please let's go
Amy it's your time to
shine they're already at my flag [\h__\h] I
did such good damage to filla before but
then they they created a nice wall in
front of a
Billa oh my god oh [\h__\h] no no they're at
my
flag ah Amy what are you
doing oh oh I got the buff I got the
buff I guess maybe this will be my
comeback maybe I would hope so
[Music]
but
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] no this is this is not happening I
think it's because Amy doesn't do [\h__\h]
why did I get Amy
twice M
Mia this is
not not
[Music]
happening just likes to watch I'm to
blond
broken the team wasn't good I don't
think I need am it didn't help me sorry
maybe
even I don't know what could we
do we could bring back the yukim we
could bring back the
shoko I wonder if it'll make a great
difference with the
[Music]
shield yeah cuz am doesn't do DPS but
with the shield go at least we have some
extra
DPS I'll
try y
canana apparently gets more useful after
stage
four all right let's I think one of my
problems was sending out the nickel too
strong uh too fast as well maybe because
we took down the flag so
early so maybe I should wait a bit more
with that our actually
goal for the super
super dangerous one of having them take
down my flag no please no that should be
my last resort in my
[Music]
opinion okay I'm sending the cat out
now
whatever see what happens cuz they're
pretty far from the flag so yeah and and
it's already dead it dies pretty fast
then we bring out
you V is level six okay
okay and we're at the
flag not a hold
do I guess we're doing
it
I don't know I don't know front line
still very
strong but we got two
poos oh we we cleared the front line
that's pretty important I would
say m m m oh we can bring in a
shield all right V is level
eight hey okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay
it's cleared my front line that's fine
that's fine that's fine thanks for the
pinky what what do I read about
fairies need more
damage yeah I don't know I don't know as
long as they don't get back their strong
ass front line Let Me Wait for I Bo
and then
C more cats more cats yes yes
yes
woohoo that was a
challenge that was a challenge I will
admit m
let's go
PR I'm impressed by how strategically
each video is oh okay this one's kind of
obvious cuz it says something about a
video I guess that would be about
video okay let's go video
and I don't know about this Strate
strategically what is that supposed to
tell me
planning I can only do
one I would say for not many likes on
all posts what what do you
mean ah I would wait until
later until this
[Music]
changes Strat Str strategically
strategically okay okay okay then we'll
[Music]
wait if this level was so difficult I
wonder how difficult will be the next
one it it could go down a little bit
again there's it won't be a flag
level
no ooh fast
ship
H the nickel uh is like kind of
tanking some
reason
oh my
God I thought this might be on the same
level of difficulty roughly as the
previous one but no not at
all can't even
compare level curve kind of
wobbly I mean I'm not
complaining it's
fine Fury exam oh my god let's go
congratulations W that that sounds like
you were under a lot of
pressure this is the last one uh of
stage
two 10 memberships thank
you I wonder if I can do it without any
changes oh I knew it would be a flag
[Music]
level in that case I don't know filla
was kind of
crazy thank you for all the memberships
we're doing weekly membership streams at
the moment so please
[Music]
enjoy at the moment it's like sounds so
temporarily but we're doing it as the
norm now you're
welcome actually let's do Bubba
first
yeah CU nle too strong and too
fast
[Music]
spooky how about now voltage level
six just like smoothie once I'll bring
out some food smoothie is exactly like
that okay what are we who are we meeting
now this is okay I wonder if you guys
understand this reference CU maybe you
saw no ST by streaming uh with a picture
like this
before it's supposed to be a reference
to a famous uh Japanese comedian who
looks like pretty much like this
uh holy [\h__\h] holy
[\h__\h] h y I don't know is this Y is this
y honestly I like that uh it's not a
comedian I guess it's more like a
personality or something a mix in
between I think I'm going to die this
pretty uh but I really like her she's
she's got some strong opinions and is uh
yeah very very
entertaining uh y y y
y
y yeah yeah okay not a hold do we need
red and uh black very
urgently not
a that was not it yeah it's fine we can
change up the team a little bit yeah
I'll make a new
team m perfect actually the the Neco
stays uh as it is quite
[Music]
fitting let's get as much red and and
purple I guess as possible takoi can
stay um the night
maybe
hot maybe since it is a flag I can save
up for hatama hatama would help with the
black
aura
[Music]
wouldn't
she
maybe oh wait I got to look at the
instruments oh so far so far it's
fine the black bird has 100% red Aura
black bird you mean this one oh okay
okay this one's the
backpack what no wait it's not a back it
looks like a Lando L me I thought it was
a backpack it was a it's a
drum okay
[Music]
M coron scheme is also
100% but I I don't I don't have them
leveled uh black and red right we need
to bring you in oh
oops but ah they're both
drums would you say that is
forgivable shoko is the different kind
of drums shoko we could still bring
shoko I don't know I don't know if this
a good
balance this is oh that instrument I
actually don't have you know what I'll
give it a
try I I'll give it a
try with the koniski uh where'd you go
here cuz
then we didn't have it yet right
yeah pirate defense oh it does okay okay
but then the only red uh black one we
have is oh wait we got two okay
okay how about this
[Music]
team can't level up though we'll
see just kind of FR together whatever
works Japanese bro says I shouldn't go
for coroni I wonder
why hat
we have to save up for hatama but it
will be hopefully worth it
tantama
okay it should be better than before but
H our instruments
are very overlapping to
[Music]
overlap V's level
four it's okay it's okay it's okay we're
doing fine Ah that's the same
okay same
same oh okay I won't get another voltage
level until I bring out hat which I'm
not going to
do
okay let
go two of theone means stronger but I
guess so so it's not necessarily
bad okay we're just slowly slowly slowly
uh getting our motivation up that's fine
while we're not even doing that much
damage on the flag that's
fine this is fine
place your bets now I could already
afford haima but I'm not going to do
[Music]
it
o they're pushing me now this is
unacceptable oh [\h__\h] I brought maybe I
used Too Much m
okay okay I think it's about
[Music]
time okay go tant tan let's
go I'm so scared I'm so scared I'm so
scared I'm so scared I'm so scared I'm
so scared I'm so scared I'm so
scared I can't even look at the HP or
anything what's going up here I I can't
even look at it because I'm too busy
down here and looking at these things
trying to balance them okay oh actually
that doesn't matter anymore [\h__\h] they're
killing me ah it's over it's over it's t
over D well it is the last stage of
level two so or stage two the last level
of stage two so I I'm not surprised I
can bring out another hot if you wait a
little
bit no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no push back push back push back come
on more morei
more
no it's all over it's over
D not
wantable going to
bring but then I would probably have to
give up
uh
[Music]
hatama and I don't know that for for how
much she's bringing me against black uh
Aura I don't think that is worth it time
to Scout and pray okay I only have one
ticket
[Music]
though oh two new ones though cost two
cost six close range single attacker
sometimes blocks enemy attacks
occasionally knocks back black Ora
enemies
occasionally self-destruct that's uh
AOE it but what on
impact so it dies like pretty much
immediately but it costs
six better do a lot of I guess it does
the base damage being
[Music]
insane let's we can we can like get them
but I don't know if I'll put them to the
team Rose Knights ah I didn't get Rose
Knights yet do doo What's wrong with the
team I don't know was koniski even doing
anything this is also AOE though AOE
pretty
good
[Music]
maybe if we replace someone maybe some
what what instrument is ah then okay we
should not lose another instr or like
overlap oh but wait it
is ah this one I already have double
anyway so it's like either this one or
this one we
replace if we want to make use of it
strong but squishy haven't had much luck
got Idols they really help oh I really
didn't did I man add kotoni and
[Music]
Ami can't even level it up it's on level
five replace the ghost of the
ghost that's like two high cost things I
didn't even gain that
much let's try to replace another one
that's like double so we can get higher
Symphony
stuff but I want to keep those
two because looking at the effects it's
pretty
strong
[Music]
or this
no replace
with how about Shield Co but the shield
Co is also really expensive
I would prefer to get back the
PO we didn't have
po why do we get rid of
Po let's let's bring Po and
[Music]
then I mean it would be good to
have cuz our only purple one coverage is
this
one baa for inst
true but
[Music]
like choose increasing attack
power happy birthday congratulations oh
thank you you're looking pretty nice too
pretty depper Mah Mah happy
birthday new
father I'd say
bubba instead
of
maybe what does that do anyway this one
increase motivation recovery oh that's
pretty good all right whatever let's
[Music]
try let's
go this one looks good you think so
remove it I did I'm scared Jo I'm scared
because the only other buff one we had
besides the Knight was the
ichim I think but we'll
see we'll
[Music]
see at least now we have a full rooster
of symphony effects
again
mhm oh
[Music]
dear wait so it said like uh oh is that
18% 15 what is that percentage bound to
how many Bubbas I have on the field
or now it's
18 oh
yeah can I even get am at this
point ah the buff
level
ah
I'm waiting a little
bit sitting it out a little bit right
now
D wait I can't wait for
am that will be another waiting for my
stream
I'm dead
already so no way why is she already
dead I'm man on the field and not doing
[\h__\h] might need a new Ur for this one
[\h__\h] I'm like so stuck F I need a
stronger Talent
[Music]
than I also don't have money to level
them up so yeah
okay wait parades featuring skilled
musicians are becoming popular in kma in
GMA
[Music]
prefecture uh skilled musicians
audio
popular
[Music]
in local Affairs kind of because that's
pretty local and it's about
music so
audio the great out ones are too tired I
suppose o am is good for
audio and the ssrb let's
go should be pretty good if if
everything goes well
let them break your flag first don't
break their flag
[Music]
first matches perfectly okay this could
go
viral
B I think it's viral did it go would it
tell me
[Music]
b
5,000 might be too low level no way I
want to finish that stage though oh wait
I just noticed okakoro
look at okakoro
Okay then if we level someone up it
should be someone that's actually going
to help us in this fight uh I heard we
should level up
[Music]
PO obtain skill but it's like random
right oh
[Music]
then oh well that won't help us actually
that's sad gold attack cuz there was one
no one there was no one
gold so the skills are just the New Aura
abilities or or one of
these reset levels to get coins
oh oh I need one milk for
that I don't know I'm if that's really
necessary right
now you can use a not using use that oh
I get that way of using it h
not anyway we're going to replace am but
with who maybe get the ghost back oh but
it's the same instrument Let's get
someone who doesn't have the same
instrument flute do we have a FL yeah we
have a flute do we have this we don't
have this
one but this one's not
leveled oh a sh let's just bring back
Sho maybe we
can max out
sh uh max out like get it to level
[Music]
oh this one's also gold defense ah man
o why not
black why not
[Music]
black how about Tacko thaty
upgrades I mean it already had blue and
red and it also gets gold what I thought
it was random why does everybody get
gold what the
hell Bubba probably worth
it black okay thank you
[Music]
10% ah one
more let me really quickly play the
money
[Music]
game that she has black
too was it it was either black or red
missing I
think how my upgrade yeah wait I just
got to quickly get get some money
here please I need I need
your you got to make bank for me I need
your
power please help me out here I'm in a
very dire
situation well pretty good so
[Music]
far
oh nice jumps can't believe I'm actually
doing
[Music]
it nice what the I never did this so
well
before my eyes hurt I'm
squinting you little [\h__\h] I hate you I
hate you go away a
[Music]
okay ah no it was going so well but at
the end I I was stumbling because it was
hard to
recover that's fine that's
fine [\h__\h] okay I was going to uh
upgrade you One More
Level please
be wait it already says here that I'm
going to get gold oh
Maga why why so much gold
what wa hat is only level five oh sorry
I need some more
[Music]
money
in bad God shots for real red or but she
has black or front line yeah which can't
be hit without block pacing units I only
pass because of the you are at out
range oh you are you mean a like a
special character like
am try older stages for trophy
oh I guess if I'm really desperate
[Music]
stupid
[\h__\h]
me why oh nice
[Music]
jumps oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah
ah ah it hurts
I want
why no I went up too far [\h__\h] this
makes me so this is so rage
inducing this is so rage
[Music]
inducing ah God damn
it I know I know I know I know I know I
I have a personal goal for the stream
today that I want to clear this one
stage because then I'm done with
non-stop story before that I can
unfortunately not end the
stream
sadly okay at least she's level seven
now that might help let's try again um
we changed the team too right this is
not the same as before is it and
everybody got like gold now which is not
helpful the only one that was helpful
was this one but only
10%
y oh guaranteed you are
true oh
well I'll try one more time
[Music]
I know I can use the milk but I'm not
sure if it's worth it cuz I don't know
how how rare rare the milk will be
[Music]
afterwards maybe I'll wait for seven
because Bubba helps with the
motivation I mean having a dog around
you a cute dog will obviously have some
real
motivation I would be so motivated
too just makes sense here we go V level
[Music]
five
oh [\h__\h] we're going for it I don't I
don't really want
to don't really want
to ah I'm not ready do I look ready to
you I'm not
oh
man oh man oh man I don't know I don't
know is it better than before or worse
guys you guys are probably actually
looking at this part of the screen
so you might have a better
idea I think it's a bit better cuz I'm
actually at her front now
but they're still pushing really
hard ah
MAA yeah I I rushed too early I mean I
didn't want to but it
happened
I'll get another buff though when they
take down the the
flag so I'm not going to give
up
yet try to take me
down
try oh they did already okay the flag is
gone it doesn't even get give such a big
buff
honestly and T dies pretty fast
too
no no no
no
no I feel
like D's it's we're close we're close to
figuring it
out
[Music]
restart I'm not trying to rush but I'm
just trying to get the voltage up like
how do I do how do I get the voltage up
without
[Music]
rushing
maybe that's too
strong that's too
strong why didn't I summon
poo poo is too strong
[Music]
oh just die
Bo die why are you so strong why are you
doing this all
alone why are you
single-handedly defending my
base oh my God
the oh oh
my oh my God
okay now we got we just level five
that's good
right PO is dead
so this is Fine 37 it's okay it's okay
we we're we have I did it right I just
wanted to get the the only reason I
spent so many at once was because I
waited for po before I did that but I
also wanted to get uh a higher this
level
[Music]
six ah wait poo was a mistake Poyo was a
mistake
but Bubba for the regen
just don't attack don't don't attack the
FL okay I have
to here I have it
already full
attack
no they flag guys I'm
tanks you know
what you know what maybe
I'll I'll I'll let him kill this
wave
oh I killed the only one what
the wait maybe uh although we've been to
this point
before right where we only
had we've been there m haven't
we it's okay you I I let them destroy
the flag
now just have Bubba out for the the read
gen even even if it's just
[Music]
3% need to reach motivation level
80 yeah even even like this it's
tough
uhhuh I can't do it I can't do it I
can't do it the looks is so tanky need
boils I know although it is effective to
balance your forces to increase
motivation but be careful as enemy stats
will increase every minute
the the N
the I can't I can drag it up the enemy
stat increase rate is displayed below
the
timer
um doio is the team not good enough I
mean yeah but like what else do I have
right
oh you need a Healer I don't think I
have a
Healer get voltage to five save until
your flag can spam tanks and shield
okay
okay well is level five spam tanks
something like
that
wait what was uh can you say that again
V level
five wh what what was that what did you
say
[Music]
then she can only attack one unit at a
time try to abuse the fact that she can
only Attack One un save until your flag
dieses okay so after volage level five I
save until my flag flag f F FL what are
we what are we missing a takoi okay what
is level five flag fly fle flow
flu okay I'm
saving I'm not doing anything I just had
to get it up to level five they're just
strong come the
BBA stay alive as long as you can okay
that's
fine
okay and then uh shield and tanks which
my only tank really is this one right
what would you consider as a tank
besides
that I guess poo right poo would be also
pretty
good sh
[Music]
poo
T
[Music]
KN Bubba's a bit
tanky
[Music]
everything
okay okay
I
mean I don't know if this will work I
don't
know can we do
it more hot
some we
try oh wait we are doing it wait wait
wait we are doing it
a you
got oh my
god oh thank you for leading me to this
point
oh you know I just I just thought volage
level five is not really good enough but
it was what is this what is
this no
what you can get it in the
gacha so I guess you can get anything
that you fight in the
gacha ah it was
tough thank you for helping H
what I got the trophy too
yay ol is becoming more and more popular
lately indeed I'm finally getting used
to having so many
followers well then I think it's time to
go on to the next steps let's open the
parade screen
[Music]
beyond the stage from this button you
can now access the tour selection
screen
oh Tokyo course sound amazing this is a
result of everyone's daily efforts
currently we're only touring within toky
but in the future we can go larer tours
okay how are tours different from
regular parades Basics are the same but
you'll be uh attempting several parades
con consecutively oh parades will be far
more challenging as any and or will
change each time you try sounds fun but
also seems you need to be more prepared
ts are more difficult instead of parades
however you will receive Awards even if
you failed oh well that's
nice
she you can obtain more coins than
regular parades and the probability of
picking up Scout tickets is also a
little higher so you can try over and
over again to quickly upgrade your
parade a well you know what I really
care about right now is The Scouting
because I deserve I can't believe it's a
you
are at this
point I can't believe I'm getting
another
pity I I didn't get no that's not that's
not cool that's not cool don't get me on
there I will kill you I will deinstall
this
game don't
[Music]
Bey
now you
are
that I've been trying so
hard with only
AIT is my so to say supposedly
strong
character and this is how you reward me
[Music]
that's so rude that's
so nah
mm- nah I'm so angry I want to
cry I love Al but that's just not
cool that's [\h__\h] up
I why
[Music]
I worked so hard to get another got you
are wait I guess I'm have to choose her
[\h__\h]
H I'll do one
more okay I mean you're not seeing it
but I'm just going going to go for
another nickel a nickel not
[Music]
Niel that's
unbelievable that's just un
[Music]
unbelievable what the
hell
why why am why is she asking me to
collab is that why she's so
needy does she want to collab with
me
why actually wild
[Music]
right Grand in a road that's like one in
a million in a million this a sign there
a sign
she loves me right that's what what's
telling me right just means that she
loves me very much and I should take
that in a positive
light and this way at least I'll
probably get another clip from the
resident Amic
[Laughter]
Clipper do it for the content they say
do it for the clout they
[Music]
say the question really isn't
am the question is am why I'm
na a
man it was fun though the game was
really fun uh I want to play again but I
did say I will uninstall the
game so so I didn't think this would
happen so now I'm kind of
stuck [\h__\h] man I'm you have put me in a
very difficult spot I have to deinstall
the game because of
you how how can we fix this huh I guess
I can uninstall and then reinstall it I
didn't say I I I wouldn't reinstall
it but that's so [\h__\h] up I'm so
mad like I'm playing with
a uh uh a
[Music]
handicap okay update her to be better
and then it might be fun make her do
some
damage some damage ell
[Music]
pull better
units can you imagine if we wouldn't
have gotten so many dupes we could have
had free myth
members how great would have that been
to see free myth members
HH how happy you were when you first got
her what happens to that feeling
well the fact is I I don't need more
than one am in the world because uh she
she can't be copy pasted anyway and it's
impossible one am already reaches
greatness and there that cannot
be you know there can't be more than
that I do get the selection soon yeah
but I shouldn't have been put in such a
in such a situation where I get so
desperate
this not fair [\h__\h] gcha I hate gcha
okay I will rate super
[Music]
chats I have to stop thinking about this
this makes me too
angry this makes me to
[Music]
angry why why is my ride screen like
glitching so much the windows are are
flickering only two of them though not
even all of them um well it's only when
I Tab out of it I
think and Super Chat time I guess we're
reading the ones from the from a Mario
Super Mario RPG stream I watched uh
dendo my favorite German
YouTuber play uh until the end of the
game and I did not know that kolx had a
fre D version after all once you kill KX
once you go back and you can fight him
again he's stronger but he'll be in free
D I didn't know I was like saying oh
it's so sad he'll never be in
3D turns out he does become free d but
then you kill him and then he turns back
to 2D which is kind of sad
[Music]
too I didn't know I didn't
no no yeah I think oh it might be after
you kill yeah after you finish the game
chat was trying to tell
me I don't know somehow you didn't get
the point
across you ignore this just like this
sorry sorry I don't know I have
selective
Vision yeah I didn't want to do boss
rematch ah wait so you can only do it if
you rematched all the other bosses oh I
wouldn't have wanted to do that but it's
nice to see it somewhere else that he
got a
3D uh version of himself what the [\h__\h]
it's it's flickering so hard I hate it
but I'm going to film it and maybe you
guys can tell me I'll upload it on
Twitter oh now you stop flickering
really you little [\h__\h] flicker flicker
for
[Music]
me oh now the chat is
flickering okay you're flickering right
now guys oh now you
stopped I'll I'll upload that later I
tried to find like solution
before but I couldn't find the same
issue on
Google Now it stopped
again I had before yeah but then I
didn't have it for a long time and
yesterday it started again I don't even
understand
why
[Music]
okay h e
d uh unknown thanks for the red of chat
it's my birthday today for December oh I
can't believe this is already my fourth
birthday as a chicken I can't believe it
either oh my God and happy I'll get to
spend it watching your stream thank you
for always giving us the best content
wow I love you so much now I feel kind
of bad that I took how many hours was
that stream so many hours of your
birthday oh [\h__\h] no it's flashing both
let me film that really quickly oh it
stopped again what the [\h__\h] why why why
why why I'll keep my my phone out in the
open I was saying uh what was I saying
oh yeah I feel kind of bad like I don't
know it was great you say that but I
feel bad like taking so much time of
your birthday and you just like
basically like you know watching my
stream all day I mean that's fun for you
but I feel kind of bad
[Music]
oh
man well thank you thank you for staying
in the kfp for so long I'm I'm you know
I I always am very realistic about how
long people stay in a fandom because I I
also the creators that I
follow I don't like some of them I think
D tendo I've been watching for a long
time now but others I also just stopped
watching out after a while cuz I got
bored that's like a really normal thing
and yet you're still here and and I I
don't take that for granted just so you
know thank you so so much and happy
happy birthday happy birthday to you
happy birthday bloody helmate happy
birthday to you happy birthday unkknown
and let's go m m m m m
m thank you so much imagine getting
bored I don't know I feel like it's
totally like I mean there's certainly
others who have had that experience and
that's fine cuz like you know following
the same Creator every day hours and
hours cuz like maybe one of the reasons
I don't get tired of dendo is because
like I don't consume him as much because
he just doesn't he's not a streamer just
uploads like 30 minute videos once per
day or twice per
day maybe it's like the fact that it's
not over
overloading or so but I don't I don't
like I feel like his personality is
like the personality is important I
think cuz one of the creators that I was
following for a while was like a Sims
YouTuber um at first I thought it was
like really entertaining but eventually
I
realized they just talk way too fast and
way too much and I noticed things that I
didn't notice before which is I guess
like when when like the same thing as
when you like marry or date someone and
then you realize the things that you
liked before and now bother you but uh
yeah like I notice that that person that
YouTuber interrupts themselves all the
time they never finish sentences and it
triggered me so
[Laughter]
hard and then I just I just
couldn't couldn't watch it anymore just
the even the video content like whatever
they were doing on there didn't interest
trust me either
anymore
yeah yeah yeah you see change or you you
you just see things differently what
shiy does shiy do
that does shiy not finish your sentences
why you guys mentioning
shieldy of course it wasn't
shy since it's actual interaction more
connection to
stay I I can see how that will be a
factor to stay but at the same time
that's also dangerous to rely on that
because as much as I'd like and I try to
give you all a lot of attention and read
as many comments as I can and interact
with you guys on Twitter as much as I
can when it doesn't happen and and then
you feel like very sad about it
well that's bad too she is is just a
stream of Consciousness she jumps around
topics oh really she doesn't finish her
sandwiches
really well I I'm not saying that would
bother me with
everybody with any person it just
bothered me with that specific uh
YouTuber and and just generally oh my
God it was just too much and then I got
tired of them and I stopped watching and
I even unsubscribed
H unfortunately
oh she only I I can imagine she would be
a great Girls Talk guest oh by the way I
did finally set up a
uh a date for the ENA outfit uh review
or showcase thingy for Advent
outfits finally have a date but we got
to prepare we got to like draw the
outfits and all that so it's not like
next week I think it's maybe
M after Christmas I
think and then speaking of
Christmas I'm having I was I've been
trying to plan something but I've been
kind of having some
[Music]
problems I I don't really it's like a
lot of complicated stuff behind the
scenes so I I don't want to drag you
guys into that
[Music]
um but
yeah
we we'll see I I don't want to say
anything yet I'm still trying to get
something to work
um I do have a backup
plan uh for like a special you know full
generation old Generations uh Christmas
come together get
[Music]
together but it's just not looking so
good right now but I do have a backup
plan as I said it's just not the IDE one
we'll see I I'll figure something
[Music]
out thank you thank you anyway back to
the super chats yeah happy birthday
unknown thank you on to the fifth
birthday yeah hope we can celebrate that
together
[Music]
too no no I mean yeah I'm not streaming
on Christmas but uh I would uh want it
to be a day before or a day
after
[Music]
thank you for the stream well thank you
for
watching for myth collab would be a rare
treat yeah but I just I don't know I
felt like um I I wanted to plan
something that has like all gens ideally
um uh and I wanted to take like all the
work and pressure off of am so I don't
think she was planning anything any
anyway so just kind of like with her
support in the back I've been trying to
get something up and
running for all of
us but yeah obviously it's more
difficult to do something for all of us
than doing something for just one
generation
mhm very
[Music]
difficult
uh the Advent calendar yeah the Advent
calendar so uh it's been going
smoothly so
far so all is
well actually I only have like two or
three more days that I need to fill with
uh either a solo or unit
video uh and yeah I've just been like
like keeping up with them like reminding
them hey so your video is up in 2 days
or one day or
so I think today's is wait let me let me
check really
quick today's is prepared right right
right right
right uh
scheduling the 6th oh yeah okay I have
6th and seventh
ready and yeah eighth is not ready yet
but I know it will
be yeah yeah I think it'll be fine well
you'll be
fine yeah I I I
prepped and reminded everyone early
enough
so yeah I'm trying to take some
responsibility off of am that um she
doesn't have but she might feel I'm
thinking that maybe she feels that way
uh or like other people have that
expectation it's like the problem that
she so far always was doing these bigger
projects
so uh and like often would like surprise
us with whatever she's planning like
suddenly hey I'm planning this please
join so maybe some other members just
like have this uh expectation so to say
that amma's probably going to plan
something but then when she isn't and it
turns out nobody was planning anything
uh surprise nothing is happening I don't
want that to happen so I that's what why
I've been trying to step
up I do feel like
um I am like number two in planning big
collaps for us so I I generally enjoy it
and um I don't mind it it's just like
the fact that VR
collaps are not my forte about my strong
suit you know so that's why I've been uh
just having a on the sidelines in case I
I don't know something or need her help
a little bit uh yeah and that's also why
I've been like kind of scared to tackle
something like
that but ideally I would want to do
something in VR for Christmas because I
feel like that's just like where the
greatest moments happen and it's just
always so interesting to
watch to see us all move a little bit in
3D more or less some on desktop mode
some in actual VR but you know it's it's
always pretty cute so far it created
always great moments so ideally I would
want to do that and I also was like
hoping to reuse the old world the old uh
winter world that we had so that it's
not you know
just uh collecting dust just used once
spent lots of money on on it and used
once and never using again I don't want
that so I would reuse it and then like
um uh add some new ideas and so
on but I'm running out of time and
there's some like at the moment I'm at a
at a point where it's just
like early early early planning because
there's a certain thing that is like
blocking me from planning
it
um and that's going slowly
so I'm scared
honestly yeah well well we'll see how it
goes we'll see how it goes more sock
puppets I need I need to remind jenma to
sent me my sock
[Music]
puppets
a oh oh my God uh
[Music]
m
since I
just came
[Music]
back sorry I had to write something to
uh JMA JMA
JMA so uh where were we blah blah blah
blah blah alar D chocolate insic thanks
for the pinky hey boss thanks for being
the best Phoenix ever it was fun seeing
you anime NYC oh thank you you were
there y
y I'm happy to hear from
you uh I have another convention coming
up this weekend and this one's actually
with a me and green so I'm a bit nervous
about it but it's nice to see you guys
M maybe this time I'll ask someone to
record the audio from the um
audience because I always regret it so
much and I can't hear it while I'm
[Music]
singing you were in the front near the
front y good job good job cuz like uh
it's such a small space right at the
booth getting to the front you must have
did you wait did you like go early to
the booth and watch watch the panels
before weren't we the first we were even
the first or the last panel I think but
weren't
we don't remember I was at the front for
n nyc2 pong you crazy chicken oh we were
last so you probably you guys were
waiting since like a panel or two
beforehand you stayed at the boo all day
honestly if you go there for whole life
mostly then that's totally
understandable and legit like why would
you check out anything else these panels
are exclusive they don't get streamed
anywhere I mean yeah you could watch it
on VR I guess but this is like a special
experience so I I understand why why
would you go anywhere
else
[Music]
why it was right at the front entrance
ooh nice
position okay I I just burped in
inside without opening my mouth did you
hear it I hope you didn't hear it I
didn't even hear it my headphones are
too
strong
okay you want to hear no you will never
hear no I'm a lady
okay a lady doesn't
burp morally IM moral D miss you D thank
you mathin d Sean r d for the pinky
thanks for streaming on my birthday you
too oh my God there's so many care fees
that share a birthday I'm now 29 and as
i gaze into the unknown Abyss ahead of
me that is my
30s I find myself nervous of the future
M therefore I request this on to Curr
thanks for the fre years can be forever
oh well you know don't you know actually
normally I only sing for red but that's
okay I'll sing for you because I I
somehow um understand your feelings
happy birthday to
you why would why do we get older
boo but gather we can
gather all the love in our shoe happy
birthday Sean
R
yay yay
congratulations
[Music]
yay H almost 30 huh one more
year ah that does seem
terrifying the age of 30 is in theand
who told you that Mar
[Music]
Senpai it's great you say you think it's
great a
I'm happy that it's like good for you
spoiler nothing
changes really don't you gain like 50%
of
uh no 10% you gain 10%
depression 15%
skin gets
[Music]
older
[\h__\h] like that 20% uh uh posture and
general body
uh
status wors since
joints and the rest is like
[Music]
random deterioration that's what I was
looking for yeah
it's like a GTA yeah the rest is
[Music]
GTA eternally dying let's go these bus
Debs are passive you don't gain them all
at once upon level up that's not how it
works in the are you sure are you sure
really I feel like you didn't read the
manual
correctly
Jacob
47 J cgar 48 the CL artist oh thanks for
the
[Music]
membership D and Jerry hon D and bad
ghost D and spank and hi thank you for
the red of chat I was in an idol meeting
so I missed it but believe it or not
some of us from the 1960s are still
alive we were just talking about age
sorry sorry sping I'm
[Music]
sorry emotional damage am I
right SP are you still here I'm so sorry
I'm so
sorry we're all young we're all py
pey in
Japanese we're all fresh and and uh
flexible and elastic our skin is elastic
like rubber we're all uh beautiful no
matter how old we are anyway we're all
uh not graying hair at all no no totally
that is if anything um just a reflection
of light and it's just just an
imagination we we don't don't have any
skin
imperfections
[Music]
no hope we're all convinced now just
keep on telling
yourself yeah thank you it's spank inhe
I hope I I I I I don't like make you
feel like negatively or anything about
that
sorry love to D Bron D D golden I D le
KN thank you for the red super chat oh
did you change your profile
picture I'm very happy to be able to
give my first ever red support to my
Kami thanks for always sharing me up and
I'm down you're so sweet and
entertaining oh looking forward to
spending more time with you st thank you
me too I'm looking forward to that too
thank you so much for the support and M
much love to you so generous thank you
what I don't even know what prompted you
first ever R to B chat but I appreciate
it very
much you're also cheering me up
so one hand shakes the other or
something like that I don't know thank
you for one of my very few Canadian fans
M the best the best of the
best I just wanted to
thank
you dude loves his Wawa I love my
[Music]
dude Canadians rise up Canadians where
you
at
the feel more thanks to the pinky I just
watched your performance in ch s for
life and it look pretty complicated but
you guys all nailed it nice job T thank
you yeah that one was pretty fun fun
thank you I'm so happy to be part of it
m got to dance with some cutie patooties
some cute
girls the song was really
difficult but wow I nailed it I I really
hope I can make more appearances in
other people's 3D lives next year that
would be an honor for me I I never say
no almost almost unless it's like really
hard for me to be there on the recording
[Music]
date I did have to turn something down
this
year uh that's unfortunate but it
happens you
[Music]
know cuz also like I have to pay for it
myself you know for the trip and it
takes up time it takes up money and is
stressful and going just for one or two
days makes absolutely no sense when I
need to fly over for like 14 hours 15 16
17 honestly last time it was
17 uh and a half or something like that
so that's just like yeah crazy crazy so
like from a logistical and logical point
of view is I just can't be in that many
but it's always great if I can combine
something with a another trip
[Music]
M yeah yeah
yeah yeah the cobal thing was
perfect yes yes yes so glad I could do
that I wouldn't have turned it down
because like birthday and anniversaries
and all
that is a bit different from being
invited to someone's debut showcase
especially someone that I was like
really close to
already I I would have never turned it
down I had to
go but yeah these things are like out of
our own
pockets and I wouldn't even like ask
them to pay for it it's not our culture
it's not how we do
things we all appear at each other's uh
concert 3D thingies more or less for
free
[Music]
so yeah it will always be a memory
yeah a good
memory a great
[Music]
memory not
you glad you made good
memories thank
you thank
you you had a lot of fun time with the
girls to makes me hi for B yeah [\h__\h]
yeah so excited it might actually be
earlier than than I would um thought it
would be for next year we already kind
of roughly decided on the
month and I didn't think it would be
like that early in the
year I mean it's not like right away but
yeah it's in the first half of the
[Music]
Year
exciting
Yoo okay anyway yeah thanks for the
pinky H see
[Music]
me that was a p right
p
H I'm my my my Korean skills are
deteriorating oh
[Music]
P close
enough space
[Music]
wonderful ah
oh yeah oh god
[Music]
um
my mama
mia
uh five Super chats of some
scientific
uh
yeah
uh t t uh t
ldr uh
time time
and room
what time and what is
anyway space yeah is not uh same or it's
not no is is it is same it is same same
I don't know what I was saying back then
but it is the same
apparently thank you for uh doing the
research space
[Music]
waterfall I don't know what was I
arguing I don't even remember what my
argument
[Music]
was t m thank you for the red of chat my
payday was recently so I can afford to
spend a little more let's go I had your
stream in the background to play a new
game and your presentence has been a
nice check on my S cuz the game made me
go crazy I'm done now I'm just going to
enjoy the res stream did I ask you and
did you answer me what game that
was thank you for spending some of your
extra money on me by the way thank you
so much I am really really really
honored for your generosity D so much
and yeah I always keep your company
whenever you want so just turn on the
WWA maybe even if I'm not live then just
turn on a VOD battle brothers oh okay I
don't know that game what is that battle
brothers
oh tactical role playing game developed
blah blah
[Music]
blah it looks not like something I would
want to play although I mean it's not
the worst it's it's more likely than me
playing uh certain other games I
[Music]
guess
yeah I reacted to the GTA 6 trailer
yesterday at the beginning of my
stream I did I
[Music]
did anyway thank you tasim if it
triggers you too hard if it tilts you
too hard if it makes you go crazy too
hard how about playing Holo
parade it's certainly something well I
hope you still like
it couple cap thank you soon looking for
the dun moral imoral dun mafin aun C
pangin dun you're still here happy to
see you mafin a d scanner Dan scanner
Dan 723
Dani scanner Dan Theo artist d random
guy D thank you I appreciate it I I
brute forc KX I did Jim Tracy D M eight
thanks for the pinky congrat on your
second fight fasy
CL glad you remembered the mobile thing
at the start I did next stream will be
the last but this has been pretty fun so
far good luck thank you very much it has
been a blast
[Music]
yeah Final Fantasy they
say who knows when I'll clear a finally
finally Final Fantasy game again it
might be a while so you got to be
patient G D golden i d that I lurked
mainly during the first year but like
your since Deb your whole time with aqua
impressed me so much oh I feel like I
read this in the moment thank you R free
d lettuce tomato D Chris D and Elsie La
D the
coupon I don't know what to use it for
I'll I'll I'll try to keep it in mind
you have to Remind Me Maybe in the
future that I have a
coupon El
[Music]
Lain ah that was all the super chats
from
here yeah free clip from Elsie lapen
laen Len
Len
hey
the GTA stream had no super chats this
there's another Super Mario stream that
has a bit more than the ones I just
[Music]
read you know what I'll read the ones
from today
first she can't do that she can't just
jump
over no
way or did you guys
wait you didn't you didn't do
[Music]
okay that looks
good it's illegal out of order she does
a Skippy
scoop what a Twist oh my God just does
what she wants such a rebel right such a
[\h__\h] Rebel wait it doesn't show
up I have to refresh right yeah okay
here it
is look
[Music]
guys
just thank you
zly D
soon thank you oh Independence Day for
finished chickens oh nice Rocka de
Sandra thanks for the pinky
oh haven't had one in a while Ki let's
say that whole life has recently won a
battle against a great evil during the
battle G was turned into
a a talking
blanket and is staying with you how
desperate are to turn GAA back to normal
and would you use her as a
blanket I would use her as a blanket
until I can turn her back um I wouldn't
even be so desperate to turn her back I
would probably go really really like
easy uh around that because GAA probably
wouldn't mind being a talking
blanket as long like she can still talk
that's like amazing amazing conditions
so she'll probably enjoy
it I mean and she would be forced to
cuddle with me but she would also be
forced to cuddle with my
cats I feel like she'd enjoy it until
they start
kneading the blanket that would probably
hurt really
badly so she shouldn't be too uh
comfortable as a blanket cuz then they
would destroy
her
um but yeah so I wouldn't be so stressed
out about any of that that sounds like
an interesting thing to happen I might
want that to
[Music]
happen
yeah that's like one of the best prompts
you've ever given me cuz there's nothing
bad about
it pyro home for the py I don't know
what to say but I must say something so
ramble
time good that you acknowledge that you
have to write something Ki will always
be Ohi I excellently through the
Forbidden Alchemy of giving money to
artist spawned a second or she oh thank
God it's just another W I can't promise
more than 10%
nonf
what you mean within that foxy waa only
10% are
human that's barely anything that's just
like a fox with with maybe human
eyes is that what you're
saying my
God how how am I even supposed to use
that as a
thumbnail but it's okay you're just
commissioning stuff for yourself right
it's for your own pleasure it's not for
me to use it for thumbnails in the end
that's just a good side effect that I
normally get oh you meant it that way
that you commissioned 20 and a 4% of her
okay okay I was wondering if it's maybe
that way
around where I yeah for Starbucks
2o uh we have a nor regian Forest cat oh
my God I love
them oh yeah uh thank you pyro 20
commissions 20 you you just gave up 20
commissions that's so much I'm looking
forward to them thank you I'm
excited
yay let's go let's
go
ah over this whole year ah okay okay so
how many are
[Music]
missing
[\h__\h] six oh o I wonder if they'll be
ready before
2024 oh my
God I just said
it the next year will be
in like 24
[Music]
days it will be 2024 oh that's
funny
2024 2023 already sounds so crazy how is
it already going to be
2024 the
[Music]
[\h__\h] I don't want to I don't W
to I'm still my mind is still in like
maybe 2022 I could I could even say
[Music]
oh oh but wait holy [\h__\h] can you imagine
I started whole life in 2020 and now
it'll be almost
wo wo
[Music]
wao
M all right um moving
[Music]
on holy moly
right ttim thanks for the pinky I passed
my favorite examp to SK celebrations
super chats and memberships in coming
thank you so
much
cration times come on oh no I thinkig
celebrate Good Good Times not
celebration time
right
Cate Good Times come
on thank you for being so generous yo
today was another big influx of members
thanks to you as well thank you thank
you and
congratulations what was it about the
fairy exam you probably told me before
but I don't remember so please remind me
Jacob 47 D Anon m d for the red super
chat and happy
birthday wait a second I'm looking at
the
chat isn't it celebration times I'm not
sure I feel like I always thought oh it
was driving license let's go yeah right
so I was I was thinking I heard a about
that like the other
day that's why we talked about
Cy
[\h__\h] ah today's my birthday happy to see
you on this day cuz you look especially
cute with those animal ears and glasses
I do don't
[Music]
I thank you I was feeling like a cat
today thank you Anon do you like cats
meow meow meow meow Anton meow instead
of
[Music]
mow a per perat
kiss cute cutest really an
waa thank
you thank you thank you well well happy
birthday to you happy birthday to you
M happy
birthday and
your shoes
to happy birthday to
[Music]
you hey
congratulations I hope you are treating
yourself to something special for your
birthday okay I want you to treat
yourself to something nice cuz you you
deserve
it Richard steal than soon
and oh that was almost what we did you
are Dan I am a cheap beep Dan spider Dan
Richard steel Dan M A
than I I I watched I watched all the re
um matches they were kind of crazy yeah
take Monkey D lunchbox D Prince of denm
thanks for the pinky I'm excited for
anime Frontier you'll be there and
terrified of being there I hope to see
the panel with my kfp shirt and orange
light stick with other fans the panel is
the main reason I'm going and the
closest whole life has been to where I
live let's go I'm so happy for
you that's
exciting you you should connect with the
other uh whole life fans when you see
them don't be shy
okay M don't be shy make some
connections have some fun
together it'll be great are you going to
go did you get the spot at the meet and
grade
too yeah I think there's a lot of people
going a pong as well oh my God talk to
me he he says he says talk to
him he'll he'll probably be easy to
spot team up yes yes you will H you will
go to the minum GD too oh please uh when
you when you go in like I I would
appreciate if you guys always like say
your name first like uh the handle the
name that I would know you for either
the Twitter or the YouTube name so just
say you're the prince of Denmark and I
would be very very
delighted and then I'll take a
screenshot and I'll write down your
name no no no no no just kidding just
kidding oh not the mle grade okay then
I'll have I need need you to sit in the
first row please of the panel okay first
row so I can see you
clearly in the middle ideally sometimes
the sides are cut off from my camera
[Music]
feet counting on you
okay maybe we can have a sign uh maybe
maybe uh you specifically can give me a
sign uh how about uh H putting up two
peace signs over over your head behind
your head kind of like you're a
[Music]
bunny if you do
that then I'll know it's
you can you imagine this
[Music]
pose
it's a a post from a Japanese idol that
she always did it's called usachan peas
usachan
PE not everyone will do that it's not
for you it's just for
him don't do it you can have a different
[Music]
one you need to buy a new
car can you not rent a car maybe
poo 723 D TI it's monkey donkey oh Jo W
another Canadian thank you Canadian here
rising up to my attention
skull all I got to do to get you guys
out of the lurking Shadows is say where
are the
Canadians why are you not always here
but you are right you're always here
otherwise you wouldn't have heard that
comment right you would have been here
anyway I would hope
so it's not like you get an alarm on
your phone and and it's like oh she
mentioned uh Canadians I guess I'll
check in on her stream
[Music]
now I wish it would show me your guys'
countries as a flag next to your
name but yeah that's not going to
happen but I I I I don't know I find it
interesting to know who I'm talking to
like where they are right now or so
Take It Monkey D oh wait I already had
that
[Music]
and I saw all the stupid edits I hate
you guys so much I hate
you I'm not going to talk about that you
guys suck you guys are so
stupid saw all the edits
of the teaser picture
from the one that Cali posted and people
put my my second my chef hat in all
kinds of
places and I feel insulted and
bullied I hate you
[Music]
guys
ultim stop being so excited you little
shits
I hate you
[Music]
guys it was
not you guys
suck you
suck i a d looking for the tough D
morally imoral D oh my God
right space wonderful than thank you you
got p as your first you are and me as
your second oh my God she's so lucky how
can you be so lucky what the [\h__\h] I
should be so lucky lucky lucky lucky I
should be so lucky in Holo parade
[Music]
gotcha not
cool you like those guys is this what
you like huh does this does this turn
you
[Music]
on a stupid ass
hat hope you're enjoying
this cuz I hate it I hate every second
of it let me at least put away my
[Music]
tail especially on its own it makes no
sense it's so stupid on its own it's so
stupid I hate
[Music]
[Laughter]
it I hate you and I hate the Hat I hate
you all rine F the
[Music]
pinky greetings tantel just passed my
PhD qualifying exams qualifying
so what does that mean you qualified for
taking an exam for PhD or what for
computer science and wanted to celebrate
by giving thanks to my favorite Phoenix
your work has been a big can you guys
calm down big factor in keeping me
smiling every day at
work as I like oh my God calm down
guys ah
no you don't if you don't deserve me at
my best you don't deserve me at my
[Laughter]
worst that was my worst by
way if you don't love if you don't love
me at my best no you don't deserve me at
my worst I don't know I said it wrong
and it doesn't make sense anyway cuz you
do love me at my worst anyway
if you do love me at my worst you don't
deserve me at my
[Music]
best whatever anyway rine
congratulations I'm not sure what that
means like if you're doing the exam or
if you already did it but whatever it is
good luck going forward and
congratulations and like respect for all
the hard
work I could not do it only you can do
it cuz you're
amazing I wish I could do that but you
know
G you
amazing great example of a smart
[Music]
chicken meow
and now get the hell out of here I am
mad the game is messing with me you guys
are messing with me the hat is messing
with me I'm going to go mhm I'm going to
go cook some food now J
SW it's so silly I don't even know why
they give me that option I don't even
know why those hats are in my casual
outfit I didn't even ask for it I do
like the uh this this here like
sometimes when I want to use my uh
casual outfit but I want to still look
somewhat recognizable then I like doing
this because it doesn't even look so bad
it's kind of
cute it's cooking that day like
literally because it's kind of a cooking
hat but not really because it isn't even
a chef hat if it were then it would be a
little bit better but it's not the thing
is it's not even a chef hat I like to
call it a chef hat because it's [\h__\h]
embarrassing if you think about the fact
that what I have on my head is a [\h__\h]
turkey leg holding
paper that is like the [\h__\h] up
[Laughter]
thing
why why why why why anyway whatever I'm
out of here and then German
[Music]
res let's just continue calling at a
chef head okay that's
better it's [\h__\h]
embarrassing
bye-bye uh Advent calendar in 1 hour
enjoy it's not me don't don't worry it's
not
[Music]
me
man why
am
[Music]
why
no go to bye-bye