all
to see you see you who are
you e
my I don't know what but it don't like
it it makes me upset well you only but a
few steps away do not worry I want to be
a few steps away I want to be by your
side okay okay from here on out I will
promise you I will remain by your
side bow bow
oh
you
L to see see you who are you
that
on my own I don't know what's but it
don't like it it makes me upset oh you
only but a few steps away do not worry I
want to be a few steps away I want to be
by your side okay okay from here on out
I will promise you I will remain by your
side bow bow
that
all
L see see you who are you
no I don't let on my own I don't know
what's wrong but I I don't like it it
makes me upset well you only but a few
steps away do don't worry I want to be
abusive I want to be by your side okay
okay from here on out I will promise you
I will remain by your
side bow bow
here
love see you who are you
I don't want to on my own I don't know
what's wrong but I don't I don't like it
it makes me upset well you only but a
few steps away do know I want to be Abus
I want to be by your side okay okay from
here on out I will promise you I will
remain by your
side bow
bow
for e
I
see you who are you
I don't want to be on my own I don't
wrong but it it don't like it it makes
me upset oh you only but a few steps
away do worry I want to be a few steps
away I want to be by your side okay okay
from here on out I will promise you I
will remain by your
side
bow for
I
he
oh oh hello
hello bow
bow oh hello hello did you want to go
and do the the Ocean Temple dungeon
together an ocean Temple dungeon you
say yeah of course I will join
the where where are you I am at the The
Guild The Guild oh oh oh where at the
guild too ah then you're on the other
side to me oh
baab oh sudden you show up on your
SE
[Music]
the good day to you how have you both
been B bow
have you been fairing well cuz you were
very scared
before it's so scar but it's morning so
it's nice that is true it is a good
morning a good morning with good company
it's very
shiny oh oh yes yes uh I don't know if
it happened to your weapons but after
defeating the
dungeon uh the last dungeon my my sword
began to glitter and
shine oh and yours do too
yeah shiny
too oh my God you got your nails then I
don't know why I said that that's very
strange with lottery
tickets lottery I don't know but you
Elizabeth but I have 800 coins oh yeah I
want to win I want to I need more bread
you want to go gamble is that what you
were
saying you know they been doing all
these dungeons we have some
coins so you want to go go play a game
or
two do we want to Che out the forer M
the fora Mt yeah it is close by sure
lead the way fuzzy one
um where am I it is this is a message
from FAA of fart to let you know that
fart is now open we are selling selling
lottery tickets where you can win big
prizes fart is in my brain what is this
every what is happening purchasing a
lottery
message and I hope that you are doing
well in my brain to any enemies she
appeared in my brain and spoke a for
M thank you what is
this you you spoke of it and then it
then she appeared in my brain what this
gadget is
crazy I'm
hungry do do you sharp head that was
fast uh uh sure oh
well do you feel
better yes I yes yes they wonderful head
Pats thank you I appreciate it
help okay uh let us go to the fora
Market hurt it hurt if you go to for
Mar would it what you'll be okay as long
as she doesn't go into my brain again
sudden sudden advert in my my brain it
was crazy that's there's no good when
there's advertisements in your
brain I'm not really sure it was the
first time although it feels like it's
not the first time that there's been
adver what
the
M that's a big a big
something you're telling
me is that a gnome
lottery tickets if you would like toe
one
okay they cost 10 gold each and every
day at 5:00 p.m. Pacific Time or uh
that's that's
uh 9 a.m. Japan time we'll be doing
drawings to determine the winner okay I
will make a lottery ticket yeah okay is
that one for each of you yes please how
much did it cost 10
Co you can buy more than one can I buy
I'm keeping an eye on the puppies from
this
witch so that is what this hat is maybe
this hat is the way she infiltrated my
brain so fast and my mobile phone
whatever this gadget is there except
it's strange W how do I how do I give
you my
coins I have to click on the gold
then that must be the source of her
power what do you think
Elizabeth about what you think she's
going to win she's buy you say 68 or 58
68 okay 68 okay since you're buying so
many long she has money for food the bul
ticket I don't think
ticket so that's 68 I can choose for you
or you can choose you're going to 68
sets of numers
I don't have much food left how many
numbers maybe more with this three
single digit numbers and the numbers
cannot
[Music]
repeat I'll
out all right how do I do this H why do
we do okay hold
on okay 1 2 3 okay 81 5 how do I do this
okay really are you so
yes I'm sure our Guild mates have to
stick together okay I don't have much
but I'll send you some PL may I mean you
don't have
to that one you can't
repeat Elizabeth of course 727 now I
have wa you can't repeat you
can't I have more uh so let me no
repeating
numbers okay
did I oh okay
48 okay
671 okay 2 40 what's going on 945 oh
that was wrong okay
954 okay
285 I don't know that's that's 1 2 3 4 5
6 7 8 9 10
10 11 12 13 14
15 16 okay we need a lot more okay 136
136 yeah okay
254 okay
745 okay 465 Bingo okay
23 okay 33 Okay no you good one
Elizabeth
okay
oh this witch has not finished to home
maybe the
Bing okay
725 okay 2
35 okay
925 okay 3
27 okay 0
47 okay 1
193 okay
143 okay 1 2 3 I'll watch from above in
case she attacks I think you had that
one already but okay okay okay I oh
5501 oh that looks dangerous no
repeats
51 we're
waiting would you like to fulfill the
rest of your numbers and and send them
to you at a later date maybe I can I can
certainly do that you are fine fuzzy one
take your time I'm just uh ready in case
this witch attacks I will send you if
you don't mind my randomized number I
will send it to you later if you could
send me the 680 okay if you put
GRE I'm
sorry let me let's try again sorry it's
okay
inventory is my inventory going to be
okay I don't
know 680 I have a feeling this is going
to be good yeah I think you have a
pretty good
chance thank you
what am I thanking you for I don't know
I feel thank you thank you for your
contribution 10% goes to support the
local library oh that's good Library I
used to spend a lot of time in the
library Li there is a library over at
the Scarlet wad headquarters oh thank
you for letting me know I didn't
know V informative
Lottery that's our aim education but my
chances of winning
um about well it's hard about one in 700
but then you get that every single every
single ticket so in 700 times 68 tickets
so that
means really good chances yes yes really
good chance
basically we have our own game of chance
too at our
Guild in the arena where we Spa I spot
in the arena you have
I have I fought I fought gura and I
won and I took her lunch money I can win
money and strength
yeah well
Elizabeth maybe head over to the temple
[Music]
D I'm watching you
witch I'll be there for my
prize what did you win
I I'll win money oh you did how much did
you win I didn't win anything yet I'll
win tomorrow uh oh I think it's this way
oh this way okay yeah I'm going to win
money
what yeah I'll be winning
back this way
this
way I don't know if this
right what
here should we make a party together oh
true oh
what let
me yes who I this this
[Music]
STS okay
yes show your power fluffy
one I didn't
forget call
[Music]
me wait not how
you well this make a party so we head on
without no I didn't forget about her we
can wait I'm fine to wait for your
friend oh I think someone's calling me
mhm no no not I didn't
forget we can train in the meantime
yeah good
morning good
[Laughter]
morning I don't think there're stains
are having a good
morning
nice good teamwork
[Music]
not Elizabeth okay we can continue on
then okay do later okay
okay
okay which one
is I have a bad feeling that we
shouldn't be letting for do this H I
cannot remember who ra
is sounds familiar did I meet them
yesterday
H oh there okay good good let make a
party invite the party okay invite the
party good job okay iome
I okay let's
Contin where we
oh there's someone who's part of
the uh the Scarlet
wand oh is this
rubius oh no this is the cor one of
scarlet one ah yes oh only Rubi oh no he
doesn't say anything oh he does he said
only rubian know the secret art of
refining rainbow Coral what shards I
must Endeavor to study
harder I like his voice yeah he has a
cool voice doesn't he oh this is his
heart I land it seems they collect
Coral it is the the Hat of app pointed
points same hat as the witch think very
carefully if you ever have given a
chance to Dawn the Hat of pointed points
the Hat pointed out your
thought think very careful
how come you do not have this hat you
made it with the red fiery hair that is
I I am
Elizabeth oh Elizabeth your hair is so
long oh yes and your hair is so short we
have to return what is that on your
head oh it's it's I don't know yet
sometimes it makes weird noises but I
forgot it's pointy what's your name yes
and your hair is very
pretty Roosevelt Gua J I
guess I was just being
forward no don't worry about it
[Music]
I'm with
AED star
sign I see I see so what gild are you
part
of the Scarlet
wand
Scarlet yes was also surprised because
uh I have a family member who is part of
the uh the Scarlet wand they spoke to me
yes they said they were my my father's
cousins sisters they're related
something R popsic how come you don't
have
[Music]
this did I oh gosh did I unlock her a
painful memory
oh I
fa you failed oh yeah he's somewhere
else he's like but I'll get it again I
think I'll I'll take part in this
dungeon and then I'll try getting money
and buying another chance for a hat oh
please don't drown will
you of for some reason I wish to break
you break have you break a leg
uh
now oh oh oh it's a fire do that already
oh okay it's a nice
horse it's a nice
horse what is what is your name again I
have to hold it in my hand under water
you miss immigrant it was pleasure to
meet you are you also going into this
dungeon it work work yeah I think so is
everybody going to the D heart with my
horse a yes let's all journey together m
to the
dungeon my
meat I'm sure be done by the time I come
back can you watch this for me oh no I'm
also going into you're on Mission the
map says over this
way can we in the she's doggy paddling
that's a good
question everyone following are you
okay just
are you okay
underwater I I can breathe underwater
now what can breathe under water you
feel Elizabeth can you
not there we go the rainbow world CL
cluster
uh
this uh have you gotten that from rubius
from rubius
I think it was Ru that gave it to
us voices in
head
toon I'm skipping it I'm skipping it I I
think I may be skipping something uh H
oh there's a piece of food a piece of
food um maybe he talk to cor and he can
help you here no he I need to talk to
the Guild Master with the Scarlet
wand I see
yes then let's head back I think
rubius is back oh he's not too far away
oh nice oh do we need to talk to
ruus uh unless you you might have done
it
yesterday
rious
well I guess oh
ah where's rubius you Rus is back this
way
R another location let's go find Rus K
Elizabeth yes we shall
okay you are very good with
directions did you speak to rubius
yesterday oh
[Music]
hello
hello car of the oranges oh it is the
big
Cates
M we are about to go to the
D okay this me get off
the we to go to the D now are you done
already yeah we the dungeon yet we have
to go talk to Ruby
yes is it you
free going go with Elizabeth but
Elizabeth yet Elizabeth doesn't have the
rainbow Coral c that's okay it doesn't
take very long but like how about we
five go together
yes it's fine with me orange maiden and
your name is okay Shakari of the
oranges Shakari you but you're in
another Shakira is okay oh Shakira okay
I am Elizabeth nice to meet you yes we
have already touched sword tips before
you
remember me yes but we did not exchange
names we just exchanged tips it seemed
which is the first thing you should do
as a night I hear ah um I'm not really
sure cuz uh I don't know about you but
i' I've lost a lot of my memories well
you you guys feel free to um proceed
with your quest we'll wait for you at
the dungeon yeah entrance okay
Shakira let's find
R
okay okay did you both speak to rubius
yesterday then
ah
yes oh yes she did say it was a big
library is this
it I imagine this is it because of the
bread where are
they I hit my my brain
Elizabeth oh yes is this is this off the
horse oh uh no I got off I thought that
was the entrance over
there oh there he is it's this
gentleman good day to you hereo V from
investigated those ruins of you I've
gotten a G from the various more or
L yes I know now s within you at race of
the power of
Revelation fascinating Most Fascinating
one night
hius those ruins are the key to
unlocking unlocking your powers our our
powers wow we a Scarlet wand have also
been investigating near the Plains and
wouldn't you know interest off the coast
we aspired a light with a striking
resemblance to re
Revelation good hero would you be
willing to travel to the coast and Aid
in our efforts there members of our
Guild already there hard at work I quite
sure they will appreciate your
assistance good luck and
exero wow I'm not M I'm
rubious
what
rubius rubius your voice has changed so
suddenly you are a
wizard
W Rubi rubius was the one that told me
that yesterday that that he was a family
member of
mine did you see the
resemblance I do you look like his very
beautiful daughter who oh thank you all
right let us
travel okay to the the co to the coast
yes off we go
onwards Jade sword
my horse doesn't like the stairs it
seems I like the lamps
here are we going the right
way it's
beautiful yes here we go okay
[Music]
let's
go I'm lost you're
lost where is
your ah wait I have a question are you a
fuzzy one and fluffy one related
I don't know what you're talking
about H I don't know what you're talking
about she looks similar to me but I
don't know who that
is oh yes I mean that's why I asked you
you look very similar except you know
you're more fuzzy and she's more fluffy
know yeah true I mean you look very
similar too I don't
know he looks little of familiar too but
I don't know sometimes I I don't know
for some reason it might sound silly but
I feel like keeping an eye on you both
of
you very
strange okay Jonathan Jonathan John
Watson
wait oh
hello there Fair Cat hello okay
Elizabeth I think you need to talk to
Cor in here maybe
yes now I remember it also
Elizabeth Elizabeth of the long sword
would you like to try uh right clicking
your radio and then pressing join party
call say with more oh really uh join
article get it yes get
job I'm excited for the
dungeon yeah call party party
party you might be a for some reason it
wanted I got confused at first cuz uh I
I just suddenly really wanted to trade
with you you know cuz you were in front
of
me want to trade your sword with me I
just had I I know I kind of like my
sword I kind of like it oh man unless
you just really want to do
wield no yeah oh dual wielding that
sword damn that would be difficult I'd
love to though no it's like I noticed
that you can actually cook stuff with
this furnace oh you can cook stuff on
the fire too yeah I'm going to go
explore
okay oh are we all are we all okay
foodwise because I have some food on me
if anybody wants I fine
too why are you M actually why why would
you spend all of your money on the
scammers I have thege to talk to the
sky you can see that're rising from the
waves the are quite a St with
curiosity you we are quite certain
something of great importance lies uh
there mayhaps a way to unlock more of
your memories alas his FR to Del those
watery depths one would surely drown for
reaching the source of that light but
fear not as is our duty in calling we
have been speaking with the locals and
gathering
information could seem there exists a
magical object known as a rainbow Coral
cluster which would allow one to breathe
underwater we believe this to be mere a
no mere rumor as the Guild Master was
able to find texts among our archives
that uh that corresponds to this story
should one obtain such an object uh one
could explore the Seas and easily as
easily as the land according to the text
it can be crafted from Rainbow Coral
shards and refines magical energy uh you
need not concern yourself with the
ladder good hero our Guild Master will
gladly provide it but will you Aid Us in
the search for Coral shards that are
iridescent as a rainbow uh once you have
found enough please return to the guild
and present them to The Guild Master I
am certain he will be happy to craft
them into a cluster for
you H the rainbow what the rainbow Coral
uh I have to get 10 rainbow Coral shards
it's is the blue ones here oh I
see and they regrow don't worry that's
easy huh yes this is a little bit too
simple what's the
catch ah the catch is just said you have
to go all the way back to the city after
you collected these oh oh wonderful I'm
sorry mat for my castle Shakira I have
to say um if it isn't too forward your
hips are quite
[Laughter]
hypnotizing I was born like this oh you
remember
but yeah uh I'm I'm I'm a bit different
from all of you girls because uh I just
like literally die every once in a while
and and then I lose my memories but I
regain them because I'm a phoenix you
know it happens often to me wow I amen
blocks
yes I'm getting blocks so I can build my
house later you are amazing Shakira
thank you Elizabeth you have your 10
corals yes I do uh so I have to go all
the way back to the Scarlet one
yeah I I can accompany you my pickax
broke uh I I mean it is fine if you do
not wish to make the journey if it's too
much of a bother okay let let us travel
then
okay me okay what's wrong I fell my
pickaxe bro where where did you fall I
fell in a bad place
huh this is a dungeon here right wait
for us
um I'm just going back to deliver the
coral and then uh yeah we almost done
it'll only be a
moment it's not the dungeo what have you
found nothing I found out that this is
not the
dungeon I made it back I have to swim
look oh what did you just
do why did you break it it sounded so
violent she knows the way oh by the way
what uh I did Elizabeth what do what
guilt do you belong to I am part the
same one as the The Fluffy one and the
fuzzy one which is the J SW it turns out
I am uh kind of part of your guilt now I
hope that's okay yeah me too me
too I did not even know that was
possible Mory kopine has um invited me
so to say
um have aligned I see I was in a little
bit of a pickle as they say in my home
Home
Country I expecting you could here I
take you found the rainbow cor shards
upon receiving word from my colleague on
the coast uh I immediately set about
making Necessary preparations for
crafting with the shards you have
brought the preparations are complete
now if you give me but one
moment
H wow he's fast and I do say my Arcane
power of prowess STS even myself so this
is the rainbow Coral cluster and objects
I had only read of now now brought into
existence by my very
hand but I should not bore you with my
ex excitations uh you need this for your
quest do you
not here you go this will allow you to
freely explore the depths of the sea use
it well and think nothing of payment or
reward as far as I'm concerned curiosity
is its own
reward but there is one thing I would
ask of you and that is your safe return
from this Quest I can think of No
Greater way to repay me now off with you
I expect good news upon your return
Exel that's dangerous wow I think he
dangerous what a cool guy danger go from
here yes I have the
coral okay wait what is this uh we shall
return what we
go I'm the here where did everybody else
go uh how do we go over here we
can't I you
[Music]
forgot I how did you
get what wait I found the way I found
the way you found the way
I don't know I've forgotten the
Navigator where is everybody what's
happening I like how her just ignores
all of
this I don't know I have I have this
feeling it brings back
memories of hearing stuff like this and
just rolling with
it can you can you make your one I guess
I'm just used to it
[Music]
hear me can I can hear you I'll need
some getting used to it because it's a
little confusing it's okay we're coming
now we're nearly there no no no don't
worry wa for
everybody you might need to you might
need to open your your magic books and
transport where'd you get stuck who got
stuck I I
stuck we dropped the new
ground let let's open the magic book and
let's go outside okay magic book yeah on
the third page on the fourth page it
says uh no wait what is it mag it says
what she went into water or I don't know
what happened so this means I can
breathe underw
now party this is amazing how do we we
can what didn't realize
P so dark P three this is amazing okay
no we cannot it doesn't
work no it
worked we had a swimming
attire oh yeah it's not good to soak my
armor and my beautiful
clo so
soggy thank god let's find
smells like wet dog
here a little I'm
sorry not you
not Oh you mean yes ha you're very funny
Shakira oh they're
back oh let's swim
where's she
there okay now we can go I think we can
go okay I'm going to put
is it this way yeah it's probably that
way oh do I need the
coral I think we're good just as we are
but oh maybe we can make like a boat oh
let's make a boat I know how to make it
come here come here come here a boat I
make a boat I make two boats I mean we
learned how to uh breathe on the water
but sure let's make a boat a boat okay
this is for
you this is from oh no actually I need
to trade you guys the boat one second
okay okay I'm going to trade one for fla
and C okay but we need free boats
then and why do we need boats you a did
I miss we really
[Music]
don't thank you you're welcome and I
make another
one
pie take it oh sorry TR
accept my okay and thank
you and Li you want to come with me
yes the
boat okay I will join somebody okay it's
okay I'm used to it now I'm in the boat
I've never been on a boat
before how do we go forward on the
boat one second girls why are you
standing on the boat you right click the
boat
my
queen no
no I don't know why I called you like
that I am the queen here yes you are the
queen of the
boat
ofan let's go you're going to marry that
little
King yeah I I don't want to marry the
king I want to be I want to be a single
queen
why are we talking about marrying the
king I think she wants to kill the king
wait wait I want to take a picture of
all of us on the boats
okay y look
[Music]
up cute okay a beautiful let's go okay
where are we going this way follow the
lights follow the FY
temples this is where I want to be
let's go is there right no we want to go
we want to go look at the map look at
the map
a oh it's that way yeah that way is this
is nice I
can't fluff all I see is
fluff I think this is better than
swimming please please actually if I
kill the king would you would you
support me uh I'm pretty loyal to the
the Jade sword and we are loyal to our
Lord oh Abandoned
Ship oh a
shipwreck what Happ like we're not the
only ones who had the ship idea the boat
idea do we have to swim
now so bad at this get out of the boat
let me out of the boat I don't think so
I see nothing here how do I get oh
everybody has boat there's a wall there
but eh how do I get out of the boat oh
we've
uh sorry sneak maybe oh goodbye
boy we can't go there for I think we
have to go oh we can't what the heck oh
God I'm going the wrong way hi where did
you girls go oh it's starting
to oh
like there is a an invisible wall
keeping us in the
middle oh there's an
invisible yeah Elizabeth is right
there's an invisible wall get back in
the
boat I think back to the boats is best I
can swim in the
boat oh okay wait is it there
no wait for some reason I'm not
drawing you mean drowning you're not
drowning yeah because of the coral Coral
yeah
oh you know the rainbow Coral we have am
I yeah yeah yeah yeah yes it's magical
it helps us breathe
underwater I have a feeling maybe the
entrance is
through uh that building over there
where's Big Cat building the
building the Temple looking small
building this one over this way yeah
where the lamps were guiding maybe I
don't know I'm I
maybe we shouldn't have skipped all the
dialogue
yeah
skip
ah see I don't know why I thought that I
should get into a boat where you were uh
the one controlling it not
see to the left to the left to the left
wait wait don't leave me
behind I thought I don't know where you
are uh I honestly don't know but we got
to try I'm find I'm going to find you
I'm yeah let's let's go let's go over
there oh there we go where are they okay
it's not here I see not really yeah did
you look did you look thoroughly not
thoroughly okay we must look furly okay
we need to find the
dungeon I have the feeling that it's
underwat because why would they make us
yeah actually yeah what would they make
us like bre under the water it was not
under the water
no
yeah big cat let us go underwater and
see if there's anything under here okay
I
[Music]
fall I mean there's some there's some
ruins over here underwater bigat bless
you te my God eyes toar your God eyes
water if I can find it oh oh what is
this over here is here this's big hole
here in the ground oh yeah there find
something yeah if you just go to the
lamps and then go on water you may find
a big hole leading deeper and
deeper look for the big hold in there
even like arrows there's arrows
literally oh I see Elizabeth
solid ah there we go that's a good way
of showing you where I am is it down
down down down by the arrows there we
[Music]
go
so I can't see my
map can you
see he's down I'm frightened what very
cute wow I made it through oh gosh
there's a whole extra world don't good
job ladies
[Music]
wow so many nice beautiful gam
Stones I'm
wored I'm I wonder if we can dig down
here as well and oh the the Diamond we
need the iron pickaxe for the diamond
but true we can come back here for
digging at a later time maybe this is so
cool I didn't expect to find a big thing
behind like a
yes fuzzy one Co you Elizabeth oh
oh you made it water anymore mhm no are
we all together yes all together okay
everybody let's go Mo Coco are you
Atlantis are you okay
foodwise yeah I have lots of bread oh no
I need to
eat chicken even I made I have potato
salad
no worries okay here's the dungeon W
ready okay ready up everybody ready yeah
am I ready ready up ready up wait it
doesn't make me
click okay done done
okay nice what is this place
beautiful
wow wow gorgeous it's so cool oh the
other water what I thought there'd be
more water over
here it's so nice wow look at those blue
[Music]
trees techology and stood at the
Pinnacle of civilization but then
cast what had taken a thousand years to
build was erased in a single m
in ages long past there was a land of
Untold
Prosperity it technology and culture
stood the pinnac of civilization but
then a catastrophe struck and what had
taken a thousand years to build was
erased in a single night somehow somehow
a lot of this looks or feels very
familiar to me I'm not sure
why like as if I've been here
before those fish well I wouldn't put it
where are the fish fish I could believe
that Shakira with all our memories being
taken
mhm lock what is this for Left Right
This is Burger left right time
okay not sure it was fiz was fiz can we
change the direction of
this no what
what it's not
card this oh those are arrows I didn't
notice how can take this no it
[Music]
go left right left right okay so we
have oh wait wait
wait I don't see anything happening can
we both press the right direction at the
same time oh
yeah 3 2 1
1 nothing happened press the wrong one
no I didn't the right one right
direction here this one I want to there
there are more buts around maybe
[Music]
not
this
suspicious so we have
ouch a few
blocks just by randomly pressing
everything let's go
uh uh uhoh put it back put it back yeah
yeah yeah yeah
oh oh wait wait wait stop stop ah oh
where do we want it oh we want a weing
wa wait wait wait we're playing the
stacking game oh green has to go first
yes green has to go next oh you can
actually climb the win so we want to
climb the wines you know then the green
yellow yeah oh yeah green one in the
middle yeah it's the
biggest that over can I try can I try to
I want to try moving something too okay
oh okay I see need the yellow to move
though how do yeah how do we get the
maybe the put the red one right to the
side
yeah yeah yeah
overow good
job easy it took us a while to
understand I don't understand but for me
didn't worked this is tricky I like this
[Music]
R we just fall to a death here I think I
think this the next rle no oh this no
did anything happen maybe there's an oh
I was going to say maybe there's an
invisible path but apparently
not this must have triggered something
was that just for fun maybe it was ahead
we triggered a button for something
ahead maybe it's okay maybe yeah did we
not have to do that maybe we
didn't I guess it did open the door
somewhere oh yeah it did open the door
oh wa my map is the logo I just noticed
I had the same thing happened just now I
just I took out my map
end where one people have been wiped out
another took his place and lived a new
happy and peaceful life oh this place is
so
boring perhaps even a bit too peaceful
I'm getting out of here the land sunk to
the depths of the ocean one might think
this was the
end yet where one people where once
people had been wiped out another took
it its place and lived a new happy and
peaceful
life this place is so
boring perhaps even a bit too
peaceful I'm getting out of here you'll
see day after day the little girl
planned her Great Escape take it all in
take it all
in I'm enjoying I'm enjoying the story
yeah
it's good to enjoy stuff yes these trees
are crazy I
agree there's sure we
[Music]
Flex a
interesting look at this what is this am
I
jump isn't it good in this realm we we
can come back to life jump
jump oh there was a button here am I
jumping
higher no oh no I I am moving a little
bit
right minimal nothing changes though H
what's going on doesn't even did this
not do anything oh
oh hey
what
happened oh was only 30 seconds yeah
yeah I think it had a
timer if I press what
happens I think I had
timer or maybe my my hand slipped I'm
sorry anything happen if I pressed Fair
Maiden I I you're a phoenix I thought
you could fly um uh I was just trying to
fit in you know I press this I thank you
for trying to like be with with be with
us peasants you know on the
ground what if I go over there and I
click this again maybe something changes
in the other side maybe oh the yellow
Bridge disappeared again oh is there a
blue or a
green we caness in front of us well
there's a
red oh that resets it I
see yeah
it's it's Buton has
own wait what happened
there he hey oh it goes
away
[Laughter]
nice I clicked the button over there oh
you clicked the
button started uh yeah see see if that
button does anything I can go touch it
leave touch it again the green
one I can touch the red
one we have
to back and forth touch the yellow one
wa touch the yellow one oh gosh that was
close not very safe work environment
again please touch it again okay wait
don't touch anything
okay oh yellow we just need this bit to
go away IOU the red one
hey go oh don't touch anything oh go
knows what I'm doing okay I have another
level here should I press it oh no yes
I'm going to press it I need the red
touch the
red I touched the pink touch the
red pink is good but I need red touched
there's no red over here to touch
there's it righted over there oh yeah
over here actually this do you want me
to do it oh
that's the
red I think they said there was a button
that made this
disappear wait is this is this a door
what button did she click was it this I
have a door in front of me
too I
I what that
do oh is it the
laser no
all right goodbye everybody else
goodbye well oh oh you made it too well
if you if you reached the uh the
checkpoint have you reached the
checkpoint you can just fall down if you
wanted to let's
[Music]
go oh there's a did you girls read the
text
here I shall I shall read it this time
yeah okay there was no nice way to put
it the girl was sick of the underwater
Kingdom and she tried constantly to
leave it behind no oh no they got me
again yet with the guard being ever
watchful this was anything but easy
she'd probably been caught a hundred
times by now even so giving up was the
last thing on her mind each failure
instead served as inspiration for a new
attempt am I just going about this the
wrong way yeah I know what I'll do next
and so another day of planning began W
very
good nice
meing more puzzles more puzzles over
here let's go so many puzzles the arrow
direction oh it changes
Direction H okay I think I probably
got what do we have to to make a path
yeah aart from
this oh a pop for this guy oh there's an
enemy
guy well didn't he already make it where
is he going out to the other
side we need to make this
one mhm yeah yeah we have to turn the
ARs okay oh there's buttons on here
before but now there
isn't oh
maybe click this there we go there we go
we need him to go somewhere he needs to
go does he does he need to go into
here I think he does he need to go into
this this cage over here not way maybe
yeah into the cage can he get EAS you
could send him already just take a
shortcut just like right uh yeah I
imagine so's not open so maybe it
doesn't work how do we send him try
that click it there you go come on go go
go okay how about the laser is the laser
okay yeah it's okay was that it I guess
it
made he's in there he's inside we need
more than
[Music]
one
oh nothing there you probably has to do
something else wait I don't understand
why there's some gold gold in here
it maybe you have to go through it we
can try it yeah's the yellow then yeah
maybe needs to cross the golden path we
can have him go down to this one through
the golden so here first and then here
right make him go and then here fluffy
one click the click the button click the
diamond
button
yeah like that to the oh okay I'm going
to click the button no wait wait wait
wait okay no oh wait okay ah no no no
it's not no no no uh oh oh close but not
work it's going to work didn't see that
one we still have one okay let's try
this again then one more
down
down down
there up this way this one what about
this
one this one yeah it has to go back here
oh then he can he can go this way first
then then he can't go that way yeah he
has to go that way first I'm
overseeing
yeah go yeah yeah
yeah oh I don't no because it goes in a
circle like
that oh there you go that should be fine
now here wait wait have we gone to this
one no we haven't wait no it doesn't
work so go down here
no no wait wait here goes let's see what
goes
wrong okay back around back
up we're missing this look good oh I
know which one to change yeah we Chang
this one this one is missing hey wait
wait stop that
man let's stop
him okay try that I think he has uh wait
no don't try that o wait a
sec I'm not let go try that okay oh gosh
TR oh I missed that one I think now
oopsie
one a he's going to be stuck ining
forever can I try one yeah go for yeah
go left here
mhm right here mm I fall right here yeah
left
here and left again actually you keep
going down down no right yeah right down
here and then left and then up and then
right yeah yeah this would be it here
go good
job go go go go go go little buddy you
can do it you can do
it yeah follow the light follow the gold
this way this way there we go
oh oh oh that was supposed to go
straight oh no so close I'm going to
close it you again again again now that
was on the wrong direction oops there's
only one direction straight come on go
go
go yeah yeah yeah go little guy yeah
yeah on yes over here yes
what moo don't mindlessly follow him
into the laser I was I was chasing
him are you okay are you
okay that look like it h a b this is why
you get scammed you follow things
mindlessly
no
okay go than me guys than
me oh there's another puzzle here here
no there's like three lights on before
there were no lights on
right really it's like a chest maybe
there's a treasure or
something it's green I want to go in
there green oh this
time we have to oh we actually need to
follow this path what about here oh in
the center have we tried going up the
center here wait wait wait oh yeah yeah
yeah there another one here cool what is
this oh gosh oh gosh oh gosh it's a
labyrinth no there's
water there's water falling I'll stand
on it water
go
water go up I fell
water I can go can you go up oh no ouch
I don't think so no it doesn't go
anywhere oh yeah we can go up but it's
just the exit over here so this is at
the very
end I think I think oh everything in
here is yellow except for one it says
green can they come oh should go guys
can you can you try to come here
actually up okay go up yeah uh somebody
has to stand on it no wait no no no we
have to open the chest first never mind
oh no no no no
no light hasn't open yet miss something
here how do I go down the purple block
what's the GRE
[Music]
block go she's back thank you oh it's to
reset and go I have an idea I have an
idea she got it she got it I have an
idea I have an idea stop okay
straight what is your idea straight
straight left uhhuh left oh yeah yeah it
has to go left leave the field and then
okay I don't know I can't change this
one but let's ah I think that oh and
then we probably go into that and then
we'll see what happens there let's try
it send him
off
interesting we anything here though
in his boundaries he's leaving yay what
the heck how poetic and now now we'll
see what does this do oh oh that's
it what about the chest the chest so
that one is interesting one light left I
want to get the test no I think can you
PR light more Co there's more light
before you think you
can it says up here please wait for all
party members before
proceeding where chest okay okay there
is a there is a message on the chest no
oh no no no well I think if we send him
for here he will stand on the button and
then the chest room will
open wait but the question is just how
do we lead him over the arrow for a
moment when this arrow is straight how
do we lead him to go that way Arrow
again oh yeah I guess the when the
buttons are back we can just move the Ro
to the right yeah okay I'll I'll refresh
this okay we'll probably have to send
him straight again later cuz that might
have that might have gotten rid of it
yeah press it is there an arrow no
button oh there's
no we might all need to go up here
because it says we can't proceed until
we're all up there anyway okay maybe the
chest is later yeah I want get test he G
yeah yeah yeah I'll send him again if
anything we can come back later in this
Dungeons and and do that again
together yeah and get the
chest oh maybe maybe this is the you
know the right order maybe we come back
here
anyway maybe all right let's
go I don't know unless there's a secret
button of some sort we haven't found
probably some puzle or something maybe
we have to come back later who knows
maybe the real treasure was the friends
we made along the way yeah
definitely I need to eat
food are
[Music]
here wait we're missing oh ah Elizabeth
yeah sorry one
sec
okay H I was just checking around oh
yeah m is still not Sal so
[Music]
wait oh let's go let's go wait okay no
okay I guess it
isn't that's
it has grow stronger oh oh wait let me
get the video first has it huh yeah
let's get the video my memor you've
recovered a portion of your
memories oh the
memories
wow took my I didn't download the video
yet yeah me neither
okay I'll do know the
video the
vision wait wait wait they haven't
downloaded the video
[Laughter]
ready wait wait okay one second I'm
almost ready one almost ready one sec
what wait wait a minute okay
record okay wait wait wait wait wait
wait almost have it I almost have it I
almost have it okay I'm ready okay uh
wait wait wait
wait
AIO Advanced Audio
properties monitor only okay what does
that
mean okay uh think I'm
ready two one one
go
[Music]
oh K it it
I'm out of
here ah she's the one that tried to
[Music]
escape yep every time
King read about
yeah wait she the one in the Hat I may
not I bet that
G and then I'll be free
want to P us or so I
thought she's a
criminal she making she's a scammer
yeah scy she's F okay now or
never see what this thing can
do wow so cool she did it w Wait that
glass ceiling I saw it outside when we
reached the
temple can we break out of it too that's
the
barrier My Story begins
[Music]
here our Story begins
here
[Music]
amazing what an interesting
memory she made it and we made it
I I let's go back in and get the chest
cuz oh yeah I think we need to the chest
I think we can figure it out we cannot
leave until we get the
chest got to get back in there it nobody
oh let go new we got to do the the
bridges again sh instead now oh and the
stacking too can you guys hear me yeah
I said that the star on your weapon now
is yellow instead of white oh oh there's
a different new shine to our weapons wow
I think I think it got stronger now o
you're
right th looks great I can jump farther
I press the
buttons I did okay and yellow okay we we
we're good now um oh yeah Green over can
I can I try as well
yeah uh I already ran out of brain
energy all
right it's too much for me so that's how
it works so we need to put everything on
the left first wait wait the over
there yellow needs to go over here R go
oh yeah over and green goes and then oh
yeah R goes far and another one left and
this one left and the red
see I know what you're doing yeah it's
easy but easy peasy actually I'll go
this way
like so simple speed
run now this not fast first try yes oh
yeah definitely we got it so fast
unbelievable we need to solve the F I'm
really curious to see what's going to
what is in the
hopefully something we can all share
like maybe
friendships don't we have don't we have
friendship along the way though are we
not after all that we're not friends but
this this will
like finalize I don't put a ring on our
fingers R we're getting
married no friendship friendship ring
friendship I didn't realize it was this
kind of commitment mhm
I'm going to press the L and then we go
do it do it press it press
it and then come over here the yellow
one yellow one I'll stay with the Fluffy
one this time okay I like
fluffy yellow one it doesn't work huh oh
why what huh glad I wasn't standing on
that I don't know maybe it's by here huh
let me one we're looking uh we're stuck
oh no no wa
soy you're so fluffy let me fluffy St
the ears of the
tail there's a door let me pit you let
me pit you no let me stop stop stop stop
stop how do you know what I'm trying to
do let me you let me P you wait this
is are these
are these doors to decide important for
you look so fluffy may I pet you or is
it just the middle door these are just
that for
[Music]
sure no oh no you did that to me no I'll
come make you up
I'm a little bit confused what should
we my D should I see if they work it out
first
sorry I got so excited for your
fluffiness I'm so
sorry can somebody T the yeah the red
one please how are you uh
Shakira I'll do I feel so fluffy now
this is a fond memory with you Above
This Pink
Arrow it for me
all right it's like almost as if we were
here before
crazy looks familiar let me see if I
can time
here first time totally yeah we're so
quick at these
puzzles
amazing it would be quicker if I didn't
push fua off
right sorry I mean luckily in this realm
we can come back to life did it worked
it worked I'm
get the
[Music]
Cheo all
right can
we yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I could have
helped you with that but that's
good I have um I I know how to solve the
puzzle you do yeah so I think the
skeleton or the chatini tell you no no
actually no actually no um I think the
uh the doll has to go through the gold
like
twice oh so like we we has to make a
loop and then go but I'm not actually
sure I I mean that's my idea I'm not
sure if it's that's correct I just I
just
assumed maybe I have like I think I
understand it does to go double time on
the cold so maybe like goes like you
want me to press it m press it maybe
let's
see
why no
I okay let me let me just try
one need theop
[Music]
place oh wait you're right you're right
you're right you're right he needs to
Loop multiple times he needs to go f he
need to go over it five times so it
lights it all
up five lights so I need to go over it
five times and
then yeah that's what I
[Music]
mean okay we can do that we can do that
how do I make this one
go this is the one I'm confused about
how do I make this one go up over the
same one several he can go here and then
he goes that way but I need the other
thing to come
up wait isn't this like already a loop
yeah we pressed it so now should be one
does the same one not
count go
okay up
once but we only have
three here we need yeah we need
[Music]
you
try
Okay and then go here go here and then
that lights yet oh preparing is there is
there like anywhere let me let me let me
try one thing
P I have figured it
out figured it out yes have you done the
previous
bit have you done the previous
bit the the bit before the
chest yeah we should do it again right
okay so you have to make the guy go
towards me through the little door where
are you I'm down here I'm outside come
backwards from where we went on the
bridges make the guy come this way hello
hello hello make the guy come this
way no way what what what I've sorted
out the bridges so that he can he can
make a a little travel down here so you
got to make him come through the dooro
you got to make him come through that
[Music]
door well that's quite oh oh yeah it
leads like here okay he's got to
I see I
see let's reset it yeah and then this
[Laughter]
Arrow I
see but at the end I guess we probably
still want to get the golden ones that
are here too of course right maybe we
with the help of me Elizabeth
bloodflame I have no idea what the
stands for need it yeah I'll tell you
when it lights up
okay oh yeah there is to
reset one more time do not go through
there he can go through there but you
cannot you cannot pass you shall not
pass okay here we go he's coming uh yeah
you can test with that one but it's not
going to have enough gold we have to uh
reset the path let's
go go go go go go go go go
easy I didn't notice there was like the
gold on the on there we go off he goes
off he goes
woo yeah he's probably missing one he
didn't get all them over
here oh then then then set it up so he
gets all those let reset it oh res that
okay let
me let me reset that okay he goes right
here down here down ah the edge to click
the button the reset
button n
and then right okay now
[Music]
now okay going on a long trip M late
okay too
late good job good job the voices in my
head are telling me
no yes he will do it I believe in him
100%
oh
look
huzzah can go
backwards you cannot go through
[Laughter]
there off he goes off he goes he's
coming I'mma die thank you
for
no I'm back what it didn't open what did
didn't he coming back still back he's
coming he's coming he's going to stand
because he going to
[Music]
here we go
[Applause]
exciting oh we got a a
vinyl oh wait
what wait what did what did did you guys
get a vinyl too yeah he need a juke box
[Music]
for one question girls you all did the
dungeon yesterday right yes
you have you gotten the vinyl there no
no I think after all that one p that I
fought there must be a treasure chest
because my RPG senses were tingling it
must have a treasure chest with an C vle
there that probably no one found so far
and I think I know where it is oh shall
we shall we go
on another little Adventure
yeah let's go let us
travel we have to finish it again we
have made the guy go no the dungeon from
the book I know it I'm so excited I'm so
excited it's my RPG
SES so real okay uh basically same path
but not down here but up up right yeah
no where did go yeah this way this way
this way this
way that way yeah yeah yeah yeah right I
forgot I don't know what's in there and
then it goes over there and then we can
okay we don't need any more of the golds
right no no no we don't need any
anything
anymore are you okay fuzzy one yeah I'm
not hungry
[Music]
ex
seeing good job
yeah thank
you we make an excellent
team I got the
treasure yeah we got music it seems back
up
oh it's very
pretty go good job let's
go to findd
y let's go I hope
is get by where do you think it is I
will show you I'll show you okay are
stronger now
again again even stronger I've quite
enjoyed this
camaraderie let
go it brings me joy okay uh like a f
memory lead us to the first dungeon Oh
Let's Travel yes my brain is empty
horses empty brain into the water we go
have to go horses into the water yeah
the horse that was a really good
D my horse doesn't doesn't don't don't
get off the horse the poor horse my
God my horse doesn't like to swim too
much yeah I don't think it knows how to
breathe under water it's beautiful
I really love this area was it was very
nice and
beautiful M was very well done yeah it
was a beautiful world
yeah
you yeah let's meet at the guy the guy
we're floating up guy with the corals
yeah
ships it's okay you can leave the ship I
don't think we need them anymore I can
always make new ones M
what I going so
slow I'm going as fast
as we have to go over here I
guess the
queen no the
queen no I I think I refuse oh
no the queen tim
chanders tim ters tim tim
who Tim ters Tim
tandas what an interesting name
back who Tim it's okay the queen I'll
claim my my statues myself I don't need
anyone to give me
[Music]
validation
Master oh oh yeah I guess we got to go
there yeah let's go to
the let us
travel first get
theut
[Music]
shortcut get out of the way cow get out
of the way are you running over cows
with your
horse yeah I'll run
over are we going to rub right yeah
this
way turn this
[Music]
way are we
ready I'm
ready let us
travel uh now that we're in this city
I'm going to put something on the chest
and then we go back
okay what chest where oh I have um I
have a chest on the place where you um
can build stuff wow I I made like two
chest so I can deposit like I
see my my my
items to see I have been rewarded with
your safe return prel what did you
discover in those
ruins fascinating most fascinating yet
more evidence of these ruins are somehow
connected to your
memories what is more I sense that the
power of Revelation within you has grown
more
potent mayhaps by exploring more ruins
and obtaining more fragments of memory
your revelation will be empowered as
well if so we must find the next ruins
post haste all of us together will
surely make short work of this
search as a matter of fact we just
received a most intriguing report Scouts
of the Cerulean cup aspired that same
mysterious light coming from the forest
along the Mountain
Road mayhaps you ought to visit the
guild and speak with the Guild Master
Celesta keep your wets about you hero
EX exio
wow do we want to see if we can visit
the
previous yes should we go to the
prev I'm currently communicating with
the queen give me one moment what queen
a queen you know the king that's me you
can tell wonder if I met this queen
before I wonder if I have met this queen
Tim I remember strange name for a
queen well I don't really know if it's
strange but it sounds quite strange I
got to deposit myself I'll be right back
okay wa for
me
uh yeah
yeah is I never been there
maybe I don't
remember ohom over here there you go oh
this is where pH was oh they're making
cute so is where the uh the the fora wit
who sells is that the place where we are
able to
build is that the only place yeah this
is the only place we can build
M what I see why did everybody go
I'm going to put my stuff over
here and later I'm going to build
something where did everybody go did you
go up the roof
yeah now up here too okay sorry I I'm
done uh are you girl on the way to the
dungeon no no where you going I'm over
here uh I still need to talk to rubius
they're over wait you haven't talked to
rubius oh yeah sorry I was kind of busy
no no we'll go back go back and talk to
him
okay okay are you done oh they okay I
guess they're leading us to the next
dungeon with that one but we want to go
to the
first
we
guys oh no wait it doesn't work
never
mind peace sh
PR I don't know how to open those
m box what is foro doing
I I'm put this
[Music]
here yeah
you the pit
does that
[Music]
mean I don't remember very
well does that mean does this mean this
is the green here is where
the the Jade sword
builds oh maybe this is where we build
something I see I see unless this is
already what someone someone's creation
h h
okay
I just want to use this
yeah his voice in his in head I was
right clicking it whilst in the menu
so that's I thought it meant at first oh
beetroot seeds
interesting here be a chest on the
ground yes do I just
okay this is a special piece of
DT person in that
[Laughter]
now oh
I'll do
great hiding spot
yes the voices in my head tell me
this is a good
spot well I think it's only my well we
can test this
actually ah there we go yes it is only
my guild members that can access that so
that is
fine that is okay with
me double check
yes the magic of these lands is
strong
okay I imagine they went to the the
leader
are you both going to seek the the
dungeon yes in a moment we're currently
in a uh spicy situation at the uh quest
uh board
uh
spicy yes yes I know she's talking to
she's talking to uh to other people now
huh come to the quest board okay come
come to the board come to the come to
the quest board
no no you're not going to win money
something's happening I don't
know no it's not no it's
not honestly it already it already has
become a worst chance because Moko got
scammed and gave them 680 coins I cannot
hear you come over here come here okay
okay okay yeah
yes hello Fair ma what where do you what
yelds you hail I am from the Jade
sword oh okay you are not of Amber coins
that's fine ambercoin are our mortal
enemies ah they your mortal enemies huh
you should Spa them in uh in the
arena we can Jade yes in the Jade sword
Arena yes oh yes now what what what are
you you doing here on this fine Moon ah
well I was told by uh Shakira and rora
that there is something happening over
at the oh yes let just join them
yes no I'm I'm a jade all the way I'm in
Jade though I've never
seen hello Jonathan I heard that your
guild is full of scamers can you verify
that you are with this member is
claiming to be part of our I literally
just went with for M and and Herb which
are Jade members uh to the dungeon right
herb they're like semi
honorary we we we get along you know
kopine has invited me into the guild
personally wait a second it's a truce
kind of
guess listen listen it doesn't even
matter Queen there is Queen thing that
red thing is of Jade's sword and not of
ambercoin thank you my Ben the name of
ambercoin thank you I don't trust I do
not ah so you are the Tim I've heard
about it's
Tim you are the Tim Tam Timmy Tam I
don't know what what is the Tim was like
what what is this queen Tim how silly of
a name Tam Tam Tam what kind of name is
B I have not I do know know what you
speak silent what this disgusting you
are the first to call me of this I do
not understand because everybody was too
polite but I to polite you have you have
yes you are right you have not been
polite you are correct on that I have
been very polite to you
actually soon as you found LED you to
the dungeon yes that that was good I was
just I was testing
you that wasn't yes I was testing you
the queen yes the queen yes I was
testing you close to the Gear what makes
you a queen huh come over
here come hi why come hi yes why are we
straying far from the group oh so we can
speak back here so we can speak back
here so we can speak freely
really why should I speak with you you
harlot in a secluded area too chaotic
Harlot I gave her a kiss without asking
for
coin Harlot asks for coin I did not ask
coin I would assum pink thing I think
you might be Mist how
rude how very very
rude darling
yes yes yes hot pink yes what is it hot
pink is
listening is that red thing over there
not harot do you even know what that
means I heard I have heard I actually
don't know what really know what it
means but I heard it is someone who does
uh favors for coined 18 plus favors coin
for coin oh okay that case I I did not
ask you I did not I did not ask the for
coin when I kissed you when I
all the the would you like me to hush
your gums oh I do not you
disgusting that disgusting thing inside
your about
my oh this I am my first my first kiss
so I remember poor that's I remember
that was your first remember you forced
it upon the I was blustered and could
not do anything about it you asked for
me to hush your gums so I did maybe this
is your wife I did not I do not remember
such a thing I did not ask what is it
and I said I will show you and thus I
did I did not know it was you you should
have asked but you did not ask for
consent that was not consensual and you
you are to be executed what
you exed ah you wish fight then let us
go to the
arena
execution F to
the hello dear Kitty must you must
execute come to the arena I about to
fight the queen oh oh she is fighting we
we about to go to the dungeon you uh it
would only take a moment come come over
to the
okay okay I'll be right back where is
the fraking
[Music]
entrance aha okay this
way
aha
oh alone
again it seems she is frightened to face
me of course with me I challeng the to
execution oh w Wait you are challenging
me oh wait why is your why is your
weapon glowing yellow wait I don't have
a glow yellow weapon well you said you
wanted to challenge me so let us I don't
I think it is unfair to use our
Revelations I think is
unfair I I think it is better Fair
you asked for
this also the door button are you not of
the a Scarlet Guild all right who wishes
to challenge me you're from the joined
the red team you are on the same
Guild yeah you joined a team apparently
when you when you okay answer yes to the
duel how much money do you need oh never
mind oh you cannot be two against one
50 I hey oh was there two against
one I do not know yes it is not 50 coins
wait okay you can't call me Pearl I can
give you some wood oh thank
you my name's I
appreciate I have a weapon of my own
they did not say we could not use
potions you are welcome I will quickly
drink this before I doel her I called
you a I use
this
I'm use this uh in order to on the death
of these door shall be mine and I be
backup plan maybe I will be queen that
has a very nice ring to it wow there's a
lot of plans ising I am waiting for this
duel I guess you are too afraid I just I
just gave some it's not
I try to accept it it doesn't sword is
glowing yellow the rest that does a you
would you cannot you cannot [\h__\h]
out right now what is pussying out I do
not know of such vulgar terms it is the
scaredy
cat oh scaredy cat SC pussying out
pussying out is that to my vo there's
something about that word that bother
you're join the red team what what is it
that word that
BS okay okay are we ready are we ready
to
do is the queen here oh the queen it is
time it is time I I came to support you
D canell in the
fight yes I you must fight okay join
again join again join again proxy of
course you you need to be safe kept yes
the queen must never fight herself so
join again join again have gathered a
fight yourself until you have produced a
male air to it is time to
[Laughter]
d i I guess we do not get our own our
own we have Revelations it it is a fair
fight a fair
duel unlucky for you I no no no no I I
am known as the hot pink oh
what
happened what am I being pushed by did
you jump back like that are you are you
pussying out is that what no I'm there
is a force that is attacking
me I'm so
confused
yeah
huh
huh huh
huh I don't know what the hell happened
but I want for a ghost pulled me around
the arena I
knew a force it pulled me served have I
served well que yes you have claimed
your destiny of being no no no no no you
must be you must be a witch I was being
pulled around that Arena no no get
out H Nay n nigh n
he Jonathan you trust me right there was
a force in that Arena a ghost that
pulled me around excuses you thank
you haunts this Arena it name is
Ping Ping
P that that sounds like a skin was in my
favor the history books in the green
Guild I believe that is a skill I
thought you could not read I see a raven
we meet again oh
hi excuse
me beautiful Raven you are here yes yes
it is I I have missed you Jonathan I
have missed you too little gem
girl beautiful fairy
demon hot P one I'm sure we were running
into each other
again should to
the I know the in my favor and
iant
yippe the ghost ping attacked me I was
being I was being pulled around I I
couldn't even move
properly do not H me we we have been on
an adventure together in the dungeon I
would not
lie I don't know like p i I love both of
you but our political um interests seem
to go into very different directions but
that shall not stop us from being
friends
right ah you know I I feel like we have
a new rule in the in the Jade sword that
we all must agree to adding other
members ah I I I I forgot about this it
seems okay I don't need a I don't need a
guild I'm I'm with the queen I'm her
guard her Knight
so I shall be
Guiltless then although I do have a
special invitation from kopine the uh
owner of the first dungeon so I think
that kind of counts pretty big she owns
the
dungeon
yeah H speaking of the D we go back yes
can the party please
yeah I'm
in she always runs into me with a horse
that is quite dangerous and they do not
know how to ride their horses in that
Guild yeah you know she's usually being
carried by a horse carriage so she's
she's a little bit um yeah unskilled
when it comes to snooty Tooty
Queen but she she's you know she wants
to help with the scam in the
problems what scam problems here this
this is the little artery the lottery oh
the
witch the
Witch H hello
hello if I ran over you with my horse do
you mean you what's happening what's
happening
[Music]
me where are you from
uh um are you with that
clown clown I think you should look in
the
mirror oh
Queen and also learn how to ride your
horse you seem to run into
people well you seem to be doing that
first to begin with oh I am not why
don't you will you get your horse out of
my horse's face no no no no will you no
you're a horse your horse looks very
directly challenged yeah yeah my horse
you are abusing your horse with a
freakishly large sword of yours and the
weight is just done bad not I I I I tug
this horse into bed every night and feed
it 10 sugar cubes a day I love this
horse sure you do excuse me get your
horse out of my horse's face 10 10 sugar
cubes you know that would make your
horse very diabe
later
onmental to its Health you already went
so you believe get your horse out of my
hores face hores your horse is
disgusting my horse is beautiful your
horse is dis I see I do not judge I do
not judge horses I do not judge a book
by its cover this horse is
brilliant well it looks like a runt
anyway I must wait very along the way
yes my queen just one thing
yes it seems I am in a um pickle once
again um I do not know where I belong
anymore but I know one thing I do not
believe she's a true my life a phony is
protecting you why does she bow down
have a destiny to be by your side as
personal uh King hero uh not King I mean
night night hero guard may I please
serve you no matter what Guild I am of I
don't want to be
uh known as anybody's she's bring to her
well for swearing your you are a mighty
Phoenix what are you doing gring to her
hey hey I wasn't talking to you outcast
out with you you judging books by their
covers she is a mighty Phoenix and you
are allowing her to just continue to you
may you abely casted out into the PLS
absolutely awful well the plan is where
we were going anyway um bloody looking
thing bloody looking
thinging makes me sick you are the image
of war and everything vile just like the
words coming out of your mouth my
lady anybody got popcorn good day out
out with you
are we going whenever you need me call
my name Shakira Shakira okay Shakira
Shakira I shall be of your service
forever and
ever yes yes hey hello was I talking to
you get the hell out of here I
mean the way you let this Mighty Phoenix
bow and grubble to you is
disgusting yes that means she knows her
standards you blue you're putting her in
her place I see what a wonderful queen
you are yes the fact that I can control
the Phoenix below me show you and I wow
I'm so sorry I it's okay it's okay I
know you're the most merciful of them
all you what are you what makes you so
special nothing you're just a rebel for
the sake of being a rebel and you you
you have no allegiance to anyone you lie
my that is why that is why you claim to
be this cool loner when in
fact without friends no companions now
it's starting to hurt well me and my
companions went and conquered the second
dungeon companions oh yeah well we've
already been unlike somebody oh look how
look at the shine on your weapons
compared to
mine yes it seems you and your
companions have not the same level we
will be of the same level soon because
we can only conquer one dungeon every
day so it'll only wait you know even if
your sword is glowing yellow you still
lost to Pink things that was the ghost
ping
someone the it was it was I'm the queen
I was being pulled around the arena yes
yes anyway I have better things to do
good day good day Farewell My Queen
ther this we had this entire exchange
yesterday no that's not what I want to
talk to you
about well I
me back with food yeah this blue woman
is are you eating chicken tender
actually care rude because I'm the noen
so I do whatever and this Phoenix needs
to toughen up second I know no you are
the second you're the second you're the
concubine porcupine what
huh oh sorry listen I have porcupines on
my mind team team Bish um I want to say
one thing to you this is so
disrespectful I can't
even I want to say one thing to you and
I'm not going to repeat
myself you are a queen you are a queen
with Castle yes walk away sty my Queens
you have no homeless you you are a
mighty Phoenix you need to toughen up
and not grel so much to this queen I'm a
night
Warrior she see my shield and my SW give
it to someone she was rude to your guild
member she left because she's a coward
no I must have my my honor and those oh
no now she's going to I am sh I am
absolutely shooked by your behavior
women my Pol our political Ambitions
shall not destroy our friendship coward
no gring no you are a mighty Phoenix you
are of
fire yes I thought we had a connection
because I I am but I am a human and I
can control fire and I thought we had
something but now I just see you as a
weak pathetic Phoenix that Gres politics
you know I must for the for the
greatness of the goodness of the people
I we have we need to help them shame
going around and I know that the one
true Queen will protect us from these
evil beings
shame
shame you got me into something okay
shall we go shall we go anyway
shame you
Shame
Shame okay but um shall we um look look
past this and go to the dungeon now H
I'll look past it for now okay good
until you growel in front of her again
are you going to kiss her feet next time
yeah I will I
will wait we should get into a call
again otherwise she's uh she's gone
party call party party now she just
needs to read our
mind let's go first
dungeon that was
intense that was
[Music]
intense speak your truth t yes I'm
speaking my truth ah who are you
speaking
to oh no are you
okay oh you want to get into our party
code I think we're we're looking past
our problems right now and just going to
do the dungeon so
I have no problem in the first place
good she did not have a problem it was
it was the
queen well the Tim Tam Queen The Tam Tim
whatever her name
is tthy I think we're we're all learning
a lesson here um sorry I need to correct
you the name of the queen is RA but but
that is your name do we have to exactly
disband the Party by the way and make a
new one probably yeah I do not know
H uh let's see I'll leave this party cuz
I
think yes see the fuzzy and the fluffy
one is still intertwined yeah okay this
hey go I invite you girls oh
okay oh wait I leave party okay I left
the
party I can be invited
now oh one uh it doesn't mean me leave
the party
huh yeah you have to not dis but leave I
have
left okay queen of I invited you and I
am inviting you too Queen of the Tim
Hortons thank you all righty remember
can you invite me one more time I'm
sorry of
course
watch
yay the outcome the S and the the
panther which one what are you speaking
of to
yourself I I received a a pigeon carried
message uh of pink color that says I'm
loving this episode of The Chronicles of
the Les
lesbians the outcast the S and the
panther which is I guess us but I'm not
a
panther yeah yeah she's the panther
who's the outcast and who's the S I
guess I'm the S but you're not much of
an outcast uh well I am a alone Warrior
most of the time that's okay together we
are not alone
anymore unless you s then I will walk
away just just look away just look away
I can't watch you do that it's go can
you guys press r Wait I think there's a
bug it because it says underworld
dungeon one of the two
shouldn't be one out of three I'm
ready let me unready and ready
again okay now ra I think you're not
ready yeah I think
it's also you need to be getting get
yourself into the the
call I am oh oh no you are in the call
yeah I'm I'm on about uh
Shakira okay Shakira is in and there we
go
okay all right let's do this again yeah
oh yeah it's
jumping I mean oh yes this is I am great
with the
parkour I feel like you could use your
big sword as like a
pole like what do you call it pole
jumping what do you call it well I would
not dance with it it's not over here
it's not no no not dancing I mean the
jumping it's over here Oh you mean like
a long p oh long jump a pole vaulting
yeah pole
vaulting oh like yeah like in the
checko o impix oh wait checkpoint okay
yes we got it we got
it where certain sausages got
caught what got nobody knows what I'm
talking about that's good that's good
sausages
have you
seen oh my God seen
it have you not witnessed it you
probably have forgotten it because of
the Amnesia I forgot everything I
already remember everything remember I
am the actual queen of skin MH MH mmhm
yeah seems multiple people are saying
they are Queen have you got to a
checkpoint yeah again okay don't worry
we'll carry you
we'll bring you to the gold I not need
carrying I was just you know I was just
taking my time at having a merry
stroll I know you could do it with that
pole of yours so don't worry we we just
don't want to we want to save your your
your energy and all that you know for
the battle I'm at the next checkpoint oh
how how are you getting there so fast
skill H I guess so are you flying are
you cheating are you flying cheating I
may be flying a little bit here and
there but you you were criticizing me
for not using my wings now I
am that is true you know got to you know
speed it up a little
bit uh oh you caught up yes I forgot
where does it go from here probably left
oh yeah and then here and here here
[Music]
here almost
there okay okay oh it's up
[Music]
here if only I was this good at jumping
at that one competition last year the
the Trident only up competition I you
got the next jack point almost almost
almost what are you bling about do you
remember something I am my old M I
already I already oh I did win yeah but
like I was like so bad at it I could
have been
better it's the
pressure it's the pressure
guys there's the music thing whoa you
zip Zapped well well well ping diff the
Ping the Ping ghost
is
Ping Ping so uh oh yeah it starts with
we all have little maze we all have a
you know
uh a uh like a a phrase as we attack
right oh my God I listen everything that
oh yeah totally yes are you going are
you going to say it wa uh
ome to the world of stability and
Harmony
waa not bad kick it
kick Phoenix Flames oh yeah I got a
couple they're short wow you have more
than one
okay do we have uh the shapes already I
got a
triangle I have a triangle sorry I was
doing something another
one I have star what is you doing you
have a star good another triangle where
is the thing to fill it
in oh oh there's so many I'm going to
die no you're not going to
die I got a triangle no I got a star
yeah I have a star oh there we go there
a triangle I have a circle we have
everything we just got to find the the
forms oh I found
it got
everything uh I forgot oh there we
go nice good job next
step oh I forgot to change my bgms even
though I prepared so many
no I didn't even turn foret mymgm
okay now there's one what does that
mean GM is this I turned it off for the
cut scene for the G cut scene code for
something this so good I love those cut
scenes BG the cat I love cat scenes too
I want more cat scenes than cut scenes I
am learning more and more lingo as the
days um the treasure is from what I
believe uh where those
trees are but this we first have to
solve this puzzle once again I remember
how to make it if oh let's go can you
speedrun it yeah yeah yeah what is the
answer big
cat uh just
like um the lights on the left are going
to light up so you got to make sure that
you oh she's
fast yeah yeah yeah she does remember I
do remember wow well done
well I think my my my uh dungeon buddy
kind of did it on a whim so it wasn't
really sure how they they cracked
it yeah it took us a long time
to yeah the first time was difficult
because I couldn't figure it out the
mechanism how worked so where do you
think this ah room I think oh well first
we got to do this thing where he gets
rid of the bridge right oh shoot us
shoot us do
it you won't coward don't although you
won't
coward oh there we are let's keep going
forward I
tried I
tried okay
Wai okay I'm here welcome welcome this
this the no it's different right well
believe me I'm sure uh that I know where
this treasure is that we're not even
100% sure that exists but I'm sure so
first of all let's do the whole thing
again with growing the tree okay we have
to on top of the mushroom to us
come yeah there we go let's make it as
tall as possible good
job yeah MH speed speed speed more in
Shakira We Trust Shakira Shakira good
job those hips don't lie
baby okay that was yeah too F the tree
is too big already another
one yeah come here do we need another
one come here come here come
here y it's can we get another
one yeah and Elizabeth are you okay oh
no I'm at the top I'm here oopsie you're
at the top yeah you're in the top maybe
we we can the tree no no no I think it
can still grow one more bigger no you
can get let's try oh but I want it to be
bigger I'm not going where go big or go
home as they say
exactly what do you think it is the next
the chest the secret chest so I
think that it my vision is hazy I do not
know
why voice is in my mind uh you know how
we climb up and we like to the next my
vision is hazy and I do not know why we
want to go the opposite direction I have
no idea because I've noticed that the
tree when fully grown it is cloudy
reaches connection the other side the
other platform Which is
higher where we originally went out but
it's hard to climb yeah
but don't don't go so don't make the big
jump if you're at the top don't make the
big jump I want to jump together okay we
jump I'll wait for but we got to find
the right path this is difficult
huh Elizabeth we uh we uh you at the top
of the tree oh no let's try to get to
the very top of the tree because I think
if we jump oh yeah yeah cuz it reaches
just the perfect height you know and
that already looked suspicious to me
when I first one was in this dungeon and
my RPG sensors were T tingling yeah but
how do you jump from here well we got to
find a way it must be possible otherwise
I don't think the tree would like really
grow this big Kai do you remember you
made you cooked something to make the J
the jump higher can you make can you can
you give one to me as well I want to
try I would need I already ate the first
first one and I don't have anym I would
need more ingredients but I think we
should be able to do it without because
honestly the jump it didn't get much
bigger it was just like like 5
cm I don't know if it's really small jum
from there yeah um there must be a
different path I guess a different path
from the other
side definitely not it or I wonder if it
can bro if this is the last stage of the
tree
Grove even like 100% sure about any of
this of
course I just had a feeling you know
yeah I mean we we here to explore it's
fine worst case we just go back wait
wait how did you oh how did you get
there oh just there in front of me so
you go
around uh
but I'm not really sure where to go from
here I don't think it I don't think it
helps what I've
done yeah there's buttons here too which
some people say the buttons uh show like
the way to the next like jumpy platforms
but it doesn't really maybe we do need a
potion I don't fix the potion okay
listen I try to jump but are you at the
bottom
yeah can you try leading another
skeleton leading another skeleton
there's no more skeleton oh so it is the
maximum okay interesting
yeah what if we may maybe the the trees
over there
connect
uh oh we can try uh growing those again
and see yeah if it maybe helps
us never know not sure because those
would be growing so far
away well I mean me and my my party
members yesterday didn't grow them to
their fullest so oh let's do that then
oh no no wait I think isn't there is
there a checkpoint there
too oh man yeah there is
there oh it's not activating I'm stupid
what do not call my party member stupid
[Music]
what if it really is
stupid okay one tree
Grove or what I if there's no more
skeletons down there I wonder can we
leave the skeleton down to the tree that
we're growing and grow it even more just
aest because you're going to D you're
going to it's going to make full damage
ah the fall for could I guess
so but if we like can you uh Elizabeth
can you try to uh wait never mind I'll
I'll try it's okay it's okay that's fine
too okay come come come come but don't
kill
me I want him to
face I'm going to
die okay abort abort
abort kill him h no difficult I want to
I want him to face the tree going I want
to push him down with the sword because
then down with some momentum it might
actually yeah if we clim yeah it does it
connects it does yes wow all right all
right all right all right all right all
right all right
okay I to
come probably enough if we just grow
this tree then if it's connec or maybe
we need all of them cuz honestly it was
really complicated to get the other C
the V vinyl yeah so maybe if we jump
from One Tree to the other tree to the
other tree yeah you know we'll bring it
over here
because you might need yeah oh oh you
think that's it finished growing this
one I feel like it I might have wait
where where it connects though are you
sure at the top if you come over to
where we are you can see that the tree
is reaching out to the other tree and
you could probably make that
jump okay m
dare there I
am nice nice nice nice I am on the top
of this tree kill me see me no
no do you just not want to heal
no a waste of bread all right okay
enough SC I don't have any I'm running
out of
bread I can give you bread it's okay I
still have meat okay I cooked some meat
before this one probably from this to
this to there so this one has to
grow yes is that is that it okay I've
grown both trees to it's fullest there's
no more skeletons spawning
think oh let me
see I'm finding a way to tr to jump on
the next
tree come over here no no I'm already on
the top which top never mind
[Laughter]
now oh no this this is the thing with
cats climbing trees yeah sometime it
happens you know you you get too
confident you think you can reach it and
then you fall yeah or or you get
stuck but cats always fall on their paws
supposedly sometime I don't the other
tree if I'm
e if if feel sleepy it feels like
there's
several
oh you made it I'm almost there for
like okay
no hold it's still kind of far so I got
to go to the top and then fall
down okay
okay and where this is not not quite it
this this it I'm getting so excited I
can
smell I believe you can find it can you
can you wait up to open it I think I
think I just realized why they would go
so far ahead so far
um wait the king GH is back confident
you can
finding Here There and Everywhere like I
I thought there was something the first
time there's there's a reason why these
uh trees grow this tall and not just as
tall as we need it yeah and noral path
yeah now that we have the vinyl from one
dungeon we know there must be a vinyl
here
[Music]
too but this is not this is too far
hello hi we need to go higher like it
looks like you can reach from here but
it's not quite enough we need to fall
from
higher so like we keep on jumping from
tree to tree you can jump over here no
yeah but from there it's still too far I
think the other tree we have to go from
higher no here go
no oh you could no ah you mean to the
left
tree is this the tree you were talking
about uh I I thought you were thought I
thought you thought you could already
jump to the front tree but yeah I
probably cuz I'm stuck here
no stop dying I
stucked got stucked
no I see yeah yeah yeah you found the
you found the way
yeah I found the I will continue your
legacy okay I am happy to contribute a
little
[Music]
bit that should
work yeah you're doing it Elizabeth come
on come
on from here how did
you
mhm
oh oh we're doing it W we're I
think I can totally see a treasure there
there there's one I believe it there's
the reason for all of this there is
totally a reason okay that wait I'm lost
I cannot find a way anymore
what it was on the uh the tiger looking
parts of the tree that there was like
another passage yeah you start from the
left and you go to the right tree then
the left left okay now I'm on the very
top of the tree where you jump right
where you got to jump yeah and from
there I don't know where to go I had to
go underneath on like some Tiger Tiger
tree looking bits like walk underneath
and I kind of fell so I kind of
accidentally found
it welcome let's wait for her okay
scared of this jump but yeah it's it's
totally totally doable oh you're still
on the middle tree on the first tree L
yeah I canot find the part to go to the
second oh wait I see the chest now I see
the chest
yes the
chest see it there is no checkpoint
though so be
careful good
job guys I'm looking for the puff I need
a i guys CP Clippers I need a clip
compilation from me doing the dungeon
the first time and then abandoning this
but I always knew I always knew there's
something more to this dungeon you knew
should we share our findings with the
others or should we keep it a secret
well we know you all s to the queen so
you are the first one I will not tell
the queen all highly doubt that I am the
queen I already know that
silly
oh this this one little silly today I I
don't know I had a feeling you will
probably say to her I know where they
other there is another treasure my queen
so please let me be night no no no no
kiss her to her
feet I think
Expos go no we how the mighty Phoenix is
Fallen when we're at the chest we should
take a an a me m m me momento picture of
us together and then Flex it to every
that we were the first ones to find this
yeah okay and then they can try finding
it too yeah can find
my uh let me see where are you uh where
are oh she still on the first come on
the first tree you've done this first
tree several times I know see no I mean
I I'm done on the first tree it's fine
just it's fine just take it take your
time we we'll wait yeah okay can you
wait yeah yeah yeah just take your time
[Music]
forever I'm
sad oh should we sell this information
wait I'm stupid maybe I was stacked on
this tree wait of course you say that
Amber how very Amber you no no I don't
want to I just read the message but I
don't want to I'm not like those
scammers from the
red you mean the the Scarlet wand uh
yeah I think this is a good point for us
to hydrate uh Shaka I'm always hydrating
don't worry oh well done good job I'm
just going to look over Yonder and and
do and
hydrate okay I'm running out of water
again okay I'm coming now I I
was I thought that was the actual last
Tre add a character I think my internet
is like bugging out or it's the server
I'm not sure something something's being
all quirky something's quirky because
people are cutting out and
everything I must we
pondering no no no one I think my sick
bands worked a little bit cuz I got my
sick bands on uh you know for motion
sickness
so I think they' worked a little
bit but after doing those that jumping
on the tree
I do feel a little bit Elizabeth after
this I think I think we'll call it for
the story for today for the episode for
today call it after getting this
treasure but and it does but you need
the other trees all connected all of
them which makes sense of like how
complicated the other chest was in the
other dungeon oh I mean I I've got it on
push to talk combin several add a
character I'm on push to talk so we
Gucci they can't hear me right now how
you doing
where are you uh at the top pretty much
like in the where the trees
connect I'm glad youall are enjoying it
makes me happy I do I do love like um
storytelling and role play so it's fun
all right I I better get back into
character Now cards up guys cards up
voices in my head cards up cards
up come on come on H uh first to the
side I think
think will she make it yeah and then the
next one on the side and then I think it
it's hard to tell from here but I think
you can reach I think you can do it
don't fall don't fall you have to run
when you
jump don't you can do it I will catch
you yes yes and now
carefully does everybody have full
health because the fall might do some
damage yes I do uh we'll go down to this
tree
first are we ready it's just a fall yeah
I think it's pretty safe you go first oh
OU okay yeah I'm fine okay cat next
yes you can do it go nice okay get up
fly
Phoenix oh
dangerous nice we're doing it good job
okay no one is allowed to fall
now unless the unless the Ping ghost
gets me then I might
[Music]
fall
yes oh my
God it's there we take a picture we'll
take a picture in front of like here
maybe
stand next to me girls yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah oh yes Elizabeth oh sorry I
was I was clicking uh I mean I was I was
jumping and when I jumped twice it did
something weird I was confused let's go
cheese and let's look to the other side
too okay
cheese
yay we're the first ones
probably nice probably excuse my rudness
oh could you please
R
God we did it oh my God I love this one
y huzzah I'm sure other people will come
to the conclusion that if the Atlantis
dungeon had a city the other should have
one too but I don't think many people
know where the the treasure would be
no what ouch I don't as send I get
confident
ABR you can let me know when you get to
the
checkpoint okay thank you it's only cuz
uh my my tum tum is turning so after
jumping yes after jumping so much on
those trees so I'll wait until you're
there and then I will I will uh oh does
it give you motion signal
yeah I get I get motion sickness oh no I
hear a lot about people getting motion
sickness from Minecraft I'm so glad I'm
not affected but yeah I I out of
character I get it I yeah I get it a
fair bit so I have my sick bands on at
the moment you know when you go on like
fairies and
stuff is it like every time uh after
like I don't know after like a like
around uh two a show like on the 2our I
get a bit like Sicky or like a bit after
a while it depends what I'm doing too if
I'm like jumping a lot and all that it
might but I think my sick bands helped
me a little bit today my wrist bands oh
well I think yeah with all this jumping
it's very understandable you've done
greatly Brave Warrior yeah that actually
was way I'm a brave warrior with tummy
issues you know we all have some you
know realistic human problems I'm only
human the Phoenix and the panther I'm
only human but even even I get Tommy H
Tommy H don't wor I got the checkpoint
you did okay I'm I'm going die thank you
forever yeah it's uh it was pretty
difficult jumping on the tree it
requires a little bit of skills
skill well hey good job just going to
get high enough to jump again to my
demise oh that was not it
but anything in settings I think I've I
think I've like changed the settings the
end of the dungeon right away or what
was it we've changed them
okay I took away bounce I think taken
away the bobbing The Bouncing helped I'm
also sick of jumping at this point from
yesterday feel like C
after let's get back into this swing
oh my
God her her legendary this was before
your time girls her legendary jump King
streams a stream dumping is frust like
water a water
stream uh yeah yeah yeah yeah a stream
of water you were jumping in the water
and you were a king is that why you Gro
to the queen kopin she used to jump over
streams of water
endlessly wow and they would lead her to
pretty high places like the it's like
the water streams were coming from the
mountains
W that is
amazing wa I'm almost
powerful you're almost dead
oh finally
nice
W Zippy zappy
yeah good job
thank you for aiding me in the quest of
this because I would have never been
satisfied otherwise thank you for
inviting us on your Noble Quest dear
Phoenix it's so worth it it was so fine
is there any place to play these uh
vinyls I don't yeah yeah there's a juk
box at the at the beginning of the city
oh oh can we go listen yeah let's go
listen let's go let us go let us
travel Have you listened to the Atlantis
one
already yeah it was playing in the
background oh okay I haven't
listen I I show you know I show you
another
way Shakira
[Music]
Shakira what is this song you sing
Shakira oh it's my original song your
original oh yes I sometimes perform in
taverns with um you are a Bard so uh no
I'm more like the Sor I I work with lots
I hello hello I don't want to I don't
want to confuse you or anything like
that cuz you have voices in your
head please come with us please come
with us we have a
Surpise surprise surprise yes kind of
surprise come with us you bring us where
where we need to go come here come here
come here come here come here follow
them come here come here
surprise yes all right come with me
sorry oh oops one sec that is a dead end
you can go in
there in there actually very
scary that door leads to nothingness
follow me follow me follow me follow me
follow me
yeah you're you're timing come here come
here come here here turn this turn can
everybody around it hear it I think so
right over here over here hold on just
one moment just one moment uhhuh uh oh
I'm sorry I had Kiara up by like 50% or
something like that sorry about that
that is my fault all right hello hello
hello are you ready are you ready are
you ready go two one
[Music]
go hey hey hey hey where you going where
you going
[\h__\h] it Monday Killers must fun more
often people Taking Lives recognizing
guns the real medic coniss is in the
ruin to Hell used to the audience with
thei the mother
human what is going on high five I see
you no one's going to buy this [\h__\h] I
believe
you somebody's working in
here we're getting down this is a party
I didn't know you play music on that
what you don't know is that really can
people really
find we found
it where the first one in your dungeon
it
[Music]
was
kaai KY
kill him with theil again on
the together glad
you I'm very glad that you are having a
good time that is what matters y the
great thank you for playing my wow look
at how many people came in here yeah
here at the
party your voice is like a siren it it
brought everyone here oh thank you I'm
sorry hold on a second I got
to would you like to hear it too
beautiful you didn't hear it at all
maybe you
have
[Music]
Jonathan this is more embarrassing than
yesterday oh gosh when everybody
[Music]
everybody that is something is
here I guess I'll use my
[Music]
yeah she's
ripping
fing oh no not the
horse I do I do remember recording it he
does remember it was a very different
time good
days her memory is give me one of your
finest drinks
the divorce
business how expensive how much are you
pay are you charging for it's going to
be um 500 coins for a divorce wow that's
[Music]
expensive coins going on no divorce we
don't need your business you changed the
name but they'll come crawling back to
me eventually is in demand you know I
could pay I could pay the fee if it
means if it means that I get to not be
the backup plan anymore become the real
plan you're not yet I'm now no no I mean
first for
[Music]
otheris confirm with your price 1,000
coins no no no no no coin 300
oh now it's time for shark song yeah
[Music]
do they have all the all the myth music
I think I'm assuming they have all the
myth music the first one yeah
yeah Pony
pony this is so
cute so
[Music]
cute even though I have lost my memories
this is a definitely a wonderful
[Music]
one found so many good things
KY hit
it I mean to
watch it
shows no that can't
[Music]
be gathan may I have this dance
I suppose but I am married is that
okay let me ask my
PE I gave you the green light for my
green I my Pearl allowed me to dance
with you when did you get married about
an hour ago oh yes I wasn't invited to
the wedding we have not held it yet it
was a small ceremony yes it was a small
cery been
[Music]
one do you hear it may I have this SCE
do you hear it so many people already
did the
quest needs to restart is your jukebox
music on your B box music B box it is
indeed
on I like the way you hold your your
diamonds oh these are the dam diamonds I
reive from
marriage wedding diamonds I see I had
proposed she's already getting diamonds
I'm jealous does this sound familiar do
you feel your memories com some with
very similar
names it was fake it was fake meant to
be very
interesting oh i s of
it do you want to hear this one too
it's bringing back old
memories my memories from 4 years
ago maybe
maybe it's okay this was before she
joined
Universal say rip let's go I don't know
what that means go I not know what that
means either
well that was a nice
Adventure went to a dungeon and went
back to another
dungeon and we found treasure
mhm that was a uh fruitful day I feel
I should probably go put my findings in
the chest before I
forget oh
well back to my new
home it's nice there
as I said even though I've
forgotten that I have new memories
now
[Music]
e e