[Music]
[Music] [Music] [Music]
[Music] Yes, good evening
everyone,
good evening Yes, this is Hololive staff friend A. This
program is in March.  This is a pre-program to disseminate information on Hololive
Super Expo 2023 and Hololive
Force Fest, which will be held on the 18th and 19th.
Thank you very much.
First of all, let me introduce today's performers.
First of all, I want to go to the sky.It
's the sky when everyone is consomming.Today, I'm excited to
see the new idol costumes, so I
can't stop feeling excited and
want to see them right now, but it's a little tough right now.So there are a lot of
things going on.  As I keep an eye on the information, I'm
excited about the new costume and will do my
best. Thank you very much.
[Music]
[Applause]
So next up is Ioffe.
I'm really excited and looking forward to seeing you all today.
[Music]
Takanashi:
As for my English training, I recently
went to Japan about four days ago.  I
was out for a bit of fun, but
today I'll be back from Austria. I'm
sure everyone will be interested in some more information today, and I'm interested too,
so
[Music]
Thank you very much. Let's have fun.
So today, I'll be presenting to you these four people.
Thank you very much.
Yes, and today's program,
during the program, we will be revealing the
design of the new idol costumes that will be unveiled at the Hololive Force Festival.
I'm sure you were looking forward to it, but
in conjunction with that, we'll also be
releasing the key visuals for the event,
as well as the
booth information for the expo all at once.  I
have some information I want to show everyone, so
please don't miss it until the end.
[Music]
That's right.
Surprisingly, there are only two months left.
Surprisingly, it seems like there are only two months
left. It's already February.  That's
what I thought when I was watching last year's concert.This
costume is nice, but I'm
sure there are some people who thought it was new.So
today, we're releasing the new idol costumes.
However, I
think there are some people who have never seen the entire live performance so far,
so I would like to take a moment to
look back on it while watching the video.This is already the
4th full live performance of Sora wa Nea this year.  I'm
sure you've become quite a seasoned performer,
but
by the way, for Sora, there are many kinds of live performances,
what kind of image do you have of an all-hands live where all members participate?
really a member other than
Since we don't all meet, I
have the impression that Hololive is like a festival. There are so many of them, and it's an important festival where everyone can get together once a year. I get the impression that the entire Hololive live is
Implant Festival Bao.  It
feels like it's a very important entrance [music].It's
become even more like a festival since it was added.It's amazing.It's true that I never
thought I'd be able to go before.  It's
hard to believe that it happened last year for the first time,
but yes, it seems like it's true.Last
yearor
last year, I can understand how it
feels to be less and less clear.If you go through the four years, you'll understand.If you
change it up, your memories will come back more and
more.  Yes,
that may be true.Last
year,
Ioffe and Chiara stood on stage for the first time in a live concert,
so let's talk a little bit about their impressions of that time.  I'd
like to ask you, Ioffie, how was it
? How was the whole live performance?
Well, it's amazing. After all, we're going to
do a lot of performances like this,
but it's only for about two days. The
number of people will continue to increase, so from now on, we'll have a
third party.  There are things like that, more and more.There
are points of evolution that change every year, so I want to look forward to those things.And
then, what about you, Chiara?I've been an
idol for quite a while last year.  I
think I had a strong feeling for it, but I've
always been a big idol otaku, especially one
at a certain company, and I
dare say
it's a lot of waiting time for 3D.  I
think I had a strong desire to move my body.
I especially like dancing, and I
think it's one of my strengths. I
regret that I haven't been able to do that at a store for a long time.  I'm
so frustrated
When I was finally able to show it to you at the concert, I
felt like I had already made history.
As expected of you.
Kihara-san's dancing is really cool.
Sometimes she's cute, and she can express herself in all kinds of ways.
[Music]
Thank you for being such a legend.  I
think it's going to be an important place for people to share their thoughts and feelings, but recently, some people have recently
learned about Hololive and will
be attending a full-length concert for the first time at Force Fest.
Well, of course, I'm sure you'll be there, so
let's take a moment to look back on what an all-inclusive live is like and what the atmosphere is like while watching the video.Okay, let's start with the
memorable first
all-inclusive live.  [
Applause]
Well, it's already been a live show three years ago,
but
three years ago seems pretty long to us. Was it really that
long?
What do you remember about it?
Impressions: I have this kind of
impression. It
was at a time when I wasn't putting much effort into dance, so I guess that's true. I
had an image of great freedom. I don't know
what to do with it. It was the
first time we were doing it together, so it was probably the
first time we had met each other, and it was nice to meet you.
There were a lot of people, so I don't know what to say,
but we kind of agreed.We started to
feel like we wanted to unite, and
from there, we
started to feel like we were friends.
Until then, I hadn't
had much contact with my juniors,
so I
realized that there were so many of them, but
at this point, it had only been one day,
right?
So, while I was feeling that way, I was watching the
video.  Let's take a look at it. Here it is.
What it feels like. Do you
remember?
[Music]
[Applause]
Being able to speak out loud
[Music]
[Music] The
first time we all see the same scenery for the first time.
In order to keep smiling.
We look forward, we keep moving forward, we keep moving forward, we keep moving
forward, we keep moving forward,
this is a live video, yes, it's true that we're
not dancing, but everyone's choreography is the
same, there's
too much freedom in the flooring
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music]  ] It was our
first live show and everyone seemed to be having fun. It
was a different time,
nostalgic.
[Music]
[Music] We
didn't all have the same costumes.
[Applause] You
came. You said
yes and saw it. I'm
glad you did.
By the way, was it the first time for Iofine and Chiara to
see Nonstop Story?
Or have they ever seen it? No, it was the
first time
in January, right
? They didn't have a private life, they weren't even born.
How does it compare to their current live performance?  After all, I
feel that there is a
difference between me and the customers who feel that distance between me and
Makuhari are really delicious.
Yes, it's true that the larger the box, the more exciting it will be, and if you do it in a smaller box, that's also true.I see.By the
way, ufy,
what did you think when you saw it for the first time?It's
always been cute.
Thank you, sister. I'm
glad you always feel that way. Thank you.
By saying yes,
Sora said that she was a little embarrassed, but
no, her voice was different after all.
When it was really high, she tried her best to say something high.  I
guess I've been trying really hard, so that's how I feel. I don't
feel like I've changed that much,
but I guess it's still there in me.
[Music] It's
amazing how cutely he talks
[Music]
This is so cute, after all.  Being able to hear everyone's voices on the ground is
really impressive, is
n't it?
[Music] I
think the excitement in those places is really impressive.
So that's it, non-stop.
It was a story. It's nostalgic. So
nostalgic.
And then, less than a year had passed since the first concert as a whole, Beyond the
Stage was held for the second time. Apparently it was
in December. It
was definitely before Christmas,
right?  Or maybe before Christmas, or so it seems. And it will be
held for two days. I
think you can feel the growth of Hololive after all.
Well, it was for those two days, but it
will be held without spectators.
But it
was still fun, and I
remember feeling very positive about the fact that even though I couldn't go there, I was able to have a lot of fun at home.  Okay, first of all, please
take a look at the video.
[Music]
This stage was beautiful, wasn't it?
[Music] It
's nice. The
video production is also in the foreground. It's something
new that hasn't been done before.
[Music]
[Music] I
think everyone was saying it at home.
[Music]
[Music] It's
interesting to see the difference.
[Music]
This is it. The
first time I saw it, the
first time I did it at the same time.  That's why it comes last,
right? This is what
everyone is like.
[Music] I
feel like I want to wear glasses.
[Music]
[Music] I
like the texture, right?
[Music] It
feels like we're here.  ka
[music]
[Music] I said
yes, so I
watched BEYOND THE STAGE.
Chiara made her debut in 2020,
but
Kihara-san was also watching it at the same time. How
was it? Was it fun? I remember.
After all, I had to watch it from home.  I'm sure it did
n't happen, right? I was
already in the chat with
everyone, and I was wondering
what was going on with them, and I was
wondering what the customers were saying
. I could hear their voices just in the comments in the chat.
That's how I
enjoy it.It was fun to watch them together,
but I guess it's
been about 3 months now since I
saw the seniors and
I was so moved.  Did you ever feel like you wanted to be like this
? I was really looking forward to it, thinking that
if something like this were to happen, we would be able to stand on the same stage together. I see, I'm
grateful.
Yes,
there were many people who received that kind of courage from this live performance.  I think it might have been  By
the way, what was the sky like at this
concert?
At first, I
felt sad that I couldn't see everyone, but I was able to create a
performance that made it seem like we were actually here.  I was
able to see everyone's comments, so
in that sense, I felt
like a new world had arrived where we could be connected anywhere, and
that's where I felt something new, such as
live performances and communication with everyone.
In a sense, I felt really lucky because I thought that we were able to create a new form of life. Thanks to this, there have been many advances in technology, and it
certainly
made me think that I wouldn't feel lonely no matter where I was.  I
see,
Iofie-san, what did you think when you watched this live performance
?Actually, at this second festival,
before the first concert, there was an
audio voice.We
certainly did it for a little while.
Seed
So, I
see. Thank you very much. This was the Beyond the Stage at the second festival. And I'm sure that memory is still fresh,
but
last March,
on the same day as Hololive Super Export, there was a third
concert called Winkyouwish.
[Music] It's
amazing, it's amazing all of a sudden. There it is.
[Music]
It's there. It
was Kihara-san's first full live performance. I
want to see it.
Okay, let's take a look at the video.
Let's go here.  It's
not very spacious.
[Music]
or
[Music] I'm
starting to feel more and more like an artist.The
scale of the concerts has gotten really big, and the
performances in the background and the lyrics are
amazing.  You've
grown so much over the past two years, I can tell. Your
style is great. It's
like Idol Fish Festival.
Even the cool songs are made to stand out.
[Music]
[Music] It
's Mr.
[Music]  ]  I'm
glad that Nayumi-chan, who was so
happy, saw it.
[Music] It's
definitely cute.
[Music]
[Music] That's
nice.
[Music] It's
hot.
[Music] The
famous kick starts. I
see.
[Music]
Here, everyone, shout out.  Even though it shouldn't
have happened, I feel like there was a lot of excitement.
[Music]
Adult
[Music] I was
wondering if you chose it because it had a more adult feel to it. Was it
interesting? It
was interesting
[Music]  The
dance is also evolving. It's full of
idol vibes.
[Music]
People who wear T-shirts get excited. That's
why it was so popular at the Hololive Third Festival.
[Applause] I'm
really happy for my first live performance,
but I'm
looking back on it again.  What did you think of Ioffe, who appeared for the first time? I
really like
it, so I really want to move it when I install it.
But now that it's turned out, I'm
happy. It's nice to
see such a cute person, and I love the sky too.
I'm so happy! It
was a great fit. Congratulations. You're so cool, Chiara. It was really great. I
think Chiara had released about 3 Oricab songs at that time, but I decided to
leave this one alone for a while.
If that were the case, it would definitely be a
blast.  I
thought that I wanted people to see my cool side,
so I left it alone, and
later realized that it was a good idea to leave it alone.  We
were talking about shirts earlier,
and I've been to a lot of idol concerts before,
so towards the end of the concert,
everyone wears shirts, and everyone
wears shirts, and it just feels
like a concert.  I've been saying a lot of things like that,
so it's understandable. It
was really good. When I
looked back at the video that I appeared in, I
realized how it turned out.  I do
n't know how they do it,
but is
n't it amazing? I don't know, but I've been dancing with a positive attitude all the time, so it's
true that it's completely AR and it's a live band. It's
amazing, isn't it? No, it's a
whole live show that has its true value year after year.
But what about the force?  I'm sure it's
going to turn out well, but I don't know if it's okay to really
hype it up.The third part was amazing, so I wonder
if I should have high hopes for it.Let's look
forward to it, I wonder how it will turn out.  The
London level is going to rise.
Let's put pressure on them.
Thank you very much. I'm looking forward to it.
With that said, I've
been looking back on the last three live shows. Yay. It's about time for the
new idols that I'm most looking forward to.  Isn't it about time?
After all, when you think of live music, you think of live goods. I'd like to introduce some of the live goods that are currently on sale.
This is also very important.
This time, I have a sample of the goods.  I
'd like to introduce it to you while using Sapporo.
Yes, and I'll be using a camera. A
staff member will touch the sample like this on our behalf.
[Laughs]
It's not me, but it's
like this.
This is the penlight you gave me. It's
beautiful
. It's so sparkly,
and the colors are so cute and fashionable. I'd
like to see the colors, so I'll ask you to show me
what colors are available.  You
may not be able to see it clearly, but
even in a bright room, you can see the colors quite well
.
[Applause]
[Music] It
's beautiful. Please shake it. If you
wave it, it'll feel like it's raining.
Please play catcher.
How do you do it?
What does it feel like
? We spin it around in a quiet part of a quiet song. That's good. I'm
asking if it's okay if it feels like this. Are you sure it's
okay?
Please make a heart.
Either way.  Is
n't it nice?
Thank you
[Music] There it is.
The colors are beautiful and I don't want to take a look at the penlight.
For everyone's sake,
here is the color list. It
looks like this. The
color is light green. I
think there are only about 4 people.  That's right.
Yes, thank you very much.
Now let's go back to this.
And we talked about T-shirts earlier, right? Do
n't you want to see the T-shirt?
[Music]
Yes, this is size L. I
want to take a closer look.  I really want to see it  Let's
take a look. The logo on the front
looks something like this. I
think it's
easy to use. You can even use it for everyday use.
I think you can wear it stylishly. The back doesn't
bother me. Let's
take a look.  It's
like an event T-shirt.The T-
shirt is called In Makuhari Messe.I
feel like they put their name on the back of the T-shirt.Thank
you everyone.This is something you can rely on.
Feel free to come and take a look.
Please, this will be my name 10
or 20 years from now.
Even girls
can wear it either way. It
's a stylish design. I ca
n't see it clearly. I like Makuhari Messenger.
Come on.  Which one do you want? There shouldn't be any.
If there were, it would be right now. It
doesn't seem to be available. Thank you. Yes, it looks like this. I have a T-shirt, but it's a little too big. Apparently, some of the usual models are coming.
Yes, this is it.
[Music] I'm
here. I
'm on my way home.
L size. This is L size.
ml. I
have XL.
Yes, it's the middle size. I
think so. There
are two types like this, so I like them.  I
might be able to buy both of them.Thank
you very much.Yes,
thank you very much.Please come and show me.I do
n't think you'll come.I
think it's impossible if you can't name it.I'd
like to thank you in this way.
Thank you, thank you.
Well, wait a minute. Well, if you're talking about a penlight T-shirt, do
n't you also need this?
Hello everyone. Touch
[Music] It
looks really nice. The fabric is nice. That
's right. It looks
nice. It's
written on it, isn't it?
Home  Doesn't it look like it would be good to use it for
? It
feels pretty easy to use. I
think it might make you feel a little better.
First, cut this towel in half.
Maybe this...  The
staff's positions
may have to be reversed, so
grab it with your tongue, turn it around
in Komaba, turn it around,
turn it.I want you to try your best.I
guess
that's what happens at live performances.Thank
you.Speaking of live performances.
That's good. That's good. I hear there's a use for it at the venue.
There may be one. It's definitely necessary. I see, it's
difficult.
Maybe you can practice.
Thank you very much. I'm
sorry.
And, and...
There is a support set this time,
but
as a special bonus of the support set, it
comes with a can badge and a backstage passpoo sticker.The
shape is unusual, and the
size is pretty good.It
stands out when you put it on, but the design is
nice.  I
like that it doesn't get in the way.I think it would be great to wear it on a school trip.If you
buy the set as a bonus, it will come with it
.
[Music]
A little bit of backstage.  The
design has a conscious feel to it. It's really nice
. It's
stylish. It's stylish. So
here it is. Pre-sale ends
at 11:59 p.m. on January 29th. It
ends on Sunday, the weekend, and the day after tomorrow.  I
hope
you don't forget to order it.No, I'm sure.If you'd like,
please let me know.Do
you like it?If you
look at the size, it's quite large.
This bench is quite large, I think. Yes, it's relatively
large. I don't know what it is. It's quite a rare
size, so be sure to check it out. The
tin badge backstage computer
sticker that comes with the support set as a bonus is a limited edition that can only be obtained with this set.
Well, I guess
I'm a guy, right? The set is definitely a good deal, is
n't it? You
can go to the sales page from the overview section, so
if you haven't done so yet, please do so.
Ah, it looks like we'll be saying goodbye to the staff for a moment.
Thank you very much. I'm sorry.
Thank you for playing with me. Thank you for your hard work.
That's it. Sorry for keeping you waiting. It's about time,
everyone. The long-
awaited new idol costumes will finally
be revealed.
The video that will be played from now on.
From the middle of the show, more than just idols will appear,
so
everyone, are you mentally prepared so you don't miss it? Let's
concentrate as we go.
Well then, please watch the Sora V-style. Now then, please
watch this video.
[Music]
[Applause]
Yes, you did it
[Music]
Yes, you said yes, and
this is the new idol costume,
Bright Costume.  It's Masu Light.
No, I'm
messed up.
Yes, it's even more amazing than idols
. I think it's amazing that the designs are so different from each other.
However, there seems to be some comments, so I'd
like to read them.  I think so
But before that, we'll start
with the first festival, then the third festival, then Hololive.
New idol costumes symbolizing the new stage of Fourth Festival.  The design is
filled with a lot of attention to detail.Yes,
and this design is the chief
art director and the
organist who designed Hololive's costumes.This is how we
were born.Thank
you for your help.Thank
you.And
Hololive.  Indonesia Hololive
Mika Pika and the teacher were in charge of the original costume design for English. Yes, it's a
little bit different for each group, but the base
costumes are a little different,
but
there are skirt types and trousers types.
Everyone has this.  We each chose which one we
liked
Sora.
For pants, for
Iori, I wore a skirt. For Iori, I wore a
skirt. But this time, I chose a skirt. It's
cute. It's
cute. It
suits you. And for Chiara, it's a skirt.
I wore pants
so that they would be easy to dance in,
but if you
look at them from the left or right, they look like skirts.They
have an innovative design, so
each person's individuality comes out and it's cute.Everyone
here.  I would like you to take a look at
this key visual while enjoying the feeling of knowing that you have chosen it.Now, let's
take a closer look at the three-view diagram.Okay,
this is me, teacher.
Yes,
this is Hololive. It
's a cart type. It's a skirt type.
And it suits my senior. It
suits me really well. It's cute. I've
received a few comments, so it
's me. Comments from the teacher.  I would like to
read aloud.Continuing
from the last costume, I was in
charge of designing Hololive's Bright costume.In
Nonstop Story, it has
been 3 years since the idol costume was unveiled for the first time.
And new costumes have been added.
Please take a look at the venue or at home. I
mean, it's
cute. I think it would look great
when dancing live. The design is such that I think it will look great.
Next up is Hololive
Indonesia.  This is ID
's
idon't
[music]
Nea's mist certainly
has a mystical image, so I
think the cat feel would be a good fit, and
ID.  This
is the original idea that created the costumes for and en.I have
also received comments from Mr. Mika Picasso,
so I would like to read them out loud.This
time, I was given the opportunity to create the design concept for the
idol costumes for Live Indonesia Holo and Live English.
Parts that are similar and different from the costumes The design was
designed with the imagination of the children of Hololive Indonesia and Hololive English playing an active role with even more sparkle in the future.They are looking
forward to the live performance.
[Music] They
're all different, but I
wonder what the unifying thing is in the back. I
wonder if it's that sparkling thing. It looks like it's fluttering and fluttering. That's great. I
thought I'd like to see them all lined up.
Ribbons.  The one on the left is the one in the house, and both of them
are in the house.Well,
I
can tell that they're thinking about their costumes.They all want to see a three-sided view of themselves.
[Music]
Of course, we have them for you. These
are pants type.
I've added a main color and a sub color to
everyone, so I
hope people will pay attention to that as well. It's cute. It's
cute.
I don't normally wear it.  As expected, all of her costumes
are skirts, so I
wanted a pants-type costume.It
's really cute, but I like it.It's
a bit sporty, isn't it
?I
think it suits her well.And Iomi-san, it's a
skirt type costume.That
pastel color is amazing.
My main characters and sub characters
have colors, so I
see a lot of that color in my everyday clothes, so I don't like it,
but I
think the live stage is quite dark,
so I think it's really nice to wear bright costumes like this.I'm
also looking forward to seeing them stand up.  I think it's
cool and mature-
looking legs. I
want to try the fluttery part of the skirt,
but it's kind of
short. I understand.
I apologize for the inconvenience. By the way, there are
other options besides skirts and pants.  There
were also
paper decorations, from the
main to the secondary.For
example, Ina-chan's
main color is actually supposed to be purple, but
you all deliberately switched the main color and the secondary color.I
see.  Well,
mine too, but the main color is orange after all. It's
beautiful. Thank you very much.
So, the new idol Deflight costume
was revealed in that video a while ago,
and it's actually from the Expo.  The
key visual was also released, right? Let's take a
look.
Here's the high kick. It's
amazing. It's so lively. It's like a spreading Hololive.
No, the poses are all posed. I
thought it was amazing. It's
amazing. I
like it.  So, please look forward to both the Expo and the festival.With
that said, I would like to share information about the Expo from now on.Aren't
you all looking forward to seeing what kind of booths there will be this year?
Yes, there will be an experience booth based on everyone's popular distribution project.The
first booth
will be Hololive.So, this
is a kindergarten where you can experience the ultimate lively and chaotic feeling.In an
area that is modeled after a kindergarten classroom.  So, it
seems like Hololive members are playing in various places. I don't
know. I don't know. I don't
know. It's probably too much.
[Laughs] I
hope you enjoy it and it's popular.  This
is a distribution project. Let's
continue a little bit here.
Thank you to everyone at the Hololive Sports Festival. It
would be nice to have a mini-game based on the competition that was held at the Sports Day. Let's play the
game with Hololive members at the sports festival. If you clear it, you will receive a prize.  You
might even get a
photo spot that reminds you of being a child.It's a
must-see.It's great.I wonder if you can get that feeling of taking first place.I
want both people who are good at sports and people who aren't good at sports to try this.I want them to have fun using it.  How about that?  I wonder
what it is called Hololive Police,
so they're coming along with Subaru Ozora. When
it's a big event,
police are needed.
Well,
please stop doing that weird thing. You
can experience mini-games in the interrogation room, which is familiar from the broadcast.  It's an exhibition. It's
like trying to guess the introduction of the members together. I
wonder what it'll be like. I
wonder who will be investigated.
And let's move on to the next
Hololive broadcast. The
Hololive members who became Hololive will be yours.  The
members of Hololive will welcome you in a private room together with the members.Please come and
see us.How
much will it cost?We'll definitely be letting everyone in for a bit, right?What will it be like?  Well, I do
n't know if you'll be able to see me in a cool and different way than usual, but I
hope you'll enjoy it. Once you
get into this once, you might not want to come out again
.
And Hololive Indonesia
Identity Records  There
is also a corner called
Mr. Euphie, do you have any appealing points
?
After all, we are usually
seen as comedians,
and as artist directors, I see. Please
prepare your hearts and ears, please. I'll
show you my artist side. See you at the Follow
Arena.  The photo spot with all the members in the background
is also a highlight. It's
nice. It looks like you'll be taking a lot of pictures.
Please enjoy it.
Let's go to Hololive Fried Cafe. It's
amazing. Is it
HFC? It's been
around since their debut.
KFP Chiara Fried Phoenix I'm
doing this, but we've been having
trouble with a lack of staff.We're really having a hard time, so this time we're going to ask our members to
help us out.We're going to
ask them to help us out a little bit as store clerks.  We
look forward to your visit to Hololive Café. I
wonder what it will be like.And then, the
images of the expo venue have arrived.Here they
are.Please
take a look.
If it were a giant blowfish, I wouldn't be able to handle it, but apparently not.It's a
spacious booth, but there are a lot of them, and
there's a memorization line on the bottom right.There
was definitely a mascot walking around, right?There was one,
so I was there too.  But what do you think? I wonder if it'll
come soon. It
seems like there's a lot of things. It feels like there's more, and there's something a little white in the back,
it's hazy and I can't see it,
so there
's still something to the right.  I
guess it's like a live summer [laughs] I
see, no, but it looks like there's going to be a lot of interesting booths, and there's going to
be a lot of things that haven't been announced yet today, right?
Yeah, a little bit.  I think we're
starting to get a feel for the expo atmosphere.General
[Music]
Sales.If you want to be there,
general sales will be held tomorrow, Saturday, January 28th at 12pm.  It
will start tomorrow.If you
want to participate in the event from today's broadcast, you
still
have a chance.Those
who failed can still
apply.You can apply, so don't
give up and try applying.For
details, see the summary section.  Please check it out.
[Music] Due
to popular demand, we have
extended the sale of live goods.Pre-
sale ends at 11:59pm on January 29th,
so don't forget to check it out.
Thank you very much.This is what I
introduced earlier.I feel
like it's
quite affordable, so it's worth it for live goods.I
think it's easy to buy, so it's nice.Pen
light T-shirt, white T-shirt,
black muffler, and cheering set.Here is this.  As
I mentioned earlier, this particular can badge
comes with it, and it also comes with a sticker,
so it doesn't cost 10 million yen after all.
Thank you very much.
Hey, if you guys like, I
'd like you to do a live show or something like that at home too.Also, we'll be hosting a
digital
message board on Friday, February 3rd at 11am, where your comments of support will be posted on the stage at the event venue and on the special event site.  I
definitely want you to write about it. Yes, you
can go to the sales page from the summary section here,
so please check it out. I'm also
planning to do a project where I can sit down at the end of the month and think about this message with you all.  I
think so, so please everyone  It would
be nice if we could sit next to each other for a while. I'm
also interested in Yoffie and Chiara Sora. I'm interested.
Everyone, please feel free to write. If you
think of it, I'll
be waiting for you. Thank you.  There
was a lot of information, but it
was almost time to say goodbye. It went by so quickly.
Thank you.
Thank you. Today was fun, wasn't it?
Well then, I'd like to ask you to give me your impressions.
Today was also the first time I
heard that I was going to be able to see the costumes, so I
was excited, but other than that, I was also able to
look back at past concerts, see some merchandise, and
a lot of other things.  Now that I'm
looking forward to the March event, I ca
n't help
but think, ``I really want to have fun.'' I really
want everyone to have fun.
Thank you very much,
please.Yes, and Iovi-
san, what do you think?Well, I've always wanted to say this, or I've
always wanted to show you something like that.Yes,
this is also really like this before
Cat.After.  It's going to be a little bit like we're going to do a live show.I
think it was really good.Thank
you very much.It was amazing.I'm sure everyone is looking forward to dancing in 3D.Thank
you in advance.
How was it, Mr. Kihara?
Yes, I was overwhelmed with information, but the thing that
sticks out in my mind the most is my
first idol costume. That's
right. I
still feel like
I'm an idol who doesn't know much about time.  Hmm, I can
feel a sense of unity and I'm really
looking forward to dancing now. We're
getting closer and closer to the actual performance, so I hope you all
do your best and we'll
be rooting for you a lot too.
Thank you.
So yes, we will
continue to send out information about events on the Hololive official channel, so
please subscribe to the channel and give us a high rating.Yes,
and
also the channel of Soraiyo Fee and Chiara who appeared today.  You
can check it out from the summary section of the summary section,
so please subscribe to the channel.Okay,
that's a bit.It ended in a blink of an eye,
but everyone, please take a moment to
think back on the information and
check out the archives.  and  I'm
happy.
Well
then, bye-bye everyone.
Welcome to the expanding Hololive.
Let's meet. Let's meet.
[Music]