hello
can you hear me everyone
no music is playing right now it's just
it's just minecraft there was some
lovely minecraft music playing
um and then it stopped
and i thought to myself ah maybe some
bgm would be good
but what if the minecraft music starts
again then i'm kind of boned aren't i
well well well them's just the breaks oh
something's approaching
and i could ah no wait a minute wait no
no no no no no
no no no no back to the game run run run
[\h__\h] run
run run get out of there run run run
what the [\h__\h] is that
yeah get it get it get it get it get it
okay hold on i'm gonna
we're gonna switch to the game in just a
moment i died
all right look let's just go to i'm
gonna
unmute kiara hold on kiara people can
hear you now
there's another one dancing over my dead
body hold on
spawn i guess we're getting right into
it because this game this game doesn't
like
to let me have any room to breathe it
would appear there are zombies
hello everyone welcome to the minecraft
collaboration between myself and
kusatori i don't know how to play this
game
i literally just got okay just run let's
run
we're not ready for the night yet just
run run around until it stays
okay i only ever played on creative mode
back beckons a date
um so this is uh this is something new
please oh please start
oh my god this is the second time you
die by a creeper
well i don't know what
people are hearing and seeing us right
now like or
the minecraft is stressing me out i
don't know what's going on people see us
right
it appears that they do it all i see in
chat is lol
lol hahahahaha um
i actually i started uh but right before
the stream i started
uh cutting off some trees and i made us
a little crafting table already oh okay
no time to craft right now we should not
survive no get up
why did i do that how do i escape come
on
don't die again
oh yeah yeah respond response
oh my god get get in the get in the hole
get in the hole go underground it's the
only safe place
no that is not very safe i would not
recommend that okay how do i uh do i hit
things by clicking the button the
clicking the mouse
ah die die die i'm stronger than you
i'm stronger than you please
you are dead again um yeah maybe
the night usually doesn't take so much
time so yeah everyone's telling me
to press to press f1 um they really want
to see
they really want to hold on a sec hold
on looks sounds good they want to see f1
so that they can see
um the specs i think f1 is brings up the
specs right
f3 is the spec one oh me but i want to
see that too
well f1 is what brought up the oh thank
you very much for the for the uh akaspas
um f1 is what brings up it brings up a
ton of numbers and stuff
f1 yeah f1 it brings up like a ton of
numbers
is that what happens to you actually i'm
so busy running away right now that i
cannot check
i'm trying to climb where are you are
you at the f3 is specs
f1 is the hood f1 if one should bring
the interface on they say hold on
kelly run i am i am
um hold on i'm gonna press f1 hold on
f3 f3 actually doesn't do anything on my
keyboard so i have a different keyboard
uh everyone
i have a different keyboard than you um
the only thing you shouldn't press is
alt
f4 i have learned that okay gotcha um
here's me pressing f3 nothing
eh that's it this is f3
ah no hold on sir please
reminding me i'm in the game i will
follow you
so this so this has a lot of spec oh my
gosh there's a
there's a skrellington oh my goodness so
the stuff that has like the pc specs
is if i press f1 so give me just a
moment
so escape oh no no no no don't get close
there's a spider
hang on can i one second i know the chat
wants me to
hang on so escape brings up this [\h__\h]
right the men oh my gosh you're going to
die
and goodbye how much health do you have
not much try all the f keys
nothing is going to bring up bad things
right
uh no no no nothing that i press can
bring up the bad things
okay then here's f1 is this what you all
want to see
is this what you want to see right now
is this what you want to see
nope that's not the one this is starting
off so chaotic
f1 then f3 oh now
now f3 brings this stuff up
no i don't gosh
stop
f1 and f3 at the same time they say
it doesn't work
f1 turn the interface on and off
i mean i'm i'm doing oh hold on okay now
it seems to work
oh it's turning day cali it's turning
day oh
but we're not safe yet it takes a little
bit of time and then they start burning
and then we say
then after you get off the set yeah
i'm here there you go
i see i see the life and the food now
stop pressing f3 no [\h__\h] this is what
you wanted
oh you meant that i want to i want to
see
if free i want to see your hold on why
are there still bad things out here it's
dating
a little while until they disappear but
uh oh my god
oh oh get away from those creepers the
green ones the greens
aren't those uh zombies wait no they're
not are they zombies
no yes no i'm going on the snow
oh i'm not playing full screen right now
i don't want to pumpkins [\h__\h] i can't
read the chat then
right now ah what this says fall damage
ie pumpkins wow in the snow that makes
a whole lot of sense give me that
dad uh if you need food you know
normally like for meat and so on you
first have to grill it and stuff but the
pumpkins
i think you can eat bread uh now you
have to make something out of it that
dude is on fire
he's on fire yeah but now they're
burning oh cool i mean that's a good
thing right because then they died
give me that you should come back with
me to my to my box to my crafting table
okie dokie i'm on the way they're
burning
i've never played this game before in
actually i have
a long time ago back in the day i played
on creative mode a couple times
um that was a long time ago where uh
where are you i see you whoa that was a
big no oh okay that
dude is gonna blow up right i've heard
of you
i've heard of you so
i think actually tonight
i'm the one control to run experience
between
us too you are i can go fast let me go
yeah yeah i'm on the way
okay um
now let me teach you
after you have like gained some
resources from the trees
you get some wood and then with this box
that i made for you which i will also
teach you how
to make uh-huh with this box you can
craft swords
and shields and all kinds of stuff
so first get yourself some wood there
just
left click on the tree okay
and just don't stop clicking just keep
it i'll keep it clicked don't okay
ah no wait what no that's that's the
left wait no that's the right just
kidding
just kidding i actually um i i don't
have a trackpad anymore i have a mouse
did i hit you i'm very sorry how do i
not use the um i would like to not use
the pumpkin
uh to to hit things how do i fix it
uh uh you if you use the scroll oh okay
okay okay
got it i've never had a scroll wheel
before
this is the first unbelievable
give it to me did you do some kind of
introduction
while no no no i didn't because i
started getting attacked we went right
into it because i started getting
attacked
because this game doesn't want this game
doesn't want to uh give me a break oh
here's the nice music
actually i can already make a bed nice
you should do that follow your dreams if
you have a bed i don't know if you
remember from the last time you played
this game but if you have a bed you can
um you can sleep for the night oh skip
the night
sick yeah then the enemies are gone by
the time you wake up
cool i'll find one more sheep and make
you another bed
well thank you i appreciate it it's very
kind of you because it's already only
only i will make you bad but only if i
can if i can put it right next to you
depends how close how many meters yeah
well right next to it next to it means
next to you
i i i require two blocks worth of space
between you and i
[Music]
two blocks that's a lot then make your
own bed
no okay fine one one how about that
can i kill this for food what
the cow oh yeah the cows they run away
i know i know it's fine i have control
use control hold on uh i need to stretch
my fingers
okay find another sheep because for
defense
give me your delicious your delicious
sustenance come back
no come back
so when do you stop moving
me oh there we go no no you're you're
fine for now okay i got i got some uh
meats from the cow
okay that was pretty weird i don't need
one more sheep because i got two more
woo
uh-huh and with the wool we can make the
bed
narehodoner where are you then we can
survive oh
i'm like uh still on that big field okay
so we should be close by i went on a bit
of a crazy chase
there but um
there you are i see you off we go but we
cannot grill yet
this is um difficult
food
so what is our goals flowers
a goal make a dope house can we do that
let us create the dopest house a shared
home
not necessarily our house but a shared
home between the two of us
i hit him with the flower oh don't do
that
just give me the bare hand between
you're already that far
with me like i'm i'm honest i'm happy
to hear that uh-huh um
yeah right
[Music]
i want to show the skin to everyone hold
on i'd like to show everyone the skin
it's a f5 okay so you can see the back
like this haha rather cool
um and credit is on my twitter go check
i will input
the credit into the description after
we've finished the gameplay
uh for the creator of the skins thank
you very much and big ups
for that i appreciate it
yeah okay hold on i'm switching back to
first person i
found the sheep oh my god there's like
lots of pigs and sheeps here
oh cool okay right for the slaughter one
moment please you know where i am
uh no i don't i have no clue just run
straight probably then you see me okay
uh can you describe your surroundings to
me
uh field and mountain
okay pigs and sheep okay you'll leave it
to me then i will find you
i can make you a bed now i see the sheep
oh that's a duck just kidding
okay there's some white dots yeah
there's some ducks i see you now i see
you off in the distance
just a moment please um so right now i
currently have what see what appears to
be a full inventory
how do i switch back to just my hands to
hit things you already have a full
inventory
well let's see one two three the main
the main bar is full
oh i'll go on e letter e e okay that's
your inventory
and then you can move like stuff that
you need right away from the hot part to
the inventory i get it i get it
the only thing you usually need on the
hot bar
is like weapons and food and
food okay dog you all put these blocks
here just in case
you callie my wife follow me
we go back can you not call me that huh
just just just kelly is fine
please i'm a guy
cantaloupe all right you know what
if you call me those things i won't
respond to you i'm sorry
is how it's gonna go they are they're
very pretty
i'm gonna break them differently i
planted them all for you
oh cool awesome i'm gonna break them
down and steal them now
no well okay yeah you can have them i
don't believe that you planted them
okey-dokey you can run faster
if you press ctrl while you're
walking yes control so i've heard that
is the word on the street
however if you run out of food then you
cannot run anymore
just like me right now yeah let me kill
this chicken
come here come back to me no
no hold on killing a chicken
yes i'm hungry got it nice but you have
to grill that first
okay well i'll save it for later then
you all right i think
i got it where are you at i keep losing
families we can eat fairies
okay that's cool yeah for now at least
cool except
where are you at i'm back where i
respond kinda
oh you went way far back okay i will
find you worry not
our crafting table is there and now i
shall make
you i see you okay i forgot this game
has fall damage ah
oh yeah don't die
that's my line to be i have honest
health
how do i regain health sleeping eating
now wait wait i'll give you food one
second
oh it's okay we should probably cook it
where do we get the fire no no
no i have berries right now okay so look
look okay i'm looking
okay this distance is acceptable
so as when the night comes we gotta
sleep quickly
but when there's enemies around then you
cannot sleep but we'll build like a wall
around our beds
soon okay we can't be protected at all
times sounds fine to me
uh wait now let me give you um some
berries
how did i throw them again uh
no oh
yeah [\h__\h] [\h__\h] i planted them
whoops no no no
no no no no no can i not i can't oh i
can't eat it
oh well i'm gonna eat this now okay can
i eat the raw meat
uh raw fish yes raw meat
i'm not sure actually if you um do
right click while you're on the item
and you can see if you can eat it okay
let's give it a shot then
otherwise maybe there's more berries
over there because i don't know how to
throw them to you
tasty oh it worked raw meat yeah not the
best thing but yeah for now
i'll take it okay um now
with the wood i'm landscaping hold on
yes with the wood that you have until
now
go to the crafting table and then put
the wood in the
top left corner and then you see on the
right side it turns into planks right
okay one moment how do i use okay uh
let's see with the wood that i have
i put it all together okay and then one
last night let's sleep
oh right click on the bed
our first night together
so yeah so yeah okay cool oh it's it's
so nice sleeping next time oh that
worked
i can't believe that that worked i
honestly i cannot believe that that
works okay
back to the body how did we not die
only one slot oh one slot gotcha okay
never mind jkg okay
jk and then what should come out of it
is planks
okay you see that uh so just one
what i have a spruce log yeah
put that in the left side and then on
the right side there should be planks
coming up spruce planks got it okay
and then if you click uh shift
shift uh-huh and on on the planks then
you get like
as much as you can get out of that oh
did it work hold on one moment
because we need a lot of those planks
anyway as much as you oh okay okay okay
got it got it easy easy easy
no problem we have 32. next thing you do
uh put one plank in the crafting table
then right click on it now one it can be
as many as you want but then right click
on those planks
and place one more below because i'm
guessing you have more than one plank
uh-huh and now on the right side it
should be able to make you a stick
actually four sticks um it says spruce
button
it's a button oh yeah you have to put
one more below it
oh okay now hold on there one more plank
right below it
i get it you can right click on the
plank
to to part it into more items i see
okay this is a really interesting game
yeah you see the sticks now
yeah yeah i got it a stick take some of
those sticks you can take a couple more
yeah four so now next thing this is also
important uh-huh put
one stick in the crafting table
and in the middle bottom okay and one
more
above that uh-huh and then
and then put three planks at the very
top
okay is this going to be the pickaxe
yeah there's a three planks right yeah
three planks at the top
okay hold on
ah yay the pickaxe
i've heard i've heard legends of this if
you only put two
then you can make a hole but that's not
so important right now okay yeah we
don't [\h__\h] around with hoes here we go
when you get a shovel okay not that much
right now
so now one more thing that is really
important is uh
uh just have um one plank in the top
middle one plank
in the middle middle and one stick in
the very bottom middle
so you can make a sword okay one one in
the top
wait middle bottom middle
hold on two one plank in the top middle
one plank in the middle middle and one
stick
in the bottom middle this is really um
wow you have to really know your stuff
to play this game
how how do you get by without some sort
of of guide or walk through yeah
you see that that that green book on the
left
it gives you some recipes but sometimes
you need to first learn something or
like get a new item to actually be able
to see the recipe for it
i see wow but if you click on like i
think you should see this wooden sword
in that recipe book
i do i have one now yeah it will if you
if you have the materials it will
automatically like
show it how to make it and then you can
just drag it out there and then you have
a sword
i will show it to you now
you got it uh-huh yeah i kind of want to
use it
no now we have more important things to
do callie
okay so one more thing that we should
make now
is uh why are you trying to hit me stop
i'm trying
i'm faking you out i'm faking you out i
won't actually hit you
click on the crafting thing uh-huh and
then go to the second page from the
from the recipe okay and then
uh and there should be i think
okay no no no no no no no
no no no no priorities okay okay
there should be a chest in the bottom
for me it's at the bottom
ah chest i see it
okay there are another
and it just it placed them for me it
placed the planks for me
i have a chest yeah
so i already made one and i place it
here if you right click on it you can
put all the important stuff in there
in case you die you can always come back
here and
find some things okay my chest will be
here
here's my chest okay hey
this stuff you definitely don't want to
lose okay no
no rotten flesh
i'll store that oh my god um some
pumpkins brought in flesh
um what else the flowers i can live
without raw chicken i might want to eat
soon
okay we will grill that soon we'll make
it yeah next thing we make is a grilling
thing okay so we shall start
with our pickaxe this is the the mine
part of the of the crap of the minecraft
let's go down here yes and uh
give me that some of that yeah
coal we need all of this stuff so that's
just
mine endlessly i like that noise
the bing bing the coal is important
but also normal stones we might need to
ah actually i forgot what i need for the
stove i'll figure it out
let us dig very deep can we find the
diamonds
ah i want the chain i want a diamond
chain
i doubt that we'll find diamonds today
already but
that's fine i'll dig until i find them
hmm
here i go and try to get something
started
and actually like um i'm not sure if we
should
build like a really serious base here
already
sure why not there's maybe there's a
better space for
for our base maybe we can maybe we can
look
we can spend our time looking for the
perfect place
yeah because eventually probably we want
to have it like really big right so
this area i think is not so suitable to
make such a big
big big big like um village
because i think everyone will be joining
us like
[Music]
okie dokie then let's get out of here
let's blow this popsicle stand let's get
out
i hate it i hate it so much hold on
let's
get moving i've trapped myself
underground and i don't know where i am
yeah that happens uh a lot ah give me
this coal
wait oh i think i got some gold oh what
no no no not gold i doubt it was gold i
think it's it's it's something else
it's uh it's like a yellow looking thing
for mining
you know certain materials you will not
be able to mine
uh properly if you just use a wooden
uh pickaxe you will need the diamond the
diamond pickaxe i have heard the legends
not the intelligence the diamond
pickaxes
i want one i want one
i get back outside uh almost ah we've we
did it
we did it deadbeats we're almost down to
the sun oh it's been so long i was
beginning to forget
what human faces looked like oh it's
gone my pickaxe is gone
wait i i'm probably broke already
because they the wooden things break
quite quickly
oh there we are oh hello i want i want a
new one
i have to go get the new one you
remember how to make a new one
yes i will now test myself
if i can remember how to make it
come here i made us a furnace
oh okay that's good we can roast the
chicken
oh no don't use that uh use use your
hand
um put the spruce logs
for the wood you should probably make um
an
axe okay that makes it much quicker and
easier oh i see
okey-dokey wow i'm so like i said
i'm like really bad at minecraft but
when i play with you i feel so good
about
myself hey what is that supposed to mean
i'm just happy that for one time i'm
able to teach someone something
it's fine i appreciate your help i
really do
thank you very much kusatori because i i
will not pretend like i am good at this
game
i don't know what i'm doing but i will
try my best how do i make this
the wooden axe needs spruces
i played minecraft for the first time
myself during stream
and it was so chaotic and so bad like i
died so many times so
i kind of wish that someone like oh my
teacher was with me at that moment i had
my viewers but still i died so many
times so i will protect you
so that you don't have to go for the
same suffering and pain
okay that's cool i mean true tr true to
your nature
you continue to come back so it makes
sense
yes have you already noticed
the addition to our camp the
furnace i haven't not yet i'm oh hold on
i don't think i'm actually actually
doing anything hold on
um yeah this is dirt
all right just a moment please how do i
make this pickaxe again
oak planks i don't have that birch
jungle um a pickaxe i feel like the axe
is a little
well i could actually make let's make
the axe i would like to make an axe
you need the axe for the wood and the
pickaxe for the stone yes
okay let me make the stick hold on the
stick is with the
spruce planks that it goes like like
this
you make it it's just saturday night so
yeah um wait hold on
i'm sleeping how do i make my stick how
do i make the stick
the sleep face wait no i have it stuck
in my hand
hang on go to bed
good morning okay so let me help you
you can just use the the recipe it's one
okay so i have this spruce oh no that's
a log
i need the plank hang one did you put
something in your
in your box that you need no it will not
automatically take
stuff from the box you have no no no i i
don't
how do i make the stick again ah the
stick um do you have planks
i do then put one plank above another
blank
okay there it did it okay i have four
sticks now and now i have many sticks
nice okay uh actually i think i can make
it
smelly good job thank you
i got it the axe is mine nice oh thank
you for the
spatcha ariato actually
now that we have some stones you could
also make a stone pickaxe or stone axe
let's make that instead because that
appears to be the more powerful weapon
the more powerful yatsu
hold on uh that's not that's not the
stone that i was seeking hold on
uh oopsie doodle um the stone pickaxe
give it to me
i have it now okay
i made an advancement good job
let me equip it i'm very excited
now i have many tools
and if you look at the furnace let me
tell you how it works
i have chicken right i do i have chicken
right click then put the chicken at the
top and coal
at the bottom okay you should have cola
in your inventory oh definitely
okay then it starts like it's cooking
yeah wow snack a little bit later and
pick up all everything but
how how low is your hunger um
let me check i'm not hungry at all i'm
only missing two
uh two chicken legs okay okay but even
then
you should always try to have it as full
as possible because if it's not full
it does not regenerate oh so
okay should i eat now then yes
okay i'll eat uh maybe not no okay
now that you're already cooking
something just eat the the one that's
already ready in the furnace
okay yeah i mean i took it out i took it
out it was it was completed
i will eat the chicken now yes
eat me i don't like i don't like chicken
but
i will i will eat it because it is all
that i have hold on
eat me no can you quit can you quit
oh my gosh
oh i hate it i offend my body to you
hold on where are the creepers
where are the zombies let's go straight
into them
they're not here right now kelly it's
just you and me you
and me and some cows and some pigs and
some
yeah where are you going away from you
you cannot escape can we find a place
for a house
okay
if we leave maybe we should bring some
of this stuff with us
that would be a good idea like like the
chest and whatnot
um it had some some rotting flesh in
there i'd like to keep
okay especially especially the the bats
we should bring
yesterday if you want to take it uh just
do right
uh like wait yeah left left click on the
bed okay
and then it's back in your inventory um
do i
so i break it like this yeah
don't worry okay break all of them all
the
stuff i guess yeah let's bring it all
do i need to this is for future
reference if i break the chest
uh does that destroy everything inside
the chest uh
it doesn't destroy it but it just like
scatters i guess
okay got it for future reference
okie dokie and the furnace
all right let's move it's moving yeah
uh which direction first snow
no it's fine okay yeah snow yes you want
to live in a snowy area
it's winter is my favorite season
i mean i love winter and i love the
snowy area but i wonder if it's good to
build like a whole
whole life ian empire there i want a
cabin i want a cabin
in the snowy mountains that's beautiful
yeah i've always dreamed of something
like that for me
but we don't have any place like that in
the underworld unfortunately
maybe a place that's just right in
between would be perfect
yeah oh my god there's a village there a
villa oh
fall damage oh no me too me too
did you see the village let's go there
there's a fellow having guna was
probably already there
i heard like she found like three
villages yeah
whoa do they have people in them uh yeah
usually yeah
wow she should probably have checked it
out during his stream since it's so
close
uh hang on let me use my sword to uh
hurt the pig
goodbye you will perish thank you for
the meal
all right i will find you now uh
interesting was she here i wonder if she
was here
huh i see a house there's smoke
wow um i on the village don't hit that
huge big golem thing okay what is he
like protecting the village
oh and like when at night the enemies
come to the village
the golem will protect the the villagers
it's really cool oh
i see that's very nice wow how very kind
yeah um apparently they're really
dangerous so you shouldn't hit them i
never tried but better not dry
okay yeah i mean i i mean i have no
problem i have no problem with homie
personally
um oh there's a farmer can i mess with
him he's got like a
funny nose uh
don't kill him he has his arms crossed
yeah he can like give you some stuff
maybe wait yeah but we don't have
diamonds and stuff right now so
okay like you use those farmers to like
exchange stuff
oh very important items oh not all done
but it's like random what they give you
is pretty random i see i sitting on the
farm
so sometimes you might want to kill them
oh okay cool i'm fine with that
burning here oh how do we stop it from
burning
is that a contained fire is it supposed
to burn i think it's supposed to
oh in the tree not very smart
i must say yeah let me get the tree
branches away
bye bye bye bye bye bye bye
since there's a village here i guess
it's actually smart
to have our whole life empire close by
because villages can be very useful
okay well let's let's do that let's let
us find some
some fresh soil to plant our seeds
i wonder if gooda already built
something up i wonder
for herself does someone maybe in the
chat no i'm not
uh i don't i'm not sure because i was
sleeping during
gunas same same i was not
i was there right for it
sorry sleepy reaper it's been a long
week
[Music]
he keeps sighing i don't like i don't
like that he keeps sighing
he keeps going and i'm like oh i want to
get away from you
i don't like it when people sigh all the
time it's fine but he sounds annoyed all
the time
is true that is true can you sleep in
other people's beds
yeah but when you do that your respawn
point will be set to that spot
oh okay i noticed that i see can you
talk to the people can you enjoy
a dialogue between them not really only
like
if you if you take some of amelia's
medicine and like imagine
they keep jumping up and down um
hold on a second it's like we're at a
rave a rave party
i'm checking out all the hockeys
sometimes in the in the houses they have
like
some special items oh it's like weird
asmr hold on a second
um i feel strange
it makes me feel strange um hold on what
are you doing
i was i was trying to converse with the
villagers i don't think that they speak
underworldy in english or japanese
so i think i'm just going to move along
um
i think gouda trapped some villagers
here because this is
not normal not normal where hold on i'll
find you i'll find you i need to keep a
better eye on you
kusatori yeah this is not natural i
think
did gooda trap some villagers here
coulda why would you do that
i want to see what is this
the ones that are sighing all together
uh there's an armor
i hate it so much yeah they sound rather
annoyed that they've
they're over there where are you i'm
gonna try to find you now
look show me show me see they're like
trapped
cool with right click you can open it
maybe she's saving them for later
yeah maybe she wants to eat them
yeah that that's what i was trying to
subtly i was trying to very subtly hint
at that
ah yeah
i wonder if she took everything
interesting from the
boxes so are we looting their homes yeah
okay excellent
i'm good at that but this is a nice home
we could take over this home there's
like
two to room apartment or too bad
apartment
we can kick out that stupid why are you
sleeping there i'm not i'm
i'm trying to open the oh this is a
crafting table okay cool
oh the villager this is probably sleepy
let me open this
oh cool some spruce locks get me
no put them together no they're
different woods
well into the hang on okay and then a
large fern
uh we probably won't use that so ah
seems useless seems like garbage maybe
i'll throw away all the uh plants it's
getting dark
oh yeah are we safe here in the village
tonight yeah
yeah i figured we might be safe here
yeah let us find a home to a home to
steal
let us find a home to steal i'll stay in
this one i like purple
okay okay no night
good night one second i'll i'll i'm
trying to enter one what
oh oh what
sorry one second i'm almost
ready to sleep a sleepy reaper
give me the mizu
where am i
sorry i got a bit lost it's fine i'm
just taking a little nap
i need to find something to sleep
uh oh goddammit you're in here okay no
problem
no i mean let me make my dream come true
i sleep next to you
huh wait wait wait wait hold on hold on
hold on i'm wide awake now
wide awake enough ow
rude that's a rude thing that you did
you can take the purple bed with you if
you want i can
yeah just left click oh sick give me
that i like purple
all right yeah let's make her forget
about what just happened very quickly
i will take another purple bed and i
want a crafting table
for myself because we only have one and
i want one for me
okay that's that's a good idea i really
like that we can just steal things from
these people
that doesn't seem like something you
should be able to do but we're able to
do it
well it's good to leave them some stuff
so that they survive overnight because
actually the game really likes to kill
off the villagers oh do they actually
need these things
yeah no passionately like if you just
leave some bats it's fine
oh well now i feel bad that i have taken
two instead of just one
don't worry about it that's nothing i
feel bad
well maybe mr golem will protect them
yeah mostly kind of you know what we can
do
did you see that little pool with the
bell
uh-huh what is that we can ring it
and then they panic they panic i wonder
why
did you hear the bell uh-huh i ranged
i ringed it i rang it make a bead out of
it
oh yeah callie come on hang on how do i
throw stuff away
music is there a way that i can throw
things away
yeah you have to like if you have your
inventory open you have to like throw it
out there
with left click oh but if you if you
stay there too long it just comes back
into your interview again kind of
annoying
oh okay now hold on there yeah i see you
i'm left clicking but oh you just throw
it out like um i get it
[Music]
you hear that uh-huh really
i do
ding-dong-ding-dong-ding-ding-ding-ding
okay sure thing here we go three two
one go uh hang on
i think this might be difficult the
reason being
um there is a lag come on stone um there
is a leg
hang on hang on
no no right click right click okay hold
on
go for it cali okay here we go
one two three four kill him with the
base
[Music]
let's leave can we leave this place good
job that was beautiful
i feel strange can we take the water
with us
uh why would you because maybe i want uh
i went to pool i went to swimming pool
and i mentioned we don't need that right
now kelly
priorities i don't care about that i i
want to have fun thank you for the for
the super chats guys by the way
and new members for joining us on the
journey
cali can i kill this guy i really don't
like the way that he's going to be
someone just kill me because i'll just
revive again but don't kill the
villagers they didn't do anything bad
oh thanks fam concert is free
but thank you
run and never come back
okay cali we need to find a home yeah
let's find a good space but
not none not in the in the it's good to
have the snow area close by i would say
but we should
try to get on a more normal temperature
area okay i think also for like farming
and
and stuff oh i suppose that is a thing
that we have to do yes
yeah give me this rotting flesh find
something nice
well let us find a good spot are there
fishes here
oh there are squid can i kill them
no you can't eat them i never tried to
kill one though i wonder what happens
will they try an f-word with us no no no
not at all
yeah they have like some sharp teeth and
i'm curious
okay it looks kind of weird yeah a
little spooky i like it though
so i heard a growl yeah
it comes instead of skrillington i think
that was a zombie
find the ocean that's where gira built
her house
what of course sasuke someone know the
coordinates oh no see she did she did
build
something hey there's another village
like when i played minecraft the other
day for the first time in my life
it took me ages to find a village i
couldn't even find it after three hours
so what the hell
sorry but a little sausage control use
control
the snowy village yes oh snowy village
hold on
i'm there i'm there
i'm really low on health
oh my god there's so much breath bread
i could use some bread right now you
hungry
yes i am where are you in the first
house
in the village okay i'm on my way
for you thank you i'm so hungry
i guess this one was not completely
plundered by gurayet
it seems not which all the better for us
yeah
now my health will regenerate okay okay
wow it's really good to have so many
villages close by we're
really lucky man mm-hmm this is a nice
area
this nice little cabin house that i want
all here let me in
actually you can make bread yourself if
you get some of these
apples there are so many apples and
breads and potatoes
i'll leave some for you i'll take half
for me and i'll leave half for you
here and i'll leave you a potato as well
but let's see i got already a bunch of
potatoes oh okay then i'll take the
potatoes
uh hold on wait yeah okay you took okay
yay okay uh i'll empty out some of the
stuff that i don't want here
bye-bye bye-bye dirt don't need it
goodbye goodbye
pumpkin seeds i kind of want one of
those
wow this house has a balcony how nice
balcony i want to see two-story houses
balcony
and the pool right in front of it a pool
this sounds like let's type a place i
want to live but i want to make it
myself
do i have to look to the left to the
left to the left behind you
left behind you oh here and no hello
hello
it's another villager he's got a funny
hat you look like a bandit
but no i was talking to oh i see you i
see you i'm coming up i want to get on
the top of the balcony as well
and then jump into the pool yes oh my
gosh what
that sounds so dope hold on oh it's a
cannon ball
oh no just kidding get a ball oh no it's
not working yeah it doesn't work
let's get rid of that yeah get rid of
this fence just break it wait hold on i
want to use
my hand
okay so what i learned is to not do that
yeah
thanks for taking the fall for me
kusatori
i can i will always be a test object
don't worry
oh i kind of yeah i mean well it makes
sense you're a phoenix right so
yeah i feel too bad about it what do you
feel about bats there's a bag in the sky
in the sky yeah it's flying around
oh a bat oh how cute look at them go
hello
you got yourself some bats as pets maybe
i wonder if that's possible
really i want a pet bat it doesn't look
like the other creatures though it looks
like um
not made of blocks yeah you can you can
kill it and stuff
oh you can probably capture it i wish i
had some
[Music]
no unfortunately chad says no it's not
possible
did the chad also tell you good ass
coordinates by any chance uh no i don't
believe so
god damn it unfortunately
we need to build close to buddha i know
maybe we should head towards the ocean
does this game have a map by chance
uh uh you can make yourself a map
but for that you need materials okay
until then you can just uh go by
coordinates i hope he's a kitty
kitty yeah
[Music]
yeah you can actually capture cats and
have them as a pet we should get like a
full house of
kill the cats
you need to have like raw fish with you
and then you can like
have them follow you i love that
yeah cool
interesting animals it's always good to
just get some more of that meat for
later
yeah i found a ton more bread and apples
by the way
nice i'll gather it and we can share
there are beds in here so i'll go to
sleep uh in the beds here
sure uh obviously since there's two beds
i'll just have to sleep on the other one
right
yes uh yes they are far enough away from
each other that this is fine
this is fine uh nightingale
night at night
good night i'll be honest again it's
really nice villages
get out get out get out oh my god
this is their house
did you notice a change in the beds but
any chance
did i notice
[Music]
let's move right along into the next
segment of the game
i kind of swore it was snowing here but
now it's not oh
yeah probably there again
we need to find a home yeah
no i would prefer that we start our own
village
personally um so we just need to find
the perfect land
what you hit me i i tried to hit the
chicken
with your sword it's [\h__\h] up watch
yourself
the potato okay let's move on let's move
on
oh yeah keep on moving oh there's a cute
cat
whoa that mountain's nuts can we live at
the top of that
um that would be a bit annoying nah it'd
be awesome
going up and down and up and down it's
kind of cool though can we live close to
it
oh problem i'll build my layer all the
way up there
so you you can have your home at the
bottom and i will be at the top
oh there's the ocean wow that's so cool
cool island
so it's mountain in the ocean gouda must
be close to here
yeah where did you build your place
there's a turtle hello he's a turtle
can we turn him into an item we can ride
on it i think i
think i saw that all aboard
yeah go back to your natural home buddy
this is such a beautiful place we got a
really nice seed
you know what that means professional
minecraft talk
seed is like the word you you spawn in
oh
i see a seed like some people
they try to speed run the game but um
depending on the scene you have like
more luck or
worse luck yeah what you have to in
order to speedrun the game
i think i get it interesting
well this is also probably not the best
area to build
a whole empire no i guess not where
should our empire be
close to one of them hey is there
something floating in the sky over there
have you ever heard of clouds no okay
listen it just didn't show up
show up until i got closer to it thanks
for the super chat by the way
come on let me ride on you wait i am
riding on the dolphin right now
oh my god oh hold on i'm riding on a
dolphin
whoa i'll check that out in just a
minute hold on
but not anymore
ah okay so someone someone just said
that a girl was trolled by a super chat
that said
that pressing f3 gives away your ip so
she never used
her coordinates the entire stream okay
we have to tell her so we need to tell
her afterward that it's fine
okay i think i asked kiara five times if
it would show my ip
oh my god that's a real shame anyway i
lost you but i hope you had fun with a
dolphin
yeah have fun look around here there's
like a huge pond here
okay cool uh someone said that good is
near by the way
oh really yes wow okay okay hold on
okay oh i would like to come over are
you riding a dolphin now
apparently yes i am i am going to now
join you
i want to ride again not anymore when
did the dolphin go you see the dolphin
how how do i catch on to him uh
you try to get close to him okay
and try not to die because like you
don't have endless breath on the right
uh-oh let me go catch my breath
squeaky noises you sound like a squishy
toy
hold on hello i would like to write on
your back sir
wait how do i grab onto them oh i think
i'm writing one
to you you don't even have a choice oh
well let's go uh oh
hold on back to the surface
you just did a jump i think you just
wrote on it i think cool i'm not sure
cool that was fun uh i'm now tired of
that
so okay let's get out of here but that
was fun
off we go um so
i've heard i got i heard it's the word
on the street
that gouda is close by if we're on the
ocean
i bet that we can run along the coast of
the ocean and find where gouda is
did you make a little house i wonder i
wonder we might be able to tell if it's
her
but i don't know which direction is it
maybe we should part ways here and you
go and one and i go in the other
that is also a possibility hold on let
me find out
whoever first finds a house but that's
not
that might take an eternal league
let's just keep on running and find a
good spot for our empire i would say
okay maybe we'll be close to the sand
they said close to the sand
she's got a horse apparently oh yeah i
heard
wow
yeah maybe it is a volcano i f-word hard
with it
let us run along the coast maybe we can
find her
maybe there's more sound over there okay
let's go i i need to press control but i
must stretch it like
let's go sugarino goes well thank you
for the super chat i will be sure to
read that at the after the stream
tonight
thank you for giving cali super chats
yeah someone wanted to give you a shout
out so
see you you are going too far from the
server entrance that
someone said yeah oh someone wanted me
to shout out to
my wife yes we're two hold on
i i read someone sent a super chat that
said that uh we're
kind of far from where the spawning the
first spawning point of the server is
yeah we are so what uh maybe maybe what
they mean to say is that good
was closer to that area but i don't know
[Music]
either way um but still i don't think
that area was good for
our empire what's this if we just tell
good at our coordinates eventually we'll
find each other
what is this it looks like a gate to
another world
wait what this has golden leggings flint
steel gold pickaxe and gold axe in the
chest
oh you found oh wait
wait did gouda make that ah i don't know
it's not finished it's not finished oh
yeah
yeah with that actually yeah we can try
to stay closer here because then we can
probably out of that try not to jump
into the lava spot there oops
oh my god anyway this is cool hey what
did you
can i take it can i take it oh
yeah they kind of um just be careful to
not lose their flint and the steel
okay yeah the golden items often just uh
break
quite quickly and easily should i put
them on
golden leggings yeah golden leggings
how nice should i put them on yeah
i'm putting them on wow you're so shiny
whoa
look at that it glows the golden pants
damn cool yeah
okay are we sure that this isn't good is
it
goudas or something like that i don't
know it's
just lucky you take your bed back
i don't want it i have too many okay
let's keep moving um
i feel like
this whole area
uh for a long long time
[Music]
continues to be very um very much
up and down and up and down yeah there's
not really a flat space but i kind of
like i like this
i like this big place right here should
we just build like
start building right here and eventually
we can always always just try to make it
flat or move eventually yeah this this
seems perfect to me start to start
making our empire here then
between the mountains with some water
with that
uh health broken navigate yes
perfect let's do it
and snow like we have everything around
us yay
the ocean is close too perfect okay so
what are you making you're
trying to i'm flattening out the area
nice so that we can build a home uh let
me
place all our boxes
you're so shiny i know right i love it
will this protect me from monsters
a little bit yeah i see it's gonna start
getting dark
yeah we should place our bed we should
let us do that
very quickly hold on wait um okay
place put it in the thing put it out in
the thing
no put the feather back hold on okay i'm
gonna place it now
goodnight yay goodnight my wife
what
[Music]
smash just like how i smashed you last
night
sorry sorry like what the [\h__\h]
i got that from amelia i got that from
amelia yeah i figured as much i figured
you got it
like i smashed your mother last night
she keeps like i got them from her i
honestly was inspired by her now okay
it's really yeah rather irreverent right
the irreverent one
yes uh-huh i usually don't do these kind
of jokes okay
yeah i'll let you have it i'll let you
have it this that's quite it's quite
it's a lot free than you acoustatory but
i'll i'll let you i'll let you i'll let
it slide this once
oh my god i wish i've been saying that
it's okay i understand uh amelia has
that kind of influence
i was inspired it's okay we all get a
little inspired sometimes
yeah amelia is such a great inspiration
and that's my box oh i keep forgetting
that uh the way that you toggle it
is by the left key so i almost end up
breaking every chest that i opened
teehee
tv takes a little bit longer to break
anyway so yeah
thank goodness all right so i would like
to completely destroy this mountain
hey what or rather this this little
mountain
at a mountain okay look
listen yes
i don't have my words right now a sleepy
reaper
there's still much to be done you're
always so sleepy you need to take more
time off callie
nah actually i'm supposed to i'm
supposed to stream again in um about 40
minutes
yeah yeah
it's a celebration muricinaida kidzo
kidzo
[Music]
okay that's english all right let me
make
i need to make another pick
[Music]
okay so yeah i'm helping now thanks for
the akka spa by the way
it's very sweet yeah and the other spots
um i have a golden pickaxe maybe i
should save it
not necessarily but should i use it save
it
for i guess it could work if you see a
diamond but until then
if you find diamonds by that time you
will already have a iron pickaxe
and with an iron pickaxe you can mine
diamonds
okay then forget it bye whoa look at it
go
yeah bye i just you i just use it once
it's just a quick hit
bye bye see you see you see you see you
see you see you see you see you see you
see you see you see you bye bye bye
there he goes coming to your chat chad
says to say
chad says to save it oh yeah it has silk
attached probably here it goes
silk patch i forgot what that does but
it's special
oh well a little too late that's fine
we'll find another yep it's gone
well it's fine it's fine just gotta get
lucky just gotta get lucky again
oh we'll find all kinds of special stuff
again
[Music]
but i know how you feel that happened to
me in my first minecraft stream as well
you got you got a golden pickaxe that
you immediately wasted
i got a bunch of golden stuff yeah and i
thought it would
since it's golden and shiny i thought it
would be more durable but it wasn't
very disappointing it's it's
no problem it's fine it happens to the
best of us let's make let's
make a an iron an iron pickaxe gosh how
do i do that
i need couples no i mean
sorry a stone stone i need cobblestone
and sticks
let
yeah i want to it's fine
hey what are you streaming tomorrow no
yeah tomorrow
is a break
then i hope you get a nice night sleep
tomorrow
thank you i appreciate it
always important to take some days off i
know but i forget that a lot of times
you seem to forget that yeah yeah
actually today all right this stream
is the first time you used a new
computer no um
i want to talk about it how's it going
like it's it's pretty good
wait first real quick how do i change
the log into the plank again
for the maximum amount the maximum uh
shift and then on the on the
blank shift on the plan okay got it
sorry thank you all right yes anyway
um yeah new computer i'll go back and we
can look at the
the specs in a minute um but yeah i
didn't really know how to um
uh i did for a quick moment a quick
moment
show them again yeah i will now show the
people uh the specs hold on
just simulate uh no wait okay and then
f3
here it is wait i mean i don't know [\h__\h]
about computers but
let me see it says cpu
[Music]
616x amd uh
risen seven through it's a it's a seven
uh three seven zero zero x eight core
processor
um the graphics card is that the rx five
seven zero zero is that it
yes rx five seven zero xt
i haven't had any problems nice
yeah i mean it's it's a bit it's a big
boy um people are saying it's a gamer pc
gamer chat they'll say it's a gamerpc
oh is it pretty good is it pretty good
yay i
i wanted to talk uh more about the
actual pc
later i'm waiting on a couple things but
i wanted to give a bit a big
shout out uh a big shout out to um to
the the people that helped me get this
thing so
um but for now yeah i'm it's it's a big
boy um
so i'm glad to introduce i hope smoke
[\h__\h] can pay a visit
um today i think that smith will be able
to pay a visit
uh maybe after a long absence yes
exactly smoke [\h__\h] will come back soon
it's possible now with a good gaming pc
uh-huh
again a guest reappearance from smoke
goon
um yeah wait i need to make up another
pickaxe
um so how do you get the stone again
where is the stone i wonder
in here just on the ground everywhere oh
well then what have i been picking where
is oh i think i have it in my inventory
i just
there's like a house there's kind of
stone too though oh okay i need
cobblestone or
stone or wait let me give you
cobblestone oh thank you there we go
they're here here here yes oh someone
said
good they're good okay yes it is at 480p
because i'm not playing
i'm not i'm not playing full screen wait
maybe that doesn't matter maybe i can
change
anyway but i have to hold on one second
why can't i make the stone pickaxe then
uh you have hold on a couple yeah i do
wait i only have one
lol of course of course let's make
another freaking
stick hold on
okay um with the planks the spruce
make the stick give me the stick
there it is okay i gotta
whoa there's a little ding sound is that
you yeah it's me
oh i'm gonna fill up whatever i'm
digging right now because there's a
some coal i want to get that and then
fill it up with normal stone
[Music]
give me the give me another one another
axe just to be safe you know you can
just use the
the the recipe book oh yeah i guess
that's right i keep forgetting let's see
whoopsy doodle please
can you put it back how i craft my
recorders oh it's a big secret
no no put it back stop put it back
what is it not hang on
it isn't doing what i want it to
the cobblestone can you just i don't
want to
switch with the flower forget this
i have this don't pick x um oh gosh i
really only have about three or so more
minutes to play this with you
kiana it really is yeah is there an
ending
then quickly let's just make something
like a bunker okay cool let's do it real
quick let me finish
let me finish this real quick yeah we
need to make uh i would at least i would
be happy if we at least had some solid
walls around us
what material should we use stone
actually i would prefer wood but we
don't have so much do we oh i
suppose i could chop some trees soon
okay
[Music]
okay then yeah let's make it out of wood
i'll delete my
my stone wall again i love
wood planks i would say they look nice
i'll go do some chop chop choppy chop
wait i have no eggs
do you need one no you're good
i'll make my own okay um
i put this here okay
i think that the sun is going down uh-oh
we can go for a sleep sleep okay night
it says you can only sleep at night or
during thunderstorms yeah almost almost
let me eat the spread
i guess i didn't really need to do that
huh oh well
i mean my health was full i probably
didn't need to do that but how well
good night
[Music]
i'm excited for the next the next year
where we play
this game together when should we do it
kiara
next week anytime but yeah next week
maybe
okay cool morning look at the beds again
look don't they look nice
why do you keep why do you keep doing
that it looks so good what is the
purpose
what is the purpose of doing that i'm to
sleep with you
no i don't like it
just get used to it no get used to it
yeah
let's see all right i'm gonna start
building a wall here this is like
actually like unfortunately it can't
save me from you right next to you yeah
sometimes i choose to ignore it other
times
i just made a wall there and then i got
rid of it again because i thought we're
making it out of out of
tree oh okay
yeah i suppose we can go chop down some
trees i do have a an axe to chop
trees
by the way um like if
if you chop the tree i don't know if you
know this but if you chop the tree and
you get like
look here to this point where it's gone
uh-huh if you look up there's still more
up there
oh there's chocolate yeah
tree tree tree
yay i got some wood now we need more
yeah into the forest we go
let's just get as much as uh possible
speed run speed right here
what do you have any vgm on
from like yourself do i have any what
any pgm
no uh-uh because i didn't want it to
interrupt the minecraft occasional music
um oh by the way thank you for the akka
spa
oh i look very angry i've been looking
very angry
oh actually calling the next minecraft
to collab we can do on my channel
okay yeah sounds good
yay i'll make the thumbnail though let
me make the thumbnail because i have it
because they have numbers on them
i was thinking like since you made those
numbers if you were like
i'm planning to just like stream
minecraft like every week or like if
you're planning to
stream minecraft with me every week yeah
it's a collaboration
we didn't even talk about this oh hello
i just kind of assumed westy doodle
i'm sorry our minecraft collaboration is
like a thing now nice yes i thought it
would be fun
yes we have many things to do we must
begin to create the empire
we have like a regular collab going on
indeed well i have the [\h__\h] in kitchen
right
so i figured with the others and then
eventually i'd like to play bloodborne
with ena so then i have a collab
with everyone okay so our thing is
minecraft oh that's
i love it i love you yeah you're fine
too
you're fine we'll go
you know there's so many things you can
do in minecraft i know i've noticed
you've shown me oh the axes x's bye-bye
okay uh
maybe i can use it maybe we have enough
almost
yeah pickaxe is really not good for the
wood huh okay well let's go ahead and
just take what we have
and then we'll make it planks out of all
of it first oh right now yeah
yeah make something you can't just put
the tree stumps down huh
i think you can that doesn't look so
nice yeah sure doesn't and i'm all about
that interior design though
oh yeah there's a pig that's trying to
get into our house
now he's not i just want to kill him
i'm hungry thank you
thank you for the bacon bacon
bacon okay now let us
let oh yes that's right we must craft
the planks
here we go i have this [\h__\h] spruce locks
shift please oh i got different colors
but oh well
it's fine i think it'll still look nice
yeah
the spruce logs and then
no do you also have two colors
um i
i don't think so wait no stop
i think i just have the um
spruce i think i have just one hold on
the dark one uh let me find out
uh so i have spruce planks spruce planks
so so this is what i have here hold on
uh this this one hang on
okay then i'll also mainly use that one
and then the lighter one i use for
something else cool
okay let's make it like as tall as
possible
yes good idea yeah we don't want to feel
like we're suffocating
in our beautiful home true
no i guess i have to jump huh this is
not the way to do it yeah you know how
to do it yep
space oh hold on okay
and then i left a space for windows for
a window right here
little window oh i want a window there
okay now of course my my room will be
underground
uh where there's no sunlight but i
thought that a window might be kind of
nice for those of you who do enjoy
sunlight
because apparently that is something
that humans enjoy sunlight
for the most part then there are others
like me who aren't such a big fan
nope that's not what i meant to do
i think we should keep going for a bit
because i i feel terrible if the stream
is only
an hour 20 minutes oh
well yeah i don't mind i'm here for you
for until
the end of time trying to say nothing
romantic but yeah i didn't know what to
say
you're you're good um cool maybe five
more minutes
or so but we're not done building the
house
hey we will get done soon okay
it will be on soon get it
how how many blocks should it be tall um
maybe one more
okay because i'm slowly running out of
them
this is fun i love this cali i love you
yeah i don't hate it
wait i can't how do i fl how do i get
higher up on the thing i can't get up on
the
oh yeah you kind of yeah just use
another block to get up there
obsidian room that's a good idea
i like that idea an obsidian room for me
it's pure black and it has torches you
should just live in the never just try
to
sleep in the nether yeah another sounds
like my kind of place to be honest
yeah it's really cool to sleep there
yeah
sounds fun i tried this before oh yeah
how did that go for you
oh well very well i can only recommend
it chad is that true
oh yeah
i'm doubting but the nether does sound
nice
sounds like home uh
are we getting we're bumping into whoa
i'll leave it to you and then maybe a
staircase we have a staircase here
that leads up to a second floor i think
yeah for now we can leave it like this
okay that's fine and then monsters can't
get in like this right
uh they should yeah as long as there's
no stairs like from outside
okay i can make a i think i can make us
a door
cool do that yeah
maybe two doors i think the ceiling
should be a bit higher ah
yeah but i think we need more wood oh
well
for now this is fine one two
and another window here excellent
okay this will do for now
ah huh
come here look i made the door
oh yeah look just a moment
ah very nice looks good if you right
click you can open it but you should
always close the door behind you
uh of course of course the enemies will
this is customary
i'm gonna make a back door um
[Music]
okay so for now this is this is decent
enough
i accepted
i accept it
wait something changed here
[Music]
no stop
yes you're gonna pay the price now i
have both
no stop enough i have actually though
i have to the purple bag what the heck i
will decide
your bed must be here
there you go okay i'm fine with this
arrangement stop
stop building my own house
hey no okay okay you sleep over there
it's okay
you sleep there and i i sleep
here okay
i don't know what will happen at night
you know i don't know i might be asleep
sleep uh walking i cannot and
it was not my fault if i sleepwalk by
accident on top of your bed and then lay
down there
not my fault
and now it's turning night so in that
sense i guess good night
good night
sleeping okay
i guess we can go ahead and end it here
then
what did you do you know no
no stop it
can you quit
well i'm dumb i'm done playing this game
for now
it was fun it was fun it was fun
oh stop yachting idiot
stop gross gross
away get away no let me out
exit the game exit the game exit the
freaking game
okay anyway um
i guess that's all i just disconnect
right is is is that is that it
oh yeah okay cool disconnecting
okay cool i'll miss you
yeah okay
we are in my room now ah double audio
now
uh sorry kiara i had to mute you oh man
too bad what a shame
i can hear you but the audience can't t
or else there will be dual audio it's
okay i'll let you go ahead and hold on
you can say goodbye
hang on one sec one sec say goodbye
she said goodbye to you okay
i think that that's what that was is
goodbye yeah
okay thanks for joining kusotorios pray
form
all right you're muted again no it
wouldn't make it
i wouldn't want to play the actual music
[Music]
yeah there she goes she'll probably stay
in the room
as i as i say goodbye to oh my gosh
okay the dance is kind of hold on let me
move the very high resolution
okay it's pretty funny you've got some
moves i i give
okay you do have some moves hold on
i can't believe how much how much you
can move
i'm a little jealous i'm a little
jealous i mean i
i actually no i'm not really jealous
because i also have my my own lovely
movements
like my hair but you're you're very
bouncy
i think it fits you though i feel like
that's embarrassing
look at her oh man there she goes
there she goes she's uh
she's really she's really giving it a
roll
look at her dance geez i can't believe
something really wait don't fly around
my room
why are you doing that what are you
doing
no stop it okay now listen that's where
you have to freaking swerve
you weirdo gosh no
stop hold on bring up the bring up
get away from me
oh my god my album is floating in front
of us
[Music]
stop stop you can't enough
the sick mixtape is in front of me
it's not as bad as the wine cooler
though
jeez you are nuts stop get off my chair
i have to say goodbye to the humans all
right guys i'm your mori hope you'll
remember me sierra bye peace out goodbye
see you
so say goodbye i'm not sorry but i wanna
see you again sometime
a song in my heart a world of worry
falling on your mind wait don't we leave
it all behind
[Music]
a heart
peace
so freaking weird
you