oh no fell into the ab unknown left me
bleeding heartless all
[Music]
alone no
control don't you dare
apologize turn my back and the cold no
listen up CU here some advice
[Music]
you're at the time way out of line it's
taking over like around g i for a night
I'll make you
cry tearing it down do you s keep
calling me no you think
so got me
[Music]
Twisted taking the crown now you calling
me King you going to hear I'm sing sing
back it up don't back it up keep that
aim I got B that will drive you insane
come over if you like we'll have a lot
of fun but I got a lot of buying I do
what I want make sure you don't forget
it an Army on my back say I'm sick I'm
just a distance living in the L in the
line I want to see the way you pleased
it's taking over like rate I for a lie
I'll make you
cry tearing it down to just water not
keep calling me yes no you think
so got me
Twisted taking the crown now you calling
me King you going to hear my Sing Now
sing Lou
I want it all so give me some more
Flames burn me up down into my core oh
you wish I'd stay down but then I just
rise you're not my
enemy baby your dad's a man hear my
voice screaming out loud no doubt yeah
la
la tearing it down
just keep calling me yes
think got
Ted taking the crown you calling me
King La La La Te
every La La La La La La Te every
[Music]