[Music]
n
oh
[Music]
la
hi darling oh hi you Darlings hi
Darlings it's your devilish Diva this is
Hell live English Advent devilish Diva
the one and only narissa Raven cof here
today with your intro is way longer than
mine it's so much harder to remember
k sorry for the wait yes uh we got
caught in a rainstorm
yeah we're not dead um so but we can't
really use it as an excuse we would have
been late anyway yeah we were we were
going to probably be late but we
definitely were slightly more late
because we were rained on so we had to
change well I had to change clothes cuz
I got completely
soaked oh how are we doing jail Birds I
miss you
guys how you doing hi how how you doing
how you doing how you doing oh you how
was it
going how romantic well it was really
beautiful we we had Barbecue on the
beach which I don't know it was very
overpriced yeah yeah no it was super
overpriced what 6 for 75 75 per person
per person but then the weird thing was
it it mentioned that there was a
10% uh service charge yeah service
charge which is fine but what it didn't
mention is there was a an additional 16%
charge but it didn't say what were the
letters it said GST and I was like um
general service tip general service tip
but they already had the service charge
so it was kind of weird
um so the full the full Bill we didn't
even eat that much it it came up to over
2090 yes it was over 200 was it yeah
holy yeah holy over 200 and
then rained on us yeah oh what if GST
stands
for uh uh 16% for
tourist generic generic storm Tropic
general sales
tag this the the storm was charged why
can't I hear the game
anymore I muted it oh so that we can
first maybe not be distracted by
the jail birds and kfb does doesn't that
singer like remind you of narissa cuz I
was like oh it's narissa
singing uh speaking of me singing did
you guys see I have a new cover coming
out it just got put on Premiere today
when is it coming out I don't know you
know no you're just like me because I
didn't know that an hour ago our new the
myth new original song came out I was
dining without Wi-Fi I had no idea wait
it's out guys did you like it can I ask
there can I ask here guys did you listen
to it did you like it I didn't I didn't
see anyone's reactions yet I'm so sad
yeah what is it tell me about the song
uh give me your ad I I don't even
remember it well I recorded it 5 million
years
ago there's like there's some really fun
fast Parts uh but I'm not singing those
I think I'm I'm singing uh like um the
singing part GDA and cie are rapping in
it ooh yeah like Kelly was like okay who
who wants to rap G signed up for
it it was great it was great it was
great it was amazing really I was
surprised did you like it like because
um I feel like you know up until now
myth songs were like all pretty like
mythical right like legendary epic
mythical but um this was kind of offered
to us as a new original song that was
kind of like in in like lying around for
a long time was like hey we actually
have this do you guys want to like
release this for your anniversary I'm
like eh yeah yeah I mean it's very
different from the previous ones but I
think it's really good to have something
different really um upbeat uh exciting
Vibe so you didn't listen to it yet
right so we got to listen to it after
the stream you have never heard it
before no oh it's very high energy yeah
I'm very
excited I love my my Dy thank you I love
Advent Dy
no just love me okay okay that's that's
I can do that um yeah but today we are
here to play um Smash and it's funny so
Kiana after I finished playing and said
that I unlocked everyone so I need to
fully transparent I I have everyone
except one it's a DLC character oh wow
um it's the piranha plant I didn't I
didn't buy it well that's fine like one
character whatever hey is that the only
DLC character I bought every other DLC
character why did you not buy what
what's your problem with pirna BL why do
you so much I don't know why I don't
have him because like I bought all the
packs and everything but I must much how
much money was
that
anyway how there's a lot of DLCs right
yeah why are they separate how much do
one are there all like one character uh
I don't think so I didn't really look at
the price I just bought them it was
pre-order oh can you not get it anymore
anyway I know you got it for free during
the if you pre-ordered it but oh okay
well we don't need it you basically have
all characters okay I'm going to turn
the game sound on cuz you guys are like
no game sound no game sound where's the
game sound okay can you hear it yes oh
my God it's so loud wait they can't hear
it they they that's us
wait I thought it was going for there
too no wait
huh wait I think this one M
angle speak to me
game oh yeah that went
through you can look here I look for OBS
screen or because you know I brought two
screens to the males so each person has
one screen but I'll look for
obs
are you guys ready to
smash yes H yes we are okay
so we can can hear it yeah yeah ah very
good very good very good wait did you
set
e a you said normal latency yeah that's
because we're we're in the Mal Dives you
guys I connections bad I had a yeah and
your computer was struggling yesterday
no it was fine what do you mean I didn't
have headphones on so I could hear it oh
that's just how it always acts my laptop
even at home it it gets really loud well
you guys are just going to have to deal
with it one sec my leg my
leg uh what do you want the everything
to be how many lives how I don't care I
think you know more about this than me
now no I don't Mama Mia I thought I'm
playing with an experienced player
[Music]
here o I don't need a
name um we went snorkeling today guys o
yeah we did that was fun wait did you
well you we we choose the the location
first oh yeah join in wa you have to
link sorry I got be excited to link oh
we should do maybe random even but can I
play with to L whoever you want I'm
going to
oh where are you
searo have you ever played Zelda games
close have you ever played Zelda games
of course I have which one did you play
um my very first one was the N64 classic
Ocarina of Time and then uh I know of
the GameCube ones because I watch my
sisters play but I never got to play so
Wind Waker I never got to play so with
uh Twilight Princess you play Twilight
Princess no I watched my sister play
Twilight Princess I play my brother play
a lot of games I watch my brother play a
lot of oh and sorry guys even though
this is on my page as youve realized I
am takanashi Kiara
today uh with the opening screen in the
chat and the end screen later
too Goa sorry that doesn't no no no no
no I'm just hijacking I'm just hijacking
yeah no I'm talking
sh
okay oh play SE he's naked can you put
on a shirt no does he have
nipples yes I don't know that's quite
important if I lose it's because I'm
playing for the OBS screen it's okay I
don't remember and I actually have our
faces in the way oh but they actually
positioned perfectly can you can you
give me like some warm up time I I'm
trying to warm up I don't remember how
to play it's been five Millen years
hey hey hey is
Crossing how do I fight
oh
what imagine being seph off like the big
bad in your game series shark wa how do
I
jump I'm losing to T link no you're not
losing wait I literally don't know how
to do anything
sh no hey I helped you snork
how dare how dare you hey hey is this
how you repay me I don't I can't see it
in the screen it's too
small wait I don't even know any buttons
okay okay so okay this one's jump I hear
BM BM B wait jump right jump jump is X
okay oh sorry then one of your attacks
is
a I picked up an item I didn't want um
then b is another
attack okay uh B it up yep B so for mine
mine does this weird like thing okay
wait how do I throw the
bomb um what bomb this one guys how do I
throw the bump probably hit the button
again it might it might be this button
oh okay wait try it wait B no where the
B where ah it is that one okay so uh
this one to
shield and the more you use it as you
know it runs out which one this yeah
yeah
hey
hey no no no no what why is there
another person here what did you guys
get into the game how did you get into
the game what no no what happened no one
else is here who's you invited another
person to this party I thought this was
our private island I don't I don't know
who this I don't know what's happening
um it's not
fair bro who was that oh wait can I have
that please what's wrong with
[Applause]
you I I I don't really remember how to
use it yeah me
neither I don't know what the I'm
doing I noticed and like same oh my God
this is like not fair I'm like getting
chased by bees be
beans I love beans oh we talked about
the Bee Movie today cuz at the dinner
there was a saxophone player who was oh
who was playing jazz so I asked I asked
narissa you like jazz and you didn't
even understand the question at first so
I had to remind you of the Bee Movie
even though you saw it and I never saw
it look who actually sees the Bee
Movie
you sepharon what a
surprise he he oh sure okay uh that was
a interesting warm-up match