[Music]
[Applause]
D
[Music]
[Applause]
H
[Applause] [
Music] [Applause] [Applause] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Applause]
AK
[Music]
[  [Applause]
[Applause]
[Music]
T
[Applause]
DET A
[Music]
[Applause]
This program is brought to you by the sports you are watching
[Music]
Masu
All High
[Music]
Allwelcomethe
poipEP
[Music]
[Applause]
Hey
[Music]
MySoundboardbest
way
ever
are
[Music]
while everyone,
MISTLetme
EXPSHOWknow I'll give you a little explanation first.
Please listen to me for a second.
isTalkWithThepurpOf
inter
andlyJapanesetalto
BRAS
is an interview talk show for English subjects.  The main purpose of this program is to let
people overseas know more about Japanese talent through live translation and interpretation.
Today is the 30th time for me to send it to you.
[Music]
Thank you.
[Music] I'm
nervous,
but
beep All please.
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
Please say hello to everyone. Also, please introduce yourself.
[Music]
Oh, wait, I'm sorry, I'm
sorry, it's muted. It might have been muted, sorry.
Wait a minute, I guess I made a mistake.
Oh, I fixed it.
Sorry.  It
was a pompon. Yes, I'm healed. I'm
sorry. Please start again from the beginning.
[Music]
Generation. It's
different. It's a different JP generation volume.
Thank you.
Ifuji Uo, I'm a 4th generation student. I'm a 4th year student.  It's been a long
time since I've been a member, but now it's dangerous. I sometimes say that it's dangerous, right?
Kiaro-senpai, please don't get me wrong, please don't misunderstand me,
happenstosay
that waynotlikethat
japanesat
so oh so cute, oh cute, close up, so
embarrassing.
Question: What kind of activities have you been doing recently?
Oh, today, I went to that corner-wrapping hub anis
day
. I went there today. That's why I got up early.
That's right. Oh, it's a hub nice day. You
can't tell me what you did.
Eh, today.  I told you about the card game. I
told you about the card game. It's a
secret only here. That
's today, but basically it's a little rougher.
Yeah, live concerts and music sounds. Yeah, yeah, yeah,
where's the
live show recently
? I wonder if it's recent. Second live in January. Is it
still recent after all? It's
not recent, it's not recent, it's okay.
I askedWhatbeenup
recentlyandoneofthe
ThingsShesaidisjust
todayShewokeupearly
becauseSherecorded
forHaveanicedayShe
WillIthinkexpltoUSa
LittleBitlaterina
different question
butIwaslikeOhSurely
notgnatelluswhatyou
didrightnotspoilIT
butdidspoilwasdoing
someCardGAMEthis timeinteresting Maybe need MA Littlehave
upMONandsaysJanuary
had
herercouldthink
that I see, Kao
English is cool
Delicious berry cool English Oma
Senpai is cool too Cool Ship, really
Yes, Cool Ship Yoon Kushi is a sheep basically
Cute but cool Ship is only Bame
Senpai  No, I don't
think so. It's a really good program.  I'm
curious about this. How did you first
find Hololive and what made you want to join it again
? I
saw Hololive's 3D wide screen by Kayuokaunkoro.
What is this?  Also, that was the first time I
saw Hola Live content. I think that's it. Yeah, I
knew that other vtuber a little bit, but yeah,
that Kinaai, I see.
Yeah, yeah, Hololive is crazy.  That's
probably the first thing I did,
and I'm so grateful. That's
how I found it. That's how I got into it.
At that time, I was singing songs
as a hobby, and I wanted more people to listen to them.
Yeah,
that's what I was thinking, or rather, a place where people would listen to me.When I was
wondering if there was a place where I could be active,
Hololive was the one that hit me, and
that's why I sent it.  Did you
have an audition? Oh yeah, there
was always an application form. I
see, I sent it 3 times, 3 times, 3 times. Or
maybe once a day, or did I wait a while? Oh
wait, 2 weeks.  Wait,
yeah, I think the big one is better, right? I sent it once. I
thought I might have gotten the name wrong,
so I sent it again. Seriously, I didn't get a reply in two weeks, so I
sent it again. Oh no, I'm glad it was the first time.  It
seems like nothing happened, so I sent it over and over,
and thanks to that, I have a senior today, so
thanks to that, I'm here in the right place.
Do that WANTEDmore
peopletohaveAccess
Hersingingsowas
lookingforaplace
where
couldBL
ACatthetimeWas
Alwaysaud
constantly
HerWethere
Oh, in English, that's amazing.  Do you have any good words? What, what, what,
what, what, Tam is team. That third time is
kind of good. The
third time is usually right.
That's the third time I've been honest with you,
or maybe that's it.
No, I haven't been able to say it until now due to the language barrier,
but there's something I wanted to say in my overseas diary.Yes, I don't know if it's
true or not, but it's fine.Wata Mate.It's great that you're
overseas a lot,
but you can translate it for me.
After all, there aren't many events like this overseas,
but even
so, I'm still grateful for the support I get from them.That's
even more so.It seems like there are
n't many events that my seniors hold overseas.
Well, in Japan, there are
n't many projects like that for a convenience store, but I want to
do my best to do more things globally,
so I hope you'll support me.This is great too.
Good answer, I want to do it.
Sheisperforming
oringoverseasas strongly
compared toJapanese
eventsinjapansoeven
thoughtheresofewyou
guysalwaysShowUpAnd
supportHersoand
passionatelysoShe
reallyGratefulfor
thatbutIalsotobring
upOneThingmightnot
havesomuchtosayyou
guysbecausetoldfrom
youHeardfrom
guys
TheOf
Mr. Watamate from Mate Overseas said
this, but Ado-senpai
does a lot of subtitles on his own content, and apparently he
does it
tomorrow.There aren't many other members who put subtitles on their own content this much.  I
don't think so, but perhaps that's why Watari-senpai's feelings have already been conveyed to other countries to a great extent.I
also thought, ``Why do
you put so much effort into subtitles?''
Yeah, it
's been a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time.  English Prefecture Yes, Yes,
Yes, I felt so great that I had to take good care of it, so I
thought, Oh, and you
said yes to me.
Ok that makes certainly I
askedHerbecauseof
alllthinkthereany.
otherJAPANMWhoput
muchefforthaving
oflandsubtitlesET
herentonYouTubeand
askedWhydoesandsaid
WhenJOINJOINsenpai andat
thattimeisWhenalot of
asviersstarted
watchingHerLIFEand
ShenoticedThatShe
wasAwareofThatShe
tookNoteofitand
thoughtwellshewants
tomakethemfeel
includedandItwas
very importantforher
toyouknowprovide
them
translations
What type of streaming does Oewa-senpai like the most
?Games, chaos, chats, collaborations, etc.I
like them all, but I guess it's singing.Yeah, yeah, they
fit in a lot, right?I've
done it over 100 times already, over 100 times.That's
amazing.No.
have I've
been doing it
, I haven't been able to do it lately,
but I used to do it every week, I used to do it, I used to do it, I used to do it, I used to do it, I used to do it, I used to do it, I used to do it, I used to do it.  I'm
sure he's looking forward to it every week,
but not every week, but no, not every week,
but for me personally,
Watome-senpai is not only good at singing, but he also
has a strong image of Minecraft.  Yeah,
that's true. That's why I want to ask you, Mr. Wanwa, who has been
playing Minecraft for a long time. Even though there are
n't many people playing it these days, he's
doing it. Yes, he's building a lot of interesting buildings.
Which is your favorite?  I
like all of them, but yeah, I really like the square rolls, the rock-paper-
scissors device, or the Cho-maki-cho-no-maki-o.I'll
show you a little bit of the roll.
likes,
and this one.Rainbow
colors, so colorful.  I'm
glad I did my best,
oh Everybodyalotof
peoplehavebeenusing
ITknowConnectwitha
lotofMemoriesInHer
MindandWhyitfeels
SuperSpecialtoher
andShefeelslike
WorthItThatShe
workedsoHardonitand
alsoIknowedWhenIwas
readingoutthe
questionThatssomuch
MinecraftACTIVEeven
Whenthere
Yeah,
isn't it sad that everyone isn't playing Minecraft?
Lonely, lonely
[Music]
Hey, can
you please come back? Everyone, Kira-chan, you're back. Even at home, I didn't really
use the Japanese server in the first place, I'm
sure.  Everyone in my family
used to use the server, but it
became the same, or rather, when the Japanese server
became the main server, all the members of my family started using it.  I'm sad that I
went there.On
the other hand, I don't see Nessou anymore.But
it's Lonely and Chiara, so I'm really feeling nostalgic for the time when
all the members of Minecraft and Hol Live were doing it.It seems like it's lonely.
I want to
do something with Nemi. I'm
building something, so I heard that I saw a huge tree.
Look, look, it's huge. Before I knew it, it was really
big
.
justB I don't think it's finished yet.
Yeah, that's right. It's probably not finished. It's
not finished yet. I wonder when it'll be finished. Is
there anything you're working on now? What are
you making
now?  What ram Vegas ah ram
Vegas oh love what is it about 10% right now
Eh what 10% but it might still be 340% It's early, it
's not early, it's not late, it's not late, yeah, it's early, it's not late, it's not late, it's early, it
's not late.  Wow, when did
you start making it? It was a long time ago. It's so
good. When that slow, slow thing was popular. Oh, I
want to go to Vegas. Come on. I'm making a lot of things. Let's
go and play slots and Minecraft. Let's
play sheep races. I'm making things right now.
Answer Hey,
let's take a look at the cutout.
Oh, I wonder what it's about. There's a lot of things
going on. Oh, there's a lot of things going on. Chin, ah,
wait, I'm sorry. I made a mistake, so I'll
start again. So 3 + 3, lower 3, is evolving like crap.
3 + 3, lower 3, so this is it.  It's 66318 No,
no, 12, wait, 3 + 3, right?
6, right, lower 3,
right?
Does Neme know this number
? 9-chan probably doesn't know the same thing. She's not
good at numbers, but 11, 2, and Kia-chan are also 3. I don't
know, I don't understand at all, I
don't know.
What's so special about Kunan?
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, recently A-chan,
Moa, cotton isn't bad, right? I'm curious.What's the origin of it?
So, cotton is
n't bad, right?I asked, where did it start?
Yes,
yes, wow,
that's right, the first broadcast was embarrassing, it
was the first time, it was embarrassing, the first time was okay, youkai, I played it for about 8 hours,
but yeah, yeah, yeah, that's when I made a video of 61 times
saying, oh, it's not that bad when the line goes out.
Battle Ikuso
Chico line is good side.
Nekunkunkun
Ku pervert is okay, it's okay. It's
okay to broadcast it on pervert broadcast.
Important pervert is helpful. Helpful repeat Acha.
Helpful Waki-Pai Waki-Pie Day Waki-Pai Oh Waki-
Pai Yes, it's true that my pako is my favorite trip.
The place is Kazuha.
Ah, I understand, but everyone. Waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa-
Well, it
might not be worth it. Minecraft was once this,
Minecraft, this was so great. It's
coming, everyone. Incident.
Incident.
Forgive me for being still alive. If you're happy now, I
'm really angry. I do
n't know what to do. I don't know what to do.
Oh, why don't you wear
panties? You're talking about kuba no panties, and you're talking about panties.
There are many English
versions.
Oh, Kripa, it's tough, it's tough, yo. There
was an old video of him, but I thought he looked more mature when his current seniors were there.  After
all, I've grown up, I've grown up Hey, I've
grown up, I've
grown up Hey, I've grown up, yeah, I'm so
excited, yeah, yeah, I've grown up, yeah, yeah, yeah, I've grown up, I'm stuck, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I'm growing, but I'm cute
now.  But even back then, Watari-senpai was a cute old
man. Now
that he's gotten better, I wonder if he's good enough. It's amazing. He's
definitely not that bad. What's the point of that?  I'm sure
it's Kaede, isn't it? Nariwata Nari was W [Music] Let's go back to Ogo [Music] Thank you for watching I havetosay notabARMPETfanbut SidePOisgood
I think it's really cool, it looks really
messed up. The pie is the best. It
goes from the side of Beth to the pie. Yeah that
LINE. That line.
Beautiful That's right, it's art,
isn't it? What do you think about it? Aboo, from below,
for example, if you
cut off your top, you can see your breasts from below, which doesn't hide all of your breasts. It's
nice, right, it's nice, it's nice, it's good,
right?  Right, yes, side-to-side, side-to-side,
A-boobs, do you look at them from the side or from below? Which way do you look at those breasts? I know, I know, I
understand, you look at the breasts from the side, or
from the bottom.
Okay, let's move on to the next one. Let
's talk about the history of Bat-senpai's Night Fiba. Please tell us about the history,
and what's going on right now. What made
you start? I was
so nervous when I was streaming my debut.
Yes, I sang, but my voice was trembling and shaking,
but I
understand, I want to overcome that.I also wanted to
perform live someday, so I also wanted to practice for that live performance and
get better at singing.
So I thought it would be a good idea to have a singing slot every week, so
I started One Night Fever. Did I
start it right after I debuted? Or about 3 months later,
maybe a little later. Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah.  After we did the song,
we did that one night
fiba. I
wonder if it's evolved. It's evolved into a real live performance. Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Sorry I was trying to get herto
betterforDADandShe
thoughtinorderto
improvedoitlike
everyweekandsolikeaboutmonthsorsointo
HerCareerLIFEShe
startedNightOfand thenafterdoingitfor
alongtimeITturned
intoRealLifeConcert
thatyoushouldknow
aboutthatwasATkyonaivenueee
Yeah, that makes me happy.It's like a dream that a project that I've been doing for a long time will turn into something like that.Yes, that's right, that's a great host.  That's great.
Oh,
thank you, you're a great guest.
Please watch Yomosa's first live at the same time. I
asked you
not to be shy. I
remember what you said, remember what you said, I don't know
what you were saying about it.  I
asked them to do a Hoover pose that looked like it would be shown in the movie, but
everyone was very modest in raising their hands, so I
thought, ``Oh, that's a big deal,'' and the customers were
embarrassed.Oh yeah, that's right.Why are you
so embarrassed?
AARaboutIwaslikeWhy
yousoaraboutthisislikeaSpecial
occasionbringUpYour
ArmsandBeexcited
takeapictureand
rememberedthat
Yes, that's right. It was
nostalgic and I was happy. It's amazing. It's got a lot of history
. That's right about Wa-senpai. No, Lu-chan is too.  Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's a lot of interesting information, so next up is NEXThasinter
Things. Please tell us about the history of cotton, which is barely bad.
Oh, it's
not bad at all. Cotton Mere cotton me isn't bad, right?  Yeah, it would be
funny if I made a funny video, right? Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, that's it. It's like a hologram. I thought it was interesting that they were able to make it look like that, so I
started singing. Oh, please sing.
Now, I'm singing. Yeah, the
lines aren't bad at all.  Ha
[Music] Let's Go!
Wow! Did you
hear the stingray? Everyone is so excited!
Chiara-chan also appeared on it, and I was amazed. It
was like 2, 3, or 2 times.
That
's what I'm asking you to do.It's easy to work together with enem and everyone at ID.I
was really happy.You can call me again when you're called.I
want you to read it whenever you want.  It's
okay to read it, it's
okay to read it, it's okay to read it, and it's
okay to read it, and it's okay to do something in Japan, or come to Europe, and I'll
show you around.
Yeah, it's not bad at all, so I
wantmakee not bad,
right?
interandalsoIwasa
fewtimesyouguyscan
rememberandsaysNice
tobeabletoina
reallyEasyand
comfortableWaywith
overseasmembersas
wellThroughthis
MediaandthenShe
askedIfIwouldliketo
beinitagainandIsaid
Yeahbutalsobeand
haveadayHerother
collaborateUm, actually, the next question is about waidai, so it's a
perfect flow.
Nokadou  How did you
get started, and how
do you want to proceed? The
risk is that I was
thinking of doing something that would be hard to do with live streaming, and it would be something like a travel show, or a
card game,
or something like that.  It's pretty messy when it's live streamed, but it's definitely
more interesting when you edit it, yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yes yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah.  I was like, ``
Wow, that's the
kind of mane-chan I'm suited for.'' I thought, ``Maybe this is the kind of thing I'm suited for.'' I thought, ``That's right,'' but I thought, ``That's a good mane-chan.
'' That's
how it all started.
Well, I can't give you a rough idea of what I've done so far, but what was the most fun time?
So I
went to Hokkaido with
Iris, and Button-chan and UiUi-uu-in went
to Kyushu.  That
's right, I
played Beyblade a lot. I
know Beyblade. That was Beyblade in Kyushu.
Well, you don't
have to go to the vital parts.  It's
hard to carry,
so it's small. It's big. It's big. It's still big. It's big. It's a big platform. It's a
big
platform to roll on. It's a big platform to roll Beyblade on. It's so big, it's so
big. I
guess it doesn't matter where you go.  It
doesn't matter where you are, you'll need some equipment. Oh,
how's the stage? What's the field
like? The stadium is huge. Oh yeah, the
stadium. Oh yeah, that's right. Translate it.
sayshavedayby
Way
BASICPurposeof
isThingsGamesthat
easilyEX
saidthatlikeirlCard
GameslikeCardGames
PCGAMEareusually
morelikeboringMaybe
asaSTREAMandsoWhen
likeeditedintoA
shorterVideomorefun
andalsosameGoesfor
MaybeboardGamesShe
sayssoforsheliketo
usethesekindofIdeas
forHaveanicedayYeah
andInTheBeginning
HerprevManagersaid
Do
[Music]
andWeKnowturnedwell
HerPRManagerwas
talking
aboutandalsoIasked
Her
likeenjoyedtrav
episode
ofenjoyto
[Music]
sowentthere withandandthen
another onereally
enjoyedapparently
wasEpisodeWhereI
askedIfthebeyblades
werebeingspunand
throwninKbutnoItwas
specificallyThere
wasaseparate
Episodejokedabout
How
[Music]
A
Let
need
necessity
I really want to go to Japan. I've lived in Japan,
and I've lived in Kansai and Kanto,
so Kansai and Kanto are fine, but I've also been to Hokkaido. I'd like to
go to Okinawa with Nekari-chan.  I
want to go snorkeling in Okinawa. Let's
go snorkeling. I've done
snorkeling before. It's really fun. I've
done it before in the Maldives.
Wow, that's
really cool. I've done it in the Maldives. It's really cool. Even
if you're a bad swimmer, you're
just floating, so just floating and
looking at the fish is really soothing. It's
fun to be a sheep, or you can go as a sheep. It's
scary. I want to do it, right?  How about this year?
Okay, seriously, I'm going to be in Japan quite a bit this summer.
Well, let's go for 200 yen for one night. I
want to go. I'll suggest it.
Well, if you want, I'll pay with that jibara.
Hey, yeah, okay, okay, okay, I want to go,
so I'm going to say, "
Hoho, it's hot in the summer, but it's hot. It's probably hot. It's really
hot. It's probably September and August. It's really hot
around there.  Hey, it's hot, okay, okay, I'm going to
swim, so I'm going to swim.
knowmaybemaybemaybe
beMaybethink
about Okinawa
Okinawa looks really fun I've
always wanted to go to Okinawa but I haven't had a chance It seems like it's a good idea,
but I don't think it would be possible to
go by myself I can't
go there by myself, but I can go to Fukuoka by myself.  I
really like traveling, I like it, I like it,
I have a lot of images of it, but I think it
's more fun when you're not alone. No,
oh no.
said SorryIsaidsorry suddenly brought up this
OFFtopicThingbutSo
ExcitedifitWORKSOUT
LetMOVENext, it's wrong.  I was
wondering if I wanted to move on. There's a lot of scope from now on,
right?  I do
n't know what it's like, but this is also a good idea.When everyone from
Tokamade came to Japan, I
went to Yessssssss.
wherewantgo
withandsaidwellyeah
Ithinkintheendwould
benicetodosomeOf
Theseepisodeswith
OvermembersWhenThey
happenPER  That's the
person who created Live Illu Kana.
How did you come up with that plan?
And what do you think about Hololive Illustrated today? I wonder if
there's Hololive Is there a certain anime? Or rather, the
music in the work is like, oh, what can I say about it?  I don't know,
wait, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, that's\hthat.
Yeah, that's definitely the reason why I made it.
When did you make it? When
did you first make it? In the beginning, you
posted all the songs you sang yourself.  I
wonder if it's up to the 4th generation or even me. I wonder what happened to the ceremony after that.
Was it the first time that I participated? I see.  I see, I see.
Everyone got
it, yeah, I think it was. I
remember there was someone like Taka, but I
didn't know if that was the first one.
Yeah, I think the lyrics said, ``I'm sure it was for Kari-chan,''
yeah, yeah,
yeah.  I remember getting it. I don't think I've been
invited anymore. I guess I'm graduating.
Times have changed. Graduation. I can't find out now. It's
just normal. It's just Chiara. Yeah, I
wonder what it is about us. A lot of things happened.
Well, on the contrary, we became good friends, oh, that's
good, that's good, I was so
excited, and now it's really scary. I wonder if it's going
to be long. You know, it
was performed at festivals, and even at expos.
How do you feel? No, I'm
happy. The number has increased.
Baba, I'm even more involved now. I wonder
if there's something wrong with me. I'm lying.  It's
not like Mr. Luck told me to do it,
but I'm still doing it myself. I
see, there
's no need to be afraid of doing something like that.
Oh said, and the management said, ``Would you like to
do it in conjunction with that festival Expo Unde?'
' It's so nice that you said that.
showyou
dolikethatandwould
beniceifwehadlike
thistowhereyoucould
alsoSingDanceAlong
you
knowandthebeginning
thefirstONEIasked
Whichonewasthefirst
onethefirstONEwas
actuallytheoneWhere
Iwasalsoinwherethe
Japanesememberswere
uptoherGENERATION
andthenIguessthe
firstGENERATIONof wasthereandOnlythe
firstGENERATIONofID
IthinkthesecondI
forLittleWEED
aboutme and thewayweyouknow
dealwithEACHOTHER
nowsandIsaidjust
likeactuallyif
anythingWeGotcloser
Shejustdoescallme
thatanymorebutYeah
ShesaysthereSoMany
Now
andsomanyandIasked
Herifforthenewone
thenewestonethat
wasoEXPO
MayNoNoStill
actuallySheistheone
WhosaysIwanttodoa
newONELetdoitand
thenTheywerelikeLet
doitforEXPOthentime
ITfortheeventinthat
caseShenotbeingtold
todonotbeingHatGun
goodI see, I
feel like I'm making so many plans.  I'm
sure the questions I've asked so far are obvious, like I don't fly, but there are a lot of things I don't really understand, and I know I'm
doing them.
] It
's okay
in English, it's okay in English, it's
okay
[Music]
It's hot and it's cold, it's sore, it's cold, it's cold, it's
cold, it's cold, it's either
Dogast or Saizeria, I do
n't have either.
Which one is it? Is there anything else that I
like? I like family
restaurants, family restaurants, yeah, everything, everything,
everything,
Twitter,
or something like that. Are you doing
Mt. Ryupopoa or running at Lasso? Are you doing it
in that range? Are you still going to
do it?  Is it
time? Computer or game console? Yeah, I do
n't have either, but they're both the same. I do
n't think I like either one.
Yeah, both, both, both,
both, both, sem sem, put a pineapple on top of the pizza,
YES or NO, it's
okay, it's okay, it won't turn into a war, it's okay, it's
okay,
oh seriously, it's spicy too,
wait for the chair, which one?  Which one do
you prefer? Spicy or sweet?
Seungsu tea or coffee
or Teen Teen Travel with Peach of the Sea?
Or do you want to travel in the famous big year
? Yeah, yeah, yeah, it's the beach.
I'm on the beach. I'm not in Paris.
Paris is different. Even if it's not in Paris, I'm
going to relax. I guess that's right.
Tell me what you think.
[Music]
Titi
Oh  When you go to bed, be naked or cut your clothes.It's
cool.EventsChristmas chairs, evenings, etc.EventsHappy
birthday, ah, birthday, Yeah,
ugly day, except for Beboof day.Halloween,
Halloween, Okay, Halloween.
7, Family Mart, Lawson, etc. The ones closest to me are the ones
closest to me. They don't really answer me.
Which do you
prefer, text messages or phone calls? Is it better to
give them a phone gift or something?
[Music]
Yeah, that's one thing.  Should I walk the distance from the station or take the train?
[Laughs]
What do you
think, Mr. Tretre? Seriously, we don't have that kind of thing overseas, so I don't really
care, even though I have that kind of naive blood type.
Speaking of type A, there's no one like that, so
oh no, it
's A, right?  It's
a bit messy. Yeah,
I couldn't come up with a clear answer. There
were a few, but it's okay. You're so kind.
Yeah, that's how you act. Even if you were asked by someone overseas,
most people would probably answer by themselves.  blood type
There are many people who don't know about this.It seems like I was asked this for the first time during Japan time.I
don't check it.I don't check it.Well,
when I donate that land to that place,
I know it, but I'm
so confused.  I don't think it's important
because I don't have that kind of personality connection, so I don't get asked about it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, but I'm glad you told me the color of the pants.
What color are the pants, Kiara? Oh,
yeah, they're
orange-ish colors.
Peek-a-peek-a-
peek. It's embarrassing. People ask me the opposite question. I'm
embarrassed. Let's help. Let's change the topic. Why?
Why?  On the other hand, I
want to see how cute you are, and look at your cute side, and
make him feel embarrassed.  I'm
scared, I'm scared, I might not be embarrassed,
but
beandmay, oh,
wait a minute, that's probably the sound,
right?  Ah,
now that you're out, you're
behind me, so you've got your heart racing, too. You're now
able to shoot as close as you can with a gun. What are you doing?
Oh yes, I've always had a smug look on my face, but an
embarrassing and embarrassing face is different from pants. An
embarrassed and smug look is different. I'm going to put on a smug, smug face. I'm cute.
Please just smile,
please. Just get me out of here and I'll
do anything to you like ONE.
You just said you'd do anything,
just don't do it, please, and I'll
do anything, okay. All that's left is, oh, Mr. Kitomi, what are you going to do
?  I guess it's
true, it
's true, it's true, it's
getting smaller. It's like this, it's getting smaller. It's
embarrassing. It's so embarrassing. It's so big. It's
so
cute. I like it. I like it. I like it. I think it's a happy cloak.  The
cloak, that's right, this is Michael Jackson.Here you
go!
That volume, Michael, Michael Jackson,
Sheep
Jackson,
oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, my face is huge, and I said,  I
'm not saying that, I'm not saying that,
FACE is Angry FACE, try
your best to speak English, and there's also that thing,
Angry Face, when you're in light fever,
but Nathuba actually looks
good with the accessory options.There's only so many that look good on you, so it
ends all of a sudden.  I could
n't help it. It always ends suddenly. It
looks like a cutout here. It's a hot
cut. Sorry, I'm sorry, it ends suddenly. It's okay.
Madison's Sheep is really good.  It's so
embarrassing.
Next time I'll do the Michael Jackson dance. It
stinks. It's hard. It's just a joke. It's
okay. I'm back in the
noral. Let's go back to the noral.
I was intrigued by this.I heard that
before joining Holive, you were
making Khao for Aa-senpai.What
does that mean?
Hey, even before I joined Hololive, I wasn't sure
about the song, and although I didn't show it publicly, there were times when I was
asked to sing a temporary song because of our musical connection, and it turned out to be a
song that I had written.  No, you just asked for a different temporary song.
Yeah, yeah, you asked for a temporary song.
That song is
Aqua Eropare,
right? Yeah, it's
Bevery Surprise. I'm amazing. Yeah,
yeah, that's it. Yes, that's it.  Was
it after I saw Oka's 3D debut when I picked up Kao? I
don't remember, but it was some time ago. If that's the case, I'm pretty
sure I found out about Hol's live show through this Kao.  Yeah, I
think it was before. That's right with Aoe. Yeah, Aqua-senpai was also
surprised when he joined Hololive. I
think he must have known the voice, so I think he was surprised about that.  It's been a long time since we
last talked about it together.On New Year's Day, when we talked about it, I felt like I was talking about it properly.It's the first time I've talked about it the other day.That's
right.Maybe it's true that I talked about it, but
it's a lie.  That's the story I wanted to hear.Let's
watch it after this.Oa-san told me that.I
see.That's how everyone, all those viewers,
learned about that story for the first time.Oh
yeah, I didn't mean to tell you that either.  I've
been silent for so long
because it's my song.
ThisisinterIwasso
shockedbecausethis
cameUpandoneofthe
questionsthatyou
guyssuggestedThank
youWaTyouknow
EverythingsaidShe
waslikedoingMusic
stuffbeforerightBut
itwasReallyLikea
publicThingsolike
sometimesShewould
Getaskedtosingthe
DEMOlikeShewould
makethesongShewould
justlikebeasked
becauseShecansing
andIknowmaybeShe
aquWasthattheoc
Maybe
thatmust
knowthenIaskedHer
ever
talkedmustalso surprisedWhenjoin theandrecognizesThe VoicelikethisVOICEI heardinmy DEMOwassurprised aboutbutturns OUTTheyfirstbrought thisupveryrecently actually  Nedeko demo a temporary song  Do
n't you
think it's easier to get along with each other because of the songs you sing? I wonder what's going on.
Cats are welcome, welcome, aren't they? Yes, they're
welcome, Kiinki.
Inkiinki is difficult, isn't it? I wonder if they've opened their hearts.
You haven't really talked about this that much, have you? You must have talked about it on a live broadcast the other day,
but
haven't you talked about it in private before that?
Well, when I came in, I didn't say anything,
and when I said hello, I actually heard a song with a red palette, and I was like, ``
What kind of reaction did you get?'' I was asked.
Shohaiwa-senpai has held two solo concerts in Japan
and one solo concert in Singapore.
Yes, I'm doing it. What's it like preparing for a solo live
? Also,
please tell me about your feelings and memories of a solo live. The
preparation
is very difficult, but it's fun. Yes, I'm a little
nervous, but on
the day of it, I feel that way.  The
period of time I practiced was because of this.
Yeah, yeah, I see. It's
because I don't have many opportunities to do solo concerts. It
's special, and it looks like it's going to be hard. I
see.
Are there any more?  More  I
want more I want more I want more
Dance lessons are hard as expected I do
n't have much experience doing solo live as a Hololive Yeah I don't have much experience doing solo live as a Hololive
Oh yeah so I feel like everyone is just groping their way around
Hold on Holo
Liveba-senpai  I didn't get to hear it, but I don't think it was Holo
Live's first solo live,
or maybe it
was Fuchan or Atan's. I don't know if they've
done it before, but it's still
It was a time when there weren't that many live shows in the area, but now
that it's my second time, I feel like I'm getting used to it.It's
amazing how my level has improved.  It's
great that you can do it.
livesarenotreally
thatcanbedoneso
easilysoofcourse
VerySpecialtoherand
Iaskedhertogiveme
somemoregivemesome
moreTalkMoreAndsaid
Yeahlikefor
examplethefirsttime
forherfirstshehave
youknowany
experiencewithityet soDANCElessonsand
AllThatreallyrough
forherandalsogener
Itwas
Ithasbeendonelives
atthispointinWHOLE
LIFEbutkindoffresh
andforherShewasjust
likeShesaidlikejust
fumblingeverything
andhavingAHardTime
butnowIaskedHer
sinceShealreadyhad
Oneandthendid
anotheroneifitFELT
justlikeeasierfor
herbutShesayswellIT
becamemoredifficult
alsobecause
Everythingwas
likeJAimprovingand
moreAdvancedandyou
knowmoreHighlevelof
technicalevolutions
ETCsoalotofNew
Thingswereabletobe
doneintheConcertso
MaybeEASknowI see
andofimprove
Yourselffrom
Improvementand
EvolutionFromThe
SecondLife
Well, what do you mean by the feeling of a solo live?
Well, what do you mean by that? Unlike the whole live show, what do you
think of the feeling of a solo live?
Everyone is on my side,
and everyone is on my side when it comes to the whole concert,
but I think it's pretty good because there are a lot of people who are fans who are even deeper than that, so no matter
what I do, they'll accept it.
Even if I do something weird  You'll
enjoy it, yes, yes, yes, yes, it
's good, even if you fail, you'll be able to say it out loud,
and the second time you'll be able to say, "Yeah, yeah, try your best," and oh, sure, that's it.The first time, ah,
I didn't make a sound.This wasn't it.
Yes, that's right,
but I can feel that they are supporting me with their hands, and I
can feel their support, so do
n't worry, I do have some special memories from the live shows I've been to so far.  I'm
sure there are many, but I can think of
many, but I'm
sure I'll be able to do the vocals for the second live.
Sing something like "chocolate" really loud. It's
nice to hear your voice.
sayUS
Thatsisfor
specifically and
everyoneisonherSide
likeevenofcourse
EverybodyWillBeLike
andthePtoyourImage
ofcoursebutlikein
thiscaseyouknowThey
reallyAllarebiggest
Fans
andForYouand
Whateveryoudoeven
makeMISTon
Stage
overyou andjustreallyreally
Warmatmosphere
welcomingatmosphere
andShesaidIthere
likesomekindof
SpecialMemoryorso
fromherlivesall
togetherandShesaid
becausethefirstThat
Shedidwasduring
CORONAtimesIfor
tocould
thatforthe
secondthelikeshe
likeheardShewaslike
backstageandheard
thefirstCheersand
screamswerereally really
overwhelming andSpecialtoherand also not justinthe beginningbutalso duringSONGSWhere there specificCHthat EverybodyDohearing loudly LThat's
true, that contrast is huge,
right?  Shonehai
NextOneis I perform with my senior Hakari-chan a
lot, but do you have
any interesting stories from our time together?
Well, I'll talk about that later.Okay, let's go
first.I wonder if the episodes are interesting.She's
always busy,
right?She seems kind of tired.But
when rehearsals and songs start, yeah.  Yeah, I'm
really excited and I
'm moving around a lot.I'm sure he's gone.I do
n't know where he gets that energy from.Thank
you for your hard work when you come.  It's
kind of like Lipa, but all of a sudden, the more I see it, the more Ekari-chan and I wonder
where that poop is. It's
amazing. In my image, it's probably a festival from that summer.
But festivals, festivals,
all over the place.  It seems like there will be a match between Wa-senpai and Ka-chan. That
's amazing. I
feel like Mr. is also pushing me. I
felt like that, but it's
amazing. They're already a unit. It's totally Summer as well.
And the countdown also includes that baby,
right?
Yeah, that's what the management has decided, but it's decided,
but even if that
doesn't happen, we're still doing something together. Yeah, that's
it.  Together, we've been together for a long time.I
thought it was strange how we
had each other.We don't
really have a lot of personality.Is there anyone else in the house that you'd like to make music with?It doesn't have to be me.
Well, it's
not like that. You do
n't have to say it.
Then we'll both say it. If it's Kia, I feel like they're making me say that. No, I don't think so. But that's not the
case. Kia wants to
do dance music. Oh yes, that's good.
Yeah, I'm heading in that direction, so yeah,
yeah, that's right, the dancing is cool, and the singing is
really good, too.  It's kind of
fluffy and fluffy when you match it.
Nene sings with a beautiful sound.
Masu Soina-chan is generally kind of slow.
Singing the song is soothing, so Watari-senpai is also soothing. So I
think it's perfect when paired together.  We
played takoyaki with a proper bounce width, and
then we said, oh yeah, we'd like to do something together.  I
think it was last year, maybe last year. It's about time to
move on.
But it's true that things like this take a long time. There's a lot to
do,
so you have to be specific.
Saidknowimpristhat
alwaysseembusyandEX
happen
toonly
their
totheman
themandalsosumerfal
recentlywas
ManagementchoiceSoI
waswondering
likeIwonderwhyIget
thisimpressionthat
Theysosopushed
Togetherbutlike
Mysterious
Managementmustlike
this
combination and
thenSECONDPartofthe
questionwasifthere
someoneELsewantto
makeMusicandsaidand
IsaidyouhavetomeI
knowkindofpushing
for
sauseDANCEMusic
STYLEMusicwith
meuseIdoandalsosays
IHaveA
goodingwellthat
makesmehappyButThe
personPER
[Music]
he
Someday Someday Neina-chan and Wata-senpai's  It
would be nice to have a collaboration. I'm looking forward to it. I
want to do it with Kira, but I don't
really need Watari.
I'm fine with the Japanese members or someone.  I'd like to
do something with you.To be
honest, it doesn't matter
who I am, but I'm happy just to do it
with anyone.I'd be honored to work with anyone, but if you
say yes, I'd like to say it's my
senior.  I have
no choice but to do it, I have no
choice but to do it. [Music] I don't know if it's Danmi or anything else, but it's difficult. Kiara basically makes K-pop-like songs, so yeah, yeah, we're in the same direction.  Yes, there
are a lot of people, like Laplace-chan, and
so on.Yes, Laplace-chan came to mind.Lapu-
chan really likes our music,
so maybe Laplace-chan
might want to do it too, but yeah, yeah, yeah.
Muna-chan, I definitely want to work with Muna-chan.
Muna-chan, Muna-chan. Muna-chan
also likes KPOP and
has a few songs like that, so that's the case with Mona-chan. And Muna-
chan
probably has the image of having something to do with her, so Kia is not a mayor.
But it's said that it's an image of the sun,
so when you think of an elongated sun, it's the sun, so if you put two people together, it's an
eclipse.What do you
mean, the moon and the sun?The moon comes in front of the sun.
That's right, the moon eats the sun in 2 colors, 2 colors, ah, 2 colors.Yes, yes, the
moon that eats the sun is yes, yes,
yes.Muna-chan and Kia eat 2 meals.I see.That's
right, so we have to do it together.I'm
sure you want to hear about it, too.  Nachan's song
is strong, yes, it's really strong, and I want to
do it anytime, any time, I want to do it, so let's do it with three people.It
doesn't matter to the sheep, but oh no, two people is a
good cut.No, I
cried.Good, no, no.  It looks like I'll be alone with my
senpai and Mu-senpai. I'd
like to say our goodbyes and hang out by myself for a while. Having
All then, uhm, let's
go to the next question. I'm going to drink some water, so please
put on that cute face.
Thank you, mytalk.  By the way,
Ano Hot Talk is already celebrating its 4th anniversary this year,
and it
's a long-running show.However, on its 2nd anniversary, it
released merchandise.Today, it
posted a photo on Twitter.
However, even though it was released about a year and a half ago, it only
arrived at my house
about two months ago, so it seems like it's been a while since I last received it, and
today I've attached a log of me drinking water from the glass for the first time.
Top Nanoha, it's really special.Paya
mer
anniversthough
annivOh yeah,
there's also a shirt.I'm a senior and I've never seen one in the back.  I have
written all the names of the guests in Tahotoku,
but next time, if you can do it, please write the names of your seniors
as well. Yeah, I
'm waiting. MaybeOne
DayDoAnotherTand
havenameonmaybe
maybe ah, let's go next.
One of your goals is to be at Budokan.  I
think it's a live show, but for those overseas,
please explain why it's so special to perform at Budokan and why that's your goal.
Please Budokan is a
place where Japanese musicians aspire to be.It's a place where
everyone aspires to a high level of prestige.For
me, it's not easy to get into.It's a
strange place, but Anonomiko
did a video called Oano Watari's song.  When I'm playing Unmaki, I'm playing Rock, Paper, Scissors
and watching the song at the same time.Sometimes I just
watch that Mame song
[Music]
Tewame Budokan
Let's go, let's go to Budokan.
After being told to cover up, I started to become conscious of the sense of martial arts.I wonder if it's
okay to aim for something like cotton.No, it's okay,
isn't it?
Having a place to aim for gives me
that strength to work hard.
Since then, I've been given a place to aim for, and I've
started to say that I've always wanted to aim for something.Now, I
don't just have a dream with Watamate, I
also have a dream, so I
think I can say that I want to stand up.  I
don't know if I'll be able to go, but I really liked the idols from the idol agency Hello! Project, so their graduation concerts are usually held at Budokan or something like that, so I don't know if that's the case, but if it's a special concert, it's
different.  No, it's a special
live show that can be done with a professional feel. That's right, I
have that image in my mind.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, no, no, no, that's
not what I mean. May
I know, it's Tokyo.
Tokyo, yeah, yeah, that's right.
likeprettybookedand
prettyBigand
expensive
toLIKEASpecialven
TheyhavemanyvenIN
JAPANkindofSpecial
youknowDononconerto
IthinkDolikelikeSPS
EValsoknowIDIspeci
concertationConcert
EXWhyalsoknowVery
Specialtoknowtryto
thereandGotIDEfor
because
ofShewasdoingA
STREAMWhereIthink
shewaslike
watchingMUSICVIDEO
orsomethinglikethat
and
thenbasicallysaid
Youshouldgoto
and
reallyformetotryto
AIMfor
[Music]
somadeHerandmany
times
inamandherDreamwith
theandHOPESthatOne
Daycanmakeit
come on
theageher
Thank you, I have
to convey my funny feelings
Neimicha
[Music]
So yeah, this year? I feel like I'm bored, yeah, this year, maybe next
year, maybe next year, maybe next year, maybe this year, well,
someday I'll have to try harder.  Yeah yeah
will
happenIthink
has the next question is so long I'm sorry, but
it's fine.
This isn't your question, it's my opinion.
However, when I was preparing for this interview, I
realized just how much influence and influence you have at Hololive.Yes, I think you have given a lot to the community and the company.
How do you feel about your constitutional contribution to Hololive
? They give you a lot of praise, even if it's
true, but you're
just doing what you want to do. Oh, I don't think it's too
much, like
carrying Hololive on your back.  I
don't feel like it's for the sake of it,
but I feel like I'm doing it because I like it, like Hololive, and Hololith.I just
want it to be for everyone.I feel free to do whatever I want.
I see, it's
natural. It's natural. Maybe it's best to do things like that
. I don't think so. If it becomes an obligation, it's
tiring. I'm Kim. I'm Kim.
I'm happy. Nanoha, I'm Kim.
Yo Kim, are you happy? Oh, hey, I
'm happy. Yeah, ref.
basicallylikeShe
reallyhappytobe
praisedsomuchByMe
butShejustdoeswhat
shewantsbasically
likenotThatShedoes
itforlikeforWHOLE
LIFESAKElikefor
pleasingthe
Managementor
somethingorlike
tryingtodosomething
forthemjustifShe
doingitfortohave
somethingforthe
vierstoenjoyforthem
tojustbenefitfrom
[Music]
Isaidprobablythe
bestifjustlikeyou  I
knowifthatwhatit
feelsIspeakEnglish
anymorejustGO,
but both in my personal life and
as a co-worker, I don't know if I can perform
live or not,
but I'm not involved
in it yet.  I'm
very grateful to Watari-senpai for creating fun places where I can participate.But the
same goes for this holotalk.That's what I'm trying to do.I'm not going to
call everyone.  Thank you so much for
translating it,
Sayana.Actually, there are a lot of things.That's
right.Nanaba-senpai is one of them.I
think all the viewers know this, but
there's a little bit more to that Japanese.  I'm
doing it with the feeling that it would be nice to know more about it for those who can't do it, but I also
feel a bit sorry because I don't have much strength,
but it's just a project like that.Yeah, I'm
doing my best too, but I have a lot of seniors.  It's
amazing that you're doing it, I
can't do it at all, so I always have to rely on
subtitles,
so no, no
asifeellikelikecan
yousayallthelife
membersandlikeother
projectswhereMaybeI
Haveninvolvedornot
involvedlikeShe
doing somethingforus
toShecreates
projectsandfunIdeas
whereWecanbePartof
ittooandIThinklike
reallyrespectable
andhonorableandI
lovethataboutherand
reallythankful
[Music]
Thank you so much
for all your comments, Nama de
Gozaru Na Mite, thank you, Ae [Music] Nonono Eunwatari-senpai,
thank you,
thank you, thank you, no, no, no, let's
move on to the next question.
There's a reason why I was able to continue being active. I
went through a lot of hardships right after my debut. Maybe
it's a crappy, crappy, crappy network.
Looks like I've been
on a crappy network for about 2 and a half months, so
wait, that's
a bit long.
Also, when it comes to collaborations, I can't call people, and the line is too tight.Also, I've hardly ever
talked while playing a game.
It's difficult at first, but I ca
n't seem to do anything interesting while talking while playing the game.But I
did improve quickly, and I
think I did it
because I'm good at speaking.  I'm so happy for my seniors,
so that's why I was able to keep going.
I guess everyone is supporting me, and the
members are the same, and
everyone who has commented like this is also a blessing.
Someday, this crappy network will become a joke.
Well, thanks to all the people who encouraged me, it's completely funny. That's right, because there were people like that, it
made sense
. It was like that for the first few months. My
computer was a mess.  I was weak, and in the first
month or so, I didn't have that much money, so I
lived in a one-room apartment in Japan, which is extremely inaccessible, and
even if I spoke in that loud voice, the person next to me would bang bang bang bang.  It was so bad that I
couldn't stream it right away, so even after I
moved, I didn't have an internet connection.First
of all, even though I lived at my manager's house for a month,
his
computer was crap.  It was so sloppy that I
couldn't even do Minecraft, and it really
felt like a bit of dj vu.You
know, it's frustrating when you have a hard time in the beginning,
because the beginning is important, you know?
Now that we've made our debut, it's
still a time when we want everyone to know about us, and
even now, I wish things had gone better at that time.
sayingforaboutwas
famousOhGodInhad
famous
shidthatwaslikefor
twoandHalfmonths
whereShewastrying
HerbesttoamHERHER
InternetCUTout
[Music]
disenbythatand
crushedandWhenwas
sayingthatIBIG
momentandShesaid
alsocouldcollab
eitherwithpeople
becauseofthatinthe
beginningandANOTHER
THINGWasthatshehave
streamingexperience
LIKETALKINGwhile
gaminglike
multitaskingSothat
wasreallydifficult
forhertooShefelt
likeMaybeShewas
reallyentertaining
becausewhilegaming
Shejustwasableto
talkaboutanything
interestingwhatshe
FELTbutsureshelike
improvedinthatIknow
ifitreallywasan
issuebutsureShe
improvedinanycase
andthenShesaid
becauseofeveryone
supportshelikeShe
wasabletogoThrough
thatfaceandShe
reallythankfulthat EverybodywasthereforherevenWhenEverythingwasGoingreallybadlyAndnow
justtoaboutthoseand
[Music]
Words like "Matawa-senpai aren't that bad"
or "[ __ ] miscellaneous" are really famous words.It's so
popular that
I used it too, unconsciously.
Yeah, it's not that bad. I'll use that too. I'll
also use the crappy line.  I think the
chairman of the shiso small fry line might be the one who
said that about his senior line. Yeah, it doesn't seem like it would be good to call him a
shitty small fish light. Yeah, no, that's right,
from It's
nostalgic, it's nostalgic, right now.  The line is fast,
fast,
speedy and strong.
Hey, it's nice. I recently moved, and the
internet was really dead,
but it's finally resolved.
spetoGOODGOOD Seriously, this
is work, so it's a problem if the internet connection is slow,
right? Yes, I
need
JO Wataru
Senpai, the next question will be the last one.
Well, well, I'll have to finish it soon,
or Watari-senpai will be streaming after this,
so that's right.There will be simultaneous viewing, so
was
Lady
M will be streaming at a really late time, senpai.  I
thought it would be a good idea to include this as a question, so I didn't need it, but why
are you broadcasting it so late? Is there a reason? It's the
time when you're most energetic, so maybe you're the
best, but maybe the viewers aren't.  It's
true that it's very difficult to do so,
but recently the number of people who do it late at night has decreased, so on
the other hand, there
is no one else who can do it at the same time as Newa-senpai's broadcast time.
Then, everyone, please come to my senior, I wonder if you'll
like it. Overseas
said that it saves time for broadcasting. Yes, on the contrary, it's
easier to watch, no, no, overseas is better.
energeticthenSoI
saidwellMaybeyour
viewersfeelvery
energeticATNIGHTbut
IguessTheygotusedto
itandalsoItseemsto
beyouknownowadays
Shesaidnowstherenot
SoManyotherpeople
WhoSTREAMinthenight
likeherbutIgoodyou
canhave
andYeahgetallthe
viersAtNightandalso
saidyouguyssaidthe
vierssaid
Overfor
Watch
EU
thinkI
can't sleep I can't sleep at night
Well, it depends
Yeah, you ca
n't sleep if you don't darken your room. If you
don't sleep,
it's not a strong thick curtain. ALSHE
LET Go tothelast
Question The last question
Wow, for seniors, Hololive is a
place where dreams come true.
Oh
[Music]
Wow, The Place Dreams
come. No, it's emo, isn't it? More  Is
it better to say something like that? No, no, it's enough. I'm grateful. The dream
has come true. There's
still a long way to go. I'm sure it
will come true. And then, I
want to do a world tour, too.  Hey, I
want to do a live on the moon, live on the moon,
live on the moon, ah
month 1 live is different, different moon,
ah, moon, moon, no, it's
so impossible, I don't know what you're saying.  I
didn't.
Then, yeah,
who's going to watch the concert?
Alien, I
'm an alien. It's
difficult. It'll take a while for everyone to go. Yeah, I
'll check the schedule for a moment.
[Music]
OK, Senpai. It's been a while since today.  It
was a pleasure to talk to you so much. I
'll contact you again when I go to Japan. Or rather, I'll contact you first. Let's
play rope or something in Okinawa.
If it's difficult, you don't have to worry about it at all.Yo,
no, let's go someday, but I want to go to Snow
Clinging.
Thank you very much for inviting me.
[Music]
I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do
my best. There's always that one greeting at the end of a senior's broadcast.
But I told you before, I'll tell you again.
Hey, what are all those lines?
But in Aphra's place, I
want you to say, ``
Dajin'',
yes, that's German.  andGERwesay
Se
[Music]
Ye
than
[Music]
see
Goodbye Mame-senpai's final greeting
Thank you very much I love you
[Music]
Cute
DETDET
[Music]
Ah
Oh
[Music]