[Music]
play play the intro quick quick
W oh my God that was
[Music]
loud I was talking to myself for like 2
minutes I I had a starting soon for like
four minutes and then and then I and
then I came live and I was talking and
you guys weren't react Ing and I I was
like why and someone says CeCe do and
I'm like haha funny because I was late
and then it just keeps
going and I just talk to myself stop
stop wait I have to turn it off thank
you thank you wait wait I'm killing it
I'm killing it okay thank you very much
I'm killing it sorry um yeah so I was
talking to myself for three 2 minutes
that's kind
of embarrassing but but it's okay cuz
it's my birthday so we can just forget
about it right can you hear me now am I
here is this real life like I'm not
crazy I pressed the live button I
pressed Live on YouTube it gave me the
little thingy it said I was live I went
through my tire stick I played my intro
twice I said hello em
iy you are here thank you we here can
you hear me can you hear am I here
welcome in everybody
woo I'm I'm really pissed okay I'm not
pissed but I'm really annoyed that's so
frustrating okay anyways what I said
earlier but you weren't there because I
was talking to myself I'm really sorry
for being late um I hope you guys still
have a nice time I think we're going to
have a nice time together today it's my
birthday
um
so thanks for coming to my
birthday I'm losing it I'm make losing
it over here at least for life that's
[Laughter]
[Music]
something oh man I guess it's time for
me you know what actually I'm so
sleepy I think I'm going to take a nap
oh my wind up key is ah it's it's it's
stopping I think uh I think maybe I
should
ah I think I'm going to take a na I
think I'm going to take a
nap maybe that's for the best
[Music]
there was no sound it's okay it was just
piano
ah no what happened to me what's going
on what's going what's going
on no no I've
been I've been turned into I've been
turned into a slightly
scuffy um
tin little bit
M no what's happened to me guys guys I
was just I was just taking a nap and
then suddenly I woke
up and my body was gone dang it what
happened do you guys know what happen
what were you paying attention did your
eyes where your eyes open Where's my
real body
was I
transformed was my body stolen where am
I who is
where so can you hear any sound can you
hear music at least that's weird why
didn't you hear the music Let me just
fix that real quick before we keep
going did you hear Do you hear music
yeah okay did you is
on how about you didn't hear music
during the video
[Music]
H okay I'm just going to troubleshoot
that real
[Music]
quick there's no piano you don't you
don't hear a
piano how
[Music]
now how
now there it is yay looky
[Music]
ah oh no I've
been turned into a
[Laughter]
Mak that's
crazy well welcome in everyone um we are
today we are on a mission we have to
find my body I don't know where it went
so um I don't know who should we go to
Who Do You Think could know where my
body could
be did you see anything I don't think so
I think earlier you already said no no
no
h okay well when in doubt here at
Justice headquarters when we in doubt
number one person to go to is and will
always be on the bath so let's try
finding her this
way no actually this way no no this no
actually see this
way come with
me guys are
you
[Music]
okay they keep breaking the
walls how am I going to relocate the
budget so it works out and no one is
keeping up with their
duties these
girls maybe I should
call Liz Liz Liz what is it have you
seen my body like my real
body I mean you did walk past me earlier
if that's what you mean do you know
where I went um what no it seemed like
you were leaving uh you should ask the
other girls oh wait wait wait wait wait
wait what happened why do you look like
that should I be worried what happened
no don't worry about it okay you got all
okay it's not okay when you why why do
you look like that why does she look
like
that I'm so
[Music]
tired yeah also did you know that in
terms of male human hi guys have you
seen my body why do you look like that
what happened I woke up and then
suddenly I was like this have you seen
my body have you seen no I don't know I
think I saw you leaving I'll help you
get down you look very eatable like this
we've got to try it no no no stop stop
stop stop stop some coffee once you're
done anyway G as I was saying
help help guys
help help help
help help help help I guess it's finally
time
huh the reason why I did a million tests
of this let's see if it
works how will you help me you have two
options Choose
Wisely oh not that one yeah what are you
going to do jetpack we don't have a
jetpack we don't not even Raa has a
jetpack at this point no one has a
jetpack we don't have a we don't have a
jetpack
guys okay okay okay okay let's see this
little time this little time ah I'm kind
of getting used to this actually
actually this isn't too bad feels kind
of nice on my hair
o okay let's see what's the
answer oh it's moving too fast I can't
see use your body to cushion the fall
okay just specification your body in
that case means your body not my body so
you better you better help me okay are
you guys
ready how high were you thrown I'm
Justice headquarters is up in the sky I
was thrown from L his
headquarters yeah yeah yeah help me help
me help me help me help
[Music]
me I'm
[Laughter]
surfing
oh thanks guys okay let's see if this
does anything
[Music]
H I live
my
[Music]
arm how could this happen to me oh yeah
let's go this way you know
what I can't believe G would do this to
me so I think I'm prob of going to have
to ask for
help and I know no one else who would be
better at helping me in terms in times
of need than my trusted who could it be
my
trusted
lawyer let me just let me
[Music]
just
hello I would like to open a case hi I
mean yeah why Gigi a chipped at murder
she threw me off a building in my arm
ripped out I thought you were super
durable oh yes usually but you know it
is very very complicated there's a lot
going on it's it's just well a case is a
case I'm hon it we'll get back to you
with more info okay nice thank you okay
bye
bye yay I know crony always has my back
it worked um I wonder if we can actually
Su Gigi actually I don't know if that's
going to work is that going to work can
we Su
Gigi what would she have to do maybe
money maybe she would have to pay us
because she threw us off a building I
mean you also took damage right actually
you didn't take any damage but you could
have taken some damage so that's really
messed up okay I will have to go this
way for one moment and test I mean fix
something um can you wait for like 1
minute while I try fixing my
arm guys do you have the do you can you
wait for me for one minute yeah I just
I'm going to try pushing my arm back in
yes okay thank you one second
H stare into Oblivion
[Music]
it's not working ah my arm arm my
arm to be fair I do not feel any pain in
this body and I may or may not be
surprisingly squishy and soft well I'm
soft in the other body as well but like
you know like squishy
squishy I don't usually have that much
squishy oh that's weird it's we're
outside but it's getting kind of cold if
I had a wind in my brain I would be
getting up to close
it which I
don't one second oh the wind it's so
cold it's just really cold okay let's
let's try finding someone maybe someone
can help us and fix our arm I mean my my
arm my body my my body yeah okay let's
see huh H what could it be um I'm back
by the way okay let's
see I'm
[Music]
flying if only if only there was someone
someone that can s cuz I can't cuz I
don't have have any stuff to sew with
and my hands are like little little
little circles so
H let's
see is that hello there little one what
happened to you hi I fell off a building
and now I'm hurt but I don't have
Disposable Thumbs so I can't you
opposable thumbs oh yeah I uh you have a
swing kit right can you fix me
up yes but you have to earn it you have
to answer my riddle a riddle okay okay
okay hit me hit me okay a sewing machine
has it a page has it you have it what is
it a a head I have a head a foot I have
a foot an ie I have an eye oh that seems
kind of complicated all right guys guys
guys can you can you can you solve this
for me please seriously though what
happened to you why are you doll I'm not
I'm not sure I woke up and then suddenly
was in this body it's it's kind of comfy
but it's very
small yeah you are tiny
yeah I wonder if everyone's going to be
able to solve this one let's
[Music]
see which one could it be guys
nice answer answer okay time's
[Music]
up what is the answer what did you
answer a foot what was the question Ena
Ena what was the
question a sewing machine has it a page
has it you have it what is it a head a
foot one ey what okay okay A a foot
locked in locked
in ding ding ding right answer yay here
let me fix you right up thank
you there you go all done thank
you thank you very much
bye-bye I've been fixed I've been F oh
she disappeared I've been fixed fixed
guys guys Ena did it she fixed my she
fixed my arm thank you very much thank
you thank youa can't believe she can s
nice okay well let's keep going we're
still looking for it my body where's my
body where's my original unique
non-altered
[Music]
body uh let's
see this way
[Music]
doesn't it feel nice to be outside
guys just the wind and the
air
nature yeah sometimes it's nice some
sometimes it's nice
[Music]
hey you
there would you be interested in my
Wares yeah what do you have to sell huh
oh so many things here a ribbon some
glue a flower oo so pretty can I have
them all all of them do you have any
money how much is one of them 10 bucks
each $10 for some
glue well yeah I mean you have to
consider the market price of the glue it
was fresh caught this morning supply and
demand the value oh okay um guys do we
have any money let's
see okay I can have one please okay okay
I mean they're all great to be honest I
feel like you'll be happy no matter what
you pick okay okay let's let's pick one
I may not have may not have fortra
premium glue you know oh glue okay so
the first option is glue ribbon flower
you won't find it anywhere else flower
okay go guys go the ribbon too that's a
fmart exclusive I'll have you know I
don't know which one I want I want all
of them we can't afford all of them
interesting interesting results we have
here only 10 more seconds on
that which one which one is it going to
be
[Music]
blue
okay okay that's that's the one I guess
that's that's the that's the one
oh great choice I sure hope it comes in
handy good luck on your adventure and
whatever you have going on here thank
you good luck with your store I hope you
sell everything thank you always let me
know if you need anything and I might
just have the right thing for you bye
bye oh man where did what did what what
happened to why glue guys I wanted a
ribbon in my hair or like or like a cute
little like a cute little flower I could
have done so much with it okay glue let
me just put that into our
inventory cuz we
have okay why why why glue put the glue
in your hair
no oh man I wanted the ribbon maybe one
day maybe we can like put together 10
more bucks and then we can ask fauna if
she's going to sell us the other
ones I could put the RO uh the flower
not Rose son a rose normal flower on my
left ear and I could put the ribbon on
my right side
mhm it's a good idea happy birthday
thank you it is my birthday however my
body was stolen so it's a bad birthday
so far we're going to see going to see
how we're going to see how we're going
to manage that we're going to going to
have to wait and see this way I think I
think if I was a
body if I was a body
I think I would go to this city cuz like
the park is nice and all I like the
forest I like the trees but there's
nothing to do here for a body so let's
go to the
city follow
me let's do it okay
[Music]
the crowded
RAV guys guys guys she's lost and is
looking for directions but I but I don't
know where that is either what should we
do what should what are we going to do
what are we going to
do o oh did I not end the last stream um
I
mean
[Music]
ho pole isn't working my pole isn't
working guys do you see a pole
more
glue we do not see a pole okay okay let
me try fixing
it test test test you see this
[Music]
pole can you see the test pull
M yummy test yes okay okay okay let's
try
[Music]
again it's okay I can fix
this
glue glue oh I would could I have some
glue with a little bit of
glue let's
see dang it it's not working
okay my poles aren't
working let's try this
[Music]
no okay oh what it worked kind of okay
well
K
[Music]
CH I'm
still thinking about it
[Music]
okay okay
uh okay what what do you guys think what
is your decision try make something up
no that's a bad idea okay okay let's
okay fine okay sure let's do that okay
that's terrible idea
okay so
[Music]
um oh okay thank good than
Che
oopsie what's that guys it's it's a
poster I hope she'll be okay I think
she'll be okay I'm sure she'll be okay I
think she'll be okay okay now that we've
done that let me just double triple
quadruple check if this is working again
now sorry for the SCF let's try uh doing
this one
test okay it's working nice it's
working what is that the crowded Raven
okay so for those who didn't understand
because she was um speaking in German um
um she was trying to get to a bar or
like a concert or something of crowd and
it's called the crowded
Raven and then she gave me um a flyer
huh let's see
okay 1 minute break going to fix stuff
sorry
[Music]
[Applause]
huh what are you doing here dogs
okay can I come
in do you have a ticket no I but I no
this is a very exclusive Club you see
only the most VIP only the most MVP very
pretty yeah so get lost wait but I'm
looking for my body
my please let me in I don't know but it
looks like she be find to too now we can
use this chance look what tell we have
to stay here I got go at the entrance
okay guys
please oh hi darling are you
losta they won't let me in please oh
come here there there you look so cute
like this do you have a
ticket no well then be a sweet and get
me some tea from the cafe around the
corner and I'll let you in okay really
okay okay okay I'll get you the best one
in the world thanks thank you get
was it's okay it's
okay I can't believe you are so rude can
you imagine how dare you cover M's face
like that guys that is it that is just
so rude I can't believe you know what
what's the glue for huh if you can't
even have any manners I can't believe I
can't believe you should just you would
just come over her face like that my bad
well don't be sorry be
better can't believe you would do that
that's so messed up okay well so on the
agenda let's see what's in our inventory
let me
see okay it's glue okay and something
else so what did she want she wanted
some
tea I think we're going to have to do it
guys I think we're going to have to go
into the enemy's
territory a coffee shop a coffee shop a
cafe shop a cafe a coffee shop a cafe a
coffee shop yeah it's a glue do you
think it's the glue do you think the
glue is the answer to everything okay
brace
yourselves okay got this coffee shop I
can I I can do it I can I can do this I
I've done worse I've done better i' I've
done things it's okay it's okay I got
this we got this we got we got this
ooh what nice fik that's a really cool
ride oh right it's so cool isn't it yeah
and it fits your color scheme and
everything I wonder how fast you can go
in that oh let me take you on a ride D
oh I would love uh no wait wait I have
to resolve this situation oh maybe maybe
another
time yeah okay another time then bye
okay bye for now I got to go get some
tea this doesn't seem to have been the
right way let's see maybe here
h h
[Music]
oh is
that
hi hello welcome how can I help you
today um I need one green tea please big
small venty ly large B big would you
like milk almond milk foamed milk
whipped cream oat milk vanilla milk soy
milk a banana milkshake um just just
normal please
just normal okay and would you like a sh
of espresso coffee cappuccino uh no I
want tea green tea get that coffee away
from me but it would be so much better
to have some coffee in your tea no stop
stop it I've never coming back to this
establishment again n h then that's
going to be $4.99 your name is uh it's s
you know my name what why you being like
this you being kind of weird just give
me some tea what you don't have to write
have a wonderful day thank
you um thanks thank you very thank thank
you very much well that was odd why
would she like that maybe I should have
given her the glue as well that would
have been an an idea an an idea an idea
okay let's
[Music]
see let's go back
with my
tee um resting in my backpack well your
backpack I'm not carrying anything just
so you know just so just so that it's
established why I'm a I'm a little
puppet I can't I can't carry
anything
H
what oh guys
guys guys aren't even in front of the
bar anymore I think we could just go
inside this was for nothing
okay let's see maybe the crowded Raven
has the answer that we are looking for
[Music]
H maybe
maybe
[Music]
maybe super
Tears like 9,000 years back and for and
combo cut me like
[Music]
AIT is guys isn't that my butt isn't
that me in the
background guys right next to ollie guys
I'm right
there no quick quick wait no she noticed
us quick go after her go after
oh no she's so fast
quick take
[Music]
me oh she's getting away let's run off
the H quick
[Music]
FAS h
use the glue where am
[Music]
I here I
am she oh what's that it's my
alarm oh man uh oh it's stat
time what could it be guys
oh we really have to we really have to
run after her however there are also
some other things that I would like to
discuss with you
today good thing I have my phone with me
I mean I needed to call crony and also
you know I just I had it to have it with
me so good thing good thing what could
it be what could it be huh what do you
what do you think let's see do I have it
I have it okay okay I have it I have it
I have it I have it okay okay let me
just let me
just okay are you ready it's my brother
which means my very
first Master
mer
yay um so for my birthday Merch this
important okay we have to talk about
this cuz it's my birthday so for my
birthday merch I picked um some items
that I liked I I'm going to show them
off one by one um later as well but I
want to announce it real quick um first
of all uh just so you know you can buy
it on um H life Pro Shop but you can
also get it on geek Jack depending on
where you're from um for delivery so
just keep that in mind if it's not
available in your country okay and here
we go first item that's that's the art
that's not an item
that's that's the art it was draw by
Deon the same person that also Drew my
starting sun screen you know the one
where I drink tea I really like that one
so it's really really pretty and um I'm
really happy it's so pretty I really
like how golden it looks you know like
Sunkissed yeah yeah and then Al that's
the illustration I will be doing limited
um Edition merch
um um the little it's like a picture
like a photograph look at this don't say
it don't say it don't say said and then
I'm going to hand sign them on limited
edition if you buy the whole pet but if
um even if you don't get the limited
edition it's still going to be included
just as a like a golden foil kind of
thing and there is a complete set bonus
video pack for both sets like either
limited or non-limited Edition and that
is a tea party wallpaper and um that's I
animated it myself I wanted to have like
a you know from the art I wanted to have
like a wallpaper that I can use with
like like an animated
wallpaper um it's very it's like subtle
animated so it's not like super flashy
so you can actually have it in the
background uh and I animated it myself
with uh live Tod and after effects cuz I
don't know I kind of wanted to have
something that you know like that I can
have
immediately you know what I mean just
like being able to have some downable
content I thought was really nice so
yeah that's uh there and then this
also uh the little um postcard style
graphic as I said and then very fast
item is an immigr tea poty
blanket do you want to be cuddly and
warm it's actually really big I don't
remember how big it is it probably says
so on the website I think it was like
150 or something it's really big and
it's really nice the back side is green
as you can see and then the front is in
my my my art and I really like this art
oh my my God look at this look at this
like look at these little otal oh my god
look how cute you look look how cute you
look which one's your favorite my
favorite is the one that's carrying the
tea and pouring it in they're so cute I
love that so
much okay um let me reposition that and
then next
item a T-shirt and I really like this
t-shirt oopsie because as you can see
the design it's kind of it's a little
bit minimalistic the front only has like
a little clock
I picked this one I mean I picked them
all but you know what I mean and then um
the back is like coog wheel with little
otos in it which is a little bit more OB
like obvious
Mer but still not like super crazy so I
really like it almost together strong
it's true and then and then and then and
then I have
[Music]
uh oh yeah situational voice pack tea
party preparation voice in Japanese
English and German uh and I wrote this
one myself as I usually do with voice
packs I think the only voice packs I
didn't write with like the very first
ones because I was there was too much
too much to do uh during debut time but
since then I've always written my voice
packs I really like the scripts it's fun
to do and this one I made a German one
so if you've ever always wanted to have
like ger one you can it's like the same
like if you buy one you get all of them
it's not like separate prices or
anything
um and then we have
a
jar the imma jar look at this look at
this I love this one okay so the reason
I wanted this is because when I went to
the f I bought a a a jar I think it was
like a dit jar and I love that jar like
I love it I use it for everything you
can put like Gumi bears in it I
sometimes I put like my um my like
supplements in it you can put like USB
sticks in it uh yeah and it has a really
nice pattern it has the little windup
key on the top and the bottom of the lid
has coog wheels and I think that's
really cool I like it a lot oh yeah this
was this was this was like I really
wanted this for some reason don't ask me
I really wanted this it's like a little
box where you can put stuff and then
obviously the logo and everything on the
front as well uh it could hold glue I
guess yeah that's that's an
idea uh and then and then and it's not
too it's kind of smallish so you can
also just use it as decoration if you
want and then my favorite item hidden
automo cup and salsa I designed this one
myself um as you can see it's a it's a
little cup with notes the notes uh it
goes like the ones that are on my skirt
usually and then on the salsa like under
the cup isn't hidden timal and then when
you in look inside of the cup cup
there's also
hidden so yeah I was really happy that
this one was possible as a um I sent
them like a really ugly drawing and then
like bit by bit there was a lot of back
and forth of like okay that's how about
this and I was like okay okay okay so my
vision worked and I'm really happy and
as you can see the OTA has two different
face expressions um I really actually
this one I might just buy a bunch myself
because I think the Cup's really pretty
and I've seen obviously this is just
like a flat drawing but I've seen some
uh of the cups that have been made and
they just look really nice so I'm super
excited for this one yeah I'm actually
excited for all of them so can't wait
okay and that's it that's the Set uh as
I said all the stuff um feel free to
check it out the merch is going live in
35 minutes so midnight
c um so it's not on sale yet
oh we'll see we'll see yeah so that's
the much oh
also if you get the much set at the
whole life official um shop only uh then
you also get like a little little um
what is it called a card a train card a
little card with the official art and
everything on it so yeah just just as
like a little
bonus so yeah feel free to tell me which
one you like the most I'm really excited
also uh what you think of the voice pack
I played a little bit of violin in it
as well and uh it's just like a little
help me prepare for my
birthday yeah okay well let's those are
my things thank you thank you wait where
is she where did she wait let me just
check if I did everything correctly I
think so I think
so where did she
go where did she go what did you
where did she go we're going to have to
find
[Music]
her let's
see she's long gone n don't worry I have
fast
feet
[Music]
actually I have an idea I might not have
fast feet but maybe you do
guys help me out will you carry me
will he carry
[Music]
me can you carry me
please H it's not working
again no yeah sure maybe jet pack time I
don't have a jetp pack oh it
[Music]
worked huh
carry me carry me carry me carry me
carry me carry me come on come on come
on come on come on I want to be I don't
want to walk anymore I'm tired I'm sick
and tired of walking around how heavy
are you I'm a puppet I'm a little plushy
what do you
think okay let's see what's the
answer yes nice okay
[Music]
there we go nice this is way better
thank you guys thanks for carrying me
thanks this is great I love it this is
working way better than I
expected okay okay okay
H well that kind
of threw me off wait is that I see her
she's hiding behind the bushes quick
quick guys quick
quick run after her run after her let me
see let me see one sec one sec one sec
one sec one sec one sec me
[Music]
see this way
oh this
[Music]
way there she
is quick quick trpp her trpp her trpp
her
[Music]
it's
time we're going to we're going to use
our we're going to use our item guys
it's just like a jrpg no this is not
like a jrpg because in a jrpg no one
uses any items quick quick use the glue
use the glue and trap
her yes okay nice nice nice nice nice
nice there we
go your evil deeds will be no
[Music]
longer what what are you doing here no
give me back my body let me go give me
back my body let me go give me give me
give me my body
back you're he never understand I don't
understand I don't care don't you you
got it all give me my body back here
give me my body back you know what
yeah okay well so I have an idea um
we're going to have to torture her in
order to get her out of my body so guys
please help me
pick what should we
do huh what what should we what should
we what shall we do please pick that's
what is she talking about shut up don't
just take my body and then take my thing
how dare you do that to me you don't
understander that I
through give me back my body come
on no don't don't do I need it there's
nothing I need more but I don't know me
your body an I
would I'm going to manually start a poll
okay we have multiple ver multiple
opport options uh
either what do we
do okay we could tell her some bad jokes
good idea we could tickle her also good
idea
or make the most annoying noises in the
[Music]
world yeah I can't write all of that
that's probably why it's not working
there we go there we
go guys guys what are we going to
do okay let's
see hell some bad jokes tickle her make
the most annoying noises in the world it
says in the world it says in the world
was really nice she sang really nicely
and I was watching a bunch of other
people it was a nice time okay let's do
that one I went
[Music]
someof oh
God let me
go fine fine ah
ah no no no no no stop stop oh God stop
stop okay fine you win this time your
body sucks anyways what but next time
I'll get a better one just you wait just
you wait what do you mean just you wait
oh no oh no what do you mean just you
wait no don't let her wait guys don't
let her Escape don't don't let her
Escape well thank God we have our
trusted jar for just that quick quick
trap us soul trap us soul in that guys
hurry up hurry
up you got to you got to you got to trap
us
Soul
pH we did
it we did
it there we
go okay you can have it
and with that evil Was Defeated okay I'm
going to go get get go back into my body
are you guys are you guys ready for that
I'm going to going to have to go back
into my
body look her hair turned from red to
Green again so that's a good sign that's
a really good sign
actually uh let's see say goodbye to
this puppet bodyy
bye-bye I wish I could wave I can wiggle
[Music]
bye byebye
body okay this is going to be harder
than I thought and I have to go here and
then blink my brain and my
soul with my real body
[Music]
go oh that's
weird don't say
anything we did
it yay we did
it weit we we did it nice
myk God okay that was very stressful for
me and my
body thank God though that's over we
defeated the evil soul I wonder know who
that that was I have no idea that's
weird
wait my phone's ringing um yes hello hey
it's me again oh hi hi Corney the court
date has been decided and the trial is
happening right now right now oh oh okay
I I
I
guess I gu I guess we got to go to
court come on guys let's go let's go to
court all in a day's worth on my
birthday can you imagine that on my
birthday on my birth I can't believe it
I can't I can't believe this I can't
believe this I cannot I can I cannot
believe
this objection your honor the accused GG
murin clearly intended to hurt my client
both emotionally and physically
objection heay it was an accident my
client has very weak hands and your
client happened to have slipped out how
does she have weak hands she's literally
called the Fister quiet in the courtroom
Iris
proceed as I was saying my client saw an
opportunity to play around with the doll
and took it she saw a cute little doll
lying around and she picked her up and
then started to play with it how was she
supposed to know that it was alive she
then stood close to a window and
accidentally let go of her there was no
malicious intent objection there might
not have been any malicious intent but
the outcome was still attempted murder
due to negligence how was I supposed to
know she wasn't as durable as usual I
was a doll you're always a
doll I am an
automaton
quiet I've come to a conclusion it's a
very complicated situation I can see but
we have to see everyone's sides and
analyze the new one's predicament and
clearly there's a lot of contrasting
evidence the court rules as follows both
both you're both guilty what what
this sucks on my birth on my on my
birthday on my on my on my birthday they
will put me in prison on my
birthday should I say on my birthday one
more time on my on my
birthday okay thank God I have my
inventory still let's see
I don't think that's going to help me
this time I okay let me just put that
away again oh my on my birthday if only
if only there was a way out huh if only
there was a
way aless I guess we're going to have to
rut here forever this
sucks huh what's that
sound wait you hear that you hear that
what is that
huh get away from the
wall people I've come to pick you up and
make good on our promise what nice thank
you let's get out of here let's this
let's get out of here let's let's get
out of here let's let's let's get out of
here
so do you want to go get a snack yeah
I'm actually really hungry the AG
minutes in
prison man those were really they really
messed with me oh I'm so hungry man
[Music]
um where are you oh there you
are oh dang it I forgot something
[Music]
guys guys guys wake up it's my
birthday guys it's my guys it's my
birthday it's for birthday did you need
saving what she's she's in the other
room don't worry about
it don't worry about it don't worry
about it and that's the that's that's
that's that's Happy Birthday to me
yay wait let me copy something over one
moment
please uh this
one
and and O that's
big
and can I make it automatic thank yeah I
don't even have to do anything does it
for me thanks
OBS there we go happy Birthday everyone
oh I will say this once sorry for the
Scuf sorry and that's what I will say uh
I hope you had a nice time I had a lot
of fun preparing for this oh I've always
I thought it was really fun I was really
happy that everyone so many people
agreed to playing along I didn't get
like I didn't have time to make a proper
credits thingy so I just have a text
thing but yeah so obviously um I thank
you very much for anyone who joined in
and also did like alternative stuff
there was actually quite a few
things this is not formal by the way no
one no one gets to see it but there was
some hidden things and I'm really
grateful that everyone uh was willing to
take part in it and um some things we
saw some things we might have not seen
um and yeah that's just how it is when
you choose choose the path of your
destiny and uh yeah so thank you very
much to all to all the girls for taking
part we had some main RS we also had
cameos um wait let me put that in front
of
me
oh yeah uh thank you for those as well
of course thank you so much and then uh
for for the uh I did the the editing and
the script and fil me if you can call it
that and also for the little puppet
model art and rigging I did that as well
I think you could tell by the scuffy
line art but I was very happy that I was
able to make like a little a little
model for today um and I hope you guys
like the little plushy plush I mean it's
not a plushy it was like a puppet it was
supposed to be like a little puppet you
know like squishy squishy puppet uh and
also thank you very much uh for for um
nor Pro for helping but making the poll
integration the reason it didn't work
was mostly my fault so please um um I
think I figured out why I think I made
the options too long sometimes and then
the program didn't want that which I
didn't think of my bad but it's okay it
all worked out in the end um oh did I
make a typo
where skipped skipped skiper skiper and
then obviously the songs that I used
thank you very much to B for Lending me
her wonderful song and also I use the
Justice above below EUR be remak and
thank you otos for taking part as well
otos Os Os Os and then for the rest of
the week as you
know already talked about it um quite a
bit but we're having a fun schedule this
week
and let me just open
this just want to show it on screen as
well why
okay
raging
uh we're having a birthday week so next
is uh tomorrow top 100 anate list don't
worry about it h hand came sing Auto
plush pouch not plush Justice Q&A with
on Thursday and then on Saturday violent
Kaa with gas um um H gas and then Sunday
Dark Souls 3 marathon with um some
guests here in there as well and yeah I
had a really fun time today uh sorry for
being late again thank you for waiting
for me I hope I hope you had fun overall
um as uh oh yeah the merch is opening in
14 minutes so um feel free to stay up a
little bit longer for that and yeah yeah
I hope I hope you guys all had a nice
time I'm glad I was able to mess about
mess around do whatever the heck I had I
had some technical difficulties not the
not the chat something else was breaking
before the stream but I think all things
considered it was okay uh I mean it was
good and it worked out okay is what I
was going to say and um yeah uh for I
also saw like a lot of fan art and fan
projects and stuff I have I didn't have
time yet to look at it properly but I
will do so and if not this week I'll
definitely do one stream about it next
week I'll probably also like Read Super
chats and everything and um look at like
anything uh so please don't worry about
that sorry that I haven't gotten around
to it yet it's going to be a little bit
of a full week ending plops should I
should I see if my PC can handle the
ending plops I mean I've mentioned this
before I have gotten a new pc but I
haven't built it
yet let's see is it going to work is it
going to kill is it going to kill my PC
it was just because there was so many in
the beginning I think it's should be
fine now uh yeah thank you very
much go out on a crash that's a good
plan there we go it's working I mean it
was working in the beginning technically
right it's not it's not that it wasn't
working it was just not working ideally
I would say but it was work it was
definitely working it's
working it just works
[Laughter]
thank you very much thank you thank you
for all the love and
um kind of loud let me turn that down
okay I'm lagging oops okay that's that's
fine okay thank you very much see you
all next time tomorrow probably
depending and um yeah uh I really
really I'm going to turn it
down I really really appreciate you guys
hanging out and uh watching when I mess
about and um I wish you all a wonderful
week and I hope um that um no matter
what you have a nice time and at you get
to you know honestly okay can I read one
of the jokes I had prepared for the in
case you had chosen jokes because I
think it's kind of funny
okay guys guys guys guys jce is a dish
best served
cold if it were served warm it would be
just
water get it justice justice justice
just it
[Music]
okay Co
[Laughter]
one can't even read the chat anymore
everything's lagging thank you very much
everyone I really appreciate you thank
you thank you for watching uh let's talk
more in the coming days and the coming
streams and hang out Lots
bye-bye see you
[Music]
I'm still here trying to make this work
not sure if it's going to it's lagging
oh there we go it's kind of working okay
let's see let's see let's see let's see
let's see let's see let's see it's a
secret ending screen me um let me see
there we go thank you very much thank
you very much for watching guys I really
do appreciate it I'm sorry if I was a
bit nervous today but I had a lot of fun
I'm going to go trash for now and then
I'll be energized for the rest of the
week hopefully
hopefully hopefully
[Music]
also let me
see okay it's lagging out I'm just going
to add the stream
sorry okay thank you very much um let's
talk a lot more this week and um bye-bye
bye-bye
[Music]