[Music]
um
do
[Music]
done
bye
oh
[Music]
do
hello
hi everybody how are you
[Music]
[Laughter]
i just randomly clicked on that one
i was just looking at stuff
[Music]
hello hello
we're cute
[Music]
i was looking at
when i can buy
american baby
welcome to the stream combo
i know i know it's shocking but i am
through on my own will my own choice
i'm playing an fps game
in online fps games games new game
um
furia furia
someone said fioria is like a phoenix i
don't know if she really is where is she
where she was she
i mean
she's got quite the hips but other than
that i don't know how she looks like me
we can try her but she has a sword how
do you how does she uh fps if she has a
sword how does she shoot how do you how
do you shoot huh
her hips don't lie yeah okay i guess
it's um because of the wings
it's a gun
oh what too what
what
of course i have ahmed's voice of course
i have it
i wouldn't i wouldn't play this game if
i didn't have alma's voice just kidding
but
i mean it was kind of kind of a
motivator
indeed um
she's so i don't know
where are you
is she invisible are you i know
um
[Music]
oh my god
are you
how cute pirate
[Music]
sparkling i love the color purple oh
what's up
it's one of my favorite wait there's
different color
what
what wha why am i here now i just wanted
to look at the different colors
apparently there's different colors
what's this
oh
who are you saris
yo
what a skin
[Laughter]
oh she's
that is that is fascinating
it's a bunny suit
and she has she
she has a prisoner bunny
[Laughter]
[Music]
what do you mean a stream of mode on
what do you mean this stream remote wait
why is my one uh
my one
monitor still off man
kawaii collection
wait what does the kawaii collection
look like
oh goo
goo oh you would like this
google would like
this street style
i mean let's pretend that is cute
we're gonna look at some skins before we
go into the game
oh
oh christmas
oh cute the broom is so cute with the
gingerbread that's adorable
oh
oh yeah
well that's a lot of skin
[Music]
kind of dangerous if you go out to the
battlefield like that
but looking looking good i wonder what
what body lotion she uses because her
skin looks so soft
you have that skin that's why i'm main
ferris oh i see
oh
wait she has a snake i just now noticed
i was focused on other parts but she has
a snake
it's cute it's all curled up
cute
oh
vivian vivian cute
i see okay
well i never mind never mind never mind
um i don't know why some of these are
not shop showing up um maybe my pc is
too red
rain can't
leon
cute liam cute i don't know we're gonna
we're gonna try some
um
cute we're gonna try some characters
that i haven't tried last time i suppose
and just try to practice a little bit oh
who is she nice
i don't see you
i need to go here to see you
oh she looks like a thief
which is probably why she's called me
maeve
oh wow
i'm a pirate oh dear nice
tammy
cammy
what do you suddenly have a different
name
[Music]
everybody put your hands up in the air
everybody everybody just like you don't
even care
[Music]
why are you birds speaking
oh my god cute
i love the little cats
demon thingy that she has tangling on
her hip
oh wait that one's cute too the cat
[Music]
it's playing with
like a a bowl a wool ball and her shoes
are dope she has strawberries on her
shoes too i like i like her
i like her fashion
probably not exactly what i would wear
but still adorable
maeve a many of uh looking cute again
what should i play with guys do you have
any
yo those shoes are so cool i know do you
guys have any recommendations what what
you think that i would do well with you
sparkly it's like she dipped into
that lush bath bomb but you know there's
a there's a black lush bath bomb with
sparkles and if you put that in your
bathtub afterwards
holy [\h__\h] you will never get rid of
those sparkles but the whole bathtub
will be like a black bathwater with
sparkles it's crazy
uh
can it be a girl guys you can please
only say girls
i only want to play with girls
um
so
limited to that
i will see
oh
skye skye
i like your voice
[Music]
why are you guys saying ying like who
was young again
[Music]
is a healer why are you telling me to
play a healer don't tell me to play
healer
evie
evie evie
wasn't shitty [\h__\h] difficult to play
didn't i try her and it was difficult
we can like at least warm up with
uh tyra was the one that went like pew
pew pew pew poo right
tyra was the one with the fast fast
goods
let's trial
around tyra
my russian tara i think we're gonna do a
russian snack box review very soon but
because it did arrive oh hello who are
you
so how do i play again and like i'm
already uh always uh
oh oh i'mma always started the games for
me so i don't really know region i
suppose reach in europe
okay
uh
what is this slayer animation
game a little bit okay i can choose what
which one do i want capture the
objective ah that was the [\h__\h] one
game mode based around eliminating
anything uh-huh so your enemies in
control
um
i think i think i tried all of them
before so i don't really care i think
death match is fast
oh sheet should i do this one huh
oh i'm selecting which ones i don't want
and then it will be randomly selected i
suppose okay okay okay i'll get it
no not
no i don't want to be will i can still
select right after after we're in there
oh my god
hello
um no i'm good i'm i'm russian spicy but
spasiba
uh sorry oh god how do i i don't know
how to play this game anymore
uh uh how do i what do i how do i push
any buttons which buttons do i push
e
crossfire
left to right q f
[\h__\h] enemy uh-huh purlin in
incendiary device that leaves a pool of
viral impact
um
[Music]
the target will be dealt with the target
will be dealt with
increase your attack speed at another
speed during the weapon shots will not
come
[Music]
i'm a [\h__\h] noob be nice to me
timbermill capture the objective okay
push push and push we're gonna be
pushing our game sounds high and it
could probably possibly be maybe i'm
close to the target stand by for
extraction i'm close to the target
stand by
oh my god
wait a second uh
holy [\h__\h] that was that wasn't it loud
i'm so sorry
uh mercy what hunting choose my talent
uh
[Music]
we're doing hunting parties i guess
hello hello
oh
oh god hey
is anyone here a friend of mine
anyone uh
whole life fans
i can't do this i can't do this why did
i choose to play without them and i
can't play without them i can't play a
ps game without them just follow the
letters oh god oh god
copper cover grabber cover
what did f do again
are they shooting me i eliminated
someone i think doesn't mean oh doesn't
mean i killed someone hello
hello
okay okay
respawning in prince soup fading one
you're dead just playing dead gets them
every time
relatable i was just playing dead gets
them every time
yeah i also don't do real death
i just play around as well uh i don't
want to go down but
where is where is the
are we losing
how does it go
[Laughter]
that was a bad spot for me to be in
objective lost [\h__\h] i'm so sorry ahmed
come help us freeze i will serve my
country to the people
maybe i shouldn't go there
guys i'm coming
i will help you
they're all dead my friends
[Music]
i'm so bad at this
i was just playing dead gets them every
time get them every time come let's go
together stamp them
what if i shut
[Music]
[Applause]
what was that
stop hiding
is that a healer
are we winning now
[Music]
not anymore
oh but i did i eliminating is just when
i help right but
but i feel like i did the last hits on
on some of them
how's it going we're definitely not
winning as far as i can tell
[Music]
ow
over time
defense failed let's go
let's go
i'm sorry guys i'm so sorry
i'm so sorry i'm not helping
so close
close to what what was i close to
definitely not winning
uh
buy item i'mma set it's not so important
auto purchase is enabled so
i think we're probably fine
i wouldn't know what to buy anyway i
have a cat hair in my mouth
ah four
three okay i got it i got it one
let's go
kill them
kill those
i follow
oh
oh my god
a second chance oh my god
to your tongue
no no
don't get too cocky kiwawa
you're still [\h__\h] don't get don't get
cocky
where is the door
[Laughter]
that always kill me they always kill me
your local bees
funny name
i'm coming
you guys here almost she's so cute
oh my dead friends
i got no chance here
oh i'm not alone anymore i'm
dead i'm not giving up
i'm bad again we were so bad 99
objective loss jehu
oh
i was just playing dead gets them every
time yeah i don't know what i can buy
but i did something like autobuy
what was that sound
[Music]
i thought too fast
let me go again let me go again let me
go again let me go again it's still loud
isn't it sorry guys i'll make it a
little bit quiet uh a little bit more
quiet afterwards
gonna save us all
what the [\h__\h]
but what what is this the game is
calling me the damage dealer
sound is fine okay okay okay
okay
the healer is bad okay yes always always
blame the healer
i mean i used to be uh
i used to ooh
i used to be a healer in mmorpg as
always
so um
blaming the healers is i i have a bit of
a pity when it comes to that
but i think i was always a good healer
in mmorpgs i think i did my job mostly
well i was like so focused on spamming
that heal button without even a milli
milli millisecond
of time in between gg i guess
uh rikyu
let's let's do another riku
okay i'll make it a little bit more
quiet though
i'm in i'm in
[Music]
good
alcohol in her flask it's not even a
flask what does that mean no frontline
no flank what does that mean
are they asking me to not be frontline
and not be flangler
what does that mean
oh oh that we that we have no flank
what's a flank what's a flank
don't worry i'll take care of it i'll
flank them is that when you shoot them
from the side is that a flank
so someone that shoots them from the
side
yeah that's what it is isn't it i think
i know that from soccer
oh does it matter if we have a flag okay
sinister organization to foil
i'm just gonna do this one now
um
oh hello hot lady
didn't want to be looked at okay so
we're doing uh oh we're doing the the
death match now where we have to kill a
lot of people maybe we have a chance
maybe we have a chance in that case
oh
football
when they say football they will say
soccer ki wawa and when i say soccer
they will say football
football is closer to the to the german
word anyway so it's actually surprising
that i say soccer but i think in school
i think in school they taught us to say
soccer
in english
[\h__\h] oh give me my horse can i get back
on the horse i'm so sorry [\h__\h] i how did
i how did i get back on the horse
oh [\h__\h]
i still don't know i still know what f
really does oh first blood let's go
are you behind that
where is you
oh god
it's too quiet are we winning
it's looking good
where did you go she she bumped under
the floor
f targets and they make more damage they
take more damage okay
i will trust i will try
okay wow we're good we're doing well
we're doing well so far
hey you [\h__\h] careful i'm dangerous eat
this fire
[Music]
this is too chill right now it should be
more exciting
it's too easy i should come down make it
more difficult
oh these people don't seem to be dying
either anyway
i'm gonna reload is there a way to
reload manually damn helmet
back up please
never mind don't need it
[Laughter]
wait for healing
i don't even know who the healer is so i
don't know who to stay close to
but that's okay i don't need healing
[Laughter]
how is that close match between you and
me
killing androxus makes you superstar did
i kill on drugs
oh she's coming
what's she doing what is she doing i
killed her kayla what the [\h__\h]
he wants to take uh revenge i see
not happening not happening
so close that bastard and drop that was
on drugs
oh it was salty
no now no i'm salty too now i'm gonna
get him i think i remember what he looks
like now
oh god
he's gonna come for me again i feel it
what is happening
is that androxus
is that him is that him
shut
up
she's playing balls with me
where's she where is she where is she
dokodokko
are you guys fine down there and they're
fine look at us winning
380 yo oh thanks to me all thanks to me
ah that's too fast i'm
coming down here oh victory
she can go invisible for real
yo
why were you so good
because of me right
see i'm like an fps player now i say gd
oh wait i want to look at that i'm
probably still the worst am i
scoreboard
let me see how well did i do
a four oh [\h__\h] i'm not so good
oh damage uh but better than this person
i'm better than this
person shielding healing i don't do that
two to five kill
uh something a sister soon two thousand
two
i mean i mean i'm not i'm not that far
behind
i'm supposed to say gt easy [\h__\h]
damn that that calyx and
that person myth myth
they did
so many kills
wow got a step up my game but maybe
they were probably like at the bottom i
was still playing it safe because that
was at the top taking cover
i out damaged the helicopters and some
[Laughter]
that should be a given
okay okay okay
gg easy saying is toxic
not if if only our teammates hear it
right right right
positioning is crucial
yes
choose your chance i i i only feel safe
with tyra right now
i'll i'll try a different one next round
wait that's so cute what the [\h__\h] the
one in the background on on
my left hand side
the one on the
weird dragon
oh that dragon is so cute what a
dinosaur whatever the [\h__\h] that is
the target we have no front line okay i
must stand in the front line then
i be frontline
a two-headed turtle
it's so cute what the [\h__\h] how does that
character
uh attack i wonder
penny wreck no that's the name emoji
mooji is the character
i have an orange eevee
cute
it vomits
the third little spit stuff
she's a girl character if you want to oh
really
it looks cute
actually that that emoji um
avatar
reminds me of lapras darkness
you see it i think you gotta look really
close i think it's pretty small on most
people's screens but that looks like
that
yes my dark
how because it's too big as horns that
go upwards they have exactly the same
shape
yeah yeah
oh sh
what are we doing
wow
oh nice christmas tree
i feel like i'm in a hotel lobby
any friends
[Music]
what are we doing capturing pushing
press t
it didn't do anything
siege mode uh-huh
looks like a hotel lobby doesn't it like
you know in a resort in a fancy resort
looks good
um account for me
four
three
is that a shield can i shoot through
anyway oh my god what the [\h__\h]
damn they were fast
we're gonna lose this
high
i will serve my country to the bitter
end i will serve my country to the beta
and
bitter and
i think i destroyed that
thing
i have to be frontline
i have to be the front line
because we don't have one it's my job
now i adopted the job no don't
[Music]
okay i will stop being frontline i will
hide now
what are they doing
oh
do we have a healer in the tank
oh [\h__\h] i'm trying to do damage but
it's tough it's tough what are the
percentages on the top left
what are what are those guys
my f ability oh my
my f ability
why am i so slow why am i so slow oh
because we're going back here
ultimate skill ah
ultimate school charge so f is my
ultimate right
oh
what are you doing
[Laughter]
that horse was floating
he is
oh okay
in 15 seconds okay i'm i got it 15
seconds capture point spawning in 15
seconds you heard it you heard it here
first i'll go where the others are i
suppose
four
three
two
[Music]
i'll follow you guys so i don't know
where you where are you going
they parted they went separate ways
i think i think
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
good
[Laughter]
that was fun
that was definitely front front line
objective last but it's okay i'm having
fun
thingy
[Laughter]
[Music]
100 is that doesn't mean i'm ready for
my old ultimate
fancy kill
i tried i was just playing dead
he doesn't know i'm behind him
now he knows
oh
and stay here
oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
they all were looking at me
my health is a buff oh yeah yeah is it
the one where the ammo is endless as far
as i know
lost am i really that's all you're going
to tell me i need some more mental
support amish it just says lost
[Laughter]
i'm man
amelia wants
bro [\h__\h] i'm so sorry i'm a victor but
i'm really [\h__\h] okay i know it
oh thank you
thank you cutie riley i i thank you i
feel too embarrassed to say anything in
the chat now but
um thank you i appreciate it very much
uh
let's look at that
oh wait i have more
more damage
than pennywreck who was complaining
about the team
no wait i have more credits
why do i whether i have more credits she
has three
kills
five deaths of herself and one assist
streak i have a five killing streak
wait top damage oh my god
wait i'm actually can you guys
screenshot this this will never happen
again
oh my god
i think we're the only ones left yeah oh
wait he's in the enemy team
[Music]
the real
i made up a new word
at kfp we don't say gg we say
edgy or so i don't know
also congratulations on
killing with me
i guess
i'll i'll i'll go again what should i
play what should i play what should i
play guys from me something that you
think i will be good but be serious like
don't don't don't give me something i
would be bad at no healers
[Laughter]
okay
uh
sword lady where the [\h__\h] is she again
where the [\h__\h] what was her name again
uh oh god uh
was it her wait what's her name
for you furious furious
can i play here we will see
uh amelia
sam bring an end to the darkness okay
let's see let's see what we can do how
does she's a healer oh [\h__\h] i love you
no they don't hate me they don't hate me
do i stay close to them right click to
heal do i heal specific people or do i
have an aoe hill [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] i'm so
sorry guys i'll kill you all
[\h__\h]
i am the protector
i am the flame oh no
um
so i guess i'll just go with this
[Music]
cherish
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
so i should focus on healing and not
killing at all like no shootie shoot
i'll just
how do i heal do we have two healers
isn't this a healer as well
oh god
what's that
oh i need to shoot is is shooting the
healing
right click the heel and left click to
shoot okay yeah bit amelia since you're
not gonna be mad at me right
okay okay [\h__\h] we didn't need two
healers
sheesh okay i'll try to follow the
people where the most people are
oh i have slow shooting shoot a he'll
heal he'll he'll heal [\h__\h] oh no
no
weren't behind us
[\h__\h] androxus
it's always that character apparently
you need it again
i am needed again
why is the phoenix
okay supposedly the fiend's character uh
oh god
i thought you were on my teeth
look at him
kicking my head oh
oh my god
i guess yeah cause phoenix is uh phoenix
better i guess yeah yeah reviving people
i only only want to revive myself though
okay let's try to be helpful at least if
i can't kill then i'll focus on healing
how's this worked
oh i think did i heal her
objective loss let's go
i'm snapping now am i snapping am i in
furious not though
oh god oh god oh god
he's out for me he's got it out for me
i need to heal this person
yep yep you're welcome you're welcome
you're welcome you're welcome you're
welcome
oh my god i actually think i just did
some damage emilia simps amelia simp
we're we're one heart we we've we
evolved amelia's sims so i shall try my
best to keep you alive
shoot this car can i do that
oh nice wait i'm we're actually not
going that bad i think
let me heal you let me heal you let me
heal you amelia simp amelia watson is
the best
cute detective gotta gotta love her oh
wait you need healing you need healing
you need healing healing with you he'll
heal he'll heal you he healed you
i got acknowledged as a healer
this is a [\h__\h] ride man
i'm healing
this is my destiny i think
i was supposed to be here okay get out
of here [\h__\h] [\h__\h] okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay i'll get killing
this reverse ceiling oh [\h__\h] i should
use cute cute cute stunts the enemy
queue sounds the enemy
my fire is eternal i will keep this
close she's phoenix my fire is eternal
she's a phoenix skye
wait i will heal ya don't die don't die
where is where's skye here
oh my gosh i didn't want to shoot you
okay he'll heal he
let
do i have to be really excited with the
aim
[\h__\h]
what was that
what was that bomb that you dropped what
was that
nine eight i am needed again i am needed
again don't die
i'm so sorry i did pretty well for a
while but now it's hard to get back into
it
you're sorry
[\h__\h] hair the [\h__\h] head is
riley how the [\h__\h] did you queue with me
again
how did you do it
i'm so sorry guys i'm sorry i'm sorry
why does everyone have the the these on
their crotches and their butts why
do i need to heal your butt stay blessed
[Laughter]
healing zone is the butt yes yes
uh
the massage lady told me when she was
massaging my butt and i said it hurts uh
please don't please don't touch my butt
so strongly she was like yeah but
there's a lot of emotions in that
spot so that's why i massage strongly
and i'm like you know one of the [\h__\h]
nerds stop
i can't do that
oh my god oh my god
time's ticking
is that is that healing aoe healing
can you riley i'm giving you a boom
[\h__\h] hedgehog okay
[Music]
lots of emotions yes
no but honestly i don't know my butt is
um
kind of uh sensitive
uh
but massage therapist tends to like
massaging my butt i mean understandable
cute but you know no it's like for real
though
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
you bastard again they're like a [\h__\h]
ninja they come out of nowhere
funny i am immortal though
i mean you know that don't you
i'll focus on healing again
stay blessed stay blessed hashtag bless
oh god what the [\h__\h]
can i heal myself
how would i heal myself
guess we're falling back
why are you shooting me oh
can i break that
whoa whoa what did that do what did that
do
i got a kill as a healer
i got it was that that was my old am i
my stun i think
be healed oh i need to heal amelia simp
amelia
no
sorry
i will get justice
[\h__\h]
does that hit anyone
my holy light
[Music]
don't die don't die don't die
oh oh [\h__\h] bunny walker
f2 f is your escape f to escape
i am needed again
[Music]
they're so close
what is that
am i am i doing trying to do too much
damage should i focus more on healing is
this a good balance i don't know
oh no why would you kill me the fate
party wine damage buff ah
i should have done that earlier
maybe
look good to me
he's doing okay
good balance
i'm sorry
should i write sorry
gt
um let's see
healing 17 thousand buckley's the other
healer with 46
i hope i'm not oh
oh
no please bunny walker i don't want to
be on your
i feel so team saying that
you're not supposed to be good yet okay
i came out there like everybody knows me
i'm famous
[Laughter]
egg oh i forgot
was one of us
indeed egg i forgot to say my own thing
[Laughter]
wait their healer their healer is this
one
i was pretty good compared to that
person
is that a healer
is that a healer character as well
yeah
yeah oh well then
oh then i'm average but kylie is good
and i'm uh i'm i'm average and this
person is just bad
[Laughter]
their healing just focused on damage i
guess yeah
perhaps so oh but holy [\h__\h]
that this person
even has a lot of damage even though
they were also healing so much but i
guess when you have an aoe heal that
kind of goes off automatically
i guess you don't really have to do much
i don't know
toxic i'm not toxic no i'm just i'm just
trying to uh uh uh
evaluate the situation
aoe is generally easy what should we try
next
what character should we try next um
i mean the healing was actually um kind
of fun as well
but we do want to do damage
[Music]
vivian
uh
who was that again
vivian vivian million
ah
vivian
is she a pew pew pew pew or pew pew pew
pew
that is the question
vivian
vivian vivian vivian vivian
is it pew pew pew pew
vivian vivian that one's hot
that one's hot look at her
oh
wow
like the beauty mark on her on her face
okay
i'll try her um so i suppose she's just
a damage dealer or whatever
i will do my best let's go
uh
play
join kill
it
let me in let me in
i will be vivian i hope i find her fast
enough on the screen
on the selection screen
also don't worry guys i want i wanted to
talk to you guys about some things but
maybe maybe after the next match uh
just
in between like in in the matches i just
don't i don't have the
show
choose your champion i don't have the
real worst
i don't have the time to focus
wait i know i know crews kfp and blade
johnny i know you guys
hey hello
am i cringe
can the enemies read our texts right now
hello kfb
[Music]
okay make me proud guys
make on me proud
no no cringe
i should have added uvu to
that i hate to get my hands dirty i hate
to get my hands dirty
booby trap your sensor drones explode
dealing 600 damage you're applying a
knot and applying a knockback to those
hit when an enemy is within 20 units
uh-huh well it's called booby trap i
want it but i can't use it yet suspect
everyone the health of deflector shield
is increased by 450 and this cooldown is
reduced by half if it is destroyed by
a deflector shield one
[Music]
what was reloading again ah
i like reload
five
four
ah that's so good
okay
where do we go
go go go go
let us in
i think that was a
kind of a stupid
route
is that really the smartest round
okay okay okay okay okay let's do it
that was too fast
[Music]
i'll make them suffer no
my friends are dying
[Music]
i'm getting healed thank you
[Laughter]
where they come from q what does q do
oh my god
q to shield okay okay
okay
how long does my shield go
oh that's just stupid standing right in
front of and now that was my fault
obviously
oh wait what oh god oh god why are they
so close
[Music]
shoot
oh no
i tried
um no i'm fine with this one
you guys keep on saying to buy items but
i would have no idea what to buy i'm
just just leave it to the auto for now
oh no
try holding right click
okay
you think shooting like that will be
better
okay
got it this is so cute
you're so cute
five
four
three i want to try the character one
maybe
sometime
okay
let's go let's do this guys let's win
let's win shall we
oh god oh god
you know this is the thing when you go
to war and you're in the front line you
must
you must
suffer you must
be
the first one to die but only in order
to keep the others alive longer you know
it's for good cause
oh
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] oh
[Music]
i don't know why i'm doing so bad right
now maybe i'm not um good with this
character
although i feel like it's not even that
different from
tyra because they both
oh i
i
i did not help much check her skills i'm
trying to use at least a shield
[Laughter]
and the right click is just uh zooming
in
oh are you wearing it i'm sorry that
we're [\h__\h] team
i don't know what that does
i'm gonna die i'm gonna die
what did that do it looked fancy though
i shoot more
oh god oh god
yeah it was pretty bad
stand behind my kfd employees should i
use them as cover
yeah meat shield meat shield made out of
uh
chronos is pretty good kiara or time to
pocket kiana the dps carry of our team
what
not a dps scary
no i don't even want to look oh my god
hey i don't know what i'm shielding
i'll win wait i didn't even do much less
damage compared to the others
ngg
ntd
yeah chicken nugget shield
doesn't sound like it would be very
protective but
stick with tyra
um it's kind of boring to always stick
to the same character though no
yeah
i'll rig you
and
i will i will go with tyra i found a
liking in tyra try a tank
who would be a cute tank
character
[Music]
um
ash
ash okay
well as a tank
i i have to stand in front i i never i
hate being a tank though i never play a
tank in mmorpgs i know it's different
than
an fps game well
no it's still kind of similar i would
say as in having the
having them
um
uh what's the word responsibility
what's that is that my oh no no more
water error error error beep beep shut
up
my my humidifier yeah i don't want the
responsibility of
having to tank you know
although they are kind of beefy this is
ash choose your champion grover's mikey
no i don't wanna i don't where's where's
my timer here tito thailand is your
champion
yeah
i it feels too
pressuring too
uh
go for a tank now
um
ash is fun is she easy
orders received the target will be dealt
with
i'll i'll play her i like my russian
lady
oh yeah so by the way i had a
um
last night
i had an interesting dream
uh
with like crocodiles
biting me
and [\h__\h] but uh the end of the dream was
very interesting because i
um
i was
shooting with with a bow
uh because
i was in some kind of like
place with a team and then another team
came to attack us uh to take over our
camp or something um but i was like i
was like okay [\h__\h] i gotta protect my
people uh it was really not that many
people but maybe like
15 people or so so i took a bow and an
arrow and i started shooting i started
shooting the enemies and i did so well
and then i woke up while i was doing
that and i noticed
i was like half asleep
but i was like doing the movements with
my hands like out of sleep as well like
in real life like i was i wasn't really
like picking my my arrows i wasn't
reloading but i was at least like doing
the movement with like pulling the arrow
back and then letting go
really slowly though and i had my eyes
closed and i saw the enemies
i killed a lot of people but at the same
time i noticed uh that was
that i was
uh awake but i was still kind of in a
dream it was like literally half house
50 50.
and i was slowly
slowly waking up
and like oh what what am i doing
what am i doing
so weird
but it was fun
okay let's capture i guess
reloading
oh he's a healer
see this already works so much better
oh
yes welcome welcome to my fire oh hell
yes yes
yes
looking good so far
yes we're winning
finally we captured something
be careful
come out of here oh we have a shield we
have a shield
yes
my fire
wait does the fire burn me my butt too
please don't do that
oh
[\h__\h]
and push and push and push
and push
target
acquired
we're dominating
[Laughter]
i might die i don't know
i'm scared wait we did it we did it
[Music]
oh i'm so proud
it's exciting when i'm actually uh not
losing
down baby you triple
point spawning in 15 seconds
thank you for letting me know um you're
you're the one that
makes me feel excited when i'm in this
game
i love you amen
everybody who missed out on the
announcer pack
you're bad you're really missing out on
something
what a waste
why did you not get the amelia watson
announcer pack huh
why did you not get that emilia watson
announcer back
let's go
got mine the next day after the clap
nice
that was the last day
don't always do your homework on the
last day though
objective
objective captured
we're moving we're moving guys he's
sitting on it
looking cool
why is that healer thingy over there
is it something you place somewhere and
it does not follow you
they like to run ahead huh
oh [\h__\h] oh
yes
[Music]
is he dead
yes
i got him
oh this this is dangerous dangerous
gamer
yes killing spree baby
holy [\h__\h]
i went all out there i had no cover but
it was still a bit fine oh my god entity
they uh
randalls will not understand maybe
they'll think i did it accidentally oops
no i didn't want to oops they want to
requeue so fast but let's see
18 000
oh kfb let's go thank you
yo
18 000 wait um i'm third third best
third most damage in my team
look at them doing no damage i guess
that's what happens when you're losing
i got a gift
not a hotel
i also got a [\h__\h] ton of friend requests
but oh here we go
that was
that was fun
you screenshotted my carry thank you
are we in oh wait i thought we were in
what was that
second most objective time on the team
oh no what does objective time mean
158 that i'm doing my job the most where
i was pushing the car
time spent capturing the payload time on
them
oh [\h__\h] i forgot
time spent pushing and capturing
okay
i didn't look that much like a noob this
time did i hey
okay let's split stone carry we're
pushing again okay okay i'll get okay
okay oh
i see another familiar name that made it
in again
okey-dokey try using your e in this
match
okay
what does e do again
i honestly just push the buttons without
really knowing what happens i can't
remember so many things so quickly
they have a sniper no problem
no problem i will not get sniped to the
target stand by for extraction yes
i'll do
i this e was the old t
the unlimited ammo right
oh my god
hopefully they aren't good oh the
snipers so yell bye
don't worry guys don't be scared oh but
we have this this up sodas or something
whatever that character was called but
people who play this this character are
usually always very very obnoxious
my ultimate
your e turns your gun into a figure gun
five
four
come with me
well i'm not that familiar with this map
oh where do i go oh
here
we go
jump right into it but we're good
it's like you offered your body to me i
know you're a kfp i know you are
sacrifices have to be made made
to make the empress happy right oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
let me back in let me back in
announcer amelia watson
it was time limited though you can't get
her anymore she's so special
super exclusive yes you missed out is
that the sniper is that the sniper
wait do they have it
do we have it i'm not sure
sheesh
[Music]
uh when we're doing if it's 50 50 not
60.
let me back let me back let me back i
need to capture no objective no
84 no
no no no no no no no no oh god
[Laughter]
[Music]
they took it from me
jesus
well i had absolutely no chance there
oh [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
did you kill my friend you bastard you
bastard
[Music]
worth it worth it [\h__\h] worth it
[Laughter]
i'm going like full
[\h__\h]
[\h__\h] died
[Laughter]
be aggressive yes gotta be aggressive
if you wanna win in life you gotta be
aggressive don't be defensive
you gotta take everything with your bear
grab hands grasp it no matter how
[\h__\h] hard it is
i did eliminate someone though
we're good we good we good
want me back let me log in let me back
him i heard that in apex you have to
queue like really [\h__\h] long so this
game is much better for me i don't have
the patience man
and when you're dead once you're like
kind of [\h__\h]
oh no
do you find successful
did we actually
defend
wait did we actually do it
like they they took the thing first but
we took them away from them
we took it away
or or they at least did not reach the
the
last uh
the goal
oh my god that's really i feel like
that's difficult
once they once they have the objective i
feel like it's difficult to get it back
i'm an engineer
ah we stopped them from advancing nice
[\h__\h] nice look at them they were so
ready
i'm gonna capture that [\h__\h] i'm gonna
capture it
uh
that's the
i could sniper
riding my heart oh my god i didn't know
it was valentine's day yet
oh my heart i will serve my country to
the bitter end
it hurts i'm bleeding can't be bleeding
i
bad idea bad idea
[Applause]
those boys they look so strong cause
they're in their little
robot i should also get into the [\h__\h]
robot
i need to get into the [\h__\h] robot
but i want to look cute so that's uh the
struggle
that's the struggle of being kiwawa need
to look cute let's capture this
killed him
i see you i failed
[Laughter]
i will defend no matter what it takes
this is not fair we deserve that
objective
we deserve it give it back
oh my god what the [\h__\h]
no i use my ot randomly
give it back give it back
mommy they're not giving back my toys
hello
where is he where is he did he die
where'd he go
oh no
okay okay okay okay
i made him run y'all
14 seconds left let's do our best
where's the goal where's the goal don't
let them don't let them into the goal
don't don't don't don't don't don't
don't don't don't don't no no matter
what i will [\h__\h] kill you if you let
them in
[Laughter]
over time
[Music]
i'm sorry
i was a bit too reckless at the end
i was so into it though
i was so into it oh my god
oh
did you guys watch the new video on the
whole live official channel by the way
with me
senpai it's out now
it's a cute cute funny video with a
typical japanese
comedic edit editing i love their
editing i love japanese comedy style
like that for videos
with all the sound effects and the quick
cuts
it was about uh having watermelon by
supposedly teach us
um
where the [\h__\h] are you going just
following you
oh my god
that was risky uh yeah but the the
joke was that vata senpai herself
doesn't really know what the hell she's
talking about
[\h__\h]
oh my god
i will kill you i will kill you i will
actually kill
i wanted that kill
wow
oh i'm on the rampage
[Music]
come here come here let me continue my
rampage please
oh god oh god
so yeah it was like tongue twisters and
japanese sayings
proverbs captain
uh
oh hello
i need some healing though holy [\h__\h] um
where's the healers
stop it push
oh my god oh my god oh my god
that had to happen that was bound to
happen but holy [\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h]
whoo
anyway those those tongue twisters i
mean i've heard them before but i'm
really bad at japanese tongue twisters
i'm i think i'm bad at any time to stoke
but it was fun i really like this group
but i think that was for now the last
the last one oh my god
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
uh
yeah yeah yeah that was the last one we
recorded i i did something recently with
eofy senpai again that you will sooner
or later
uh see as well
um
maybe
oh but yeah this for some reason we did
a lot with this combination of people
i don't know why
i know why it's always me and eofy who
get called over
bye spy spice puss
this gives me cover right oh god oh god
oh wait there's a shield there she let
me let me
who's laughing
who's laughing no more for him yeah
those were recorded those two videos as
i recall correct and they were recorded
at like 4am
oh they defended didn't they
what's happening
what's happening right now
push fail no
if i try though i tried
because you're so perfect and say so
thank you that's are you trying to score
some points with me
you know but i think maybe maybe they um
maybe maybe they think that i have like
a fitting um
sense of humor for these japanese videos
because i think i do like
15 seconds i do think my like tempo
and my humor my sense of humor is like
very fitting to japanese humor style and
maybe maybe the management is like ah
okay wawa will do well
so let's call kiwawa i don't know if
they think it through that much but also
i'm
yeah probably the best at japanese and
myth so
maybe they were oh
maybe they were like yup let's get
skiwawa to do the job
oh my god
what the [\h__\h] is happening
aggressive
aggressive oh god
[Applause]
[Music]
let's get that objective
oh man yeah my japanese gets uh there's
a word called katakuto
i think
it's a combination probably never
thought about it i just used it without
thinking about it but i think it's a
combination of the word katai which is
stiff
and kotoba which is the words
um
and it's used to describe someone not
speaking very
smoothly or naturally so my japanese
gets very katakoto when i don't speak
japanese
for a while
when i get back into it i get back into
it
oh thank god
thank god
[Music]
it was fun though it was fun
i feel like i was doing pretty well
[Music]
i'm out again okay right okay we tried
so hot we did wait let me
oh
look at my damage
it's okay it's okay don't worry about it
wait i have the most damage out of
everyone
even the enemy team
oh my god
it's okay
holy [\h__\h] and i was even doing small
talk on the side
oh my god
i i was the carrie
17 kills nine straight okay the 16
streak is impressive
but wow
objective time also pretty high
and we we lost but i did the most damage
good healing though good healing
oh wait you had a 16 streak and you
still you were the healer oh [\h__\h] how
the [\h__\h] did you do that
how did you do that
what how the [\h__\h] did i do that
they weren't dying much
true i have seven wait i have i have 17
deaths
wow did i die that often didn't feel
like i died that often but i always got
back quickly and did a lot of damage in
my time that i was there thank you guys
for the gifts what am i getting here
how do i
know what i'm getting friend request
is it the gold no
is it am i getting the goal where do i
look at the gifts
where do i when do i look at my gifts
check this door
hmm
ah
store
oh god and when you're new to the game
it's like what the [\h__\h] am i looking at
chess thing maybe this one open gifts ah
oh
thank you
what is that
this thing that'll work
oh a pose
[Music]
another blows oh
that's like a winning pose yeah
hot potato was the other one yeah
yeah
small gift
what's this
i love these new gadgets a timer there's
a time with specific posts
am i not already using that i guess i'll
equip it
thank you
oh no i know i wanted to open the small
one first oh well here's a big one
oh this matches those shoes oh my god
did you just what did you oh my god are
you also talking like a valley girl even
though this is not even the valley
girl's skin
this matches my shoes she's dad oh my
god she's hot
oh yeah
crow crow cassie oh another gift
all right is it because i'm level 10 now
i can uh
i can
get gifts now yeah
small gift
hey thank you guys christmas
oh
coopers yeah perching pose
crowds are cool but also very scary
oh my god i'm getting so many keys
[Music]
oh
oh wait can you only um
apply the poses to the specific
character or can you
use the same pose for a different
character
lounge gift
with level 554 what the [\h__\h] shiny shiny
oh yourself looks like i'm star wars
only for that character oh
thank you for skin
skins
do be looking nice this one's on me
thank you
another gift surely this is the gift
from the mother
wait that's the that's the statue of
liberty
oh i've only i've seen the statue of
liberty before but in japan
in odaiba there's a statue of liberty a
small version one day i must see the
real one
never seen the real one cool thank you
oh another one
thank you
who has time for spraying [\h__\h] on walls
while we're in a battle wanna play
oh i wanna play um where do you wanna
play
hot girl
not although it's a sky skin
thank you
a large one this one told me thank you
what do we have another skin
whoa
well that must be a tank holy [\h__\h] that
hammer
holy [\h__\h] you can make some nice
schnitzel with that hammer
some nice flat massaged soft smooth
schnitzel
let's [\h__\h] go give me that schnitzel
hammer i actually don't own one at the
moment
turn me into a schnitzel with that
please
awesome oh my god oh my god
it's never gonna end is it
for me oh god
oh it looks dangerous oh cute
oh
i need to try willow sometime then
it's a gift opening stream now
why don't
ah his frosting tube looks like he has
more control over it than i had
mine was like all over the place
[Music]
i can do that too of course i can
it's nothing
that's nothing
at least it isn't hot excuse me
we don't need cards oh
hold on to this one oh he looks cool
what is this here
healer i wonder what he is looks more
like a supportive role torvald
wow wow wow there ain't stopping he's a
tank oh
another one
another different look for him
he looks nice
nice gift
[Laughter]
of mine
what
dear lord that's me after going skiing
those abs those those coughs that can
cut
a tomato
oh
what is this
damn
long board
oh my oh my
not quite my type um but still um
i respect those abs
roboforce yeah cool robo
okay i think we're done i think we got
all the older
gifts what is this we have a community
chest
can i open it
i got another gift thank you
yeah
oh thank you very much
i haven't got another gift
level 166 damn
is this oh this provides
oh you
you
just
oh no you didn't
oh no i have to play her now what is she
is she a
tank or healer or or fps damage uh
i meant a dd damage dealer she's a
healer
is she difficult as a healer
damn she looks fine she looks fine i
love i love it
no one can focus if she's in the team
like this
no one will be able to focus
sexy class yeah she's she's healing
people just by
looking at her
oh my god
she's eating highest heels does she do
aoe heel or like one person heal
why not how the [\h__\h] are you over level
500.
i like it
well then let's equip this because it's
for that same character oh my god
oh my god
mono target heal multi-target huh which
one seems like more like it's one thank
you
new maine i don't know i don't know i
don't know i want to play an mmorpg and
be a healer
oh
ash
yo
this is this this is
some proper armor
but her butt is not protected this is
kisada style proper armor everywhere
except for the butt
i mean
going to the toilet would probably uh be
a pain in the ass
if you are covered there as well
cool poster
dad vibes with the pose yes
she looks cool
cute what the [\h__\h] are you oh my god
what is this character you're so cute i
love the character design
yeah
he looks like he could be like
a character out of a different video
game yo
cute i have so many gifs
bomb king
can you what if what if you give someone
the same thing that someone already has
or does does the game tell you that
cool wolf though what the [\h__\h] let's
equip it oh my god yes give me mounts
yes
or will the game tell the person who's
trying to gift it that they already have
it
yes we have a new mouth no boring horse
anymore and it's it reminds me of okami
[\h__\h] yeah nice thank you gift give to a
random
oh so the game will know and we'll only
give you stuff that you don't have
though i wonder
oh oh it gives you credits
hold
[Music]
oh
damn
wait so it's random so that person
didn't know that they were giving me the
bunny suit skin
i see
that was uh oh kfb you have kfb
oh man
this one's
kind of cooler because of the fire i
will try to use um both of them but now
i have to use this one like holy [\h__\h]
look at that that's sick
[\h__\h] chunkers man
it looks like chocolate it's on fire
sick
cocoy wow i'm getting i'm getting uh
i'm getting so blessed here
oh my god
surely
yo isn't she the same one that got the
the statue of liberty skin she gets some
[\h__\h] weird cool skins
what is this
they do have some fun designing her
skins huh
what do we have
a five slapper i love it love it
very funny
yo stop giving me gifts i want to play
another round i think
he looks strong
i think if he would give me a hug he
would squeeze me to death i would
literally suffocate in his arms but i
would be happy while suffocating
never seen anything like that how cute
watch gift
oh my god it's not stopping it's [\h__\h]
christmas oh kills it
wow you're so
cute
it has stitches so it's supposed to be
like a pushy
oh
you look wait
maybe it's a human a creepy human in a
suit just trying to look cute i mean
that's obviously
a suit so
is it is it a plushie that has come to
life or is it a human inside of a
bodysuit that's just trying to creep up
on me
it's so cute though love those eyes they
look lifeless but they are cute
god
wait that's so cute
oh my god
what do we have now
oh
is that the same character that we were
just looking at
but a different skin
would you look at that real cassie skin
oh
interesting
june crawler cool
thank you ah
no
thank you no no no team no no no i i go
random
cute thank you okay last one last one
last one last one
what grass is in session
you scare me
[Laughter]
thank you guys you guys are so sweet
thank you
thank you should we play another round i
don't know how how long to play maybe
maybe
two more rounds
i guess we could try out that healer
what was she again
question which one was it again
who was it again
it's tutorial skye
no serious sarah says the one of the oh
it's the one of the blindfolds
oh you look very different with that
well let me look at your other outfits
serious
oh
this one is best paris
cool serious
oh i i love this one
she looks like a different person every
time whoa
this one looks nice too
oh cute
serious i don't know you have to you
have something um on your head does that
hurt is that some kind of new beauty
therapy or something
she's a cute belly
oh that one's cool too and obsidian no
no yeah i actually think this is the
best one we were so lucky to get it yo
okay
i will try i will try um one round with
her and then one more with tyra because
she's the only one i'm good at
are you guys ready to queue with me
are you ready
sorry sorry sorry it's the one with the
blindfold the one with the blindfold and
one with a blindfold
i also have a cute belly i know thank
you
hi
i'm the healer
no other heroes actually it would be
good to have another healer
look at me looking hot
oh i'm so sexy
[Music]
i'm sorry guys you probably we will lose
probably because everyone will be um
devastated but looking at my looks
everyone will be distracted
whistle
check mount well i equipped it i should
have my
my fire lion mount my chunker's mount
wait we have we do have that vacane
person again okay so they're backing me
up but we also have everything else
covered i think
so
looks pretty safe
all right
i hope i do well with this one cause i
want to
i want to make this work
so that i can use her again press h to
jump on your mount early to show it oh
okay so glad we're going to tonight
uh-huh
i don't know what that means
i don't know what any of that means oh
is this shooting bubbles bubbles bubbles
bubbles and then healing
healing
uh
don't know what f and q does uh wait
wait where was the button for the mount
again
what was that
what was the mouse button again hold it
down
uh-huh okay is that a stronger one h
doesn't work i guess am i on the mount
already
h h i'm pushing h
am i on the mount
five where are the where's everybody
i've been melting all that snow
there won't be any snow left after i'm
down here and look at my butt
mmm okay oh my god don't die don't die
what the [\h__\h] don't die don't die
oh my god don't die don't no why would
you die why would you die
[\h__\h]
cool mouth yeah
what what does my q and my e do
um i tried pushing q but i'm not sure if
it did anything
a second chance let's go
oh [\h__\h] oh no
[\h__\h] i'm all alone all around me
no
[\h__\h] we're losing
bad bad
objective loss let's go i didn't know we
were doing objectives
you causes your primary fire to detonate
extra damage to people you already hit
okay that's an easier
easier way to describe it thank you you
need to speak in baby words with me
when i play this game i literally can't
nothing that i read enters my brain
i'm healing
uh
yeah it's not going so well
did emma really just say that god she's
so toxic i love it
makes me love her even more
[\h__\h] you
i love her i love when she's toxic send
me all the ammo's toxic uh uh clips
please
defense fan let's go
but at least i'm looking hot hmm
sorry guys i tried
hi bacali how are you such a good uh
healer how do you do it how do you do it
how does she do it guys feel better feel
better
press f
[\h__\h] why did you tell me to do that now
[\h__\h] oh
yeah
how was my 15 seconds wait it makes me
go invisible is that my ulti no it's not
my ulti
e is my opti
five
four
okay makes me invisible
one passive heels you're invisible with
that recharges okay elbow
my ultimate is a black hole i want to
use that
[Music]
i was playing i was kind of feeling more
i think
i feel like i did more
useful stuff oh god
[Music]
i feel good was more useful what the
other healer when was i playing i want
you for gore
damn
serious is difficult gotta practice huh
no one
no one uh
goes on a rampage on their first try
today
oh wait i can spam it
[Music]
yeah didn't you guys say it was easy
and she heals the most apparently
sometimes the other team is just too
overpowered
that that must be it
i feel like they'll they might fail uh
defending
ultimate is ready ultimate is ready
really oh my god i want to use it
stay alive stay alive
[Music]
what did that do
is
i think i'm gonna take a bubble bath
after this stream
invisible can i still shoot oh wait once
i shoot i'm out of the invisibility
you skew after i shoot someone
[Music]
okay that's okay sometimes you have to
accept the reality
even if it looks grim
it is how it is oh i'm sorry can i say
sorry i am sorry
sorry
sorry i was not good at that
um
wait i hear about the same as cheetah
but she focused more on damage this time
i suppose
don't oppose this to me i was [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
i was [\h__\h]
i didn't have one kill though
hey
okay neo repo goes on the on the
blacklist it goes into my burn book
what the [\h__\h]
kfb reigns supreme is what i learned
thanks to cc and the subtitles in the
head whole live official
channel video otherwise i would not
have known
what that means
i learned english thanks to cc
thanks to the subtitles let's go
they translated kfb cycle as kfb reigns
supreme
okay one more time
i
i'll go with my strong tyra
one last one and then read super chats
and i'll tell you about uh how the
doctor visit went because i'm sure you
guys are curious
um
let's [\h__\h] go we need frontline we
need support guys fill it up fill it up
come on
come on where's our healer
healer please healer
you gotta be the healer
i don't wanna lose this last match
please be a healer why doesn't he do why
doesn't he choose anything
he's probably like
why do i have to be the healer i don't
want to be the healer come on please
no you have
to sup
sup everybody
afk did they kick him out if he doesn't
choose anything until the end
yes
what the [\h__\h] is that what the [\h__\h] let
me out let me out
he didn't show us anything
he went for the healer okay maybe he
just forgot to lock it in
let's try this one
launching
let's go
i'll show off my other mount
look at that butt
on the bottom right
i'm ready let's go
split stone quarter we have to push
again
with my newly acquired abs i think we're
gonna have an easy win
please go easy on me opponent team
another sinister organization for you
yes
okay
hello nice to meet you i'm takana
zucchiara from whole life english nice
to meet you and i'm a phoenix and
potential uh yeah i'm on youtube please
watch me please subscribe thank you
everybody for being here today i will do
my best and i've been getting better so
i hope i can be a worthy team mate uh
while i'm also a teammate but you don't
know what that means probably yeah
listen to that beautiful emma voice and
always listen to it and you'll
understand and you will also become a
teammate
become a teammate but also become a kfp
probably i should probably um
prioritize that yes become kfp and then
a teammate additionally it's a good
combination you get like an extra
cheeseburger if you if you support both
of us
look at my fluffy boy
where am i going
we're in when can't be
i see you cassie
molotov cocktail
i see you i see you
oh i see you [\h__\h] come here don't be
scared
i'm getting healed what's up
we're all being very uh careful here
apparently
i want to kill her i want to kill her
cassie [\h__\h]
oh we're we're waiting though
let's let's defend
we must let's call the front line assert
dominance
why is she where are they we're just
chilling here
they're coming back they're coming back
soon
come on
show me your face
don't be such a coward
are you surprised really you're fighting
against the phoenix of course it's hot
hot wings is my second name
excuse me excuse me
i will remember yo you're the one with
the name i can't read with the fancy ubu
name
i'm on my way guys
i will carry you to the wind
takanasi hot wings kiwawa
that is right that's me
yeah we're pushing now
let's go
push and push and be careful they might
come from behind again
that lady from before
oh nice nice uh trying on the front line
oh easy this is too easy
[Music]
oh no you did it
i was just playing dead got them every
time
no i was really dead this time
revealed
yeah
can you not
we're still good
okay
i need to kill her i need revenge
yeah i saw the bump but i didn't know
how far i need to move back i thought
that was good enough man
i need to push i need to push i need to
push i need to push push push push push
that egg out
let it out it will feel so
nice
[Music]
oh come on
we need to push harder
to the better end that's right oh no
give me over jump push it push the board
where the [\h__\h] is it
[Music]
wait for me
i'm here i'm here now
[Music]
did we do it [\h__\h] this [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] we do it
come on come on come on
it was just come on
so close
ah
wow nice wall
okay well we're gonna never try at it
this time we'll do it
i lit my whole team on fire oh because
they can also take the damage from my
molotov cocktail oh i didn't think about
that i just wanted to do as much damage
as possible
what are you doing
i was posing
no i can't
i need to start a fire today i need to
stay true to myself you know
oh god
get that heal
okay okay okay okay okay
a wall is actually in the way
[Music]
oh that [\h__\h] step it she's going down
she's cleaned [\h__\h] down
i will get her i will get her
i'm gonna find her and i'm gonna kill
her i'm going to kill her
i wonder if she's watching the stream
if yes then don't take me too seriously
i'm sorry
but but the justice has to be done
what was that
where is she
is she
show yourself
[Music]
this is my arch enemy
i hate her i hate is she the one laying
the bombs oh my god she triggers me so
hard
shut
damn it
oh god what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
[Applause]
see who i'm shooting
nice i'm only eliminating though where
are my kills
stop stealing my skills we pushed
successfully
that [\h__\h] though i still can't get her
down
for god's sake
okay
one more it goes off
yeah the sky girl
[\h__\h] sky man
[Laughter]
i will not be satisfied until i i take
her down personally
ah
i need to mark her mark my territory
i know i know the wall is there so that
i i'm protected but
five
four
i want to shoot through it
[Laughter]
i guess it's kind of for like dire
situations where there's like a lot of
enemies you just can't let them get
close to you
under any circumstances
oh
i want a kill
i didn't see
[\h__\h]
totally by accident didn't type that on
purpose
okay i could have done more damage um
was not my best one
uh holy [\h__\h] that healer
uh
that was
holy [\h__\h] that damage this this
character
is overpowered and needs to be nerfed
that sky character needs to be nerfed
omg
17 kills 80k damage
nerf her
paladins what are you doing
needs to be nerfed
pip with zero healing
pip
who is who is the healer
in their group i don't know
well that was fun
i'm enjoying paladins i don't know if
palace is watching again this time but
thank you this game is very enjoyable
not sponsored but i am enjoying it it
was a good short stream i will read
super chats now and so let's go to my
office
and
the furry is the healer ah i see well
good job healing then
what were they doing they were in the
preach ah i saw you guys reacting but i
didn't see the message
ah
i see i say i see it
oh it's a definitely a short stream for
kiwawa uh standards thanks for your
stream thank you for watching
thank you
they had three flags oh
i see
your it
is in your face
it's on purpose it looks cute doesn't it
it's on purpose man
am i was that toxic
maybe a little bit
ah the new whole live music studio the
one with the uh
like the really cool um well what's it
called or girl and uh like i don't know
uh yeah it's very very chill very quiet
[Music]
not nothing wrong with that you did i
did i did not get toxic
just a little
i it's not like i'm you know when i
would play this so probably i would i
would not be this what's happening i got
a gift i think
or i think so i would not be just
aggressive hi smoofy
help me out i wouldn't be this
aggressive if i
if i uh
meow
if i was playing privately of course i'm
only exaggerating because i'm streaming
high school me
how's it going
this movie is actually um
kind of worrying me right now because i
i got home today from the doctor and
smoothie greeted me on the door as
always and i was shocked like she threw
herself
on the ground
and you know how she does it like she
goes on the on the on her back and then
she stretches and rolls around to say
hello on the floor she wants a belly rub
to say hello and what i noticed is that
on her chin
suddenly there's a big chunk of hair
missing
i don't know what happened
i i don't think that was uh missing
yesterday i think it like happened while
i was gone she like must have really
aggressively scratched herself on the
chin
um
i don't know if i should be worried i'm
gonna observe
i'm gonna observe i hope she doesn't
i didn't see her scratching at all
though could have also been maybe uh no
no fleece she doesn't have fleas man
could have also been fighting with with
jonkers but
um
no it's it's just like
like completely missing on on that one
spot on her chin
it's like maybe the size of of
of uh
my pinky's nail
about that
about that size yeah but
i don't want to take her
to the vet immediately i will observe i
have a cream that helps with itchiness
for cats but
uh and and and helps with some other
things i think oh but she doesn't seem
she hasn't been scratching it at all
i've been observing and she hasn't been
scratching the whole day after i got
home
so maybe it was a one-time thing
but i'm always concerned with her
recently so
ah
yeah i'll see i'll see
if she's missing more hair tomorrow then
i'll decide um
let's go to my office yeah
also where are my korean bros as well
i'm young korean bros local
where are my korean bros are you bank
and my japanese bros i'm so hungry
korean bros are here too
[Laughter]
they were hiding or they were maybe
using an english language in the chat
huh
oh
they're camouflaging
[Music]
yeah it's pretty late over there so it's
actually impressive that they are here
let's go to office soon
hello where am i
[Music]
did you guys see me
immediately
ah
that's where i left last time
what
what the [\h__\h] i put the chat url into
the chat in obs
and i heard myself and it doesn't show
what
it's alright
no you know what i did input the wrong
url
i input my stream url oh well here it is
here's the chat
so that's all that
smoothie she's just chilling on the
floor am i not too noisy for you are you
good
meow
yeah meow
want some you want some pets
[Music]
yeah you want those pets
she's so needy
she's so needy man um i'm feeling very
hungry um i still need to cook after
this and i don't want to stay up too
late it's like 10 p.m so we're probably
gonna do a speed read
um but just so to update you
know
and i went to the i went to the doctor
that checks
uh throat and nose and ears
as i like to say uh has nothing
organized
because i can't pronounce it correctly
because i had issues with my throat for
a while like a month
i think it started like a month ago that
i would um
have pain in my voice very early in the
stream usually i would only get a little
bit of pain after like like i don't know
eight nine hours but
uh yeah recently it just happened
immediately um
and uh yeah so i uh
i told him that i do this as a job
and
like i i i'm a voice i said i'm a voice
actor when i do it full time like three
to eight hours per day
uh
and
i have a lot of pressure on my throat on
my voice i suppose and
um that recently
uh it hurts way more than it used to
but i do use a humidifier a lot and i
drink a lot of tea and with honey and uh
and i uh have fruit candies always with
me i use them like in every stream like
i said all of that and um
it was a it was a doctor that um
we have like we have private doctors and
we have like general doctors that most
people use because they're free if you
have a health insurance so this one was
one that is free
um
because i got it recommended for my
friend so those doctors usually they're
a little bit like
they don't want to use up too much time
but he he was kind of like
fast fast fast fast but still he it i
felt like he still listened to me at
least and took me somewhat seriously i
think so that was okay
no guy
yeah so i told him and then he checked
my uh he checked my ears and my nose and
my throat he checked all of it i guess
it's all connected uh he said that um
uh he said they're not like inflamed or
anything like not in tunde it
he said
he made me like
make a noise when i was when he was like
opening my mouth
and and i guess that resulted in him
saying that my my vocal cords
don't close properly when
i speak
i guess
um
so that
probably
i'm not sure he didn't quite say what he
thinks is exactly the reason because the
other thing was he said that uh
i'm not very clear if just my nose and
my ears are dry or my fruit as well but
he did say in any case that i am very
dry
which i'm surprised because i spent uh
the last couple days in the sauna and i
always have the humidifier on when i
stream
and i tried to
um drink a lot of
fluids as well but
yeah he did say very dry so i guess it's
a maybe a combination of
i mean
the dryness and and the way i um i use
my voice the vocals vocal cords not
closing properly but
i mean
that
i feel like if if that was the issue um
i mean it's definitely something that
needs to be fixed but if that was the
the reason why i have so much pain right
now then why didn't it start earlier you
know what i mean i think it's like a
combination of both things so so he did
um
uh me uh
no
uh uh
uh
he wants me to go to a different doctor
who is a specialist it's called logo
pedi
uh logo pd i don't know what's it in
english but it's uh someone who
specializes in the use of
uh your voice uh like how you speak yes
over pharaoh
and
and he wrote down diagnosis is a
functional
what's it again in english i looked it
up functional
functional
dysphonia
where pretty common
and
makes sense and
this one i can't translate i looked it
up but i didn't know how to translate it
internally
don't know what that is
[Music]
in um australia i don't even know in
german what exactly that was supposed to
be
uh but yeah
so yeah i'll be uh
uh going to this professional specialist
to
train the way i use my vocal cords i
guess
i gotta go there like 10 times one hour
sessions
so 10 hours
and then if i need more i can still take
more but this one i think it's a good
one because this is a private one the
one that i got referred to
is a private doctor
so
yeah my health insurance probably won't
cover it only a tiny part but
that basically private doctors are
better so i kind of prefer it anyway
and he did
he swears on this um
on this tee
uh so he wrote down some stuff for me to
get at the pharmacy and i already got it
i didn't use it though
uh
ibish
t
english
huh
what's ibish t in english
uh
what what is that i don't i can't find a
translation
ibish
marshmallow no
it's not marshmallow
high biscus that's hibiscus no that's
not hibiscus is it
is hemp leaf hollyhock
huh
oh baby
no
oh
he's curled up like a snail on the
ground wait a sense here and a latin
name as well alpha
a
ah that's it marshmallow plant no it's
literally called marshmallow plant
the [\h__\h] there's a marshmallow plant
that that's where marshmallows come from
wait but they don't croak
wait what that's i thought marshmallows
are just i don't know made out of sugar
or something
oh they used to be made out of that
but what the [\h__\h]
marshmallows
no come on
i am fascinated and but he wants
he swears on this team so if anyone here
has uh problems with their throat then
my doctor extremely recommends it he
says everything else is [\h__\h] he also
said pineapple juice he doesn't believe
in it um
he doesn't trust it i told him that i
had
that i i was recommended pineapple juice
by a um a colleague but he says it
doesn't work
he says the only thing that you can
drink that works is this tea
this very specific tea uh and he he gave
me like a recipe on how
very specifically on how to make it like
don't just make it
but
start making it on the previous day
by soaking the tea leaves in cold water
and then on the next day
fill it up with hot one liter of hot
water i suppose and then
put it in the in the furnace and then
drink it like 10 times a day like uh you
know get a big bottle and then spread it
out for the day
is he sponsored by his team i don't know
man he he really says that this tea is
the only thing that helps
i mean when it comes to drinkable
things as i will try it out i guess i
guess i'll prepare it today and then
drink it tomorrow i hope it tastes good
does it taste like no [\h__\h] way that
it will taste like marshmallows
no way and then another
um
special special cough drops that
actually um my bff recommended me too
um she tried them and she says that
they're amazing uh
yeah they are called if you're curious
they're called i don't know if they have
them anywhere outside of here but jello
revoice of g
gello calorie voice
[Music]
they are apparently really good
so i will use i bought i bought a [\h__\h]
ton of them
uh
they're amazing apparently oh so on
[Music]
uh
yeah those those cough drops apparently
make the throat and everything very
slimy
but the good news is that generally it
doesn't sound like anything is too too
damaged or
yeah
i i i said that i was like really very
dead i completely damaged my vocal cords
and he said no no no they're just uh
just not closing properly and i guess
they're dry but yeah it's not too
serious thankfully so good news yeah
yeah
i know
um
i don't know
i just wonder if i do that therapy
uh and she's gonna the doctor's gonna
teach me how to
close my vocal chords properly i wonder
if i can really like
like that sounds like something i
wouldn't need to really focus on while i
speak
uh like if i can do that properly during
the stream uh i will try of course but
it sounds difficult
sounds difficult
and yeah maybe my
maybe
i will let them know that i don't really
want to you know change
this voice too much but
it might change a little bit i don't
know
takes practice yeah my my friend
my bff she also said that she took uh
she went to doctor like that before for
voice therapy as well like many many
years ago and she said that it helped
her a lot that originally she spoke like
she spoke like very softly and highly
like this but uh it got fixed thanks to
that so
it's it really seems to help
your health over the voice yes yes yes
yes but you guys can shut up now because
the doctor says my vocal cords are fine
okay
i did not damage them eternally for life
uh we good guys and we're gonna test out
the tea and uh and the other things that
will cough drops
and yeah and i'll make an appointment
with that doctor
hope the tea is good let me let me smell
can i open it here
oh wow that's a lot oh
oh
interesting it does not smell disgusting
it does also not smell very good though
i see okay
uh yeah i think tomorrow will be a
somewhat long pokemon stream so we can
see if it helps tomorrow
if it's better than my other teas
he said that i don't even need to put in
honey i told him i put honey everywhere
but he said the honey doesn't like
necessarily do that much apparently
yeah
does it smell like marshmallows
no
it smells very much just like
like herbs
like dry leaves
it really just smells like dry leaves
like random dry leaves it doesn't have
any like
strong smell to it that really stands
out to me
um
pokemons tomorrow yeah i think so
[Music]
you guys are
you guys are like
desperate without a weekly schedule
aren't ya
what is going on chihuahua
when can i expect your stream
uh probably
um
probably
uh
[Music]
2 p.m
my time 2 pm gmt plus one
i've been managing to wake up early
these days uh
naturally
so i think i think should be fun i'm
gonna make the reservation after the
stream
gonna start early
uh at 2 pm
[Music]
um
yes
okay let's read the wait i need some btm
though
let's read the the super chats
um
what do i want to listen to
what was this again
wait i need to stop paladins
oh
okay
cute
maybe more
energetic ah these are my pokemon tracks
um
what is this what is this
[Music]
you know what i'm going to play this it
reminds me of ammo
will you play simon the sorcerer
wait i know that game
simon the sorcerer
point and click adventure game from 1993
[Music]
it looks familiar
that looks familiar
odd choice indeed
wait the music or does the game feel
like the game is an odd choice
[Music]
um no i will probably not play this on
stream and pro it's probably um
abandonware anyway and abandonware is
kinda tough to get permission for
because there's no one to answer our
request
[Music]
it's available on steam
oh well i i did um think about playing
some nostalgic games and i i requested
permissions to play them
um
already a while ago
not really hearing anything back on them
but
not giving up yet but there are some
nostalgic games that i do want to play
for you guys that are nostalgic to me
my starship titanic is one of them but
that's probably never gonna happen
i think i requested that
while let me see again
i think starship titanic is also
abandoned where
uh
but yeah i'll see what what i can do
to rock
oh my that reminds me i wanted to figure
out what that game was that was thinking
about because you guys are really good
at
um figuring out what game i'm thinking
about even though i only give a very
very very vague description so i'm
thinking about a game that
um
it's not first person you kind of look
at it from above
i don't know what i guess it's a bird's
perspective it has like uh it's only i
played it on gamecube i think um it's
like a rpg style but not no no not not
really no there's no levels or anything
but you kind of i think you hire like
um you hire warriors uh
and then i don't remember much of it
um but yeah you hire warriors i think
and then you go into like a battle
and you move like um
from field to field
um
gauntlet it's really old by the way
gauntlet doesn't sound familiar
no what
i always see fan as gauntlet
[Music]
jack alliance
no
maybe
[Music]
no lost kingdoms is different the one
with the card i know i know i love that
game but that's not what i was talking
about lost kingdoms is not it
heroes of mine imagine
um bowlers baldur's gate
no
no maybe
maybe it is that
no it didn't look like that it looked
more
shitty
[Applause]
didn't look that good yo i'm talking
about a gamecube game
more details
dark alliance dark alliance
[Music]
i remember for example there was this
like
arena
and where i would go into a battle
um
[Music]
[Applause]
of course it's not quake
half of radiant
i feel like i would recognize it just by
the name
it kind of looked like that but it was
not a fire emblem game
it it looked like that
similar
a little bit similar
it's not fire emblem though
i would have known if i've played fire
emblem when i was younger
it does kind of look like that what the
[\h__\h]
no it was not fire emblem it was not an
animal game it was more like realistic
style but fantasy
uh but like in in that kind of in that
kind of world like not future but
[\h__\h]
is that one so difficult to it's
turn-based yes
gladius wait that must be it
wait game gamecube
that's it that's it that's it
i think that's it wait i think i think
that's it
yeah
that game was kind of cool
i remember really liking it
when i was younger
oh my god it's so old
you know what do you know it
[Music]
oh that's so nostalgic looking at that
screen with that bar at the bottom
yeah
yeah oh man
good job who said gladius
you said that
kyle collins said it
and dancing
you guys
oh and fallen penguin said it too
and kyle waving good job guys good job
good job
[Music]
never heard of that one you're not
looking at it now it doesn't look that
special but
it was kind of fun
i don't know
i don't remember anything about it
besides these few little
details
but yeah
yeah
i need to look back into it
probably not gonna play it on the stream
though cause don't think i would get
permission but
maybe you guys can look into it
looks dope
it was interesting it was a
what genre is that anyway
tactical role playing oh this is an rp
video game developed by and published by
lucasarts it was released in 2003 for
the gamecube and playstation 2 and xbox
[Music]
yeah so you hired gladiators i suppose
um
[Music]
lucas arts
terminator
you mean they're gone they closed their
offices
[Music]
did mama told me about this game no i
don't think so
i don't know like
how we got the game but
i think my my brother may have
chosen it i don't know
they're disney now what
[Music]
i say
no i should be reading super chat though
but thank you for uh reminding me of the
game that
i feel so
relieving now knowing what what i was
thinking about
i keep on
keep on forgetting these old games that
were really fun when i was younger on
the gamecube [\h__\h] love gamecube games
yeah one less thing on my mind
but it's good to know that there is a
few people who know the game
it's not very well known i suppose we're
very old and yeah
i do still want to get a gamecube yeah
and a win
oh yeah by the way i did watch the
nintendo direct last night but i will
keep that topic for tomorrow for the
pokemon stream so that we have something
to talk about because i do have some
thoughts i do have some thoughts to be
honest
um
[Music]
i stopped reading super chat somewhere
around the end of the last stream do you
guys remember which i i think i know d
more hollis was the last one i read i
think yes yes yes yes
yes found it already can i give can i
give smoovie a hug before we before we
start
i need to keep moving she offers her
body to me so kindly down there
hi baby
[Music]
oh
ah i think she why do you want to chill
on the floor just chill on the chair
next to me and i can pet you easily
[Music]
oh she's so cute
how is she so cute
oh she's she's licking her paw
she's so cute everything she does is so
cute
oh she's so cute
damn it i can't take it
she i i'm so happy that she like wants
to be close to me
even when i'm streaming she must really
like me
[Music]
oh my god okay i'll i'll have to cuddle
her afterwards some more
okay um uh
okay i think this was where we start so
maxwell the first thank you soon
[Music]
my cat is sitting in front of the
monitor they do they do do that
sometimes don't they i love it though
okay
i love anything they do i can never be
mad
[Music]
thank you thank you soon pudding channel
duncan baldi and thank you for the
rainbow
i'm so sorry i'm reading it now you
probably won't hear it for a while my
answer let's see there's a rainbow by
our tanker who's stationed in in france
in the military
wait you are here what the [\h__\h] why are
you here
shouldn't you be tanking just kidding
it's pretty late are you like are you
liking bunk beds right now
are you in the bunk bed
or are you home now
how does that work where are you on the
weekend
taka nasikiwawa wants to know your
location
bunk bed
usually is but i'm home for a week
that's so cool okay well then perfect
okay so i was supposed to get more time
off once i integrated
my squadron but i've been lied to what
the [\h__\h] [\h__\h] bamboozle
they should be frightened because you're
in a tank they should be respectful
and give you anything you want
[Music]
commando course weapon certifications
military driving permits and the endless
cleaning of every nook and crannies of
our gear and regiment got me busy from
sun up till sundown
should you really be telling me all
those military secrets huh
i'll be leaving for the next two weeks
uh to what we call the school of fire
where we'll get to fire all sorts of
machine guns while sleeping outside and
eating rations
ooh sleeping outside you
life here is just as tough as it is fun
really is it fun
i still try to catch the archives
whenever i can though love your needy
streamer overload stream what an awesome
game thank you
so many good moments where i love my ass
off can't wait to see you in 3d finally
at the whole festival i won't be able to
watch it live but i'll catch up to it
later for sure yeah yeah of course you
have to
it's great to finally catch a stream
live for once and hear about your
adventures with mr yodel sounded like an
amazing dude i'd love to meet anyway
much love from friends grass besock
thank you thank you thank you thank you
i'm glad you found some time i hope that
i hope that you don't
you know regret it i think i hope like i
i just can't imagine you know being
so
[Music]
being in an environment like that when
you have to
where you can't have any like private
time like almost no private time and you
can't go after your hobbies and stuff
like that just sounds terrible to me
but respect that you're doing it man
just
keep it up keep it up
cycle i would be miserable and
i would not be the right type of person
to do that
it's not for everyone
but i heard that i heard that at least
you make good money after that
i don't know how true that is
but
i heard people
who
uh have a job like that they make good
money
oh no at least that's something
hmm
no
eh
oh
[\h__\h]
if we go abroad oh damn
we don't wanna we don't want to do that
no no
yeah i heard something different from my
brother but i'm not sure what like where
the difference is in what he did
compared to what you're doing i mean
besides you know being in a tank
i only know that like
[Music]
my brother said he was making good money
for a while while he was like in that
spot but i don't know [\h__\h] about this
i don't know anything about it
yeah i guess it depends on the country
too maybe
maybe you should have joined the
austrian military
[Music]
you can't be sure that
not much will happen either because
austria is neutral
[Music]
[Laughter]
anyway so yeah i'm glad you're here
please enjoy the time that you're able
to spend here
and take care of yourself thank you for
supporting me and not forgetting me
i'm glad you still are interested in me
not great on the resume you don't have
to say why you went there
maybe you just have a
imaginary girlfriend you don't have to
say it's imaginary but it would be a
better reason if if you don't say it's
imaginary
then you have a girlfriend in in austria
and then you must protect her
you can't can't be against her
anyway
thank you so much for the rainbow wow we
wish you all the best
you have our support
yeah
our tank
i shall heal you and i shall i shall be
your damage dealer while you tank
all the enemies alright
just waltz over them
stay safe yeah be careful
and and uh
yeah do your best i guess
man i would cry if if like i if i had a
military
dribble guy be like
dude
i feel like i would be i would be a
[\h__\h] wreck after the first day
mr yoda was similar to that but um
he was still kind of funny and nice
about it so
[Music]
yeah backseat it is kind of backseating
at the max
yeah like boot camp i imagine it being
like boot camp
that's what i think of when i think of
the military boot camp
um
[Music]
so i don't think we can call
valley and a chicken anymore if he has
to toughen up for the military
he
he would be
hmm
[Music]
maybe maybe in in his his body would
still look like a chicken but he would
be much more than that
the buff chicken from the cups that
video
wow
a rooster
okay
[Music]
that doesn't necessarily sound that much
stronger but okay
[Music]
your majesty welcome home i missed you i
was shivering in the cold because of
youtube mcn while hatching
but thanks to the warmth he left behind
i could hatch safely so can i be
assigned to the department in charge i
can fry well and do office work well
oh oh it happened at a bad time for you
huh
but now you're now you're a little chick
that's cute congratulations on hatching
thank you for the red super chat mwah
and you want a job position hmm
how about
um kfp
and
what's a good word i wanna i wanna give
him the position of licking the papers
when flipping the papers you know what i
mean like
um
moisturizing
the papers
when before i flip them
uh
maybe a
paper
moisturizer page liquor pinch
paper licker
chief moisturizer humidity engineer
that's
that's a very
honorable way to describe it
[Music]
no
that's confusing we won't know what it
is
[Music]
but okay you're out of humidity engineer
all right chick that's your job
you will be licking the paper since you
say you're good at office work i wanted
to give you an office job we need more
people in
behind the scenes you know
[Music]
please do your best at your job okay i
need those peppers to be moisturized
only at the corner though not the whole
thing okay don't lick the whole paper
that's disgusting
only link the corner the bottom corner
so that i can flip it
[Music]
oh i love locations you guys should go
to though
you should treat yourself
i feel i will feel bad if i go
if i'm the only one going on fancy
vacations
but it was something i was never able to
do before hold on live going on such
very fancy locations and
it's really nice to treat myself to
something thank you guys for making it
possible
[Music]
no
thank you
i will always bring content home when
i'm on the vacation though so yeah it's
not only about treating myself
but it's it's a a method of keeping me
longer in this job so
it's only only positive things about it
thank you taiji spoke what the [\h__\h]
i just said good morning two words
that's quite something
[Music]
big sweet
dpj duncan raven mcallister thank you
for the ransom
thank you very much for your generous
support no text of it but thank you
nonetheless
your support has been received
successfully
thank you so much
hope you're enjoying the streams
[Music]
okay
he didn't get into the ticket selection
thinking you know the random
raffle
he tried to come to the concert in
person but he didn't get a ticket
yeah the raffle he lost in the raffle
yeah [\h__\h]
[Music]
but he will watch it online
at least something my
[Music]
foreign
yeah i was just talking about how just
the the possibility of being able to
watch it online
i think we all should be very grateful
for it because when i used to go to
concerts for like real idols real life
not youtubers but like real life idols
and
it was not a thing back then
there were no
such live streams i mean you could often
get a dvd afterwards of one of the
concerts of the tour
but yeah if you're not if you can't get
a ticket then you're not watching the
concert so it's really cool that it's
not impossible to watch the concert you
can't just you just can't watch it in
person but yeah
it's still a blessing
[Music]
so everyone gets a chance in watching
the concert i think that's great that's
a really cool thing that i think the
culture of each of us and
the see thing
the sea thing brought in
it had to be done
yes yes
so
that's one thing to thank
cool
for right one thing
one good thing that they brought to us
is
us trying to improve
and find ways how to make everybody be
able to see a concert
[Music]
i see your profile picture there though
when i opened your
when i opened the url
of your profile to read the whole thing
because otherwise it cuts off there
it shows me who you are
[Music]
what a kid
by the way hi you want to sit on the
chair
let me introduce you to the chairs movie
you know the chair just sit there
i can i can pet you all the time if you
hear
[Music]
join us movie
oh
no she wants to go behind the monitor
now
okay
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
similar hiragana looks so confusing to
me let me write it up
[Music]
in
oh i'm getting better i'm getting better
i'm getting better
shut up
[Music]
top kid talk to
[Applause]
[Music]
you know what you know i think the key
to reading this correctly is not just
reading it but actually understanding
what you're saying
[Music]
you know let me put a space there
take it
[Music]
off
sounds like i'm making
chicken noises
[Music]
yeah i think i think it's fine
it makes me think of arrested
development right now when job does the
cook
the stupid dance that makes people
aggressive around him i think in mexico
was it
[Music]
you know what i'm talking about
wait let me find a link for you guys so
you understand what i'm saying
uh job arrested development chicken
dance
yeah that's it
[Music]
so stupid is this is this really a
dangerous dance to do
[Music]
oh man this show is just so good the
show is so good
okay continue continue
uh
i wanted to ask uh actually
i was thinking of asking for permission
to play with members only
mr kaspick's donkey chain runs thank you
and terraria
oh letters let's go let us go with the
letters
satisfied english and type
yeah my beloved ex-wife i appreciate the
love but it's time to let go of the
christmas intro [\h__\h] shut up no
no
jacob 47 out thank you in kobulikan 808
oh wait you were didn't i kill you
several times in the game oh my god you
were one of us
flag armor dankesh and sirek tankishan
happy distinction
same same
i want to apologize for any problem i
cause i'm sorry same
same
i feel very um
very apologetic when when playing a game
like this where i don't know what i'm
doing
but i was getting pretty good with tyra
at some at times
she's my main now
she's my girl mr cats makes thank you
not lu duncan
[Music]
thank you don't worry i'm [\h__\h] as well
emilio what's up thank you when there's
so many people who participated who are
super chatting thanks guys
i'm also a tyra main oh most of the
other people didn't know what they were
doing either i feel like there were a
lot of noobs um because a lot of stream
snipers started the game because of you
know ama and me i suppose
so
they yeah a lot of them were on the same
level approximately i guess but i think
a lot of the stream staffers at least
have fps um experience with other
fps games maybe
[Music]
thank you for the pinky hello pencil
this is my first time sending a
superchat to you it also happens to be
my birthday
uh i felt it was a good time to say
thank you thank you for being such a
wonderful and inspiring presence for
giving us such joy and laughter much
love
happy birthday
birthday birthday birthday
wait a second
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] i filled up my glass of water to
the very very very very maximum
oh my god oh my god oh my god can i
drink it without spilling yes
okay
[Music]
happy birthday to you
happy birthday
[Music]
much love back to you thank you for your
sweet support
yeah hope you're celebrating your
birthday nicely today
you need some cake that's that's all i
know you need some cake birthday people
need cake treat yourself to your
favorite cake tonight will you
you must you must
[Music]
you must you have to
and yeah stay healthy take care of
yourself
and uh yeah i hope this year will be a
great one for you
but hopefully you will spend it with me
as much as possible thank you
[Music]
cyrux and kill you kurtan kishan kill
yooka danke and kakundan
[Music]
any plans to queue in the game with us
champions would love to play a match
reveal
well you guys made it in a lot of the
time so i don't know how to
i don't know if it's possible to make
like a lobby where i can get you guys in
specifically
is there an option for that
you guys made it in nonetheless so
yeah i'm always happy to play together
with you guys
take her amd
hi baby
[Music]
welcome back
you can set up a custom
do i not need to be friends though
[Music]
sounds kind of annoying too um like add
everyone as friends in order to invite
them
[Music]
well you guys did fine
oh you can just set up a code
oh that's
if that's the case i might look into it
[Music]
okay okay
and take a 47
[Music]
outback and thank you for pushing that
because like that game is so fun
one more game that my mom used to love
to play and i really liked it too
um i forgot the name you guys will
probably figure it out anyway it's like
uh
it looks like it's made with um
um
what's it called
uh like stop motion and uh clean
um
and it's kind of a creepy game
uh i think it was a point and click
never yes how the [\h__\h] yes it's never
hood
did i mention this one before
that was so weird like back then i was
so young i did not understand what the
[\h__\h] was going on in this game
i named it before ah okay okay i would
love to like revisit it and see if i
if i understand it now like what what
even needs to be done because
i had no idea what i was doing back then
and it was it was kind of creeping me
out back then as well my mom was playing
it um all the time though
yeah never heard
callie played on stream what no [\h__\h]
way that kelly played it
hold on i streamed at once the [\h__\h]
that was probably before
before
getting permissions and stuff
she played ever heard not never
wait but cold on it did she really
caught on
uh never
good
oh
no i don't think she did
maybe if i type in japanese neva
[Music]
maybe it could private date
bgm stop it you don't hear it
i don't i can't find the stream
maybe you got deleted you can hear it
okay
no [\h__\h] way did she
you should really play it
oh wait she did but it's private now i
guess if i when i googled it i found a
fun thing i found a tween about it
no
and
it wow
where the japanese name is
kureman
kreman
ku kuraiman kurayman japanese title
that's why i didn't find it it's not
neighborhood it's just craymon clayman
clemen
i know she plays old games but that was
unexpected
so it's looking up the game
when was that
january 15 2020 that's two years ago
over two
[Music]
um
i think it's abandoned where as well
ask her for private link yeah if i can
play it then at least i could watch her
privately play
or i just i just play it myself
privately but i want to kind of
experience it together it would be fun
i feel like abandonware should just be
okay to play
like
it's abandoned like who's gonna who's
gonna complain right but yeah
have to
have to follow
the
the rules but
i i will ask again
[Music]
yeah right it's kind of a gray zone i
think
uh super snake mario thank you for the
pinky a poem for kiana kiki king
greetings to you best bird i want to
share so much with you i'm at a loss for
words
all i can say is that watching you
brings me joy really proud to call
myself a carefree employee again i love
what you do thank you
is that a poem
aren't poems supposed to rhyme most of
the time
there were not
they i didn't
only burden words maybe rhymed a little
bit
be nice
[Music]
it's uh it's cute though
it didn't rhyme much but it's cute
the message was conveyed and i feel i
feel flattered thank you
you thank you super snake mario
thank you for enjoying my content and
supporting me
thank you for being a carefree employee
[Laughter]
thank you sam very sweet of you
[Music]
what i'm being nice
will say as a former conscript what's a
conscript ah something military the
point of boot camp was to get
disciplined and broken down to be built
up so bloody scary when a ranked officer
walks into the room and starts yelling
at your bunk buddy oh my god
no i just can't
[Music]
i just can't like no
no
i i can't i can't like support that and
no no
like i can't even yell at my cats when
they break a glass
but thankfully they never do anyway
yeah but you guys are you guys are
mentally stronger than i am i guess at
least when it comes to that being yelled
at by scary men
yeah
respect
[Music]
i don't spoil them too much if i spoiled
them too much they would be
they would be spoiled
i mean they are sport but i mean like
they would like do [\h__\h] and
and think that they won't get in trouble
for it but they don't like they wouldn't
get in trouble
so they're correct with that but they
don't do [\h__\h] to begin with that they
could get in trouble
for
they are good babies
[Music]
time to thank you for the red super chat
good morning to you too tarty
isn't it nice waking it up to this
beautiful sun in your face
you're welcome taiji
thank you
for watching me early in the morning man
hope you have a lovely day tai chi
thank you so much for your support heave
thank you and dragon's fire danger for
the pinky next vacation fun
my next location i think
is either like a food trip
uh to
a certain city
or
the maldives i'm not sure what comes
first probably the food trip
[Music]
thank you thank you i won't eat good
food
boo seven two three thank you
for the pinky tanjo i don't know if it's
possible in balance but one of the
chances of getting a five versus five
ian versus japan stream oh
i hope everything can work out with your
vocal issues looking forward to finally
singing in 3d to be honest after that
uh stream of ahmed
i was
kind of like
hoping
that all five of myth could do a collab
on it like that we would always be on a
team together against randos
but i didn't ask because
i don't wanna
push it on them just because i am
personally enjoying the game right now
uh
this is a free game but yeah also
everybody's [\h__\h] busy right now like
kelly is gone ahmed will be gone for a
while
yeah it's a bad timing now
um i'm sure they would be on board i'm
not sure like i wouldn't would be on
board i guess gooda probably would be
two cause she
played it once
you know would probably join just for
fun someone just said kelly doesn't like
fps but i don't i don't like every i'm
not into fps games either but i still
enjoyed it maybe callie would just do it
to be
just just because we're
hm you know what maybe it's not that
impossible
but
but i feel like this is just me pushing
my my own personal interest on them now
because like there's so many fps games
why does it have to be paladins just
because it's one the one fps game that
i'm cool with right now
maybe five of them would be easier ah
like randall like not not just one gen
it still feels like i'm just pushing my
own
agenda
[Music]
it seems like a weird
choice but it is free and it is new
friendly that is true
[Music]
i don't know
yeah
and i'm also like supposed to plan other
things like the valentine's thing but to
be honest like
i suggested it
um
and got some some replies but not much
um i like already like wrote out the
whole idea
and i'm not i kind of lost my motivation
a little bit maybe because of the lack
of
replies
to plan to like organize it properly
uh so it's definitely not happening
happening on valentines but i don't know
if it's happening at all because like
planning a full member collab again
it's uh
kind of um
[Music]
i feel like if we were to do it it would
be amazing and everyone would enjoy it
but getting there getting to that point
is tough
it's challenging yeah
i i feel like right now i want to
organize something smaller
[Music]
i wanna
actually i was wondering i wanted to
play um
like uno and mario party again
and
i was
i want to invite uh
i want to invite
some horo
horokusu
hello six
gen
members to a collab because like i
haven't collab with them yet and
but
i want to do like a group collab but i'm
not sure like
[Music]
in what kind of shape and
what game
[Music]
i'm actually
i'm actually kind of um
interested in
um
koioni
koi i want to talk with cuyoli
and uh and iroha
i wanna talk of coyote and iroha
[Music]
of game of thrones not only that i
really like coyotes um personality like
she's very bubbly and talks a lot
and and it is a little bit a little bit
similar in that regards
um
they caught my interest
uh
i think i've seen
certain eon members doing um
minecraft
en server tour if i'm not incorrect i
think i've seen it isn't it happening
tomorrow like
like louie and
chloe
with
with two en members
no three in members if i look at the
calendar now no two two two and two end
members two two two two
so
dad still leaves
uh
three other members who have yet to be
introduced to the i don't know if
they're actually doing an and server
tour i just see minecraft i think it's
an en server too
you don't know who for me and yet i
thought so that's why i'm not saying it
so i'm thinking i guess
i guess it would be at least one reason
to collab with them so maybe i should
ask them if they wanna if they want a
tour from me but
even then it probably wouldn't be on my
channel because i told you guys before i
haven't haven't done one
i i don't want to do many more on my
channel because like they
i i don't want to pressure them to speak
english and i
don't want it to be awkward and i have
done so many on my channel
so maybe on their channel
um is good enough but then again i also
want some collab with them on my channel
i just
i'm lacking ideas like um like reasons
to collab
because i feel like if i collab with
iroha and coyotes since they don't speak
english
i need to
i need i need it to be a collab where
it's okay to not really speak english
but
if it's on my channel then it also
shouldn't be fully japanese you know i
think a lot about these things to make
every every collab partner comfortable
[Music]
i don't want to do another boring
english and german lesson
[Music]
is there anything you guys would like us
to play
i could i could imagine like a four
member collab too
like idol and clyoni and me and someone
else
maybe playing
maybe
maybe enoch because then we can speak
some decent japanese with them
no
i don't want to play uno
but but
in mario party more things would happen
it's kind of easier to have a
conversation i think
i feel like uno might be a bit awkward
mario party
okay
i will no it's good that mario party is
busy it's a good thing
okay
[Music]
okay i'll think about
it uh i will not i want to get to know
them i really like those two
i mean they're all sweet but especially
coyote and idol
they
they caught my interest fasmophobia no i
don't like phasmophobia
it's boring
the past few times that i played fast
before we were always a failure because
we could never find ghosts
so boring
we always failed
monopo oh man i want to play monopoly
don't i can't
raft uh i think they're already
some of them already playing raft
with someone else
i think
ultimate chicken horse is cute yeah
that's a cute game um
you know i was interested in amen
[Music]
i guess it's like a japanese monopoly
but people can't clip it but i guess
that's okay
[Music]
yeah coyote played with chloe corona and
marine
aqui is playing monopoly later
what
where is that reservation
where do you see that i don't see it
huh
[Music]
wait a moment
which monopoly
[Music]
or the switch
the new one
that's the new one isn't it
i did not know that we can play that now
i i asked for that like
in december
i am confused
i will ask about it
okay good to know that we can play it
now
[Music]
let's finish the super jack rating i
need to make food
[Music]
yes
we have a delay
sometimes mm-hmm
um
calcuttan loved your video thank you
h a bill a bill vancouver oh are you
bail bail duncan adam
[Music]
what
did she never go to the en server yet
sonora thank you
plain water
oh thank you tomahawk
and that's dance dancing thank you
no no fastball doesn't need to get any
more stressful even in easy mode it's
just like can't find [\h__\h] ghosts
it was on the break when all the tours
happen oh interesting you guys know i
was looking for a reason to collab with
marine again
for my secret plan i see
i don't know she might also feel like
it's kind of too late now because the
maybe the hype of the enters is gone
she's a business lady after all but i am
i might offer it to her
get aqua too
we could do marine and aqua at the same
time
[Music]
half of umi c
it's true
true
and
[Music]
thank you
yeah i need to set up all these collabs
that have many many
rough ideas but
[Music]
um
okay i have to do something about the
food situation now
and prepare the stream for tomorrow uh
so thank you everybody for watching
today
soon it was nice having you guys was fun
doing the pew pew pew
shooting again
[Music]
that was a great stream thank you
you were lovely as always oh thank you
fun indeed thank you
have a great night you too
thank you thank you thank you thank you
thank you let's get back into the
streaming rhythm shall we
[Music]
thank you guys
i was up by the way really early today
as again even though i didn't need to i
was up at like
eight eight a.m or something hi baby
came here again perfect timing
you were cute at the pupil game oh
thanks
thank you also to everybody who um
participated and played together with me
in my team or in my opponent's team
[Music]
your shooting is actually pretty
bloggers
there were some good moments holy [\h__\h]
when i went to the rampage what was
happening
i was uh on a high
feel so toxic phoenix
i'm not sure if i can sleep early today
if i i kind of need to cook something it
kind of takes some time so i'll go now
yes 88k damage holy [\h__\h]
berserk mode
[Music]
i showed you some potential today
perhaps potential
sniper kiana not really sniper but um
okay then thank everybody for watching
and see you tomorrow
in germany
[Music]
potential
you tried you tried
good job
potential i guess it's pretty good
[Music]
oh nice timing bdm
so
[Music]
do
foreign
[Music]