[Music]
[Applause] [
Music] [Applause] [Applause] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music
]
[Music]
yes I love you together with review I
love you I love you
[Music]
full introduction of each we can Start
with Srikandi  cheers
here okay
[Music]
okay
that's familia family yeah
Hello everybody loves you
[
Music] [
Applause] [Music] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Music] [Music] [
Music  ]
[Music]
nice nice nice
already
using yourself
[Applause]
[Music]
Pertiwi
okay
[Music]
that's it he can  how come you
see that's the picture of five,
it's possible, no download point,
understance,
thank you
yey
[Music]
everyone my name is lose the blacksmi
from follow ID genre Hooray ID sanq Seno
kajia Kaira deh si risk ini mah
yes
[Music]
spicy
enter
best version
[Music]
now
please 6
[Music]
[Music] [
Music] [Music] [Music] [Music
] hi
[Music]
My  name
is today
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] [
Applause]
[Music]
it's time for us to have a shouting match
because there was Pertiwi on stage
Pertiwi first No,
Zombies
[Music]
[Applause]
okay  okay
start okay
[Music]
okay okay let's go let's go Srikandi le
Let's go Let's go  Let's go
[Music] ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha  The
sky is ready, it's a
struggle. In my opinion, yes, it's really
Wow, Fish Pertiwi
[Music] is
really finished now, Munasin Pay
will tell you the list of these little games,
guys,
event in the killne  eventory school
ayomi Mas regarding
[Music]
[Applause]
from chapter the fourths with Colin
Bentengan and up to date remove To The
Potter the secrets and up to date
without toko for and then after that we
have badminton from the eye site  and
badminton from beside and also of today
soccer
and that's
or and day
[Music] [Music]
[Music] are
we going back to respectivision
or not, is each team okay okay okay
[Music]
[Applause]
games
[Music]
Next we have to move to the word
fortress, let's
interview,
move,
OK? Yes, we've told them to move. I've told them I want to interview according to
Rondon. Yes,
suddenly-  suddenly come and pull it out like that,
okay, stay for now, but it's okay, okay,
if that's the case, we'll just move,
OK, let's just move, okay,
let's go
[Music]
come on, guys, fillet, how about it?  here's the cloth
guys
[Music]
Thank you Thank you Thank you animation
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
What are you most a Friday of the years
team not
[  Music]
[Music]
[Music] Are
you afraid we have a
tactic? Really there is a tactic.
No, I don't think so, why do we have to believe that
we only exist? There definitely is, but if
I'm them, I'm not there, I
said yes, you know
[Laughs]
for the Srikandi team, the leader
seems to have forgotten to click, yes, in the
initial stage, no, he hasn't
chosen a team yet
[Music]
He
was told to just type it in, please don't forget
to choose a team, yes, Heroine is red, yes  yes yes yes yes yes yes
yes oh thank you Thank you Thank you
[Laughs]
I want to fly, how do I do it?
Just here, creative near here, everywhere
[Music]
click Wow then when does this start?
okay okay
[Applause]
[Music]
each one and this is the
white one, who is Pertiwi, Pertiwi, straight
away, wow,
in
Pertiwi there is absolutely no one
looking after them
[Music]
but it seems like Pertiwi has
started  wow
ver please comment squishy really fast for a
moment Winner please come
we need an explanation what is this
[Music] who
was that
[Music]
[Applause]
yes I know
n
[Music]
draw  to go to and me backhand and
basically
wow
[
Music] [
Music] [Music]
[Music]
Pertiwi impress
coding
[Laughs] [
Music]
yes [
Applause]
[Music]
[Laughs]
hmm
already play the Benteng only  only for
like one time playing so we move to the
Nur game okay okay
keep going
[Music]
we can't go that fast Wow that's okay
kiyoso is that the Japanese name Yes I
like potato better  Kyosuke, because Potato,
who from
Pertiwi will race from Pertiwi
is Jeng Jeng Jeng Jeng Who
is
Risuk Fauna and Sora Sempak
from Srikandi, there is
also a Marine
representative from in
GP, ​​guys, so look at this, they have to
play 3 times, you have to do three laps,
right?  only once, so it seems like this is
a bit longer than the other one, it
has to be longer because it's longer. That's
true, yes, the Alien team that
wins from the capture will win 40
points, right?
Winning Story Oh, this time it's 30, this time it's 30
points, so this is the game, no, no
relay, no relay, so it's
straight away,
whoever comes in first, right?
[Music]
start, Brother. Yes, they're
very excited, right?
[Laughs] I
think Yes, it's ready. It's ready.  everyone
[Music] is
red
[Music]
H here comes the starting point
[Applause]
[Music]
squishy is
quite advanced, that's senpai's voice. That's it  at the
front together with the fauna Eh,
I think the apple is stupid
[Music]
the fish is still attached to
Spider-Man Oh my gosh ora Oh my God,
it seems like they've been practicing a lot,
right? And they don't
know
where it is, guys
[Music]
just  There are only two left and so it also disappears from the
server.
Oh, if that's the case, I'll enter
the server first, I can just enter the server
first,
I'll tell you what it's
raising, I think I'll give it, so I'll do this,
don't ask, please try Oh, look
Try it, there's one thing that's funny,
tell us to recard, okay?
Sorry Guys, my squishy is that so nothing
not
[Music]
Dead and
God, okay, okay, Guys, no, it's okay,
but now you can go to
mainhop,
thank you,
thank you  okay
[Music]
if that's the case,
but if that's the case, it's better for us like
this, maybe it's
okay for us to repeat it, but for the next one,
I don't think it's fair enough.  For
people who have done this, they can't do it anymore, they
can't
say it's okay, let's try again, OK, let's
try again, OK? I'll check again
[Music]
Maybe I said it the first time, yes, to the
team, both of them
just told them to race in the sack, but instead they went into the
kidnapper's sack.
Who's that, it's
a bit on the edge of a cliff, I'm sorry
[Music]
here's the score, it's not a score like 1 2
3, but the score is based on points,
so for example, if you
look at it, if you guys and the explanation
and I'm ready for it  on the Twitter
and no so talking about it on
[Music]
where talking a Where pointing about the
Coins on every game
yeah
[
Music] [
Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Music
]
[Music]
[Applause]
[
Music] [Music] [
Music] [
Music]
[Music]
hmm everybody that's the best but this is what you
have to do when it comes to sack racing  the
three of them finished first Oh I
thought only one person
had to be the three of them.
This is really crazy, it
turns out, huh?
[Laughs]
[Music] You
already won, which was really cool,
now they win, this will also
make a comeback. No, right?  I think
I can still make a comeback
wow wow
[Laughs]
[Music]
thank you
guys thank you guys gold everything in the
back I've won twice you want
twice you think you  can with the next
one yeah yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
[Music]
Wow, that's
really high, you
can still give because we've
only given two really
[Music]
Yes, I want to believe in Mother Earth, I
really want to  trust like
[Music]
[Laughs]
okay okayokay
so whatever is ready hmm I think
Let's ask these guys to choose Indo okay
[Music]
who we have asked
there are three Bocil deaths  there's a frog,
there's a Gura, there's a fire, Empire curase,
but this is funny, it's really blue
versus pink, isn't that
cool
[Music]
Wow,
if Pertiwi wins, it can be done for
example
[Music]
If, for example, you win,
you have to chase the softcase
[Music] wait a
minute, the team
[Music]
one of his friends is
still under
[Music]
guys
this stitch is really cool
[Music]
actually cool,
different from Srikandi friends by
being chased but not Pertiwi  still
[Music]
This is already 100 points, the difference is
180 rings, 180 points
haven't
been caught yet. It was 3 but it could be really far,
it's really far,
it's already 50 Diamonds. Yes, no
difference. Heeh, 100 only one left, wow
[Music]
I  like
wow wow I know the finger finally
their first
Wow indeed finger Queen on the edge
Queen
queentem really Queen really wow
[Music]
thank you
alright yeah guys
Pertiwi with the first when What yes What yes is
this if they wih this can catch up
loh this is this now
[Music]
eee the badminton
Please just like one thing
if one team just wins badminton that
one adds 20 right for
me because I don't see it  they practice
badminton, you know, badminton is difficult,
in my opinion, the most difficult of all, let's
see what badminton is like,
so badminton is divided into two
next matches.
[Music]
we'll be there for a moment hehehe
Pertiwi has Kayla Kiara Ilfi and the afternoon
[Music]
cool for Pertiwi there's Kayla and Tiara
so they're going to fight okay against a
and b against B
versus
ready okay
[Music]
lots of practice so I think they can
carry if they can only hit once.
From one save, what are the rules for
badminton?
So, for the first save, it has to be
diagonal, after that, whatever happens,
if that means, the
other team gets it.  like if we hit
or pants, the other team will get points,
but if we hit it and then it turns out that we
touch it in our place, it means the
other team still gets points.
Wow, but I've been practicing, I'm sure I
can do it, hmm.
Come on, let's fall, we're ready, the gang has
started, right?  I don't know okay
this is now
versus Kayla Kiara eya
[Music]
with Pertiwi with Kayla Tiara and
Srikan with Toraja
then that's it the ball is in the team is
here
[Music]
this is Pertiwi
oh oh oh oh oh
oh
[Music]
we look at it too high,
so the technique is that we have to be
straight
[Music]
[Laughs]
[Music] it's
really hard for her to look yes it's
really hard this is really hard  no
no no lie
[Music]
[Applause]
too excited maybe
[Music]
earlier
Oh no no that doesn't go in
that's why Oh it doesn't go in
Oh yes because you have to diagonal it
Oh yes for this yes  Later this score will be up
to 10, that's right
[Music]
just keep catching up, this is cool,
maybe the film came out but it turned
out to be TV
[Music]
Wow, this is a relay, this is cool,
they are here
[Music]
who took one more point from
Srikandi but there are still 3 more left or not
Oh no two more
[Music]
game finished 3-10
310 a
So now Pertiwi's points are
60 Wow, this is really something we can catch up with
Let's  Let's see what happens,
then we go straight to B, isn't that
right,
continue to the grave with Bey and let's
go to our respective positions
[Music]
Dozo in the position
okay
[Music]
will win again Oh my God
sip sip sip  sip
OK
Heroine starting from Heroine this time
from the Bay, welcome straight
in, come on,
I can't play this after that, is the
trililintar
one on one one one cool, is this cool,
come on, OK, so it's a fierce battle,
coffee and  Come on, Flora, friends, yes
[Laughs]
[Music]
So the secret is that if you can't
relay, how come it's hard to paint
because later I have it, so it's
really easy for the opponent,
right, so as long as the first service
can be relayed, they can relay, but
if  no it's okay hmm
unfortunately it's auto eh but it's still on yeah
but the sound
but if it's from American pop it's
hard isn't it really hard to see it
like this
[Laughs]
[Music]
it hits  I'm lost,
this is actually more difficult than
it looks. I've seen
it too. That's how we play it.
What's more, the
direction is too high, so it
falls short, it
affects us if, for example, we go
too high on him. So it's short. Oh yes,
because he's too high
[Music]
[  Laughter]
29 only one point left for Pertiwi
[Music]
wins
so we are 40
so 70 80 can now be replaced 70
Pertiwi 80
narrow win  so that Srikandi
can win
[Music]
Oh my God,
Where is
[
Music] [Music]
[Music]
everyone has practiced as much as possible
and
that's it. Let's see the results of
their practice, OK? Hmm I  I'm just here watching
Football
of the Galaxy
[Music] it's
starting to come in oh no one's buying it
right he's ready too they're okay
[Music]
but I'm the one who's close
on the way team
oh hang on a minute
[Music]
senpai Heaven click Draw
they
[Music]
were
giving this morning before
it started, I want to practice
badminton
[Music]
I really intend everyone to practice for
this ee, holoid Cup this time
everyone is practical event super last
minutes  like you hours one our for this
that I want to be practical
[Music]
from everybody
okay okay
[Music]
crazy
I keep going from who
[Music]
[Laughing]
[Music
] [Music]
[Music]
he saved and kept the oath to
keep it
[Music]
cool too
too bad
[Music]
yeah right
taken again
The kick was not very enthusiastic, it was
emotional,
then
immediately
[Music]
started to be taken but I don't know.
now the one holding it is the
team from Pertiwi but it was kicked again, the
gokick from
[Music]
was already very excited  that's it friends
still no
one has entered,
goalie
[Music]
OK, we have entered the 5th minute
and with a score of 10 for the Srikandi team, yes
friends, he's right, he's 10 10 minutes. Continue
rafting for 10 minutes.  again
Oh
I see, that was the ball, it was like it was going around and around [Music] ouch. Let's look at this. Yovi, this time,
make a splash, maybe if they make the
wrong move they will score because it's
really close.  Let's see what the ball will
do
[Laughs]
oh
how about this how about this will
there be a breakthrough
[Music]
there needs to be a very aggressive skull yes
as the goal scorer from the first
but he's still aggressive
huh
[Music]
oh
there's another goal scored  discussed,
it turns out you're really good at
kicking. Wow, aggressive friends,
now I'm
[Music]
OK, I've been kicked and I'm starting to get close to the
goal, but that's OK, it's
okay, I'll start
kicking again by Emil, who was
taken by Ouch,
if I saw that  What's the distribution like
? The Srikandi Team really has
someone guarding it in every area,
that's really good. Yes, for example, if
there's a ball here,
whose job is to take it? Yes, what's more,
Emmy looks at that senpai, sometimes it's
like he's also coming forward.  you know, so if
they advance, everyone advances, so everyone,
no one can enter
their area, they're crazy hmm
[Music]
Let's see Mother Earth
almost 9 minutes 5 seconds left  we're
going in and in 1 minute we're going to
end the first hall
[Music]
maybe because it seems like it's going to be a while now
[Laughs]
[Music] be
careful
where he's going to kick the three
[Music] he'll
be able to get in
just a few more seconds before  let's
rest for a while
Yes
[Music]
456789 10 minutes
it would be interesting if we called
one of the Srikandi teams, okay, yes,
let's kidnap one of the irons then kidnap
one third  Do you want to know the
strategy
first and then stand up,
if that's the most common,
then who is our opponent, who
is from Pertiwi, who should we
invite
from Pertiwi, who can we win? Yes, maybe yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
maybe
[Music]
hi,
Lionel Messi's mother
[Music]
[Laughs]
Astagfirullah
OK,
first of all, guys, Sushi Master will give it
to China, okay, one one
[Music]
OK,
we'll send it
[Music]
even though  I only practice once
the ball was as high as I didn't reach
it, so
the wall was as high as you are short
[Laughs]
I'm defending
this and that and that, how come
all the balls
didn't reach the top? Oh, that's
how it seems if the moon is
higher.  I'm sure I'll be hit like that.
How do you feel? You're
guarding the goal, it seems like it's
really tight. Yes, the ball is being held a little bit. The
ball is being held. Yes, yes, that's okay.  Isn't it good
that the ball is there to hold and
to hold it a little, that's how
my job is to touch the
ball, is
n't it? Bold handler or not, but if it smells like a handle, actually Pertiwi has a strategy or not
using our feelings.
How do you feel about being in this,
right, because of Srikandi?  I'm already in a hurry
to steal gold. Is there a strategy
so that we can make a comeback, maybe Pertiwi,
we really believe that we can do Epic
Comics, because we
can do it now, right?  like that Oh,
there's a Miracle Shot, you
have to be careful,
Heroine is crazy when we look from
above, their defense is
really strong, so you have to step up too,
okay, finished,
both MPVs from each team are really
cool, eh, let's ask
if
this is all like this.  I'm very vengeful,
huh? Second
[Laughs]
I'll give you this so that your team wins,
for example, in the original game, you
were given this red card, but we
can't give you my record,
are both teams
as ready as they are?  That's right, it's both
fierce, you know,
and trim, trim again, the Pertiwi team
believes in Lady Luck, they can make a
comeback, so what do you think, in the end, my
friends are still sick,
let's continue, it looks like everything is
going to be
brutal [Music]
fortunately, it's immediately held by
the win  he won straight into the middle
But unfortunately there was Srikandi
How
about he went straight into the
middle whoever it was and that
ironed who
else it turns out a little more friends
[Music]
where do you think it will be
ouch
Pertiwi Pertiwi How do we have to try
hard so that they can make a comeback
because three is already here, Ouch, three
is really hard, fortunately, it was the hottest
by the vice senpai, otherwise it could
happen 4 0 that's it, ha, Abu,
Yovie, come on, come on, who is it,
I'm calm again, you  not the water, it's
really scary, like
oh,
this is a bit worrying because he
said earlier he really believes
in Lady Luck but the glass is dregs
[Music]
but it's really cool  I saw
the Srikandi, like every time they fit,
it's exactly right, so it's like
right and then it seems like I already know
each other's house
[Music]
tomatoes wow,
very, very blue-blue, that's a bit
scary, very scary,
fiber Yes, maybe this is
what it looks like  revenge or not
because of the tug-of-war if that's possible.
Anyway, we have to uh flatten them, they're
starting to get close and ah,
through Sun, it's a shame there wasn't enough
enthusiasm if we could get in like that, the
football is full  passion
yes again unfortunately Said
who is the
direction to the water pipe there is
waiting but suddenly
the counter but finally it is hol by okay
okay okay okay
[Music]
wow
same
come on let's
take it by
this it's been 3 minutes and it's been 40 How
am I  I just said that's it. It does
n't feel like it's been 3 minutes. I don't know,
come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, oh, that's
okay, it's okay, it's okay,
come back again  kicked from
[Music]
who was that to the gorgo?
Fortunately there were those who defended, oh
yes, okay.
It's scary if I'm the
white team,
but if you look at it,
this Srikan's position is really good,
yes, this is really good, you know.
[Music]
but if you say it like this, okay?  I mean,
Pertiwi also looks like they really
tried their best, yes, how many
times did they attack
[Music]
until they jumped from the oath chair
but like this  OK,
but I've been kicked again by Zaskia.
I was being chased by Kayla and
Mori,
bye bye bye, come on, come on, do we still
have 5 minutes? Do we think there's a comeback
or not, a comeback or not,
they can't, they've found it. I think that's an
OK strategy, right? Gold  here
[Music]
the ball is
free-free-free to take it okay but
often you want to push again what
will happen they
immediately okay guys
[Music]
the kick starts again from science via
sending to the center taken by the government
[Music]
that time, right, watch the back, yeah, then
there's Luna. Then the ovens are
Koyori and Kiara. Actually, it's
quite good, just like Come on, stay again
so you can draw if  What's the draw
BTW Oh, if drama happens
then there will be a penalty, there will
still be analysis
if the penalty is a draw too
[Music]
time is running out, friends.
Is the Miracle Cake that was hoped for
going to happen? Let's watch the boholder
finally get held up by YouTube
[Music]
finally horrified
Wow, this is what it looks like, oh, it
looks like this Srikan won, this is
really good I don't know how it's
like eh
[Music]
so even though it's the same as this, it's also
in the position of being divided, but it
seems like  It's like Srikan is
always there to receive passes like that,
really sometimes when Pertiwi
they pass like that but there's really no one
there
[Music]
like it's spread out  everywhere, so there's always
someone who can take it.
Oh, it's started, it's started, but
it seems like it was taken by Srikandi, it was passed
back to the middle, finally it was taken by
[Music]
maybe what was lacking from Pertiwi was a
lack of defense.
In my opinion, it's not a lack of defense, it's
more of a  For example, if he passes,
it's rare for anyone to take it straight away
[Music]
so his over-over is better,
that's why he's good,
come on, come
on, come on, can't do it?
[Music]
Once in a while, it's too late.  I see
thirty seconds Not yet but I
want to receive this receipt. His defense is very
sharp, friends, he's really
always the one who takes
[Music]
Oh my God,
it's like he's ready to catch
[Music]
again
five four three
[Music]
[Applause]
wait,
we're the ones who are sweating, I think I
really understand
[Music]
[Applause] [Music
] [Applause] [
Music]
crazy
World
[Music]
golgi
Yes guys
[Music]
[Music] [
Music] [
Music] [Music] [Music] [
Applause]
[Music]
Come on I've been selling meatballs
before the competition started but before
I didn't  it's okay, it's okay, it's not
allowed to go up in meatballs
[Laughs]
[Music]
lings
Your Heart
peop you
[Music]
[Laughs]
[Music] [
Laughs]
[Music]
okay
[Laughing]
[Music]
[Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music
]
Pertiwi
sport Pertiwi [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Applause
hands]
[Laughs]
[Music]
[Music] [
Applause]
[Music]
[Laughs]
[Music]  [
Applause]
[Music]
[Music] [
Applause] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music
]
[Music]
[
Music] [
Music] [Music]
[Music]
thank you
[Music] [
Music] [Applause] [Music
]
[Applause  hands]
[Applause]
thank you thank you
say Our last Goa is a
fotbar or not yeah
let's go let's go
nded On The Spot okay
y
[Music]
with you ready
okay
three two one
[Applause]
[Music]
Piece OK
thank you
[Music]
[Music] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music
]
[Music]
[Laughter]
Can we be able to take a photo where we are
taking a photo where we are here,
yes yes yes, yes,
okay,
it's already 3 2 1
[music]
but you don't pay attention to
these viewers, unifornia  everyone is
wearing jerseys and there are numbers on them
if you pay attention. Oh
yeah, how come
I have long hair so I can't
be seen, but let's take a look at the
others.
I wanted to see which one, which one, which one?
Yes?  Yes, because the committee has long hair,
all of you, if you look at yourself, you
know the number. Oh yes, there is,
there is, there is,
but it's not that obvious,
that's the truth, but yes, that's the
skin. Everyone
has prepared a special skin for Solo ID Card
2023 this time and everyone is wearing a jersey.
with the number on the back to
add a spirit hollow ID card, no, the
trailer continues to run out, everyone
gets a skin, this continues until it is made,
so that the game can be played
smoothly, it's like badminton,
suddenly there is a racket.  That's the place where
meatballs and soto are given, guys,
let's go first. Oh yes, this is it, eee. This is new.
Hello, ID card, yes, while we have a
lot of Gelora holo.id series of events that
haven't finished yet, really,
there's still a continuation of the event on
the 15th and 17th. What's up?  Yes,
basically, just look at it,
yes, yes, this
Halo ID Cup event this time, this one,
yes, not all of it. This one reaches the
closing point. Yes, that's right, what are the
impressions and messages, all of them
Wow, starting from  Who was this in the
old days?
I actually asked the viewers, but
if you want to answer, you can also
watch YouTube. It's
really exciting. Oh, the most difficult thing
is that it seems like everything is difficult, actually, I
hope you all are happy
with the Halo ID Cup this year and hopefully the
next one will be Step  Is it up again,
next year we have to think again about
how to make the game even cooler
so that it's more popular than this.
Yes, yes, that means if we imagine,
remember, last year's Hola ID cards
were like printed, but like
this one, they're much better.  Is that neat? Yes, that's
true, but I'm very happy. Next year,
next year, what's more, it's
crazy, the pressure is already high,
yes, there's still a year left, yes. Yes, I
've handed it over to Oli or MC
MU or MC again or maybe Muna who
wants this is here  the other thing is that's all so far,
so we can close this event
because we are at the
end of the event, so
for the teams who might still
want to play, the world
will be there. So if the
teams-  the team wants to play again  just until
what date,
20 20
Yes, if you want to play, hurry up, that's right, that's
right, August 21, the world
will be available until August 21, so
maybe there's something for fun, I
want to play this or maybe there are
other members.  which turns out to be
no or no, yes, don't go here
and then want to try it, you can, you can,
yes, fans can play or not, wow,
you
can look carefully at the description,
maybe it's possible
[Laughs]
that's how it is
Yes, if  That's it, let's close the event,
thank you, Eee, Oli and Rainy, they have been
really helpful because
actually using it doesn't really mean that much.
See you again in Halo ID Cup 2018
[Music]