[Music]
huh oh
it's newbie dare to complain about my
outfit again huh
what do you want
oh wait
oh my god
here
goddammit casper is loud and as noisy as
usual i can't get my work done like this
the people who come to my office for a
meeting also get freaked out about ya
what
who is
damn you're really new here huh
all right then
let me tell you about casper
[Music]
oh there it is
let me put this here
it's springtime baby
hey fb 101 how to become one with the
bucket
episode casper
it all started when i moved into a very
old house while i was living in japan
i slept like around i think 11 p.m and i
heard like lots of noises in my ceiling
let's just say i have ghosts i've had
the ghostbusters over quite a few times
they showed me pictures of dead ghost
bodies that were in my ceiling then i
started realizing but they're so cute i
don't want to kill them i feel so sorry
i'm taking away their home i know
there's still some in there because i
hear them walking around at least one
ghost is in there the ghostbusters did
say that there's some spaces that they
cannot reach outside so maybe they're
still able to come in and go out and
they're bringing in their own food
so it's been two weeks without a dead
mouse
i said it
if it's gonna survive it deserves a name
casper oh that's cute because it's that
i always say it's a ghost i'm gonna
freak out if one day he's going out of
the ceiling and i see him like running
around in my living room i'm gonna freak
the [\h__\h] out and that we know as
something called foreshadowing
oh my oh my god oh my god i was
downstairs
at my door i took my order and at that
moment casper
ran
up the wall and i never saw casper
before i thought they at least managed
to get rid of all the entrances and
holes
i tried to stay cool and
to not let the uber person
know what i just saw i just took my
order like he was literally giving it to
me and on the side of my eye i see
something running up
i see somebody running up the wall
and i saw him
when i was sitting down having an idol
meeting from one side to another casper
ran through the room oh my god
like
swoosh
okay more like sush like that he has a
brown hair by the way brown hair oh
isn't that nice to know when i went
downstairs to go take a shower and i put
my bathrobe
[\h__\h] casper like for an instant i
felt him on him on my foot right over me
and back into his little hidey hole
and i legit i i got a [\h__\h] heart
attack i was like
i was wearing slippers but i felt him
running over
my foot
passport i'm sorry i love you but please
even though i had direct encounters with
casper i wasn't always quite sure if he
was actually alive or not
because sometimes he was noisy but later
he would be really quiet or completely
silent for a long period of time casper
trying really hard
to open up the hole again that
the ghostbusters have sealed
casper has been so noisy these days and
like really running around like crazy
and like if i don't hear him again for
another 24 hours then he might have died
recently in 24 hours i don't hear him at
all and um
now it's been like 48 hours and i
haven't heard him again today
i heard casper moving and stuff so he's
still alive he's been so quiet he might
not be alive much longer
in the end i just assumed that casper
moved somewhere else since all the holes
inside the house were supposedly sealed
but while all this was happening
casper started sending some super chats
talking about his life i can't get out
of my hiding hole anymore what happened
that's why i could just get out
see excellent casper's super chats make
me feel so bad for casper
day two of confinement i've yet to find
another way of escaping from my hearty
hoe stop it stop calling it hidey ho
that's way too cute
i made friends with a local bird who let
me know about a series called fruity
eats now i can get food deliveries in my
lounge for my uncle mickey
i'm now cozying happy birthday
i don't know why i get so emotional
about this stupid mouse i finally found
my way out so i've been playing a lot
outside these days it's cold but santa
gave me some bitterness from my paws am
i
allowed to call you mama
oh
casper of course i'm new mama
keeps bragging about touching this
girl's foot and i'm just like mate where
the [\h__\h] are you
casper from cheese bmp is wrapping my
hidey hole for now i hope he's been
behaving casper please come back i don't
want jasper
oh no jasper is right
i hear cass has been asking you about me
telling him what i did
hasn't really come with me to australia
casper are you going to make me cry i
will kill you if you're going to make i
mean you're pretty much invincible by
now
together
hope that the chocolate didn't make you
poop too much these super chats
continued after i moved back to austria
but they started to get less and less
frequent until the time came to sadly
[Music]
he told me that i can't stay
and i have to move on but he said mama
and papa will be waiting for me
[Music]
breaking character i'm sorry that
casper's goodbye made you sad kiara
maybe someone else will continue but i
didn't think it was right to keep going
when i started to skate since there was
not much you could do my reason was that
i hoped it would turn a source of your
fear into something that's more
light-hearted hoping it might reduce
your stress oh
i don't think it's no it definitely
worked what the [\h__\h]
because of you i had like
this feeling of of love towards casper
but i hope you enjoyed ghost casper at
least now you're with your babies and
casper he's gone and no longer concerned
i so i once wanted to give closure to
you to the kfp goes no
i don't want closure
casper might be gone but i'll always be
around and support you just in a
different name and form but then who are
you give me closure tell me who you are
casper says goodbye but see you in the
next stream
no
thank you for all the cute little super
chats they all shared me up every time
was my highlight always was my freaking
highlight thank you so much whenever i
saw your name i was like oh my god guys
this time i loved it but of course i
refused to let that be the end so i
managed to bring casper back into my
office
look
even though in the beginning i want to
get rid of casper because of him
terrorizing me during my time in japan
i felt so uncomfortable in there and the
traumatizing moments of him showing up
in front of me are deeply engraved in my
memory
but i ended up feeling sorry for wanting
to kill him and for the super chats
actually i started to see him as more
than a random mouse and felt sort of
attached to him anyway were you gonna
ask me again
you forgot
are you [\h__\h] kidding me
you come here to my office make me go to
long terms and completely wasted my
[\h__\h] time and you dare say to me that
you forgot what you were gonna ask me
ride it the hell down next time
get the [\h__\h] out of my office and get
back to work
these chicken brains am i right casper
big ups too and shout outs to casper
please do please don't go into cusa
tony's house anymore