[Music]
we're just waiting for kelly i think
kelly's still not
transitioning
she's leaving hello we're leaving
oh yeah she's waiting
oh yeah right she's she's muting us
whenever she does that
coming soon soon
it's only a matter of time and she'll be
there soon
[Music]
yeah make it today i took off my hats to
not destroy the cali's face
i think she wants to eat my hat she
should play maybe she's there instead
chickens all my on my hats yeah it'll
feel like antennae no
chicken no
[Music]
it's kelly still doing her introduction
an impression of you but maybe next time
there we go you can still do it you can
go ahead and do it
i'm here it's your boy
that's how i sound nope it's your boy no
i tried i tried
[Music]
that's how it's supposed to be
that's just my that's just me this is
real this is me
i'm exactly how i'm supposed to be now
let the light shine on me
i can i go to the room now or guys look
at my question in the chat do you think
it's okay
should i go to the room yeah it's fine
which one come on come in
here we go it says you're from usa
alabama wow
wow yeah you got you got me
how is alabama how is that place it's
fine
is it hot how is it decent enough
oh okay is that
would you like to would you like to
explain what we're doing today since
you're so smart
ah so we're gonna be playing uh rio
wheel tetris too do you guys know what
buoyancy is
no no i know a tetris i've played it
before buckets a day
well people you have these like uh
colored jellies
and you gotta line up four or more of
them
and then it's kind of like tetris yeah
you get rid of the blobs
by matching colors and uh you try to
uh get as many combos as you can
lining those up and then you can get
more points
and then you can kill your opponents
quicker
to 200 percent too meaning as loud as
kelly sounds the same to me
i don't know why good now okay
i'll speak louder which you said while
whispering i was closer to the bike
right
anyways anyway i would i would like to
say that
we all have practiced a tiny bit before
the stream
and while i was an absolute horrible
mess in the first
two rounds i have since then recovered
well and uh
got a basic grasp of the game
kelly is basically around the same level
as me i would like to
say although she has uh pulled out some
great moves like
throwing all those stones at me good job
kelly
yeah you're i mean yeah thank you that's
kind of you to say
how do i turn up how do i turn up ina by
the way only you have it
do you have a turn you have me turned up
on discord to 200 how do i turn you up
on discord you right click by a name
and they should be volume okay it's
fixed
i fixed it
oh my god okay all right so we're going
for the
[Laughter]
i don't think there's a friend's only
thing
all right all right
yeah i left well let me put up let me
put it on
it's cause it shows my name on and wait
it's not anybody
what i just said to i had it set to
locked the password isn't up left corner
but i thought it was for friends
okay let me let me hide the lobby for
once well we're gonna have to do this
the hiding all the way hold on okay i
hit my screen
to join your room
[Music]
oh there we go i thought it was friends
only damn it because it says join
friends hmm oh well join a friend's room
i'll come to the membership
i'm going to do my business
[Music]
maybe maybe do a more complicated
password like one two three that's like
super complicated one two three four
sorry
yeah that's the new password is one two
three four
what one two three four four
oh you know
with a small image you'll be fine okay
yeah hold on where i don't know i don't
know where it is
i'm just gonna join for now okay okay
let me give me a screenshot
screenshot of my my screen oh thank you
oh oh no i'm in the room oh there i see
i see where it is
no what do i put there can use the bird
there's a small bird
here oh i don't have it right now but
i'll use a chicken
because i have a new pc so
okay that should hide it i think
yeah no don't show it
don't show it kiara don't show it
i'm gonna make the cali pogues a little
smaller now
don't show it oh hi
oh emilia's here hey amelia oh my god
amelia's muted someone unmuted amelia
she's loud
amelia's too loud
why are we stealing her ability to speak
that's just rude
that's very rude i can't believe we've
done that i'm ready
are you guys ready for our first warm-up
game
hell yeah i am i sure am ready
so let's go so in this game we can
choose between puyo puyo mode and the
tetris mode
um i'm going to go for booyah i was back
let's show everyone what it's like um
you don't have to match the colors but
we have to match the colors
and but you also don't have to make a
line like in tetris you just have to
connect four
or more yeah yeah and it doesn't have to
be in one line it just
can be in random connections just has to
touch each other
sorry i forgot to play okay
don't worry
okay i'll show you what i got can i hide
my
my my password uh thingy now by the way
i wonder yeah i put it away yeah you can
put it away for now
[Music]
oh
i'll get you i'll get you
[Music]
you're the best out of us though you
guys won against me in the practice not
just remember
remember
and the history has been recorded on on
twitter no one can take that away from
me exactly
hot fries no lies
oh
look at that totally
i like
oh
there we go first one out baby that's
expensive
we can't play video games we love it we
love to see it
some of my viewers have placed some bets
saying that i will lose especially after
the first tweet that i sent but i think
they're rethinking that
uh now i wonder i wonder what they fit
[Music]
it's right in the end it doesn't even
matter because you know
oh that's no problem no problem i will
do that right now
exactly
i mean i think i like how the chicken
that i place to hide the the
password is perfectly positioned in a
way that it implies that the chicken is
me because it's now on top of my
cryo for your screen like in my how do
you call it you guys probably don't know
what i'm talking about
you probably just like oh yeah
yeah just keep on talking kiara whatever
yes yes focus on the game here
oh now focusing focusing focus on the
game here
right push
i can do it i have a headache though god
damn it
happens to the best of us oh god i'm
this is my bad round
this is a bad round oh god
oh
[Music]
fine okay i can still make it out
excuse me what the hell oh my god
what the [\h__\h]
i love that you have that
i did that's so good i i can stand for
myself
but i i usually forget the sensor myself
and it just comes too late
nice that's good
what the beep what beep indeed
so you two love me ladies what did you
have for dinner today huh
i mean though it's way too classy
because i guess she's in a different
time zone but she also lives in a
different time zone
like then she actually like sleeps in
don't worry about the shoes so did you
eat the
dinner yet you know uh i had a meal like
i don't know
what meal i would call it but
what's that fried rice yes fried rice
hmm fragrance like jahan i love town um
i put like a mountain of hot sauce on it
it was delicious
to make it to make it spicy yes
you like spicy stuff yeah right you did
say that before you were so excited when
the indonesia
second generation girl said that they
like spicy stuff yeah and then they're
like
i'm not gonna eat spicy food but spicy
food i'm just like oh oh oh
i am i am stench we're going back to the
lobby guys
it's always been there it's okay my
image is there permanently i'm too lazy
to remove it
kelly what did you eat for dinner um
i had pasta what kind of flavor
it was tomato and mozzarella pasta
i'm gonna be this uh this emo kid who
looks like he's a fan of my chemical
romance
you know what means no your name it's
a little salmon oh tuna i'm sorry
yes so i'll call you tuna now yeah
yeah that's fine oh uh i'm gonna
go for puyo puyo again oh man it's
tetris versus wheel for you
yep i'm the only one with free up yes oh
i think how'd it go but the bloopers
look so yummy they look little jelly
ease
yeah little cool tangos i'm not a big
fan of jelly but sure
sure sure you don't like jelly i mean i
can't eat it but
i used to like jelly stuff much more
when i was a kid
hmm oh yeah but now i'm a phoenix that
is a million years old so
i'm kind of over that stuff you know
you're a million years old i thought you
didn't have it
i don't even know i mean i don't know
man i've been reborn so many times i
have no idea
i guess you lose after like a few
millennia or something
yeah yeah it's hard to say you know
i mean didn't wait how old are you
emilia recommended it to me kelly i need
to pick one of those up
it's really good it's so fun to use
and ever since i got it everyone told me
that i sound even crispier i already
sounded crispier
after getting my shure sm7b not
sponsored
but but now
it's like a whole new world has opened
itself to me
yeah crispy chicken is really good you
know
i mean who wants sloppy wet old
chicken when you can have crispy chicken
can someone stop sending me all that
[\h__\h] over here
nope nope don't feel like it
stop it
eat wait
bye all right citrus time i'll take the
time to hydrate myself everyone
hydration time
you're watering friend you know
oh darn it hang on okay that's fine
uh i should have put
which is basically a bowl of rice we
have a bunch of
uh uh what kind of
uh kind of yeah
um it's
[Laughter]
[Music]
could you girls eat a raw egg
depends if it's like what's mccall maybe
pasteurized or whatever it's called
what you can eat rice
like they do like special treatment on
it so there's like no salmonella and
stuff
oh okay you would it would actually i
mean i'm asking if you would want to do
that
yes want to i don't know it depends
apparently it's not really good if you
lift and stuff if you do work out it's
broken
yeah who needs that kind of stuff huh
let's just keep on eating pizza and
chocolate and all that okay
they're not saying don't have to ask me
twice i'll do it
nice we got similar taste i like it
yummy i'm getting hungry oh yes
you oh bless you thank you thank you
sean
oh was that good yeah
i mean what did you just say i said
thank you
thank you that's close enough
[Laughter]
thank you
i say that in my super chat reading
that's probably how you picked it up but
um i i tried to like mix it up every now
and then and say for example
it also means thank you but i said uh
phil and dunk and my viewers would think
i'm saying i'm feeling dank
oh i'm not feeling dank at all me
neither in fact i am really boned right
now
yeah oh
[Music]
i'll go slowly i'll go slowly
oh one more try don't want to retry or
do you want to change your oh wait um
okay okay well let me know next time if
you guys want to
stay the same okay
i'm just going to do tetris yeah okay
another minus one i might just want to
change to
tetris right now yeah okay i'll try to
do it
okay yeah i'm not as strong
i wonder if they sell candy
marketing i mean
it's probably like at least there's
candy that looks like that probably hmm
let's see what we can do
how do people have the time to look at
what's coming next i don't understand
oh yeah just real pros to be honest i
can't even imagine
oh god i already messed up i already
missed
no oops
i also mentioned should have never
changed
um there we go
how do i get something in there though
[Music]
oh no um
how do i fix the bottom line
no oh god tetris is not my thing
i prefer i don't know you i feel like we
feel you actually have to think
to maximize your uh what you call it
combos
chains
[Music]
yeah you can like stack them up
certainly so that it'll like hundred
percent combo
no yeah okay i can't do that in puyo for
your either and i definitely can't do
that
in touch
[Music]
okay okay okay
my brain not work oh yeah yeah my brain
is on
how long have you been awake yes
okay you already told me
i know i'm messing up
oh no i'm not i messed up so i'm not
getting any
chains
one
oh my god
oh
i want you to destroy us please do it i
don't know i feel like i'm gonna get
destroyed if i
actually try it's like when you
like when you like don't try you do
better but then like when you actually
try you like mess up
that's a good point i'm gonna try to do
the things that the professionals do
where they leave one line open and then
try to
keep on you know clearing it all up i'm
gonna try that
oh okay no i'm gonna fix that one right
right now okay nice oh
okay i'm gonna try to be cool now
i can't do it i believe in myself leave
me
away from you okay i don't know what to
do
no
really i don't think so let's go oh god
hold on
did not let me do it
when i think of tetris i think of
suicide senpai
yeah terrifying yeah i saw her play and
i was like
oh i don't ever want to be against her
not that just
no i think yeah no no no no no no no no
no no no
you could be good if you want to just
believe in yourself
i'm like it drinks my dream no
confidence
oh there we go that's the end
no confidence no confidence
[Music]
if you're trying to challenge me here
you know what happened to youtube when
they terminated me
their service went down yesterday so
you know what happened there my revenge
is bittersweet
definitely this channel your inner gamer
i believe
in you oh god okay maybe maybe next
baby
[Laughter]
you'll be fine
girl
you can keep one and then you can uh
hold it until you need it and then like
you can like switch it out for when you
use that
i don't think i have the skills yet to
do something like that
first need to get used more to the room
to the to the
[Music]
okay okay
it's the only way we could win you guys
only
you guys want against me in the practice
matches you'll you'll do fine
i don't know you know you have the i'm
pretty convinced that like the uh the
old ones have given you
like the kid
the ancient ones the ancient ones love
these ones
i actually got to focus up now
[Music]
please ancient ones give me give me more
straight sticks
what a straight
hmm no no no you don't
oh you listen to my fingers
i wouldn't even bet on our spotlist what
the hell you guys have
no you don't believe in me hey what
about commodity i thought you guys liked
tacoma
believe in our power combined the power
of love wasn't enough for something
gotta the enemy is just too
too strong and too big yeah i mean
on top of us in my land so believe
believe in your selves
thanks for the encouragement um actually
no it's actually looking bad for me oh
damn it
oh god she's going all out now
she's ready to destroy us she's not
playing anymore
oh god no yeah
oh god
oh my god
oh
please oh no i didn't just need a purple
i'm burned no matter
can you see the whole thing as well in
pueblo i don't think so
just touch this
[Music]
well i'll give it a shot all night i
believe in you
oh thanks you believe in your enemy well
that's very nice of you
keep your eyes keep your enemies close
and your enemies close your friends
your enemies close when your enemies
close and your enemies closer very nice
i quote not i quote it it's something
like that
a little dead today do we get some
sleepy asmr reaper
reaper sleeping with the sleepy reaper
again
now you're having some trouble just as i
was with your words
thank you i'm just impersonating you at
this point
i actually tell you so much how are you
feeling
uh
[Applause]
my dude is so cute playing kendama
i there's still one more round i can
make it back
thank you for doing the hard work for us
oh no problems
it's so nice to have someone rely on you
know
oh my gosh really that powerful
goodness gracious
oops
it's okay not to make mistakes it's okay
i'd encourage you to continue making
them please yeah i feel like
yeah they're a good thing i don't know
if i can make it out of this one alive
probably not
um
[Music]
yes that's what i wanted
or something yes please oh my god yeah
ice cold what's cooler than the
encounter with some aroma oils
to relax your senses that reminds me i'm
gonna go do that after the stream is
over
i just wanted to stream some fried
chicken
fried chicken oh i can send you some i
have a lot thanks
i have some people to sacrifice sorry
and not people totally not
i mean like you know
it's not like i fry my employees or
anything like that
my child is panicking my child is
panicking you didn't hear me
clear your ears everyone that's not what
i said
my rival is totally fine i
or maybe not
[Music]
oh god
callie's just really cheap
[Music]
okay
let's do all against each other okay
yeah then it's time for me to
kick your ass callie wow okay that
escalated quickly all right
you're allowed to feel that way i in
turn will hurt you severely so don't
worry
oh my god that's pretty good
bring it on cali
certainly it would be my pleasure bring
it up
oh my head hurts god damn
it's okay it's okay it's okay
let's go concentration
concentration it's the battle of the
gods no repeats
or hesitation i'll go first you go
second
category is foods
what did you guys concentration 64.
what did you ask me or hesitation i'll
go first
what are you talking about what's
kelly's saying i don't understand she's
saying
why did she say my old cat
we're all confused it's an old it's an
old chant from the school yard
which school you wanted
i've went to school i guess
lessons whatever stop swimming
he got me really very dead for a moment
oh
uh who loses like who has the least wins
at the end
must in their follow-up stream whatever
it is yes
and puyo at almost as possible as many
sentences as possible
you would be like uh hello everyone
how is it going puyo are you sure you
want to do that
i
or yeah everything i remember well
okay which i i guess it's uh maybe not
maybe from now on because me and kevin
played together sometimes
not so hard to count that
no okay from this game on which i
[Music]
from the game before so this is the
second game that we're counting
let's see let's see
i should already try to learn how to if
i can do it put up
you should practice right now and then
practice and bleal
how's it going is everyone doing good
i'm actually enjoying it i would like to
get this batsu game
[Laughter]
you should just take it i tried to win
anyway but i would enjoy having this
uh it's brought upon me
[Laughter]
i can't believe you actually like saying
it for you i like it
i wanted a you call that in japanese you
call it the uh
gobi puyo gobi does that that's the part
at the end of the sentence i don't know
what you would call it in english
because no one does it i guess
is there a way to get an english winner
chad seems to think the same
[Music]
yeah i just ignore all the friend
requests for young
there is no meaning in sending me friend
requests guys we all
give up all of them i heard you guys
rejected
kyrah's marriage proposal for you where
did you hear that
from your
oh
[Laughter]
i'm not that smart i think you all got
you all know that i'm not that smart
though
it's working brian i don't see cat
oh no oh no oh no
no problem for y'all
no no is doing that
retry uh you guys okay with other people
okay
i will not you will not get me to say
well i won't do it i saw my life
before my eyes i want i want cali to use
puyo and her and
at the end of her sentences after no i
want to hear that
we gotta we gotta line up our combos
okay
i don't know how to do that i think my
brain is that big no somebody isn't
either
no it's a conspiracy stop it
chap don't you wanna hear it don't you
wanna hear kelly go for your foil
i wanna hear it i definitely wanna hear
it
it's not funny when i do it i've been
doing it the whole time now please
it has to be calling me out no exactly
oh no she's working towards it
i'm working towards this world oh god
what the hell kelly when did you get so
good for y'all
the game i just really don't want to say
that
she's motivated you want to get super
motivated
it's cute it is
come on tally accepted accept it
stop it no wait are we only counting the
last place or like
you know i don't know really i think it
will be very obvious in the end who had
the most losses anyway
i don't even think we need to think
about it are you already preparing for a
camera
how you would like me hi oh my
gosh
you know you have to do it so that i
don't lose only callie loses you i don't
know i can't aim my attacks
yes but you don't succeed
when you get
[Music]
or my third
that that was the last time i lose we
believe in you
really thank you
you know you're so sweet yeah you're
really so sweet i'm so
lucky you guys thank you that's sweet
for you i also want to hear you
why don't we all say yeah
[Laughter]
i would like to not do
i this that's something i'd not like to
do oh my goodness
would you prefer it
no maybe absolutely incorrect
no wait i messed up maybe she is
incorrect
now just accept it
oh my god
do your best we got it we gotta get we
gotta get cali to say
puyo i'm drawing
you're not making it easy for me you
gotta try your vest i believe
[Music]
come on give me give me more give me
more reds come on yes
oh you did it nice spin something
oh my god yes
i can stay alive for a little while
longer but cali is doing pretty good oh
god oh
okay i gotta focus gotta get cali
[Laughter]
i had a great time for you
but it's still we still have a long time
to go there's so many chances for me to
win puyo and turn this whole thing
around for you
[Music]
why because
kelly's like super focused she's like
really desperate now trying to not say
puyo
do it you won't get me too
i i'm putting on my gamer hat
you can't see it but oh gotta get i
gotta get kelly's
wheel never and that's not gonna work
because
i always die first
[Music]
how did i win the game
good job good job
everyone uh i don't know let's just do
the way
whatever way you want to play how about
that okay yeah
it's your choice actually stresses me
out i
i just wanna i wanna use tetris now that
i know the whole thing i'd like to try
it
[Music]
what should i do kelly is getting too
good kylie's supposed to be warming up
it is beginners it is simply beginner's
luck
delightful or tetris
okay here we go surprise sir past your
limits okay i will do
i just realized i am i getting the same
things and what if i copy exactly what
she does
oh my god it's already too late for that
but i feel like we're getting the same
like wheels maybe
now it's already too late yeah it's too
much it's too late
it's too late to apologize i had the
same thing in my head
because someone like at least gave me a
chance to play the game
i gotta kill you in order to kill callie
okay
but like we can't i think we counted
i guess i mean i guess callie loses as
well when i look
um strange line of thinking
[Music]
okay
yeah thank god oh thank god
no did you forget how to speak english
[Laughter]
sometimes i get to leave to speak
english
when i get too lazy to speak english i
should speak um
[Laughter]
what am i doing uh
we're almost there we're almost there
oh no oh my god well what were you
sending me it's not happening
it's not helping me no i'll donate
one job
[Laughter]
wow
oh one last call again i'll master the
whole thing i'll master it
like right now i'm going to put this
away for now i have no idea no i
shouldn't have died first
i shouldn't have done that no i'm
now i'm f-worded i think we're yeah
we're really getting into
the same point i think so when you start
off i should just really
maybe next time you try a bit slower and
so i try to follow you and then we can
defeat kelly maybe
but no i don't think i can do that that
that that requires some skill
which i don't have let's be real skill
is up
[Laughter]
looking good
oh
yes give me purple yes thank you
how about this
do you believe in miracles
i missed opportunity oh my goodness
what's up after you just drop on me tell
us kelly
to do that no excuse for slipping right
now
[Music]
oh no no
you guys are
i've had it with tetris so i'll go ahead
and do a
run all right
you do so good each time well thank you
chad i don't know i i'm getting better
you guys are getting better everyone
[Music]
last trope i guess yeah
as long as you keep as long as you act
no no greetings
[Music]
i'm gonna go for this one time let's see
how it goes
oh i have a feeling kelly's gonna
kelly's gonna crumble us
[Music]
i can see the future
do you have a vision yes the ancient
ones are called
yo
i want to win i
yeah i think we all do i want to win for
you
damn wait
uh same you've been waiting
don't worry about hey that's a good
point
don't worry about it
wait hold on no no no no no oh no i got
greedy
no why not do that it makes it
impossible for me
[Music]
i need a long boy give me a long boy a
long boy yeah one of the longboards
okay i'm whatever i'm just gonna do this
that's okay
[Music]
no no no you can look here we can do it
i don't know what's inside
i don't know what i'm doing i give up
oh yeah
all right i think you gotta you gotta
brush up on your puyos
um are people gonna actually force me to
do that i guess
yeah it was your idea though
yeah i mean i don't
i don't i don't mind it's cool what's my
next stream oh my gosh
what is your next stream do i have my
next stream is
uh well tomorrow i have the day off
uh-huh um my next stream is
fire emblem which is gonna be a long
stream i usually
stream fire emblem for like six hours
good luck for you
maybe i'll just do a quick gorilla
tomorrow maybe for one hour and mario
cheating for six hours
well maybe actually for you
games
it's not cheating shut up chad it's not
cheating
is that cheating that's really good
cheating not cheating on the next dream
i never said
that
you are not the one to decide the rules
okay
you are not the one to decide well
you mean six hours of me saying yes
it's hours of this game for six hours
all clear
hello
is
[Laughter]
it's okay it's okay i
i'm used to it i'm used to it no i
believe in you
you wanna keep me in the practice run
yeah
how did i do that you can totally do it
but that was when cali was
still a noob and now she picked up some
basic knowledge about the game
i sure did very quickly
whoa whoa
[Music]
actually getting so hungry yeah i always
hungry when i stream even though like i
eat right before the stream
yeah people will like that i don't
understand why they would like it
yeah if people like something that i
don't like i just don't get it
it's so weird okay i mean you don't do
i it people people be people people like
different dreams
that's true okay actually
i actually have to focus i can't focus
when i'm hungry
i'm forcing myself to do a gorilla
tomorrow instead of uh
taking a break oh man that's better than
doing a six hour
screen gone
six hours
what if i what if i do a stream where i
just literally say nothing
then i also don't have to add meal oh
just look at the camera for one hour and
just
stare into your soul i'm sure someone
would enjoy that very much
holy i think yeah there was a youtube
like a youtuber like in boomer times
who did that like she looked uh into the
camera
for all of her videos and said nothing
and sometimes she would say hello does
someone know who i'm talking about i
will not say the name but do you guys
know what i'm talking about
[Music]
do you know what i'm talking about nope
you don't know maybe not i guess you're
not a boomer
oops no why i didn't do that
i didn't send that down there
no no i'm not talking about the girl of
the peas
oh
much older than that
[Music]
someone might
today well you also made a lot of weird
noises there young lady
i don't know what you're talking about
it's just a normal day for taco noises
compilation there is uh aren't there
like compilations like cups of uh weird
youtube noises
with weird uh beach river noises i think
i saw him in that yeah
today is a great day for them to collect
[Music]
content
oh i guess there's clippers who are into
that
i love you wait no stop
i think we don't even have to count
anymore
you ready
[Applause]
just a little bit you kind of walked
into that one you know when you came up
with it
like you know maybe
[Music]
maybe things would have been different
maybe callie was just lucky
you know oh
[Laughter]
you're welcome clippers
there are a lot of good cookie bloody
noises in the stream huh compilation of
chiara noises
i'm trying to make up for it um cali
concentrating so much that she doesn't
talk
tell us about something that happened
today did something happen today
you're trying to confuse me and make me
not win
no i already lost one
archived
[Music]
oh yeah i'm actually practicing your
song as well
why are you doing this i'm not
okay good job yeah keep going keep going
it's not fair
also shrek swamp infected my chat
shrek slump infected your trucks yes
no just everyone's spamming green hearts
oh i don't like it
why aren't you dude you want to go back
to the lobby i want to play tetris again
yeah
why is the green doll white ring because
i sang many shrek songs look at them
infecting my child
in many tricks and i replaced some of
the lyrics with the with the word shrek
and i started spamming the green hearts
oh that's cool yeah i love red
the deadbeats love shrek
did you think somebody wants i don't
know i was just about to be
i don't i just have to like slide in
just like yeah somebody told me
once told me i can't can you just say it
between practice
all right is getting good because
there's a bunch of green characters
oh my god like three green let's be
greece again
[Music]
yes fitting that i'm on the green team
oh
can we all be we can't be nothing team
right all in the same team i don't think
the game would let us
yeah well here we go
anyway i also hit eight eight uh
what is it yes i did
i did during this
during the karaoke or yeah well i i did
i reached it right before the karaoke
and then i mentioned it and then i said
please don't unsubscribe and then many
people got 100
but then they subscribed back when they
heard that i wasn't going to just
[Music]
it would have been the trick if they
defeated
i won't stop singing until
now and then like they like keep like
unscripting to keep hearing you sing
actually i did one of those before but
then um
i reached it like after like five
minutes or so ah so i was like i'm gonna
keep on singing so i kept on singing for
an hour or so
ah i guess that's why
yeah because i'm still i mean at that
point i'm celebrating now
celebrating for reaching the marathon
which um loves me and i also raised in
my phone recently
ah yay
and there's also a lot of stones on my
field can someone stop
like i'm trying to celebrate our
awesomes together
oh my god oh wait that was the wrong one
no
stop it that wasn't me
i saw it fly from your direction
[Music]
was that a challenge
i'm not good at it but i wouldn't say
i'm really bad at it
exactly everyone starts somewhere yeah
there you go anyway i've messed up so
oh well
we all messed up sometimes yeah i really
boned myself no
darn it you burned yourself i'm sorry
but
my understanding is someone who's first
language is not english that sounds
very weird to me you're boning yourself
isn't that kind of a wrong
way of i mean i don't family friendly
streams
now listen here we don't do that here
those two
like family nonsenses here i guess we
don't i mean i definitely don't
know i've been doing it wrong time
no no wow but you're doing it your way
all right
you're saying your family not as dreams
as family are family friendly can
someone
come confirmed totally no streams are
i guess they are it could be nope
have you ever seen have you ever have
you ever said the f word on your string
i said fudge oh wow you can't go
like that wow
so you you never said the outfit up
until now
i not very cold
wow that's i've said
yeah i swear a couple times without my
mistake
it's weird oh
like completely you know not saying
anything at all
of those words um
i'm doing good how long is this going to
be like that
[Laughter]
i wish i was doing just fine gotta go
can you guys do an off collab karaoke
yeah
yeah we're planning on it eventually is
there like english songs and japanese
karaoke i forget
yeah yeah yeah there are there are no i
mean like if they are in the mouse i
mean
if they are in the machine yeah in the
machine yeah they are
like plenty of them ah the new songs
come in
kind of slow but they do come
oh man
[Music]
because i feel like why would you do
such a thing
because my my hp is running low
interesting are you implying that dr
oopsie doesn't raise your hp
it lowers it in the long run
[Music]
okay
oh
well done
you don't want to lose me one more time
against me do you i don't think we want
to see you losing again
it could hurt your reputation right i
can't lose a reputation if i never had
one
that's what i call a comeback my friends
congratulations i mean come back
compensator phoenix's uh
specialty exactly but i think i
think it's a bit too late i already lost
too many times to make up for it
by now uh you never know
at least you came back in style and
you've done yeah
how are you
come on come on
[Music]
hungry hungry no
i should have probably saved at home
that was an accident oh that was an
accident oh no
yes
you gotta go for the phoenix town okay
uh uh phoenix down
only happens when youtube bring
terminates my channel hashtag phoenix
down
thanks guys for everyone participating
funny you know phoenix down is a revival
item
yeah in which game final fantasy
yeah see people pointed that out to me
but not here
oh yeah i already said oh god it's
coming closer that was close
stuff is closed coming close no no no no
no no no
[Music]
i don't know what i'm singing this is a
random song that no that doesn't even
exist
so copyright can't strike me cause
copyright got nothing on me
oh yeah yeah yeah youtube got nothing on
me need me again if you can
but you got nothing on me youtube you
got nothing on me
youtube you got nothing on me
youtube phoenix down only happens
when you cook your eyes and you
have your ass in luke
oh
it died for a moment how do you know my
child
i want to change back to puyo hi what
that was your channel saying that my
child is down
mm-hmm it was down for a moment what how
did
my child was just uh telling me that
your your
chat was broken it was i was i was
noticing that while i was singing what
the hell
i thought it was only me maybe it was my
wait what was your beautiful singing
yeah it was gonna handle things like a
magical spell or something
okay girl carve uncle
i think we are getting closer to the
final matches all right i think uh we
know who the uh
who the boss game winner
quote unquote winner
i don't think it's that obvious i think
we have to start some recounts
first comes denial
[Laughter]
i mean
i mean in some worlds maybe
pounding weeks differently and then i
would have won
[Music]
makes sense right maybe i'll just i just
terminate
uh youtube again
people people um have made up a theory
though that it wasn't me but it was cali
as a revenge for me
oh or it was i mean like there's these
two theories either it was american with
county what do you guys think was it
kelly rowland isn't it i think amelia is
a little more likely than me amelia's
okay
ground pounding you know yeah
i might not be able to tell it from i
mean there has been evidence
everywhere on the internet even on my
debut re-w stream i showed the evidence
of uh i'm a ground pounding uh
coming into the youtube offices ready to
ground pounds looking really ripped and
stuff
oh
i saw that coming that was a little
quicker than i thought
a little bit too quick here real speedy
you're a speedy one you're a speedy one
you're
you're you're a snake
got em it sure is about to be the
holiday is that
yes holidays oh my god wait
guys it's eight eight days until
christmas
now here's last minute maybe nine days
for you enough
oh nine nine but i
i personally from where i'm from we
celebrate christmas
only in the evening the christmas
morning on the next day is like nobody
cares about it anymore people
don't care so we give gifts we open the
gifts in the evening christmas evening
not in the morning
yeah we usually open it in the morning
i can't wait that long
to be fair we usually just like you know
open it like
we know what's in there already yeah
oh why why why would you know darn it
because
you know because they're buying you what
you're asking for
yeah yes are you that spoiled
charlie's like super focused her eyes
are scaring me
wait is her eyes wide open staring at
the screen
i can see it this is how it gets to be
sometimes
um it's not santa bringing the presents
it's a it's the christkind which is an
angel
oh it's an angel bringing little
presents to
how is it is it the same for you know
right
uh no oh in the underworld we do things
a bit differently
it's a child angel though yeah
those are those australian um traditions
yes this is australian
oh it's a it's a little angel
riding on a kangaroo bringing us
pregnant kangaroo
[Music]
oh i got distracted by the kangaroo
i play in the kangaroo don't believe me
i i i know this is wrong but it's indeed
a child uh angel that's that the clutch
the clutch
[Music]
how many rounds left in like this like
round of applause go back to the lobby
uh if i win once more then we go back to
the lobby
okay no more say no more
because i'm looking at the time we said
like one and a half hours
yes and this might be the last match
what all right let's make it count
i will win oh god
no no no no we don't need to have space
speedy you can be slow you know
you can't just take it off
no reason to stress yourself
oh
oh you guys don't hear the voice of my
character i keep thinking
oh i didn't hear it i have the musical
huh
oh my god
i'm barely alive oh my god
why
oh my god no
i'm still alive i'm desperate oh
no i don't believe in anything
you believe in yourself no i don't
believe in anything
no confidence no
oh this might be up
[Laughter]
you might win this one
[Music]
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait
wait wait we got another round
i'm proud of you stop talking and i
actually concentrate i have a chance of
running
i do oh my god but i'm an entertainer at
heart you know i'm an entertainer
yes i have to talk gotta give i gotta
give the people some
money yes oh my god you guys disappeared
on my
uh room but that's okay oh you also
disappeared for
me oh it's okay it's fine you're your
final stretch so
yeah final stretch
this map probably will not change
anything on the uh official
outcome but i will still fight until the
bitter end
and show you that the phoenix never
gives up i told you this guy's a phoenix
never gives up
stop it stop it just stop just stop stop
stop stop stop
no
[Laughter]
i panicked
you know if you could do me this honor
and
play maybe you don't have to give it to
me but like at least like
give me a chance all right we re
re-think
oh man one thing iana better watch out
but it is still chilling no stone blocks
on
the board
another chain is he gonna do it um
oh and she connected the green the the
little green
i'll give you ten more seconds hey what
what seven
six five what's going down
[Music]
uh
you made me really nervous there you
know made me really nervous
all according to plan
um if i just stay calm if i just stay
calm
i have a chance you do it's the final
countdown
we're just we're just really nice trying
to get those copyright strikes today
aren't we
okay i have challenged uh my luck with
that many times before and nothing
happened so
i don't want to text messages foreign
oh wait a second
this this game is taking a while huh yes
[Music]
now it's not not looking so good anymore
attack by the way if you press a button
oh my god
[Music]
um it's not so obvious who who has to do
the bachelor game i don't think it's so
obvious so we will have
sure about that yes i think so i don't
know
let's do it let's do a count uh let me
check uh see here
it says uh kiara
that's not counting it's just that's the
same way yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
well i will i will take the honor of
doing the batsu game of the in my
following stream which does which
doesn't have to be the final one it just
has to be the following stream
at the end of every sentence i say for
the whole stream
okie dokie
yay
that must be wrong what the hell but i
believe that you that eno won 11 times i
do believe that
um
wait actually
kelly won one time enough won
13 times and i won two times
[Music]
does this mean that we get a puya from
cali what nope i'll never do it
come on tables
doesn't it
nope how about we both do it callie how
about we
do it don't cheat i never agreed to it
okay how
how about you do it uh because you said
you have uh a segment after
after the stream and see what how about
you do it
not the second i can't i'm too tired i
might scream tomorrow though i might
stream tomorrow
[Laughter]
if i do say it it's not going to be all
the time because i don't feel like it
okay okay every
yes yes yes yes that was fun wasn't it
anyone who has some something to say
like announcement or whatever it put on
uh you guys go ahead i don't have much i
think i've got nothing
just a regular all week i guess okay
same here
i think all our schedules are up so if
you guys want to check those out
for when you're streaming oh but we
finally after a long time we have a a
full member collab oh yeah
at the end of the like friday for some
saturday for others
she's already started she's already
started bless you
[Music]
yes it does i guess oh my god
are you dying oh no
just trying to get away from the field
all right everyone in my stream at least
we say at the end of
[Music]
i'm glad i need to go get a drink that's
a good choice
which is why you guys are getting dj joe
for the odd show again so i know
we were supposed to stop but i need to
go get a drink so yeah okay
anyway with that bye-bye
you