[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
um
kick it again
[Music]
uh
oh
that's understandable Manuel
that you can't make the whole stream
hello okay
no I didn't sleep that late but
um I left ama's room
a little bit past midnight
because I was like sorry girls sorry
girls I'm gonna leave now
because I no I didn't say that but I am
a smart person because I know I have a
stream early next day so I will be I
will be the responsible one and leave
the room before everybody else
um
[\h__\h] I need like tea I don't have tea
I have a lot I know
ah
[Music]
um
I need oil yeah
do you hear this
uh I wonder if anybody else is awake
how about a throat candy huh
um
I didn't have breakfast yet and they
canceled my breakfast order but I I
ordered the Netherland
um I have a door that sounds similar to
you
look at all the Rings yeah breakfast at
Tiffany
wait
Breakfast at Tiffany's and bottles of
bubbles girls love tattoos who like
getting in trouble lashes and diamonds i
t and machines by myself all of my
favorite things
been through some bad [\h__\h] I should be a
sad [\h__\h] who would have thought I'd
turn me to a Savage rather be tied up
with calls and nut strings write my own
Jacks like I write what I sing my wrist
stop watching my neck is flossing make
big deposits my glass is popping you
like my hair defects just bought it I
see it I like it I want it I got it yeah
I want it I got it I wore it I got it I
want it I got it I want it I got it you
like my hair gee thanks just bought it
see I see it I like it I want it I got
it yeah
she doesn't even say anything about
rings in the song now you don't
understand why I'm singing it
it's called Seven Rings The song is
called seven rings I mean I have more
than seven rings but
you don't get it you wouldn't get it you
wouldn't get it
uh am I engage here yeah uh I'm doing
hands only today maybe
uh
thank you to the amazing
gorgeous Flawless blue for making these
rings for me uh am I wearing the correct
amount right now I wonder
also I love how my Elgato is German
kinds ignite
um
absolutely look how pretty my hands are
my chicken
actually it's not correct because I
think at the moment I only have four
rings but
uh well
I think I I think I only have four wings
one I can only tell you have rings but I
have like specific rings
yeah just joined why is it 720p cause I
didn't remember that
uh
that I would have
settings on 720p on my laptop again
yeah but at least that one that assures
us to have a smoother stream Maybe
um 720p is plenty
that's good
not good tonight that's all yeah imagine
me punching you in the face of these
this is what these rings are really
worth uh getting all for if you have all
the rings on your hands you can do some
real damage to someone's face
[Laughter]
what who's smoother
where did I ride smoother
um
thank you Joe star what's up
why why am I 19 Joe
I I said it what ah
shut up
um I just woke up
and you're doing this stupid ass dad
jokes
what the [\h__\h] what what am I I forgot
what it's called casual what what am I
doing
what's my mode
something casual right normal casual
what no more casual hard I'm oh it's
cold hard oh my God so cool
okay because I thought it's called
normal because it's pretty normal
um
but when I say it like this
it definitely seems cooler because it
seems like it's more difficult yeah
gamer gamer
ah
so
hi everybody it's my first
no not my first stream from Japan but
it's my first stream from the the aen
house
yesterday I set up everything
I'm quite proud my setup looks pretty
nice pretty clean I ended up bringing my
own laptop
um because Ina told me about
uh the other one that they had
um I think we're like supposed to say
something at some point but now they
said it's still okay but
we like got a lot of equipment sponsored
guys
myth house isn't just Sims anymore yeah
yay
yeah the chair the chairs oh nice
um
also
um they had like two different
uh like what do you call them like uh
sound board mixer thing is to choose
from but the one that was already here
uh what's it called
something media
um should notice
or so
um they I don't know they have one of
those that they have a like a mixer
paint it looks pretty cool and Ian was
using it but she told me that it's like
pretty complicated to set up
um
so Ava media yeah she told me it's
pretty complicated to set up I wanted to
give it a try but since it's pretty
complicated and I just I was I just
wanted to set up everything
smoothly I ended up just going with the
go XLR yeah
ghostly has more choices of like effects
and so on too
ah
yeah yeah
um yeah better to do that than to suffer
from
all the complicated things
um by the way let me see
how's my order going how's my order
oh it's coming soon but I ordered
something now just eat on stream
um
what type of food did I order
well
I originally wanted to order something
that's not bread but now I ended up
ordering something that's bread but one
one of it is like a hot bread
because it's like a
like a hot sandwich
with with some
eggs and stuff and then also croissants
yeah I did this
um
and yeah
um it's gonna come in a minute
I might actually mute
so
because
I don't want you guys to hear the
doorbell
I mean I don't know but
you know okay I I see I see it
foreign
[Music]
that's a little paranoid well I don't I
if I was alone here I wouldn't care so
much
uh but you see I live with some girls
who are very very understandably worried
about their
safety and all that so
um I want to be like you know
the one
now let me be a bit quiet because I
chose put in front of my door
peeps
it's finished
ah
okay there we go sound is there
okay
let's go my food is there wow okay I'm
gonna go to the door
[Music]
all right
I got my breakfast
occurred so much
oh yeah I was using YouTube
um when I was like at the airport
because
um
you know I had some
some layover time and
um
and YouTube the game
and uh I wanted to watch something on my
phone but I realized the only headphones
had earphones earbuds that I have are
um are are with like a you know the old
Jack but nowadays phones only use
um the USBC type ones
yeah this [\h__\h] sucks and I I didn't I
didn't bring I have I have a pair of
USBC ones but I can't find them anymore
so the only ones I had with me were
normal Jack so I was like wait don't I
have the YouTube app on my switch
which I did and then I just listened to
um more of Kunk on Britain on my YouTube
um
that was fun that was good all right oh
my God that's so loud I'm also loud holy
[\h__\h] ah oh wow okay uh
holy [\h__\h] shush
ah
okay
um
that's still loud
okay
Maybe
around here
oh let's see how loud that will get
you
[Music]
laughs
haven't been to a streaming so long
hello welcome
I didn't upload uh
Fire Emblem engage
[Music]
don't engage me I can't engage so early
in the morning
yeah
um in the airplane I did two skirmishes
so I didn't do any story but I did two
skirmishes
they were so easy they were so easy yeah
um I got some I I got an insane amount
of iron I think it was iron or Steel
from it
I'm so tired I'm so tired but I I did
steal a Red Bull from
um
in the studio
so I have a Red Bull just in case I
can't uh handle anymore but
Matt I did not do parallelog no only
like two skirmishes
um but it was good in the airplane I got
my my the whole First Flight I was doing
Fire Emblem
so
um
way better than being bored as hell it
was the first plane didn't have a screen
you know
okay so how's this audio balance
is it probably a little bit too loud for
you guys too I'm gonna do it a little
bit before look
for me to okay how about now
wow
that's fine sounds good
[Music]
beautiful
I'll do it like this okay
talk to someone because I think it might
support ah
yep
well she they don't say much
[Music]
just a bit louder than me really
give me your girl out
no
uh
reference support I already did all of
them
mmm the breakfast smells so good I want
to eat it but I still have the fruit
candy in my mouth
[Music]
yeah I did a lot of things guys I did I
was I was very very good
[Music]
um
I think the first time I saw this was a
phylum stream
I live in life for emblem but here I am
two years later yay thank you
don't let your food get cold yeah
you know what
I guess I don't know
okay so do you guys mind if I eat my
breakfast
the warm thing the warm thing I'll eat
first and then the other thing maybe
sometime later this is this one oh yeah
it's a warm thing
[Music]
oh
yeah I hope that's not spinach but salad
in there yeah I think that's salad oh
god
oh the the bread to other ingredients
balance kind of off
it's too much bread
and give the rest of the bread to Ahmed
ah
[Music]
I don't think this is scrambled eggs I
think this is just egg salad warmed up
you don't call that scrambled eggs I
think
it's good though
I love I love Japanese egg salad
[Music]
dog is dead
okay why won't my dog died let's go
[Music]
I didn't download the next DLC it's like
Anna is it worth it it's so expensive
it's so expensive
[Music]
oh I already bought it
that's the same thing
hmm
[Music]
oh oh how do I get it
is that what the other parallels were
about
because I looked at the map of the
Divine parallel map and there were some
understood I couldn't access yet when I
was in the plane
[Music]
yeah I thought it was just Ado cards
which would have been very expensive if
you think about it
okay
I guess the game didn't update did it
maybe it did
come on
I'm playing right here I think I did
oh I'm not connected to the internet oh
oh
[Music]
um
I'm not in the mood to connect to the
internet now though
[Music]
um
I don't need it today
maybe next time
I would be too strong
if I got the other emblems already now
anyway
right I got Kiki are the others super
overpowered too
and someone tests them already
hmm
and besides
blue would have to remake these Rings
all over again
if I got old and cam is pretty good
they're broken
they got hot lady I know
um
[Music]
starting pretty good
foreign
[Music]
this is how
I currently have the Rings
[Music]
um
there's no particular meaning I wasn't
sure who to give Tiki to
um
I gave her to college soon and I played
a bit with cockatoo
okay yeah she's strong well my voice is
so [\h__\h]
oh man maybe I should go grab a tea from
the
[Music]
um vending machine
I know I don't know about using Anna
[Music]
um
I'm so sorry but
the other is that we have the other
Majors like ivy
are like strong and so
um
I have too many majors yeah
[Music]
um
she gets ridiculous growth I've seen
like videos I've watched a couple of
Fire Emblem videos
uh
like advice videos like
how to play the game
as if I didn't already know
how to play the game and
[Music]
um
which characters to reclass
stuff like that
[Music]
um
what did I learn I think most things are
new already but
one thing
I was made very aware of
is to give
um who was it
um
[Music]
that one emblem I have to give him to
everybody but everybody learns his
inherited skill
to move around after their turn Panther
app was secured
now I wanted to do that but then I
realized oh I don't have cigarette right
now
um but now I also understand like a bit
more even though it should have been
obvious when you guys first told me but
I wasn't quite you know in the zone
but now understand why you guys wanted
me you know to give him around
you're just trying them oh I guess so
bad
um
yeah it's quite costly um
[Music]
just passed around
and our non-writers feels lame Ohio
well I mean he's helping he's helping
it's really just egg salad
oh my God what up what a scam I mean
it's yummy but what a scam advertised as
scrambled egg spot sandwich
please play your game pretty much of
nothing relationship
[Music]
I'm eating a sandwich I'm eating
breakfast okay
it's not even 10 a.m here okay
hmm
oh Bond six oh this one I forced
this one I upgraded
um
whatever you call it
[Music]
I'm almost done
but everything's like
falling out in the end
Fallout mansion
[Music]
and someone must be feeding me
and choking me intentionally because I
have my hands up in the air
came out of nowhere
[Music]
for turning the stream on
ah
[Music]
one more bite
not really
I knocked
I waited for
two minutes
didn't open I went back
she asked me
[Music]
um
on this card koala did you knock and
said yeah that was me then she probably
went to the door
after that
and then there was no one there because
I was back in my room and then uh
because she asked me did you knock
after that I went out again to knock
again but by that time she was back to
her computer I think
no she didn't
oh
[Music]
okay my hands are full of egg
that was good
and orange
but now I'm gonna think about it I feel
like I should have ordered some tea hmm
okay
oh
Papa
yum yum yum
yum yum
okay
I think I'm ready to go straight into
story time
do I drink run Oh I wanna a kind of
water
[Music]
is anyone else awake
can't ask them to bring me something
go for it
Medina she's usually always so awake uh
but
let me see
[Music]
are you awake
I don't think any of them are away
because
not one of them has a stream right
[Music]
and it's not even 10. I feel like they
probably stayed up longer because also I
saw I mean especially
and uh who else someone you know
probably
on Twitter I saw them tweeting at like 3
A.M
what the [\h__\h]
why would you tweet solid
I know I know it says me but like
but
okay I don't think we can really have a
discussion about this
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
don't want to talk
oh I slept I I slept early these pastors
or tried to but then I would wake up so
and this night I also I took a melatonin
in but I still I woke up a million times
uh
I don't know I feel like the bed is also
kind of uncomfortable I feel the Springs
I'mma said she likes it but I don't like
it
I literally feel the springs
it's not too hard but I feel this brings
okay we get it we get it we get it now
thank you
let me move on
and that's not good right I need a
Topper but I'm not gonna buy a Topper
I'm just not staying here for a year
maybe the couch the couch is not big
enough for me to sleep on
[\h__\h] my throat is so [\h__\h] up
[Music]
oh my God
oh tea woman
go get a drink okay I'm getting a drink
we'll see you in a moment really it's
just like a moment like really just a
moment okay okay you've waited so long
you can wait two more minutes okay
um
[Music]
foreign
ah
you you are
you're putting on my fluffy socks
[Music]
sorry
[Applause]
I got some
oh hot tea
[Music]
um
um oh
it's like magic okay let's go
I think
I did everything beforehand
uh uh
I think but let's check
um
not much will the rain here
Let's uh trade no that's mad oh my God
why is this
oh broken
uh let's swap with some
normal amounts uh Anna you know what
I'll take yours thank you
okay
um
[Music]
but I don't think I'm taking her so
that's okay okay
because this this what do you call the
the cross thingy on the controller
I feel like there's something in there
but it's not
working properly the d-pad yeah
[Music]
uh
eight months oh my God
that sounds like a lot
thank you yeah I didn't uh like update I
guess yeah it's okay all right uh [\h__\h]
um yeah I guess let's begin
chapter yeah
and snooze
[Music]
Plus Nails it's about the Rings
and the bracelet thing is so this is
song
it's very
[\h__\h] Sandy oh my homies hate sand
well the queendom's land is covered in
deserts I believe this one is called
Tula
because you've no don't noticed it's
much hotter than an illusion
my fear I may melt what now Divine One
we better head straight to the Palace
the hounds haven't gotten there first
during my time in Lucia the four hounds
did pay a few visits to Seoul but they
came back empty-handed each time so I
expect the palace is unharmed thanks Ivy
pretty handy having an enemy as a friend
huh I will choose to take that as a
compliment
which emblem ring was entrusted to solm
the radiant hero
said to be among the most powerful
needless to say it would be quite a boon
sounds like exactly what we need right
now let's get going
radiant hero hukudabi Ikea
I know you can
let's see
which way to the Palace again Divine one
I believe we passed that enormous Rock
earlier oh my God really
all this terrain looks the same to me I
wish I could help
geography comes only from Maps
Prince Diamond your nations are allied
with song why don't you go into the
palace before I did but you can't quite
a long time ago
I don't remember the way I traveled from
fear in a I've got no clue how to get
there from ellucia so none of us knows
where to go great
useless all right I'll say it we're lost
I'm afraid so you can't afford to waste
time
I wonder if there's a landmark to go by
e now
okay raria
what she's sweating you don't look like
you're from around here what's with the
outfits huh
sorry I didn't mean to startle you but I
took one look at thoughts of myself so
they are lost it's gestures and uh who
are you who am I I'm this guy here to
keep the peace in Tula desert call me
fogato yes as captain of the Sentinels
it's my duty to help people in need
you fine folks need a hand just let me
know
thanks for that as for myself I'm the
Divine dragon
we go oh
you're telling me the Divine dragon is
here in my desert here in Wild Desert
yes
I had no idea I'm so sorry I didn't mean
to be rude you weren't there's no need
to be formal with me
yeah he's got Charisma that's cool
but hey brings you up casual yeah
so we're on our way to Solon Palace but
we don't know how to get there this is
your lucky day come on just follow me if
I know how to get anywhere it's the
palace you don't mind
of course I don't you know what's out
there sand as far as yesterday and I
would rather you not have to deal with
that huh
[Music]
thank you fogato we appreciate your help
I don't sweat it oh you know what I do
have a quick errand to take care of
first
and Aaron what kind of errand more of a
mission see not too long ago these
freaky creatures started appearing
everywhere as captain of the Sentinels
when I get a report about a problem in
the desert I take care of it sorry about
this the sparkly eyes remind me right
after I'm done actually why don't we
come with you we can help oh that'd be
great my friends went ahead of me let's
go meet up with them
he's nice
um I like his uh uh voice acting too
sometimes he has this like a weird
accent that's kind of cute
the problem's even worse than I expected
you're late I think you wanted us to die
out here you got us
these creatures would have made a meal
of us
oh God I forgot his buddies what the
heck I brought help
what do you mean to help
oh Andrea my pie is friend this is
really gonna blow your mind Laura
foreign
Dragon nice to meet you
the Divine dragon
what were you thinking bringing the
Divine Dragon here the fire
like two scoops
swirling together in the desert
toothpaste save it for the kitchen
you're talking about Blanc I knew this
would get you too fired up Divine One
these are my Sentinel friends passionate
ready
[Music]
oh yeah they're they're clowns all right
oh we'll find them together uh well let
me take a look
uh
I'm tired still give me a break
um
okay we're here
we're the blue ones
then there's some green here and oh no
oh villagers gonna have to rescue oh
[Music]
do we have to
are they coming for us are they gonna
stay here to protect
The Villages
also I see emblem energy and I see a
quick sand oh no
[\h__\h] are standing in the quick stand
you guys if you think you're like above
the law what
there's one way of saving others are
fine so let's die don't they give me
like money or something though
ah is that why only ones is worth saving
because one of them gives me money oh
wait this one has an elixir
are they gonna give that to me no wait
that that one has a monster seal
now I see what it's about
okay
[Music]
I need those Master Seals I was checking
you know my levels and all that and I
think I think if I'm not wrong a bunch
of them are ready for our Master sale
huh it looks here that's hot what that
house that's supposed to be said that's
how it's
Sherman and I said it a little bit more
english-y it looks here
what
Elixir what
elix it Elixir what
[Laughter]
nah it's Elixir shut up that's so stupid
he is
[\h__\h]
[Music]
up kaito you're making me mad and if I'm
mad I'm gonna wake up my my neighbors
we don't want that
um
although like when am I was streaming I
don't think I heard anything
at all I don't know if she was like
particularly loud though
um yeah so far it seems pretty like well
soundproofed like probably not like 100
soundproof but
good amount of soundproof yeah
she screamed a lot really
I don't think I heard anything
but I think I left
soon after like pretty soon after I she
gave me that book so our
pronunciation Works in French duh yay
she wasn't playing Mario yeah well still
she screamed just once oh
two or three times
she even said that she should be quiet
yeah but I think it's really not that
because like I've been I haven't been
hearing things at all so
uh anyway
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] is that
corrupted on on a wolf are those like
um what's what's good against a wolf
night
[Music]
and this one I can shoot down with an
arrow
so I'm gonna put out Chris in the middle
writer's Bane oh who has a writer's pain
again
someone has a writer's Bane
armor Slayer
was it our beloved Alfred also
okay here it is ah Lily hasn't he here's
these sounds of my buttons
of my d-pad
so [\h__\h] loud it's hard to push them
uh okay then I need to come back for
Lily because I'm too lazy to switch
items
instead of um
because we have them already on Armored
okay
and then
um
oh yeah swap spaces
wait did I bring out Chris
fine now
you're fine there
oh Chris is there okay good
oh and you guys are there you guys just
I can't change you guys anyway right so
all right here we go I think oh wait
does uh does this do we have anything in
this inventory though
oh yeah yeah
[Music]
yeah yeah
save the people threatened by the
corrupted
the real goal let's do this thing
Sentinels
and
guests
finally time to get this party started
I will serve up a most deadly fish
before I forget watch out for those
patches of quicksand that stuff will
really slow you down
quick stand clearstone is a Terence hat
that's great leaders it leaves the space
What quick sound when possible to
maintain your Mobility
[Music]
proud the enemy so uh kill all of them
was that what that meant
I have to kill all of them
don't turn it up turn it up turn it up
yeah okay
um
devoted to you thank God we have some uh
units that don't give a [\h__\h] about
quicksand or at least I have a brain too
there's two flying units
oh
go get him
hi there
um
sword
I am full of them I can't get that far
should I go there anyway because we
gotta move we gotta move on
[Music]
I'll just wait
whoa whoa
wow that's so good
time
understood
oh that ax guy
but the magic guy will not come for me
for real
[Music]
oh we can read the magic guy with uh
koala
do we only level 11 yeah because I
didn't use him for a while but hey he's
back he's gonna get some levels this
time I'm gonna try to give him a couple
of kills
23 damage
so I want to hit okay one hit and should
be good I am the Divine dragon
Chris that was so unnecessary well good
job wait how high was the percentage
program
damn
nice
As You Wish
uh you're gonna go that way so oh you
can
can shoot that though let's go I wasn't
even thinking we could take that one
down but yes we can with a hundred
percent hit chance
and 70 per chance
let's go still alive
Nice Nice cleaning up nicely right away
I thought that one would stay alive
oh and nothing we can do
another beautiful thing I'm gonna stay
in the middle I guess
staying in the middle thank you a little
don't want no Riddle I don't just say it
back
[Music]
s
for Chris oh
[Music]
chance I usually don't get Crips
I'll try it then
[Music]
okay okay
redeemed yourself
[Music]
Papa
[Applause]
um
[Music]
quick chance
I'll try and Eugene sandstorm
s
okay no crit for us that's sad
another inspired today
I just can't get those ladies out of my
mind
[Music]
my mind
that song goes hard right done I'd say
I think new jeans in general
really good for people who are don't
like really know much about
oh he's a fist fighter
okay Pop
um
[Music]
uh that's a problem
because that dude
[Music]
um
let's do this better go this way maybe
maybe he won't go for you then we'll see
I don't wanna
let me go let it worked for you
[Music]
I don't know if if I warp him here if
that ax guy is gonna do a lot of damage
on him potentially
[Music]
we're up to protect villagers
wow wow wow wow wow wow and he might
take one hit at least
did we just hit first
was he gonna use like one of those like
things where the enemy hits first
[\h__\h] nice oh here we go
that's fine that's fine
oh
going for fogado
but you forgot to look at your hit
percentage dude
okay
oh
[Music]
heavy smash weapon that's what I thought
is when we attack first that means
exactly that ah doshio I think I might
um
engage here and try to hit that bastard
phone store I won't die
he would not die
but I mean that's okay I can give the
kill to someone else I guess
question is do I still want to help with
it though
higher level than I am six chapters
later really I mean did you do
skirmishes because I did two skirmishes
um since my last stream
might as well you think so yeah I can I
can charge my thingy right there
oh
sleep now
oh that's the golden deer for you
I didn't expect that at all
Kyle
[Music]
hey
49 49 49 damage
that's the golden dear friend
bearded here
oh do you hear those
OBS shows that you guys still hear the
audio but
I don't hear it
it's like lagging the audio is lagging
well it's lagging really bad
holy [\h__\h]
well as long as I hear it I guess
you see it's doing fine
why would the audio be lagging your
fingers maybe the capture card
oh it's back now it's back and what's
going on uh I'll spare oh
as long as you guys hear it
well I feel hot in my cozy comfy pajamas
let me turn down the AC I'm so happy
there's a nice scene I love Japanese
Apartments
[Music]
foreign
wake up are you are you tired too
[Music]
yeah and it does heat
I know and I turned it down because
uh it was on Heating
makes sense huh
should be cold in Japan yeah it's cold
but I I have the AC on hinting
um
wait
a problem
maybe Chris please
[Music]
that's bad that's bad unless no that's
bad
that's bad you might die but whatever
don't care
a fine recipe
[Music]
all right and you're just gonna heal him
yeah maybe get a hit with my Lancer as
well
um
77.92 okay 92 92 still sword all right
as barely any damage
[Music]
Chloe stole the critlug
what
see if she has it
we have
nothing to really kill Liv oh man maybe
49 is pretty good
see I told you
I never quit when I expect to quit
but okay
um
I'm gonna stop
uh no I'm gonna uh physics
I'll he'll die when he fights back next
turn
he's got magic who
you mean padrea
yeah whatever
it's okay
why are things so far behind
oh la la
[Music]
nothing left of you
um
Chloe is dead
I had lethal of magic yeah
probably
if I engage can I do the the tiki shot
or so let me see oh wait wait
what can I do with Tiki again
no I can't do [\h__\h] undo
all right wait you're so far behind
[Music]
man
I gotta catch up
uh-uh oh oh [\h__\h] wait yeah oh
believe believe the process or whatever
what do you what do you call it a really
really what eleven swords
got 11 sword
oh
give me stream is cutting out a lot
a lot that's the first time I hear it
from you guys
Moshi Moshi
are you [\h__\h] kidding me
I was told the internet has been fixed
apparently not
um what do you call that what's it
called again speed test by Oakland
I will not accept this
oh download speed is incredible
impeccable
thank you
I go to upload please
go to upload
oh
yeah impeccable
it's really good
[Music]
slang
oh my God it says my stream is offline
that's weird
that's weird because my my speed is
higher than the one that I have in
Austria
maybe that's YouTube woman
pricing
just for a few seconds okay well I hope
it calms down
Wi-Fi Wi-Fi mode
[Music]
foreign
you can reach let's go
get some EXP
some well-deserved EXP
don't even ask me for it
not necessary
give me that sword oh
I know it looks strong 11 sword what's
that good for
I wonder
you want to hit me from there
I refuse
how far are the villages
oh right there okay I'll rescue them
with uh uh Ivy then
they cornered themselves over here oh no
they're so scared
two range magic sword
that means you can use magic Jacks
do I give it to a mage them
I
this map is a little bit lame
you can't
hmm
lame
so much waiting time [\h__\h] sand
it gets everywhere
hide hide all Christ
Louis come on you need a Kill
come over here move your butt
oh no here we only have this one enemy
left who somehow survived
some reason he survived
um
I could kill him with him or I could use
him to warp someone
which I I will do I will warp him I will
warp someone
and 77 is kind of low but
live live
[Music]
hey
to train High magic blue strength
characters into sword classes oh
save the warp is very rare step
why I didn't do it why are you doing
that's it why are the little girl
um
what were you guys saying
[Music]
foreign
Celine should get the sword
Ina wrote back
good morning
it's all right
[Music]
good morning Ina
good good very good morning
um is it really not rare
is it really though
[Music]
well then he can't do [\h__\h]
right now oh hi
hi I'm papaya
[Music]
which side to choose do I really want to
be in range
no I'll just hide here
and
mend
if you never use it then you may as well
right it's like the RPG syndrome that I
have just normally I'm the type who
doesn't use any items but the staffs
didn't feel like those kind of items to
me
uh and normally I am I'm saving up on
everything
well they scare me
are they affected is that one effective
against me I have full HP whatever
yeah hoarding
hard Maps coming up that you'll
definitely won't work for none of it'll
go oh
the
enemies just come from the back
[Music]
I mean that's no problem in general but
I have to kill everyone and now they're
like so far in the back and I have to go
back to kill them
that's so annoying
couldn't they have come from this side
Louis has someone now
[Music]
oh how annoying and I can like only go
one step is does anyone here have a
working staff no right
hey yo what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
ah
oh you must be kidding me
that's why there's so many charging
spots here
[Music]
that's one nothing comes to you
um
I mean they'll probably catch up
although maybe not what one two three
four one two three four five six seven
was it seven I thought maximum was six
never saw that before
Nana
this [\h__\h] technically you can level
every step oh my God that's sticky
mom
you think chicken plants that is that a
thing or are you just like kidding
because you love Tiki so much
um
how far can she get
I could also just rescue one of them
that's the one
oh but she has oh I don't want to waste
her
well I mean in the end it's like it's
all the same isn't it
exp you're 10.
you're four
so she needs things but I would say
each dad has a growth rate security
reasonable by 50 percent
hey
70 increase chance of each step
what holy [\h__\h] what
man wow
uh
[Music]
I can't talk to them
what is it
I just defend them oh as long as they
don't die we're good
how do I get the item
just give it to me in the end baby
yeah I don't even I don't need to do
that
that's the golden deer for you
okay
[Music]
okay and I don't have to waste my time
talking to them I thought I had to do
that
in that case we're going back
um some of us are going back at least
Louie
man I really want him to get expanded
you're we're done on this side huh
except for except for these two
all right hold on
I I can
kill this one without fire
trying to get Louie out of the quicksand
yeah yeah yeah well he's kind of you
know stuck in there now
he'll get there
now let's see how much damage this does
oh pretty decent and we can break him
foreign here
the most damage I can do is this
all right I guess I'll finish him off
with Chloe
[Music]
running around in central like yeah that
seems very very very exhausting
I'll do it from here
my eyes are still so tired guys
oh
I woke up so many times so annoying
so annoying
on this like yesterday yesterday I had a
physically exhausting day
before that I also had a physically
exhausting name
uh tomorrow
what's happening tomorrow tomorrow
in the evening I have hollow bags right
but before that
I do have some
work I forgot something something
we work out at least yeah
yeah
um oh wait
never mind I just realized something
I can't say
which I am metronome yeah I'll be in
metronome tournament but I don't think
I'm streaming uh yeah
I don't think I'll I'll do the stream
just for that but I have to prepare that
ah I don't know guys you have to tell me
like um I've watched like Mexican
Tournament of the others so what I know
is like um the level gets raised anyway
um so I I can use the Pokemon of any
level but does it also what does it not
only raise the level but also the stats
hopefully
and I need to get uh yeah yeah
um Lena told us where to get motrinum
metronome and a shop yeah yeah
I don't know I don't know which Pokemon
to use should I just use Tinker Time
I'm fine with using Tinker tone I mean
it doesn't really matter in the end it's
just about luck
that will always be what the Pokemon
will have in 50. okay
so imagine I'm going to take it down and
you're done okay but I think we're
supposed to have two Pokemon not sure
why
but I think yeah I was supposed to
remind we might need to have two
[Music]
really bad of RG yeah
in case one use of explosion ah in that
case
I'm allowed to switch someone in the
water Ina just sent me a
an image of a
what's that a sloth like a really tired
sloth she said she keeps on using that
one recently
is that how she feels
you know I'm so proud of Ina right now
uh
because I she I I saw her I saw her
dancing
a little bit yesterday
I'm so proud of her well done
some legit so proud of her
I know that it's like hard for
inexperienced people are there gonna be
reinforcements from the left as well
please tell me so I don't get bamboozled
after sending everyone to the right side
to Twitter that you're proud of it yeah
when did cheetah die I thought she just
set it on
on the Stream
nah okay
hopefully you better be right
before sleep yesterday she did
I keep on telling her like I'm so proud
of her
makes me so happy and yeah as I said I
know it's like hard for inexperienced
people
to learn koreas
and I saw like
some some things she's learning are
surprisingly complicated
I was like damn you know you're learning
this
holy [\h__\h] damn
laughs
I mean complicated for and and a
beginner I think for me I'm not trying
to flex but I think for me it wouldn't
be such a like big uh challenge not
trying to flex but you know
Louie please Louie
I don't want that kill
Ed Lucille
should I just stall
oh no question quotes
[Music]
dancer I'm very flexible no I'm not
flexible though
uh no I wanna stall for him
[Music]
he has like 10 legs gotta be hard to
coordinate
hmm
someone's finally be on my experience
yeah
I was on a massage the other day and the
massage was like including um stretching
and and I gotta say they stretched my my
arms a little bit too much I think it
really hurt and I said it really hurts
but
but they wouldn't stop
it was really painful man
so I can just leave these guys off
all right bye
[Music]
I got it kind
uh God damn it Lucio
[Music]
um
ah
[Music]
77 pretty long I might I might uh I
might miss
oh I didn't
like those massages horrible but
generally that mustache was good
but
I don't want to kill them all right
you're going back laughs
mother
I'm so nice
it's like a babying Louis oh
oh [\h__\h]
oh oh oh the other one's gonna go for
him too yeah bye
ah fogado I'm so sorry
[\h__\h] so I don't drag you down I'm so
sorry
I'm so sorry
no
I did that now please tell me you can
heavy armor and
can I warp him with that so ah teleports
the user
[\h__\h] girl
you're ah
[\h__\h]
all right all right all right all right
um we're running around
it's only a pain because I'm trying to
give Louis exp otherwise it wouldn't be
so bad
[Music]
nice
yeah having units are kind of [\h__\h]
over here
I'll bring you
um
[Music]
foreign
I might just skip with everyone else
except down here
[Music]
I think you've got it oh you think you
got it
[Music]
Cafe here
let's end the turn and see where they go
oh
huh
I don't care about them dying but I must
Retreat or I'll say boy they're so far
no there's more
wait if I would have
killed those two before the
reinforcements come with the battle have
been over
no
[\h__\h] you
yeah
well more exp for me
it was soyama today
[Music]
no [\h__\h] that
I'm good
[Music]
we're playing hard casual look at the
bottom left
oh Magic Magic's good grasping void
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay okay so I
shouldn't have moved them all back after
all ah
[Music]
um
I am going to more at least I didn't uh
come from a side where the villagers are
close to
oh my God there's so many here though
[Music]
this hurts my brain
[Laughter]
insane looking good no we're okay
we're gonna be all right
come on do something
do something
you gotta level up hey hey
oh
a good one
oh [\h__\h] oh sh no oh no
oh my God
open it oh
oh okay okay
I thought he was going for Louie too he
could have maybe he probably could have
maybe he should have
oh
well now the whole friend group is dead
um
nice Miss
oh
that crit really hurts oh
Shish
God
Handle With Care hello there
hello
why so
why is a pool
oh thank God
sew your tail ends
Mia
[Music]
can I attack with my engagement
and yeah okay we have to end this [\h__\h]
now I'm I'm hurrying no more stalling
last if I lost no I'm not gonna lose
Louie
[Music]
cannot lose
good
we're fine we're just fun
engage I'm ending this [\h__\h] now
nice fro why are you talking about
[Music]
Eternal claw
Smash and
Eternal clock Hill
both 100 okay
I'm getting sleepy
[Music]
ah I I got the DLC but I didn't update
yet apparently
anyway
what do I do with kiwama
Oh wait we're done we're done on the
right side right no more enemies there
um don't we need kiwawa anywhere right
now I'll just move her
um just in case someone's coming down
here I'm gonna move kiwawa here okay not
leaving them alone don't worry
and
in the hopes that we're really done on
the right side now
to here
oof Chloe
Chloe Chloe Chloe can you like lead them
over here maybe
[Music]
but then I'm stalling even more
I don't think I can take him down though
let me see
down down down
maybe it's a kill ones 43 percent
it's kind of dangerous for Chloe though
[Music]
um
in crit We Trust gamble trying to run
not the best odds
I mean let's do it
I'm sorry
uh YouTube
YouTube I I did crypto do you guys hear
me I cried
hello hello
I need to know what happens to Chloe
yeah right let me tell you what happened
hello she did the crib she did the crib
guys I'm so proud of her
Chloe is the goat oh yeah Chloe is the
goat Chloe is the girl oh yeah Chloe is
gold gold
d-o-a-t gold God
hey okay I'm tired
please no reinforcements please please
please please please
it would come in the beginning right
ouch
said Chance was hitting and he did it
unbelievable Ally Face
okay
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] well can she do it alone maybe
with another kill online
yeah but if we don't kill now
um
if we don't kill now she's gonna die
YouTube broke again
she dead
but that's the only chance I get to kill
him and the others are all too far away
and what if they send reinforcements
again
he's on 52 anyway again
come on
come on no no Chris but he misses
Chloe is alive
yeah that's a problem nobody reaches
[Music]
nobody reaches
uh wait where's my warp uh the warp
guy's dead
engage Lynn
uh
foreign
[Music]
What if I
just make up
doesn't get a bigger reach from this
maybe next turn but yeah what if they
call reinforcements again
[Music]
I have to prepare
please don't color reinforcements I beg
you
only guy
okay no reinforcements Chloe dead though
hold on oh okay
hmm I won't be much use in this state
I'd better head to the rear lines to
rest thank you Chloe though you were
pretty amazing as always
okay this is the end
No Escape
oh
[\h__\h] God's my God someone reached
92 okay
finally
yo but I did all my skirmishes in five
turns by the way
just letting you know
I I just I was stalling in this one
um
no I really did though
don't Shore me I really did
save yay story progress
who else and Ian is streaming right now
by the way
tell me
tell me tell me
[Music]
da
no no no no no no
and what time is it for you guys
I think it's a good time
here and what's with me is to tell me
your time zone and
what time is it 9 00 p.m 8 50 EMC so 9
pm EST
friends 6 p.m PST
beautiful isn't this so beautiful I I
don't remember the last time
I streamed in this time frame must have
been when I was last in Japan or in in
America I guess
a camel
no
[Music]
oh my God nearly 2 A.M I live in Finland
hey I was
chilling
not really no
I'm the best animal oh I can't I can't
oh God
3am Europe oh thank you guys for
watching even though and you're in
Europe but I'm so sorry you know this
like sometimes while I'm here might be
shitty for Europe but
you guys are
you know normally most of the time
streams are good for you guys so what
the hell thank you one question if I
don't talk to these uh people that give
me Bond Bond thingies fragments when I
talk to them when I just get them all
um after like leaving here
because I remember it gives me bone
fragments I get it at the end anyway
okay so I don't have to talk to them
okay I don't see any more items on the
map maybe I'm blind but I don't see
anything else
Samuel
anyway I think I'll actually really
um use this month obstruct obtained yeah
it looks it looks there that's a sale
I'll use this mom too
um stream for he's gone with the Divine
Dragon a bit more than usual okay
stay close but hey for you to split off
and get lost again this
ought to be interesting it's been years
since I visited the palace years
I thought Solomon firenay had a good
relationship our countries are allies
sure but that doesn't mean our families
are close-knit in fact out of Psalms
whole royalty Emily my mother and I have
only met Queen sephoria what no one else
nope
uh princess and not her brother the
prince that's strange I never met them
either same thing happened to you huh
I may have forgotten the way to the
Palace but I remember well what happened
there it was a strange scene the queen
received us alone with no one attending
her when we asked to meet the princess
and prince she told us they weren't
there she told us the exact same thing I
asked when they'd be back and she said
no idea it didn't make sense if you're
royalty you can't leave your Castle
whenever you like I got the feeling she
was hiding them from us but why were
they sick or shy shy
that would surprise me everyone we've
met here has been so friendly
Queen is too
they're just some things about the royal
family that don't add up let's be on
guard
got it
no I'm not okay
I'm feeling comfortable in my streaming
setup at least so I can say that but
besides that I'm feeling we're here
tired and in pain now all that's left is
asking those guards to open the gate
that's okay I want to do a long stream
today because thanks for leading the way
I don't have much time I don't know how
you'd have gotten here without you of
course just another day in the life of a
sentiment I'll be sure to commend you to
the queen
anyway now we'd better be on our way
huh uh fogato what are you doing talking
to the guys
sounds so funny does he have a meeting
with the queen as well
beats me maybe he's here on some kind of
Sentinel business
fogato wait for us
[Music]
today is the only day where I have so
much time welcome back Prince fagato
I'll open the gate yes let the gate be
open the floodgates
did that God say prince unless we
misheard him in exactly the same way not
quite the prince
we're a little confused
are you the prince of songs
and the prince of song
welcome to my family's Palace come on in
you wanted to be mine
visitors
intrusion
here I stopped the dialogue for you guys
are we back okay it was so fast at least
it comes back really fast
what is happening I didn't realize it
was royalty
Prince personally going on Patrols
not something that's so much royalty
Among Us why we never met him before
it doesn't seem sick he's certainly not
shy it's a mystery
anyway let's head in don't want to keep
Prince fogato waiting
am I in my OBS was just showing red
in kb per second
but now it's back to green oh stolen
miserable torn apart from your friends
how delicious
lady Vale
zephia tell me what are the Divine
dragons forces up to they pass through
the shadowy more it appears they've
arrived in Seoul so they did not return
to rhodia they're Gathering more rings
good can we go after them lady Vale I'm
itching for a rematch
patience Marnie if we wait
we can steal Souls ring from them along
with the others
pretending to be
Pride of the four house
you two really keep on the praise that's
why I love ya
you're such a child he's scary this is
for Chumps it's too much more fun to be
punished worry not great freaking me out
you will soon have all the agony your
heart
that's what I like to hear the perks of
the gig right there then you mavier
how would you like to be rewarded
nothing for me my lady
the unibrow guy how cold uh that's all
right
for now we wait we watch
and then when the time comes
the lady Veil I've been awake for too
long
because you're still like five years old
I'm asleep
here are your instructions bedtime
for the little lady
as you wish
uh little [\h__\h]
because
I missed our bedtime
I should tuck her in
I would if I could
you won't let me hey welcome sorry for
letting you die
Samuel the holiest of the Holy place is
survival and I'm honored
you should be
new page on Pandora
okay
um wait there's one
ah here we are hey hello Prince
invited me to such a beautiful place
I've got to admit you just keep on
impressing me
[Music]
um yeah sorry for forgetting about
protecting you forgotto
I
I know
I I I was a little bit you know I need
to warm up this was my warm-up fight
okay no I don't want to talk to the dog
oh my egg sandwich
just picking up all the items
hey I'm gonna give one to Jade
remarkable I love you
sorry for not bringing you to the fight
but honestly in that heavy armor you
wouldn't have been very
happy anyway
Sarah yes I did order by the way and
kisara perfume
but it won't arrive until a long time
later I ordered it through janma's help
uh but it's pre-order right now
I think it will arrive in like May or so
and it comes in a set with
uh who's who else was it one of the guys
I don't care about that perfume I wonder
if it's if the guy one is actually like
made for a guy to wear like a scent for
men
then maybe yeah maybe I'll give it to my
brother or so
I wonder
I wonder if that's yeah cologne I wonder
if it's supposed to be a cologne or if
they're both supposed to be I mean you
know anyone anyone can wear them of
course
but if it's generally aimed for a guy to
wear then um oh I also I also tried
fishing I tried fishing
um this is so cute
I can't even go inside
I tried fishing off stream
it was fun
they aren't a pair in the game room yeah
no I know I know
everybody enjoys a robust fishing
industry yeah a mini game
is coming
pick a rod
I'm gonna pick the modest Rod where were
you thinking
uh I was thinking like right about here
is that the right spot
it's hard to see
[Music]
I'm awake
no
nah all right that might have been kind
of off off ribbon but the person was
really perfect holy [\h__\h]
do you want to keep going
[Music]
I'm gonna do all my attempts where were
you thinking
[Music]
no no you know what I'm gonna is that
how how exact does it have to be because
it's kind of hard to
after seeing it and then it disappearing
to aim for that spot
pretty difficult
[Music]
no
you do know how to use a special what's
special
oh
perfect
ow
good catch nicely done
give me the other thing I have one more
try do you want to keep going pick a
rock oh yes I want the bonus one where
were you thinking
and you'll see my job probably
eventually we'll do them
eventually
fishing mini game I would not say it's
more interesting than the main gameplay
no
hey
performance
[Music]
I'm impressed
oh easy to catch a dawn doesn't mean if
I like
fish at night time or so or morning time
I'm gonna get there
[Music]
honey
we feel fish at different times
[Music]
This Grass looks edible This Grass looks
edible don't eat the grass
that piece
you're welcome
my beautiful Celine I love you please
cook some food for me
um
how about we bring in the new ones to
apologize
I hope it's not too late to apologize
the lake
the way peach cake yummy Peach hey all
these ingredients and the rare fruit
I know a few things about cooking do you
what about bacon cookies plating to
shine
they should make for a light meal
oh it's just pancakes again I should
serve it at one of my parties
I wish I had pancakes for breakfast
yeah I like it we'll get those arms
you look like a Barbie doll
d a b c d
really
that's pretty bad I didn't expect that
incredible
I have to trap because I didn't bring
her to battle for once that doesn't
happen often
um
Sports
too
hmm
[Music]
yes I see it Princess Ivy dinner tonight
shall be
vegetable stir fry okay I see your
response is very underwhelming
do you dislike stir fry I don't have
strong feelings about the menu
[Music]
then what does it mean when your face
wears this dubious look
I am thinking you have the ability to
see the future you never predict
anything important but your predictions
are correct every single time of you to
notice it was not a compliment for real
I don't understand how you do it I find
it unsettling I am unsettling
why you are an unknown quantity
I dislike unknown quantities hook you
just like me Princess Ivy
we each have our tastes I suppose but
this makes me sad oh wait this makes me
even if you do not like me I like that
you makes me sad so there is no problem
[Laughter]
you are a strange one kagetsu what did
you say there is your dreams to bring
such joy to your face as at least some
compensation for your
dislike
no it's called get too
really don't do this to me
well that's over and done with was that
easy or was that easy those losers
thought they were tough but we showed
them huh you both died
[Music]
yeah
oh
come on what you're bumming me out here
oh sorry oh sorry give me a break light
up seeing you down in the dumps like
this freaks me out let's dance it out
come on oh
my God I hate him
uh no he's so [\h__\h] obnoxious you know
what that reminds me of I saw this
recently the hair in your chowder I'm so
glad I'm not part of this disgusting
world of YouTube where what's this dude
that uh I saw I saw like
um
some some Snippets of this dude who goes
like
some streamer or YouTuber or so he was
[\h__\h] idiot
do you guys know who I'm talking about
and I think I think he's the same guy
who had like some some Scandal recently
um
how do you not know what I'm talking
about Tyler one
one you see it
I show speed all right let me see it
Tyler
do you know when I was barking looking
at it no I don't I don't think so
it has to be I shall speed
yeah I think I think that's him
[Music]
I show speed parking
now it might have been him yeah maybe
there was this video of him just like
barking like like a [\h__\h] idiot
be careful
uh but maybe maybe the one that I talk
about like with the scandal with someone
else though I mean this person truly has
his own scandals but
um talking about someone else I think
[Music]
why are you watching it it wasn't mine I
think it was on my Twitter timeline
oh is that him I saw I oh
[Music]
does this guy have a crypto scandal
I there there's this Channel that I
discovered who does like really good
um like not a documentary but like uh he
um
what's the word god it's not inspections
there's this channel yeah coffee table
yeah and I was starting to watch him
because of his uh Logan Paul
uh crypto Scandal videos like how Logan
Paul like scammed a [\h__\h] ton of people
and I'm like how how
Paul Brothers still get free with all
this [\h__\h] and then I'm on the same
algorithm as you guys
but then because of that it also
recommended me more coffeezilla videos
even though I didn't really care but so
I I watched a video that was about some
people that I have never heard of ever
before
um but it's quite interesting to see
what [\h__\h] these people are up to
um
scamming people because of their power
they have on YouTube and especially on
their like like pretty young children
teenagers supporters
um
but yeah it's pretty sad to see really
sad to see that's like the dark side of
YouTube
and yeah
it's crazy it's messed up
yeah they're really manipulative
um
but they don't only have children fans
because I saw like the Logan Paul video
showed that a lot of the investors for
his stupid crypto [\h__\h] were adults and
they invested like some of them ten
thousand some of them hundred thousands
of money into something that was never
even finished and something that never
even worked and so on but like oh man
oh man it's so [\h__\h] it's so [\h__\h] up
sorry I was just thinking about yeah the
party what that's why you're so
distracted yeah I just can't wait to
tear up that dance floor
there's the prince
get you to that bash before you pass out
whoa can't wait to
party down oh he doesn't see myself
shut up oh my God
that's the most obnoxious character so
far
because as I said okay he reminds me of
that barking guy
so [\h__\h] obnoxious just talk just talk
use words
oh
[Music]
um
when
oh man
he hung out the way
yeah the drama Clippers
yeah
I don't mind that getting clipped though
I don't care I'm proud of my standpoint
point of view oh yeah
like I think
um
I think all of my audience like we have
very different like audiences and I
don't want those like crypto YouTube
[\h__\h] audiences I don't want them
I don't want them but it's like even if
I wanted them it's completely different
like kinds of people who wouldn't get
into my stream anyway
Divine One
is it all right if I come in no
is it
got it all right so
how do I do this how do you do what
you're an important person so I better
be polite about it got it
Divine one huh
this means I'm still sleeping so I
didn't give him the permission to come
in and he's still in here what ah
good morning Vander asked me to wake you
up today huh that's what I did uh
you know what he's kind of sweet I
forgive him
thank you for showing me that again why
does it why did it like did a fade out
and then faded in again just to show me
for one more moment who's right in front
of me what was that
hmm
thank you
um
let's go Arena
love your boss You're So based thank you
but like I don't even think I have to
base I have to be based I think that's
like
um common sense
I just have common sense that's all
[Music]
those kind of YouTubers are just like
the worst kind of YouTubers like
go to a different platform please
you're messing up so many children's
like
[Music]
way of thinking
I'm gonna train Chloe
this should be a picturesque match now
they all want to become YouTubers too
royalty but not the good type of
YouTubers those kind of viewers they
want to become the really awesome
oh 32 hit chance oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
you they just want to become the bad
type of
YouTubers this is a really interesting
battle it's gonna take a while we keep
on getting Crystal because I gave her
the kilowatts as her first weapon oh
[\h__\h] okay
one time he didn't miss but what even my
crits do free damage okay
[\h__\h] you tried cloyda but you're you're
I did your um enemy was a bad choice
he hit twice with 30 yeah in a row
can you believe it
[Music]
I think I'll give her another chance
I am Chloe you're someone better
meditation
I got the heavy
I said chance she hits me anyway and I
keep on getting those Crips but it
doesn't tonight has met her match
no no no no way
oh yeah
it's okay we got our level up it's okay
it's not okay
not okay it's not okay
that's [\h__\h] full soup was bad
what's that
[Music]
who else is close ah El Crist
I am all Crest a prince
I am here oh
it matched up
come picky oh
I was close are you hurt oh it's close
good matchup though okay
these decent okay level up minimum Luna
oh no no
no no
[Music]
no
um next
best skill up what does that one do
I had a fight when I wanted damage I had
to skip what
no one got damaged what kind of matchup
was that
oh who do I want to use the master
shield on good question we'll check in a
moment and we also have to check if the
the shops have some more
um
I know let me um no uh what am I doing
my polish rings
uh
I don't know I don't know man I I don't
know I don't know
I don't know I don't know
you guys are already level seven do you
do I even need to improve your bones
anymore thank you for the membership
gifts thank you
ah it ignores three percent of all
Poland's defense absolutely busted wow
welcome members yeah thank you
[Music]
you have to think so hard about this I'm
not sure
[Music]
I can't think
nah
I'll just I'll just do whoever
please clean it up
maybe maybe Louie can get that it's
clean afterwards because that looks good
thanks she's with someone
who already has her uh
I'm like full
full Bond
it's all we need
you're full God how about you
he's a boss
what are you doing I should like if it's
worth investing into him oh it's all
shiny now
what do you think guys
well I do like Alquist a lot too
oh night is a great class
you want
my favorite units definitely
[Music]
uh what am I doing oh
how about Jade
we talk it's immaculate
huh you sure you know what you're doing
thank you I apologize many rings before
I look at my hands
look at my fingers
you can only trust me with polishing
your rings
no one else can do it as well as I can
okay okay
[Music]
um
or any of those polish look at them and
you will see clearly how polished they
are by the way that is this not helping
me I always thought this wasn't a really
clean a ring but it's a bracelet on my
on my hand so is it actually a bracelet
but they call it a ring not necessary
it's just a big ring I guess
did I not have enough fingers for all
the Rings huh it's a bracelet
we'll see is a bracelet
oh wait it says Rings slash bracelets
it does say that
so
um
if I inherit who was that who was that
was it you no
who got the one thing you
no who got Luna
should I inherit it and then switch
Rings is what I'm thinking
[Music]
I'll curse oh thank you
wait okay
that's not not that's just normal scale
Oh I thought it was like a ring thingy
yeah I think I'll I'll switch Tiki to
someone else now though because she's
already on level seven with her uh but
uh I did what
I did buy
one thing I think did I
I guess I didn't
did I buy stars star star fear I don't
really understand this
I bought geosphere and I guess this one
I guess I did
so yeah I thought geosphere sounded kind
of decent
dive spear is the best thing if you want
a pump stance
GS3 is good for Jada Louise oh
um I'm thinking of switching tickets to
someone else now
um
so
some rings
remove sorry
you
you can have
[Music]
um
potato guard Count on Me unbelievable
unbelievable action is being taken
[Music]
Tiki can you believe it
I switched out edelgard
never saw that one coming
because I thought they're already so
highly leveled together bold move uh-huh
you could get behind this this change
how scandalous
um what a Twist oh my God X web now
and what they Rings back for [\h__\h] sake
I have not enough rings I'm so mad
Onna you'll be my kinds don't see you'll
be back
[Music]
oh let me in Harriet
so
okay Wawa
no I have to equip them right oh my God
let me see let me see let me see let me
see it did I ever get something for
chihuahua
in was it inventory
so stupid
manage skills
this is so stupid okay lineage increases
genetics earn experience oh yeah I think
I bought that one the other day in in
the airplane Maybe
you want to raise level 10 keep it on
them there's no point in switching that
much really
oh really
what level were they together though I
feel like they were already really high
leveled
on everyone
yeah
um I figured maybe some of them would
want lineage
um
there we go beautiful
got my birthday
nice I haven't even uh gotten mine I'll
ask like what's going on why I wanted I
not get my merchandise yet because you
guys are receiving it and
um before this time
I always got my merchandise
like around the same time as you guys
but now I don't know maybe it got lost
maybe I didn't send it yet I'm not sure
but I want my blanket
you're wrapped in it now oh cute
please draw
um my chickens wrapped in my blanket
please
it's such a good blanket Ryan
yeah
I really love the blanket yeah I love it
too I'm thinking though
you know remember originally I I did a
poll I did a poll of um
uh towel big beach towel or Brank and
and then we chose blanket but I'm
thinking spoiler maybe next time I go
for a big towel because again I want to
do merchandise that's like useful
and I do still really like the idea of a
of a big towel beach towel
um
but I think I would not or maybe I could
do two sides so you can choose if you
want either like a big illustration
and just Flex it or if you want to go
more normal on the beach and put like a
more like
like normal looking side to the top
and a subtle side with some things that
only someone who is kfp would really
immediately recognize as kfb yeah like a
pattern or I don't know just maybe just
a kfb logo whatever something like that
hmm
that would be one thing and you know so
far all my merchandise was like home
themed like for kitchen and for getting
cozy right
like the slippers and apron everything
kind of works together slippers and and
blanket
so I was thinking something that works
with with the towel and I'm thinking
flip-flops are pretty like
flip-flops work with a lot of sizes
um like as a one size but we I think we
would have to do at least two sizes like
one more like male big foot size and one
uh small lady size but I don't know if
that would be possible but besides that
yeah I was also thinking about a bag
like a beach bag like a big
um relatively big
bag like you can pack some stuff when
you go to the beach I think that would
make a lot of sense
and
yeah
it's probably I mean I don't want to
spoil too much and I literally I just
started thinking about it I haven't
liked the sounded anything yet
yeah I told back I mean you don't even
have to use it for the beach you can use
it for anything then
yeah I do go to the beach a lot even if
you don't go to the beach you can use it
at a pool as well or you can use the the
beach towel for your shower time as well
but the main use the main design for it
would be to use at the beach Maybe
hmm
piano surfboard that's a little bit too
much I think anyway
um
uh maybe uh uh shopping before we go
that's maybe one thing I thought I
didn't do yet
Ohio
ironing board swimming trunks no no no
no no no then you know those those are
kind of like you know difficult
because I would have to
make different sizes I guess
yeah I want to make useful birthday
merch
foreign
[Music]
do you have more this is the lady that
see that seals sells the Master Seals
normally right but she doesn't have any
girl
please
I thank you
don't forget froggy wildflushy
Maybe
I don't think I can do that much for a
birthday
maybe for anniversary
I could maybe do a chicken beach ball oh
that sounds cute that sounds cheap
enough to do as a third item because you
know I have to I can't be like do free
super expensive items
or so it has to be like balanced I think
yeah oh that beach will sounds so cute
yeah easy to ship too yeah you can slap
it
spherical camping yes let me write that
to General right now because
um I think it's about time for me to
start thinking about birthday merch
anyway birthday
merch idea I don't even care about
keeping all this a secret I prefer to
like discuss it and then have you guys
be happy about it you know rather than
thinking about it on my own and then
making bad decisions and then you guys
are not as happy as you could be
um
big beach towel two-sided
uh
beach bag tote bag
and
inflatable beach ball with chicken
design
[Music]
small or medium size
hey
but the thing is the time it will arrive
for most of you guys it will be winter
time right
you order it in summer but most of you
guys it will be winter time unless
you're liking in Australia also
or in New Zealand
maybe New Zealand also summer at that
time
you could actually make good use of it
but there's indoor pools guys who are
open which are open in um
in in summer and winter too
New Zealand too
um
we'll be ready for your next birthday
Argentina also summer ah South America
too oh nice okay well thank you you know
hopefully you guys will make use of it
right away do come again yeah maybe I
will come again maybe okay uh Master
sale
um
how do we use this again
um who do we want to give it to anyway
let me see
level 10.
if you want My Level 10 right now
just turn level 10.
besides that I guess it could be Louie
who really deserves it too
uh wait what was that
fogado could he be upgraded too because
he's 17.
and I can't own kiwawa
[Music]
I'm confused
yes
and uh probably citrine too
but I'm not sure about like how much I'm
gonna use here in the future Alfred and
what about Alfred
Louis deserves it yeah yeah I want to
like bring him back up again
um into the higher ranks
now him not
to drink and heal after she promotes
[Music]
lapis
I'm not really using lapis I'm so sorry
I wish you know at this point I wish I
would have chosen classic I just kind of
really was worried about how much
um I would struggle
with classic
running out of units but
honestly especially with rewind we
wouldn't have that much of an issue
or is it local
didn't I get a master sale
[Music]
where is it
huh
okay I'm so confused
yeah but now I feel like it it would
have helped me as in like I could use
even more units because if I lose them
that is a good opportunity to then
try out the other ones that keep on
being added because you get so many
units
[Music]
I wouldn't even mind losing them every
once in a while
hey he has the same armor as guitar
right now
that's like holy [\h__\h]
is that normal wait do you always got
almost all of them when you change class
when you advance oh that's normal okay
all that one okay I think I saw that
before
okay okay
so I only had one right only one master
sale
[Music]
okay let's pick up some items
um
I wish I could switch to Classic now
Midway through but I guess I can't
okay
[Music]
well if I play a fire emblem game again
on stream
which I really don't know how if it will
happen because
when will they release another big fire
emblem game huh
and it's kind of too late to like redo
it now but if if it happens again I'll
play classic next time all right I feel
so ready now
I'll do hard classic
yeah
[Music]
wait there's a tournament today I
thought it was tomorrow
so it is tomorrow
because Cali just now is riding
she'll be late
Kelly it's tomorrow
[Music]
I think she's confused which makes me
confused too
laughs
she's saying she she's rushing over
she'll be late
Kelly don't worry don't rush
don't rush it's not today
[Laughter]
Callie it's okay
okay oh man
Cali Cali Cali noticed me
[Music]
foreign
am I gonna be in trouble but I feel like
you guys would have told me yeah why are
you streaming you're supposed to
participate in a tournament right to
find one yeah you guys would have told
me killing time are we
um
no I would never do something like that
to crony
uh anyway
ah one thing I forgot last time was uh
caring about QP
I didn't know you were in the tournament
until this evening well
you don't rush
wait what now
[Music]
let me check schedule
uh
uh calendar
what's she doing that she has to rush
what day is it
no this way
okay I don't know what she's doing
oh yeah
holy [\h__\h] our schedules look so [\h__\h]
incredibly packed at the moment it's
insane
myth schedule because I see them all
right
I mean sometimes people don't put
certain things in their calendars but
mostly we all use the calendars very
active actively
and it's so freaking packed of so many
like
lessons and stuff
recordings and [\h__\h]
good morning Ohio good morning
damn I need to put something
[Music]
um
at all
I have to squeeze something in tomorrow
because
after Ubi photo
after the tournament I have to go do
something really quickly
yeah Kobo will be co-hosting
interesting
milk
I have a whole of us yeah me too but all
the preparations
have been keeping me busy
[Music]
I did bring by the way I did I tell you
guys I brought the sock puppets
and I brought
um
I brought the I brought potato chips all
in my luggage
I think I told you huh I brought it all
over I was gonna send it originally but
now
I'm I'm bringing it
I brought it in my my suitcase and they
look fine I thought I was a bit worried
about them being like squashed squashed
but the sock puppets look fine yeah
and uh what else was I gonna say oh yeah
I asked
I asked any other myth girls if anyone
wants to do a hand cam stream of them
did not seem to like the idea
[Music]
doesn't trust my setup
so
um I think the only one who would do it
with me is Cali
so I'll try to if she ever has time do a
sock puppet stream with Callie hey I
think she would do it
yeah
Raiders
[Music]
interesting
hello welcome
to camera and no she doesn't anymore I
saw her recent cam uh camera streams are
like really high quality it's beautiful
okay beautiful beautiful because she's
using a high quality camera right
but uh she told me like she sets
everything
so
like look like she puts screws and nails
in the [\h__\h] so it really doesn't move
and then she like boards everything up
on the sides
he hides behind the boards
I was thinking
because the only way she sees what she's
doing is through the screen of the
camera
um
yeah okay well of course my my hand can
stream setups are usually uh
definitely less
safe than that but nothing ever happened
but streams did it huh
nothing ever happens with my dreams
they're they're fine I'll be wrong
if you're not like super
well collecting and bonk the camera over
with your whole body the normal Air Base
oh yeah
raccoon dropping but but that's that's
not a fault of the setup that's a fault
of me letting my cats in that's a
different problem you know
um I think we're ready to go next
did I forget something
polished rings
I bought bunaries
[Music]
I did the arena
or did I do the arena before eh
things are mixing up in my head
what we're cool raccoons
and that wasn't recruiting sure
open upgrades
I never know what to upgrade though
ah oh wait you're not the right one
be well
you have to tell me what to upgrade
the stuff that I use hmm
those icons are so tiny sometimes it's
hard to see who they even are
[Music]
um
I upgraded some things randomly recently
[Music]
what do I use
killable killer ax kill Spirit Queen
still alive is a safe bet since your
balance is an upgrade everything across
the board not that expensive
elevens
the last plus one should I upgrade it
further
kill a boat
oh he just joined I don't know if I'm
using him but
look at my iron I I was wondering if it
was a bug the other day you know when I
did a skirmish oh my audio was lagging
again
and when I did a skirmish I got like 140
iron from one collection point
I was like is this a bug because
normally you get like three or five or
so
and I got 140 and I was like
that's normal
oh
shook head I was like is this okay that
I'm taking this it feels like I'm
exploiting a bug
on my my audio is fixed
um
I guess that's steel steel someone said
steel right
I'm gonna upgrade to this fancy stuff
wait is that the lemon sword
looks like a lemon sword and that's the
the wool dowel Maybe
what's this
yes
but yes yes to yes to upgrade to one of
those
silver sword check out a silver sword
can you never buy a silver sword in a
shop do you have to upgrade it like on
your own
silver
what is 11. all right
perfectly damn I can't buy them later
hmm
extra powerful normal sword
I can buy them in the future
[Music]
so is it a bad idea for me to upgrade it
now
is a better killer sword really
[Music]
I did get 11 sword I was gonna give it
to uh
uh Celine I guess
okay because you guys said good for
swing
two plus five is better for resources oh
I can't get to plus five but
you know I'll go for a plus two for now
because I gotta upgrade others as well
[Music]
I'm gonna upgrade yours to
hmm
now I'm out of iron now I have to go um
collecting some more iron
writer's Bane
[\h__\h]
look at that pretty spear
[Music]
okay yeah I'll be here let me give the
leaven sword to our beloved Celine and
we'll might bring her to the next fight
again
um
instead of iron sword or should we throw
that antitoxin can go right
definitely
[\h__\h] help
I hate the inventory thingy
I was struggling with this
in the first Fire Emblem 2 or am I
imagining things
from Men on instead of heel ah
uh all right
[Music]
yeah the whole system like not only this
part but yeah generally
a lot of it makes no sense like having
to manage skills here I I just I really
this is the one thing I really don't
like about this Fire Emblem game
so far is
the whole like this [\h__\h] the menus
yeah the interfaces are just [\h__\h]
menu management name where you find
things and all that it's just [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h]
you enjoy it no it sucks
it makes no sense compared to a complete
compared to other jrpgs and so on
ah
we have finally arrived My Stream
welcome
[Music]
okay what's up okay I think I'm ready to
go
I'm Gonna Save
it
did I eat I think I ate right in the
beginning right no wait no I don't
remember him cooking for me
glad you could join me
oh no we did oh it just changed because
uh the time of the day okay okay
no no
[Music]
she's gonna be so relieved though
once she reads it it's almost 12. once
she reads it she'll finally
you're really relieved and like oh
[\h__\h] why did I Rush can you call her I
could try because sometimes she picks up
[Music]
let me try but I'll mute
uh
game yeah no no come here um audio but I
don't mind not being muted
she's not picking up though
ah she's not picking up
Kelly
don't rush
the stream uh the tournament is tomorrow
I tried I tried I tried you know she's
already like uh generally like a
stressed out person right because she
has a lot of [\h__\h] to do I just want her
to be a little bit less stressed out
I did what I could and the tap was Mania
[Music]
um
what was that
what's that
I'm going here first
Oasis Village oh
[Music]
the other thing is a little in parallel
linen but I already have Lynn
but does the Lin parallelog do for me
this link gets stronger also is it just
lower
get her to rent and increase max volume
for lin only
I don't think I'm that far yet
yeah Bond nine so
no rush with it
but almost
maybe afterwards
okay
let's begin
let's try to not have so many casualties
this time huh
oh but we're playing casual so
are we getting the cute girl now
I hope so Divine One Royals of the Three
Kingdoms welcome to the Zone Palace
is pretty
I'm sephoria the queen of songs you also
have sparkly eyes must run in the family
and you really it's a treat and a
surprise I never expected fogato to
bring the Divine Dragon here out of
everything he's done on his outings this
is the most impressive I was just doing
what any Prince would do for us my
audio's so laggy on my side that's Mom
to you Mom my son tries to act so cool
so detached
foreign
those introductions when you arrived
there were a lot of them first you
divine one and then the Pyrenees brodian
and illusion royalty I like the guest
list really I was so overwhelmed I
nearly fell off my Throne you have my
apology
you hear about a very important matter
yes you said Bell Dragon sombron's
return I had no idea all that was
happening and he created those creatures
that explains why they're so vicious but
your Palace hasn't been attacked by the
corrupted or Illusion forces oh it has
we got rid of them
see you got rid of them
nice wait really
all of them you seem surprised I think
we came here to fight depressed
but certainly glad no one's reached the
palace I'm sorry to hear the other
countries are having a harder time of it
and queen Lumera and I visited her Legos
she was always very gracious naturally
the queendom of Psalm stands with you in
your war against the fell Dragon see
thank you on that note I have a request
which was entrusted to Psalm
may I take it of course I'll get it
right away
wait
where was it again
well I haven't seen it for a while
forgotto oh you know where the ring
might be no clue maybe it's in the
doodad drawer hmm please wait here
[Music]
hasn't been lying around in a musty
cupboard this whole time
is this one of the strongest emblem
rings I
I don't know what to say
ah you know what I just remembered
Tamara that must be her Tamara or my
sister also tomorrow
and like forgotto she's always out doing
who knows what to be fair I acted the
same when I was young she's been gone
for years probably on a camping trip oh
my God
so it's true the Crown Prince aren't
around much
[Music]
I think you guys gotta go on whole life
English Channel
right now
[Music]
and another tab
I think
foreign
[Music]
unicorn eggs
whatever that means
find out soon
[Music]
this summer La
um
find out soon
maybe you guys should start planning
or like thinking considering
to be in uh La in summer
[Music]
and read
but no I can't say more but more coming
soon just I would I would recommend
waiting a bit more
for the info for the rest of the info
today
announcement of an announcement
is
[Music]
yeah I'll be in ax either way
ax
that doesn't ax in does AX stand for
I know LAX
but ax isn't that only for the Anime
Expo
those AX stand for okay see ax is Anime
Expo right
an l a x is the airport of LA or is LAX
also just Los Angeles
Anime Expo
oh LAX is the airport okay see very
confusing
oh
yay I should retweet I should retweet
people people
eat sweetheart
yay
and um
a comment first even though I'm not
first but I'm the first member
to comment oopsie here I commented on
the video
if I say I was first then I was first
don't doubt it
oh isn't that exciting huh guys that's
what I was like um 20 minutes ago I was
like I can't say I realized that
something's coming up some teaser
[Music]
did you guys all watch it can we go back
to normal
um
okay
don't delete all the other comments and
you'll be first
already watched it noise me dial again
[Music]
doesn't know when they'll be back
we can look for princess Tamara
do you have any idea where she might be
I think she was heading to the southern
desert in which case she'd set up camp
in the Oasis all right then we'll head
there
you know a trip to the Oasis is just
what I need I'll pack my things
actually mom how about you stay put oh
all right new kids go on without me
[Music]
if you find Tamara do some in the emblem
will you I'd love to meet him be careful
please
um well actually
oh
this meat is gonna hit the spot oh my
God
I hope you're hungry for fun cause
that's what's on the menu first
and now an exclusive performing from The
One and Only
[Music]
I love the cutscene I love I love I love
her I love her voice I love her design
I'll be performing my favorite song with
my backup singers Marin and Pinette oh
ready as am I oh she belongs to her and
a one and a two
[Music]
squawking away in the night
[\h__\h] don't underestimate Birds about the
ring that one has let's grab it
[Music]
yeah
what do you think we're Bandits Bandits
and what a Bandits do take stuff like
your fancy ring there give it oh really
oh oh oh
that's all you're in trouble really in
it right now in it and surrounded by it
we've got monsters big fans of ours
these two and way more
we have to go rescue them we asked
nicely but you had to make us mad now
that's so tacky
It's gotta be her
talk to your dialogue yeah what the [\h__\h]
girlfriend's singing oh
sorry
don't worry about it people call them
the racket of Psalm for a reason where
that they stopped
let's get over here
um it's cheesy tacky Samira
potato
so okay you know she will be a permanent
member in my group right whatever class
she is you're the Divine Dragon right
she looks like a dancer bogado wouldn't
have come here unless he found you first
reminds me this game has dancing too
right what uh not important things
it would really helped if you could use
your summoning powers on this ring
hero
I've always wanted to meet the person
who lives in here a pick and you make
that happen all right
[\h__\h]
fight on can she not be a dancer
we should make her a dancer
wait did you just give us Ike
on us huh
did they do the thing again where they
move my ring to someone else or like to
no one
now I have to get the new one for [\h__\h]
sake
wait like you can't dang those are nice
must be hers right I'm ready to fight
let's give it to Tamara okay make sure
you use me wisely thanks for your help
Mike
you'll be fighting alongside princess
tamarans okay I would hope so
what's a bacon sounds like a lock
picking person
so like a thief but she's not a thief
right
[Music]
and also that's that orange haired weird
lady with the makeup on her face so the
edgy one
look at her
that's emo golf koala
a zombie Berserker
uh-huh accent
and her she's cute she's pretty oh my
God
it's a wolf night
and wait she's just
a Lancer oh man
well that's so disappointing
and
it's got a funny Hammer though for her
uh thingy
promotion is pretty good
okay bunkers she's still good everyone's
Class is strong okay because that's just
a spot I already have like so many
Lancers you know
we have those too okay I guess Chloe is
not fighting this time because you know
too many Lancers uh y'all [\h__\h] huge
dear Lord
what where am I supposed to go
oh these ones are these just dark no
it's open water oh it's open water oh
they're coming over here though right
they're gonna come over to the land
uh what's this
why is this one right
it's just very important
bottom right
they'll just have to kill those two
not the villagers you must visit ah okay
that's what that was
okay
they're a must
oh this map I don't like it already it's
confusing why is it so dark here fix it
I know no it's just eh is that just
Shadow but there's there could be
enemies in here right
it's probably a shadow from like big
palm trees or whatever
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] of War map get your torches
what's this yeah welcome we just reacted
to it I cannot tell you more oh
kill me
oh
thank you
[Music]
she did mean tomorrow she's just already
she already knows she will be late
tomorrow
silly doodly do
how does she know what she just knows
she knows she has some things are like
slightly
overlapping and
not a hotel
well okay good then
ah
what should I do
my ring
so uh not bringing you
um but I wanted to bring Celine again
right
I don't really want to bring pandoria
careful him I like cute girls
uh Jade or Louie why
do I need strong
armor I can bring both of them
you're not good on dark Maps
yeah uh was that because she lights
everything up or what was that
I got her vision yeah there was
something there yeah yeah yeah okay so
we can bring Lily
and and these two yeah
um I don't mind switching out like
diamonds for example perhaps
but he's one of our
rare sword fine no wait
yeah sword fighters
who can use an ax apparently as well
I guess
um
should I switch them out this was
someone else um
I don't know I like this team it seems
pretty stable
my diamond is surprising squishy
join us tonight yeah
Celine you have four sword fights get
someone else okay true
[Music]
or of
diamonds
what level
okay I'll get rid of diamond I'll get to
slower
[Music]
to bring uh
horse
Archer
why not
and then rings
you can have a
uh but who who is that this one this one
right we see this
am I still bringing kangatsu
yeah okay
[Music]
okay
good should be good
and that uses X-Men and uses sword and
Dagger
come on come on
ax
wait what did I just
oh no I think we got another two hours
remember I'm having to watch this is
fine if they're adding
two close combat
just wait free free free free close
combo
[Applause]
just let me check uh weapons and vulneri
[Music]
oh
I'm just going to optimize here see what
happens
if they just get rid of the voluntary
let me give you one
where's he Elixir oh that's like a
vulneri
might want out Chris is coming
many flyers on the map
we're starting let's say okay no problem
give something
[Music]
I'll just give you up on the Range
I'll give you a little less
to use this one up
love RPG strategy games well then you
have to check fire and One games out in
general
I saw oh I'm so excited for like all
those like
things that are gonna be on Nintendo
switch online I really want to like play
some of those like
um like old Zelda games and so on
old Mario games
and I will tell you now
I think not right away because I'm busy
right now but I think I will play the
remaster of Metroid Prime
um
as a full playthrough
I think I will
because I played that a little bit as a
child
on the game kill
and really only a little bit so I don't
know [\h__\h] about it
messing around with my brother's safe
mode again that's what I say they won't
beat our monsters
you're welcome not to mention our
thieves experts in the yard of rant
Zachary
foreign
[Laughter]
indeed they shall sorely regret
terrorizing these poor innocent people
she's so nice I thought she would be
like evil
yay you love when you see the super
chats from this stream
oh like before this game started did you
guys like send some please play Metroid
please play Metroid super chats
you beat orange so you will be fine yeah
orange is very different no
of course it should be very different
I tried to hold off on that to not spam
yeah but you know it has the The
Nostalgia bonus for me
and uh oh [\h__\h] they're right in the
middle
[Music]
right the gamer yeah
you know
something unexpected for a lot of you
guys I I would say
um [\h__\h]
[Music]
placement
ah
Cairo so I could teleport some wait who
has the California stuff
are we unexpected but welcome
to explore and got cool stuff
[Music]
yeah I saw his FPS but my will is first
I will like it no I can't reach
[Music]
your orders please
bad start I can't reach anyone not even
the first one
at least all right from her
yes I should have the second DLC but I
didn't update yet
it has a lock on well nice I don't need
to aim nice
Nintendo build as a first person
inventor not a first person shooter
[Music]
trailer ing well it kind of didn't feel
to me like those other FPS games oh we
revealed Something Beautiful
and just I feel like typical FPS game so
I'm quite open to it
um
[Music]
exploration focused I'm looking forward
to it
different vibe
[Music]
first person Adventure
yeah
that's really rare actually now that I
think about it I will obey what's
another first person Adventure that I
would know
oh wait no all those like um
oh Elder ring is not first person
[Music]
I feel like
oh some Skyrim
Elder Scrolls yeah those kind of games
yeah yeah
that's all I can think about
Fallout oh
we can reach someone yeah
Thunder
tomorrow wine
an old one
yeah but seems pretty rare huh
[Music]
can't reach [\h__\h] also going here makes
no sense right you can't go anywhere oh
wait what is that
so I'm like
at the street ah an obstacle but um
two obstacles to reach that area down
there I don't know about that is that
worth it
all the way to the South there's a house
and you want to reach the bottom Village
no I don't want to
I don't wanna
TBH
really
seems like a pain in the ass
at least not without Chris maybe with
someone else
okay what do we do here
all these [\h__\h] obstacles are pissing
me off already
[Music]
uh-huh
I see that I'm gonna start working my
way forward is blocked but not for long
go Tamara with my strength you'll have
no problem opening up a path you want me
to engage just with that and Lems Ike's
robust offense and robust offense ever
and endurance increase as increases as
he takes damage
the sync Skillet resolve increases
defense and resistance as HP decreases
the engage weapon Hammer can smash
blue hair with that
can Smash Bros and deal bonus damage to
armored ones
Friend helps incoming damage but it
reduces a void rate of elbow to zero
the engage attack great aim for hardens
the unit's defenses for one turn then
attacks in an area okay whatever I don't
get it I don't get it so am I supposed
to just smash this [\h__\h]
instead of taking care of the enemies no
I want to take care of the enemies
I can break him but
I barely do any damage
[Music]
right if yes or no isn't this far
oh
right away
hey what's that
Sarah
[Music]
I feel like I should
start advancing
so I'll destroy this one
[Music]
I can't destroy it completely
unfortunately
oh I have I think I have a couple of
them of course
[Music]
I'll just
I'll just work on this [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh nice
okay
[Music]
it's best to do it doesn't matter
because it has ACT has a skill that
completely destroyed I think the village
don't even need the skill get going just
works with my normal weapon yeah start
at that house there
it what the [\h__\h]
let's go how was I supposed to save that
one
with a warp baby but no that I could
have only warped in one turn and then
visited in the next turn
because uh bamboozled
um
[Music]
the lyrics
ah he doesn't have a um what's it called
short ball
oh
[Music]
shitty ouch
yeah more ounce
mini bow yeah
right
oh
[Music]
no were there any charging thingies lend
me your strength I think there were two
or so maybe
[Music]
I kind of expected to be able to do
something from here
oh that's lame
one last name
I'll do my best uh you can do something
why not
you can even to him or do him
talk about again
thank you thank you
I appreciate it
oh
[Music]
um
all right
slows me down
once you let it start yes soon
I'm gonna use it soon
nice level up
nice nice nice nice nice I mean very
cute I love Celine so much
and let's attack
s yeah
I always feel like
I almost feel like they're so powerful
so we visited this place so now we can
take care of you because you're right in
front of my face get out of her face
will ya
80 and no problem we do exactly the
amount of damage that we want
Raised by Wolves
interesting character design really
really interesting
is that like a
floor that she's gonna tell us about
herself as to why why she looks like
this
but she's got those
makeup or tattoos on her face
yes
sorry now
it's just weird
[Music]
uh which one to open up ah left side
that's where it is if I go down and then
lift I should reach but I wonder if
she's fine to be stand alone
foreign
guys
probably help her out right
I really like the Joker movie
that's the game nah that doesn't look
like
something they would make you do here
I'll I'll help you out
oh you can break something oh this one
you can't really do much
yeah I'll give her maybe maybe together
those two
be all right
is Louie just once again not gonna do
[\h__\h]
you need some
writing to me
okay
do you wanna
bring me a tea around
vending machine
said she's gonna Crash My Stream and
said well you might as well bring me
something
Taco eats
Taco drinks
[Music]
foreign
it's so nice
[Music]
ran out of orange juice
and out of tea
let me open the door ahead of time
what's up
[Music]
you can't judge me for the state of my
of my room because it's way less messy
than hers
[Music]
mm-hmm
I'm just gonna do it it's gonna bring me
my tea
I need to buy some tea bags though so
that I don't have to rely on the on
those ones from the vending machine I
need to rely on tea bags so I can get
them whenever I want what was I doing
can you do anything if you engage
probably not
huh no
boring
delivery by Enya
well I think so much waiting
and yunaka can't even help with her view
because she's so far in the back too
ah
oh oh [\h__\h] okay they're coming from the
back now
well our Chris is right there so no
problem
[Music]
I'm still alive
prevents the Bamboozle
we're really far back yeah I should have
swapped them beforehand but oh well
nothing's dark here anyway but here okay
yunaka is catching up
um
I'll keep him close to the shore because
that's where
all those others are coming from do you
have a bonary hell yeah you do
my audio's lagging again I don't hear
[\h__\h]
[Music]
door open by the way
yum oh right here
so weird you guys hear it and I don't
what does that mean
[Music]
what do I sense to destroy the rest of
them
[Music]
probably waiting for me
it's open
okay she heard me on on her phone she's
listening to my stream a little bit of a
lag delay oh
[Music]
no because I already told them you're
bringing me teeth
but you did didn't you
um I know you guys tried that several
times now but you did it on someone
where it actually worked who was that
Gemma told me
yeah right
oh you
know
yeah
they did the um I'm the assistant
manager thing on Alma and it worked I'ma
said what did you say
like
um
she said did you believe
[Music]
look at my ass
and acid
the emblem emblem rings and I have a
version of my hands for every like
chapter where there's like different
rings and I should possess
and got the bling bling
what did I say
I said look at my rings
that gets it Chad gets it right right
a little bit right agree agree no they
didn't
oh I guess I said assets it will because
they're called acids they're stream
acids
did you see uh
uh 39 minutes ago an announcement was
made of an announcement
did you did you miss it
oh you're retreated okay
oh oh she just sits down on the ground
there's a sofa right next to you right
oh she's lying down
no okay
um oh you know do you know maybe like
why
um
do you think it's my Elgato like the
sound sometimes lags and I just don't
hear the sound at all but OBS they still
hear it
my sound from the game though
legs just cuts off
hd60
Plus
uh the 4K
[Music]
uh capture utility
so quiet
yeah maybe it's not because at home I
use a different capture software also
for my garden though but I don't use
this utility thing
oh
I'm so fine I don't even hear you
can you turn down bgm so we can hear it
a little bit I can't hear you know
they're complaining already
ah she's like my manager because she's
doing technical support
yeah
anyway yeah it's fine
it's fine it's fine for for Fire Emblem
oh it's German sorry
uh
I didn't even like notice these settings
before
[Music]
um
looking at the settings
I'm so exposed I told you guys before
I'm playing it on obs
oh sorry the social German everything
[Music]
which one are you looking for the top
one I think
[Music]
hey
oh oh that's weird
that's weird
but they hear me through my my no chat
mic that's pretty sure well it's
probably because you yeah because I said
it there
it's a problem though because
um
they hear it as long as they hear it is
good
oh
you're learning German for this
let's go into some oh oh YouTube is
dying again see today several times it's
dying on me but I think it's YouTube and
not the internet Because the Internet
was fine
oh
I did a speed test it was good
hi guys we're back
don't don't feel obligated to fix her
right now I don't really I didn't mind
that much
kind of wondering if you know
so into it
maybe it's really just a capturing
software I don't know
they hear it though
you hear I I don't hear it sometimes
they hear it always though
it just lags
only the music though
this is like when Ina was on your final
episode no this is not like that that
was different she was on my final live
stream in 2020 though
when you suddenly showed up
true though
nothing interesting
[Music]
music really loud how come
did we change those
[Music]
oh hold on
um
okay
oh
you can still hear the mic though
okay so what it is it's not loud it's
just enough it's quiet yeah she's she's
not speaking in a loud streaming voice
people can barely hear me when I talk
about my credit that's also why when I
go to karaoke with people and we sing a
song together I'm always the one
overpowering the others because the
others like singing like a quiet voice
somehow
mm-hmm
what are you doing
just she's changing everything
oh it's here
yeah I I are you
are you
going out with the girls
maybe maybe
[Music]
um
no no
oh that was canceled wasn't it yeah oh
no it's really loud we have to lower
that immediately
[Music]
you're crying
well how's it all out there they say
it's reasonable loud now now it's better
yeah oh now it's really quiet even
though it's maximum there uh because
dependent on this okay
wait is this the game uh yeah it's
coming through here yeah okay you can
change I like having it quieter in my
ear than what they yeah
foreign
doesn't that also change how loud I hear
myself in my headphones I don't want to
change that
that is up to you hmm okay
okay you play and tell me if it
okay
[Music]
oh I don't want to see that though
obviously it stopped moving
I didn't open like on the other side
[Music]
I'll do some healing
it's super quiet
[Music]
in my ear you know what did you do
no but it's already maximum in Ambience
enough
[Music]
theater
100 what did you do start again which
one's gain
[Music]
and the lowest one
um
[Music]
and I can lower it again a bit on my
side
okay now
we will see you
know I'm thinking really hard in y'all
you're really behind my seat
she's really doing back seating but
you're not you're not saying much about
the gameplay oh a certain clips
yeah
anything anything
let's just speak louder and you think
you uh remember
a certain clip when I was playing what
did I say something about Eno
did I say something
look unless you're talking about guys
huh
[Music]
did I say something about you being a
wall
very well
hi
[Music]
oh you want to give me a shoulder
massage this feels like you're trying to
give me a shoulder massage you're
welcome to give me a stroller massage if
you're back seating
[Music]
I wonder which one did you see
huh
what exactly was the the context
and look at you
[Laughter]
it's okay flat is justice
oh she's looking up the clip I think no
plan is Justice they'll run down to
where can I run it's my room
[Music]
ah
he now has a wanted poster are you
saying she's dangerous
[Music]
you know
okay okay
he's about to commit the crimes
wouldn't commit any crimes she's
sweet girl she's a sweet
[Music]
sweet gonna punch me and he went okay to
my dad meal dog
no no you know you're leaving now
no you're still here
oh okay oh if you leave you can give me
a hug
if you want to
just walk wandering around my beautiful
room which is not as messy as yours but
a little bit messy
[Music]
it's not that messy
making up things and shaking them it's
not that messy no that's just the paper
bag
for my breakfast
it's not that bad
she's exaggerating
oh man
all right
oh
can Tiki do something from there please
I know it just does the Revival Stone
well might as well give someone that
gives me exp too right you know do you
know what does it give me I think like
you know anything gives you XP in this
game like when you heal so maybe uh
divine blessing gives a yes okay well
done might as well do something
I'm dragging
dragon
[Music]
yeah it's like a bird Dragon huh
it does look very Birdy
you're right Ina
see I got this did you see this edgy
girl before Chi panette did you see her
design before she looks like a golf emo
version of me don't you think
kind of right
I mean I uh
if I put some yellow contacts contact
lenses in my eyes and do some makeup
around my mouth wait wait the makeup I
feel like as a with an asset
I could put that on my face
I think I could put the tear and the
mouth thing is
I think that could work
blue
my my go-to
asset creator
hold on the makeup I can do myself oh
this is very dangerous I should not be
doing that
[Music]
no no that I would die first
[Laughter]
oh Louise so far back again Louie what
do I do with you Louie
oh whatever
um she's the only one left but oh man no
I can't do that
I have to stay back
all right it's so slow yeah
you know so back suiting me but she's
not really helping
but hey there hasn't been a lag for a
while now you know
you did some German things oh nice
Nice kill
[Music]
oh oops Miss
well a 45 chance he hadn't had much of a
chance wait she has a tail
she has a tail
she has her own Palace yeah
f word
she said she's a furry I won my princess
but she doesn't have the Mimi though
so can she really be a chemo Mimi if she
doesn't have the Mimi some more was it
okay
mommy is the translation
Maybe 30.
yeah
mermaids are like half women half like
yeah and you call don't call them fish
is that what you're saying yeah but then
like what if the top tap is the fish and
bottom half as the human Kalisto
mermaids
that is a that is that is uh that is not
a mermaid no that is a nightmare
dear Lord you know you're you and your
fantasies
tough human
no what is the
what is the definition of mermaids here
let's go mermaid definition
mythical Secrets here with the head and
trunk of a woman trunk and the tail of a
fish conventionally depicted as
beautiful and with long flowing building
here's it says tail of a fish rest is
but then what are they called
well that's something else that's that's
a
probably in German we would say a
mystery
kind of a very bad insult
um in general but
someone who was born wrongly in in the
wrong shape oh have you ever watched
familiar
oh is there someone of a head with a
fish head oh but maybe travel understand
what I'm going towards here
do you understand guys
[Music]
is that the one with like the water
world there's a coyote
in the same Studio
you know you're pushing down my head
with your elbows thank you
maybe you were trying to serve
I just felt kind of like
[Laughter]
so fine I found out all that you were
trying to strangle me or so
oh we gotta do is just be friends
It's Time to Say Goodbye just be friends
all we gonna do just be friends just be
friends just be friends friends
[Music]
let's go
that's fine spines
that's how it should be
just be French just be French just be
French and we we
what are you looking for
what I'll just y'all you wanna try
something
next to the TV there's one open
Oh you mean oh USBC
ah look in uh over there there's the
shiny the glowing the glowy one has
three different choices oh my God your
cable
feel free to unconnect what's connected
no problem
my glowy it's so easy to find because
it's glowing so red
uh it's taking me
too long to make decisions I have
freaking dragon is too far away man but
I can shoot them with him
but we got the correct place or kill a
bow
too HP but for the two current please
please
I beg you I beg you for God though don't
forget about the crit
looks like a crit yeah
yes baby
I'm so excited
thank you forgado you did not forgot all
about the crate
um
okay Louie Louie
Louie please
make yourself useful
enough
you never never enough it's never where
are we going with you I don't even know
there's one more enemy here what's the
quest to Route the enemies because then
I have to reach this guy home
or was it just to kill those over there
defeat the bosses okay
um
then then
I don't think I care oh you're not
getting up
where are you going
don't leave me
are you leaving
oh she's letting someone in
but this is what I'm waiting for for my
whole life
he was just coming into my room one and
after one after another this is what is
where the good stuff this is this is it
this is it well guys guess who it is you
have a few seconds to guess
who could it be I mean there's not much
choice
are we gonna get a hello
possibly
hello
say something hello it's
baby
boy welcome yeah I'm streaming like a
streamer I need to stream fire and blend
because I'm I'm addicted
you know you know
sort of red and blue
hi kfp did you play it one before ever
no oh too much reading switch texts no
you don't have to read you just have to
listen because there's voiceovers
but you can do the thinking slowly
that's a good thing you can just take
your time
I love my girls there's so many pretty
girls you have no idea oh my God it's
like oh oh they keep on adding more and
more girls
it made me think I should just play
classic you know where the characters
die when they die you know people people
kill if they're dyed
yeah oh oh goodness smells really good
come on
I listen to do you like uh five minutes
ago you listened to do it five minutes
ago yeah I was listening to it
oh my God
can you sing some do you for me
do you do you say do you feel my face
something like that
stream do you do you do you say you do
feel the same spot
they're all just that is I'm I'm also
going to come here I wonder everyone's
just coming I told her I said we're bomb
rushing chicken coop
and I didn't hear anything
operation operation bomb rice chicken
coop which is always welcome the doors
open
did you just book book at me no no
[Music]
um
uh
when did you girls wake up today
what time hmm
you don't know when did you wake up
you guys wake up before 10.
what 10 30.
nothing for me you know it's been a life
since 7 30. damn did oh no
well that's no um
[Music]
Lin Lin Lin can Lynn shoot
can she do it oh I I turned down the
audio by the way so low so that you can
hear the girls in the back um I think
you guys all prefer it this way right
now
what why is Astro storm so weak right
they turned into chickens I turned a
taco and a shark into a chicken oh my
God
um who do I go for
ah
I could go for the close one
does that
yeah you know what I'll do it I'll do it
I'll do it so maybe next uh in the enemy
phase
he will he will be destroyed
by a hit back and one of us oh you guys
are not one of them congratulations
girls you're not chickens
[Music]
right before
you came in I was discussing with me
about mermaids if maybe uh if it's the
other way around yeah if the tail is
okay go ahead
[Music]
and human legs
that's like in a minotaurs and centaurs
yeah I have a human body with horse legs
it's a
already
but the but the Google definition no the
Google definition was that mermaids have
a a tail that is fish I know
they're an Abomination it's different
yes yes that's exactly what I said but I
said it in German
it does
Abomination
um yeah
she says she thinks it's a mermaid
she's wrong she couldn't be wrong
I can't I can't focus anymore
all right I'll go down here uh and what
I'm doing
merman
no
I saw some fan art of me entering Ina's
room and I made out of it because of the
things I said I want to get a main
outfit
to to clean inna's room
oh nice
good floor have you guys noticed the bed
you I feel the springs in the bed do you
feel too right
[Music]
um
yeah whenever my phone vibrates on the
bed it like vibrates the home what
is vibrated
well that's a that's a massage function
of the bed that's great oh nice kill
that's great
a Topper would be nice but
it's okay mermaid that's more fish than
me no that's fish head and you have to
feed a fish food it's a human foods you
can save money
right yeah I know what they're talking
about
I can't follow the conversation
your food scraps
it's like hydro pump hydroponics on the
recycling consisting we have the the
fish and the plants and then the fish
and the fish fertilizer you can just
hire a bunch of freshmen
did you get it guys
did you get it
let her cook okay I'm letting them cook
I'm cooking
hey what you cooking uh fish
what are you talking about
oh bake cookies
oh
my God
bacon too though someone needs to stop
her
French to fry you you french kiss the
fry
what would you like to French the fries
gouda would you like to French
I was just trying to do a Deja Vu kind
of thing come back
who said that back then you were me
Pop-Tarts yeah and I was like oh I was
like I was like oh are we sharing
Pop-Tarts isn't that like an indirect
kiss and you are missing a beat
yeah yeah
I feel like you started that one
[Laughter]
[Music]
that one also exists in German
Y
is calm
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
Christmas tree
it is and you get those like artificial
care oh
interesting
wow interesting interesting I'd like a
good
right Miser
oh yeah I used to love those videos the
midterm lyrics videos
yeah
foreign
[Music]
oh man I'll go here
mom yeah that's animal crossing wait
where did you get that
um I think
possibly in the Nintendo shop let's win
and nothing kind of shop in um well yeah
yeah because it's Japanese on there so I
bought it in Japan but it's like a while
ago quite a while ago but I think you
could probably still get like a
different design Animal Crossing case
pretty sure they sell something like
that still at all times because Animal
Crossing is too popular hmm
I also uh
um last time last last time when I still
lived in Japan uh you know in
convenience stores here and I always
have like some kind of like
collaboration with something right and
at that time they had the Animal
Crossing collaboration
so they had like these like plastic
pouches with different designs on them
and one of them had like the money bag
design yeah
and I got that one and then I put like
obviously I put money into it it's
perfect it's my money bag yeah
they had really cool stuff
yeah right
oh this American or like n a 7-Eleven
also have uh like these kind of collabs
no no
nothing
for Dollar Deals
[Music]
oh probably shitty Sushi I would assume
you haven't lived since you had a
gas station right now gas station hot
dog
can't be that bad right
[Music]
okay so let's say you had an appointment
you didn't want to go to the next day
an appointment oh okay
bye
no you just
um here's the instant good get out if
you want to do this to yourself wash
your dishes but leave some soap in the
bottom of the cup and then drink it do
you get like fever or so would you throw
up what happens
oh you want to know what something
really is stupid that a child Chihuahua
once did to get sick
uh please don't do this guys but kivama
Smoky Wawa I told the story before but
small Chihuahua once attempted to
eat
um
little pieces scraps of uh aluminum foil
because I read that it gives you fever
Powers
I think it's you know very toxic and so
on but it was really just a tiny tiny
tiny tiny tiny tiny tiny tiny tiny baby
scrap and it was really I don't it was
really hard to eat I think
I kind of I was thinking that would come
but I didn't think it would come from
you I thought it would come from chat
man no please don't do it guys don't do
it please don't it's not not
recommendable at all
um yeah the crazy things we do with
children most of the time I just said ah
I'm sick without being sick and that was
mostly enough
you know
yeah
yummy I guess
[Music]
what you have the aluminum hat now oh
yeah
I love my tin foil
conspiracy beers I love conspiracy
theories
I love the the pizza uh conspiracy
theory of What's That Pizza Place
together entertainment cheese rat
entertainment cheese friend I never had
Chuck E cheese pizza before
one time I was at Chuck E cheese and uh
I want to go up in the tubes but a kid
left something in the two a kid a kid
[\h__\h] in the tubes two two what tube the
subway yeah Chuck E cheese they have
like the the play place that's like the
main appeal the big tubes it's like for
your hamster you know the hamster tube
you can get yeah it's like that for your
feeling you know for kids and you can go
on the ceiling yeah
they just run through there yeah what
that's amazing do we have to go with
Chuck E cheese
no I think
they probably don't have one in Japan
someday
that's that's wild okay that's how you
how they keep their children busy
um
we have ball pitch I like ball pits
uh crazy
that's like putting it's like it feels
like a zoo for children
putting them into hamster thingies
it's kind of creepy oh God Louis why are
you so far
along and he's always so far back
no but like he's getting no experience
points which means he will eventually
just fall even more behind in terms of
level as well
Pokemon
yeah
he's not gonna die don't worry uh oh you
know what I could call doubles make
yourself useful although so is it like a
board game
I guess it's kind of a board game
yeah it's a strategy game
now it's enemy phase come at me turn
turn yes oh okay here she goes and they
go for my double because algorithm makes
them go for the doubles and they'll
regret it did my dog double just attack
back and do a lot of damage holy [\h__\h] I
thought the doubles couldn't attack back
what
that's incredible
okay okay
we're getting there guys
[Music]
did you also see it
um an hour and 18 minutes ago yeah uh
the teaser that announced an
announcement
yeah what was that look exactly what it
was what am I allowed to say no we don't
no we don't know at all I don't know
totally not no we don't know what we're
involved in
like turn the light on yeah it's cool
it's
a thing wow a thing
in L.A hey Los Angeles the city of Los
Angeles
rescue is that up what is that
is that another opportunity for me to go
back to to the American lands oh my God
second time for chihuahua and the
American lands
oh my God if you get to a cowboy hat oh
we
he's just hitting the obstacles because
he can't hit other [\h__\h] damn it
I like I like cats
I like cats there's cowboy boots I like
cats and I like cats
These Boots are Made These boots are
made for walking that's just what they
do
yeah
is that how it goes on
how does it continue after that's just
what they do these days
[Music]
oh yeah
who sang that
who sang that I don't know
yeah right Chad will tell us
Nancy Sinatra collie Simmons which one
Nancy Sinatra
why do I know that though why do I know
the song I don't know Nancy Sinatra
I want to engage
okay I'll I'll charge up here
waiting
Miley Cyrus that's why I know from Miley
Cyrus is dead
yeah no I know for Jessica
Simpson
yeah does she make a she made it
fabulous yes she did make it fabulous
no they're laughing at me
not like fabulous things excuse me how
can you blame me
I love that
fabulous
[Music]
family
two HP man
shows with your family's Rings yeah look
at my rings
I was wondering what that was that those
are the emblem Rings because in this
game you like get a lot of rings and
with the Rings come the heroes from
previous games and
I'm using the forts that I've recently
learned by watching Star Wars okay
hmm oh yeah I watched Star Wars the
other day now I know the force
now I know the force and I know the
memes and I say
I say
he shot first
[Music]
yeah that sounds familiar
he said I say
no only handshot yeah yeah I mean yeah
of course and I actually only handshot
did you guys ever watch Star Wars
no no yes no you never watched any Star
Wars
no
okay well it's about time I've seen Lord
of the Rings though I still get brownie
points for that yes
yes you do I had the urge to watch it
again
me too I always have the urge I want to
watch the extended version again
how long
like all three
[Music]
we could do
oh we should do it together it's a movie
Once along yeah maybe watch a Barbie
movie yes yes
she laughs about me saying something
about Jessica Simpson but when I say
Barbie she goes like yes
but some Barbie is timeless Flyers
biased
assistant
who
oh man 2006 called they're looking for
Jessica Simpsons I wasn't really a fan
of Jessica Simpson though I was a fan of
like Kelly Clarks and and so on thank
you and
[Music]
um Black Eyed Peas and
um excuse me now she's laughing again
judging me no no no no I don't like like
the later like a piece like I only liked
them back in the diet okay not when they
started doing their whole EDM [\h__\h] I
love EDM
but I didn't like when Black Eyed Peas
went for EDM because it sounded like
really [\h__\h]
about your passion they're passionate
about [\h__\h] music well okay good for them
cover your ears
I love them though
what
um can you do something please no
useless
[Music]
I had breakfast
you should you should go order something
[Music]
um
supposedly a scrambled eggs hot sandwich
but it was just warmed up egg salad
which I would say is not the same thing
as it was good though but I would say
it's not scary
it's good though I love Japanese egg
salad
um what should I do this is so what a
stupid [\h__\h] map I hate this map
I still have a chocolate chocolate song
when we
[Music]
um
there's a shield candle I mean what else
what else is there to do
colossal
let the doubles get into him yeah I
guess so because he'll go for the
doubles anyway right
now what about these arches there is
there no no more of those units left to
attack me
I guess so
you guys are lucky we're not doing story
right now because this way I can just
mute everything you guys hear the girls
in the back
sleepy think think
[Music]
are you for real
why do you have to remember if you ate
it reminds me I need to drink
yeah true
um
you know when we watched your Nintendo
Direct like five years ago yeah yeah
um you know we woke up so early and I
took a nap after that and then I had a
long day after that still
so the whole Nintendo Direct thing felt
to me at that point like the day before
no
so long ago days can be so long and
sometimes days can be so short
[Music]
true so true
only in 2018 yeah yeah five years ago
2018 that's when we watched the Nintendo
Direct
hmm
though
I saw a good tweeted about being excited
for that what was it partially I don't
know push sarcasm came across
but then I saw what they did with it I
said no why did the Charming Fantasy
Life
uh experiencing the story right yes
there's the door there's a master store
it does look like there would be story
but how would you know for the trailer
that there's no story I don't know it
didn't feel like it felt like here's an
island Builder it was like Animal
Crossing where they did New Horizons and
like they just were like okay we'll do
that with Fantasy Life which I hope is
not true
I don't know I think I just like the way
the first Fantasy Life was experiencing
the story as
just the main character who has pulled
along with it kind of thing instead of I
don't know
um she's very she looks very stressed
out about it
and then a trailer
yeah
I don't know I never heard of that
series before in the first place but it
looked fun looked cute
hmm
I'm excited hmm yeah let's let's uh just
hope it turns out good
told the story and their vote for their
story games I love think they were not
that story yeah no there is a story it's
like a girl who can like Time Hop but oh
yeah
it's just like a first look and build
your Island that makes me nervous okay
it might just feel like a side feature
okay so that was part of the chart like
you walked you had like the whole town
the whole village was already there and
you just weren't experiencing it as a
nice
[Music]
oh
I don't know I guess okay just just pray
sheesh so you're at the level coffee
survived and killed him
oh
Marion I'm sorry
what Mary
oh you say that fun Aaron would die
I'm such little HP she crit him out of
this [\h__\h] world into the void oh my
God okay
we're basically at the bosses now
uh what else are is there there's like
one unit down there three units here
um that's it what are there like still
houses to rescue
uh this one I rescued
I think not
okay
let's bring Tamara back
tomorrow
what the [\h__\h] I was like what's that
sound
hmm
[Music]
waiting goo
oh wait oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
in here
damn it
oh
I can't one hit this one huh
the most I can okay you know what I'll
take I'll take this one down
Colleen house is real yay
yay
and house and it's gonna be for a while
like last time we were all together it
wasn't that long
[Music]
on this time wow we're together forever
foreign
that was a Disney song Together Forever
I was not familiar
oh
wasn't that that's not Rick Astley
[Music]
ah yeah I think it's High School Musical
or so did you hear the behind the scenes
of the making of Never Gonna Give You Up
music video no Rick honestly no talked
about it and he was like yeah so
everybody thinks it's a big mass of
production but really those are I'm
wearing my clothes all the clothes are
there are me I don't know how to dance
that was literally just whatever I could
think about it against the channeling
fence there was somebody yelling
profanities at me the whole time because
they're blasting the music
video it's so good oh
I don't know
I knew I would miss well I didn't when I
looked at his dancing it didn't look
particularly like that was really like
good dancing oh the guy in the backflip
I remember he said that there was just
some guy in the studio that was like I
can do a backflip and they're like yeah
do it
oh yeah make it more interesting why not
hey
content
I can do a backflip yeah do it
oh can you do a backflip girl no and
then I guess you won't do it
so unfortunate I'm very disappointed now
and in certain situations
[Music]
certain situations in VR chair VR uh
come on
week no wait did I just do the same
thing that I just did no that's I did a
different thing right did I do the same
thing I did before going back with the
time Crystal I can't believe he died are
we charging our crystals no that no that
was different that was different
feels like the same outcome though no
I'm just going back with the crystal
different character but still missed
yeah what the [\h__\h] but this time she
died interesting I'll change the RNG by
doing something up here
it's like I feel I feel like I'm
cheating when I do that
um
why is that no she will stay alive
you know with Onyx you know the song
he'll heal them uh yeah but then at the
same time I wanna kill them
so
is there someone
exactly
are you telling me he can't reach
it's because he has no long bone
probably
right guys week week he needs a longbow
what if I switch over because he's right
next to him if I give him a long bow now
and then he walks over there couldn't he
reach then
check the Convoy well no but yeah I can
do that right
that works with a stretch
incredible
impeccable
the grounds are really far behind me by
the way sorry guys I already like raised
the volume like as much as it's
reasonable
but
hey [\h__\h]
you even hear them
[Music]
Longbow right
now they're doing it must be doing it on
purpose talking about you right now what
are you saying
[Music]
mumbling yeah you hit him perfectly I
don't even hear them
it's because my headphones are like kind
of noise canceling a little bit
it's open
[Music]
she doesn't hear me it's too soundproof
it's it's open
you guys get up I'm streaming
oh she's trying now is she
I forgot sake
slowly getting up like
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
before they count
no oh was it even open
oh it wasn't open
they did not leave the door open
yes
now I complete
yay
and here I get my kill of the Longbow
Hallelujah
good morning
sorry I told them to open the door
because I'm streaming but they wouldn't
get up
what
am I setup
or day yeah yeah damn on the couch is
cute too sorry there's a little bit of a
mess there
[Music]
really
no
[Music]
you guys don't have that no
no oh I thought I thought you guys had
it oh by the way this this wasn't here
before it was there and I moved it over
here because I thought maybe I put my
second monitor there but now I figured I
actually don't need it so but now it's
like I don't know it looked better when
it was there I guess but now the chair
is for the sock puppets you can look at
this
oh
snack is actually broken because the
glue is coming off because I used her so
so strongly
I was shaking her so much
some of them I didn't have the right
colors for the hair so I had to dye the
wool and I didn't have anything so I
used acrylic color mixed with water and
just yeah that that I think the inner
hair no the inner hair was not dyed the
inner hair I had the color already yeah
get into your own sock puppet yay
they're kind of smaller right but
I think they work well
thank you
Ina is in a sock puppet
[Music]
thank you it's so cute
yeah there they all have like bald heads
though huh what you're looking at I'm
looking at the sock pot then you're
you're looking at me
I'm really proud of how I did the side
tentacles and so on right
[Music]
I'm I'm still so sorry about how I made
ama's sock puppet look
[Music]
tea
but I like the Hat
I'll try again you're just gonna try it
it's right on I tried the soft puppet on
as if it's a piece of clothing oh she's
getting in there hell yeah you uh what
do you mean
[Music]
it's like
you can yeah you know you can kiss that
I'm a sock puppet
their mouths look so funny
I'm gonna stop freaking gouda out stop
freaking her out
you're not shaking her puppet well
you're pretty good at that
have you ever been a ventriloquist
no no
you should give the buck teeth a kiss
[Music]
about this
he's so dramatic
[Laughter]
I wish you guys could see it she's
really good at
commanding the sock puppet
[Laughter]
have you seen the the bay window it's
insane yeah it looks really good I use
like feathers for the hair just make
them stand off yeah that's good and I'm
gonna make two Guru song puppets I know
I was gonna because I thought you know
for I'm gonna like have them be
showcased at the I don't think we can
say that because everyone's working on
it yeah for the art fest and
um I think having two good ads makes no
sense so I was thinking of gifting you
if you want the car do you want the evil
ones
you should get cool noodles and like
the pool noodles
ambitious
yeah I was thinking of putting them on
something like straight but I'm not sure
what yeah what they can organize some
some stand yeah
be careful with with buck teeth looking
at me I think that's what it
is
the eyebrows um those are actually more
supposed to be like something to make
the eyes pop more not really eyebrows
but
that's right I should have given them
eyebrows
Garden wire and pipe cleaners
what for making them stand
does it smell like classroom Like Glue
and stuff that's cute
well thank God they don't smell like
feet right because they're no they're
all fresh socks don't worry they know
they really are I bought like so many
sets of fresh socks
The Saga no I shouldn't have said that
but it's true that's true they're French
socks I never wore them
I looked specifically for long white
socks so that I can literally like pull
them all the way up for hand cam streams
so
finally
AMA is also here AMA has awoken
I mean we have a meeting a meeting a
meeting about uh with this one he's an
idle meeting this is an idol meeting
technically hmm
Louis can say at the end of the battle
he was there he was part of it and
that's that's how that's how he will
cheer himself up I I may have not
participated but I I was part of it I
was there he gets a sticker
all right guys I'm talking a little bit
about the game but go ahead talk
continue talking about other things
when did you wake up Emma
for a while oh yeah like two or three
hours did you like ever like hear me
no okay good
so I can get louder
oh yeah um
Sometimes It's gotta be like that
sometimes
all are in Japan now
kind of not quite not quite
um I don't know
where Cali is
I don't know where she is I'm here soon
yeah I haven't seen her in a while she
went to the underworld on the other side
or something I want to see her kitty
cats right we have to check out their
kitty cats yeah we'll have them off
collab on
is that Wednesday I think it's Wednesday
hmm
then for a lot of viewers yeah really
yeah is Valentine's Day on the 14th or
14th
here is Valentine's Day there yeah so
okay so 14th actually yeah okay
Valentine's Day is 14. I guess yeah
oh yeah 8pm EST Valentine's day yay
[Music]
yay
but I'll probably be my my whole
attention will probably be on the cats
should we do Secret Santa but with
Valentine's or just give everyone like
in school like you used to like
everybody did I did I do that no I think
okay
[Music]
Family Mart if we can't even grab
something before it's all sold out
foreign
[Music]
that sounds like fun cute that would be
cute
and then give each other during the
stream on the 15th yeah yeah
okay
we'll have to figure out like who gets
who though
it goes in a circle yes
where you connect the wires oh it's like
that okay
okay
it works it doesn't matter what number
it is wait if you have a pen and paper I
can do it quickly so yeah look at just
imagine a circle
I'm always
pen paper
yeah
we did it in the Christmas collab before
we already did secret santa before it
worked back then so it will work now
yeah when I forgot how to breathe for
two minutes
who was
who is my secret Channel
I was you
I have you I gave you you had me
but this time we can real things because
this time we're hitting reality oh my
God
I'm so hyped
oh
okay not working
yeah
can I just say one thing can I just say
one thing whoever gets me uh don't buy
me chocolate because I don't like
Japanese chocolate
I like you oh my
God I can't decide what to do
oh
maybe it's because on the plane or
something the pressure made the pen pop
oh I have a cute pen in my okay I guess
you have a different pen okay can I
throw this away somewhere
uh yeah I don't know which trash it goes
but I'll put it in the convenient dress
okay
I don't know would that go into like
which trash would that go
wait she has a hand wait you can kill
with the silver x right
71 but we changed to RNG let's see if it
works system
[Music]
s
Focus
see that's how it goes that's how the
table turns and the turns table
number one through five
tomorrow
number one through four oh
we're doing it now
but we can't say the results yet right
yeah
I was thinking over one before
um but where's the rest of them
it took good a moment to reply to that
I take the I take two
okay
I still watch that clip sometimes uh see
you you're fond of it it's fond memories
yeah
oh [\h__\h] what am I doing
oh he has 60 maybe again this is [\h__\h] of
course he doesn't
I guess the last number just get goes to
Cali right
R.I.P
pray for you
but well I'm well I'm a no
well I'm a no who gets people because
she's gonna tell us yeah okay
then you'll know who has you we should
let a manager do it
again
it's not too late we can scrap that
yeah but then you know everything it's
not a surprise for you but you don't
know what
it's gonna be you would still
no last time it also uh I think a
uh oh okay okay okay so if I tried this
one
well
God damn it I want to finish the stupid
fight now
do you have you have soap don't you
don't eat uh
probably do we have soap yeah
but not very nice for the hands
she's getting rid of the Inna ink the
Enoch
it's not mine
it's so cute that's like
saying that like Inna inks is like like
some cute kind of like girl accident
the little baby
[Music]
finally we can attack
um
well we can't do much damage
they're probably gonna
kill her
maybe I should wait for the others let
me see how far the others can get
um
bait them out should I
wait a turn okay
are your hands-free you think oh yeah
it came off
to pull out the
definitely was there
oh
didn't you already asked these questions
do we
go get some breakfast then
I'm gonna get breakfast and then we're
gonna come back and pick up Kiara for
dinner yeah for dinner Yeah Yeah by
dinner I will be ready by dinner time
okay I drew my name
is
will not know
you will know no you won't know no okay
no no inside my soul yeah that way
nice smart
yay we're doing Secret Valentines
thank you
68 oh six
[Music]
I will not risk that right now
y'all's gonna say goodbye to my stream
goodbye
thanks for stopping bye
she's scratching my head
oh wow you're not scratching my head
[Music]
foreign
oh see you later alligator that
I guess I gotta go to to lock the door
all right this was basically an off
collab how long were they here
like
felt like an hour at least for Ina
I think you know what's here for an hour
right
you're welcome see this I helpful I I
hopeful I hope more like this will
happen right I'm glad they all
came here said hi
that was cute ah now I can turn the
volume down again I made it like really
high so the microphone would pick up the
background
uh
um
and then we can hear bgm again
okay
there we go
time to finally finish the stupid map
thanks for what thanks for encouraging
it yeah I'm glad okay even gonna spoke
I mean that was the first time a lot of
you guys heard her
in a in a long time right
actually I make myself a little bit
louder because I barely hear myself
ah wait ah
in a long time yeah
what was I doing uh
uh I was trying to kill this dude but
[\h__\h]
such a [\h__\h] mess down here I guess
I'll sacrifice
whatever it doesn't matter I'm not
playing classic whenever whatever
whatever
can you tell her we miss her she's
already gone but I think she knows you
guys miss her
she knows 68 percent
here we go fingers crossed it's not
gonna work
Raised by Wolves
that's I think the second time she
defied the RNG
whoa
sheesh girl calm down
Mamma Mia
I'll I'll put her in the front and you
know what I will do a shield Gambit
because why not
I feel I feel so I feel so fulfilled
with wholesomeness right now
the only problem I had just the whole
time when they were hit there the longer
they were there the more I was sweating
under my fluffy pajamas I changed into a
t-shirt when they left but I hope they
didn't think I was smelly
you know was uh
was putting me under some pressure in
the beginning
nothing I hate worse than a meddler
who knows in our business
you'll pay you'll pay nothing I hate
what whoa
holy [\h__\h] with 45 and he leaves me with
one HP not a little faster okay
ah thank you
[Music]
glad you're happy you guys are happy
then I am happy
you're so lean man
please please be nice okay
oh and number five oh yeah did I give
her and see how I can see the future
I don't even have to heal her
as if I knew she was gonna be in this
position position a little while later
okay let's um I couldn't even do a flame
Gambit or I'll engage
and take this bastard down immediately
oh wait they also have two HP bars and
just realized I thought you know they
didn't really look like proper bosses
but I guess they are
yeah that's a nice block
houses unite oof doesn't even
do that much I'm surprised
incredible foresight right what if I do
something else
oh atrocity kills
all right I take a lot of damage too
though
it doesn't kill I guess it kills the one
HP Barn
Celine could heal him
[Music]
low enemy hit chance oh I didn't look at
that this time all right all right
oh
yeah oh look at all those suddenly
they're all
coming here to the rescue but I still
got all my arches over here they can get
some kills before
before it's over
nice Louie can finally see some action
will he know will he'll apologize he's
stuck on a farm
Lily
invaded
Lily Lily
I I try
I work very hard
I do I try my best
oh
I'll go for the flying one I guess
wait how was the percentage oh pretty
good okay
oh yeah yeah it feels like you guys have
all been healed by the Titan huh
it's really nice that we all like in the
same
place makes it so easy to just say hi
randomly
um
Cali's not
around unfortunately but
you know what I'll Place him here just
taunting them because then he might get
some EXP
um
this is the Holo dream yeah you know the
thing is for like I always was saying
this I've always been saying it and I
will still say it I'm just really
I was kind of sad you know ID members
and Japanese members they can always see
their gen mates so easily anytime
um
because they all live in the same area
yeah but Ian is like all over the world
we have people in Australia and not in
Austria
and a and some en girls are even in
Japan so it's like we're literally on
every side of the globe
that just makes it hard doesn't it cut
down
I wonder if with the
11th sword how much damage was the iron
sword
together with two hits I could do a
little kill probably
that's why it's so special yeah but
that's like that's why we didn't have
much opportunities to like Bond as much
as other like generations and and and
whole like groups like idea in Japan
until now
um
it's just it makes it much harder the
only way to
have a conversation being online always
feels a little bit cold
and
I don't know I've noticed when I started
doing off collabs
um already like the first time I lived
in Japan I definitely noticed a
difference in like how
how the bonding
how strong the bonding is
you know
there's a big difference
let me help
long distance relationships is different
yeah but
but you know not quite because in long
distance relationship normally
I feel like most people don't start okay
maybe that's not quite right but
you you start a long-distance
relationship at a point where you're
already in love with each other right so
you already have
those feelings that
you know you already bonded already
that's why you decide to have a long
distance relationship
but we're we're we didn't start our long
distance relationship being in love with
each other right so we started from zero
Rivers
yeah glad we can meet this time and this
time you know we're like
not only
like chilling together but
we're also practicing some stuff
together and I feel like that's
that gives like an extra boost
for the bonding experience
like suffering together sweating
together
being exhausted together walking home
afterwards together talking about how
[\h__\h] we are how tired we are
stuff like that all right Nice Nice kill
uh
um I already used you okay
is this the last one
the wording one I'm just trying to be
tainted
oh
oh we can take him down nice outfire
yeah yeah that's why I bonded so much
with AMA especially when we were working
on my birthday
um concert last year
because we suffered so much together
also Liv you know like she was helping
out a lot
gouda too
but the most was of course me and Ahmed
you know they all saw me suffering and I
really appreciated Ahmed for going
through that [\h__\h] with me
um
yeah I I saw having a clip or so
where she said that
uh I won't waste it
where she saw that you know one of her
most fun projects
uh in the in the past year or so or you
know her whole time in her life
was the birthday content
uh the whole like
project behind it creating it
[Music]
and that that made me happy because I
know I took off a lot of her time but
I mean even after that she continued
improving and building her studio so she
must have definitely
felt a big interest in it and I guess I
was basically like a testing object you
know
that she could try out all these things
and troubleshoot and all that get it to
a certain point because I think it would
have been more difficult if she would
have started setting up all of that on
her own
if she wants her own testing object but
also the tester you know
I think I would have made everything a
lot more difficult and a lot more slower
this way she could just be behind the
scenes
and look at it and troubleshoot it
um
[Music]
so finally we're reaching final face of
this panel and Louie
I'm still quite good
oh I think
86.96 don't even have to step forward
but I guess I'm doing it anyway
I can't believe it Louie I can't believe
let's go so happy for you I'm so sorry
though like it's so unfortunate
so unfortunate
yeah
I know I know the
um
strategy of killing others first before
killing the boss yeah that's what I'm
doing right now but oh that's all that's
it that's it that's all I see on the map
so let's kill this mage
but I also want to see who can do the
kill on
on the bus
who's got one HP bar left let me see the
difference here
no no hold on maybe she'll just take
care of the mage
no they left the room that's why it's
quiet now
they left the room they said goodbye but
they were in here for like an hour
it does Levin only strike from a
distance can I not use 11 when I'm right
in front of them no I can't I can't I
can't
the house in the South uh
uh yeah if it's if you mean the bottom
left one I did I did open that one oh
wind
nice nice
grants to the perfect person actually
I mean uh this one I opened that one
was there one here that I didn't see
because of the Shadow
is this one one is this one one
thank you endless
monkey
[Music]
I got them all okay okay
oh
we have uh plenty of beans what's your
level uh uh five
three
Seventeen the whole level system
confuses me so much too
it's not free houses right
oh [\h__\h] you're funny
huh you see that
I'll strike you down
blessed indeed once
I can't believe in I woke up so early
or you know
I wonder if she also just can't sleep or
she just chose to not sleep
[Music]
although wait I want to see
ah wait is that
[\h__\h] up Lucina oh you got Lucina
I've been rough here it will look cool
so I'll I'll engage
alpha one and one for all
you will go get him go get him
on until and free
and fun
for anyone who didn't see it yet you
guys should check
um the whole live English Twitter or the
whole live English YouTube channel
for some exciting announcement of an
announcement news
by the way
that's Overkill
yeah but everyone was involved so let's
uh kill together hey ten turns but it
felt like 20.
oh how is she MVP
I don't think she did that much
weird I'll never understand
never understand
who's dodging I guess so
it took me ages
that takes care of that
sorry for roping you into the scuffle to
find one that's all right
but I haven't had a chance to say why
I'm here I already explained this to
Queen sephoria and Prince fagato but
the fell dragon has been released
it's back oh no
sudden I know
you're probably shocked that's already
new you did Mom and fogato did too it's
sudden I know you must be shocked a
while now yes you too sorry truth is our
chance meeting in Tula desert
wasn't totally by any chance are you
deceiving us
the opposite
huh I had to make sure that you weren't
deceiving us
returned we had to take steps to protect
our country I'll lay it out for you
the palace has scouts all over Elios
keeping an eye on the Three Kingdoms
well it's not free houses we learned
food early on but we couldn't beat him
without the emblem rings and we couldn't
use them without you
our only option was to focus on defense
the corrupted started appearing so we
had to quickly lay out a plan and what
was the plan first off mom would stay in
the palace she'd work with the royal
guard to keep out Intruders and we'd
send out our militia the Sentinels to
bolster soldiers efforts against the
corrupted Wisconsin my job was to watch
out for the corrupt and near the
illusion border if someone claimed to be
the Divine dragon
size them up and bring him to the Palace
that's why you hid the fact you're a
prince
as part of this plan did you ever
consider asking for another country's
help no because then we'd have to help
them
we can't fight in other countries
battles we're stretched then fighting
around that's how Psalm does it and
going is that your own back we'll
scratch ours thank you very much I see
wow I'm sorry we misled you so we did it
to protect the queendom I don't mean to
criticize your country's way of doing
things I'm just surprised here's the
most important part of the plan though
if you did turn out to be the Divine
Dragon we'd give you the Ring of the
radiant hero and then tell you where to
find our other emblem ring Tom has a
second ring yep the Ring of the Crux of
Fate look so far everybody had two rings
at least your highness a message from
some Palace oh oh no is the queen dead
what's up oh [\h__\h] Hortensia princess of
illusia has preached
wow
oh what oh
have to save Mom let's go potential my
beloved
wait are they okay they keep on killing
the kings and queens
the the bronia king died my mommy died
purine came so kicking oh
okay but generally there's like this
pattern going on don't you think
well good for the princes and princesses
because they can finally inherit
all the insurance money
not only insurance money but just
generally their money
I'm good for them finally they're in
control
um
died too huh illusion illusion King
yeah yeah yeah that's what I'm saying
that's what I'm saying
where is this here
[Music]
uh I think I can't adopt the camels yet
I didn't uh donate
yet
as well we were away now let's get back
here mm-hmm
we shall do that exactly that
my beautiful ivy
what are your plans planning hotensia
are you sure you have no idea
don't you know her well enough
to talk to this one
don't go
there's so many dogs already have plenty
to fill the whole farm with it
is it even worth
where's an item
outside the map
thanks for the bomb fragments
Blended
never enough that was useful for iron I
know no no no no that's why I've been
putting them all on my farm
which you I can talk um
she didn't give me [\h__\h] though
pigeon
yeah in this game um a little bit of a
dark person by force
not that I want to
holy [\h__\h] is that real can we ask her
wow
oh the Divine Dragon I adore dragons if
the palace wasn't being invaded I love
to chat
like it it
comes out of her
oh what do you call that part it's not
her butt
is it not real
thanks
she didn't give me anything either
tailbone yeah
I guess that's
that's normal though that's where
normally tails grow
from the tailbone huh
makes a lot of sense
well that's a bomb fragments
not outfit oh do they all get a tail if
they become a wolf knife
and simple if you don't have a very good
plot armor and fire alarm games oh
really
fathers in particular
ah they maybe understand you know the
whole thing that at least you gotta try
to keep the mommies alive because
mommies aren't just mommies
I'm understandable right
they make us all happy
welcome back to this omnio
thanks for steal we should donate to
um the area now so we got more stuff
from them
I'll do that if I don't forget
hey we we're making decent progress
today even though I was just
really slow
for that one map
we're making good progress right
that you are
huh
next oh
over here should I do fishing again too
I don't know if I always have to min max
everything oh wait this is new
oh
antique shop over
wait who's here the flea market
well nobody's here
no one is sending this up
oh it's normally Tamara the flea market
offers items you might not find in
regular shops there's lots and changes
so check in regularly interesting day oh
they got like interesting weapons no
those are those are presents
a red fancy dagger and I thought it was
weapons
oh
yeah okay all of this is presents except
for some steel
hmm
is this a good price
or Steel
I think I should buy it
huh
not worth it
hello
thank you good morning good morning
ah European time huh
good morning hey I'm still gonna stream
for a couple hours so if you had an
early wake upper
then even as a European you're not
missing out on too much
hey guys I only use it for gifts
I'm gonna buy
favorite by Brody and fans of flowers
who's a brilliant fan of flower that we
have
Bernie's fan
oh there's one for each of them
it's interesting
hmm
[Music]
fragments
blonde fragments
six a.m that's really early did you wake
up from me or for work or just naturally
if you wake up naturally at 6am then I
feel really sorry for you
it sounds like you don't get sleep
oh we're close to filling up that bar
nice
I already passed midnight in ESD
totally decent
you guys wake up at six a.m voluntarily
dear Lord
what time do you go to sleep
are you happy now you're a little [\h__\h]
seems so
because he gave me a little [\h__\h] that is
Bomb fragments okay
to run all the way around
[Music]
stream at seven in the morning
yeah for for USD PC maybe sometimes yeah
that doesn't mean that I woke up at
seven
why are you telling me that's why you
wake up so early
thank you
hey nothing inspires good conversation
like hanging out around the campfire so
let's have a chat
no well let's do our support all right
all right
fogato I want to thank you and the
sentiments for your hard work today
oh
hard that was nothing we didn't have to
resolve a single quarrel and they were
barely any corrupted around I only wish
every day was like this
you're so easy going wait why are we in
that world now that must be why your
people love you so much as your ally he
told me to sit down instead we went down
from the somnia back to the desert to
talk oh I think I feel a blush coming on
but thanks for the compliment how about
we grab dinner together sometime yeah
you me and some hard-hitting questions
like who is your very best friend and
why
um that's pretty personal feel pressure
you could tell me a super secret wish
you know one year too embarrass to
reveal no that's even worse we just met
as much as I enjoy your Devil May care
attitude the banter is a bit much better
I'd be all boring and serious nah that
wouldn't be me if it wasn't a rascal I
suppose you're right it is hard to
imagine you without that Carefree
personality of yours it may be your most
likable trait
yeah
I don't dislike him
I dislike his friend very much
ah
more about the stone Palace let's go
back as soon as we can yeah don't worry
about it but also take
um
does she like flowers
she must thanks yay
[Music]
I like her and The Barking guy is the
worst
absolute worst
it's kind of cute how he runs
up to me yeah I'll give you that low-key
cute let's do some fishing
oh man there's fishing too
I'm bringing into my battles so sorry
it's time to
of course time to retire
too much is when they really like
something oh how many hearts was it
where were you thinking
uh
oh [\h__\h] that's not quite terrible oh
well
it's for time and home
[Music]
you're so serious about it
good catch nicely done
go
oh wow whale wound the long beak
occasionally breaks oh really the meat
is often ground due to all the small
bones interesting
yo that's all I wanted to keep going was
that difficult to get a garage
[Music]
thinking
here
why does the water look like a lot of
fish peed in there hmm
no
next time
such a pro method but fishing in this
game is like a million times better than
fishing in the tales of a ride
like for real
okay I know it's a lighting I know
where were you thinking when I got a new
fishing rod um
it's just so much easier here yeah ah
sneeze
foreign
that was perfect that was kind of late
in my opinion
easy
with fishing in free houses
was a stunning performance different
similar wasn't it I feel like it was a
bit different but not completely come
back soon
thank you claired
[Music]
a bit done really was it a bit doll I
had fun I think you died did I you know
what I don't know it's two years ago
thank you guys it was more simple
timing instead of mashing
this area is so pretty and I never come
here
uh every time I feel obligated to pick
up every single item
I don't know if it's really necessary
I am
saying
I think he once felt like an undeserved
blessing but I've grown accustomed to it
now
I love you
you're looking a bit gram saline
problems
ah Divine One do you remember the tea we
enjoyed together the other day stop
calling me the vine it's so good that
I'm not likely to forget it anytime soon
it would appear that shipments of those
leaves are becoming a favorite Target
for Highwaymen changing the trade routes
has made little difference
each day brings more victims
that's awful I am not often called on to
intervene directly in matters such as
these but this is an emergency and no
one in fiorinae knows more of tea than I
so mother has requested that I handle
the problem personally how do you feel
about that
I I suspect it may be part of my
education even if my brother is first in
line for the throne I am still princess
of firenay so what's your plan for
dealing with them
I thought I might drive them off with
pranks
uh wouldn't it be lovely if things were
as simple as they are in folk tales but
real life isn't so pastoral no it's not
I will show no mercy to anyone who
causes suffering to the people of
fiorinae and I will go to any lengths so
that my people may enjoy the peace they
are accustomed to
don't look at me like that Divine One
this is a duty I must bear now then
please excuse me action must be taken in
this matter swiftly
understandable
[Music]
um
I was writing to uh
they know about the tournament telling
her I can
I can stream my point of view to her but
I don't think I'll be streaming it as a
stream you know
because what if I
lose in the first round
and then the stream is like
15 minutes and that kills my algorithm
because 15 minute vods have let way less
views than a normal violent and my
YouTube algorithm says oh this channel
sucks
you know just YouTube things
keep streaming no but because after that
I I need to do
something
um
one more item
[Music]
maybe you keep the stream comedy nah I
wonder how long it will take though it's
a pretty small tournament in terms of
participants so
it might not even take an hour
who knows the Japanese one recently
had quite a lot of participants and how
long did it take
how long was the archive
I would probably
in an hour you know
two to three hours for the Japanese one
and that was long bam
uh what am I doing Aya and okay I'll
crisp very close to level up
mmm
[Music]
I pretty much only him
Maybe
brunette but I'm not planning on using
him
18 am but I gave up on those ones
all right I'll give one to Al Chris
I'm leftover scraps compared to diamont
but I must try
I am panette brace yourself
let me support my homie
why am I how am I not supporting her all
right
are you hurt
how am I not supporting her
we don't have to stream it and honestly
I'm supporting her more by not streaming
it
because then you know the
views will not be like separated
[Music]
who should I get the expert to oh you
know what Louie Louie probably needs it
I've been observing the way something no
not really I'll be your opponent oh
he's got a chance even though he doesn't
do much damage and he's got 61 that's
kind of lame but she keeps on
oh come on but Kiana has the shielding
art in her hand what's going on
[Music]
huh
what
why is she carrying that
I don't know
that happens after a while I thought it
just happens when you when like you
cancel it yourself
[Laughter]
well but I think that's quite a
compliment to Louis to have done
actually it's not really a drop they
would have continued he would have won
against the Divine dragon
yeah
that's quite a compliment for him
I am Louie
come on come on I always let this chance
Slayer oh [\h__\h]
oh come on
she had the right weapon in her hand
she can punch people interesting
that was three times right yeah okay
okay
um
hmm
[Music]
next uh we can do cooking and we can go
sleeping so much things to do before we
go back
repeat the right weapon so it's a fair
part it was it was
the weapon they use in Arena is random
oh I was wondering if it's maybe the one
I placed at the top than that but that
wouldn't have made any sense with
Kiara's chosen weapon
[Music]
hopefully you are I would hope for you
let's go eat with
um panette and Tamara
my cuties
is there one of the Sparkles the one
that the name specifically is good at
cooking
or why is that one sparkling again
yeah
soft pork all right oh I got no pork
no pork for the salt pork it's just salt
excellent leave it to me
now to bring out the essence of the
flavors yes a bit more good
sounds good voila please enjoy double
hearts
thanks double hearts
oh double hearts
perfect
drank cheese please take this and enjoy
it your leisure thank you I never eat
those in the fight I really should I
make so much gifts go to wait and so
many so many meals go delays I just said
what I read
sumotainai
[Music]
why don't mine never do that but S rank
I keep on forgetting about that as well
it's like I really like desperately need
them anyway
the bulletin board oh yeah [\h__\h] okay
okay okay
um let's see let me just polish
some rings
important business
make it Sparkle
yeah I think that spot is clean this box
[Music]
don't stop don't stop just go your own
way hey
or his buff
how about buff one
which is the buff one that ring though
is also like soap holy [\h__\h] work wow
begins oh
no
I like things like smaller ones
the fin one let's clean this up
they're prettier how does it look oh
it's all shiny now our Ring's got a
six-pack yeah that one had a six-pack
this whole ring polishing
it's kind of annoying after a while
like you have to kill them kind of
sleepy they should automate this
got them
polish that [\h__\h]
I try over there
yeah
hi hi hi hi
because I want the bond points y'all
I want them but
you know
I Can Count On You the bond Rises fast
really
already clean that was fast
it's also funny yeah that's why I'm
doing it but it's annoying never done
this just spent one fragrance in the
arena to get a bunch well I am Min
maxing as you can see
trying my best here
um
next I have to go to the cafe again
[Music]
um
you never did it oh my God
disappointed
what's this
ah
um
okay okay
okay sorry many many messages again
I have to I I never used to be like a
Min maxer in games when I played them in
my private time but ever since I stream
like RPGs and so on I feel more and more
like I have to min max everything
uh
uh a thousand right no five thousand
There Goes My there goes my mommy wait
where'd all my money go
why do I heal me
where did I spend it
I know I donated but
what
[Music]
oh
at least I got six five seven thousand
seven thousand Bond fragments
huh where's my
where's my how do I make money I'm gonna
sell some things
time to use Anna
you can get 3K by updating game getting
DLC what like for free like I mean just
they just like give it to you like they
gave you the outfit so what
oh yeah I want to sell
sheesh what a deal
30k
damn
[Music]
okay I don't need the search I don't
need the fire I don't need the wind
um
[Music]
do I need to spare
powerful throwing lens I should give
that to someone
wait if I go from here can I
Ayah I can sell the quick ones okay
sequel to Javelin better Javelin okay
okay
um
ah
wait
I wanna go back to the Convoy
oh actually no you know what I'll sell
your weapons from the characters that
I'm not using will I regret that
will I regret that
[Music]
at least some of them now that looks
kind of nice pollax too
okay you might be useful later
this stuff I'm selling
the heel still has 24 users I'm keeping
um I realized in selling
oh wait do you have L surge but we don't
use search don't we
I can sell that one
we don't know what you search
[\h__\h] right
this is good
I'll keep it for now who's Amber you
already forgot who's Amber
How Could You Forget
I'll keep the mini bow
someone needs a mini bow the the new
horse Archer
I think
um
[Music]
whenever I'm selling if I really need it
back
I can
uh
buy new one
okay that's kind of
oh and they're fired
a little fun
[Music]
okay okay okay okay
so
the do come again wait do you have do
you have a seal
please restock the seals
oh we got enough money for them okay
they got two
you thank you should I buy the second
seals too
give some people new glasses let's go
[Music]
buy one do you need them
all right now save it okay but the
master steals
definitely what we need
inventory change class
um
foreign
[Music]
I have a character that's called Nana
who are you calling Nana
oh
fusing me
huh
[Music]
can I do her she's S rank so I'm
guessing what
promoted and or tomorrow if you want to
use Abraham promote yeah but they're not
the right level yet
oh wait she is she
because she's 18 being
Advanced picket ah
that's what we wanted
what's She gonna look like the icon
looked really cute already
whoa
nice
oh her movement moving those hips
I'm strong enough for you to never I'm
frankly on fire here ha don't get burned
did she just get all stats
not leaving one out but all of them
oh I want to see her in all those
outfits
what's her next one
comes after Pickett
there's no next one that's it oh oh okay
[Music]
being like a Pokemon trainer
um
who was the other one
ah oh god oh I forgot about forgot
funny
says if they knew they gave me exactly
two Master Shields as if they know Cupid
oh that's on purpose right a Charming
bull Knight who fights with casual
flares filled with both bow and sword he
toys with his foe
is that just for him
[Music]
oh
wow
cute horsey
whoa he also got all the stats
nice all the lines get an exclusive one
right yeah
okay
[Music]
um
we decided to do
um secret Valentines for each other and
give them each other on
the 15th of collab at your place Cali
thinks it's um it's spam because it
really looks
like Ina to sent a Spam message
it does look like spam I didn't click it
yet I want to click too but I'm not
going to tell you guys who I got because
you guys are gonna like tell them
and they'll find out
continue and that's who we are uh and
that one
fill in your email address
um which one should I use
I can keep a secret no I don't trust you
well what keyboard how to type
okay
join group
okay okay
let's see
couldn't I get
confirm
plate
and draw how do I draw
a name
[Applause]
oh
okay
[Music]
I think this one's pretty easy to get
gifts for
another photo
nice okay
you will see
ah
[Music]
what kind of
um this time we are doing physical
physical things because
[Music]
um
I think
small raisins
[Music]
just saying but no chocolate for me
please I don't like
can't wait to see what you guys get yeah
it's like Christmas
I wonder who gets me
no my little Talent would be different
because from we're still early on in in
my stay
and I would actually be happy about
Nutella but I I'm probably just gonna
get Nutella on my own
um when I walk by
a Nutella Shelf
hopefully soon
or I'll get Nutella that's at Cali's
place you can just steal it quietly just
kidding
um
yeah didn't she didn't she say she
doesn't like Nutella
because she got the Nutella from Ina
right did you say she doesn't like
Nutella I'm not sure anymore
I don't think she likes it
she does she like
she doesn't like it and Nina gave it to
her perfect she must still have some
Nutella at her place
okay uh uh one more thing I wanted to do
is give the the like the Lance to um
foreign
sounds Javelin I Chloe a lot
um
I think like I said used a lot of money
up in with the upgrading too huh does
that take a lot of money that could
explain a lot of things
and I upgraded now the despair plus one
at least
hmm
maybe have you oh
should I give it to someone else
isn't Louie a spare Knight thingy
Louie was spelled all right
where are you
yeah he is could it be better for him
okay
[Music]
with
okay well he got something new fancy
good for him
let's see how much it costs to upgrade
if I have anything at all
oh
okay I can do plus one
here we go
I will give him some range I'll be here
it isn't being arranged in a javelin no
right same range
oh did I forget something to do I did
the Rings I did the food I didn't do the
sleeping
[Music]
[\h__\h] that
same range yeah Javelin is a pro too
yeah he had a javelin but I guess you
know the spare is better
should Kelly some wheelies so he's
faster
yeah no next time I bring him along I'm
gonna Place him in the front line so
that he can make the First Steps early
on
um
you get more chunks of money but you
gotta be careful
if you're spending next time yeah yeah
but at least I still have that
um
40K upcoming so ah wait one more thing I
didn't check all the supports I'm gonna
go
I'm so sorry are you glaring at me no
Prince
but at least not intentionally but I
can't take my eyes off of your armor
in Lugia we are taught from an early age
to keep watch for Brody and armor
I think I understand brodia has invaded
elusia more times than I can count
my country has a lot of cancer for for
what
I am sorry
and what do you mean by that exactly huh
I uh what did you just issue a formal
apology from the kingdom of brodia for
its invasions of our language
of your people and swearing to adopt
peaceful foreign
between nations is a serious matter
not to be taken lightly that's not what
I what I like to say was uh if brodia is
at fault then we absolutely should
apologize but that apology is not mine
to give
the king and nobility would have to
convince and agree so when I said I was
sorry it came from me as an individual
not as a representative of uh
I know that
you are a little too easy to toy with
you are a little shy
I was so nervous my ill feelings toward
brodia are in the past but I could not
resist teasing you a little look on the
bright side we are comfortable enough
now
yes oh of course I I did think my heart
was going to stop but I suppose it was
funny
bullying
interesting couple
not really
a ship that I would ship
but who knows what happens between take
a look at that Louie isn't it lovely how
that couple shares a meal together huh
that's a boy and then the boy Returns
the gesture do you see what she's doing
guys Chloe's like oh isn't that hey hey
you you got next to me look at what that
couple is doing isn't that nice
so intimate like a prince and princess
from my fairy tales it's quite a sight
what imagines the sort of lives they
leave but I don't think that's actually
what she's really trying interesting
change of pace to observe your favorite
scenes
uh-oh for someone who just said it's
interesting you don't sound so invested
I'm sorry
there is something I feel is lacking
after all it seems
and what would that be I'm not certain
but I suspect what's missing is you oh
me how so everyone adores you Chloe
you're perpetually surrounded by friends
the closeness you show with those
friends
is nothing quite like it he's the side
of it fills me with such joy that I
would hold it in my mind
the drawback it seems is that scenes
without you in them lose their luster I
can tell you mean that as a compliment
so thanks Chloe but I'd be careful who I
said that to I know where you're coming
from with that hobby of yours but other
people it takes a lot of explanation
before people will understand not all of
them have the patience
I'll bear that in mind we should
probably get going that couple we stared
at is starting to stare back yes perhaps
it's time for us to withdraw shall we
see what else we can see
okay his hobby is people watching huh
oh no hold up okay there we go we did
that
um some bonds okay one Bond Lin
[Music]
I still find it odd to fight alongside a
family heirloom but I'm glad you're here
she's Martin She's a family heirloom
family has a special place in my heart
I'm happy to lend you my strength swing
in Japanese history really
Divine sword wielded by Emblem Lin
effective calorie armored
oh
nice
all right we're done and go next go next
we're six hours now oh my God
I can't believe we're in six hours now
oh
I make um
probably play for like two more or so
um
what time is it guys
tell me
one more chapter and midnight
at 1am
um it's getting late huh you guys ready
to stay up longer with me
um
and you guys fine with that
hold on let me look at my schedule is
that did I was I like supposed to do
something besides streaming I don't
think so
getting early you can go for more
yeah oh thank you
you're like make use of the rare time
where I
for once
stream in the evening for n a rather
than the morning time also it's weekend
so what the [\h__\h] just stay up stay up
let me check my
calendar
[Music]
schedule
I uploaded the schedule by the way guys
it's in the middle of the week but
yesterday I uploaded a schedule in case
you didn't see it
uh I would recommend you guys
check it out
yes yes yes
the TBD I don't know yet what to do
there or even if I stream but if I
stream it will be at that time that I
put there
[Music]
um
pretty packed schedule you guys don't
have any idea that schedule if that
already looks back to you you should
look at my real schedule
it's quite something
wait how are the emblem Rings looking
right now you're on you're in bomb 10
well then I might as well move her
because I don't have it can't go over 10
right now right
unless I do the Divine thingy
with Lynn I guess we could do that now
the divine
Paragon for lin should we do that
[Music]
what about like the others like Ike who
are not from uh
do they all have a divine parallelog
that one is hard and long
all right Michael really in like 30
minutes
you guys told me that the one from Tiki
was hard but I had no problems with that
one
they all do oh okay
okay
[Music]
I just want
I want that one back for the Canter when
are we getting them back
I need I should have done that all
before we had them taken away but you
never know
stats weapons and better skills don't
hire bomb levels there's no point eleven
if you're not gonna keep them
hmm
it will be a while imagine that
is
chapter 17.
wait what chapter am I in now
does it say that somewhere here
13.
the maybe next stream then next stream
next fireman stream we should get it
back
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
has it's from an old game it's known as
no one hell
and should I okay
you guys said it's too hard for me let
me let me check the
uh
level
which one's for Lynn
how do I know which one's full in
oh wait these are just DLC oh
confused moment uh
I don't want to begin this one
fast travel to it
okay
it's getting so dark in my room can I
just turn on the light really quick
because I can't see the buttons on my
controller
all right
no
you don't tell me what to do
almost knocked off my teeth
[Music]
oh
hey
what just
I just got a really cute message from
Cali
I will not say what it is but
it made me like a goat so
hey how do I know which one is falling
and then there's a skirmish this is a
scrimmage this is a skirmish training
this is training it's Grimace I know
Swift wins aha thank you
I lean here
the Divine Dragon will face an important
trial base class in level 19.
we can do a different one if a different
one is lower maybe ah
[Music]
Wait no that's just that's not that's
not that
this one is from Lucina this one is from
Lynn
this one is for Ike advanced class
levels free
to Chapter 14 verse
[Music]
okay
all right
I guess how do I go to the left
now okay I kept on doing left and she
kept on going up
[Music]
some Palace chapter 14.
hmm
uh
I'll keep the emblem Rings how they are
whatever at least for now until decide
who I'm bringing
not doing the prologue I guess not
but I will change the ring from Lynn to
someone else maybe finally
Let Her Go
yeah I don't think so and don't you dare
come any closer I've got an emblem ring
it's like a circus circus easy to kill
her oh sorry everyone I didn't realize
she was still on illusia's side I don't
see any other soldiers did you get in by
yourself
uh-huh I told the guards I'd been
separated from Ivy and they let me walk
right in now you've got a choice
hands over the Rings or I kill the queen
potencia
don't do this ivy
it's been a while
you know I I thought you were dead oh it
was so relieved when I heard you'd made
it oh but now what
you're with them conflict of feelings
since father sacrificed himself
illusia has been working in concert
can I just say oh you no [\h__\h] you
abandoned them sorry abandoned me okay
she said this she took sides with the
Enemy
I just want to say her left Circle hair
thingy is bouncing so much and looks
funny look at it just the left one is
bouncing
he's cute her hair is bouncy
okay sorry
[Music]
no
no he's betrayed anyone
hello Raiders wow another rain hear
another word out of your
oh [\h__\h] the Rings
oh [\h__\h] the drama
never
oh [\h__\h] I heard you
but I'm not doing what you want you will
have to cut off my fingers in order to
get those Rings Tamara fogato and the
people of Psalm have done
I won't give you the Rings
I won't let you kill queen sephoria
those rings are staying with us right if
we let the felt dragon have them my
country and my people are doomed so
threaten us all you want take my whole
family hostage if it makes you happy
but I swear and I always will there she
is the future queen of Psalm and her
Ally it is my child at risks my death
give me what I want oh
[Music]
okay now I feel sorry the fell Dragon
murdered him you watched it happen
there's no way we can bring him back
they're playing on classic Hortensia
[Music]
everything's all wrong
stop trying to get in my head all right
I'll kill her I'll do it I don't think
you can
not if you know the pain of losing a
parent
well get on with it then if that's what
you truly want don't Ponder if you're
doing this or aren't we
she needs her sister now
it's all right Hortensia
I'm worried about you not your key hug
oh give me a haircut scene what I'm
afraid I have to cut the reunion no
sick music though what are you doing
here missed you two Divine One
I must thank you for helping us gather
so many rings
all of them I thought
until the princesses rather form
princesses thievery came to light
enough about that more importantly
princess Hortensia
taking a ring without permission
sneaking off to a place like this
naughty naughty
naughty Lord sombron and Lady vale's
orders were clear to wait to watch
oh your retainers by the way they tried
to stop us but they failed
where are they
for yourself
planned on making a move this early but
since we're here it would be a shame to
return home without a few souvenirs
wouldn't you agree
[Music]
pounds I did not expect it would be so
easy to enter the impregnable song
Palace is
killer
Alice can get pregnant when
evil
Falk
come to Palace
no Lord sombron will want to save her
every last drop of sovereign blood
Queen sephoria
what a good girl you are princess
Hortensia coming here to get rings for
Lord sombron now that the three of us
are here why don't we help finish what
you started Welcome to our side kill
them all and head back home to illusion
what do you say but
but I come dear take command just think
if we take their Rings we'll be so close
to having all 12.
so close
[Music]
yeah
what's going on is she morbing she's
mourning step back the Rings
then father will that's right King
Hyacinth will be resurrected we'll make
everything just as it was before no
before no no wait they're gonna
no return
's gonna be like
no I will kill them all no I will take
their rings
it's the only way to save father
is she really going to fight us I need
to say it with you snap out of it please
but last time someone can see you turn
it to them unfortunately I think I enjoy
killing one another I had to kill them
wasn't that the thing with the King
I want it I want tortencia to join my
party that was different
it was a zombie
I was trying to corrupt okay maybe I can
save her chance here I mean look at her
design her character design just tells
me that
that it was a lot of money put into it
so she can't just like die like that
thinking very very in a financial way
you know
wow
that's a nice palace
yeah she looks too important too cute
it's eye candy they can't let her go now
wow wow the palace though
whoa
oh my God okay so uh
it's thinking time again
um
do we split
yeah right we have to split
split for the treasures yeah how many
are we ten that's okay four five
twelve or 12.
six on each side
get the treasures go back down or only
send one to the treasure or two to the
treasure and then like split again and
then wait stall until everybody mixes in
the middle again
um
wait what no
what kind of units are we dealing with
probably like a good variety but
um
lots of Acts on this side
uh no flying units barely barely
maybe two on each side that's pretty
much it
maybe that will be reinforcements still
where would they be
only I only stayed on
possibilities from there and the main
big round haul
okay left side is Lance ah I know this I
know this right side all ax left side
all Lance
Spears or whatever
I know this I know this I know oh that's
all lands holy [\h__\h] has a lot of lands
up here even more ax oh my they made it
really easy for me to like think
where to put my units
it's like they're they're giving me like
uh
a big big big hint
I think he's so obviously writing it out
in big big fat ladders
um
what was it sword
sword against ax
and
uh accidents
that's
yeah okay sword against ax
okay actually pretty good
um
I can't move quinoa
she the only one I can't move on
uh what did I just say uh ax against
Lance so you can go over here
I don't know if I want to bring
two lances
it's honest
and we might only need one Archer
I might leave out Chris behind the Sun
I mean one I guess it could be good to
have one percent
um
and do this and then we'll probably
switch out either Louis or I think I
love you
um I think it will be Louie
that might be Lily
Archer can we use before the blast
um
play for Jade yeah I need another ax on
that side that's what I was thinking
anyway
okay
I don't know
[Music]
what did I say what did I say
ah Jade
there you go strong armor ax beautiful
it's pretty well balanced one amount
I'm bringing Marin according to my
current plan
what
um
well this ax one I want to bring
sword I guess
hmm
sort of sword and Dagger
A Healer on each side
um
there's some healing from Celine
and she has some healing too
so we want to split Celine and Ivy which
is good because they're both healing and
Magic
it's decent that's decent
so
ah but Celine is also sore so she so she
sat on that side
yeah okay okay
yeah
looks good
amazing
looks like the perfect setup
uh in terms of rings I think everybody
with rings is in the team
right
here we go
then ring yeah that's okay
just one fun yeah
oh wait okay a certain amount of people
have to be killed well whatever I'll
just reach whenever I reach the middle
not only good don't have to think too
hard about who to kill
oh pillars again okay okay okay
whoo soundtrack
unfortunately I can only
I could engage and like try to shoot
that dude probably
atrocity right let us become one
atrocity
uh Fallen star sorry that's the one
not worth
where are the
charging ones
charging pattern
oh oh there's four here and four there
right about that yeah I mean
they're saying not worth it though I
guess like why the hell not because
otherwise I'm just gonna like save
endlessly with my
engagements I I do that quite often
although it's not like we're like really
cornered or anything you're really in
danger here either
um
now I made me question myself
I won't do it
ah
I made her wait while engaged
someone I just did
oh
ahoya
[Music]
it's okay we don't need so many rewinds
my will is firm
[Music]
perfect time for the lemon sword
so magic had to
wait isn't that so perfect because
normal sword
even though he was ax wouldn't have done
so much damage because there needs to be
magic for it to be really effective on
on heavy armor
so 11 sword is literally the solution
understood
oh my God absolute
banger
whatever you need so big brain
apparently I'm bringing both thieves on
that side
um
[Music]
should I switch these
yeah I think I'm I'm switching them
bringing her there
I know but yeah no that's okay
is it okay
no it's not really okay on it
but what's on that side
Lance I mean Lance versus Lance is
better than Lance versus ax
yeah okay
[Music]
um
well that makes me think
bring one of the access to the right no
that's not I'm not supposed to do that
I'll protect you
knock I should have been on the right
side after all
damn it got it
foreign
because otherwise it won't kill anyway
the nine percent crit on the other one
is too low
my sound is lagging again I thought that
what Ina did fixed it but apparently it
didn't it's lagging oh now the problem
is now that you guys hear the lag too
before you didn't hear it
made it worse
can I change it so that you guys
um
[Music]
but this way I changed it back to what
it was before in OBS so you guys can
sorry
I'm sorry but now you guys hear it even
when it lags for me
[Music]
you're awake Kiana
I'm awake Kiana
it's me
I hear you
right
hmm
[Music]
if he throws a javelin that Javelin at
me I'm gonna be mad
uh here is better
works here
your Ivy's tanky as heck is she how do
you know I'm ready
um I end up bringing her over to the sun
anyway because now I traded yunaka in
the end I feel like it was the wrong
choice but whatever
I just don't want two thieves on the
right side
it's clearing looking well going well
figure it out
tomorrow we'll figure it out right
she'll figure something out all right
and then uh what sword writes at yeah
is that an even number then
on your side
of course one two three
yeah I think so one for free 60 okay
[Music]
the payback is unreal
what's that point and another Miss
eighteen percent
dare to attack me not worth it dude
that's what I'm gonna do
hurry
I have no choice but to win
can't get that far but
oh well
it's okay
keep on moving my defense together
Keep On Moving
[Music]
so far I like every single soundtrack so
much
wow the silver Jagger
from a distance
sheesh
a
[Music]
that was cool was it not yo
I forgot about throwing daggers nice
sorry I want to move this side
um
Nintendo games popped your music
as always yeah
thank you very much indeed that was very
cool that was really cool not gonna lie
wait did you why are you guys all
reacting to that did she say it herself
that oh I'm cool or something
are you just all in sync
incredible
oh
for the condo
[Music]
oh she calls herself cool I didn't
listen that much okay
I guess it was cool
I guess
[Music]
is there going to be reinforcements from
the left side
there better not be
[Music]
all right
yes oh [\h__\h]
oh
try me
remember this they make very bad life
decisions because
it literally leads them to death oh [\h__\h]
that was a bad life decision for me oh
but Archer versus Archer look at that
look at that damage
[\h__\h]
this is also a bad black decision
oh but he didn't survives
well it goes into the pillar that's
pretty smart from him but I got 98
chance oh
failure didn't help you
need a life coach yeah
I'm not gonna be the one though
oh oh
[\h__\h] I am sorry
it's he's on fire
oh oh Dragon coming over
I blew it no
wait no
I can't believe I lost
I'll back off for now no I won't forget
this
wait that's an undo everything I don't
like this outcome no no no no no no no
no no no no I'm not doing that she can't
die that early no we just started
golfy Wawa
what the [\h__\h] was that crit
I didn't do that that late it was just
there so if I just
move her somewhere else hopefully no one
else will die but should be safe here
right like here okay I get that
here she said
come on come on
now the whole kakitsu fights will have
possibly a different outcome but we'll
see
beautiful you put up a good fight
beautiful
they're fine
last time I think he survived with like
two HP or so yeah yeah yeah yeah and
this RNG doesn't change
I think I forgot about the a
no I completely forgot about that I
think that was a thing in free houses
too
oh this time they go for
Goto
believe it
I'll Retreat so I don't drag you down
you must be [\h__\h] kidding me
foreign
[Music]
okay no one is allowed to be in reach
for that bastard
actual [\h__\h]
no hair is good
what's up what the [\h__\h] man
[Music]
's fine I think
this will hurt nice nice
remember six percent crit payback [\h__\h]
RNG is on my side this time
haha
RNG changed
[Music]
that's okay better turn so far yeah all
right
all right we have dealt with that stupid
ass dragon
whoa
thank God
made me pretty mad
you're pretty mad not gonna lie
what if you
can you reach no
not the longer one there what kind of uh
ball do they have that they're able to
arrange me but I can't reach them what
is that a long bone I don't have one I
forgot that wait ah
I traded the long ball with the other
one
ah okay I need to buy a second longbow
remind me of that another time
um It's The High Ground
let me take a frog candy not the old one
that I spit out
I'm gonna put that one in anymore
Chuck Conley with Alia if you want oh
my
[Music]
God
I don't think I have another one
[Music]
I'll apologize later still getting that
kill though
[Music]
are they gonna come from that side
how close should I go to the mage
[Music]
and over here
I'll risk it
wait
emblem engage no way I keep on thinking
Tiki does the same thing as Linda's
keep on mixing them up the green haired
girls
um he said Marin
does Maron even get that far
[Music]
no boundary on my baby
I hope she survives I should give her
the
uh Revival Stone
oh
wait I could do that right now
I'll Stand in here
I'll
should I do that now
maybe it's a bit too early
next turn although next time I might
want to attack
when I need to protect her
a divine blessing for my beloved Divine
Exquisite Celine
it's all right I can recharge at the top
it's okay
[Music]
oh she got geosphere already
how is kagetsu's Magic resistance guys
15 is that good or bad
[Music]
I have no idea
man
decent
wait I can do the shift down bed
wait that means if if that one goes for
her with a long range attack AKA Magic
would my shield Gambit work
or does it not work for magic does it
only work for like bows and javelins or
so
it works
my work
thinking it looks okay well fabulous
so if the AI is smart and goes for the
one that would be weaker to Magic but
then turns out they have a shield gamut
that they don't know about then we happy
here Lauren that's a lot of people
targeting him
no please
uh 100 19.
[Music]
break
no they all break anyway
uh careful here no I'm angry
you put up a great fight
ah she doesn't have
um
blue
shade lagging behind
stay like 61 86 66
okay I'm gonna go
me first
[Music]
oh
so can we follow that up
[Music]
a dagger in your heart
you're such a beast yeah
you know ever since kisana now with Jade
too I have quite the appreciation for
armored strong women
ah
um
they are very Charming
[Music]
dangerous
and if I'm here will that uh
no the dragon won't come to me okay
[Music]
um
wait arrows are good for flying ones but
what about javelins are they they're
very dangerous to me
as a flyer
no
okay thank god well then
[Music]
why am I why am I letting him like
attack me because
from here should be good
because he have a he does have a javelin
but it doesn't do much damage okay here
I see him he's my own eyes there's a lot
of guys don't yeah I know we'll see what
happens
[Music]
don't know
if all four of them
go for her I might want to give them
another option
but that's
what if I engage
[Music]
can I do something
um
Palm
I know
ah
oh I could do a bonded shield on her
what do you think about that
if I take a step back
[Music]
why should I protect him though he's not
really protected with that though
oh well
okay beautiful already they didn't even
go for the front too
yeah I love this game so much it's so
much fun riveting you were a worthy
opponent I love seeing how the strategy
plays out yeah
ah
[Music]
well and here we see the effect of our
Shield
what is that is that is
the Sheep it didn't look like it
was Unforgettable
I'm only having 53 chance
we just missed
they also tell me what the [\h__\h] it's not
working
but she's she's burning them all it's a
nice tonight we're having horse meat
whether you like it or not
and I don't really like it but you know
sometimes it's gonna take what you get
so yeah yeah I saw it's like 80 chance
or so but that's pretty high even though
it didn't work
[Music]
because we're already grilling it
yucky yucky um
don't need no one protecting her yes she
refuses
the help of fogado
all right here's some beautiful magic
for you
some L fire
me first
unforgivable feels so good
game
strategy is so much fun
but now I should I don't even need
[Music]
Ed
no one she lets herself cook
as she can
yeah out of dragon guy range I don't
know what the [\h__\h] is the matter with
that one well we need our Archer to deal
with him
on our archers I don't know where's our
Archer
Rogers right here forgotten for God is
our Archer I forgot all that I forgoto
is our Archer I forgot
um
[Music]
I don't remember when
we had those runs did the dragon ever
kill diamond
I think he may be another that's what
I'm thinking like
it could be quite helpful to get done
um so otherwise
yeah okay I'll I'll I'll wait first
because the others have to come closer
anyway it's okay
see
because they they have to catch up
down there so far
mama
what about here no okay
there's one more left
[Music]
your ivys is once defense is Jade holy
[\h__\h]
what
it's not even heavy armor
[Music]
go for the left one I'll go for an
almost kill on the right one
[Music]
I think might go for the top one
the death grip is pretty huge
oh nice very tanky that's good because I
plan on using her
a lot
[Music]
in the future too
left and Bone Shield
[Music]
wait who does bone shoot
that was cool was it not
yes yes okay it was I was listening this
time sorry for ignoring you last time
and you had to ask a second time
so cool
pillar is unreachable
nah okay with my Lancy girl I'm gonna
stay one step back or two steps back
Shield Gambit there
all right fine with me
[Music]
it doesn't work like that I just
realized hey
we did it for the right person because
he's going for coffee but
wait Shield games
man oh he died so
yeah arranged only
throwing a hand accent me man
I love appreciated that do I really want
to go this far
[Music]
Shield
there's only three enemies up there
though so I don't have to send everyone
[Music]
are interesting
I'll go for it I'm impatient I'm like
really impatient
I'll be fine
I saw the show and if not we just have
to rewind
[Music]
come on
oh
I love the tippy tappy sounds from the
wolf
the
only Wolfie girl here
[Music]
he had 20 hit rate though would have
been Fair trans
dad like everything else so far
[Music]
I guess so Opie
all right here we are
but
sadly
not a kill and our hit chance is really
low with the killable
please please
okay no credit but we did hit
um
can we finish it with magic with the
fondue
no not quiet
um
what other options do I have
[Music]
um
yeah that's it
kind of
yeah the magic lamp system with green HP
chances of the two no way
[Music]
Astra storm
grant me strength
yeah well okay there's a charging plate
over there
I'll do it this one
[Music]
work and worth it
meditation
[Music]
I forgot about you all Chris
he's probably like yeah
understandable I'm so forgettable my
name should be forgotto
yes
that's not helping his confidence I
think
thank you
foreign
slapping me with the wings
oh pretty ones wow
thank God he doesn't get a second hit
didn't miss
but yeah that's right kage so you have
become Unstoppable don't worry you'll
get a heal now I'll do my best to heal
you
can I reach yeah okay
maybe I don't even have to reach what
what healing staff does she even have
mending okay
have to reach
that was close my father had to rewind
again
my Pinette is a little lagging
why why
percentage really low
hmm
not at the pillars
maybe I should engage too
our machine where it does okay I'm not
gonna engage for so little HP not gonna
engage for 10 HP
59.80
but he might not he's gonna miss me too
like
if I miss he'll miss too
I haven't
oh you love my respect
yes girl
see
come and face me
destroy
oh he needs two hits
and I'll finish with kiwawa down here
[Music]
can you finish him though
oh don't make me
don't make me make me engaged for that I
can't even engage already engaged
[Music]
can you reach no no
nothing but truth hi yeah
seven percent crit
[Music]
seven
seven percent oh wow
oh wow
there was no crit
but
I don't think this one will give us much
trouble afterwards oh look actually
hey we can finish it after all
I have no choice but I forgot about our
first candy
[Music]
at least I remember him at some point
that's nice right
okay uh how are we looking up here two
enemies
um
what comes from doubles
she has one turn left
for her engagement
I know there's still one down there I
know I know
oh cool doubles
so they'll be busy with that for a
moment
I will not lose
[Music]
kill the kill to connect
77 percent
for the first no for the 34 one
[Music]
thank you
I'm sorry you had to see that
[Music]
in Japanese there's a word
or like kind of slang word
Japanese
it's a phrase
Maji is real right and punished is like
awesome like and then it's like really
awesome
so I think for panette we can say Panet
is Maji panis
[Music]
well you're welcome for a random random
knowledge
foreign
[Music]
they are gonna go for the doubles right
usually they go for the doubles
so I will risk it
oh
break it open forcefully
yo
devils are sick
yeah oh
good side
on both sides
oh
Alan those are sword and uh
those are Lance oh
oh yeah that's
it
[Music]
what I did there but I got
eh
I Got One X fighter here
[Music]
anything's anything's fine
I always expect unexpected
yeah nice I know this like last time
when I streamed Fire Emblem and I used
the double doubles once I don't think
they got to do any damage
which is why I
didn't realize how good they were
hmm
[Music]
but yeah now I definitely do feel like
Unforgettable
wait what he missed
realize that happened
oh oh whatever
I can I just I was so short I was so
sure he would be fine
God damn it
[Music]
he won't
come over here to attack me anyone
so I might as well go in range what
about the others so far
I don't just want to charge though
oh he's safe in there
you say
all right you know what it's the
stalling turn
it
all right start fine
oh no
next turn
foreign
[Music]
26 months
at all
I'm pretty sure the percentages are
optimized
nah they wouldn't do such a thing to us
they can't just lie to us
the numbers must be true
they have to be
Civic
[Music]
um
yeah
I'm gonna go over here you guys don't
need me
oh Chris how you doing
can't reach huh all right
[Music]
oh 28 months 16 months thank you guys
thank you
[Music]
I don't remember him
okay
did I forget someone
and besides our crease
and two even your name is who sounds
kind of like me
[Music]
for one thing we're able to touch
untouchable
ha
hmm
so nice looking to tell them though
thanks for the membership thingies thank
you guys
I was going for endurance stream what no
this isn't normal you should know
normal length
but see I told you I would try my best
to have like
normal Chihuahua length streams
although next week I will not be able to
play Fire Emblem the week after though
[Music]
boots
Magic Ball the ball is cracked
oh
quit
[Music]
not a whole door
exciting
javelin
what else can I do
okay
thank you it doesn't sound like much but
they're probably the best item in the
game
um yeah yeah I really have to put them
on a slow slow boy
Jade could use some boots too but um
yeah verily
thank you guys
for being so supportive thank you soon
we're gonna use both tanks then so what
do you mean both tanks
Jayden Louie you mean yeah
I'm kind of wanna
[Music]
I'm so indecisive
I still need to open up here
and there were only two
ah you're not gonna go back and help
maybe maybe is that worth going man
[Music]
don't have to go
wait and wait for them anyway
I'll be you've been using it since you
were small
okay but I didn't steal it from you
either okay
let me go up here I'll fire the [\h__\h] out
of you
for alucia
[Music]
yeah I guess
um
just thinking that
Fiona could
open the door so then we would have one
turn less wasted but
[Music]
to put up a good fight
oh 20 moms thank you yeah y'all are
flexing on me
hehehe
could you possibly do something here
um I wonder if that's a kill in
combination with the wolf girl I forgot
how much damage she would be doing
I feel like I feel like risking it
let's have some fun
[Music]
see can we get him out of the way yes
wait did he get a crit
because
okay I'll take back I take back my
doubts about the numbers being lies I do
think they're lies
[Music]
I'm happy about it but
that makes no sense
me first
you were a worthy opponent
search up fa Fates RNG for full
explanation
there's an explanation which means they
cannot admit
that the numbers are lies
[Music]
there's a true hit formula an equation
okay
um now we need these ones to come back
ASAP
I wouldn't mind if they spawn some
enemies here
[Music]
is it possible for them to one hit the
door
you know can't reach after all
[Music]
hmm
oh yeah at least we can like warp Ivy
back faster but still
um
this is what I was trying to look at
it's all the same
should I just leave everything to you
and I've got one that was kind of too
late but
um
what am I doing
I know
I don't know I don't know
foreign
I'll just I'll just have to wait a
couple turns for everyone to come back
I said that and then
my fingers just
decided to wait as well
oh
no when when you're doing what you're
saying even though you don't want to do
this I I very confused look at his steel
blade it's green
but my percentage is too low
51 that's even lower
oh yeah I get it yay
um
I already appreci should be okay
[Music]
everything's going all right
wasn't him with Marin for the damage
book oh well I mean the outcome would
have probably been the same
this time Darren gets the kill
no he doesn't oh [\h__\h]
the [\h__\h]
me
huh
I don't have to longbow
come on
[Music]
let me help
Orange
let's go a really shitty level up though
still little Dane
that's
all the useful things I could do this
turn I think I don't want to infiltrate
yet
so I'm ending my turn
hydration and stretch check
um okay stretching hurts so bad right
now
I can't even move my arm
up much
it hurts so much I'm so [\h__\h] I've been
like stretching though trying to make it
better but it's not really getting
better
right now
I really think the massage overstretched
my body
[Music]
like only my only my arms though
number one
okay I just need these people up here to
get their freaking business done
[Music]
just open the door normally she's like
Ivy calm the [\h__\h] down don't try to fire
the door down you can just
open it normally like a normal person
look
[Music]
you're late
you're late you didn't hear my request
for face tattoos
I want tattoos like connect
in PNG form please
I could do it myself if I had my tablet
here
no I don't
I feel I feel mean I've been requesting
so much
Lulu likes it right
I hope
how far can I go okay
[Music]
I don't wanna heal a great deal of um
allies HP she only has such little
moment you know what I mean
I have to say you
are your team
was she in range just now
oh she might have been
okay let's try the battle early
I guess
fine with me
yeah she can take it
[Music]
pulling the bus early that reminds me of
Emma Murphy tea time so man when you go
into a dungeon people get so [\h__\h]
panic panic panic panic everybody starts
panicking we're not ready
I'm buffing everyone we're still doing
the Buffs you little [\h__\h] you [\h__\h]
idiot
and then the whole party
wipes
oh man it's too relatable
I think they'll be like that
oh
you look you little [\h__\h]
[Music]
unbelievable well now I can use my
mending
unbelievable
unbelievable I I just
saved me
[Music]
no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no
you think that's a 10.
[Music]
yes she did
hey I'm sorry you had to see that they
keep getting lower yet they still keep
Landing
yeah I'm incredible I'm absolutely
cursed in my 40 hours I only got credit
four times
yeah I've been getting credit a lot
today though like
in it what was it down here right
down right right here
so many crits today
what's going on maybe I am cursed
all right how we looking here
should I just
um you know what since she can warp and
also goes really far with her dragon
love her and I'll go back
worms wear one oh that's for the flying
dragons isn't it
yeah effective dragons sick
like pay close close attention to this
whole room
I see pillars I see two a four I'm doing
so
besides that I don't see what else you
want me to pay attention to
[Music]
a couple
that boss too
I mean no
you know so that's why I'm waiting for
everyone
reinforcement pieces to murder modern
Farms
I will not be murdered so easily
and we have all engaged moons
[Music]
except for you
ah okay
huh
but they are so far
but they I guess they can just fly
straight over
well I'll crisp
our Lord and savior our Christ
and forgado who will not be forgotten
will wait for you guys gladly
[Music]
I guess
well more memberships let's go thank you
it's made out of all Christ
oh Christ
more eggs for my breakfast egg salad
[Music]
I think after this chapter we'll end it
because we're already at seven and a
half hours so we'll be at eight hours
after this I didn't think it would take
so long wow wow wow
[Music]
I mean it broke didn't have more was
that the last board
so
what
what oh not longer still had had a
couple oh well she got really far with
that so
I'm happy
I think
that's it again
here they come now I think they're in
reach from me at least once I think I
think I think I think I think
I could even
use her and then just charge again
no because when it's a wrong
wrong right not taking it where's Lynn
um
[Music]
Blends on you
oh man
and you're not charged
oh God damn it every time Green Girl
gets me every time
[Music]
but
where is my
ideal
would I be able to reach
um and Jake
the
no
no I wouldn't
sad
do we get some healing here
okay she couldn't go to the middle
anyway
you can only hit wait
because you don't have wait
[Music]
reach the middle and then with the rest
I guess we'll just
let ourselves be hit
[Music]
and
um
maybe I'm bind
uh yeah I'll just wait the turn and see
what happens I think
unless
um
I have another life to one of them
and then just lend me a strip
that's one thing I can definitely do
you are safe with me
if it doesn't work I'll just I'll just
rewind
both arches away Flyers come closer come
to them yeah
wait who knows maybe orange juice on my
side
you never know
[Music]
oh
oh no okay
believe it
is
[Music]
all right no problem I mean
no problem for me
wait but they will still go for him
right
[Music]
although if I stand here to give him the
stone
um one of them will probably go for the
other one because he can't go around
emblem engaged three one brother nah
it's okay
I like it this way
although we could bring someone there if
they're gonna walk over here anyway we
can just bring someone there who has
high resistance against them
and put all crystals aside for now
right uh
who like Jade Maybe
she lacks one sword but I don't know
like
would Jane be strong enough she would be
fine right
build a wall
what about diamonds
but diamonds
Diamond cool too
it's good
[Music]
sword
uh
should I really do that
I'll take the steel sword then
interesting interesting strategy
it's almost like we're playing Prodigy
game
[Music]
oh wow
that's impressive damage on my jade
oh
still the hammer that's answer Hammer
um
okay
interesting
and now they're going down she lives so
we're good yes
I have plenty of time down here
are hot you're telling me you cannot
take down this Dragon are you sure no
still
that's where it says
I'll apologize
[Music]
they didn't take even half of her speed
damage from a freaking hammer
I guess yeah if you consider how
effective it is and yeah that's
definitely very strong
and we'll take some Revenge right now
you wanna let's go put the combine ax I
love the ring right I love them too I
think I already got one more than than
what's shown on there or no wait no
there's still too many isn't it
oh is it does my hand have the DLC rings
too
I'm not sure I don't recognize them all
but I think it's missing the new ring
that we got
ah the place
so
what are all these rings then
[Music]
do I really have this many rings only I
only have like four or five
I thought I took the ride in the right
hand though
oh it has the ones I lost to okay I
guess so I thought we wouldn't have them
right now
you know on the hands
but
okay okay
Unforgivable
she's so sexy
[Music]
I think
I wanna go straight in
because I want to make use of my
engagement
what do you think
do it
yeah
before it runs out you know
[Music]
how far do I go how far do I go too far
sword sword sword sword sword
sword bad
[Music]
there now the front one is definitely
spotting me that's okay
I just want to finish this map now
else I'm gonna lose it
no
[Music]
oh you went for the wolf girl after all
huh
a lot of damage there
oh wow
my problem is that Kiana is poison too
it's not really nice
but also once I walk in there are they
all gonna come for me
that would be a disaster
yes
hmm
okay first of all
[\h__\h] um
antitoxin
[Music]
toxins
it's not worth it no I need to recharge
all right I'm going back okay well I
want to recharge
[Music]
uh-huh
at least you can use it right away
still going yeah
I must keep on going
there's no other way
[Music]
uh
I forgoria that's what I was planning to
do though
we kind of have to wait for kiwawa
anyway so
I'll do it next turn
[Music]
USA
I don't want to go too far inside so
this way works
work
teamwork
way to shine
but who has it right now
oh look at her and hello they're so
sweet together
I want a fluffy companion right now too
but my cut those are
so far
oh if I go here I'm uh pulling some mobs
I feel like I'm ready for it
but I'm scared
plenty of things Shield Gambit hell yeah
[Music]
lineage
okay he can go pretty far
without being targeted
[Music]
stay
stay wait a second
there's someone there next to me who
could use that no
that little blade I got in my inventory
of her
yeah I know I've been on charge I know
that's what I'm doing now don't worry
the stolen rings for the music was sick
no
oh oh 43 43 percent
why
your army is not to be trifled with
because I respect you oh foreign
[Music]
oh
yeah bye
just like rave music or so
where can she reach
okay
oh actually it might be about to go here
charging
[Music]
turn it up turn it up
all right well well how do we deal with
this [\h__\h] bye yeah bye I mean there's
one flying one so
all I can deal with that one pretty well
four run
oh hey but fugano has the the extra life
so it's okay that he takes some damage
and even if an exchange she can take one
full HP bar
if you didn't
I'll engage him after he loses the first
one
good good good good good good
was good that we gave him that
beforehand
without uh again without knowing what
will happen
wait who are we
what who's that who's that
okay we'll engage
let us become
houses unite that bastard but it doesn't
kill him
can you believe it
flame Lance
hold up combat Arts
oh atrocity
atrocity kills okay I'm I'm perfectly
happy with that
um okay
my orders do not
I would say kill him but they all got
two HP bars
or did I already
take one
Excellence
he was a normal unit
um
that's embarrassing for him
oh only defined Hortensia all right then
then
[Music]
is that another red mark
Marnie Marnie also just a normal unit
damn damn uh
all right
freaking access sick but she has is she
considered a full armor unit a heavy
armor unit that's
problem but
this music is so intense
[Music]
yeah my mage
bye-bye
Philadelphia morning next turn
[Music]
kill kill her with
no
no no no no no no
[Music]
all right first look at the normal one
okay
I'll curse can't read [\h__\h] I think
the hammer would be good on the left
side
[Music]
Collectibles next turn so if she goes in
there it will hit her
but it doesn't
even kill
the lady
well I might finish with diamonds
it's at the lane and you're to hit Area
next turn
okay
all right well we'll see what happens
we'll be interesting and then
how much damage does he take again oh
two months
but it's okay we can lose we can lose
some units for a greater
grade of purpose right
but maybe someone who loses a little bit
less
75 shouldn't Miss
yeah she
she I don't think so
at least Marin would take way less
damage from that so and 53 is pretty low
I'm gonna go with that
uh looks like she didn't miss but okay
[Music]
what's up
but then it isn't a great a for a huge
waste unless the other one walks over to
our side into the Aether area
but I think she'll walk in I think she
will
foreign
especially if we bring Diamond over here
too
where where was it again it was like
here
here or also here
was it here too
I don't remember
two squares two spaces around Samara one
two
and this one too one two
one two
so I don't want to block that I I would
go I would go here hoping that okay it
will lead Marnie to come closer to us
[Music]
okay and in the meantime I'll just move
everyone closer
[Music]
okay
curious curious outcome
oh
nice
that didn't really do anything
Palace is so pretty oh it's a nicer tune
than you deserve
oh
foreign
she went right in my range
grade A for hitting
here we go
what about the hammer
but it was kind of cool though
I lived an eye on the hill
I'm fine
I am very fine
now uh who gets to
he has to finish this
Celine Selena is Selena range now yeah
but it also puts her in a dangerous
other range oh wow
gotta take some risks now it's time
you're slippery that's the only reason I
lost
sure make those excuses
and hide behind your Shield literally so
that we can't see your shame hurricane
eggs
I like that one
looks very strong magic eyes we're
getting some new magic weapons now
we'll think about who to use them all
next time all right
um
my range
will not reach right
emblem
not time yet
[\h__\h] the music is so good
job it
that's better
man
[Music]
am I getting
can't sleep without my blankie
I must Focus
oh
[Music]
no
I do what do I do oh wait I can even
reach this dude
this might be
kind of like suicide for diamonds but
I kind of want to do it
yeah it's like a train
understand
remember
show how cool you are diamond and leave
exactly two exp out there yeah to
trigger me real hard
all right whatever I'm moving in like
I'll give you a big Choice again and uh
oh
take down this
illusion soldier with me
hard Mode's too easy
I'm so easy
finger licking easy
I'm licking my fingers that are covered
in the blood of my enemies
[Music]
foreign
let's just go
don't care
all right stream vampire stream for
blood both of them
so she had three HP bars
these are strong
strong lady mentally
Brewing
um I feel so sorry for her though cause
like she was crying
and now she's all alone and we're going
at her with like a full party
oh Louie what a beautiful beautiful
watch this
attacked first with a dagger
hmm
if you poison someone and they lose one
HP bar do they still have the poison
afterwards
oh it's oh I'm sorry I'm sorry
sorry skip the message with the Rings
I must say okay
[Music]
I'm just I guess I'm getting okay for me
it was a big big dialogue I'm so
beautiful why it really
probably just like two sentences
I will defeat you
the only way to
oh she's trying to resist you see it
because she's holding one eye closed
the emblem is searching the Spell dragon
Energies
anime characters and you ain't always
have one eye closed
both sink with dark emblems may enter a
rampage State when they use Revival
Stones be careful their additional
strength comes from forcing their
emblems power out of control
I'll be fine oh they uh just got some
new peeps in okay
[Music]
oh
my God
what is that
my normal attack is stronger
literally like
what the heck
um it's supposed to be used when I have
yeah yeah true true the one for all yeah
yeah because it gets all the chain
attacks
indeed
how can we do this
one kind of late
could have given another Stone perhaps
but
strong first
shouldn't be stressed out about wearing
killing the boss right now I'm not sure
no I'm not late to something I'm never
late to anything
I watched the clip of Muna Senpai
um missing or not missing but like
forgetting and being late to her
meetings two days in a row because she
was playing for too long
funny
yeah
it's always like her gem mates or cool
eyes
reminding her
um
wait this should this should finish off
one HD bar
72 percent
foreign
[Music]
let's go boss I am going
I I can't kill her so I'm gonna take the
ESP from him
you put up a good fight
honey I and did I give a handbags I'm
not sure
okay next move next round
that's it
that will be it
final blow
yeah and anyway I don't think she was
able to reach
next week
are we going through this with not a
single casualty perhaps
that's quite out of character for me oh
[\h__\h]
shut up added Joby that hurts I don't
want to hear such a thing
it's probably partially crony's Falls
too
she influenced us
oh calm down we don't have to kill
him
come on
who wants to kill we can't share it too
much unfortunately you know what I'll
give it to Tamara because she just
joined us
but 68 is actually really low she might
lose she might miss
she has the sword of the Creator me
first what is that called that because
oh
sharing is caring is it called that
sword because it's the first Fire Emblem
ever don't worry what's what's that all
about huh
we're sharing the kill after all hmm
but flux something will yeah
yeah oh it's the bile of salt what why
does nothing go my way
what why does she have the bile of storm
19 turns well that's the longest one yet
I think
[Music]
that's
it
oh that's male bilaf
but Justin red because he was angry and
Evil
but I want female boiler will they show
me female by love too does someone have
female buy love please
no what the [\h__\h]
what
what the [\h__\h]
why is male part of Cannon
it's not fair
patient at least get let me make the
choice
oh
what the [\h__\h] that's
[Music]
we live in this society that prefers
males what the [\h__\h]
I'm just joking but
what the [\h__\h] man you
like I love my female violence she's
such a cutie patootie and I went for so
much reverse no oh
Erin I don't give a [\h__\h] about those
others free houses the only one I played
[\h__\h]
man
oh man
Ivy what happened oh you've come back to
me thank goodness
where'd all the illusion soldiers go
they retreated
I should go with them no it's not safe
safia could take control over you again
but
trick father left behind that is true
but it's out of our hands how can you
say that don't you care about illusion
come on
[Music]
I would have given my life to protect
our kingdom but it is not our kingdom
anymore it's the fell dragons surely you
see that
Princess Ivy I didn't want to admit it
but father stopped being King as soon as
the fell Dragon awoke since then true
power has rested with sombron his
daughter and the four hounds
[Music]
if you went back now
you would become an instrument of their
designs just as father was
how badly
feat the fell Dragon after allowing
father to relinquish his power to
sambron
we owe our people no less
Castle
my only home since I was little
we really can't go back now can we no
we can't that little Nook where I had
tea with my friends
the garden where you and I read together
and old Mary oh I've left everything and
everyone I don't know what happens to
them
all right I'll find them help join this
fight we'll find them so that someday
things can be like they were again thank
you Hortensia
yeah it took her long enough to join me
before
what I did
Divine One
you should have this the Ring of the
instructor
one of the Rings stolen from lethos
thank you for returning it
don't give me too much credit I like it
I wasn't exactly planning to hand it
over even though my thanks
[Music]
teach us emblem of the academy
the Simpson
okay he looks really good
look female Palace is cuter I am emblem
bylith it feels as though I've just
awoken from a very long dream and she
ships so well
[Music]
with my beloved
anal guard
I'm glad to be where I belong at your
side
use my power to guide everyone I will
thank you emblem so true
[Music]
so
how is everyone
Euphoria you're all right that I am some
illusion soldiers tried to seize me but
I was saved at just the right moment we
took him down
Alfred and I intended to help
but by the time we'd run our weapons the
fight was already over
that's the song Royal
guard pretty good right I'm just glad
the queen is safe well done everyone
well done yourself no more trespassers
my Palace is rid of them yeah
thank you for protecting the Rings and
my family
the way you spoke the look in your eyes
you were the spitting image of Queen
Lumera
your words mean so much
thank you
um excuse me Queen sephoria you I
assumed you had gone back to illusion
look I'm really sorry about what I did
I'll accept whatever punishment you give
me I owe you an apology as well
Queen sephoria please
zafia was using some sort of magic to
control princess Hortensia as soon as it
wore off she stopped fighting
even gave me her emblem ring I don't
recall about you being there when the
young princess held me hostage look me
in the eyes you two
okay threatening a queen's life is a
grave crime you deserve a room in the
dungeons oh
but
I won't send you there you won't it was
the film dragon's minion her usual room
with the conflict right your only crimes
were slipping in Uninvited and
threatening to kill me if you want to
make amends defeat the fell Dragon
rebuild your kingdom
when cooler heads return to illusia zom
can only benefit
let's move on now shall we thank you
Queen sephoria your show of compassion
will not be forgotten
we will restore illusion
I swear it for my part I think I'd
better look into Shoring up the palace's
defenses Hortensia looks like
like her eyes
make me feel like it's an aqua Senpai
that's drawn by uemomo
or of course
Bales mama
but I think it's actually also kind of
similar to Lee Mama
um you know
surrender samplines
eyes
um
actually not that different
you're right the fell dragons similar
way of drawing eyes I can leave some
soldiers here to help keep you safe
Oh No need no need I have lots of family
members who can handle things here if
the situation really boils over I can
always leave a double here and wander
the land so don't worry about me you
just focus on taking out the fell Dragon
we will
thank you Tamara it's time you showed
the Divine Dragon where to find some's
other ring what's your thing mom one
ring of the Crux of Fate coming right up
imagine me right away the northern
Fortress no oh
you don't scare easily do you I'm doing
now a fight for it
or dancing
[Music]
finally 40
000. finally there's some money too
danke schoenya military funds you better
I helped I saved your country
save your queen uh-huh
I deserve more than that even
emblems talent for instruction boosts
allies
instruction
that's funny reference I guess because
they were in a school
uh stats and guides them to Victory the
sync skill the Bible will sometimes turn
this attack since it hits
[Music]
yeah I get it I get it I get it that's
the point oh yes I'm just so happy
because this is the only one I really
understand
emblem violence first engaged weapon is
a hero is Relic an item that is
different for each unit type
oh
yeah yeah the engage skill instruct
grants a stat bonus to surrounding
allies
do you like him now no the engagement
attack got this dance grants a stand
booster and Jason Alice in the powers
those who have already added to turn
that to act again yeah
really cool really cool really cool
uh anyway so if I have buy love
uh do they have like an inherent thing
for dancing
then I can teach everyone
because that's kind of what I was
waiting for
no
oh what
[Music]
what
that's it
and
no time for dance
[Music]
y'all
it's really pretty
this
place is really pretty
[Music]
they did a good job
on this one
[Music]
um
well details
sorry are you a guard
Divine One
it's gonna pick up all the items and I
think um
I'm gonna leave it at that
and then
I guess I'll read some super chats
again someone will fall behind again but
right now I think I'm do I only have to
read the ones from this stream
forgive me
four more hours
I'm gonna eat um dinner with the girls
when they come back
so yeah uh I'm also hungry now damn I
could eat the croissant though
I stream eight hours what
I'm behind on hold here ah okay
all righty
hmm
another ring in the Divine dragon's
hands
still
not enough to turn the tide unless I
activate my DLC
girl
sleep
curse this feeble form of mine for
plunging me into darkness I pray that
next time my waking hours will not end
so soon
know about the DLC
she didn't watch the Nintendo Direct
my
respect to normal
why does this keep happening to me hmm
well she really doesn't know
she likes critical information
I guess like her eyes changed her red
the same way that um hortensia's eyes
changed to red
so she can go back to normal just as uh
Hortensia did
[Music]
okay
she got possessed that's all that's all
there is to it she's a good girl
and
or the other one is normal there no who
gets possessed and then turns from Evil
to nice it's always the other way around
okay uh do I have oh
[Music]
I might just read Supercuts in here
I'm just gonna read them here
um
[Music]
yeah we have a nice bgm here
uh wait brain horde uh here uh
monetization supers
okay hold up here super chats do I have
the thumbnail for that somewhere
think I saw it somewhere
[Music]
I feel like
where where and when did I make the
whole look here from now oh I made it
I made it before I came
in oh you're right because I was like oh
oh oh on the day when I come to Japan
I'm gonna stream hola cure
because that's gonna be extra fun
[Music]
being really exhausted
okay I have to download it
[Music]
damn it
free a.m good night thank you for
staying for so long
a cool stream thank you happy red girls
talk oh bye
maybe I haven't because in the members
only I probably only read the members
only super chats
and then I might have not read the girl
stock ones
[Music]
[Applause]
okay but they shouldn't be too many
foreign
[Music]
what's what's with all these blue cat
sticker super sticker
super chats
and the bananas
are you trying to scare the cats with a
banana
[Music]
sapling thing
pretty odd yeah that's pretty odd
uh-huh
is that what they always do with fauna
[Music]
oh there we go
I miss my cartoons
they better be all right I think it's
supposed to look like snail it does look
like snail
okay here you go and Katie Bitcoin Jim
Tracy Duncan
no I can't read this one
[Music]
hmm
I belonging
ITA thank you
let me explain to the pinky work has
been busy lately but I want to share
that race I got to you ah thank you I
may be missing more streams and sleeping
through them more often for a while but
I'll make time to say hi and watch the
birds thank you for making me smile like
you I will love you my Aussie thank you
are you able to watch today
where's your minutes I'm looking for
other you are yay
first you were here the whole time yeah
because um you're in an sea time zone
right and it's the weekend so
we woke up early for me thank you but so
during the day so
yeah not the worst time for you I'm
happy nice
thank you so much for the raise and and
I'm proud of you for getting that raise
in the first place good job for working
hard but don't overwork yourself okay
thank you so much for the support Unix
thank you soon
seven Channel
Canada Goose
[Music]
where only saplings aware that fauna
wasn't gonna be the one reading the
super jumps
Evan
foreign
[Music]
to avoid winter cold in Germany right
now so I booked flight to Vietnam again
time for me to join sea gang next week
oh
well that's actually perfect in terms of
watching my streams I guess
but wow cold chunk of elderly that's a
thing
so you have to bring your dad somewhere
else
for for a week or so to avoid the cold
orange
my grandma was like that
that's nice of you John for like taking
care of your dad and going with him to
camera that's really sweet
Spirit bedtime
well think about it guys am I orange
Bono or is fauna orange green Chihuahua
[Music]
JB dancing
made a good point right
direction sir 956 extension brick pain
medicine thank you
Giancarlo Gilberto
the girls talk will be very informative
for me since I had strange luck of being
surrounded almost my entire life by
men's because of having two brothers and
having chosen engineering as my career
choice ah my curiosity is awakened thank
you for the stream ladies
well do you regret it or did you enjoy
it I wonder I hope you enjoyed it maybe
you learned something from it
thank you for coming by uh I felt a
little bit pressured after you guys
being so hyped about it in the first
place but I feel like the real the real
spicy girls talk stuff it's not really
something that would be discussed in a
stream here so
um I was like you know trying to find
inspiration for girl stock
um
like on topics so I I looked up on
YouTube Girls Talk podcast
and we're just girls talk I'm not sure
and well
they all kind of talk about the same
thing
apparently girls talk on YouTube Just
consists of like one category of topics
um very different from our girls talk so
uh yeah
yeah like it's more like boys talk
um and very spicy Boy song so well that
wasn't much of a help
anyway thank you
I appreciate it very much thank you soon
plain water down because soon I'll run
the wins thank you soon Joseph
no idea
Mr empty block done kitchen Mrs
dankishan
thank you
foreign
but if you don't pop the pimples how do
you collect the pimple cheese
that is so disgusting
that is a very disgusting Super Chat
and I had to read it because it's a
pinky
that's so disgusting I
I hate it
[Music]
sir 956
what
film thank you
second time thank you for the rest of
the chat thanks for sharing all of this
classified girl information with us we
promise only to use it for good also I'm
apparently an honorary girl because I
love cats no that's not really what I
meant
it was hard to explain what I meant
um I just I didn't want to like say two
obvious things so I went with something
like that but
that's yeah that's not what I meant
I saw the Chad's confusion while I was
talking and I was confusing myself too
um so I tried to backpedal
oh well oh well you don't seem to mind
spankenheim
thank you so much for watching
I don't know what you meant at all
who knows what I meant
thank you so much I appreciate it
hopefully the next girls talk
will happen eventually and you'll be
there too
honestly I don't think women need to
shave anything unless they want to
should be no shame for body hair
blue of course
of course but um yeah certain people
will
like make you think that it's necessary
and you know that's the I think the most
General
um idea because uh you know we live in a
society and when you look at like models
and so on and models are generally what
will teach young girls what's beautiful
and none of them have body hair
um normally
that just like tells you
everything yeah
yeah papa on the shore that question is
thank you
virtual environment
thank you there's a lot of the like the
exists of makeup that looks like there
isn't makeup I've been about whistle
pierced by this really
should know by now
you're welcome
[Music]
okay girls talk done
I'm gonna do a hollow cure next
month
[Music]
Connection
Blue thank you for two pinkies what's B
and D where's that from ah Vietnam
baby
Vietnamese dollars
probably yeah okay
okay
yesterday was my birthday the second one
that I celebrated revealing kfp thanks
to you I've met so many lovely timkins
and received so much support from them
it's truly amazing to be part of this
community
I didn't even think you were going for
cult I thought you were going for
culture actually
that you have built I'd love to tell you
more about how I feel but some strangers
and green clothes have come and
threatened that I have if I can't manage
to get froggy Mama to sing me a happy
birthday song they'll turn into a frog
help just want to be your cute little
housewife chicken
[Music]
I can't
blush
I don't I can't
it's a rain check
[Music]
no I'm trying to temper no she's
frogging
no no wait
um
uh is Eden watching right now
Eden sent me a certain frog item before
you remember is it in here
you've eaten is here can you really
quickly send me that one
via DM
thank you then I think he even sent me
one before like um yeah the Frog hoodie
with the boobies
yeah
I think maybe it was also uploaded on
Twitter before
I don't see even
[Music]
I could put that one on
if I find it I'm here oh you're here
um
I'm I'm looking at my DMs oh sending one
second are you
can always rely on Ethan
ah kfp you guys
you guys are always here when I need to
always
I'm always on standby
here it is
I did not think
um I would use it uh
like this
now
[Music]
I guess I can take off the Rings now
ah
[Music]
one moment please
does this work
[Music]
a bit bigger
oh yeah
[Music]
oh
no no no no no
no oh
trying to figure out what to attach it
to
uh
[Music]
foreign
happy birthday dear blue happy birthday
dear blue happy birthday you little [\h__\h]
blue
now stop frogging
dear blue
yay not frying time
never once frogging time
it's cute right it's cute but I need to
figure out if there was like a better
way of attaching it because this way
it's
goes like
hi
Eternal time do I look like a turtle to
you
do I look like a freaking Turtle to you
I'm not a turtle anyway happy birthday
blue thank you so much for your support
you're such a sweetie me
and the Rings have been a great asset
for this streaming series from now and
also the other things like I don't even
think I used your QP asset now my
problem is
I want to use both the Rings and The QP
asset now I I'm torn but thank you for
everything so far and also in the future
[Music]
thank you so much I hope you will stay
for a long time and I hope you had a
lovely birthday yeah it was already
three days ago right
I hope everyone treated you well as you
deserve
thank you so much
I hope your resistance against frogging
become stronger now because it's better
unless it doesn't then I have to
push you into the usual room
unfortunately and we don't want that do
we hmm
Cruise thanks for the pinky my sleep
schedule was just recovering from you
last Japan trip but I'll do my best uh
to catch what I can lie well no this one
shouldn't have been too bad for most of
it you're streaming you're streaming in
Japan Japanese but in Japan you mean uh
right and playing final I'm sure is
nostalgic though yeah hope you have
plenty of fun can't wait to share at
home for you and for fast yes
at home is fine too
four fests and some other things are
getting me really excited recently too
so
such as also the thing that was
the announcement that was announced
today
oh so many things to be excited for
um
and some things
you don't even really knows
[Music]
foreign
wish I can be back in Japan this quickly
I was there for snowboarding last few
weeks seeing my schedule I can only
watch this year's Fest again online
yeah too bad but
yeah maybe maybe you can be
in L.A in the summer
for whatever happens in L.A
hmm
we will never know thank you junkie
Chung although La is really far from you
too I guess so
what do you mean
what do you mean I can't contain I'm not
saying anything
I love it I cannot clarify I cannot
clarify I'm gonna get bonked to the void
[Music]
it says it says la
yes I come to LA because apparently
something's happening
thanks for the pinky it's something very
bad has happened so I turned on my
computer
I watched archive blade to have a fun
stream
[Music]
Canton
are you here are you feeling better
[Music]
I hope you're feeling better or
something has cleared up
[Music]
thank you hug sending hugs
but I think it's a good choice to when
you know
I mean I can also cheer you up I guess
but I think it's also good to you know
take a step back
when something bad happens
and uh yeah take care of whatever
happened or you know
get your mind off of it in different
ways
so I hope it helped
thank you ebarden come back to me
most bear dancing and happy belated
birthdays
foreign
I didn't I didn't do that mental Jenny
but yeah interesting how that kind of
happened
um
forcefully in America to meet boxing and
then dogs Miss up at the airport though
they asked me
tonight just
and I would be suspicious looking if I
didn't answer if I refuse to answer them
I can't refuse
whatever GD thanks for the pinky taxi
fund
for which taxi for which taxi I've been
taking a couple taxis
very interesting in Japan you know you
guys maybe know about the doors opening
on their own
that's not the only thing
a lot of the time most of the time only
one door will open even if you're
standing in front of the uh door of the
other side they will not open it for you
just because
[Music]
they will not it's locked and they can't
they're not allowed to open it
um
happened to me like yesterday
yeah the guy told me to go to the other
side and then gave me a lecture on why
he can't open the other door and I was
like yeah I forgot I understand I forgot
I know it's a thing yeah yeah
it's okay
yeah why because he said it's not safe
there could be accidents but the place
where or the streets where he stood to
open up for me was
a quiet
Street which may have even been a
one-way street I'm not sure
and that's why
you know they drive on the left side
normally right but I guess
in this case he was
a parking on the right side of the
street which must mean it was a one-way
street right
right is that what that means trying to
figure out traffic without having a
license that must have been what that
meant yeah yeah so which means in this
case I don't really think that they
would have been danger but it's just
like by default they either don't do it
or they can't do it
hmm
yeah anyway so don't try to enter a taxi
forcefully from the other side okay and
normally they will open it anyway and
they're gonna get a little bit like mad
if you forcefully try to open it on your
own
just wait for it to open I think every
taxi opens their doors in Japan on their
own
I don't think there's any exceptions
hmm
yeah the right door facing no no it was
facing the the path though the the the
sidewalk in this case
most of the times it would be the left
door facing the sidewalk but in this
because because taxes uh or cars in
Japan drive on the left side but in this
case it was the other way around
don't ask me how that works it's just
traffic
um
he opened the door facing the street
yes yes he did the left door and in this
case that was on the street side
yeah
that's nothing too much about it
I'm getting confused too but onions
oh this is when I was when I went to the
other meeting huh couldn't hold back
anymore
that's really weird I mean it happens
sometimes it can't be um
it can't be helped yeah that that would
be more dangerous right
[Music]
then he should be opening the other door
because those cases do exist
oh I should have thrown that argument
back at him
[Music]
hmm
I think I think it might be locked in
general but I feel like he would be able
to somehow open it if need be yeah but
I'm not sure
oh well
Santiago my team thank you for the rest
of the chat Hi boss it's been a long
time since the last Super Chat it was
always almost a year ago oh when I told
you that I was working on a big personal
project but I'm putting it aside for
irrelevant things do you have any advice
on how to focus on 100 you're the best
hmm
well
well I mean first of all how important
is it to you second of all
how much do you really want to do it
um
maybe maybe if you don't really want to
do it then maybe don't force yourself to
do it but
um
[Music]
but if you already have the realization
that you're putting it aside for
irrelevant things for like a whole year
then yeah I'm telling you now to do it
just finish it
finish it and then you're it's done it's
overwhipped and you don't have to think
about it anymore do it
yeah give yourself a deadline I guess
soon deadline and just
do it
watch my Just Do It video
the day when you stop coming to my
stream Tai Chi that will be the day
where I really question what I did wrong
[Music]
foreign
to stream the game one day thanks for
showing off the new Step unfortunately
it's a few more days for us and it helps
for today's story ah well now by now you
guys are already playing it I think
right
and yeah today is that right I didn't
have any hopes for it
because the last one was already so good
and I I had no idea what to expect but
it wasn't okay okay Direct
it was okay
you guys I saw so many guys being really
hyped about silk song
yeah the direct was a lot of today
who are you playing Zelda yeah I think I
will but I think almost everyone from my
whole life will probably play
Zelda so hmm
hmm
but will they finish it that's the
question
[Music]
Zelda will be popular yeah
I think there will be probably less
people that will finish it that that is
truly the question
um for me you have a high chance
that I will start it and finish it as
well so
I am I'm totally up for it you know I
wanted to play another Zelda game this
year anyway and even after
um this one I'll probably play another
one like around the end of the year like
some older one
I'm so
so up for that
Minish Cap hell yeah
would love to play Minish Cap
or any anyone really I actually also
um
what's it called the one that noise is
playing right now a twilight princess I
want to play Twilight Princess too
[Music]
I think I did watch a full playthrough
of Minish Cap a long time ago
but I don't believe it you think I
remember much
[Music]
midnight yeah I like midnight
pull it in
finish cap super fun yay ah the game of
Watch Color yeah I just like realized
later on when I re-watched the Nintendo
Direct afterwards that that was
something I played on
the DS Maybe
before
something like that I played before
looks so familiar
a cow that likes cookies done kitchen
Mary Pippin's Danke Schoen
yeah yeah yeah
I played everything as a kid is
surprisingly more and more things
are coming to light
under that TV
drive by shrimping down Santiago Martin
oh
yay
update looks pretty cool great job on
the clear endless energy drinks watch
out for all those meetings you get
called to for having so many empty cans
especially if they call on the way home
or in the middle of the night
I can mostly control myself I think
mostly and I don't drink that many
anyway no worries I was thinking maybe
drinking one today
so I took one home
yesterday
with the plan of using it today but I
didn't so we good so far
[Music]
thank you
oh that's it for the whole cure super
trans all right I think I'll leave it at
that
it's been plenty long oh my God nine
hours what the [\h__\h]
buddy could you come
[Music]
okay
tomorrow
I'll be at that thing uh tournament and
then later in the day Hollow bags um and
then during the day I have one small
recording and I think
um
and it never ever ends to run
so busy day actually
um
but whole bag should be fun
and uh
[Music]
uh thank you well I think
I think got it what was it gonna say
no idea
too high for all the bags
yeah me too I'm looking forward to that
one for a while
yeah I'll I don't know uh if the girls I
don't think they're back yet I'll be
waiting for them
[Music]
I'll get ready though
I forgot to say something what was that
oh wow
um
enjoy that myth bonding time really
happy you girls have a really nice
chance of going yes me too
me too you still need to practice up the
stream oh yeah
I do need to practice something but it
doesn't necessarily have to be today I
might do a little bit of practicing like
after dinner or so
[Music]
hate comments remember to check the Vlog
for the official level yeah there was
like a one hour off collab in my in my
room
foreign
[Music]
I'm hungry I need to eat the croissant
now I think
myth has already amazing
well I will do my best to continue
streaming
um
properly
uh you know
uh uh there is going to be
quite a couple streams in the next
coming days
this one was an extra long one so I
don't think anyone can complain
I will take I will accept no complaints
whatsoever
I'm doing my best here okay I'm really
like squeezing in filling up every
single free time that I have
um
yeah okay well I haven't been to the
idol meeting for nine hours either so I
will go now
yeah I would love to play more if emblem
too but I don't have time for it for
until uh at least one more one and a
half weeks or so
um
I complain that tender is too cute okay
that one I will accept
for some reason can I dress like a
turtle instead of a frog excuse me what
the [\h__\h] is that's not a turtle
hey
but I'm happy the stream also went
pretty well it was kind of like a test
if I can stream properly here
besides some YouTube troubles
yeah but I'm not sure if that's because
of YouTube or because of my you know
into that connection but and it later
happened was fine right so
um
ice skating teaching who was I who did I
want to teach ice skating muffin
help me
remind me a little bit Anna
ice
ice cold
ice skating
I don't ever have time for that but I
never went ice skating before in Japan
I think it was YouTube it was okay for
me at times when other people oh okay
then it must have been YouTube although
my OBS does tell me I have quite a bunch
of
um lost frames
but I think that was mostly in the
beginning of this room eh would OBS does
anyone know like when it says lost
frames
in OBS is that because like YouTube was
like messing around or is that really my
fault like my my side
[Music]
oh my audio is lagging again
no idea
can be encoding yeah maybe my OBS
settings like because I I had them
changed right to like 720p Etc
though okay oh well oh man it was a fine
stream yeah
considering it was nine hours long
okay
[Music]
alrighty
I'm doing the 720 helped didn't even
notice yeah I'll probably keep it this
way
can be a green bear costume for [\h__\h]
sake it's a frog
okay guys thank you very much for the
long stream it was very comfy and I had
so much fun playing Farmland I love
problem makes me feel so powerful
thank you soon everybody and good night
thank you lots guys
[Music]
foreign
um
thank you
[Music]
foreign
there we go
[Music]