[Music]
[Music] [Music]
[Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [
Music  ]
[Music]
[
Music] [Music] [
Music] [Music]
[Music] [
Music] [Music] [
Music] [
Music] [Music]
[Music]
Gather at the venue  We are
finally starting the broadcast. Our first large-scale event,
Hololive Super Expo 2022,
started at 10 a.m., and a large number of customers have finally
arrived.
Thank you very much, everyone.
Yesterday, the weather was a bit bad.
However, it's been a beautiful sunny day, making it a perfect day for an event
.
Well, that's me. My name is
Nana Noguchi and I'm here today.
Thank you very much.
How are you doing? We've only just begun.
However, I'm sure everyone is already enjoying the atmosphere of the venue, and I was able to
enjoy the venue early,
but I was already excited to see all the
talent's
costumes.  I
usually
see the upper half of my body when I stream, so
sometimes my whole body comes out, but when I thought that I could see her
full body and
in real life, I was
so excited, even thinking about how big she was.
And then there's the
recreated area of ​​the office, where I
looked at the whiteboard and started thinking about medicine,
etc. You can also
see it from the tea stage,
and there's that life-size panel.
How are you all going to the corner
? Hey, there's a lot of talent there too, so I
feel like I can't take it anymore.
But I've been really
excited since this morning. So I said yes,
right away.
This is Makuhari Messe, where a variety of projects are underway.However,
everyone has been really strong since the morning.Thank you very much for
coming here.Also,
everyone who has been watching the latest news has really been working hard
since the morning.  Thank you for being with us. It's
true that no matter
where you look, Hololive is everywhere.Even the
staff members are passionate about
this space.Before every big event and
festival, this is a hot water-boiling ceremony that
takes over and hopes for everyone's prosperity.  To
commemorate the success of Hololive Super Expo 2022, we will
be holding a Kagami Biraki ceremony.
Everyone at the venue and
watching the broadcast, please join us
as we celebrate the great success of these two wonderful days.
That's it.
[Music]
[Applause]
Thank you. Let's get excited
.
First of all, I would like to introduce the people who will
be witnessing this event.
First of all,
Mr. Mikonamin, please
take the stage.
[Music]
Okay.  Ah, it's okay. Everyone here,
let's go at our own pace.
[Music] This is a character created
during the activities of Hololive 0th generation Sakura Miko.
[Music] Take it
slow. Yes,
everyone. Let's proceed with the
event safely.
Continued  Also,
Subaru Cup, please
. He's so cute when he's toddling around. He
came up with a light swish.
Marunouchi-san
is a character that was created during the activities of Hololive 2nd generation member Subaru Ozora.
Next up, Mr. Ahn Kim, please.
He's called Hololive 0.  This
is a character that was born during Tokisora-san's activities.
Yeah, I'm giving it my all.
Next, Mr.
Udin, please talk to me, brother.
Slowly,
slowly,
yes. Uri-san was born during the activities of Crazy Onii-san, a
second-generation member of Corona Inns Indonesia.
Mr. Small Am, please take the stage. [Music] Mr. is a character born from Hololive English Lease Watson Amelia's activity live. Yes, he is full of energy. Finally, on behalf of the organizers, I would like to express my gratitude to Cover Co., Ltd. President
Tanigo  I'm Mototeru.
[Music] I'll
be greeted by a big doctor.
Thank you very much. Well
then.
Before Kagami Biraki, on behalf of the organizers,
Motoaki Tanigo, President and Representative Director of Cover Co., Ltd., will give a greeting as the representative of the organizers.
From now on,
please understand that I will call you Mr. Yago.
Hello everyone.
Everyone gathered at the venue.
Everyone watching the broadcast.
Thank you for coming to Hololive Super Expo 2022 today.
Thank you very much.On
behalf of the talent, all the cooperating companies, all the members of the cooperative company, and all the cover staff, I
would like to express my sincere gratitude to all the viewers for being able to hold this event safely today.Four years
ago,
Hololive was born.  When we started, we never
thought we would be able to hold such a big event,
but we are very happy to be able to hold this event
for the fans of Hololive and Follow Stars as Coronaine Productions.  We
would like to collaborate with the recording companies to hold events that will please the fans.
Please enjoy Coro Live Super Expo 2022 for two days starting today. Thank you very much.
Now, let's
move on to Kagami Biraki.  Itadakimasu The
fish used for this Kagami biraki event yesterday
was provided by Mail Type Co., Ltd.
Thank you to Meiji Mainstream Co., Ltd.
Now, we
will perform the Kagami biraki ceremony. On
behalf of the organizers, I would like to cover the Kagami biraki event.
Representative Director of Kagami Biraki Co., Ltd.  Mr. President, Yagyo
will be conducting the event.
Please join in the fun with all the characters. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much, Lego.
Yes, then, I
will take the temperature of Kagami Biraki.
Everything related to Hololive Super Expo 2022.  We hope that everyone
will have a great time, that the two-day
event will be held safely and successfully, and that health will spread from this Makuhari
Messe
to all over the world.  If
you are watching online, please feel free to sing along in the comments.
Well then, after this, I
will call out to you, so if
you are watching the broadcast, please leave a comment.
As for everyone,
unfortunately I can't speak today, so I'd like to
ask you to shout out ``Yoisho'' from the bottom of your heart. I
hope you'll get excited with some applause as well. I hope
all the characters are okay too.  Is
everyone OK? All the
visitors are
ready.
OK, thank you very much. Now
let's go.
Thank you very much for the dream in the middle of the light.
[Music]
2 days long
Now then, theater  With this, we will conclude the Kagami Biraki ceremony.
Thank you very much to everyone who attended.
From now on, it will be time for the Goto session.
Now, media members,
please follow the staff's instructions and proceed to the shooting area.  [
Music] We are
currently preparing for a photo session.
Regarding individual requests, we are
considering time availability. We
will respond to your request, so please send us your request. We
are currently adjusting the positions of the characters, so please take a moment.  Please wait for a moment.
[Music]
All of you who are visiting us
will also be working on PR, but we
would like to take this opportunity to take a commemorative photo with you.
Now then, are you
ready? Okay,
everyone who is asking questions, please look at the center first.  Please,
please.
3. Smile, please.
[Music]
Ah,
if there are any people who need individual attention, please raise your hand and let me know. Do you
have any specific poses? Is it
okay? Yes, we
had a lot of fun over the two days.  Let's move on. We're
currently having an original session. I
'm asking you to raise your hand and look at me, so
please turn to this side.
Everyone, I
'd like you to also look at the person on your right.  By
the way, thank you.
[Music] Is that
okay?
That's the end of the photo session.
If you'd like, could you please move a little further back? To
all the speakers,
[Music]
Those on the left, everyone on the left, wave your hands.  Thank you
Yes, everyone, let's get excited. Is it about time?
Next, there
may be some people on the right side watching the movie, so
please move your hands limply.  Is
everyone okay
? Finally, I would like to ask the center.
Yes, everyone who is watching the broadcast,
please share your screenshots with the hashtag Connect Hololive Rain 1.
With that, we will
conclude the photo session.
Thank you very much.  Well then, that's all for now.
Thank you very much to all the speakers.
Please continue to enjoy Hololive Super Expo 2022.
Thank you very much
[Music]
Weiss Schwarz
Hololive Production Booster
Weiss Schwarz that won't stop even with packs Booster
Pack
Hololive Productions Now
on sale
[Music]
Bushiroad
Ah, I love anime Chugai Kogyo Contents I
want to enjoy Mansion Anime We
plan and develop anime goods and sell them on the internet A
cafe in collaboration with anime Moya  The
latest information is on Twitter
[Music]
[
Music] [Music] [
Music] [
Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music]
[Music  ]
[Music]
[Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music]
[  Music]
[Music]
[Music] [
Music] [Music]
Everyone who is coming to Hora Live Third Festival, are you
having fun?
[Music] I'm
thinking about it.
Okay.
[Music]
Our project starts now.
So, the
project I'm going to do now is to
connect photos,
and I'm Mel Yozora, the MC for this project.The three people who will be taking on this project are
three people.In
turn, I'd like each of you to introduce yourself and the contents of the photos you've taken recently.Hello
hello.
[Music] I'm
Roboco, a regulated virtual robot. The
photos I took recently are a lot of my cat's cha-cha. That's
nice.
[Music] It's so cute. I
take pictures right away, like when someone gets on my futon. It's
so cute.  Hey
[Music]
Next time, please. Hey,
this is Orange-san who came to the live show, and
Shizune Momo, an idol Vtuber. The last photo I took is called Mama. I
remember taking a photo of the hot pot
. It's been cold lately.
Okay, so let's take a look at the last one, Button-chan. The
photos I've taken lately are, well,
when I looked back, all I saw were pictures of food.
Thank you.
[Laughter]
[Music]
So, these pictures will be connected together, and the
story will be
four randomly displayed pictures.  It's a game
where you create a story on the spot based on the pictures
[Music] It seems difficult,
but I guess it's okay. It's difficult. The
person who can create the story with the most unusual ending
will be the winner.
Well, first of all, let's assume you try it first.  The person I'm
going to take
is Roboko-chan. OK, show me Japan. Roboko-
senpai.
Let's have some fun.
Good luck. Hmm. Good luck. Now, please
make the four photos that will be displayed into one story. Is
that okay? It's okay. What kind of photos should I
take?  I'm sure it's coming.
Then,
let's start. [Music] My future is over there. Wait for me, princess. I'm
having fun. You
said you're a princess anyway, so why
don't you wait for me as a princess?
From now on,
I'll go there on foot
.  [Laughter]
[Music] It
seems like these kids have made friends before they knew it. They must have a lot of friends.
[Music] That's
delicious.
Who are you? It seems like you
ate too many cookies and became tiny.  It's
like the same problem I had before I got small, it's disgusting. Ah,
this person seems to
have gone a little crazy from eating too many cookies.
[Music]
I was about to give him a massage to get the cookies out of his neck.
2  People are doing it
[Music]
Before I knew it, I had
turned into a dog.
Wow, Cookie.
I don't know what's going on. I'm so happy to have met my husband now.
Wow.
[Music] It's
still the beginning, so we're all like this.  It's hard,
but it's because I
don't understand it yet. I
didn't say that. This is the second one. It's
like using cookies well. I guess it's like
Megane-kun.
[Music]
[Laughter]
What do you think about it for me? It
was a good response, but as I was thinking about the story in episode 3, I realized that it wasn't like
doing something like that sick person at all,
but rather a massage, and I was
thinking about what to do, and I
rushed forward.  I
wonder why they're trying to get some air in, so I
use acupressure to
push it out.Next, let's move on to
Nenechi, because the
world is pretty amazing too.
[Music]
Please, let's
start.
[Music]
I
'm in the middle of this intersection.  The man in front of the counter is
going on a journey today to find his lunch,
right?
Where is my lunch?
Where is it
?
[Music]
[Laughter]
Where did I put it?
Where is it?  It's been a while since I've had lunch, and my
stomach and back are starting to stick together.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Wait, wait, lunch. Hey, you're
hungry.
Become my lunch.
[Music]  Are you a
red
panda?
Red, is
there a place to eat? I'm
eating, I'm eating, I'm eating this.
[Music] Looks
delicious.
[Music] I
put this together on a trip to find lunch. I
see. Finally, let's eat panda.
Yeah, it was beautiful up to the 3rd one
[Music]
Well, it would have been nice if the red panda came on the 3rd one, that's
for sure.
[Music]
What's that?  I guess it's
soothing, is
n't it? It's probably good to have animal power. It's true that it's not a flag. Let's
take a look at the animals that might come at the end.
[Music] It's
Button-chan.  Okay, I'll do my
best. I'm a new researcher working at this research institute. Because I live in a white room, it's always hard to show off the finished product. I can't say I'm very happy about being here, but I'm
able to make a pretty good living.  I
'm thinking
[Music] There
's some money under the microscope that I've never seen before It's
a secret, but I was told to keep it a secret,
but apparently a new species of bacteria that turns people into zombies has been
discovered.
We can't do anything because we've been told by our superiors to keep it a secret, but
when we hear something like that, we get a little nervous.Can we
run a company like this?I
thought it was a very good company, but I felt like I was a
zombie.  Even though I was
told that, I didn't really understand it, so I
ran away.And
as expected, as is often the case with zombie movies,
if a biohazard were born in a laboratory,
I would be the first to die.  Maybe, I
handed in my resignation to my boss and
quit the company.From
today on, I'm a free man.As
expected,
Hall's Zabi is amazing.That's how
I became a backpacker and
traveled all over the world.  It's
been amazing, after all, every
day is boring, right?
That's what I originally thought.My
daily life is quite boring.In the beginning, I get a good salary and
live a decent life.
[Music]
Freedom is the best thing.  Well, I
don't know if there will be zombie outbreaks, but I'm
thinking of just living my life as is for a while.End
[Laughs] I can't put together any
good photos.
[Music]
[Music] It's a
special festival, so it's
going to end with a bad ending.
[Music] It looks like
there are still more images, so we can do one more
lap.
Eh, I
want to see how good your senpai is.
[Music] It's
okay, Mel-chan, you can
do it. Show me your story. Okay, I'll
try it.  Well,
we're black,
that's us,
that's who we are,
and there's a
woman in the company named White who
uses her white hair, which I
really don't think is possible.Yes,
but black bullets use black hair.
Why
can't White be fighting? That's seriously
impossible. [Laughs] Why white? It's already strange.
This is White, the traitor of the Black group. This
is the
culprit. This is the culprit. This is White's culprit. That stag
beetle, even this
Black.  This white thing to crush,
this smooth floor,
after all, we have to be black.All
kinds of colors have come out that we swore we shouldn't be.Blackdown is
black, but this,
we blackdown, used revenge to
obtain new abilities.That's it.  That's
right,
this lightning is white.A
white
woman has turned into this lightning and now she's living in it.Yo, she's
been turned into an ability.That's
right, she's no longer a human.She's
not a human anymore.It's a
normal person.  Well, it's true that
we, the Black Group, will
continue to live in the darkness.
A lot of white people have come out.
[Music] He
pretended to be a black bullet, but he's already been one since the beginning.
He's a gray original who has no white problems. Betray him, gray.  Hagureyo Ah, I've done it
for the second time, and I think I'd like to see everyone's world again. I
want to do it first.
Next, let's start with Botan-chan. Are you
ready?
[Music]
What's this?
Eh.  I wonder what this place is.
It's an old inn at the foot of a mountain. It's a small inn that provides rooms for tourists who come to climb the mountain
without meals,
but it's bustling with climbers every day.
One day,
it's a secret. Well, I think it's time for this inn to
grow in size. For that purpose, we need to
add tools and
make the inn bigger. This
is the story behind the inn.
Behind the scenes of seafood. The
owner of the inn is...  I
called Shishido Kogyo and
decided to have them renovate the back of the inn,
thinking that this would make it easier for inn guests coming to the mountains to use this facility.
[Music]
Here I am!
Wan Wan  It's a gift.One day,
a dog
came down from the top of the mountain
to the foot of the mountain and put something in his mouth.  I wonder if it was a
dog that caught a fish.It
had something on its neck.Perhaps it was a
consultant, or maybe it was someone who
brought something to the dog and contacted us for advice.The
tension exercise at the inn.Some kind of
incident was happening in a hurry.  That's
because I thought that if something happened, I had to act quickly. It
was an incident. Please
help me. One day, a
very large
typhoon hit us directly. The
mountain was blown away. The
inn and everything else was
washed away by the typhoon, but
everything happened at that time.  The dog had
brought a tube that was in his mouth, and he had
brought a long object for a long throw.I managed to
get it out on the ground, and somehow the excitement
survived, and it stuck after all.There are good things to be done to be kind to animals, after all.And
the excitement started all over again.  They were
thinking about rebuilding the Rope Inn. Ah,
I understand.
[Music] It
's okay next time. I'm at a dead end.
The dog was probably a messenger from the mountain.
[Music]
Hey, he
left it behind.
[Music]
OK
Yes,
I'm
23 years old. My
hobby is
fighting.
Today as well,
I'm training hard to kick and defeat my opponent. I'm
sure I'll be able to defeat this guy and tomorrow.  I'm in a position where I can defeat him,
so it looks like he's been training.If the old
lady looks like she's in trouble, we'll
have to hold our guns and practice.Hey
, we're
planning on fighting here.  I should have been,
but I wonder if I've become a blur again.No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, here, here, here,\hhere, it's
supposed to
be right.  20
[Music] It
looks like the old woman and the old man
got lost. Are you
coming here?
Sweets
I was supposed to
be muscular, but when I
noticed it,
Summer
Yoshi
turned into a cat-leg. That's
weird. Maybe his eyes are a little bad.  Shiren,
please put on your glasses.
It's amazing. The world is so dazzling today as well.
[Music]
[Music] We
need to create a story with animals in mind from the beginning. That's
meow.
With direct probability, it's a dog.  It's a cat, let's go with that pattern.
Okay, let's go to the final story of Nenechi. Let's
go.
[Music]
Look, it wasn't there. Don't look anymore. You can
squeeze my dick quickly. I'm
so hungry.
Wait.  I'm going to narrow it down right now. Wait a minute.
There's nothing there.
[Music] There's something on the way down. [Music]
If I keep going like this, I'll fall and
end up in my imagination.
[Music]
Help me, sweet
potato.
[Music]
Someday,
yeah  This is the newest powdered milk these days.
[Music] The
first 50,000 yen. It's so
colorful. Let's
bathe our whole body.
Ingest the temporary preparation into our whole body.
[Music]
This
[Music]  ] It's
not
about milk, it's about infiltration [Music]
But it was number 1 after all. I
'm glad I predicted it.
Today's episode is
good, but there are two different animals.
Who are they
?
[Music]
From now on, the night is coming.  I
would like to choose this picture story queen.
[Music]
Who is this?
[Music] The
one who created the most wonderful story
is Nenechi's Hungry Lunch Man.
Yay,
this doesn't count.
Yes, everyone tried it. It was fun.
[Music] Well
then, everyone,
please continue to enjoy the cat live third festival.
[Music]
Good Day Tour Cherry
Swarkunz
[Music] Hello, my name is
Calliope Morley and I
'm bitter. Thank you.  I'll do it. Do
n't let it hit your skin. Good morning, hello.
Good evening and thank you for your continued support today.
Hello, everyone.
[Music]
Hello everyone. Kiara Takanashi, who
is the president of KFP but is also
called the store manager. But she's already a shark.
[Music]
It's fun
[Music] [Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] [Applause] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music]
[Music]
[
Music]
[Music]
[Music] [Music] [
Music] [
Music] [Laughter] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music]
[Music]
[Music  ]
[Music] [Music]
[Music]
I see, I see
Carrie
[Music]
[Laughter] [
Music]
[  Music]
[Music]
[Music] [Music]
[Laughter]
[
Music] [
Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Music] [
Music]
[Music]
[
Music]
[Music]
[Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [
Music]
[Laughter]
[Music  ]
[Music]
[Music] [
Music] [
Music] [Music] [Music] [
Laughter] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Laughter]
[Music]
[Applause]
[  Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] [Applause] [
Music] [
Music] [Music] [
Music] [Music] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Music] [Music]
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Music] [Music]
[Applause] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [
Music  ]
[Music]
[Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music]
[  Music]
[Music]
[Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music]
[Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Applause] [Music] [Music] [Applause]
[Music  ]
[Music]
[Music] [Music]
[Applause] [
Music] [Applause] [Music] [
Music] [Applause] [
Music]
[Music]
Dice Schwarz
Hololive Production's booster
pack won't
stop you  Nai Beis Schwarz
Booster Pack Holo
Live Production Now
on sale
[Music]
Bushiroad
Ah, my favorite anime, Chugai Kogyo.
Enjoy Contentvention and anime. We
plan and develop anime goods and
sell them on the internet. We have collaborated with anime to create
past works.  For the latest information, please
visit Twitter [Music] Everyone coming to Hololive Super Expo 2022
[Music] I
will be the host of this program. I
am Kanata Amane, a member of the 4th generation of Hololive.
Thank you for your support.
[Applause]
[Music]
[  [Applause]
Oh
[Laughter] Let me
introduce you to the performers here. First of all,
Color:
Okay, I
'm Aten Hunt, the world's strongest idol.
[Music]
And 3
: I
'm Flair, who I don't know about in the new year. He doesn't talk so much
that I'm
starting to cough.  Thank you very much.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] I do
n't understand Japanese very well, but
when I read the atmosphere, it
seemed easy to understand.
Thank you. This program will be presented by the four of us. We hope to see you until the end.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
Hololive Super Export 2022 Are you
having fun?
So it's just the four of us,
but of course it's the first time these four of us are
together, watching the show and talking.  Then I
wonder if there's something we
all have in common. Not everyone in this world is
crazy. It's funny because it's just one person.
[Laughs]
That's me.
Well, I
don't see much in common at the moment.  Well, I'd like to find
it while we're working together today
. So, it's about time to start
planning today. Let's get started right away.
Thank you.
Now, let's do a project with these four people.
[Music]
Okay, everyone.  During the walk, I asked the children to
challenge Sam and
compete to see how many challenges they could complete in 3 minutes.
[Music] The
person who completed the most challenges was the
challenge holder.
Everyone
understood the rules.  OK.
Well, first of all, let's take a look and see what kind of challenge we have.
Okay, let's
go. Check this out. Here we go!
[Music]
[Laughter]
Sort by talent debut Challenge
Maximum clock time: exactly 10 seconds  Make
3 other people laugh 3
tongue twisters without chewing 3 times in a row
[Music] The
3 people who will disappear don't know Trivia
challenge This was great Catfish
Your brother is a genius Good luck
[Laughs]
6 of these things in 3 minutes  We're
going to have you compete to see how many things you can accomplish.What do you
think?Everyone, I
feel like I'm pretty unreasonable, but I
always do that bus gag.
[Laughs] It
makes us laugh.  Laugh!
Laugh
! That's what happened after my seniors. But, are
you all
ready?
Let's take on the challenge right away.
I'm willing to run as a candidate,
but I'd like to make a proper decision.
[Music] I'll
do it. The closer
it gets to the end, the more disadvantageous it becomes. Hey,
[Music]
[Music] Will there be
an earthquake? No, it's
not likely.  But as long as I can, I'm going to
try it out. I
love you,
Flare-senpai's
challenge. Let's
start.
[Music]
I'm trying to get my body clock to match 10 seconds. I guess I'm the kind of
person who wants to
start
something like that. It seems like I can get a better start here or there.  I hear you
saying I'm going, but [Music] I wonder if I can disturb you with this? Hey, hey, hey, it's not coming soon. [Music] What do you think? Well then, [Music] [Applause] [Music] I'm still going, right? The tongue twister is the tongue twister.
Tell me a tongue twister, please.
Grilled ribs, grilled ribs, grilled ribs.
[Applause]
This is
strong, strong,
scene knowledge that the other three people don't know.
Challenge
Which is better, mushrooms or bamboo shoots?
Maybe not everyone knows this, but
everyone here.  I think I'd like people to know a little bit about it.
[Music]
Do your best, do your best
[Laughs]
There are quite a few. Well, hey, challenge to
sort by talent debut. Yeah,
name first
Experience
Straight line
Choco-sensei Um
[Music]
Here it is.  There are two challenges for Flare-senpai. I was
only able to do the first two. I
thought everyone didn't know either one of them.
Because I like it, I
thought everyone didn't know about it. But I
did it. It's perfect.  Well,
I'm happy about it, but I don't want to make a fuss about it,
but in the last three minutes, I'm really
nervous.
Yeah, yeah, everyone, please think about this. Well
then, let's do the next house as well. Finally,
bye.
At the Genius Head Shop
[Music] Do
you have confidence, brother?
Not at all. You
talk a lot.
If you don't go, I'd
like you to do it. Now, introduce
Grandpa.
Okay, then, a request for the 10-second debut version.
Yes, I'll do it if I bring it to you first. Yes, Iroha-chan.
[Music] That's great. [Music]
Mameshi, please.
Yes, that's right.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Next is uh,
math right away. Okay, 30 seconds. I'm
smart.
What's 7 and 7?
Um, uh,
791, right
? 10
[Music]
Second challenge
[  [Music] It
's starting. I've
been waiting a long time.
[Music]
[Laughter]
I'll do my best.
3 times 3
times
It's dog nature, but for now, yes [Laughter] [Music]
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music]  ]
1st
place.
How was it, brother? It
was difficult after all.
[Music]
Thank you. Well
then, Heartsuma will be the one to decorate the final stage, but
how about being confident? Well,
you're also responsible for the management.
[Music] That's
it
[Music] Let's
start,
please.
Men and women, young and old, young and old
[Music]
Please challenge us for 130 seconds
This is cool this time,
uh,
100%
[Music]
Please, I'll
do it.
[Music]
[  [Music] [
Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] Do you
have any trivia about apprentices other than me?
[Music]
Well, green onions are ready. Do you know why they're no longer spicy?
That's it. Don't do that. Let
's try the talent debut order challenge.
It's terrible. I'm a little worried that I might make a mistake. It's easy. [Music] Um, Gura-chan. [Music] Look at your brother's face. [Music] Lie. Wait a little longer. Surprisingly. [Laughs] This is difficult.  Well, it
wasn't good enough.
[Music] I got
one shot to make three people laugh. I never thought I'd
do it all.
It's a lie.
Wait a minute, one trick that makes three people laugh is a
challenge.
Well then, do your
best,
gorilla. You're not a gorilla. I've
been wanting to go there for the first time in a while.
[Music]
[Laughter]
You
[Music] That was
interesting
[Music]
I agree with you
[Laughter]
[Music]
I did it too, but I ended up
putting it on this person.  It's
about time, I
want to go out.
[Music] No, we're
all small fry.
[Laughs] Well
then,
[Music]
Please,
[Music] You have
a good tongue. You seem to be good at it.
[Applause]
[Music]
Stop.
Now that interference has become a breakthrough, let's
do it again.
That's it. Let's start.
[Music] I
was battling an illness.
[Music]
This is it, huh?
This is it.
[Applause] I'm a
little nervous about this
.
Actually,
[Music]
First of all, we've
found a completer. Let's move on.
[Music]
[Laughter]
Please give me more. [
Music]
No more.  This is all that's left, but I'm sure
everyone will laugh.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music] It's
over, but I'm sure it's over.
[Music]
So, out of all the cats, who has completed the most challenges?
[Music] -
Thank you very much, so
to the challenge holder,
[Music]
Please let me know how you feel now with the results.  That's good, I wish I could do it.
[Laughs]
Thank you. Congratulations.
Thank you. Here's the main announcement.
[Music]
Weiss Schwarz Premium
Booster Hololive Production is
on sale as part of the Hololive Super Expo 2022 merchandise.  This card contains cards of more than 50 talents, including those from Pro Live 0th
generation, Forox, Solo Live
Indonesia, and Solo Live English.
Be sure to get at least one card.  &Creative Flag
Out will also be exhibiting Hakusho Cards,
so be
sure to check them out.Other
supplies that can be used with the cards are also on sale.
[Music] The
local booth sells card binders and
acrylic card stands.  Maasu -
Store your favorite cards neatly or
lose them!
[Music] In
addition to the products mentioned earlier, the
50+
sleeve deck holder set and acrylic holder
rubber mat included in the booster pack have been released.
Well, everyone, come on in.
[Music] Okay,
next up, here's the
product.
Holive Super Expo 2022
Training
Recognize this
Volume 1 to Volume 77
[Music]
[Applause]
More than 60 talents.  What I'm
introducing is a
plate
using key visuals from the radio from Hololive Presents V, which is currently being broadcast on Hibiki Radio Station.It's
like Acrylic Star is recording a radio show.  The
plate acrylic stand is 2,800 yenB
Niitabe The
products I introduced are
available at official merchandise stores and mail order.Please
buy them.
Well, that's all for now, so here's the
full live Super Expon 202
23 people
Now, let
's go to the end of the show and say hello.Then, our
guests were Kanata Amane, Mr.
Red Foods,
Flair, who I don't know, and
Play Cooking.
[Applause]  ]
[Music]
Bye
[Music] [
Music] [Music]
[Music]
Wow, I
can see you all, so
everyone who is coming to HoraLive Super Expo 2022 and this
distribution.  Hello everyone, this
is Gokise's IKEA Lamy, and yes,
this is Shishiro Button, who is new to this live show.
Makuhari
[Laughs] Well
then,
for those of you who can't be there, this program will
show you what's going on at the venue.  We at Shishiknit would like to deliver this to you.
[Music]
So, I just noticed something. It's
not really cold today. I'm
sending all of my office stuff to the expo, and
that kind of thing.  Ah,
[Music] It's
starting to feel like that. I see that you are
going to a Buddhist altar over there. That's
right, so please
keep that in mind. I'm
in the process of moving, so please come and find something for me in Makuhari. Yes, click
here.
Well, first of all, today, there are
some tweets that were solicited in
advance, so I would like to introduce some of them.
]
Yes, thank you.
[Music] A
two-shot of Kanatan and Kanatan. That's
obvious, but I
guess that's why they took the picture together on that app. I
guess it's because of calories or calories.
Eh, it's
so cute.
In reality, you can play like this
quite a lot.When I was looking at the tweets, I saw some
people playing with murmurs,
etc.I'll take a closer look at it later.Click here for the
next tweet.Okay, what is
this?Once again,
what is this?  When I looked at it, it
probably meant that there were too many goods.It
was like what and how many items I wanted when I was buying goods.It seemed like they would ask for it
in advance, so I asked them to give it to me in advance.I see, I
wonder how much it
costs.  If I recall correctly, there
seem to be about 4 sheets of A3 A4a paper.It seems like there's
a lot of excitement in sales, too.Thank you
everyone for
buying it.
[Music]
Here's the next tweet.Dawn,
Mr. Showman, this is me.  That
carrot in Hollow Alternative's [Laughs] Senpai scene. It's
loaded with carrots. It's not a horse-drawn carriage,
but it's more like a cart. You can
actually take pictures
at Peco Land, let's
GO let's GO like
this.  That's right.
[Music]
Well, let's take a look next. Next up,
that's Yukimi.
Even though he's a professional controller, I
definitely wanted to take a two-shot with Larry as a memento of today. I
didn't hide Ramy-chan from the unfamiliar operations.
But it's okay. Anyway, it's still cool. Please
read it.
There's a purikura, right? You can
get some kind of stickers there. There's
all sorts of Horror Live's original items.
There's also others besides Rami-chan that you can get forements. I'm sure
there are various members.  I'll
probably check this out later, as some people might post some tweets about it later. I
said let's take some photos, so thank you.
Let's go see what's going on there.  It's
a bit
empty here too, so there's nothing here, so
let's take a moment. I'm going to look around at various places in Makuhari. I'm going to show you around, and the staff will be holding their cameras in the storage room and doing various boosts, so it's a little difficult to see.  Please be careful if you
hide your face because you'll
be wandering around, but the
staff will be visiting various places at the end,
so if you're asking me to let the manager see if I don't want to be seen right now,
please make your face look a little like this.  I'd
be happy if you could do something like this, please.Yes,
wait a minute.I'm working on various texts today,
but
are there any booths that I'm interested in?
Laughter] I
may have said something like that,
but I
'll ask a staff member to go to the booth and explain it there. There's a
courthouse. I hope
everyone is looking forward to it and is having
fun
together.
At that courthouse, Maramy and
Shishiro were both
present at the booth.I'll tell you more about
that later.What
do you think?The
divine voice of the staff
says that the broadcast will be connected soon.
So let's take a look. [Music] Look at the comments on the stream. I like it a bit. That's right, I can also see the comments on the stream, so the comments on this stream can also be seen by Ramy and the others. So, everyone watching, what do you think? I'm ready. Let's go.
Great.  - Wow, Sui-chan and Azuki-senpai
are here too. This and that are all changing smoothly. See you there. It's
amazing. I'm so tired. I'm
so excited.
It's a huge monument.
Life Spikespo 2022 is huge. The
monument is so big. I want to stand here
and take a photo.  Hey, that's
amazing. So if we wait, we'll show up too. Is
there a possibility
? That's amazing. This time, if the staff at the site had
a little patience,
we're probably still gamers, so it's still a
long way off.  I thought it was going to be even more difficult,
but with the aggressive camera work of the staff,
this is really the booth.The venue is
extremely wide.Makuhari
itself is a bit big, but Makuhari
Messe itself is still quite
large.  This
monument itself is probably
huge, and I think that's probably true. It's amazing when you actually see it.
People think it's big.
Everyone, everyone.
[Music] I wonder
if I can
hear you. I wonder if I can hear you.
[Music]
[Laughter]  ]
Well, that's it, now we're in the 3rd season.
That's right. I'm already a little drunk,
but I'm a little
drunk. I'm going to
ask you to wait a little longer. When the 4th season comes, I'm sure you'll be able to wait a little longer. I'm sorry, but I'll have to wait a little longer.  Please let me know
and I'll come. That
means next time we'll have
fun. [Music] [Music] [Music] So you're a
6th generation
student. Thank you.  I
have a feeling that this is the guest.
Who is that? Who is that? They've
changed. They've been
taken away. They've
come to court.
Oh no, these are two, Danie-san.
Mikotania-san. They're
cute. They
come to every event, right? They come here all the time. Let's
get a taste of it. It's a bit popular.
I have a feeling that it's becoming more
and more
cute, but I wonder if it will become popular.
But I'm sure there were other characters this time as well. I wonder if they'll
come or not.
From the court.
Why?
My brother's mascot character.
This is Ame-chan, right?
And at the end, Anki
[Music] Is
this Hololive or
something? It's gotten so
naughty [Music] Ah, that's pretty aggressive. You just
won't jump.
[Music]
Everyone poses like this.  I wonder
if there's a special pose for it when I take it.Refreshing
Nico Danie Rico Danie is so cute Udin-chan
[Music]
When I saw this at the scene, I was
told it was okay to take pictures.It seems like it's okay to take pictures of this,
so I'm sure everyone was glad.
Please take a picture of me, please
[Music] So cute. Well, someday, my Daifuku will also be like this. You should feel like an old man. He doesn't have anything. [Music]
Maybe he's watching the stream on his smartphone.
There's a possibility.  Well,
today, after I watched that broadcast a little bit,
there was a small child in attendance.This
live show is so loved by so many people.Wow, I
guess I'm glad that it's being recognized a little bit.I'm so happy.Thank you very much.
Thank you everyone
. We've been so excited since the beginning. I wonder if it's
okay. I'm looking
forward to it. Let's try not to think of anything after this.
[Music]
[Laughter] You're
getting used to it. Just get used to it and explode.
Step on it.
So, without further ado, let's
take a look at the booth.
First of all,
let's go to the place where Lamy and Cecilon are interested.
[Laughs] I
think both the people watching the broadcast and the people in real life will be interested.
Why do these two keep on going to court? I want you to
take a look at the courthouse.
[Music]
Well then,
ask the staff to make a flower path for you. It seems that the
fan club will be renewed. The fan
club has been closed. It's
right next to this entrance.  Kana
here is something that looks like a festival venue, and this is a courthouse.  We are
appearing as both the plaintiff and the defendant.The
plaintiff and the defendant who come to the booth will
act as jurors, listen to both sides, and make a fair judgment as to whether they are guilty or not guilty.  It's the
plaintiff or the defendant. It's the person who
got sued.
[Music]
It's easy to get sued. It's
fun to see who gets sued.
Please take a look and
join us.  It's a day. I'm
guilty now. I
'm begging you not to be guilty. It means I can see your insides.
Who are you doing this with right now?
It's the teacher, Choco-sensei.  It
's a change, it's the
one who changed it. I wonder what it conveyed. I'm
curious.
She has a really cute face and she's angry, but now she
listens to both sides and
says she's innocent. That button...  It
means that our fates are parting ways.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Please be innocent. Thank you. I
hope everyone, including those who are currently on trial, enjoy it.
Oh, I see
. This is amazing. This is quite a
full-fledged production.  That's right.
Thank you for your surprise.
But I'm glad that so many people lined up. I'm
glad. Let's go to the next booth. The
next booth is
nextto Jean. I can
see something.  Yo, what's
over there is a
Holo fortune-telling
hall. It seems like you
can't even tell fortunes. This is where the
members of Hololive act as fortune tellers and
tell fortunes about everyone who visits. As you
answer questions, the fortune teller will predict your
future based on your personality.  Maybe they'll give you some advice to improve your fortune.This is
it.I wonder if it'll appear right now.It seems like the
ghost side will
appear randomly, but there's a room.It's been quite a
few days.I wonder how many there are, maybe 1235 or 5,
but it's random and various.  It's really hard to tell
who's going to appear on the follower side.
I can hear who's Poro Poro, Poru Pari -
[Laughs]
If it's a robot personality, it's called a fortune-telling house, so it's likely that there will be
seniors, but
if they're not there, they'll come out.  That's what I think,
Hey,
this person who has been exposed is
becoming more honest.Which
one are you?Are
you the
type who can't be honest?Ah, are you
okay?I saw this person
's okay.I'm sorry, I
couldn't do it.  I'm sorry, I'm going to
enter now. Yes, it's next. I'm going to
get a lot of questions like this. Is it
yes or not?
Who is
it? I'm so excited. I'm so excited. The
various
follower faces will tell me my fortune.
[Music]  ] Looks like
a lot of fun
[Music]
Hey, I want you to do it, I want you to
do it, and you made some choices, right? Yes, at home, the
holo face that appears again
will change,
right? The answer will change, no, the answer will change, too.  I
guess everyone, everyone there, please play around and
check it out.
[Music] Well
then, let's go to the next booth.
[Music]
Where's next? Where, where, where?
This
is the error booth that we both are familiar with.  Please explain this.Yes,
this is
Aogami High School, the setting of that story, which
has been recreated in a wooden school building.It's a
complete reproduction.It's a complete reproduction,
with life-size panels of the characters from the play.
We have
prepared a variety of exhibits, including the
latest information that can only be seen here.
This is a booth where you can become a transfer student and enjoy the world of Hololive Error.
Hey there, what's the latest information? It
's probably too much to say here, but it's just for the
fun of those who are visiting the booth.
Please, everyone, it was one-one-ship, wasn't it? It
was
amazing. It didn't entertain high school students. It was hospitality. It was all a little bit unpopular. It's been written, but it's here, that old school building in Sicilon, yes, it's from the past. It's amazing.  The set
is amazing, it's so hypnotic, ah everyone
[Music]
There was a notebook left there. It
's there, I wonder if it's okay. I remember the wall that was really crumbling. Ah, I
remember it being so bad. I also remember the keys I'm apologizing to.
Yes, that's amazing. I can
see something, so I wonder if this is a secret.
Yes, maybe this is the latest information. It
looks like an amazing notebook,but
[Music] I wonder
if it's something for people who went well. It
might be fun. This is an
amazing system.  It's kind of
nostalgic. Look at Ademonaru Shishiron, which makes me feel nostalgic. The main character is
playing a character called Fukami C.
But Makoto's school building is the same
character that appears, so it's
nostalgic. He
doesn't really smile. No matter how you look at it, he's
having fun.  So,
enjoy history. It
doesn't sound like it's going to be super fun,
right? This is a bit like what you're thinking right now. Maybe
it's information about these two.
There are new possibilities. He's
quite a mysterious figure right now.
Amazing.
Wow, the outside of this thing is quite elaborate, isn't
it? This looks like a hallway. Look, look, look, my senior took this. I wonder how it's going to turn out. Even so, the clothes of the present day and those of the past are passing each other. And I wonder if there's something amazing about it.  Well,
let's go to the next one. OK,
next time. It seems that
all of Hololive's talents are
on display in their costumes.
What do you mean, all of them?
All of them. All of them had their costumes taken off. The
staff told
us.  I won't be able to go home today because I don't have the energy,
so I'm wearing idol costumes, but
that's
true.
Lammy and the others won't be able to wear those clothes until the day after tomorrow. I wonder if I can
go home today.  You're
leaving, aren't you? You're a bit
conspicuous.
[Music]
People will ask you if it's Chihiro-san. They'll ask you that. You can't
say
no. No, you're not.
[Music]
Everyone's so friendly. It's amazing. We've
been part of a group from the beginning.  I'm going to go on camera, so I
told them to be careful of the people who can't be seen, but everyone was super aggressive.
Thank you for waving so much. I'm so
happy,
but
this is it. This is the
best way to realistically recreate the costumes of all the talents of Hololive Productions.
Yes, I heard that you can see up close the designs of the costumes that were carefully designed to the last detail.It
means that our clothes are now on display with hippies stabbed in them.It's so
cool.It
's outrageous.
Well, I think I might be able to smell something from this distance, which
means that my senpai has already
taken off her clothes.
That's right. He's
tall, and from the looks of it, I think his
body lines are quite tall. The
recall rate is high, and if you ask me, it's true. I'm
sure this is a Robocon senior. Yes,
Roboco.  Even my seniors were able to show me their legs,
and I was
like, Wow, they
really made it all the way to the end. They
left me out.
[Laughs] I
mean, they usually wear things like this. I
want to take a closer look at this one by one.  I think this
corner is quite enjoyable even if you take a close look at Neko. It's
Kitten-senpai's sudden costume, so Neko-senpai is probably safe.
Well, she's safe. It's
good that she can go home wearing the new one. She's
wearing her usual clothes.  I think
[Music] It's
really amazing. The parts are so
beautiful.
Even the way he stands is a bit Sui-
chan. I
think everyone is paying close attention to it. The way his
waist is a little tight like this makes it look so
tight, Azuki-senpai.
If you ask me, it's true that everyone looks
a little different.Even
Mel-senpai, who is very particular about her poses, probably has her skin on. Even Mel-senpai's
skin is almost visible.
[Music]
Nice, hmm,
nice.  If you
look at Hachama like this, the
design of the skirt is really cute. It's quite
detailed. There are
parts of it that you didn't notice before, but you
'll notice them when you look at them properly
. Hey, the
upper body is often shown in the broadcast, so
this is it.  I don't think I'd like to look closely at the lower half of my body,
but I think it might
be fun to have people take a closer look at it.
Yeah, yeah [Music] We all have
tails, right? Eh, tails, too.
Really, tails too.  I
have a spare tail for today, but
ah, this senpai is cute too. The
new hot spring bomb is so cute. The
ribbon behind Ayabe senpai is really missing.
This is amazing. The three-
dimensional effect is amazing.
Hey, and it's
also easy to see how tall he is.  Hey, yeah,
Choco-sensei, your chest isn't that big. I
have a senior who lives next to me, so it's
a bit unnecessary.
But if you look at this, you'll understand. It's
a bit impressive, isn't it?
What's the height of the side end of this chest?  It's
amazing that we had to recreate that. You
can almost see the
voice like this. You
can almost see it, sir.
Kismarisen is
healthy, but it's healthy.
[Laughs]
Epidemiology
is healthy, isn't it? I'll use it in the future.  I'll
use it, it's healthy. Wait, wait, it's
okay
. I couldn't see Luka. [Music] That means it's Neko Lab. That's nice. Everyone's watching. They
also
have EL and ID.
[Music]  There are some
3rd generation students from Marin-senpai, and
there are also some 6th generation students.If you
look closely, you can see how tall Yama-chan is.She's so small.Wow,
when you line her up like this, she's that
small.If you look at her, she's probably tall.
Oh, it's expensive because 3 people are relatively expensive at Nepo Lab.
That's right, that's
right. That's right. It's
cool. It
's a pirate. This is amazing. It
feels like the usual, usual, usual clothes.
[Music] Let's
take a closer look.  Don't lose your vocabulary.
This is nice. The mace and other
weapons are included.
I'm going to fight. It's so
elaborate. It's so
amazing. It's so amazing
. I'm going to look at it as if it's a lot of fun. But you know, I want people in Makuhari to
see it.  I really want it
. I think it's going to be a lot of fun because the costumes for all of Hololive Production's talents are on display, so I think it's going to be a lot of fun.
[Laughs] The
wings are red.
Ah
[Music] -
Come on!  Hey, when I came here, I got
lost and was taken away. That's a
terrible story. A little
later, a little later,
a little later. What's going on? I
wonder if my master is the same way. Wow, when you
look at him from the side, that's what he looks like.
Ram-chan, what do you mean? I'm
always watching Ram-chan. That's right.
Stop with the camera work.
[Laughs] The one
next to her is Nene. She has an idol feel and
is really cute. There's something extra about
her.  It's
amazing, this lace is so voluminous,
and the skirt
is really fluffy, so it's really
nice.
[Music] The
clothes have a lot of ribbons, so it's very girly,
isn't it? It's really cute.
And this side is  It's white.
[Laughs] You
took your clothes off, you took them off. That's
amazing. You took your clothes off. It's okay. It's torn
in one place. There's one more place. That
's why. When you get back, you might have been drunk.  If I
don't look at it, even after looking at it, I still feel like this standing
figure is my usual master.It's
amazing, thank you.I
would have thought that the balance of the body is very white.The
way the legs are bent, this is a four-character idiom for the body.But it's
okay, cc's spare.  So,
what's the situation? It's
not that oil
or that thing. Isn't your breasts a little bigger than usual? Well,
it's a
little bit more like that. Omar
seems to be holding me down a little, so I see. But it's going to
end, so
when will I feel it?  But I guess that's not the
case. Hmm, I feel like it's already there. Let's do it again. It's
okay. It's a beckoning cat, so it's okay. Well, I guess it's because the
Will Castles are lined up next to each other. It's
a bit of a
contrast, after all.  They're
all voluminous, too. Yeah,
wait, they're really
small,
so I can't mess them up.
[Laughs]
That's
amazing, isn't it? That's how
fluffy the reproduction techniques are. I
want you to show me a little bit about
Reine-chan's this and that.  It's
a cart, it's a cart, it's
amazing. This is amazing. The skirt and that on the chest
look like flowers
. It's amazing. It would be helpful if you could raise it a little higher. Oh, this, this,
this three-dimensional effect. It's
amazing. It's
amazing.
[Music]
Amazing.  Enemy:
Even the big brother doesn't wear a skirt. It's
amazing.
Everyone is so amazing. Look, this
looks very much like Reine-chan. She sleeps. It's
expensive.
Hey, it's
true. She looks
really worn out. She
looks like a zombie.
Wow.  So cute
[Music]
Nice! That
's amazing. Ricchan is so cute. Her tail is so cute. And here's the Korox. Iroha-chan. That's amazing. There's so many people there. There's so much. There's so much. It's
amazing.
They're quite tall, aren't they? They're big.
Chloe-chan and Rapulapu-chan
But I guess it's a bit small. I wonder if it's a big sister. It's amazing. I was able to recreate that thing on Lapu-chan's neck. It's true that it's not a chain, but what can I say? It's
not handcuffs.  He's a big guy.
[Laughs]
Handcuffs around his neck. Poi guy. Poi yara guy. I do
n't know what to call that, but
wow, look, everyone. Chorui-chan is
just
right. It's okay, it's so amazing, it's so
amazing. When we
go to the concert,
even the newcomers are wearing costumes.  They're getting ripped off, they
're fighting, they're getting beat up, so they're putting it up,
so Hololive is tough. It's
amazing. Maybe this side
killed it. It's on display, so it's
already lined up. It's
true. The
costumes of the talents
are on display. It's a fun booth.  Hey,
everyone, please take a look.
[Music]
Well, after this, I'm
going to go to the next one. It looks like I can go to the next booth, so I see.
Let's go. Let's
go. Next time, I
guess this is
Hololive
Alternative.  Is
there a booth? Yes, that's right, the photo was taken just now. Is it carrot-shaped? Let's go over there for a second. [Music] Oh, wow, wow, wow, that's it. It's the Holo Live Alternative booth. This is the Hololive Alternative booth from the Another World Creation Project.  I
see that it expresses the world of Hololance, which is the setting of the story. Please come and see that space. This is a
booth specially designed for the event, so please enjoy it a little. Ah,
but please enjoy it.  Oh, the
girl was doing it right now.
It's
Asora Senpai. [Music] It's a really big carrot. It's big. I
hope you enjoy taking pictures. Be careful of your
skirt.
[Laughs]
When I think about it, Pecola-senpai is
carrying something this big. It's
amazing. It must have been difficult. She was carrying it with great force and seemed to be having fun.
But in the cat's
PV, she was
carrying it, box after box.  I'm
a little curious about the future of Hololive Alternative as well.It seems like
they've had a lot of followers for a while now,
and I'm really curious about the progress they've made.I'm
personally
really interested in Alternative,
so I understand.
]
Well, I heard that next there
is a Hololive ID booth. I guess
this is it.
There are so many different booths.
That's amazing. There are so many different booths. That's
amazing. I can see it now.
Oh, this is Kororo.  I'm boottracking Live Indonesia
[Music]
Yes, I mean, you can look back on the history of Hololive ID,
see the history chart, and
experience traditional Indonesian games like gardening and rec engelik.Acting
ability Yes,
Hololive ID  There are many exhibits where you can enjoy the world view of Indonesia and the atmosphere of Indonesia.Game
What kind of game is
Engelic Engelic?What kind of game is Engelic Engelic?I
wonder if it's the one in the back.Wow, this is Engelic Engelic.I have
no idea how to play it.  If you do, you'll play.
This is Engelic. Even with this, I'll
ask the monitor in front of you. Let's play.
So, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, that's true. Yes, yes, yes, yes, let's throw. Do
n't you throw? I won't throw on the way home.
Even with this.  I'm curious. What kind of game is this?
Eh, I wonder what it is. It's like, you have to throw it and let it fly where it lands. You're skipping
where it lands. You're skipping to the next one, and it's amazing, it's a sandy beach
. Even so, it's a sandy beach, and it's delicious.
If you're eating something like that, I'm suddenly
worried about Bafang. It looks like it's going to be fun. It's
amazing.
[Music]
It's so amazing. It's so
amazing.
The temperature is so amazing. It feels like it's going to
explode. It's like this. It
's the atmosphere of Indonesia.  Oh yeah,
again, I'm wondering if I can enjoy a slightly different atmosphere from the usual JP.That's what I'm
thinking of, that Lamy.This
time, there's that bento.The bento
is only from Hololive's JP.
ID's
[Music]
Ah, that's right. It's pretty
much like a cat inside. It's
amazing, with such an Indonesian feel. It
looked delicious, so I
wanted to eat it.
[Music]  ]
Well, here's a complete reproduction
of the weapons held by the EL1 students in just a few
seconds, and
that's what's on display.Also,
there's also apparently a photo spot where you can take photos that will make you feel like you're in the DN member's cat streaming screen.
So, please try taking a picture.And it looks like this.Guru-chan's, that, that, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, it's typical of the University of Tokyo, is there a figurine? Yes, it's here. Let's go take a look.
Please also take a picture.
It's so cute. Do
n't step on it. [Laughs] You're stepping on it.
Wow, that's amazing.
That's the one in the back. That's the
mini 3D one. I wonder if you can take a photo there. I wonder
if you can take a photo. The
photo spot is great. Starting today, you can also go to
Hololive.  There's no
way it's going to be en.I
want to see amazing weapons.I want to see them.I want to see the weapons.Oh
wow, this is Kari-chan's one.Kani-chan and Hina-chan's are wearing belts.It's really scary.This is amazing.I'd be pretty
scared if I was forced to.  Hey
[Music] It looks like a
TV drama has been decided. I wonder
what it's
like. I originally wrote that this book was amazing, right? It's
ranked up a little bit. It's
amazing. It's pretty detailed like this kind of weapon. I
think it's
cute.
It's amazing.
There's also one of Osami-chan. It's
quite a shark. It's Doki. When you
think about it, it's huge. When you look at it from this perspective, it
means that it's holding this thing in its small body. That's amazing. That's
amazing. It's so well
made.
[Music]
It's so
cute. There's Abu-nee-chan too. Kiyora-chan's illustrations are so cute Hey, everyone's A's are good. Everyone's A's really good. It's not like I'm going to become an artist by writing something like that. I can't do it. It's cute. I
like it. I want to take a photo.  I'll
put it in one of the en machines. I'll
put it in. Will I be able to become a phantom member all at once? Is it just a
phantom? Just take a photo with me and you'll
become a member. I like
this 1:11 life-size figure. Really.  I
definitely want to see this.You
might want to see it.I can only see a little of it here.I
can see the cat's costume earlier, too.I
can understand the height of the cat, but the
figure feels even more realistic than the cat.
Yeah, right. Chan,
hey.
[Laughs] She's
cute. That's amazing. You
can have someone like my girlfriend. Seriously,
instead of a Touhou boyfriend character, you
can have a sideways boyfriend character. Only one side of the heart is like
this. The one who does this. One
side.  Just
like it.
[Music]
If you post it on Twitter, I
think we'll all go see Follow Mega again. So, yeah.
So what are we going to do next? Hey, see you then. Hey, let
's take a leisurely stroll around and visit the event booth.  The event
booth means that we can probably be reflected in the
image.Ah, that's
amazing.The mist has
narrowed down.Yes, it's humidifying.It's kind of nice.Everyone is
taking
care of their throats.Look
at the hood, too.  There were
some people who had several bento boxes, but
this time they
were selling 5 different types of bento boxes, but I'm
sure there are a lot of people who bought 5 types of bento boxes.  We
have lunch boxes for 1st, 2nd, 3rd, 4th, and Hololive Indonesia.
Yes, this is the place where food is sold.
By the way,
Nepo Lab's 5th generation is selling blue cracker
drinks
.  [Music]
[Music] I've
had so many cookies and drinks
. I see. It's very
popular. Thank you.
Everyone, there
may have been something like this too.
How was the prince? Was it delicious? I'd
be happy if you could also post the company and other information on Twitter.  Please give it to me
Hey, everyone doesn't like it, but when I look at the bento, I
get hungry.I just ate lunch,
so yeah, and there's a place in the back that looks
like a rest booth, and you
can eat that bento here.  It's like, ``I'm going to do it.''
Everyone is so nice.
[Music]
[Laughter]
But I think I can hear your voice, so that's right. We're
eating lunch right now. We're all
watching Bethel a lot, so we're all going to eat together.  Please
eat slowly! It
was delicious! Everyone looks
so much alike and is
eating heartily.
Hey, everyone is eating it. I hope it was delicious. So,
is it here?
[Laughs]
[Music] It's
everyone.
Thank you for showing us.
That's amazing.
Thank you so much for coming.
[Music]
The fox jay is also coming.
Isn't it a festival where everyone has so much love
? That's amazing.
[Music]
So this is
not the event stage.
[Music]
Speaking of this kind of broadcast,
Shishiro Yes, it's
a call and response that is unique to events.It's
Call Land.Thank
you everyone.  Why do
n't you say something like that?
Everyone raises their hands,
etc.Then what's good
about playing rock, paper, scissors?
Something like if I beat Shishiro, something good will happen today.I
think it's a big deal to play rock, paper, scissors with Shiron.
Well then, I'm going to give you some goo. I'm out. I'm going to give you
some
goo. I'm going to give you some goo. I'm going to give you some goo. It
seems like I'm begging you. Tellamy will be shouting. Leader, please put your hand out.  Purge with a piano heart
[Music] Don't
trample on everyone's hearts, but believe
in the goo. The one who got that par is this sea. The
one who read the wrong side and gave a punch has won, and now you
know. The one who won is the one who is Aiko.  Let's
have a battle. Let's go ahead and win. Then I'll
give you the signal. Please, let's
play it all. It
hurts my heart, so I'm
hurting. But do you really think that?
Goo,
Rock, Paper, Scissors Pon, Goo person, Goo person or savings person, Congratulations to the previous person, Goo, Congratulations to the person in front of you, Congratulations to Goo, both times now. There are a lot of people here. It's true, Irian is here. We're lucky, let's go to the last boss, Shishiru Button. Let's go to the last
boss, too.  Let's use it as much as we
can.
See you then. Let's play the scissors. [Music] It seems that the white button will give out the scissors. Everyone pretends that they're going to give a goo, but then they make a par.
This is a psychological game. So let's go. At
first, it's a goo. Rock, paper, scissors, pawn,
properly.  I gave it my last punch.I
thought I'd make your heart hurt a little.Congratulations,
congratulations to everyone today.Everyone who
won, everyone who lost, and
everyone who lost, will
have something good happen to them.I'll just
leave it as something that can't be helped.
Ah,
thank you everyone.
So, today's broadcast is almost
over.
However, the booths that we couldn't introduce today will
be introduced tomorrow as well.  So, please look forward to it. I
want you to see the office. I
definitely want you to see that. I
want you to see how busy that office is right now. I want you to see it.
Oh yeah, we're saying goodbye. I understand. It's
sad.
This live super.  Expo 2022
Well, it's still going on, so let's
get excited after this
[Music]
Okay then,
thank you everyone. Yes, the
reporters
were Shishiro Botan and Lamy Yukihara
[Music]
[
Music] [Music]
[Music] [
Music]
[Music]
[Music] [Music]
Everyone who comes to this Live Third Festival
Enjoy Hololive Third Festival  Are you
having fun
? Our project is about to begin.
So, the project we're going to do now
is Hololive enemy press conference rehearsal. Yeah, I guess that's right, but it
's a little sudden, but it's a bit like Hololive.
To all the superstars who will be responsible for a little bit of the future, thank you very much for coming here today. Don't be too picky. I've warned all the superstars that
someday you'll be holding a press conference or
something like that.
Hey, today we're going to have a rehearsal for this press conference,
and we're going to have a rehearsal for this event.It
's a stage, but we're going to
do a rehearsal for the press conference.It
's a luxury.I'd
like to ask you to introduce yourself and ask me the most difficult question I've ever been asked.
I think so.
But what is it? Well, Mr. Fubuki,
I'd like to ask you a question.
Yes, everyone, this is the most troublesome question I've ever been asked. It
seems like you're in a troubled situation right now.  I didn't expect a message like this to
come all of a sudden since the three of us were together. It's
strange and that's what's
bothering me the most.
[Music]
Please, yes.
This is the comet of a Vtuber who appeared like a comet and is burning the raw stone of tomorrow.  The most troublesome question I've been asked is: Have
you ever laughed out loud recently? [Music] I often get asked about things like surveys, but
that's why I laughed so hard recently.
When I burst out laughing, I
don't burst out laughing anymore, so I want you to stop it. Please
stop it. Please
leave the question as NG. Thank you for saying yes
.
Hololive 4th generation
butler, Tsunamaki is no good. Yes, yes,
listen.  The only thing that bothers me is when the
next three-day holiday is,
when is it, when is it, when is it?
[Laughs] That's
true.
[Music]
Yeah,
yeah, but please be careful about your health and
have fun streaming.
Thank you in advance.  Today's rehearsal is
boring if we just answer questions, so each of the three of us
is the Prime Minister of Shirakami Kuni Hochimachi, but we wanted to get this one
[laughter]
What's wrong with you? Moderator
What do you think?
[Laughter] I
would like you to pretend to be that late Prime Minister and hold a press conference.As the
Prime Minister, I would like you to be as fluent as possible,
answering questions like this, and not getting bogged
down like this.  After all, this is the best part, because it
doesn't make you feel like a person, so please
answer the questions fluently,
keep a cool face, and leave a famous quote.I've
set the bar high.Yes, then first of all, yes, are you
ready?Are you ready?
Mr. Watanabe, who is often forced to risk his life on the official program,
thank you very much. Thank you very much.
And everyone on the train.
Fubuki-san and Sui-chan are on the train.
Hey, these two reporters.  I'm feeling scared,
but
if time permits,
please ask me a few tough questions.Okay, let's
start with the press conference with Mr. Watame Tsunamaki, the Prime Minister of the country with the horns.Are
there any reporters with questions?
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
what kind of country do you want to turn into now that you're inaugurated as prime minister?
Great, by all means,
what are you going to do about it? Now that you
know that the number of sheep will increase,
isn't food important after all?
Oh,
wait.
Establishment By the way, is
there a lot of sheep in that country? Well, they
almost look like sheep. Are
there a lot of girls and boys who are sheep? That's
right.
By the way, what kind of laws do you want to make in
that country of sheep?
Lawyer:
There are so many people who don't sleep [music]
Isn't it true that when you count sheep, they go to sleep, but they don't sleep
? That's right. After all, trying to get them to sleep
means they
keep
running, which is dangerous.
Are they the country's sheep?
[laughter]  ]
No, I'm
sorry. It
turned into an apology press conference, but that's true. The
Prime Minister says he's not a sheep. By the way,
what kind of country is this? Yes, yes, yes, what kind of
place is
this?
Well, to put it simply, it tastes good. Is
there a possibility that it will be eaten up when the Prime Minister changes?
Sorry.
[Laughs] Is there
anyone you would like to be your secretary? Or a minister, or
someone you would like to consult with?  I
don't have anything to do, but do you have any plans
? Eh, I'd like you to play Sui-chan.
By the way, the money is a bit negotiable, but I
'll buy it for how much I like, and
then it'll
be 500 yen per month. No, no, no.  I'll take you on the train for a moment. I'd
like to know your motto, Prime Minister. I guess I'll
have to try it myself.
[Laughs] That
's amazing.
By the way, what does Victory want to do now? What do you
want to do? I'd
like to have a second live,
Prime Minister.
Yes, there
will be a live performance at this event, so let's do our
best here as well.
[Music]
Yes, but it looks like we'll be able to bring in some other ministers,
so we'll do our best. Let's do our best.
The same goes for this third festival. The
fashion is strong.
So, it
's almost time for the press conference. Accounting is over.
[Laughter]
So I tried it, but
what do you think? Both the person being attacked and the
person asking the question. It's quite intense in Europe, but the
person asking the question.  How was the two of you?
Well, it was interesting because you could poke at me with whatever you wanted. Hey, it was interesting.
Mr. Watame, who was poked so hard at me, looks a bit like he's done it,
but it's
difficult.
[Laughs] I'm
saying something that contradicts myself.  I know what you
mean, but I'm going to say this,
but you're too kind to be a prime minister,
Dame-chan.
[Music]
Next, I'd
like to ask Mr. Fubuki, the prime minister of Shirakami Country. I don't think I can do it. I'd like to ask him to act
like a prime minister.
Well,
that's the start of Prime Minister Shirakami's press conference.
Please give me a message.
Is it a
message? I understand your message. Well,
my fellow citizens, let's
continue to push for good health today, Mr.
Prime Minister.  Of course
you guys are idols.
What are the people?
To the prime minister, the people are
like horses. The more the
people
are flirting with each other, the more
power the prime minister has. The
people of Shirakami country  What kind of people are there? The
people of Shirakami Prison are full of unique people.
Various attributes,
comics
, girls are okay, boys are okay, it's okay. The
combination
is the Prime Minister's favorite combination, right? The
Prime Minister's.  My favorite combination is
the one I mentioned earlier, the one called
Ominori, and the older sister and the cute girl making out on their phones.Is that
correct?It
's also my boom.Do you have any
recommendations?Reporters, I
haven't taken the course.
[Music]
Even if you take the class, that call is
coming in Yes, that reporter over there
is watching because of the side pay, but
Waki-tei
is already justice, justice, right? Apparently he collects the idol's oppe mouse
pad as well.
Yes, it's
from 10am to 10pm.
What do you do on your days off, Prime Minister? I
like to play my favorite games and watch anime. By the way,
what kind of work are you planning to do?  In the future, I
see, first of all, I
think we'll divide it into underground categories. I
think there are a lot of different genres.
I see, there are
people who want to be idols. I see,
that's what adventurers are.  I think there are people who are
fantasy-type people, and
there are people who are okay, right?
Well,
what district will the Prime Minister be assigned to? In
that case,
of course you will be in the idol district.
Cool and cute idols,
called Sorry Prime Minister.  Are you still attracted to your job?
Yes, Mr. Prime Minister.Of
course. After all, you can do whatever you want.  I
think so. [Music] I think so.
What should we name the shop? A
Mr. Dame, who was assigned to the district, asked me
right away. I see.
What should we do? What should we name the shop? Bye.
There are a lot of side cups. It's the one
with the sign.  It's
okay, it's okay, isn't the shop turned into a castle or something? From the outside, it looks like that
What do you mean by buying that reporter?
Prime Minister Shirakami, I guess there
wasn't enough room for scale.He
created a country of two reporters.That's quite a feat.I thought he'd
try to make a little more money out of it.  That's what I thought, but it's quite true.
Akagi's ideals are too high. It's a bit surprising, but what do you
think of the Prime Minister? Did you
have any leeway at all? Well, I've got a lot of
leeway. The
games and anime where I've opened up my desires.  I heard that it didn't turn out to be a wonderful country where comics and manga of all genres
come together. It's a
completely happy island. I'm
sure everyone in the venue right now is probably
thinking that they'll be included in the [Music] district, right?
Thank you
very much for your support in the Hololive area among idols.It was a wonderful press conference.And at the
end, you were quite good as a reporter,
but what about you as the Prime Minister?
Sui-chan, yes, is everything okay?I
feel like being a reporter is my calling.  On the
other hand,
even though I'm a mom, I feel like I have a strong defense, so I'm
really looking forward to it. We're going to
build things up. Now, Prime
Minister Hoshimochi Koku Comet's press conference will begin.
[Music]
Hello everyone.
Thank you very much.  From now on, I'm
going to have a question period, so if
you have any questions, please let me know.
[Music]
What's the appeal of the job of rating ratings? It's
more than just an appeal, it's about supporting the people,
so
[Music] I want to
support you.
What kind of things do you do when you just want to do your best
? First of all, you lose your morning.
[Laughs]
Is that so? Is
n't that okay? Is there only night?
Does that mean we live without sleeping? That means we live
at night 24 hours a day.  Well, it's just that the sun doesn't rise.
No problem. Yes, that's the kind of country we are. Yes, that's
right.
What are you doing now?
On your days off, that's right.
In our country, we only come at night, so I
'm lying down.
To the Prime Minister:  I'm sure you've tried your best in many ways to achieve this goal,
but
have you ever felt like you've failed?
Well, until I became prime minister, this country was
lost without a single morning.  There
was a time when mornings were a breeze, and so did I. Well, they
wouldn't allow me to work before 3pm, and then there would be times when I would
be late because I was called to work before 3pm.
[Music] I
think everyone will be able to spend a more peaceful time by spending the night.
I see. I see. I see. I
see. I
understand. Is
it okay for your body to stay at night? It's true that you're
healthy.  It's important, so I
thought everyone would say that,
and we're currently developing the latest technology.
[Music]
Oxygen Cylinder
Woman We're
developing food that will help us survive. It's a
famous product, isn't it?
Moonlight bathing.  It's
suspicious, but I'm curious.
What color is it? What color is it? It's
blue. It's
rice, right? Does that
mean you have no appetite?
How do you spend your time at night? The
people of Japan
like to work for about 3 hours and sleep.  You're not doing things like doing other things or
taking a bath. That's
great.
By cutting it down to three hours, you're actually more efficient.
[Music] The
reason why it's so great is that there's a scientific
basis for it.  Well, there's a doctor who says that it's better to work
in a short period of time instead of lazing around for a long time.Who
is this,
Koyori in a white coat?The person who
turned off the sun is also a bit young.  It's more like a
doctor than a child. That's
amazing. It
seems like it takes a pretty huge budget, but
I wonder if the finances are okay. I've been doing it, so what do you think? By the way, if you were to have a doctor do something in that white-coat hut, what would you have him do? Sounds like it.  Next, I'm
going to have to win the lottery.
[Laughs]
What kind of restaurants do you recommend here?
Music] There are
no poisonous substances [laughing] But it's still
Hoshimachi Park.
What's there? Well,
our country has already given us a
very wonderful super idol star, the Machi
Comet, and it seems like it
would be fun to have a star studded with it nearby.  Is that so
?
[Music] It's an
area where you can be chased by a comet.
That's what it's like. It
's a stage where comets sing. There are
plenty of greetings, and I'm
sure it's fun to have a parade, but it's
a lot of work for one person to do it.  So you're
doing it alone.
Accounting is over.
[Music] It
seemed like it would be a pretty fun development,
but at the end Park came out and it was a
bit of a pain to be managing it all by yourself. It's so
black.
Let's add more.  To
all of you who have enjoyed such wonderful health,
please share your thoughts in a few words. First,
Mr. Makiwatabe, please.
Hmm, it was fun. I
don't often get asked questions like this, so I'm
not sure.  So, don't you have any time like this reporter?
Don't you have any time?
Please leave a comment to the first customers.
Thank you for watching. I
hope you too become a butler.  Please
become a sheep at dawn.
Thank you.
Thank you.  Yes,
thank you very much. Thank you very much for your support. And what
about Prime Minister Fubuki? Well,
after all, our country is a utopia,
so I'm thinking that my child will live in a utopia,
but it's
a bit naughty, isn't it?  It's not okay to go too far, so in
that case, the penalty is the death penalty.Ah, it's
beautiful.That's right.It's because
of the sales of Kitakami's arbitrary decisions and transformations.Isn't that
right?
Survival rate
[Music]
Schwarz
Even Hololive Production's booster pack.
Unstoppable Weis Schwarz
Booster Pack Holo
Live Production Now
on sale
[Music]
Bushiroad
Ah, my favorite anime, Chugai Kogyo.I
plan and develop anime goods that I want to enjoy anime in contentvention and
sell them on the internet.In collaboration with anime, I've
collaborated with the past  For the latest information, please follow us
on Twitter
[Music]
[Music] [Music
] [Music] [
Music] [Music] [
Music] [
Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music]
[Music] [
Music]
[Music]
[Music] [Music]
[Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [
Music  ]
[Music]
[Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music]
[  [Music]
[Music]
[
Music] [Music] [
Music] [Applause] [Music]
[Music] I'm
tired of that pot and I'm sweating, but I
'd appreciate your help with the instrument.
[Applause] [Music
]
Uh
[Applause]
-
[Music  ]
[Applause]
Ok, I'll
show you the Indonesian game. I'll show you my red hair.
Please come and worship Rahmando Grasshopper for a battle of guessing.
[Music]
[Laughter] [Music] [
Music]
[Laughter]  ]
[Music]
[Music] [Music] [
Music] [Music] [
Laughter] [
Music]
[Laughter] [Music] [Laughter]
[Music]
[Laughter] I'm
sure you missed this.  A
senior with doubts, a
purple pick-up
[
laughter] Gita, even if it's an ideal, it's somehow sweetened [laughter] -
[music]
[laughing]
[laughing] [
music] [music] [music] [laughing] [laughing] [music] [
music] [
laughing] [laughing]
Music]
[Laughter]
[Music]
[
Music] [Music] [
Music] [Music]
[Laughter] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Laughter] [Music] [Music]
[Music]
[Laughter]
Even if Elia, who I admire,
really
posted it
[Laughter]
OK, so
[Music]
But when are you
going to open it?
[Laughter]
[Music]
[
Music]
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Laughter] [
Music] [Laughter] [Music] [Laughter
]
[Music]
[Music  ]
[Music] [
Music]
[Music] [Music]
[Laughter]
[Music]
Meow the Enma Brick.  Kare-sama and Kan-
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Music] The
girl who is sorry for that face is Mika,
and packet comemon is stupid.
Nyanpa, long
face or face miso is a stupid
idiot.  Bapastic
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] [Music]
[
Music] [Music] [
Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [
Music]
[Music]
[Laughter  ]
[Laughter]
[
Laughter] [Laughter]
[Music] [Applause] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music]
[Music]
[  Music]
[Music] It
's the Expo! Let's get
excited. [Music] That's why everyone is excited
. Let's do our best today. [
Music]
Yes.  I am the moderator this time. I
am Matsuri-chan, the passionate idol of Natsuiro All Live.
[Music]
Kai
[Music] The
true person in charge of purity among Hololive's 1st generation members is
Akiloze, who is also known as Akiloze.
Thank you.  You're watching.
[Laughs] Yes,
everyone. Let's
go with this flow. The
leader will do a fair copy.
[Music]
Well, I'm Noel Shirogane. Thank you.
[Applause]
[Music] A
different kind of festival.  This is the corner where you can participate.Please
come later.Memory
Quiz.Yes,
yes.I will explain this corner.One of
you will be asked to ask the questions, and the
other two will be the ones to answer the questions.
And from here on, I
think it would be easier to understand if I explain it a little bit along the lines of the actual process, so I'd
like to explain it a little while pretending that the festival is the person asking the question, and when the question opens, Noel is the answerer.
[Music]
Please give me an image.
Yes, first of all, it looks like this,
but the image will appear. Yes, that
image will be the first time I've seen it, so
please be careful. And at this timing, the
person asking the question.  At the festival, we think about a problem.Yes, I
see.Well, it
could be anything,
like how many carnivorous animals there are.Don't say it out
loud.I'll
think about the problem and perform.
While the person was thinking, the two respondents were
wondering what kind of problem Noel would come up with,
and just memorize the image.Okay,
yes, time
passes and the image disappears, so the image disappears.
After that,
at the festival,
questions will be asked there, and
the two of you
will have to come up with the answers based on your memory.The
questions will come out later, like yes, yes, so
it's a later quiz.Memory: It's
a bit difficult today.
There are confident people.Confidence in this group is
good.However, I'm thinking of changing the questioners for each question.Yes,
everyone can ask questions.Yes,
yes, yes.By the way, the
questioners are also images.  Since the correct answer is announced while the
student is listening, the memorability of the questioner
is also important.I see, I
have an image of whether it's okay or not, but I feel like I'm going to ask a question that I don't understand.What
kind of question is it going to be?  It's going to
turn into a quiz show that I don't understand. Let's
try it for a while. OK.
Let's start the festival with the questioners giving an explanation.
[Music]
Now,
please give me a picture. It's a rice ball. I
want to eat it.
This is just a lot of information.  There aren't that many,
so that's right.I'm going to
start thinking about the problem by the end of the year,
so please think about it carefully.Okay, let's
go.Looks
delicious.I'm hungry.You can look at the image when making the problem.I'm
worried.  It's so simple that I feel like I
could definitely answer it,
but
it seems difficult.Okay
, I decided.Okay, let's do this.Memorize it,
remember it,
memorize it.Even if I take a good look at it, I'll try to memorize it.If I keep looking at it, I'll get
hungry.  Hey, I'm
hungry. [Music] I'm not hungry, I'm getting hungry.
After all, the rice balls are delicious, and they're delicious.
Well, there was a problem at the festival, but if the two of you said
that you had memorized it perfectly, I
think it's about time.  But what do you think?
[Music]
[Laughter]
That's all. Now, I'd
like to present a question from the festival.
By taking the time, we'll be able to remember the two of us.
What color was the desk?
[Music] The one in the middle
is
That's right, I guess I was just looking at the rice balls.The
color of the table is the same as the body.
[Music] You do
n't have to memorize it to get by.There
are quite a few different colors, but
yeah,
everyone laughs.The
venue is here.
How about that? [Laughter] How about that? Did you get your answer? I wonder if you
get it?
Listeners, do you get it? I remember it properly.
Well, it's time to go. Well, I
'd like to ask someone who is confident.  But the people I work with
[Music] I
answered that I'm sure so
Coffee video
[Music]
There's one.
Next up, Mr. Noe. Over
here. It's
Rodon
Dark Lone.
[Music]
[Laughter] I
see.  I see. Well then,
Matsuri-chan's
that one
is different. Hello, that senior is different. Because brown is like this. It's
not that bad.
Even if it was brown, I
didn't notice.
[Music]  Let's
go, then.
Here's the correct answer.
[Music]
Okay, please check the image.
[Music] It
's black. I
thought it was black, but it's brown.
That's just my preconceived notion. I
also have a preconceived notion that it must be brown.  Because it's there
[Music]
Hey, I didn't follow you. This is
frustrating. I was
n't drawn to the color of the black seaweed on the rice ball. And that's it. There's a light on the left side, so it's
quite bright.
It's unnecessary. I think the image of black was a bit off.
But I think the
correct answer was black. It
must have been difficult for everyone, the listeners. I see. I think I've created a good problem. So we've just
started, so yes, it's the first problem.
Now, let's move on to the next problem.  So,
who wants to ask the questions?
[Music]
Well, it's fine if you want to create the questions. Is it true? Since you
gave it to me, I
feel like I have to do it as a junior.
So, please proceed a little from here.
Okay, I
think so.
Well, let's start with that. Is that how you feel? [Music] I see. There's
a lot of praise. I'm
sorry, but Nobita is the only one. I see. You have to try a little harder.
I see.  This is it, so I'd
like to go with this image. Now, I'm going to
create a problem, so I'll create a new one.
Eh, open this sticker. I want everyone now.
[Laughs] As
expected. I want people to
praise me unconditionally. I'm just alive.
That forehead. [Laughs.
]  [Music] I'm
going to walk around town with this. I
see. It looks like I can do all sorts of
things. [Music] Yeah, it looks like I can do this. I might not be able to remember it. Difficult sentences are difficult, aren't they? [Music] Yeah, I see. There are so many different patterns.  Don't memorize the problem before you make it.
[Laughs] The
problem is probably serious, but it's true. I'm
starting to feel anxious.
[Music] I'm
shaking. I've
given up. I tried to
erase the burned wood.
OK.
Yes,
it's a scary face.
Okay, that's okay. Now then, the image. I
wonder if everyone has memorized it. Now, it's okay to ask questions and ask them. But here, I learned Matsuri Senpai's technique a little while ago, and I'm a little nervous. I've
only memorized one thing that everyone can make.  No, let's
go, okay? Now,
the question is,
how many flowers are there behind that flower on the far left? It's a cherry blossom, but
what is the number of flowers behind the cherry blossom? The
back of the cherry blossom.  Hey, the
petals are red. I
'm looking at you. I'm looking at you a lot. Let's do our best.
[Music]
So, by the way,
in terms of numbers, what numbers do you like?
Wait a minute.
By the way, what are you
talking about? Just once.  Why
don't you just forget about that and try drawing a picture of a cherry blossom?I
think you can derive it from that.I think
it's okay to use cherry blossoms, which are known for their classic resignation.Hmm, I do
n't know if this is a problem that can be solved with a combination of memory and intelligence.
But I see, I'll
buy it based on my knowledge. Yeah, I
'll go. I didn't write about men and women.  I'm
sure you have
glasses. You're wearing glasses. I
'll ask you from my senior. Yes, Akira-senpai's
answer
is, ``I see. Well, speaking of cherry blossoms, there are five of them.''
Yeah, it's good, isn't it?
[Music]
This is an illustration.
But it's a really mysterious technique.  Now, let's say it's nice. That's
right in the middle. So
there's a seed. Well
then, Ematsuri-senpai, look at this answer and say,
hmmm.
Now, let's take a look at Matsuri-senpai's answer as well.
Well done.
[Music] I see.  I see. I see, is the
leader's answer correct? Well, I
think the leader is correct, but
here is the leader.
Delon: Yes, 5 pieces, so it's
possible that everyone is wrong about [music],
right?  Let's take a
look.
Can I have a picture?
[Music]
In one word, that one
from earlier at the festival was very well
done. I can even remember the
word ``ta''.
So, I'd
like to send it to you. Let's try a little harder on the podium. It
's wonderful. I want to give the sticker to everyone.
Who will be next? Well, if it's in this order.
Well, I should open it. Let's go.
Please.  Yes, please. Next time, I
would like to create a problem that will make everyone say VV. This
is an image.
[Music]
This is a
huge collection of information.
[Music]
[Music] I
see.
Okay, let's create a problem.  I think so,
but I
can't seem to remember it. It's
certainly cute and I've seen it many times, but I do
n't really remember how to remember who is here.
[Music] I
see.
[Music]
No, but when I look at it like this, I
think that Hololive has really gotten bigger. It
's amazing. It's really amazing. The amount of information. It's like a person in school. It's getting more and more like that.
[Music] I
can do the problems, I
can do them.  I've done this.
So everyone is fine,
so I'll give it to you.
Now, let's move on to the question. Yes, it was
definitely there.
What was the text written at the top of this?
Please look at it.  [
Music]
[Music] I
thought that if I forgot, I'd be staring at people too much, so in the
spring, I'd have to do a
reverse meta-read,
give them the questions,
and read the instructions,
etc. But I have no choice but to
read the meta-read, and now
this event is over.  Let's talk about what it is.
Yeah, okay, maybe I should write it in color. Hey, maybe that's it. What is it? I
don't know what it is. Ah, please spell it in English properly
. I
remembered it in my head and
wrote it down.
Maybe. That's
what the manager said.  That's right,
that's right, that's it.
[Music] I don't
think anyone would make a mistake with this. I
wonder if I should wear some glasses. My
eyes are huge. There's
no way they'll disappear.
[Laughs] It
appears.
Okay, so I guess it's melted.
Okay, so I'd like to open Matsuri-chan and Nore-chan Kaito at the
same time.
Don Do
Don
Super Expo
200022 Ah, they're both the same
[Music]
Content
Wait,
Festival
[Music] I
'm saying that.
[Laughs]
So, here is the correct answer. It
was Den Super Expo 2022.
But everyone is too senior to me in town, so I
thought about whether or not to include Ai, but I couldn't
.
[Music] It's a shame,
so please study a little more.
[Music]  ]
Thank you all for your support,
please. I mean, everyone is always
[Music] It's a
dream, right?
[Music]
By the way, I'm
happy to be able to perform live, and to be able to
do things like this.  Let's end on a nice note, saying that the plan was
completed and that everyone had a great time.
[Music] There's
still a
lot of fun to be had, so I hope you'll
enjoy it. Lastly, I'd like to
give it a try and tell you how it was.  Well, I
think I've managed to hide the fact that my ability to retrieve memories is weaker than I expected.But I
still have a lot to do, so I'll do my best.Let's
put it on my forehead and
do my best.So,
that's all for the section you've been waiting for.  Yes,
everyone, did you
enjoy it? Yes, I enjoyed it. There
are many things to see at each Third Festival Expo, so
please enjoy it to the fullest.
Bye bye bye
[Music]
Weiss Schwarz
Even with Hololive Production's booster pack, Vice
won't stop.  Schwarz
Booster Pack
Hololive Productions Now
on sale
[Music]
Bushiroad
Ah, those who love anime, Chugai Kogyo Contents, who
want to enjoy options and anime.We
plan and develop anime goods and sell them on the Internet.We have
collaborated with anime and done things in the past.
For the latest information, follow us on Twitter
[Music]
[Applause]