[Music]
okay
listen to the to this dope
game bgm though
[Music]
groovy
hello
can you hear me i hear myself like kind
of quiet
what the hell uh uh uh
[Music]
uh oh okay probably probably fun
hello guys
we have to talk about this
what what did you hear it
if you're not on twitter you might have
even missed
is there anyone who has not heard of it
anyone who hears this for the first time
i heard yes yes yes
no what what has everyone heard
was announced i was sleeping while it
was announced
i wanted to be up for the for the full
hype experience
but i would have had to be up at
5 00 a.m which is if anything i could be
up
if i would stay awake which which i
didn't want to do this
uh last night so
yeah i was sleeping and i woke up and i
was like i was like
i i had my alarm at 11 a.m which is
quite early for me
and i i wake up and i'm like
oh wait wait wait i want to check out
everyone's reactions yeah right we had
announcements
we had an announcement and suddenly i
was super awake
this is like you know that's why
yesterday
and and even before that i kept on
saying that i'm like super excited
and um also like yesterday i said i'm
looking forward to friday
i was like guys guys tomorrow is friday
i just couldn't say anything but yeah
i was i was like teasing that i was very
excited but
that wouldn't necessarily have meant
that i'm excited because of these new
outfits because i had
more many more reasons to be excited
as you guys know tomorrow i am moving
into new apartment which is one thing
that i'm excited about and then
possibly next week yeah pretty pretty
definitely next week
i'm releasing uh a pretty awesome song
cover
which is another reason to be excited
but the thing that i was
really in reality excited about was
easier outfits i just couldn't say so i
was
i was just saying oh i'm excited for so
many things yeah yeah there's a lot of
things going on here you guys know you
guys know
it might i mean it was it was legit it
was legit i had
from you from your point of view i had
enough reasons to be excited
[Music]
um how to say oh
predictions that i've seen until now
um my
the predictions for me have been like
pretty
close uh
i feel like my my uh
outfit in the silhouette is very easy to
guess
now maybe like cali maybe isn't that
easy gouda
besides you know those weird pointy
things on her
head besides that you don't really get
much from what her outfit will look like
the same with uh amen you also don't see
it well but because my silhouette is
like so tight
and uh like you know you can see like
you can you can really guess it it's
really easy to guess
it's very easy to guess and i i i've
seen a lot of
uh ideas from people on twitter already
that are
pretty close i mean no no one really got
it hundred percent
and let me just tell you there is more
to that
there will be more than that um this is
not
everything i have i have a bunch of
like secret weapons
yeah you could definitely call it secret
foreign i'm so excited to show you i'll
be the second one
um cali goes first on monday and i go
second on tuesday
however in japanese time it's a
wednesday so there's
like yeah 24 hours of no
no reveal well yeah we weren't allowed
to just um
decide the times on our own uh
because well we live in different
countries and have different um
viewership uh different people like you
know
you know you know so oh yeah i went for
it this time
and it's 11 p.m my time
6 am japanese standard time
i hope it's an okay time for you guys as
well for everyone
and i think for my fake australians
it should be 7 00 am wait is fake
australia one hour after
like uh like like after japan or
like plus one hour or would it be seven
a.m or is it five a.m
five a.m one hour ahead okay for
for the fake australians it's 7 a.m
this seems okay that seems acceptable
you could get
for such a special stream you have to
get up
so wherever in the world you are you
have to watch this you have to watch it
and if you want to participate in like
you know all making some like
assumptions some ideas sketching out
some things even if you don't have like
a super great art skill i've seen some
people with like not
much of an art skill and
doing some some some funny me me me
ideas and i would love to introduce them
in my stream so i've uh if you check on
twitter i did like a hashtag
and it's called hashtag phoenix fashion
so there you can
use this silhouette and then um
yeah guess what it will look like uh for
me specifically and i will
show it on my reveal stream which will
be on tuesday
and um uh
i i'll do a proper tweet of it though
and give you guys the silhouette if you
want to work with that i'll give it to
you because
uh you know there's something in front
of it and and ina is also a little bit
in front of me
so i'll give you the actual file later
on
um yeah it will be fun i know mine is
really easy to kiss but please go crazy
with it
i already saw some funny ones uh
and some ideas where i'm like [\h__\h] why
didn't we do that
okay
i love the idea of you know i mean
i mean even if it's obvious i'm not
gonna say
anything but like ina is holding
something right
and and and there's something around on
the top of her head
wouldn't it be fun if she had like you
know because of monster hunter as well
if she had an actual freaking afro like
bob ross
oh asparagus and bread
oh yeah yeah could be it
yeah why it doesn't have to be what do
you think it is maybe it is
asparagus and bread maybe she went for
the french look i don't know
i mean asparagus is not necessarily
french i guess but she couldn't
she could be carrying a baguette around
yeah i love i love how
uh okay okay guys actually i saw
everyone
already and i gotta say like my personal
favorites
are dina and
like i would wear her clothes
same with inna possibly but i feel like
what ina got it just fits her
so so so so so so so well
and it's just ah so cute
and what oh my god it's just so cute i
would wear it like every day
i can't see more but yeah everyone
everyone's outfits are really cute but
um i'm so excited i'm so excited i'm so
excited
[Music]
are you guys excited too this is so
exciting oh my god oh my god oh my god
oh my god
oh i should have just done a talking
stream today to be honest why am i even
playing but but
i chose a very fitting game here as you
can see i'm moving out tomorrow
night
but today won't be a long stream because
i'm moving tomorrow and i'm not done
packing
i was packing today before the stream
and uh i was doing some other stuff too
and oh my god well well maybe i'll get
to taco i need to keep some
talking points for the stream uh i'll
talk a bit more
uh pacquiao thing zelo mayo i cannot i
need to stream because i can't
stream on the weekend that's okay well
this will be maximum two hours
okay so okay a new outfit super hype but
whatever
what have you guys seen oh my god oh my
god have you guys seen
next week is not only our outfit review
but like three members from the fourth
generation and i am a senpai as well
so it's like wait let me count nine
outfit reveals next week
oh my god
nine outfits oh my god but i'm glad that
we're not like overlapping because the
whole end is mostly doing it in the
morning
time japanese time and japanese members
obviously are doing it in the
evening time japanese time so we're not
overlapping but still it's like
sometimes
[Music]
i think i understand yeah because
japanese uh
people have a golden week right now
which is like one of the few
days in a year when japanese people get
some days off
for once and uh i think they probably
tried to have it during that golden week
holy fashion week oh my god you could
really call
it that you could really call it that
let's walk a freaking
runway yeah
oh god i need to think about what to do
during my
outfit review as well besides you know
this is the first time i'm doing
something like that properly
besides doing uh you know
the the review of the of the of the
predictions
i don't know i was thinking of some
other things to do but i'm not sure how
how i will do those things and i don't
really have time to think about anything
but
yeah maybe i'll also sing with a song
yeah because you know lots of people
going to be watching i want them to hear
me sing
i'm
something in the chat that that that i
i saw and i'm just like wow if if you
only knew
if if you only knew oh my god
okay and by the way i think i decided to
release that
um song cover like right after my reveal
stream
uh on tuesday and
possibly i'm just waiting for uh
the mixer but he's he's fast he works
fast
and then uh the the person
that i'm singing it together with which
is
someone on this picture and
she uh needs to re-record one little
part but
we should we should make it in time we
should be able to make it in time
uh so anyway oh my god i need to play
this game let's move out let's move the
freak out
[Music]
okay get rid of that okay okay
i'm so excited but i'm also so stressed
out oh my god okay let's play this game
new again this is the first time i play
it
and and i wanted to play controller but
i realized
apparently i cannot use the controller
on the steam version
at least it doesn't give me the option
uh does anyone know
has anyone played this on steam and was
able to play it with controller because
like if i go back
i have to connect it i have my my switch
controller connected
uh well like if you go here it says key
bindings and then you can go like here
you can set it to that but that's it but
oh well i guess we'll play with keyboard
i hope it's
not so difficult i hope it's not so
difficult
switch yeah
check your controls in this stream
alright okay okay
ah wait did someone say something about
big picture oh
switch pro configurations assistant
it does see my it does seem my nintendo
switch pro controller
you have to does it work now
uh yeah okay okay
uh what what about this big picture
configuration
the controller configuration allowance
and controllers
it uh okay let me try to restart this
i was trying to do it outside of the
stream but i didn't get it
that sounded hot oh you want to hear me
speak with german huh
okay okay wait let me hide it for a
moment
[Music]
yes okay
attack yeah
[Music]
all right please tell me my controller
is working now
oh yeah it's working you guys are all
[\h__\h] geniuses
[Music]
too hot i'm burning up oh i mean it
makes sense i'm a vegan so of course i
make people around me feel hot
press anything
oh he's telling me to have a smooth
smooth
move okay i hope so too wait why did it
go back to
wait why did it close an obs why did it
what okay now but why did it close
was it never open no there we go okay
okay
now here here we go
[Music]
wait it's english right okay
sorry i'm like i'm like excited oh that
looks actually that looks like me
now these these others don't look like
me cat
and it actually does look like me you
guys
wait you can change the color body
oh i can be on the wheelchair that looks
like clump
comfy but i'll uh
where you can
you can change that part too
but actually the default one really
looks the most like me
wait that was one with a burp on their
head
and these ones are being eaten by fish
oh a pineapple
pineapple friend
why is the default one i can't can't
find it anymore
where is it where is it
[Music]
give me wait is this just random
combinations
will i ever get the default one again
maybe i should just like
i do want to look at them that was not
it by the way it looks similar but the
hair color was not accepting
it i want the burped up
i want the burp on my hat as well
wait and then that one had a cooking hat
is this just throwing random
combinations together
paint i can oh oh
no i don't i don't know how to choose
that
[Music]
and now i can't go back god damn it now
look that looked fine and
it was not okay okay
it doesn't go back to the orange haired
grill anymore
but that one looked so much like me
oh give me back
i i don't i don't want any of these
i get i'm getting really picky
don't press white no i have to i have to
change
something
[Music]
give me something with orange hair at
least
ah it was so perfect in the beginning
why did we destroy it
you know you can what press x
no i did you have to do that at first
like now you know but then it says y
x for classic i'm pressing custom
i mean press x but it doesn't do
anything only wow
it changes everything here just randomly
up and down selection oh
oh there's more
i guess like this one changes everything
randomly and this one
no what ah
oh oh disco
dance oh okay now
we're talking oh oh
oh oh oh chef's at what do you guys
think
foreshadowing is that that's chef's hat
all right okay
i guess we gotta go with that no
no no no that's okay i'll actually wait
let me check the other
hairstyles oh that looks similar as well
i guess but but i wanna go with that one
oh britney glasses ah wait
you know what that looks like
zelda wind waker
confirmed
[Music]
i really love this bgm oh my god thank
god it's such a good bgm
because i have a problem right now i
have this
i heard this song before the stream and
it's so good
and i have an ear warm and i cannot let
you guys hear it though because it's
secret
kelly had a mustache back then and this
is from
that was a video from a different
dimension lifting objects since the dawn
of time
welcome new employees to the smooth
moves family
this is your first step to becoming a
certified furniture
arrangement and relocation technician a
certified
well you're in luck this training module
will provide all the necessary
information you need to be a safe and
productive member of the smooth moves
family
okay i love this music
yeah 80s wave oh my god
picking up objects is an essential
moving technique
try kicking them but this way is much
quicker
okay nice okay this is a little training
intro something was invented by the
vikings
no problem is that okay objects with
your back
with my back oh okay well that's good
because i have
noodle arms what do you mean my back
but i'm playing alone though you are you
aware of that
wait i can't move that
what do you mean with my back what does
it mean
wait is that what's with the eye is that
because i have v-sync on
wait a second oh
you think that will be better
it looks better looks better right
hold the object and pull like i can't
hold it i can't hold it
it's got my knuckle what
what what i mean i can probably
push it over there but i don't think
that's what you what are you supposed to
do
oh ah oh oh lv
but don't worry these boxes are trained
for this
you should
okay take that and then hold x to aim ah
adjust out release uh extra throw oh
[\h__\h]
oh i did it i did it okay i wanna i'm
gonna train a bit more but okay so this
is how you do it when you play with
someone else throwing objects
the ground will catch it oh
okay okay i'll try to remember those
controls oh my god
you got this oh my god we broke a lot a
ghost
slap him out of the way if he gets too
close
i ain't afraid of nothing don't cross
[Music]
okay look if we have a vase
we we have we have a vase
where do we bring it oh wait i wasn't
supposed to do anything oh it probably
told me to
slap the vase always focus on what needs
to be moved next how do i know what
needs to be moved next
nice ah you're almost there i
believe in you thank you thank you for
me do you guys believe in me too i'm
moving tomorrow like for real folks this
is practice mode
legal requirements to start moving only
the only
minimum what we what what do we want the
minimum
and when do we want it now what do we
want the minimum
and where do we want now
we got the minimum guys high five
okay we are a car now say hello to
packboard tell them where everyone's on
the go
oh my god they're constantly leaving and
moving oh my god that's sad no one ever
settles down
as you get jobs it'll appear on the on
the map this is your trap there are many
like it but this is yours
nice let's get those smooth moves moving
track moving
that was a tongue twister surprising
enough
smooth moves moving track moving smooth
moves moving track moving smooth moves
moving track moving smooth
smooth okay
use the l to drive it around okay
you want me to go there okay holy song
okay
i left something for you in a giant hole
in gift box see if you can find it
okay wait in that house you mean
okay
[Music]
oh wait what what was that that's for me
i know that's a mandatory training okay
well then let's go gta home version it's
a cute version of the cta it's like a
mini
mini version pocket version
okay so uh
i like how it i like the detail it says
send faxes to 555 a real fax number
[Laughter]
okay so there's 14 items here
and if we want to get gold we need to do
it in two minutes 25 seconds i think
that's impossible but okay
get moving let's go let's go
let's go let's go help me guys and i i
can't i'm the next
i got noodle arms let's start off easy
with a one
bedroom house can't wait to get this is
michael jackson
am i allowed to play this
i can't wait to get started with this
back breaking label yay
and i can't wait to sit in the truck
teamwork yeah
okay okay okay those items okay okay we
got something in the bathroom too
a toaster couch table
okay move us
slap the door open hello okay uh uh
maybe we start with the sofa
yeah okay okay the time is ticking the
time is ticking tomorrow we actually
really don't have
that much of a like time limit
i want to move that more to the like so
we have more space here
there's gonna be a lot of items i think
this is tetris as well
stop stop come on no no this is not the
perfect placement no
ah okay there we go that's that's
beautiful okay
[Music]
oh was it okay we didn't break it right
it was just the cable was a little bit
plugged out not not so smoothly not so
nice
okay but i want to put that in oh my god
it will we
just one minute okay just
i hope we really can't fit everything in
there can we
no okay wait
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
wait do i really have to move that to me
actually
you won't get the pizza if you want help
me
okay okay we don't need gold we don't
need gold we're just we're just going to
do
it our own stuff wait does it what was
the button for
okay okay maybe i didn't need to move
those things
uh wait what was it okay there you go
okay we need that
yeah the microwave
that's one of the things i need to buy
once i'm done moving
and then we got here toaster ah
take it i lost it
no no no
okay i'm not stressed out it's not like
i want a medal or anything
i'm just here to move keep it up okay so
we're silver now we should be able to
get silva
okay um yeah
what is that is that little like a
projector for the wall
or maybe that's a playstation yeah
this is fun like i see like people
playing that
with their uh friends like in co-op but
it's only couch co-op
so anyway i couldn't organize a collab
so suddenly um but i thought this game
would be perfect so i'm playing it alone
here
tomorrow i will thankfully not be on my
own
because tomorrow i have a lot of friends
helping me i started
[Music]
okay wow wow i mean browns is easy
we're almost done oh the bed oh there uh
how do we get that out of there [\h__\h] the
door
no more door
i can't can i get it through the window
no i
okay so actually guys what i did today
is
oh part time i uh i
i uh a friend
i think you broke a chair i did not
excuse me
i got um i picked up my bed because my
bed
i uh didn't let it be delivered to me so
that we it would arrive quicker if we
pick it up ourselves
so i picked it up with my friend's car
and uh
i was absolutely shocked because like my
friend
like borrowed this huge car from
their family like really really
pretty big car but surprisingly
uh even with that huge car
my bed didn't really fit in well because
it's a
box spring band and they're like and
they're like huge and they're like
pretty much already put together you
know
rice over thank you for bringing your
card it's very helpful
yeah it's a big bed
not no not not 9k not even close it's
not didn't even cost me 1k because i
in the end i wanted to spend a bit more
money on it but i didn't have any
like i didn't have much choice but it's
okay it's still a good box spring bed
so ah
wait i was quite shocked when i saw
how like the the people from the
furniture place they rolled it out
and then they were like here there you
go and then we needed to put it in the
car
but it was so freaking huge
and it came in three parts uh
like the the the part where you sleep on
the mattress point
was like together with like the whole
bed like
like like frame and everything but like
that was two parts like
um
60 centimeters
[Music]
wide and 200 centimeters long
each part and we it was so close
one of those parts could like barely
fit into the car so we had to drive
twice
and it was really really a buy in the
end we had to take out
all of the seats of the car in order to
like yeah bring it over smoothly
i was huge with 7 inches i have no idea
thank you guys for the super chats by
the way thank you let's do another move
uh put an oh break the windows don't
break any windows
what do you mean with that ah okay
bring bring the flamingos ah okay no i
want to do the next move
i i could replay it with those goals but
i want to do the next move
where is it
[Music]
20 minutes is six foot six ho ho
and you did such a great movie and the
client referred you
to their friends they love your work
thank you
i only want to do my own move though not
other moves
we're not just moving furniture we're
moving hearts oh wow that's way too
romantic we're not moving any hearts
don't
i don't know what you're talking about
you think people are falling in love
with us or what peppa rolling planes
place the peppaloni unless something for
you in a giant pulling gift box see if
you can well he told me that
for that house as well wait was that the
box
in in the bathroom i don't know
i don't know what he means i didn't see
anything besides that did i miss it
was that like a secret are there secrets
yeah
in this game okay well that's pretty big
oh my god it really has peppa lonely
pizza
all over wait is in the back in the uh
bedroom in the living room in the office
in the kitchen it's everywhere it's so
good
ah oh well let's get moving
pro will let's have one word pivot wait
what does that mean again
remember don't hurt yourself our
insurance only covers the truck
ah the bus is always looking out for us
best yeah you guys don't hurt yourself
well you guys are not insured
or so a pivot means rotate
aha ready
everyone help me okay why don't we move
oh god i guess we start with the couch
it's huge
and we could get it out from um the back
is that we have to move that too okay oh
my god it's going to take ages
okay i'll move out that first
uh let's move out that too let's put
everything like in the garden first
maybe
why is there a turtle here are you
stealing stuff
what
what the [\h__\h] are you doing get out of
here
daddy
okay get that box it's leaving me alone
now
i don't know why oh you get that
uh microwave toaster and
uh the fridge
why did you not [\h__\h] prepare your
apartment for the move who leaves their
apartment like that
right before the move what is that
turtle still doing there
nadia no comments
okay okay and then let's get the chair
and then another box in the office room
oh um
this only that in that room okay oh my
god sorry
okay away from me stop it
can i get rid of the the tree no okay
let's get the
fridge i think though the strategy that
i went with we're bringing a lot of
items outside
first actually it was pretty good um but
i still need the bed
and that suitcase okay let's get that
it's coming from here okay
i don't really want to destroy any more
windows
because i probably get like minus points
for that we're doing
quite well
[Music]
one
okay put that there okay
was that it was that one too i think so
okay we're doing quite well at the time
right now we'll probably still not get
goats
okay let's get the big couch the biggest
cups [\h__\h] trees on the way
okay and that is the cat toy i think
some kind of cat
tunnel i had one of those too
okay would like to see this as a collab
yeah i was actually
thinking about it like a while ago when
i heard that we got permissions for this
a lot of the games from this company
are like really cute fun little games
that are perfect for this
so yeah i also want to play like the the
ufo the
working ufo game at some point it's also
a fun
small game that you can like play
anytime
let's show four objects left green
we're going for silva we're going for
survival
[Music]
left for silva sounds good sounds good
uh we got oh also the grill
[\h__\h] oh no i broke it
i broke it down so we have
one broken window and one broken tv by
the way
stay in there okay
one more object which is the bed okay
okay
where's the turtle not here okay good
stay out of this turtle no no no i don't
want to fight you i like turtles okay no
it's oh it's helping me now yeah it's
probably not it doesn't want to happen
but it is happening
that's hill bit me a [\h__\h] turtle's
[\h__\h] joke
i think that means he likes you oh do we
have any kfb turtles
in the shower who knows if that's true
all i can do is the romance
[Music]
was faster than before like because we
got silver down before we had bronze
even though this is a bigger house oh
a canal is a turtle is it true what they
say about turtles when they fight you
it means they're like you clients will
tip you for completing bonus objectives
nice oh don't break the face oh
deliver the turtle
we could have delivered the turtle and
what does gold mean
ah apparently was there a soccer ball
somewhere and we were supposed to like
uh kick it until go you can spend those
tokens at the pack more okay okay
okay i'll probably never ever play this
game ever again
but thank you sounds good
unless i move again then i'll probably
play the game again
oh dream still come true it's our newest
employee
why does he have an f it's a german
german letter
er with the two dots if you were in my
german class then you know how to
pronounce this
that daz that's le
des le hoff
our new client saw our ad and pacma post
wow very nice
the hoop house oh that's a big house
we're going there next
i left something for you ah did we not
find it again
a giant floating gift box what does he
mean
whatever he's talking about i am not
sure well i can just
destroy a lot of things to tell you oh
my god that's fun
gta the minigame okay
here oh only 12 items before it was 14
but the house is way bigger and the
objects might be bigger
as well uh okay
well then are you guys ready for another
move are you
ready to run out pull up your sleeves
and wipe off that disgusting sweat
let's go let's go let's go let's go i
love the music playing the whole time i
love it so much the client says to not
break their things
but be careful just kidding they paid
for moving insurance smash
oh so we don't have to be careful
okay question
okay start with maybe that room and we
can throw things out
so uh
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] that was bad aiming
[\h__\h] wait wait first can we break the
[\h__\h] glass
okay and now we should be able to throw
it nicely
okay it's kind of heavy so it doesn't go
that far but here
i wish i could throw the in the bed but
no that's not possible
we have to bring it though right now
okay that's it last thing in this room
so
let's get that [\h__\h] out of here
okay and the crown do we have to move
that soon though okay you're leaving the
fishies
how's that those poor fishies
okay we should probably bring out the
table because it's gonna be in the way a
lot of times probably
okay there we go
we got the bed the beds are always
one of the heaviest things and most
annoying things to move
pick it up pick it up
huh
oh
[Music]
that one doesn't have to be moved but oh
[\h__\h]
you have it move it out of the way
and then actually probably
oh my should be fine no now the [\h__\h]
table's in the way
get
love that song yeah there's some people
in the chat who don't know perfume
it's a japanese like not exactly an idol
you wouldn't call them an idol group
they they don't call themselves an idol
group but
it's like a free free women in the unit
um and they do like
uh like kind of electronic pop music
produced by the same person who produces
can you put me above me i think if i'm
not wrong
and they've been around for a long time
so they have a lot of songs they're
really really famous in japan they fill
out
whole arenas
if you haven't heard the music yet it's
really good
you can't get really addicting even if
you don't normally like that kind of
music but every once in a while i like
listening to perfume music
so good gosh
okay we got that part now let's go to
the kitchen uh only the fridge
and the microwave no problem
uh maybe i shouldn't throw it out of
that window
oh okay now the trees here are kind of
in the way
never mind i'll take the other way oh
god wait gold is
all already like gone in half a minute
can we get silva silva should be
manageable
uh what else do we have here not much
more
there's a chicken i hear a chicken
we have to save it we have to bring it
along we can't leave the chicken here
where is it did you guys see it i only
hear it
maybe that's a secret like mission to
find the chicken
and bring it along a trapped employee
can you breathe is he okay maybe outside
in that in there
you better stay i want you to stay it's
so cute it's so fluffy
it's kiara shut up shut up [\h__\h]
you know nothing
can we do it can we do it anytime she
can stay here
i know you guys language i've been just
trying to communicate with it
so that it will stay
what is this machine is it supposed to
be a computer like a really old-school
computer
like a typing machine oh it's so cute
it's actually staying
what if i slap it maybe that's the
actual mission to slap the booty of the
chicken
do you guys want me to slap your booty
wait that's the last object
[Music]
oh
yes please choke the chicken no what the
[\h__\h]
wow that was so close we smashed the tv
too
no we didn't they're just saying that
employees save do it again extra for
that
come on come on
object object
pets stay outside what do you mean with
that
that was not a secret mission
[Music]
burn the chicken no
now time to face no no no no no no
oh pets stay outside of the chicken
maybe maybe maybe because we didn't like
when we moved it
i thought ah stay outside maybe they
mean because i
uh it was trapped and we got it outside
of that little house
okay i'm glad we did that then the other
thing is when i shoot some hoops
eh don't break any windows
but you told me it's fine because they
have insurance goddammit okay
that went pretty well i would say uh
even though it was really close to silva
that pissed me off a little bit
you're building quite a reputation we
had someone specifically ask for you
who poolside pad
i left something i can never find it
this music is vibing it really is i love
it i want it in my playlist
okay oh stop stop sorry
oh wait there's a huge soccer ball here
oh my god wait we can play with it wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait wait no no i want to go
no no wait i want to go go
[Music]
good position good position it's way too
strong
[Music]
i wanted to save the ball
what is over there what's that
oh heckler island
[Music]
the ball maybe we'll come back after
we're done with this level
um let's do a best 18 items
let's do our best
search the map for presents not the
house ah okay
oh nice pool
oh my god it's music
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
not 60 60 fps anymore that wouldn't look
so good
in 60 fps guys yeah too bad too bad
i don't know why it's not 60 fps right
now kind of sad
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
anyways
is that does that does that mean you
want me to get everything wet
their furniture was water damaged when
we found it yeah yeah
that sounds about right smart thinking
wait i can jump into the pool too
[Music]
oh okay
i guess it's no time for going for a
little swim
what's with those cars there what that
was that mean oh my god
did i actually um make that happen
so proud of myself they also have an
aquarium like built into the wall that's
so
dope and i wish i had like a pool
i wish i know like in
america a lot of houses
and and i mean i guess a lot of houses
not apartments but a lot of houses come
with pools
we don't have that many like houses with
pools here in australia at least not
like
cheap ones it's really not that common
very uncommon only if you like super
rich
like if you get a really expensive house
but i know that in america
where why did i wink i know in america
it's not even that expensive right to
have a house with a pool
it's not not so super super luxurious is
that
okay the suitcase
i guess like on i can throw some stuff
over the pool
hopefully but i want to test it out with
something
that like uh it's not oh
oh my god okay
okay okay i can do this i can do this
girl
yeah okay we can do that
[Music]
oh oh maybe shouldn't have
thrown that
i jumped into the pool by accident oh
yeah
that was really close okay the others i
will not throw
because yeah
good that i don't have any like glasses
or like
other other kinds of uh
like like cutlerial plates i don't have
anything except the
the cups that nen and john gave me
before i left japan
so i gotta buy everything new i actually
don't have nothing like that to move
so not such a big problem
okay these glasses can also break we
don't want that
we don't want that let's be careful guys
oh
gold is gone in three seconds okay but i
want to do silver this time
[Music]
oh my god i almost lost it in the pool i
almost dropped it
fire's weak to water be careful
i keep on forgetting that yeah i'm a
phoenix
nah
i keep on forgetting that i just wish
wishful thinking i guess
whoosh chicken cans kind of swim
i guess so yeah probably can't candy can
i swim fine
candy what is left there's nothing left
in the kitchen
but something here oh my god quite a few
things at that chair okay
okay help me left me a hand guys give me
a hand
come on wait don't bronze already
what about silva oh
uh in the middle of getting silva but if
we don't get it done
wait did i did i miss silva no we're
right now we still have silva right wait
let me get that and then throw it
okay that's okay that's okay that's okay
get out of there quick
uh no no we don't what do we need we
need uh
uh that box i can throw
that what is that come on
okay nice i i think that one shouldn't
be frowned that's a
s-s-n-e-s
no what what what's that what did you
guys say that thing is
really old gosh
boxing
[Music]
that is
time for them to upgrade yeah it really
is get that nintendo switch
and playstation 5 i don't have one yet
by the way do you guys have it
in the chat has a playstation 5.
no no me me i got one i do
no no no no me huh not me just to switch
me nope nope lots of nose hmm
what it's okay guys i don't have one
either we didn't
even try to get one so
it is
next time we should fill the pool with
jello then we could walk across
mmm smart you can't walk across jelly
you would sink
ew if you make it hard enough then i
would just eat myself
on my way out
good idea that sounds like spoken by a
true potential
wait wait why why do we got bronze what
happened to silva
keep everything dry oh jump over the oh
i could have jumped over the pool
don't hold the box for more than three
seconds ah if you throw all of them
all right all right all right we only
got bronze that's sad
and it's even one minute too much yeah
it could have been much quicker i guess
oh well that's okay it's not about time
it's about you know making
doing your job properly with love
[Music]
now i really want to eat some ramen but
today i'm eating something else
roommate actually uh cooked for me
because i don't have time to do anything
today
um i have to go back to packing after
the stream as well
but for now for now we can have a little
bit of fun and then then i'll go back to
packing
i left something for you oh yeah okay
now let's try to find it
wait wait wait wait wait okay slowly
slowly
go go go go go finally
australia gets a goal in soccer
we suck at soccer now where is that
giant gift box
is it not that but it's flowing there
but like when i go there
it just says it's like the mandatory
train thingy maybe he means something
else
ah here
that's what you've been talking about
this makes up for forgetting your
birthdays
you forgot my birthdays oh you guys
remember my
okay who here knows my birthday
who knows my my birthday is my heart
it's okay if you don't know it but if
you know that i'm i'm impressed
a lot of guys immediately knew it damn
okay everyone else is just you know
copying the other people
thank you oh yeah it's july 6th
oh
his name is teapot like thomas pot or
something like that
cute is that cheese
is that cheese it's probably no it's
probably wheat balls
but myself look at that dude up there as
a snowman
nice all right next one where's the next
one jeremy's apartment okay let's look
jerry's apartment
he has 12 items oh he has stairs
okay stairs
oh
shut
forgive me i tried i tried i tried i
mean wheat balls
sounds about right sounds like some food
like a vegan option for meatballs those
wheat balls
[Laughter]
what's the deal with packing peanuts
they don't look like peanuts
they don't taste like peanuts involved
it sounds like a like a joke
a pun on the bus is the [\h__\h] is that
inna
is he not my boss he should do
stand up i didn't get it
ah there are those phone things ah
okay now if i would have underst stood
that and i
might have laughed at his joke okay
now that i know that um okay that was
okay
that was funny maybe a little bit okay
big apartment on the second floor on
your mindset go
[Music]
let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's go
where did we start oh my god oh we start
we start
let's start with uh can i is it okay if
i break through windows whatever
uh okay chair oh we can find a lot of
these things they probably won't be mad
but the pc super [\h__\h] oh you need a
upc anyway but right now it seems
impossible to get a new pc anyway
right a lot of parts are just
impossible to get as i have heard
are you sure but but that's
such such an opc someone give like help
him out
i feel sorry for him he can't play any
of the games
okay can i like drop no okay we have to
get that one down the couch
down the stairs i had
gpu well i'm glad i got my pc
through uh i mean it was not like free
but i got it through this company in
japan
i just told him i want a gaming pc
a good good pc and that's that's
basically
what i have now i think
i i guess you could ah [\h__\h] i guess you
could call it the game
pc but i don't i don't really know any
anything about that kind of stuff they
could have
sold me a really bad pc and i wouldn't
even have noticed
oh live doesn't supply with a pc no they
do not
my equipment is also all bought by
myself they do not
uh uh contrary to
uh what a lot of people think
yeah i had to
prepare all that by myself actually in
the beginning
since i didn't have a proper microphone
i did ask the company
if they have any spare megaphones that i
can use for at least the first month
until i get my salary
but they said no so i had uh that i
that's why i asked kelly
that's why i was borrowing cali's
microphone like her old one
yeah the phone the phone we get from the
company
um
but they did help me with getting a pc
like they helped with like
uh that that company like contacting the
company
and like sending it to me
okay we only got some items from this
room left oh we can throw it here too
sorry anything else the bed
oh god okay well this bag we have to
unfortunately get through these rooms oh
no
okay okay okay oh okay yeah that's a
good position
no we won't get we won't get silver
again
[Music]
silver no
no wait wait we've come so far
it's sad okay whatever i said i don't
care about the time that's okay but
but when you see it like that you want
it you want it
and then you're sad when you don't get
it i think i heard my uncle what's the
deal of sick days they're right
but you're not sick you just hurt we
don't have hurt days
yeah sorry guys it's it's the same as
the kfp
no because no one gets it sick anyway my
chickens are the healthiest chickens
always happy always
high healthy guys yeah good job
me i don't even know why i'm high-fiving
you guys i told you guys
to help me but here i am moving as the
only person what what about these people
who keep on talking to me in the game
why are they not helping me don't break
hey we got one
bonus objective we didn't break any
objects
give a bird a bath there was a burnt
and i could have bathed it
did you guys see birds thanks guys for
giving me the
the hand or the high five i'm not sure
yeah you shut up i'm not the i mean i'm
phoenix
i guess that is a bird maybe i should
have bathed myself
dan what the hell thank you but even if
i wanted to i can't buy anything
i do once it's available i want to buy
that super famous uh uh
graphic card good old has it i think an
ammo has it too
right they have that what which one is
it 317 or something like that
i want a free ninety four ninety i i i
have the free seventeen maybe
and they have the three ninety you know
how is it two
wow it's not worth it
well yeah right now it's not worth it
because
it's so expensive like or or you can't
get it all
at all you know has a free ah you know
how's it for 17.
at 3017 and i have like something else
but that's still
like good it runs
too hot on the memory oh i thought
everyone loves that
graphic card and and everyone was super
excited about it
so it's not actually that good
you have a five thousand seven hundred
five thousand seven hundred xt oh yeah
that sounds like what i have yeah yeah
yeah
it's amazing but it's so expensive oh
then
what is worth the actual price if it's
not if the
30 90 is not worth its actual price
which graphic card is like super awesome
and actually worth
its price is there anything else
[Music]
your pc is fine yeah i would think so
30 80. would have been fine if you could
buy it
ah oh
okay thank you thank you for the
blessings
may wait so inaudible 90 or the 30 80.
if they have the 30 90 have they been
having like
like problems with it heating up too
much
well let's show that yeah forever it's
probably going to go on for another year
right
ah omiyama and kuda ah
you know has pretty i'm gonna have
foreign
you guys know everything and
i i really wonder how the hell they got
those graphic cards it's so hard to get
them
like at least in my country it's
impossible
a friend recently got it like but he was
like super super super super super super
lucky
anyway more prestigious clients are
calling it uh
are we gonna move like out of the villa
we'll soon be the biggest moving company
in town
i think we already are cars on the cliff
well what a name
[Laughter]
spanish right and cliff is english boys
cliff also spanish for some reason
what a great name well then let's help
them move
heads casa de la polo
shut up let's clip in spanish
what's what's good in spanish can you
marry cali already i already did in my
dream and some
sims apps and since we're gonna marry at
some point
cliff is a name oh um oh i guess yeah it
could be a name
but that sounds wrong that just sounds
like they combined an english word
and a spanish word word and that's it
okay nice house
wow they got a billiard
uh pool table cool table
wait do you actually cool down and they
got an actual pool but the pool is
rather small but it has like a
nice positioning but look at that
annoying like
stairs with the fence there's like
barely any space that's going to be
tough
do i need to do a spanish study stream
maybe maybe maybe maybe he had an
architectural review
yeah it's an interesting looking house i
like how the room on the bottom left has
like a curve
you don't see that normally okay let's
go let's help them move
ah i guess yeah that is true remember
lift will be back not your arms
isn't it the other way around
hmm well i'm not sure actually
i heard a chicken again when is the car
um started though what does it say you
saved the manual you didn't give us a
safety mic
sounds like kfc
all right okay okay so okay three items
in that room
kitchen free items pool ball
four items there one item there one item
there
and one two items there oh three items
okay
okay you ready
[Music]
mobile
by the way today my roommate was also
helping me
uh to move that bed uh into my new
apartment like and move it into the car
first and then move it oh i broke the
vase oh [\h__\h] and then moved into the
apartment
and like there was a friend and my
roommate
and they did it like almost on their oh
oh [\h__\h] almost on their own there's
definitely a mission to not break those
fences but that's like impossible
and anyway so i was
i was so useless like i wanted to help
but like sometimes there wasn't even
real
little space you know to help okay
they were doing so well on their own and
i was so [\h__\h] weak i couldn't lift
the [\h__\h]
it was like only them doing stuff and
then i was like
holding the door open and stuff like
that and i was just saying hold on hold
on
and i was happy doing that but
i felt so useless so weak and so
helpless i mean i don't know
they weren't mad or anything they knew
my roommate
the only reason why she tagged along i
told her like
i don't need you to tag along it will be
fine but she was like i don't trust you
in noodle arms she literally said that
she watches my streams too much she says
she doesn't trust my noodle arms
well i don't trust them eva and that's
why she came along
after a long work day she was actually
working today
okay and she was like tired from that as
well
but she came along and helped me what
would i do without her and now she
cooked for me again i feel like recently
she's like
really like upping her um wife levels
[Music]
up
my
a sweet roommate roommate on life levels
for real oh by the way i've seen some
ridiculous rumors
some people have been like uh
speculating is that a word
is that the word whether or not i'm
dating my roommate
which is so stupid if i'm dating my
roommate why would i like
move over from japan live
here for like two months and then move
out again
no i am not dating my roommate
ah we're
we appreciate each other and we have fun
and
yeah she sometimes recently cooked for
me but
that's that is only that's not because
like
she wants to be my wife or anything
that's just
most of the time because she cooked too
much food
and then she's like oh you wanna you
want some of this i cook too much
yeah and i have cali anyway so
i don't know that was just like a few
people being like oh maybe maybe maybe
she's dating her roommate
which is so ridiculous you don't
actually believe that do you i hope they
don't that's that's just
reading oh [\h__\h] i fell down
damn it that would have been good we
would have saved a lot of time
[Music]
uh
okay we're probably only doing bronzer
again anything else okay that
what is that the thing on top wait it's
gonna break probably oh no that thing
okay
uh can i throw it no
okay i can't throw that one what is that
it's a night table
okay oh wait so far it's already like
the time is oh no okay
you know i should have followed this
earlier but i should just bring
everything
close to the door
and then move everything from here that
will save me a lot of
uh walking god damn it why did i not
think of that earlier
okay well now that we broke it
can we break yet is that is that broken
what i think that was a secret mission
probably
what just happened there
what did i do i didn't know i had that
kind of power
i unleashed my true power
okay let's bring that down oh i can go
down here too okay
[\h__\h]
there probably wasn't and she would like
park the car or so
i'm not sure you get up here nah
what's up this one
radio i don't even have a radio who has
a radio these days
no one really i thought that was some
kind of secret again
i have a radio okay okay that's cool
okay radio
having a radio is cool but i feel like
nowadays
barely anyone buys a radio anymore
same with like tv like people might have
a tv but only really use it for like
like you know netflix and stuff at least
that's the case with us
[Applause]
i have two items left okay one is over
here
and one is at the pool oh my god
okay okay we can do it we can do it we
can do it we can do it we can do it we
can do it
[Music]
no
hello cat sorry for waking sorry for
screaming sorry sir sorry
she came she crawled out of my bed
whilst uh
while stretching so she was definitely
sleeping i'm so sorry
nicole nicole
okay okay i pet her belly a little bit
uh i think she forgave me
oh wait wait we cleared the level like
anyway they're just like missing some
items now
well it's just a freaking pool ball who
cares about that stupid poo ball
okay let's do that one again daddy now
see
we can't we can't accept that they'll
they'll spread like
they'll give us a really bad yelp review
okay let's get silva come on
what was that with the car anyway
okay let's
let's get there these heavy things that
i can't
uh throw okay move that here
[\h__\h] those chairs it's a hot dog yummy
i wonder if there's like any secret
items
uh don't fall in the pool okay any
secret items that
i shall uh give you like extra time
ah [\h__\h] fell down but okay we got one
item
okay uh
okay i just had a green screen for a
moment did you guys see that
what does that mean
that was so [\h__\h] weird for like a
second
what is that why
yeah that makes sense if i get a green
screen
for a moment what does the green screen
mean
what does that even mean like in terms
of technical
gaming [\h__\h] the tv brook
ram dying
we just talked about the fact that i
bought this gaming pc
oh sometimes i really wonder what
maybe something broke on on the
transportation
but hmm wait we're doing so good in time
right now
this is definitely the right technique
because otherwise we would be walking
much much much more
that was close that was really close
i wasn't really aiming thank god
my output and my my me being low fps
has something to do with my internet
connection
not the pc unfortunately but like i had
some
recently i had some moments where i was
60 fps so that one made me really happy
but it's prime time now so that's
probably why i'm not 60 fps
i have it well we could
i mean gold is probably impossible but
we're doing really well we should be
able to get silver
yes okay let's bring those items in
uh in first oh
can i jump up there okay nice
tv is already broken so whatever
okay nice
throw that um for that
can i prank no
[\h__\h]
did it respawn there oh yeah okay
ah sit
[Music]
okay
come on come on come on you can do it
yeah
[Music]
who needs stairs when you can jump off a
cliff
oh no oh wow
i'm really doing way better when it
comes to checking oh well
we might still look at silva 30 seconds
left come on come on
come on come on come on come on okay
jump
jump jump
[Music]
okay guys that was not me that was the
character in the game what the hell
why would you do that people are gonna
clip that and be like oh there was kiana
she played
well we already have breath so no stress
now but
okay was difficult
i hear my cat meowing in the distance
we got one item left the box
i probably could have jumped through
that window oh well
yo bye-bye oh my god
[Music]
we did it guys high five yeah
i can't think of anything else i'd
rather be doing that moving review ah
that's sweet very sweet
what about swinging with the dolphins on
on the secret beach under the stars yeah
that sounds much better or getting the
trust of an unruly horse and let
and it lets you ride in forever
or eating an entire plate of spaghetti
well maybe i can think of something else
i'd rather be doing yeah
me too it's a
actually moving i don't really like
moving i've been moving so much
in my in the past couple of years
so often but this time
oh there is a goose that's what i was
hearing
no stairs for you ah if you don't use
the stairs at all ah
i use them in the beginning break the
windows
oh um yeah what i was saying is that the
move tomorrow
will hopefully be the last one in a long
time
i plan to just stay there for
a lot of years until i get like
until i find like a uh like an apartment
that i actually want to buy um
at some point but i don't feel ready for
it yet so i'm just like renting now
but i'm really excited
i am quite excited to move
into this new apartment like because i
am i like the new apartment but
but move oh [\h__\h] i did i pressed no no
no no no no no no no
no i'm happy with what i did no no that
was that accident okay uh
what was i saying uh what was i saying
it's buffering the stream is buffering
i wonder why i was saying um forgot
i forgot what was that thing about
moving yeah but
what exactly was i saying ah
i forgot chicken brain
oh yeah i'm happy with that oh yeah
thank you happy with the apartment
that's why i'm excited but like actually
moving again
is so annoying especially since like i
just came back
here and moved from japan to a different
continent
just like two months ago yeah
yeah and now i'm moving again but
yeah it's because because partially
because like
you know the internet connection and
just like
it's being more um
easy for me to work if i have like my
own place
and but yeah i'll miss my roommate of
course
she was so sweet and so understanding
but i don't wanna you know i also don't
wanna bother her too much because like
like even though she's she she's been
fine with the noise
i still think that it will be better on
the long term definitely
because yesterday and the day before
like she
she slept early and i was still
streaming and yeah i don't i don't wanna
what the [\h__\h] is those cars down there
i don't wanna bother her too long so
that's why i'm moving yeah and i hope i
can settle
into that place i really hope so too
yeah
rmt rmt rmt
shall we do one more level oh
oh my god that's so cute that's so good
coloring
koi tamagoyo excellent the coals keep
coming a new client needs help moving a
few things things are my favorite
whoa summer chalet
let's do that one and then it's the end
of the stream
let's do one more house
snowman die oh my god now i feel sorry
i destroyed the snowman
[Music]
oh no that's huge we're probably gonna
fail again the first time
16 items where are the stairs
[Music]
i'm seeing the stairs i see a hoop
though
we'll probably get extra points if we
throw something into that hoop
are the stairs covered by the snow
all right let's go
last blue last move get my training
going for tomorrow
ah no timer no jumbie this is one fancy
vacation home
every day is the occasion when you get
to haul heavy objects
well he really likes moving well he
likes his job a lot
good for him
okay let's look what we got uh one bed
and then four items there two items
there uh five items there one of them
there
one here right here okay no fridge
couch table okay okay okay okay
and the stairs are there oh i wonder if
i can just go down the snow
move us
okay i got ya is it like slippery
okay there we go maybe break it and we
can like slide things down there
okay
i forgot the controls for a moment go
down nice is that little yup
that ball too okay now let's bring
the things outside first well i guess we
can slide that one down already
does that work with the couch
all right together hey
the camera we can do it just
work hard together teamwork
i'm getting better at this now i feel
really prepared for tomorrow oh [\h__\h]
oh nice back in the morning
this way is a bit faster somehow
how did i do that i guess i just kind of
throw it
ah through here as well
okay now the tv
the tv right i don't know the thing
about oh thank god because the tv just
broke
okay uh the chair
no problem i'll leave it here for
now now uh
what's next maybe that thing
wow okay we lost the golf clubs but you
only need to you only need the outside
of it right
and this box no problem nice bathroom
you got
it
don't jump out we're not here for
snowboarding or skiing
unfortunately we're here to move i don't
mind
we should rent this occasionally i mean
the people are not need they don't need
it anymore right
maybe we should rent it guys have a kfb
vacation home
of you guys feel probably feel like you
guys need a vacation right
if you click on the vacation right now
where would you go
to the beach to the mountains to a city
what city
my bed finland japan oh yeah a lot of
people
feel like i asked that before and
everyone a lot of people said japan
japan japan
hawaii okinawa okay
everyone says japan why did i even ask a
question this this room is filled with
weeps
why did i even bother asking the
question
okay snowboard uh
okay oh god i think they want me to
slide the bed down there
because i don't know why that would be a
little bit of it
otherwise that would be way
[Music]
wait the rooms would be way too narrow i
think
okay okay bed bed bed bed bed
let's try to get it
down the the right path on uh with the
snow
oh my stupid [\h__\h] table
the green reaper is super chatting oh my
god
no no no okay door thank you
get that throw here okay now wait can i
oh yeah that's the door here okay
come on turn around
[Music]
i want silva today well it's probably
not happening
it's probably not happening okay but
we're gonna get bronze we're not gonna
fail this mission
come on come on yes
i think that was the last object in
there anyway is there a cat
something looks like a cat there
okay get in here
snowboard champ
what's that out of the the ball okay
no problem fits in here
you're sure you're strong
i'll throw some things maybe
okay
uh she stops running when she froze
things
[Music]
grab it grab it
[Applause]
oh my god okay stupid chair we're almost
done
with that okay we're definitely getting
bronze we're done
[Applause]
hurry up hurry up this is the last item
let's make it fit
uh i have it come from that side
and up and up and up and there we go
hello cat what do you think about my
move
oh she think she thinks i did a great
job i just remember today's my birthday
no
no no no no your birthday is july 6th
july 6th
remember it chiara you're moving boxes
on your birthday that's the greatest
gift of all
[Music]
but okay in game kiara birthday
congratulations
we have friends on first try nice no
stair run
no go snowboarding wait we we ran up the
stairs once i shouldn't have done that i
knew it
because nobody avoid the snow oh i said
you could probably also do you can
probably not do all of them at once but
yeah
happy birthday fake kiana
yay i thought you never make it in time
i am a professional mover now okay
i i got a legit license and all as we
have seen
you underestimate me
all right guys we can have like maybe uh
10 more minutes of talking time but
there will be no super chat reading
today because i need to go back to
um black friction thank you
i need to go back to packing but we can
go over to the talking screen and talk
for like 10 minutes
um and that's it
yeah i don't really have time for it but
i've been reading
super chats all week this week even
though i have been busy
i was saying i did a pretty good job at
that
keeping up with the super chats new new
show on netflix keeping up with the
super chats
yes there we go
i'll keep the music running i actually
really like it
thank you guys for watching i hope that
was fun
it was a really funny stream yesterday i
was thinking about what could i play
what could i play what could i play
at first i was thinking about playing uh
mario kart or sliver or a mangas
but then i was like nah i've been
playing those games a lot
i want something else so i went through
the game permission list
and yeah figured that
moving out would be a great choice
if not now then when else would i be
playing that game
[Music]
oh
i wish i had time maybe every once in a
while i'll try
uh if it really helps it helps the
algorithm
i want to try that face
my faking face
[Music]
youtube comment system isn't great well
i mean
what do you mean from from your side
over my side like as a person who
replies or as the person who actually
comments
you're only one verb it's okay if you
don't
you're saying that it's a lot of work
yeah it really is like managing all
these social media accounts really hard
really tough
with so many comments every day so many
replies on twitter recently i
also haven't been able to like
uh like everything in the art tag
that as well has been kind of tough
yeah oh
but i'm trying my best to keep up i mean
i
i i will i'll be back phenomenal please
forgive me if i haven't
liked something that you guys put into
the art tag
sorry sorry
um how did i come to lania today's
stream is a bit
uh short because i'm moving tomorrow and
i
didn't finish packing you know what this
is
i rarely ever use this screen for
anything besides super chat reading
well here we go since that time
so um was there anything else i wanted
to talk about we already talked about
the new outfits
and we talked about me releasing a song
probably on tuesday
uh anything else
did that miss something
welcome to the membership welcome
take a rest after this do your best i
cannot i cannot rest
i will rest on saturday after the move
is over
and on sunday because sunday i'm just
like chilling
and vibing but uh
yeah today i still have to pack until i
go to sleep and then tomorrow
i have to get up quite early to pick up
the the car that we rented
for moving thank you for the red super
chat by the way
thank you guys for the super chat thank
you soon
yeah i have opinions on the other girls
i actually talked a little bit about it
about the um other girls outfits already
did you missed it i said my favorites
are
ame and enos outfits
i should do that after the move ah
monday i'm planning to do
yakuza actually um we also
got permission to play pokemon snap and
i saw
some gameplay of it actually looks quite
fun
um surprisingly even though like
at first i i wasn't i wasn't very like
impressed with the
like happy with the idea but it's the
first and the
single only pokemon game that we
currently have permission
to play like freely without like a
sponsorship and all that
so if i want to like maybe
maybe even with a player then i should
play it and now i guess
um yeah i would prefer like playing like
a like a proper pokemon game i want to
fight i want to battle but pokemon snap
looks kind of cute from what i've seen
i've seen like uh a let's play of
someone
playing like the beginning of it a
little bit and it looks fun
i don't know do you guys want me to play
it on my channel like maybe like
once or twice i know
yeah really
really you guys think that is fun to
watch
you guys will watch
[Music]
yes yes very chill game it's a very
pretty game like i i looked at
what the old pokemon snap looked like
and
wow yeah that game really deserved
a remake um
yeah that was a nintendo 64 the old game
i never played it back then but i know
that like like a lot of people
hyped it up a lot like pokemon fans
really loved pokemon snap
back in the day even though it's
basically just a game where you take
photos of pokemon but for some reason
it's like so much fun anyway
which i think is really fascinating um
that they make like like a game where
you take photos of pokemon which at
first doesn't sound so exciting but once
you play it you like
really really enjoy it and like get
addicted
and really start like appreciating it um
you had fun taking photos and writing so
it's not that crazy
mmm yeah i guess one girl try it out
i'll check out i'll check it out but
like
the thing is we have the yakuza going
going on now and then
yeah i don't know oh yeah yeah i ordered
i ordered
the collector's edition of tail of a
rice
and because you guys tweeted at me that
now that
uh they announced that even for europe
for a limited time only and only
a few limited um
items of the collector's edition are
available which was originally only
available like in
america and i couldn't get that
but i really wanted to collect it
actually yeah i think it was also an
issue of it being sold out
and anyway but yeah now they i'm not no
no it was because
europe had a different kind of
collector's edition and i wanted the one
from america they have like
way fancier one yeah
so my prayers have been heard
so i i ordered it from uh uk
amazon and it's gonna come in sometime
in september
yeah we have this hudu which i guess if
i play the game
i might end up liking that mascot but
now
not obviously the game is not out so i
don't have any connection to
to that mascot i don't know what it's
like so i don't really care about that
special edition
with hoodle all over it i would i prefer
having the normal collector's edition
because i don't really know what what
hoodle is all about
you know i mean owls are cute and all
but like when you
didn't play the game yet then it's like
oh yeah okay but who the [\h__\h] is this
like afterwards i might be like i wish i
would have gotten the hoodle edition
afterwards but now i'm like
wait is it is it hutu or houdi i don't
know what the actual name is someone
wrote it in the chat i don't really know
but yeah now i got them the collector's
edition
for what was it hundred ninety pounds
yeah it would be like getting a feed
this november riser yeah but that's
that's again something i would have not
gotten
before actually playing the game because
it's like who the [\h__\h] is fame
oh i'm excited for that to come it looks
really fancy that's the first time i
ever buy like a collector's edition of a
game
do you guys usually buy like fancy
versions
like special versions of the game what
do you just go for they're like the
basic one
are you are you guys basic bees
see i held myself back from like
swearing at you guys there for once for
once
the cheaper one the cheapest option
yeah i would often just go for the
digital one because like i don't want to
wait for shipping
i just buy this the digital one also
especially now with the pc i have now
doesn't it doesn't you can't even put a
cd into it
and also um i bought the piece uh
playstation 4 version because i was like
um the pc version doesn't really have a
collector's edition
if i understand it correctly and uh i
was thinking
it will probably run better on the
playstation anyway
right even though my pc is good but
we've seen issues with
near as well so i don't i don't know
maybe they maybe they
did a great job or they're doing a great
job on the pc edition who knows but i
feel like
it will be safer to play the playstation
version which is why
this time i decided to get the
playstation version but i'll have to set
up the whole
like streaming uh situation but
anyway it won't come until like
september middle of september
yeah are loading times a longer
on playstation really yeah i think like
tails off generally doesn't have much
loading time
though well like like the games i played
until now
i also played like all of them on
console
and they usually don't really have much
loading time
especially with the most recent tales of
games like you
you run around a lot on like
big fields like it's kind of like open
world
i don't know do you call that open world
maybe not
maybe i got it wrong but like it's like
a big field and you
you run around and it doesn't really
have much lonely time
september so hot the way you speak oh my
god are you guys
again with the r
i feel like i talk normally open world
it's not it's not over the world god
that means okay
i don't know
what do you call that then i guess i
don't know
thank you guys for the super chats thank
you
it's so cute you are cute
oh no did i miss the stream yeah but i'm
already ending so we can watch the
archive i'm ending now actually right
now
just a short stream two hours only today
um yeah and on the weekend on sunday i'm
probably gonna upload some some small
video uh as an addition to my absolute
videos
yes yeah i have to finish packing now
and i have to
uh pack the pc as well like
i'm probably not really going to pack it
but yeah okay
okay shortest cast remember there have
been shorter ones there haven't
actually i will i will beat that record
with a one hour stream for my outfit
reveal
i think i think they are all gonna be
just like one hour
you know the classic outfit reveal time
one hour reveal it around the end of the
stream
i hope you will all come to check out my
new outfit
life check it out live i want you all to
come live
don't watch the archive come live please
please
it will be so exciting and i as i said
i have some secret weapons
yeah so look forward to it
and and and probably new song cover
and also on tuesday
[Music]
night
the way did you just hear my my stomach
growling while i was speaking japanese
you might have heard it i hope you
didn't hear it
i'm gonna go eat something and then pack
okay you didn't hear it good
thank you guys for the super chats thank
you
thank you i'll be reading them sometime
next week
whenever there's time okay
thank you guys for watching and in
german we say
[Music]
next stream will be in my new apartment
okay
thank you guys for watching this short
stream i hope you enjoyed it see you
next week
[Music]
you