maybe I did them a favor maybe them
being a slug is their bad Incarnation
after having a a Bad Karma life wow I
wonder
whatcar they're reincarnating as a human
again now to live an interesting life I
remember when I was a like if only I
could go back would you still love me if
I was a worm for real for real I think I
would like not love someone if they were
a slug because they can't talk anymore I
think what I would do is they would be
my specimen and I would take multiple
pictures of them and just posted on
social media you would use them for
cloud is it really cloud though but then
it makes me wonder am I technically
taking like nude photography of them
they like it
proba if they didn't like being naked
they would become a snail and put a
house on their body