[Music]
feel it rush through me
we
feel it
R feel it through me
[Music]
oh honey
in there you know to kind of be like yo
serious [\h__\h] being in Japan at that time
right like people weren't messing around
you know that's the vibe that I got wait
sorry I think I need to do a quick intro
cuz I just switched to the gaming uh
screen go for it
K you guys may have already been seeing
me on on K's stream I was just you know
chilling and uh preparing the stream
excuse
me but we are so back aren't we Callie
oh yeah that we're back big time and
today I got shaders oh my God it looks
so pretty nice wow you're glowing Callie
glowing and shiny am I do I look radiant
right now amazingly even though you
don't look at me so glad hey yeah so if
you want I can go right away uh give you
a
tour an update let me drop this away and
let me drop this like it's hot Drop it
like it's hot boys and then we'll go
ahead and take a look at what you guys
did cuz I have no clue what anyone did
yeah I know it all I know
I am all right show me what you guys got
down to business with cuz I so yesterday
I started alone for 30 minutes and that
created some chaos I unfortunately uh
had to explode some things because
creepers were everywhere in the
beginning um and that resulted in some
issues here you may have noticed the
merchants and so on are gone yeah
they're all super dead yeah they were
eaten by zombies and this is a big
problem because we need Merchants
villagers again villagers so but the
thing is like they spawned only in
specific phases so our job yesterday was
we were in Phase seven and there were 10
so we were mining for hours those last
three phases took a while um so that we
can Circle back but turns out it doesn't
Circle back it just like after 10 phases
it gives you all phases at once so the
cool of blocks and things you can get
from mining now is way bigger than in a
single phase you know what I mean cuz
it's all phas is combined yeah yeah so
the chances of us getting what we really
want is lower now but at the same time
we can get
everything at once yeah um that's
chaotic as hell yeah and then uh we
noticed
um
some uh things uh that could be improved
here this is still the mining area this
this block here uh in between the
chocolate blocks is the one you mine uh
I'm going to buil like something where
uh it goes immediately into a chest here
through the water oh so that our okay
what was the actual purpose I think
because our inventories were always full
I don't know I don't know anymore but
yeah now it's looking really chocolatey
and nice and then you can like click on
the chest here on the side and like
there's more to sort for you
there's so much to sort yeah there's a
lot in there yeah cool I don't even know
how do people even get the mechanism
that's crazy oh she worked on a while on
it yeah and then besides this
contraption we have another new one I
saw you already were standing here but
didn't notice what it was behind you
yeah yeah what is this this is a
cobblestone generator that uh go created
surprisingly she made
it wow basically I think maybe you know
that stone in between the lava and the
water you mine that and you get endless
Cobblestone try it yeah okay I think I
can actually see how it works cuz of the
lava and water yeah it takes a second
but I feel like it gets faster yeah yeah
cool yeah why is it endless cob Stone
yeah so for like building if we need to
build paths or whatever this is maybe a
good option and then there's some extra
Stacks in this chest here cool
are we able to replace the floor do you
think or is there floor we shouldn't
replace M oh generally it's always good
to for example replace these wooden
floors here Stone floors so that they
don't
burn yeah um the grass I would keep the
grassy blocks I would keep because we
need some grassy blocks anyway to grow
the trees grow things right the trees
also have uh experienced some [\h__\h]
yesterday like oh no a lot of big holes
yeah a lot of big holes here and then
the trees were gone and then we had to
replace it all yeah this is not a normal
freaking tree what happened here oh
that's like a big like what do you call
it again dark oak dark oak they grow
really thick yeah but when you when you
plant them if you happen to mine them
and you want to plant them again um like
from the leaves they will drop the
little thingies right um but you have to
plant this one in like like a four um
space thingy like 1 2 3 four um next to
each other uh you know what I mean uh
what's it called 4x4 yeah a 4x4 or
actually 2 by two but I for me it's like
four because yeah 2 by two oh I get you
yeah yeah yeah yeah I see why don't we
just plant a bunch of those I feel like
that's most efficient well we don't even
have that much space you see it's
already pretty cramped if we can get
this uh area extended extend it yeah
that would be fine but we don't have
that many dirt blocks either true I wish
we could generate dirt blocks
yeah well grass grown a few yeah that's
all all maybe I can go find some dirt
blocks around place I don't even think
this takes priority um I think yeah uh
the Sorting for now takes priority also
you like fishing right I do I'm a big
fish we do have fishing rods now or or
the capability of making them and uh
Amma made a fishing pond next to the
watermelon space so if you feel like
fishing yeah cuz like we've been running
out of food the whole time too is what
we've noticed oh yeah PR rough fish is
pretty good at the moment yeah that
would be a good idea honestly what else
the green horses by the way are zombie
horses that are only in creative mode um
they somehow spawned as well you will
never see them in the normal legit
playthrough of Minecraft oh really yeah
that's why they agree and they're
they're non hostile yeah they're fine
they dropped zombie meat when you killed
them they're so fancy that's pretty neat
M wow L yesterday am was struck by
lightning that was really funny cool
yeah it's pretty funny and we got some
new pandas some Ponda babies and yeah I
don't know they're just chilling
here what do they do for the cause how
do they earn their keep honestly it's
just like in real life it's just they're
cute and that's how they earn their
right to live on God really yeah they're
not like just being lifting any of the
heavy weight for us really absolutely
nothing can be gained from their
existence here
then I think we should murder them no no
no no no they're taking up space here
are we G have cows there that would be
really sad all right I'm going to use I
won't touch them arrows for now you guys
better your days are numbered all right
your days are freaking
numbered I don't think they like me they
hear the mean things I'm saying about
them it's fine that's not a threat
that's a promise panda bears that's a
promise let's see what do we got here
that I can
sort um I'll just grab everything and
just start sorting it
out damn it sand bone blocks I wonder
where bone blocks would go
into and Bone blocks you
can I've been making a lot of those into
bone meal but I think we have enough
bone meal for now so oh yeah should be
fine damn it Quartz in here oh you know
what I want to make K is I want to make
a trash can yo um me I killed one
Phantom do you still have the Phantom
noises over on your
side I think they're gone now but I'm
not totally sure okay oh now the cats
will finally shut up let's go I hear no
more
hissing yeah those cats were pissed to
tell you
what let's
go okay any other iron or should we mine
for some more iron oh just kidding iron
okay great yeah yeah generally iron so I
think you read on the board diamond
armor diamond tools and all that but
before that we don't even have a full
set of iron armor that would probably be
our priority before making diamond stuff
okay that sounds good are you welcome
for killing the Phantom everybody you're
welcome yesterday they were also like
constantly hissing and
screaming it was crazy yeah the cats not
very happy kitty cats uhuh not
happy definitely not feeling it hey why
can't I make a cauldron I wonder a c a
cauldron yeah cuz that's uh you put the
lava in it and that's how you make a
trash can oh okay okay okay but M what
do you want to throw away does that not
exist in this one oh it exists uh stuff
that's just just gets in the way in the
inventory don't throw away too much
though we might need like a lot of
things yeah
of course not is this there are some
things that just like get in the
way your boy loves trash cans I don't
know I don't know how to defend myself
from that I know it's wasteful it's
wasteful myy how could you how could you
but hear me out hear me out some things
are just yucky to look at hear meow
panda bears we could we could throw the
panda bears in the fire if you guys want
meow
meow hear me out M you could throw the
panda bears in there yeah yeah oh yeah I
mean they just getting the way for it I
think I know I just I feel like you know
we're becoming hoarders Kiara we can't
we can't let that happen you know we
become hoarding the pandas attractive
it's good the pandas the pandas serve as
trash can for the
bamboo yeah yeah I mean I guess so but
although the bamboo isn't entirely
useless to us cuz we can make sticks
with
them okay oh yeah that's a good point
maybe we should not get rid of let's see
that has a purpose wa I see the purpose
there let's go I can make us some beds
not through wool but through spider silk
I'm making beds now our first beds just
need some planks yeah finally I didn't
even know until last night's Super Chat
that we can make beds out of spider silk
I think someone mentioned it once I
don't know if it was G or Ena but we
were all kind of preoccupied and I
wasn't really
sure you know not
certain uh let's see well I like the
idea of Let's Make A let's make armor
and whatnot so mhm I'd like to mine for
stuff but we have to be mindful of uh I
might I might mine a little bit here and
there yeah y we got bed we can sleep for
the night now oh yeah I'm I'm going to
go put them into that house oh my
God what's he doing here oh he's
chilling oh he's so glowy
cute he's just ch he help
here he here as long as we don't look at
him don't look at him
okay Goods shut
up the they're looking at him and he's
not attacking them double standard much
the thing is on my side they are only
heads they have no
bodies oh might have something to do
with the shaders
yeah uhoh the shaders did not account
for
parrots cute this is this stuff for
stuff we find in the forest like uh
saplings flowers Etc uh yeah that chest
on the on the pumpkin that's basically
the forest chest for now if we want to
plant more trees and stuff okay I see
some not food the floor um under ground
has been built yesterday too so nice
like for example if you accidentally
like because we had accidents where
right I think you were there actually
when somebody mines the ground that
you're standing on to replace the floor
and then the person who stands there
innocently falls down into the void that
is a situation yeah that can be avoided
stuff like that or when occasionally
yeah that may be a thing yeah or when a
gas shoots their fire onto the wooden
floor and it all burns down now we have
a floor below so it will catch us and we
will not fall die fall and die excellent
avoid the void avoid the void hey don't
have to tell me twice sounds
good I I guess I could have been told
once but that's okay oh and we have uh
uh a DJ mixing P thingy now ooh so we
can play music do you hear it oh did you
turn down okay It's haunting beautiful
right now we can make use of the CDs
that we have yeah that's right if I
remember correctly also um golden armor
is not very good is it yeah golden armor
we might need just like one piece each
if we go into the the one piece is real
if we go into the
never sounds good I'll cook some but
there's not really a reason to cook too
much gold is there aside from you know
that one set I mean
yeah if you want to cook I don't want to
waste too much
coal it's
fine yeah oh you're doing it directly oh
I didn't even fig that yeah maybe an
iron pickaxe would be good yes yes yes
yes I'll make another one I shall use
some iron for an iron pickaxe Kelly
where do you want me to put the last two
pieces of wool that I have in my hand
and that's a good question I haven't
really decided where wool was supposed
to go but since we're not using much of
this PLS chest anymore where was it um
the bottom one here it's kind of empty
so I'm thinking can repurpose that into
something else see I think we can make
another yeah the the there's free I'll
make one
more yeah don't you mean
Iron I run what are you talking about I
run say I earn money and
I earn the
money no you now you're see I see what
you're trying to do yaha what am I doing
I know your game you're trying to get
out of saying the word iron correctly
aren't you you little rascal
[Music]
iron even if I figure it out like now I
think I was still default to naturally
saying iron because that's just what I'm
used
to she's too conditioned to it now we've
lost her
no it is what it
is see another oce there will be five
beds here and we can
cuddle all of myth cuddle session
sleepover party just like Bakin a day
yay uh yeah this whole storage room is
kind of not I mean I liked the idea in
the beginning but now that all the items
and we're mixing they're all mixed up
now right so like yeah jungle and desert
and ocean so it becomes a lot more
difficult it's fine though it's fine
make it work maybe I shouldn't put it
here I'll put this into the Sorting
chest sorting chest chest very very
serious about the Sorting in this
G all right let's
see be can you cook be I know this bow
is special and but this needs to be in
the weapons chest
[Music]
let's see what else we got get in
there Beachwood soup oh man so many food
items turn into soup but I feel like
soup is so unpopular in Minecraft cuz of
the bowls that don't stack until you
until they're empty oh that's right it
just takes up so much space sucks
yeah I'd never want to do that or use
that that's horrific you kidding me well
we don't have much choice at the moment
besides eating
soup
oh I guess so do be like that okay I
mean I love soup
IRL IRL is nice
sick yum yum how you doing Callie by the
way well I'm alive you know living day
to day just still trying to heal but you
know we'll get there can't we
eventually yeah you're taking your meds
get there eventually of course of course
I am take your meds Kelly like legit
take them take them I'm taking them only
as the doctor has recommended okay only
recommended little of course of course
not good y when taking the meds physical
thing oh for
sure I no
the doctor recommends I shall destroy
because you're going to eat animals
aren't you uhoh who needs to be
killed a little little what was it a
wolf or a fox a wolf I think the dying
animal noises do be popping off these
[Music]
days what's that down there the horses
that spawn here will not like suffer
anymore what down where Ah that's where
I went down to build the underground the
floor for safety I see that there's like
a portal or something like that being
made oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah oh yeah
that's because we already went to Phase
10 and when you're done with all the
phases once it spawns the um the portal
to the end automatically right under
this one block oh should I put the sand
back was it supposed to be a SL sand
slabs here and here
uh this it doesn't have to be S I think
no no okay I just want to make sure that
I'm not messing it up no no no but yeah
we we're in Fury already we can go to
the end as soon as we have more ender
pearls thingies but yeah we're just
severely not
ready see where's the block is it the
sand or which one is it oh the chest
oh M the block to mine you mean
that chest yeah please please
sort oh boy please get to sorting
immediately oh my god this is my future
this is my
soul this is my soul kill the bunny now
there's a bunny the bunny can stay what
did he do to you what did he do to you I
think the bunny's oh I think it already
escaped
huh there it is we're going to need a
bigger terra cotta
chest cute let's
see oh no oh no it's gonna it's gonna
don't jump bunny I know that's your
thing but don't jump just this once
s
where concrete powder that probably goes
here okay wood if you do happen to mine
uh at the one block later um mhm just so
you know the blocks are now like they're
going into the chest first rather than
going to you so you got to also check if
the chest is
full I
see otherwise they won't go inside the
chest yeah cuz now it's full for example
oh I see I
see let's see all right so looks like
we're going to need a bigger terracotta
chest what's this an ocean chest or I
know what I can do I'll need one more
ocean chest okie dokie wooden
see oh this can go in here and that oh
sh look nice they
Doo even like in normal version
Minecraft I haven't been using shaders
recently cuz I was too lazy to update my
OptiFine ah stupid op that'll do it but
I did it now just for
this nice so that I can take a nice
screenshot and put it on my
thumbnail that's the main reason
oh yeah cie I Callie remember a while
ago I asked
you not not that long ago I asked you
what your favorite cuz you told me you
like Bak I was like what the [\h__\h] who's
your favorite P character and you said n
and then like one or two weeks later I
see your collaboration and I was like
well well well this lady no wonder you
like
nadle yeah yeah now that that was a
coinky dink that was a
coincidence W how was it like talking to
her so cool I was very nervous so I
didn't really say much but I was like
excited to work with you and I got to
you know watch her record some of the
song and then I recorded this song it
was cool she a legend always remember
she is a legend so I was very doy doie
um my favorite role of hers is actually
in an anime called psychopath oh um
she's uh she's the main character of
that so that was like where I first
encountered her and so I was just very
ducky ducky doie doie what does she
think of
YouTubers I know she seemed pretty like
naughty NY about it like you know cool
and stuff like that I mean she did the
um the commercials uh for for what was
it the the Expo right like they had a
couple like you know Tik Tok SL YouTube
shorts commercials that were like kind
of animated there was aama the mod
cenal yeah she anim not animated though
she she narrated those oh like I think
that she had kind of you know
encountered us before is so she kind of
knew about it but tell me about working
with her tell me
more W it was really cool I gave her you
know my CD and she gave me her CD that
was cool I was like wow you're going to
give this to me yeah damn it's very doy
doie it's such a like unexpected
collaboration honestly to me I was like
what as well but I mean um you know the
the producer joint Beauty has done some
tracks for my new album and I guess you
know was releasing his own album and was
like oh I want I want two singers on
this one song I wonder who would be
interesting to put together um and and
for some reason he thought of the two of
us we That's So Random somehow I know I
thought so too but I was kind of like
okay
cool did you talk did you tell her that
you watched bakon Kar I did of course
but I didn't I didn't Fang girl too too
much I I would have man oh I would love
to tell her that I love I'm currently
re-watching like all the seasons because
the new season is finally coming oh yeah
I need to rewatch it I completely it's
been so many years it has been so many
same like I forgot so many things about
it too yeah I surprised about how how
yeah how how loot the loot moments are
but I mean they're also humorous and you
know mhm yeah the first time that I ever
watched bakim manari I like I think I
dropped it after the first two episodes
because it was a time that is a big be
yeah it's it was a it was there was a
time in my life where I was just very
like adverse to fan service and whatnot
but then I grew up a little bit and I
was like eh I don't care and it really
for me it's the opposite I was okay with
it back then and now I'm like I I can't
I cringed it kind of that's pretty funny
but for bakani like it's it has the the
bonus of being like my favorite since
forever and you know nostalgic Vibes and
the characters are just so intricate and
the way they all get together like you
get to know them first one by one and
then it all becomes one Tangled story
like a spider web and that's just like
the super cool thing about uh B bakar
for me you know it all comes together
it's epic I really like stories that
have like a big ensemble cast that you
get to know over time mhm like I don't
think I've ever felt
so into deep deep into a story like so
what's the word
um when you're when your really into
something and rapturing
okay okay and rapturing let's go with
that English student I'm sorry I can't
help myself invested invested and
immersed is what I meant sorry what am I
talking
about whoops I think yeah mon got Daddy
series is like just so so so un
rapturing and I when I was watching it
with my viewers and some of them saw
have been seeing it for the first time
now they were also like hm okay
interesting but like you got to give it
some time until like all the all the all
the cobwebs all the spider sils they get
together and then you're like w whoo
whoo wo yeah but they've certainly been
enjoying the spicy uh
moments I can see all the AOS in your
chat right now
AO kind of makes it more fun though I
think yeah it makes it more fun do that
please shut up I'm talking with my
friend right now um what about besides
nle who else did you
like
III oh oh you're actually bringing up a
guy rather than one of the million girls
I know I know it hurts everyone to hear
that but I think ADI is such a g if I
could say that what a gangster what a
cool guy I've been like honestly the
more like I watch it now the more I
dislike him why he's such a
do I know that's why I like
him I I love his um hold on a sorry I
really need to make sure I say the right
freaking one um yeah yeah I also like
coton coton yeah she's so fun yeah she's
so
motivated
mhm oh
yeah haki am I right yeah
don't tell me that's why you like
her there's more to it
right OB of course but when I think of
her I mean I can't help that that's is
more than just scene okay I'm sorry but
that's the first thing my mind flashes
too I can't help dental hygiene is
important I'm sorry man she's more than
just Dad she's a really great sister for
justice you know fire sisters she fights
for justice now kiaha I did not wasn't I
did not say that she was not I'm just
saying that that was that's sticks out
my
mind grow
okay let's see I really want to mine for
some diamonds we need to this is
actually really ridiculous and mine for
diamonds that's just mining at that
block over there but don't worry about
mining right now yeah cuz now like
there's how many blocks is it that you
could get out of that it's the 10 phases
combined it's like everything so the
chance to get diamonds is pretty low
now that is true I guess the best thing
I can do is just try to organize as much
as I can so we can keep mining yeah um
but I think do we have some dirt
somewhere because I'm going to extend
the block of dirt wait I have there's 20
blocks of dirt in the chest um which one
over there the the one block chest okay
okay okay okay okay yeah go grab it um
we need a bigger field
I love all these terracotta blocks I
just can't think for the life of me what
we use them for oh yeah when we get a
merchant um we can trade our emeralds
for diamonds and stuff I guess diamond
armor I want to hold on to emeralds too
I'm guessing yes yes yes yes yes do you
have any bgm playing y oh I need to put
the this thing back on M I feel like no
bgm is like kind of a trend or whatever
so I was like I'm not going to put on
any bgm for collabs like this I don't
mind it being quiet cuz we're talking
anyway and there's MC stuff going on so
yeah exactly there's Minecraft things
happening it's fine
exactly let me get rid of this or should
I just make it somewhere else I don't
know because this is small space
classical
sound that's actually why don't I just
build straight on this tag for fun you
have so much wood it's good though I'll
make another one maybe
gravel
here I'll make a new place and yeah make
it right although can I
even I guess if I
make I have an idea I have an
idea let me know if you want me to help
you with something cuz I'm available
okay I'm just important
things can
you wait in a in a moment
actually I need you to just stand there
so I see where you stand from
below okay and then I'll make a hole
under so I can put water there you get
what I'm trying to do chat so I can just
use this cuz water needs to be there but
if there's no you know you know you know
there needs to be a pool of water
here sure you just tell me where to go
boss I'll make it happen
mhm what do we want to extend what what
kind of call you would know what blocks
do we have so many of that it's oh
maybe that is really annoying yeah that
I can use it terra cotta no terra cotta
do you want me to use terracotta too
much terra cotta yeah go go grab it from
the Terracotta chest there's so much it
makes me want to die which one's the
Terracotta
chest um it's you'll find
it so
[Music]
pretty it is a pretty one I'm going to
cook some of this fish can't eat the
tropical fish can we no I don't think so
for shame yo game come on hungry we're
starving here yeah I watched oh wait no
I didn't watch this is not a reality I I
just fought for a moment that Dave the
DI was reality uh but in Dave the DI
they make sushi out of unusual fish like
tropical fish and that's really cool cuz
I learned so much about
fish M oh from Dave the diver yeah yeah
that's a fun one okay I just play that
on my own time yeah follow me okay I'm
chopping on a fish I'm on my way though
I'm coming maybe where would be good
stand um stand right where I'm standing
right
now okay yeah gotcha maybe here on this
block and and then after uh that when I
say next you go like a little bit like
further ahead maybe next to the torch
and then stand there too okay yeah wow
riveting job you got oh yeah I'm just
happy to be helpful happy to be of
service cuz now I
see and then I know where I got to go
from below I'm underground Kelly oh yeah
ah I see working on that second level E
Yeah extending it a bit further so oops
see Then I then I'll make a hole where
you stand and then uhuh then I'll put
another block there and then I put water
there it's I don't know how to explain
you will see when it happens oh okay is
everything water elevators or can we
make some stairs cuz you know your boy
likes stairs St did the chat tell you to
do that no they've been telling me to
well now I'm going to tell you to I like
stairs I like the insurance of stairs
you can totally make stairs uh if you
feel like it you can put that on your to
Kara I called you a coward I like Kiara
I'm a coward I see coward I'm a Kiara
so put some stairs down okay no
problem where are you okay misu hydrate
puu oh the bunny on the second level
what the hell it's all alone down here
that's so scary you fall down the
waterfall what's he doing
there hey make a pocket of water to sit
in I
see pocket of water to sit in MH what
yeah what is Kiara
planning making a second bigger Farm
there oh my cat um but yeah you you're
where you're standing is where I'm going
to put the water but I just need you
uh so yeah I need to make a hole where
you
stand okay we're staring at the sunset
I'm I'm I'm getting
there n Kiara is working I'm staring at
the sunset cuz I have nothing else to
do tell me a story tell me something
about your
break my break let's see what did I do I
sat down and I only watched a lot of
anime um yeah one of the ones that I
watched was I watched the entirety of an
an so my mother first I'll start it here
my mother um and my my step father yeah
she's great she was watching Netflix
with um with stepdad and um and they
found a movie that they loved so much
they had to tell me about it and they
said little myy you got to watch this
movie called Golden Kami and I'm like
I'm like um how do you know that and
they're like we watched the movie it was
so good well it's cuz they watched the
live action and they thought it was
incredible I was like all right so I
decided to check it out and I marathoned
the whole anime cuz I really liked it a
lot and I was very excited to tell my
friend about it um who I you know talked
to about anime and whatnot through high
school and I tell my friend about it and
she says Mor that's an anime for men
only men like
that only only older dudes like that I
think that you can say that about any
anime even if they're like shjo or Shen
anime like it's very common that the
other render will watch it
anyway see that's what I was saying too
I was like well this is also my friend
who's not a big JoJo fan um and I feel
like I feel like you know they're not
the same but I can see why why maybe she
wasn't into it
M damn I need torches okay I'll make
torches afterwards the golden comy fan
base is predominantly female see I wish
I known that so I could have told I
could told her that there are some
moments in that show where I'm like oh
my God yeah they like went for it like
well this is the
B so it's it's like a kind of historical
historical uh Japanese anime it's like
an old like um Hokkaido story Hokkaido
story yeah there's like this um this
Japanese soldier guy named sugimoto and
he's really cool and he helps this girl
um like get it's it's kind of hard to
explain but um it has a lot to do with
um like the the you know um old Japanese
reishi um and like the the IU of uh Hulk
kaido and there's this gold um that that
was hidden and it's there there a bunch
of people trying to get it and everybody
wants the gold I'm terrible at
explaining
but that gold it belongs to the Inu you
know hidden gold bloody Chase yeah
exactly so he teams up with this this IU
girl and they go to find the gold but
all these other dudes want it these like
other military Bros and then like the
shin sgom are involved and stuff like
that and it's it it gets really intense
but it's it's super good I like it a lot
it seems like you remember it so well I
mean I did just I did just finish it so
wait wait why did your why did they know
it because they watched the live action
on Netflix and just watched it like it
was a normal movie oh based on an anime
or anything oh oh yeah the the map to
the gold is tattooed on the prisoners
and they have to skin the prisoners to
get the map to find the gold okay like
the girl doesn't want to kill anyone
yeah it's interesting I like I like that
a lot but like sometimes there there
will just be dudes like all together and
then all of a sudden they're all just
naked together like posing with like
Rippling muscles and it's like why did
they decide to do this but at the same
time let's go okay I almost I I got a
dirt block yeah okay I'm making maybe
I'll just how how about I make a whole
line nah okay go next okay uh to the
torch yeah okay this is it the one over
here maybe I guess so yeah the one
that's next to the tree oh yeah yeah
then that's this one it's hard actually
to tell where you are
standing is it here yeah
here hello Madame welcome to the
underground okay welcome to the
underground so that should that should
be
sufficient D let me show you the way out
no problem wagon Faron let's
go it's kind of dangerous but you go in
here and you press uh space to go up all
right do I hold it or do I hold it hold
it hold it okay yeah he's gone see it's
easy we're
safe oh wait they said I have torches I
do have torches let's go all
right and I used some of the pretty
terra cotta yay yay Callie feels happy
that the Terra Cotta is
gone we have too much of it we have to
get rid of
it oh yeah I'm sure I'll talk more about
Golden com during zadon streams you guys
I have l feelings about Golden commy I
really liked it what about you Q what
have you been watching recently aside
from rewatching monari uh well shun and
I finished Fallout recently and
apparently today I thought it was next
week for some reason but apparently
today the new house of the Dragon season
is coming out oh my God I think at like
3:00 a.m. in the night for me you going
to wake up and watch it no I I'll watch
like when I wake up uh like hours after
yeah you don't need to get up super
early yeah are you going to watch
it me House of the Dragon is that um
Game of Thrones yeah Game of Thrones uh
prequel that's right yeah I need to
watch Game of Thrones first oh my God
why are you all not watching Game of
Thrones What Game of Thrones what's
why I mean I I want to now that I finish
Shogun and people are like oh shogun's
like Japanese Game of Thrones and
whatever I'm like oh maybe I like Game
of Thrones no no no think so I would not
call it that at all that's what I keep
hear people saying I'm like are you
sure you think that's not accurate
nah
nah never would say that it's good but
the ending I mean well yeah of course I
know about the ending not being first
five seasons are great maybe read it
some people say read it
by the way guys I'm doing this on
purpose I just want to get rid of some
of the bamboo cuz I feel like we don't
need it everywhere in our
face
so
see yeah I feel sad that we can't get
more Diamond you know actually we do
have 30 diamonds that's pretty good yeah
I think maybe you can um if you're done
sorting if you don't want to do that
anymore you can just mine a little bit
we we really need to mine and mine find
a sheep sheep is really important
villager is really important any any
Merchant Trader is really
important right got yeah anything like
that the chest is empty oh damn yeah
sounds good okay so it's this one and if
you see something like obsidian that for
that you need the diamond pickaxe it's
in the chest of the okay gotcha yeah
sounds good for now we'll use
iron good
yeah oh hello oh should we kill this
guy uh oh what who the hell oh he's a
Pillager I think is he yeah that looks
like a Pillager so we so we rattle him
yeah yeah kill him so hard to get out of
here once you're
in once you're in it's hard to get
out oh
Emerald oh creeper head nice that's good
oh oh you got a chest
nice I love when the chest spawn it's so
fun it's like what's inside yay lots of
gold and then we also got what's this
enchanted book
impaling oh enchanted book mhm impaling
waa which is pretty cool I wish that it
it was something maybe a little more
useful to our cause but do you think
that's a good one or um what impaling
was that for was that for Trident yeah
good I wanted a trident maybe we'll
somehow get
one okay well we can save the book oh
we're going to need a chest for a book
now oh boy for the one book boy oh boy
for a single book oh nice obsidian okay
I'll go grab the diamond picka oh yes
yes
okay then I will put it back I will put
it back because this is a
treasure well I've been using it a lot
even when I shouldn't have oh
no that's okay that's okay forgive
forgiveness try to use Stone
but occasionally I'll switch back to
yeah for iron that's fine we do need
more iron thankfully though we're
getting some iron here so that's good oh
you guys go into the chest yes or
no okay we still have some some more we
can mine
good good good
[Music]
yeah the issue really is that like in
those first phases where we got those
things like sheep and all that we really
had we we should have but you know now
we know better we should have protected
them better so don't that we don't lose
them because now getting them now is
really difficult those simple things
yeah which is a shame a little smaller
here we
go yeah that's okay though we'll yeah
we'll find
one just have to be really careful when
it spawns in you know yes yes we'll be
fine is that a diamond block nice o
emerald and then enchanted book infinity
and enchanted book aqua
affinity interesting we're getting yeah
we're getting enchanted books now damn
you're getting all the fancy
books yeah maybe it's cuz your boys
really lucky I
know I yeah maybe sheep aren't such a
important thing anymore more now
actually because I I did make some beds
with the uh spider silk yeah but still
it would be nice if we could all if we
could all sleep at the same time to like
get through a night or something like
that you know and when
um in cases where for example uh a bed
would burn down or somebody dies with
their bed or so you know then we need
another
one we need another one m
that's a good
point oh uh oh what he do I think the
chest is full so I'll go ahead
and yeah sort it out baby I will sort it
leave it to me block of diamond can we
turn that into
diamonds uh yeah block of
diamond yeah block of diamond you mean a
no you mean just a you don't mean a full
block of diamonds right where are you
I'll show you it says block of diamond
here I'll show it to you you can have
it what the [\h__\h] you that was
mined yeah oh my god let's
go going to put that in here for safety
that's nine diamonds in one go wow luck
100 today I guess guys yay it's cuz it's
my first time streaming that's why this
is my first time streaming one block
yay yay good stuff
y get some more and let's
see another
brick
okay yum yum maybe I should make a few
more water sources here guys right
there's not not
enough I am stard you
valy
actually build BAS so you're building
the basement right it's it's already
there but I might keep on extending it
okay sounds good we'll turn this into
the enchantment chest okay have to
rename this water lets you plant four
blocks in all directions yeah might need
a bir that's not
more come
on hey guys if I want to rewrite
something on a sign I'm sure you know
this K if I want to rewrite something on
a sign I have to remake the sign right I
think you have to take it
off dang it I can't people said you can
rewrite without taking it off but
honestly I could not figure out how just
take it off it's fine it's it's cool I'm
a big stupid dummy can't think oh yeah
it's in this version of Minecraft like
in newer Minecrafts you can change it
while it's still on there I see yeah why
we weren't used to it books yeah
enchantment we can put books in there
there too I think that that fits no no
Bey okay um I go and cook this iron
actually make a fence
here I hope I hope nobody will fall
down fingers crossed fingers
crossed only happy
accidents but of course and what do we
need bone meal for by the way uh uh to
grow things faster like the trees and
the crops or anything I see I'll put
that in the item box the glowstone dust
and Redstone Dust
okay we don't have a ton of room in here
but let's
see I know where I can put these
things
okay need pickaxe I will make
bigx I love organizing I hope you guys
are enjoyed watching the endlessly
organized I'm so glad you're up for that
cuz I really couldn't care about doing
it I didn't know I didn't know that it
was a legitimate like thing that needed
to be done
here that's like one big thing that
people enjoy in Minecraft too
no crony is also a big organizer
oh really I didn't know that I once
hired her for a whole collab Minecraft
stream to organize my
things e really that's smart yeah and
she did it with
pleasure nice she was delighted the
same heck oh crony
yeah croner does have those vibes yeah
she
does yeah she does I love her for it all
right let's see W done I love this
little creeper head he jump scares me
every time I turn around creeper head
yeah what the [\h__\h] a creeper head was in
the chest that I
found yeah
n yeah so
weird it down
somewhere yum yum yum yum yum yum yum
yum you were scared for a moment yeah
this looks like a DreamWorks
Sky oh yeah on my side at least with the
shaders which one are you using are you
using um what is it I for what it's
called
silder oh silder that's a new one that
I've never heard of M I've been using it
for
years there's so many Shad yeah silder
and OptiFine together because OptiFine
is just to make everything run
smoother I
see one 2 three 4 oh this is is actually
fine one two three oh I can make another
one
here more Terra bye-bye feel free to use
more of this terra cotta cuz we got lots
of it one two oh yeah this will be
become dirt too at some point one two
three four oh this didn't have to be
there but that's okay one okay wonderful
that's actually that goes really far
with just these two little pieces of uh
water huh nice we're going to get a big
fish Farm I want especially SE wheat uh
cuz we want the bread go get the
bread the bread sounds good to me mhm
and then we make bread I don't like
pumpkins cuz they're so big beetroots
also honestly [\h__\h] them yeah there's a
lot of pumpkins here I'm kind of like
why do we need them I don't want those
pumpkins like watermelons are okay
because watermelons you can eat like
that without making it into a soup I'm
just want efficient food you know I get
you I
agree maybe I'll use some bone meal to
grow the
crops uh is there more than just these
19 do did you put them somewhere oh yeah
an item box I think they fit better in
the item box instead of the ore box okay
wait item box there there okay I'll
check it out it's the top one right
there
okay Dy
problem oh now playing money yeah I'm
too lazy to change the CD but if you
feel like you can change the CDs too see
do they have the cat one cat one see
where's yeah it's called cat or
something I forget Maul Maul could be
fun let's try Maul although you can eat
the beetroots raw right maybe they're
okay I
wonder m
I like this one
M wait how do you plant melons properly
can I plant them anywhere here but don't
they need space around it so if I put it
here can it grow next right next to the
water is maybe not
good tell me Chad tell
me Chad always knows the
answer
see plant it on the side one block next
to it has to be free okay okay okay
maybe a little maybe I can make a
ceiling so that I can put more torches
there I don't want to take up the space
of the for now it can go
here wow this music is good yes it's
good right is it chill hell yeah my
fave it gets a little loud though so I
might need to turn it
down only when I'm close to the duuk Box
oh you can turn down the bgm the like
jukebox music in the settings like just
the Jukebox music jukebox okay
gotcha there we go Farming Simulator
let's go farming s yeah I totally forgot
that you can really like Farm a lot in
in Minecraft like Farming Farming
there's so many things you can
farm so many crops and animals so much
variety like planting bears and stuff
like that yeah berries although berries
are I think mostly berries get ignored
because they don't heal that much
and yeah they don't I don't think people
really see them as crops in Minecraft
usually oh I
see you see this guys you see this how
how efficient this is I'm making a big
bread
Farm maybe no watermelons needed
yeah lots of Wheat and whatnot yeah some
bread get that bread although generally
we don't even lose that much
hunger but anyway I still think we need
more
food understandable especially if you
know enemies come out and stuff like
that and then they you know F us up and
stuff yeah it's bad that happened a lot
yesterday that did happen oh yeah
yesterday yeah there it was so funny um
you remember the shulker box enemies
that like spit at you and then you fly
oh yeah those uh showed up in the 10th
phase
yesterday and every like it felt like
every 10th block that we mined a shulka
box appeared and it sent us all flying
oh my God it was so funny and then I'm
she had a fishing rod so she can
actually this is possible it was funny
she threw the fishing rod at us up in
the sky and then she held us like a
balloon oh my God was cute that's so
cool I got to go that yeah that sounds
insane that was fun it was like a what
do you call um I uh the the fun
fairs the fun
fairs yeah like at a carnival or
something like
that a fair kind of ride or something
yeah balloons where they swing you
around
yeah cool yeah Carnival Carnival kind of
thing
nice also just got a block of emerald
too wow okay H not so bad actually to
get all these blocks I don't think we
got full on blocks
before yeah it must be a new thing are
you going into the Hey DJ the music is
already
off Hey DJ turn it back on again and Mr
DJ jump on the r play and Mr Magic want
you turn the and Mr D want you turn the
music up it's a Rihanna song an old
one oh I feel like I've heard it before
it's like one of her first
[Music]
ones P the
replay p p p p p p the
replay do every time you want to play
music do you have to go back and punch
it
yeah I wish you could like put a que on
it right it's very inefficient
this is my favorite track though I think
it this one feels kind of
short maybe that's why ended so fast a
shorty but a goodie oh hello short
King wow already half cow what should we
do with the cow there you got a cow nice
can you try to wait what do cows eat
again Chad is it wheat because now we
have
wheat come on buddy um we want to lead
it to the farm and keep it safe there
sure let me see let me or I can find
some wheat oh there is I think one piece
of wheat in the food chest but I got
some more if you need it all good I'll
just hold it and leave him
yeah come here I'll open the door for
you now you want this weed you know you
want it you want this weed oh
can't come on no you want this weed oh
is it having a hard time getting out of
there yeah I think he's wait I'll try to
push it give him a push maybe it's the
wrong way can you try leading him around
the corner of like like here is sure
well we just get rid of the block for
one moment actually that might be
better wait I you can lead him I'll get
rid of the block sure as soon as I can
jump out of this hell hole that I'm in
hold on a second let me out or out or
this door this stuck wait maybe no I
might be stuck looks like a young little
trapped yeah it's difficult to get out
get go try to go here to the red block
thingy the red behind yeah yeah yeah
here
uh-huh let me kind of It's Tricky here
we go it is a little tricky yeah that's
fine okay can it move now or does it
need the help n it needs okay I broke it
buddy let's go I know you want this weed
you see how hold this weed follow her
why do you want my weed go to her why
don't you want my weed come on you guys
said it it's weed right go go follow her
follow okay I guess we'll push it want
my weed guess we'll push it push it all
right we pushing him we have
yeah but pushing works too oh no no we
want him to feel safe oh oh now he want
to come oh no he doesn't oh wait oh yeah
here we go here we go yeah oh is he
following uhhuh oh there we go yeah okay
I guess you just got to just keep on
walking yeah and now and now do I feed
him feed him plenty although I guess
they can't make babies until they have a
second one was that the
case oh maybe well there's a mushroom
cow can they not breed
together uh those two probably not huh I
don't would be good if they could maybe
they can no no okay we need a second cow
a second cow would be
great all right let's cross our fingers
then and really try to pull pull for one
it's kind of like
gotcha yeah yeah see we can pull a pair
for a spare inter species
relations oh
boy oh okay this makes me so happy this
Farm makes me so
[Music]
happy like that Tiny Farm over there was
good for the beginning but we really
need something bigger and yeah we should
expand for sure I'm always up for
expanded Farm we should try and make a
legitimate Farm you know more
legit we could work on like eventually
separating the animals properly into
cows only and so on so it's more yeah I
think that would be good easy to handle
for example if we want to kill some of
them for meat just so we don't
accidentally kill other animals that we
didn't want to kill exactly good idea s
this I dig it potatoes potatoes do do we
have some potatoes you have some rotten
potatoes
rotten yeah I guess like growing on the
sh all right I'm going to keep mining in
a minute here what do we have all right
uh block of potatoes definitely want to
save that
potatoes potatoes potatoes potatoes
potato
tots
potatoes
sure okay this this is really nice
really really really
nice I mean I think now we can just let
it grow on its
own right guys yeah don't need to force
it anymore just wanted to fill it up ah
happy happy happy
uh you can turn the mushroom into nor a
do we want
[Music]
that I think for now it's fine like this
we'll find another cow we'll find
another one yeah cuz that mushroom cow
it gives us endless mushroom soup so oh
yeah
mhm wait the only way you can get the
mushrooms from it is it by shaving it
yeah but then it turns into a normal cow
you don't want to get the mushrooms from
it you just want the soup from it trust
me I
see it's a Val pick them you're not
going to not going to shave it how do
you pick them up uh if you if you wanted
the soup you need to make a bowl out of
wood I think there we used to have some
bowls we have a couple
okay where are they I think they're in
the item box okay oh well should be
there going to put in some things for
sorting actually this one I'll sort
myself
okay found quite a bit of sorting maybe
we can keep mining a bit huh guys yeah
go mine let's mine I want to mine a bit
too come mine these blocks popping
off that's a bunch of blocks more
efficient this way we'll get faster to
the things that we want oh Two Is Better
Than One yes but sometimes they take a
minute to get why does it not go in no
yeah it's really strange I mean it's not
full oh now it looks like it's going in
no those are just staying but it's not
full the chest is not full is it CU
we're too fast is it cuz we're we're
going too
Speedy put the slab back it's the slab
oh okay
wait the slab where did it go can I just
put a full block like this Hopper
overloaded maybe
H does it have to be a SL a hopper yeah
I think it's too fast it says the
Hopper's
clogged it got full wrong space what go
oh
goo gooy I didn't expect
[\h__\h] hello hello hello
hello hey is that a is that a that Cape
is that an to find Cape or so do I have
one too oh I have yeah I got the Phoenix
Cape oh cool good bab are you listening
to our streams do you hear
us you're almost at a thousand you in
VC oh we're in the different server I
think oh no you are here you just muted
okay oh oh she's in here three more
blocks and then you have a thousand
three more oh boy let's go she's been
mining she's been putting in the mining
hours okay I I'll try to fix this guys
to the
m uh so the
slab how about here here
right and then we can get rid of
that chill
999 blocks ooh exciting correct okay now
it should go go back in I must
stay she's got something to prove by
staying at
999 the 1,000 one it has to be a special
one I can respect
it lots of Terra Cotta but why but why
ooh
Emerald actually have a ton of emeralds
all right leave it to me I'll leave it
to you I'm still not going in though
strange H oh well we'll just have to
sometimes you know pick it up ourselves
that's okay it is what it
this oh bless you oh there you go does
something break just now yeah might my
iron pickaxe I'll make another
one I have enough iron it should be okay
thank you for the blessings everyone I
appreciate that tight very kind oh gazon
tight
thanks may you be
oh thanks I'll do my best
M especially now I really should be
obsidian please oh gotcha leave it to me
gotcha I'll put some I got your back
I'll put music in I want to hear this
one DJ K take it
away ah it's that
one this one
it makes me feel like I'm in Fallout New
Vegas Oh yeah I can see that it's got a
nostalgic feeling to it
[Music]
m I know we should use axes on the
stumps but they just appear so quickly
yeah it doesn't feel like worth it to
switch around yeah it takes too much
time oh chest you oh yeah you can do
that one uhoh there a bunch of eggs in
there that was weird though it just
disappeared yeah did you pick up the
stuff oh I picked up the stuff okay yeah
I guess just like uh uh yeah just are
you planning to start a kfp or something
Kiara no no no no no no no not this time
no no I'm too busy you know too busy
with other things yeah too busy with
other K
ofps I get you yeah cuz I've been trying
not to use too much of oh block of gold
nice I've been trying not to use um the
eggs too much cuz I was like oh what if
Kiara wants to make a kfp or something
oh you got eggs yeah yeah hey yo quite a
few
actually good are you just here to feed
the pandas is that all you came
forab important she's so into the
breeding got to make a brown one oh okay
she wants to ca
rity he not playing around what's that
brown one
I'm sure with your luck so far if anyone
can get that brown one it's
you Goa I just feel Goa follow me follow
me show let me show you the world follow
me I'm so proud I thought we need
this I'm oh I did some cool
stuff well I need to make it a bit safer
still but um uh here full Farm of wheat
for for uh bread
it's I think more efficient than the
food that has to be made into soups so
this is good this is
good and we got some beds now GAA free
of
them so we could sleep two people are
still sleeping on the floor yeah well
for now we are indeed only three people
so now we could all sleep if we wanted
to so yeah that's a a little bit of an
update the
nice progress yay
yay um don't do
that lots of good progress I
feel cut some
Baboo baboos are really good for the
sticks this
there I shall take
them seems like a much more efficient
way instead of of wasting wood yeah just
exent the the
pandas I try to remember
that cobbly stone I feel like the phrase
sticks and stones may break my bones but
chains and whips excite
me oh it's kind that's kind of something
a panda would say oh my God n now what I
mean with that is Sticks and Stones
especially bamboo sticks but also stones
are bad for their stomachs right but
chains and whips excite them that means
that the zoos that they're being held in
excite them too because they get so much
so much more bamboo but no Ze I don't
like zo that much but that's doesn't it
sound like something a panda would say
maybe that's Ranna meant maybe she sang
about pandas all the time
I don't know about that Kiara I I don't
know I don't think but they get so much
bamboo and it hurts their
tummies right so I guess so it's not
good for them but you know you love to
eat what's not good for you me too me
too just like the
pandas yeah it's human
nature it's human nature why is my Oshi
like this she cooked with that one guys
I I didn't cook Rihanna cooked
I don't know if that's what Rihanna
meant though what do you think she
meant I think that she meant that sticks
and stones would break her bones but
chains and whips excite her what does
what does that
mean when she sees chains and whips in
what way how do you use the chains and
whips oh Kiara let's not play
games I mean you know what never mind
you're right she was talking about
pandas I'm sorry about yeah yeah yeah
I'm sure she loves
pandas Rihanna a big Panda
fan fluffy chunky didn't know
pandas
yeah we have so many I wonder why so
many spawn for
us well a lot of them they should give
us babies as a result of the
breeding oh I see yeah
I got an enchanted book with looting
three by the way I don't know if
that's nice you get such cool books what
yeah lots of glowy enchanted books these
days Y Wonder
Why hey dead be can we not stand right
next to Papa thank you what am I doing
right now huh what am I
doing oh it's raining again oh my God so
much dirt it's gone here
[Music]
yeah lots of pandas and lots of Terra
Cotta for some reason i' like some more
diamonds
torches why is it so dark here why we
why do we why don't we have torches
here oh I already made a bunch of
torches let's
go okay not a lot of entities spawning
to be honest
mhm wonder why but no you scare them
because n because there's just so much
more from the the roster rooster roster
the roster
yeah there too much possibilities of
what could glad we're getting more dirt
I'm glad there's more dirt yeah the one
time we're actually happy about dirt
because we can use it for the farms and
stuff and expand the forest yeah that's
big do I have permission to expand the
forest
yeah oh just be careful just making sure
don't like I'll be careful I know it's
near the edge but you know the forest it
must be
expanded very important for our
mission
okay we really do need some uh some
villagers that can turn into Merchants
because we have so many
emeralds like so many we'll find have
them but no well it's kind of my fault
but um I couldn't do anything about it
in the moment that's okay you do what
you could I was stuck I was chased by
enemies and then they died as well you
did your best
Kiara R that's all anyone can ask
for
okay extension
domain
expansion you guys really like saying
that domain expansion I guess domain in
this case is like a place where you live
not a not a Internet
domain I would assume so not a that's
the vibe that I get interesting learning
English
oh I am the ruler of my
M
right I they are more technically smart
people in the chat you know I don't
really understand it I'm too smooth
brain for that well what Jud it's a kaen
reference is is that some currently
popular anime oh my
God I mean oh my God Kelly you
know did you k and it's I think it's
maybe the most um popular anime right
now oh um ever in the recent years
yeah I
think oh
yeah I would say definitely it is go the
currently popular an don't take the bait
she's not lying though I like your name
tag maybe she is fooling with oh there's
goo H can we overall make ourselves
smaller so that we can separate
ourselves nicer and hold on G grumbles
is here
hold no goba go in the middle so I can
separate you Bo booy
thanks okay hold on guys it's just a
little remodeling going on
here
yesah gooa is moving
in yeah goa's moving in so the
dimensions look a little strange Shifty
right now just we we're breaking
Dimensions right now so GL your singing
was so beautiful
yesterday yeah it was Majestic I tuned
in for just the two of us it was very
doky
doie yeah
goba there she
is like
so like so yeah okay all
righty
[Music]
nice yo okay what was I doing ah I think
I wanted to make a roof
rooftop for the
[Music]
farm I am the freaking organizer us
still feeding
pandas it's a very important job
understand see
P they do so much for us they're
definitely not living they block the the
path to the am Road where there might be
enemies that want to hurt us so they're
like the meat Shield I suppose oh yeah
that is something
valuable hold on I got to get rid of
some spam just a sec
oh was that not your intention
gooa
away this is good let's see this is
there anything here that shouldn't be
[Music]
here Redstone
Dust now the farm cannot be destroyed by
gas
attacks let's
go W big
brain oh genius wait I'll put on music
again yeah could use some tunes
M she's so
small this one was good I
think wait there we
go I love this I would totally use this
as like a stream
bgm yeah it's VI I like
it damn it why do you have Miss 99
blocks no no sticky Keys stop it I was
just trying to dance like girl wase come
on now I also always get sticky keys and
they always tell me to just like turn it
off I'm like I don't know where I'm sure
it's simple but that's for smart
computer
people all right mining
time call did you finish Red
Redemption yeah I'm in the epilog now oo
I've always been not always but I've
been interested in playing too how do
you feel I feel like a different human
being After experiencing the end of that
yo my Arthur was so goofy though I gave
him only mutton shops and a top hat was
really freaky so like everything felt
unserious my Arthur oh my main character
oh you can kind of change how he looks
and whatnot
but yeah so I'm in the end game now yeah
but I just I have a lot of I haven't
really talked about my feelings yet cuz
I'm still sorting them out it kind of
hit me like a bag of bricks I didn't
really know how to react to it in the
moment no spoilers I saw a scene where
you shot someone and then you went on
your horse and ran away screamingly or
or rode away screamingly now I was
curious like cuz I played a lot of GTA
games now I was wondering so if you do a
crime how does it work with the police
are they also on
horses um yeah yeah they have horses um
I mean I feel like it's a lot easier to
get away oh to be honest um in Red Dead
I mean and you're wanted and you have to
you have to pay off your Bounty if you
want to be pursued by the lawmen anymore
but Constable I suppose yeah exactly the
pranker yeah those guys suck some people
in the chat I think are making jokes
that saying that they do have cars and
helicopters but that's not true right no
they don't they're they're uh messing
with you because those things did not
exist Oh I thought oh it's sad far back
in time I thought it was just like you
know Texas
there are uh no mods they do not
have was just modern time
Texas I'm so sorry I know I know Texas
people they get like you know sad when
people think they like go to school on
horses and stuff on horses I'm
sorry confus it looked relatively modern
to me from the little bits that I saw I
don't know why I just saw really little
bits like tin the tiniest bits mean some
of the cities are like you know they're
they're uh they're like they're not
modern but I mean they look similar to
you know some more antique looking
cities that exist in this time of oh
yeah yeah yeah yeah see I get I see why
you maybe thought that
okay also I like how we got um not a
sheep but another freaking Panda that's
cool thank you for [\h__\h] sake come on
yeah give it to goba y lead it to the
panda Farm more for the panda aquarium I
guess congrats do pandas even drop meat
when you you know take them
down I I don't think so I think that
would be too messed up I think this this
stuff needs to be sorted go yeah we got
to sort thing I'm going to sort things
now don't worry I got you this is what I
do I'm a pro you can trust me you can
trust this in my hands I'm going to turn
this one it says it's a snow chest I'm
going to make it a rock
chest e
okay U where did I put the Terra Cotta
before or is it just gone now have so
much terracotta we have so much over
here I mean the the fancy white like the
the pretty one too was also over
there oh yeah I put all the pretty ones
in here as well okay if you would like
yeah design in
sense that cool
Wow music why do you
stop play
music oh oopsy do
uh-oh or she
blows so chill hey lots of golden
carrots I like these golden carrots cuz
we can really stock up for the final
fight yeah I mean golden apples would be
would be much much better golden carrots
are not even that good but yeah we can
use them it's nice to have them maybe we
should build a chest um Where We Gather
stuff for the final fight no yeah yeah
yeah could be see where should we put we
put it behind the storage area and that
can be where we we can store things for
the final the last battle mhm okay well
just kidding never mind these horses are
in the way we'll put it behind the soon
to be Merchant's house does that not
work I don't know if that works all
right this is final fight
storage and I'm going to put a I have a
totem of undying so I'll put that in
there too oh
yeah that is
good I like this one too this one's a
bob see our Treasures are in here so
move some of this nether quartz and
whatnot I'll take
that apples apples very just a note
don't eat the normal Apples because we
can eat turn them into golden apples
eventually the ones in the chest let's
collect Okie
doie
Captain I shall
take a chest Sur we had some chests
here yeah we have a ton in the wooden
one that's a
beehive beehives aren't made of wood
they're made of bee things we'll just
keep it in there
anyway yeah what do we do with the honey
I mean the bees are cute so I think they
have a right to
stay what can we make with honey candles
I think that's
it I mean they're aesthetically pleasing
but that's about it
right all right we keep doing some
organization a your boy such a trooper o
Diamond watermelon
nice
[Music]
oh I shall do some fighting downstairs
maybe cuz there's some zombies there
guess I got to put more torches
[Music]
down yeah see one reason that I really
wish we had a trash can is so that we
could throw away this Burning rotten
flesh oh
yeah cuz you just don't need it just
takes up space in a chest you
know that's how your boy feels about it
dump it over the edge true over the edge
right I didn't think about that even
though we have so much a bone head
now I feel like such a bone head no I
mean we all have a bone head we all do
true that is true everybody does have a
scroll into the void of course here I
true
enough I hope I don't meet the
edge oh okay oh that's it that's it you
want to be at least the cat is keeping
the creepies
away so why did it spawn though there's
enough light come
on maybe
here here
[Music]
are you okay yeah just hearing weird
sounds trying to be
cautious get
okay with the shaders I can see the
light glowing so much
nicer I see the dark this reminds me
this music reminds me of like a really
old RPG
mhm a particular one or just generally I
don't know in general maybe a jrpg or
something like that I don't know it's
hard to put my finger on it but I like
it it's
nostalgic I wish I had more stuff like
this to just play in my ear when playing
random games you
know nice looping tracks I'll commission
some put some bone meal here honey block
where should that
go yeah chono trigger yeah maybe Chrono
Trigger ah wait I'm so smart for making
it slams because enemies can't spawn up
there right cuz for a moment I was like
oh I got to put torches up there but
enemies can't spawn on brilliant move
boss very intentional brilliant
move
Wow Let's go oh let's
go I thought that was the intention no
actually not I just wanted to save
blocks not overuse blocks okay it's time
to
mine it's time to mine
put some torches here so that I know
where they are I know where they
are
uh let's see more terra cotta
here oh there we
go keep the dirt okay
Ika mining it's mining time she started
mining all over the place let's go
budy see what you get I want a book
too yeah an enchanted book you might
find one in a chest just keep it up give
me the the chest
though the chest of my dreams please I'm
going to start a different box for fuel
Like Flint and uh coal
obsidian do you have the diamond
pickaxe I do here I'll give it to you
thank
you okay here you
go thank you you're
welcome where does this
[Music]
stuff is unbreakable just takes a lot of
time
[Music]
fishy buiness that fit sco that sounds
like exactly her kind of
business good if you were to create like
a business like kfp what would you call
it maybe your own kind of like fish
restaurant fast food restaurant what
would you call it selling be fried fish
F fried trims all kinds of
stuff here hold on you can go by the
popular for formula of starting it with
a G like kfp like the
K oh you can do something like that or
make it a full written out
word I wonder what be good what are
those places next to prisons um let's
see you got a little more specific G um
what like what do they do with those
places that are next to the
prisons it's like a couple more details
maybe Waffle
House OH Jes no that's where people
fight before they go to prison exactly
exactly then they get sent to the prison
for causing trouble exactly that's a
little
different Bale bail
next to the Oh you mean like a
courthouse I'm confused where is she
going with this o o oh no so pretty woo
that's a valid answer
uh-oh you little
[\h__\h] uh uhoh oh yeah yeah yeah
yay damn Dy doing good damage give him
the old one too bail bondsman but I
offer seashells and Aquarium Rock box oh
okay cool
a nice nice I ever get in big trouble
when I'm out on
bail is there is there a pond there or
why is it why is it called baale
bondsman I got you yeah with seashells
you have to
accept why would you call it
that oh wait bale bondsman is just a ah
you're not calling it that it's just the
business
model or
so yes a business chant had some good
ideas for the
name H I sell seashells
ink seashells seashells
seashells she sells seashells ink that's
what it should
be I think that's solid
sh this chest is very shy shiky chest
she sell seashells by the bond ink Bales
that's so [\h__\h]
long the longer the better chicken oh we
have to protect the chicken we have to
protect the chicken wait wait don't
don't free it yet I I I'll bring some
wheat that's a you job Kiara y we had
one chicken and it died uh but nobody
noticed it yeah I don't I had birth it
and nobody even noticed that it existed
poor guy come here baby should have
alerted you come
here a okay where do you want to go we
need a little little shed for
you like a chicken shed I guess I do be
making a kfp but for now we'll keep you
safe in here wait this can be the
chicken shed come here you can't help it
kiar it's in your
nature oh you're already you always end
up taking care of kfp yeah it's just
your destiny I'll get more of you um
I'll get you some friends that you can
play with and make eggs
with need a rooster I
know I know how it works
what yeah K knows the
Deets got lots of
watermelon I need to eat more
watermelons now that it's summer this is
the time need a big strong rooster yeah
that will go k KY in the morning and
that will motivate the hens to make some
eggs it'll do right kfp right you know
how it works I'm doing it all the time
knows how it works are they they are
they do be what do you call it they what
do you call the act of laying an
egg laying an egg damn it they do be
laying
eggs should y y
y and if there's another one correct me
if I'm wrong chat they do be
ovulating oh that's what okay but what
about the the male ones or the they're
also OB in my world they're also don't
have they're also laying eggs they're
all laying eggs all right they have the
capabil capabilities in my
world oh I see you know ah
Goa come here come here come here you
can pick it up finally just like in the
picture yo pick it up goba show us you
can do
it what is it's chilling in the water
it's
swimming what do we do
let's well do you want to like free it
and bring it to a water ah we should
bring it somehow can we bring it somehow
with a bridge a water slide to the the
fishing pond that would be
nice that is a really difficult Quest
but if anyone can do it it's you
go it will jump out of there no way you
need a lead what you can actually but
like Elite but still it has to be in the
water
right surely it has to be within the
water it seems to
hand she's
sing he can hold his breath really no
way can he that seems fake
girl yeah it has to be in the
water we've add water too but not too
long do John who's DOL John oh yeah you
kind of have to go over to this block
and then like
Swizzle your way
out it's difficult to get out this dop
John right
here what you named him Johnny
Boy somebody help dop
John oh no oh you're on the donkey oh
yeah all I had to do is and Donkey oh my
God what a cute couple TR and
Donkey well now I can't get on him
anymore so I don't know how it happened
but uh okay she's she's going to do it I
believe you're going to actually try to
drag him through the no water section I
hope he can survive that maybe make a
first stop in the in this first water I
don't
know uhoh oh he's going to die really
like hella die wait I can get rid of
some slabs for you if you want some
blocks oh wait what's hurting you the
dolphin I mean he is dying like he's
definitely in the process of I know they
would Breathe
properly yeah he's in a state of peril
they attack but they also protect and
and transport people fast what's a word
for that with a cc at the end oh my God
what what I mean I think it's sensing
what you're trying to do
GAA oh don't die here do you need some
food have yeah yeah let's go let's go
ah oh go go go run for it bring the
dolphin to the
water oh she oh yeah let's go W mission
accomplish she did it let's
go wow I'm so emotionally moved
damn you guys are in the scary bottom
part aren't you damn you under there
under no no we're at the top oh we
didn't go down there we brought it to
the fishing pond up here next to the
farm
yeah yeah yeah look uh at the chest
section the chest over here over
here this dolphin will kill you
eventually it will jump at 100% really
yeah he heard you there's no place to
jump into no safe no safe
Zone we'll see we'll
see let's stay close by let's keep an
eye on it why he do that maybe he wants
a deeper pond
why he do that though add higher
walls yeah that would be good do we have
some more oh that never no that's a
little well go on put it on the leash
put it on the
leash no oh no no that's not
good oh sorry I got him I got him okay
it will totally I just don't know how to
get back up is the thing yeah let's let
him catch his breath sorry for hitting
you dolphin we could try to make him a
pond down here you
could this dolphin's
doomed Dolph John he doesn't have a
prayer it's got to be so he doesn't J
pry High walls would be but we won't see
him a yeah what a sad
existence dooming him to Hell Stu
to me I don't want to be stuck don't Cas
of a monal me please actually I really
don't want to use dirt for this but oh
well
in his dirt
cave can we leave like one window like
this open oh actually if it's just one
block can he attach the oh yeah right
why don't we just attach the lead to a
fence and then he will stay right he'll
just not be very
happy but he will be in water instead of
falling into the
void okay wait I think that's a good
idea goba can you bring a fence for the
dolphin what do you think dolp John how
do you feel about that buddy
oh that's how he feel hey do John the
come on buddy it's not good for you do
John maybe had glass windows we do have
a quite a bit of glass oh yeah we can
make it from Sand easy enough yeah some
glass windows
M we going to make an AUM person little
little
Shamu yeah why not
amazing John you guys
sh it's so cute how he's swimming around
zo oh get back get back nobody come here
no no come
on he sounds like he's in pain at all
times that's fine he'll get over it
we'll give him some fishies to feed him
can you feed the dolphin in the game I
wonder I feel like I haven't
tried right I'll attach him
here you go
oh oh boy it's like he's choosing to
die yeah you might need to set it a
little closer in
there oh oh will the lead
unleash yeah oh oh leave it to the
experts wait
uh come
buddy he's chilling he see he likes life
he likes living so there we go there we
go he's leashed that should be good
enough yeah yeah and then anyone who's
bored can make him a a glass cage as
well yeah maybe I don't know sounds good
to me yeah yeah the cliff the cliff is
scary
so how this water get down here I
wonder
flood oh
flood I
suppose hold I'm scared to let not
die I'm scared I'm scared oh
nice let's see oh I think we're good
100% jump off ah we really need the
glass
then well there's plenty of glass
thankfully yeah should we go ahead and
yes yes yes yes save them yes yes yes
I'm going to get some glasses this is
just for
now we have nine glass we might need to
cook some more we do do we have sand we
might have a lot of sand that we don't
know how else to use oh
Kawa thank you
Kaa all right let's see I'll start
cooking sand
sand I'm sure kawa's fingertips and toe
tippies are tingling when she sees us
playing Minecraft on our own server
she's like I want to I want to play
Minecraft one block Minecraft too has
she ever played one oh it's kyella okay
I didn't know who the heck you were
talking about for a moment Kawa
Kawa one block Minecraft or like Sky
Block would totally be like up her game
oh yeah for sure she she could probably
complete it on her own to be honest mhm
her senses are
tingling what are you thinking
goba typy typy
T dolphin hate you hate dolphin or
dolphin hate you or mutual
feelings feelings Mutual possible did it
did bite you a lot
oh man it might just be a LoveHate
relationship that's love hate all the
same if you know play the Minecraft game
yeah up
inside
messo Korean version what's in here oh
some
soup go and we can grab that
stuff wait all right I'll take it don't
wor can do cuz it it will end up being
sorted anyway so true
enough we share everything here by the
sorter of all
sortations that's right all sorting goes
through your
boy at all times I'll let you uh mine
with the pickaxe and when I see a wooden
block I'll quickly chop it off how about
that oh nice idea then you don't have to
switch around here's a question yeah
here's question what if um you get to
you know the level where there's obsid
obsidian but you haven't been saving
diamonds and then you can't make a
diamond pickaxe you have to start
over oh no well if you have an obsidian
block here and you have no more diamonds
left I think you might be [\h__\h]
yeah then you H you can break it with
your fist it just takes forever
oh you can okay just takes a bit you can
mine you can dig but it's very slow yeah
this takes a long time they say just
mine it really
hard so yeah we want to cherish our
diamonds for now until it won't drop
itself yeah I see but I mean we I think
we're fine is with diamonds as long as
we we we can't maybe we can't do a
full-on diamond armor
but uh we shall see we got some good
have a fair amount of diamonds iron
armor would be first step yes and with
the iron armor and a golden Helmet or so
we might want to go into the never
tomorrow
maybe yeah maybe see what we can find
tomorrow's Monday right yeah okay hello
welcome KY cats hello go go do your
thing do your kitty
thing all right I'm going to sort oh
Kitty thing is bullying the donkey I
suppose Kitty thing is hey what's up all
of you suck I'm going to kill all of you
ruin your lives cats be cats oh you're
making the glass let's go
mhm oh yes we are cooking
glass lots of glass
[Music]
let's see ah yes and iron we also want
to cook some iron too but we'll just go
ahead and put that in there for now sit
on
that we have so much gold and like we're
not really going to use it
huh it's okay don't a shame we'll find a
way for it we'll make it useful somehow
yeah you know what I'm going to go get
some soup from you yum mushroom St yeah
make glass paint means to save glass
good idea I want to learn to like
mushrooms I want to become a fan of
mushrooms
yeah well you can't force yourself you
straight up don't like
them CH cow carrot
[Music]
CH wow oh you said you were saying cow
yeah cow all right I thought you were
squawking like a like a parrot like
youing I was kind of like doing both I
see at the same time yeah cool okay here
go come with me cow it's breeding time
it's breeding time yeah and so they keep
making babies and then we destroy them
for their meat right uh yeah and yeah
cool pretty much and maybe sometimes we
might need some
leather you can't milk them right we can
milk them yeah yeah we can oh okay all
right breeding time oh sexy music please
oh we got a baby we got the baby here
grow up big grow up
fast she's really experienced in this
huh
yes I put the cows together have you
ever like I've done this uh in in like
what school what what do you call the
school before Junior High School
oh um Elementary School yeah in
elementary school we went to the
countryside and we made like butter on
our own and before we made the butter we
milked a cow have you ever done that
before I've never milked a cow
before yeah I'm a bit of a city Reaper
well me too but yeah we we did go to the
countryside as a trip as a school trip
that sounds fun
mhm now let me fix this up
[Music]
again but I think as kids as since we
were all super young we were all kind of
like ew don't want to touch the the
milkers don't want to you do it he
touched the
milkers
cooties he likes cows
yeah I can see that that sounds like uh
definitely Elementary School the end
game survive the end game Fact what's
the end
game you think the end game is here is
said I guess apocalypse and
then cows are the only way to get food
you have to milk
them wait what is the end game future ah
for a moment I thought it was a
sheep you can go to Hell polar bear go
to heck oh it just walks out okay
bye-bye oh well we haven't seen a polar
bear in a while didn't all of ours die
we had so many yeah yeah and they all
just annihilated by that yeah that one
dude which is fine what do we do if
another one of those dudes appears again
what do we do M this big that big squid
guy that flies through the sky like the
[\h__\h] Death Star they can also just
despawn um anyway if we just ignore them
if we stay out of their sight yeah but
we also have arrow and bow now
so so well give him a taste of his own
medicine i r a runaway is good
too no we need bit more
iron because yeah we can cook some more
honestly we still have some iron blocks
in here yeah uh well I just took them
but if we get more iron soon we can make
an
anvil and the Anvil will be useful for
you know repairing things and naming
things and putting together enchanted
weapons and stuff yeah I think so
too but now I'm going cook some more
iron blocks I'll do something else with
bit no no no no
no okay that's why we have the second
floor for and oh yeah and also good
thing we have dirt we got lots of dirt I
got
it oh that was frightening I was going
doie doie for a minute
there oh my goodness hey that's
Minecraft though that's Minecraft for
you yeah one dead beat horse died
unfortunately oh no the dead beats are
always the ones to suffer why the fact
that a creeper spawned there tells me
that it's not lit up enough
so oh there you go I can't help it to
fix
it baby
girl are you okay down here little kitty
cat I was talking to a cat
[Laughter]
yeah girl was the baby girl from woman
there it's fine we're all baby girl at
some
point a what was I doing oh yeah
o okay maybe that helps what was I doing
ah I was making new pickaxe I was going
to get I was going going to get the
[Music]
sticks those donkeys really like sitting
up there huh
donkey
donkey dunk on him dunk on the donkey
yeah yeah that's right yeah what I doing
I'm so unorganized I don't know what
when I'm doing sticks sticky yeah tell
them CH
you're uh pick
axe maybe a second
one oh oh you made another baby what
eyes does it
have oh
normal a but it's flipping so cute oh
the tongue it has a tongue face
is he
special good has been really into this
since
yesterday she she sent some playful what
was that like a a a face chart of uh
pandas into the chat like what is this
yeah that Panda looked pissed I don't
understand what did you do to him I
guess it just gets born like that right
it can't change its face it's just
resting [\h__\h] face
Maybe where's in her Panda breeding
[Laughter]
phase everyone goes through one she has
found her new profession time to die but
it's kind of crazy we have two PN snot
pandas that's kind of
[Music]
crazy that's pretty insane all right
here if a fish pops up do we kill it uh
which kind of fish that's was just a
random codfish but I slayed it and I
think it it oh yeah that's fine
sometimes there's like enemy fish like
things that look like a fish oh yeah
suck yeah those guys are the freaking
worst yeah the creeper head it does
scare me
too that's the that's the goal for it to
frighten
you that's what I wanted but everything
already scares me by default oh no oh no
you little [\h__\h] you're not going to kill
any no Fox sorry but foxes will have to
die because you're going to kill my
animals they're so cute
or you little [\h__\h] you little [\h__\h] you
little [\h__\h] stop zooming where is it oh
oh the polar bear killed the fox kind of
based I don't know maybe that's why we
have polar bears oh yeah they killed the
Riff Raff it's nature hoping they aim
for the pandas next now my reputation
will not be destroyed by killing a fox
the polar bar we do it's like like right
behind you watching you it's like in you
now go it's awaiting more
sacrifices he wants me to hit him so he
has a reason to get angry at me P bear
remember when true would be so
cute I'm surprised we don't have one yet
those round ears but then in white
M it's got to be a big
one like a tall
me yeah tall all big little would you
size I wonder if the chest is full I'll
me
check little more that's okay I'll start
organizing I think a few months ago I
was talking to my chat about if they
were more birds what kind of birds would
I be hoping for I thought I think I said
like a parrot would be amazing cuz you
can make this whole joke where as a
parro YouTuber you're going to like
repeat what everybody says just to annoy
the [\h__\h] out of them in collabs or so oh
my God it can be a whole
gimmick it would be so
funny yeah it's a good one and they can
be really colorful in their design too
so I think it's kind of genius oh I got
a book power free let's go ooh let's go
bird of paradise that's the thing like
birds do you have so much like Choice
they're all colorful beautiful you can
make so many different kinds of
birds Man true Flamingo
doco I know we have Ry but Flingo R is
not quite a
flamingo yeah it would be cool to have
another yet I bet they'd be like super
bright pink so many animals to choose
from yeah where's like a maybe we get
like a fret or like a koala or something
I don't something koala yeah koala would
be fun right
a it's got to be an Australian member
though yeah true true hug Hol man
y lazy koas are pretty lazy
right KO Tiger Tiger would be nice too
yeah yeah we've got lion but that's
about
it Lion's also great
what do you call those um safari animals
with the really long legs that
jump giraffe oh no
no long Gaz Gaz sounds like a horror
movie I think a gazelle uh member should
have like really the longest legs ever
like kind of like crony thin legs but
even
longer even
longer
oh a might ow sorry sorry horse or
donkey Dam
it 125% leg exactly you fought you
fought that crony was all legs oh we'll
show you gazelle vtuber we have now zel
vtuber is here you thought
wrong though she is still you know a lot
of leg a lot of croner leg we need more
though oh yeah I can go for
Mark see GFF tuuba yeah super long
extended neck I mean we it seems like a
trend for us YouTubers yeah to already
have long necks that's a long neck right
there look but can we get
longer can we
CU I want to see want to find out expand
neck expand
neck nice iron do be
cooking you actually have a good amount
of iron oh well we did but now it's all
that neck expansion long necks fauna
FAA what you you say that because she
she has long neck or because you see her
as a giraffe she's not a giraffe yo
she's not a giraffe silly
but is that the heck that's not what
like you know how people I'm a phoenix
but they call me a chicken is that what
people say to
fauna ah yeah ignoring the
truth stupid Pillager [\h__\h] give me a
villager not a Pillager one letter when
you say give me a villager they hear
give me a Pillager can't can't be help
just a miscommunication please
forgive can we UNP the pillagers like
can we heal them and become villager
probably not a nice idea yeah purify
them or something like that have a have
a nice sit down with them a nice
discussion wa another Panda another
Panda that's exactly freaking Panda but
no sheep yep mhm 50 bajillion pandas and
zero sheep makes a whole bunch of sense
Goa get your panda out of here where are
you they give the the useless ones to us
coming
oh there she they don't want to give us
the useful ones ah [\h__\h] no the sponge a
that's [\h__\h]
sponge okay uh block machine currently
broken okay that's fine I'll just keep
sorting I'll have to find the right spot
to put it back
onto oh good gives me plenty of time to
move this stuff around God damn it so
damn cute I hate it why is it so cute
how dare they how dare they be cute and
useless I hate it for
real what was I doing I was going to get
a bucket bucket bucket bucket think I
saw
buckets
nice bucket
to I don't want to make new
bucket what the
hell
ah blind
Wawa she can't
see okay Chad where is it to be
placed do you remember from yesterday
what Emma was doing chat is it like
H at the top hold shift which top like
there's many
tops look
here that seems wrong oh no that's
that's wrong that is wrong uhoh oh Yik
I this is why your boy very happy to
just organize things top
middle what wh which block tell me which
block is it like
here
wait no I went the wrong way I went the
wrong way no it's flooding yeah no way
chat crazy I don't understand why you
guys in chat are saying this as if it's
such a obvious thing where to put it uh
on the closed trap this this one this
this one oh yeah baby we're flowing now
oh yeah no more flooding just
flowing nice
y fixed fixed
EMP just in time just in time the chest
is empty
now which means more mining which means
maybe more
diamonds uh what am I what's my brain
doing where my brain doing where's my
brain dooring
how many blocks has everyone mined I
wonder I'm probably very far behind
yours says
1,700 1,70 blocks what does my number
say I thought wonder I'm here next to
you oh yours what do it say
2882 I caught up in the in the first
stream you know everybody was like a wow
it's was just a the camera man she's not
mining at all only has like free blocks
to her name ah now we're over 2,000 how
the turntables
wow wah The Miner well done
W well
done I'm going to catch up to you though
are you are you
oh Apple Fortune to and an enchanted
golden apple I'll put it in the special
chest yes for the final
battle Fortune well so so far we got
fortune and aqua infinity infinity
impaling we got a lot of trident books
man oh yeah looting power that be good
for maybe a trident for gooa I don't
know yeah maybe we'll be in a chest or
so one
day I could see it could that
be is this music else use it for you
fall asleep gooa
he's definitely very late and glorious
Neon right now
y ah she Ganky we're
good
relaxing Minecraft is really chill not
going to
lie it's chill hello rabbit
I love when little animals pop out I
don't like when pandas pop out uh it
just scares me I don't want to hit them
accidentally when they spawn right here
I get you just got to maybe aim to the
side or the corner especially when the
bigger ones
spawn true enough I'll start clearing
out some of this oh yesterday I was
watching a little bit of the aiple uh
cuphead endurance that they were doing
they were going for 15 hours
yeah that was crazy it's insane I was
watching like the last hour or so I'm
getting hurt I'm getting hurt couldn't
get my eyes off of
it I'm going to die what what who's
shooting you what the hell skeleton a
skeleton
oh okay he's very strong I have no
food see anything I can eat
no don't hurt the
donkey okay he's gone thank you where
the hell did he come from did you see
where he came from not a clue but I
think it was kind of near the storage
area sort
of not
certain but I feel like it's lit up
maybe the top oh the roof no the roof I
the roof is also lit up it's pretty well
lit no
wonder storage right the water broke the
Torches uh around here so okay
it do be like that
sometimes
interesting let me just get full
health H okay this maybe I should wait
I'm kind of wasting the
melon yeah this is good that's
fine I'm going to put some more things
into the Sorting chest yeah yeah
although you already have sorting chests
like
everywhere that's
okay no problem how about that glass by
the way is it finished oh yeah here 61
glass I'll give it to you now okay I'll
make a little aquarium hey BOS take that
glass I cook you some glass today yummy
don't tell anyone it's my finest glass
though she
cooked yes it com must number one C okay
go thank you for feeding the pandas you
later yeah was F thank
you bye go you
[Laughter]
helped all righty she go I helped I can
still see her helper can still hear her
voice
now I mean yeah you know the the typing
I can hear her to
type does it have to
be so tall
chat I'm going to make it a bit shorter
[Music]
here maybe we'll get more water animals
eventually that we can add into this
aquarium have you heard so I I think I
only heard about this because I
you know it's it happened in my
neighboring uh country um and this is
kind of like a crazy thing that happened
a really [\h__\h] unfortunate thing but
oh yeah have you heard of this uh German
hotel I think it was in Berlin that had
um like a huge aquarium dome in the
middle of the hotel o cool um and they
had like thousands and thousands of fish
there right and it looked beautiful and
it was like a huge attraction and there
were rooms that were facing that and
it's like this whole thing right and it
was going for several years just fine
but one day one day in the early morning
like right before checkout time so it
was actually a good time because there
weren't many people in the lobby where
this Dome was it exploded it was like a
big tube that like how many gallons of
water was it I don't remember but it was
just really huge it was was the I think
it was the biggest
aquarium in
something the biggest of something and
it it exploded and all the fish
obviously died thousands thousands of
fish died um thankfully I think no
humans uh died maybe one got like
injured or so a little bit but it was so
lucky that not many people were around
the um cuz like it was also it was
centered in the lobby right and around
this this thing there aquarium Dome
there was a bar too the the hotel bar so
if this would have happened in the
evening with people sitting at the bar
that would have been really
disastrous wow I can't even
imagine that would be rough exploded and
then there were a lot of Investigations
of like how that happened and it's like
still a mystery cuz there's several
reasons of why it could have happened
but it's kind of interesting there's
this like documentary in German that I
watched about it oh shouldn't they have
done a gajillion different check
they they always do and like it was
supposed to be super secure but you know
and then the question was are they going
to rebuild it or not because like this
should never happen again it was kind of
ridiculous in the first place and so
they decided to not rebuild it and
that's the right choice because how
could you after killing thousands of
fish right oh yeah forget that I mean
What a Sad thing the fish didn't deserve
that you know yes simp OB there's some
kind of design flaw to all German
speakers the channel simply tmos is
amazing it's so good they have an
English Channel too actually they make
really nice documentaries nice I love a
good documentary to be honest just chill
and oh it was 1,500 fish okay that's
still a lot wow you know that's still
that's still a lot of fish though well
let me let me it's a sufficient amount
of fish life lost was it in Berlin
actually uh Aquarium hotel broke
burst how sad yeah oh
fish oh I I'm going to show you a
picture so you can imagine later I I'll
show you I'll show you I'm curious cuz
when you when you say Dome I I try to
Envision it um and like I I'm having a
hard time seeing it in my head so I'm
curious if you could shoot over a video
Yeah s a picture one picture via DM cool
it was 50t
tall and if you his foot is foot what
you can understand feet 50 fet yeah I
can understand
that oh that had stuff in it okay yeah
taking that ooh uh so this is a
enchanted book Thorns 3 and 11 Gold ah
264,000 gallon tank and of course it
like leaked everywhere onto outside onto
the street and everything it did so much
damage too to to the hotel it needed a
whole renovation it's crazy man that's
horrible what the heck y that that stuff
should have been checked properly
mhm what a shame those fish didn't
deserve that there was like dying you
know whatever but fish that hurts me oh
like that skeleton hurts me but guess
what I it could have been the pressure
and other things yeah could
be
S no
water damage is the worst damage oh yeah
I guess the damage is
well Hotel must have been like is it
even worth you know trying to mop it up
with I feel like just a yucky rag
because of all the would all the poor
fish that died I feel like having to
spend so much money to repair [\h__\h] is
kind of
karma true enough you kind of deserve
that after that ah [\h__\h] sponge you
know what this happened it's because one
sponge block SpongeBob sponge block uh
spawned and that will get rid of the
water uh let me fix it oh that can
happen all right I'll empty out the box
in the meantime but what the heck it's
so random but what are the chances what
are the freaking chances Man O pretty
low considering that's the first time I
think I've seen that happen today it's
the second time today though oh it is m
happened like a moment
ago did I do it right yeah okay okay
okay
[Music]
okay okay
right imagine the smell I was going to
say the same
thing espe to clean up if you have a ton
of dead fish it's like it's not going to
smell very good either this kind of
sponge block could have helped them
clean up all the water damage
precisely they just filled the whole
room with Minecraft SpongeBob all their
problems could have been solved yeah the
irony all of
them download
Minecraft sunflower
wow cute sunflower let me let me plant
it
here and
sword D oh DJ
time yeah crank some tunes it's just
always the same cuz easier to put in but
I like this one so no
problemo heck yeah also if I don't if I
don't stream but I want to organize a
little bit I might you know do that as
well oh always
welcome cool yeah had to just hop in and
and really quickly just mhm do a little
organizing and hop
hell yeah I'm so like surprised that
you're willing to do that bless you
bless your heart I mean it's something I
think it's hard to mess up at so
true do my best little
bread are we growing bread Kiara do we
have a you want more bread let me let me
go farming a little bit I'll make some
bread cuz the farm is looking good well
I'd be happy
yeah you share some of that Brad with me
so thank you for the redirect
yeah it's an important job I didn't know
I was just kind of like okay what can I
do and not mess up
that but I think you need to let go of
that Minecraft trauma that you have it's
time to let go call it happened 0 no 84
years ago how many years ago what do
they say
oh gazillion year for score and 70 years
ago
I know it was a while ago but it's fine
it's more like in general with games I
feel that way like in group games I just
kind of don't want to get in the
way don't worry about it like to be
helpful especially if it's you know a
game that I'm like I know I'm not really
an expert at
right yeah but I've been getting better
at Minecraft I feel better about it now
than I used to mhm I'm so happy because
you once swore off my Minecraft but then
yeah that was kind of was it the
fomo I
wonder I don't know I think cuz we
always do a lot of stuff in Minecraft in
whole life you know I would understand
like having
fomo yeah I think when it ended up being
that like there were uh was suddenly
like a big shared server I was kind of
like all right I guess I might as well
try again to join and also the Sakura
biome I really want to oh yeah do I kill
him do I just do I just kill this guy I
guess I kill him oh yeah yeah yeah but
it will split into several smaller
slimes okay got and then you kill those
slime balls slime balls are useful for
something I think right I forget yeah
Pistons I think pistons for example but
Pistons I don't think we'll be making
any
Pistons I see I see but it's good to
collect
everything okay it's really crazy to
think all of this came from one block
mhm
everything created here that's
amazing let me go do we ah we still
don't have a second chicken wait it can
just lay an egg right ah right that's
how it happens they don't they don't
have eggs they can sometimes turn into
more chickens but not always it's like a
chicken gotcha oh for a moment I thought
oh my God I thought you died but someone
ate you oh
no okay egg gotcha
ah unlucky unlucky unlucky make more
eggs please you'll get one eventually
mhm you'll get another chicken
eventually I'll give you some bread into
the bread into the um food chest yeah
thank you oh yeah definitely oh wait
there's a couple of eggs here that also
I got a couple more books uh rip tied to
en channeling
waa Rip Tide let's go one two and three
and four Dam
hopefully that'll help somebody breed
cows oh yeah yeah okay good good good
good good good
[Music]
good but I need the wheat right I have
one there there was a hay bale hay
bales hey
b
bs yeah sometimes it's hold on a
[Music]
sec so much lapus lazuli like what are
we supposed to even use that for give to
P does she like leus lazuli for some
reason
yeah but why hey
[Music]
hey
why but
why what can you even do
with GI
me not gim me GI me
oh it's used for enchanting good thing
that we have a ton of it we have a
butload I did not expect riding on this
monster no it's not a monster you're
good you're
good I love alpacas need more alpacas in
my life except when they spin on you
then it's not so fun stupid alpacas it's
a love hate
relationship and it's a good aesthetic
block for building and dies says chat
what which one see
that this Laz oh yeah I guess
so oh more stuff to sort that okay
somehow I'm seeing the trium of the
soups now a little bit just a little bit
uh just a little bit yum
[Music]
soup ah I guess I'll stay here
this works
too never
works actually we can put the seeds in
the forest box yeah and the
bamboo I'm actually so
shook like on the first day we made so
much progress and I thought oh we can
like finish this in two days but oh wa
what is this now you kind of feel
differently do you think yeah I feel
like we're we're going to be taking a
while and now I just smelled a spider's
ass
oh nice what it smell
like
smelled smelled
like fuzzy fuzzy butt fuzzy smells like
good night's sleepzy wait fuzzy
mococo Moco
Moco I like the fuzzy and fluffy
thing I actually I think I would say my
cats they're also like there's a fuzzy
one and the fluffy one oh yeah but even
the fuzzy one is a little bit fluffy for
sure let me guess smoothie is the fuzzy
one no smoothie is the fluffy one
smoothie smoothie is a fluffy chalkers
is Fluffy though yeah she's she's fluffy
yeah because she's very M her fur is
very thick and big and she's got like
more layers of fur true but smoothie
smooth's uh fur is
softer so I wouldn't call her the fuzzy
one right I see cuz fuzzy implies it's
not very
soft no no
no interesting books
okay I guess it applies to both
really H see
that I found another um well rather you
mined another diamond block um yeah yeah
I saw it I was like heyo hey yo should
we not split
those uh for now they can just stay like
that it'll be nine right
yeah Tut is the fluffy one oh yeah tutu
is my fluffy one and then ghost cat is
the fuzzy
one small
baby yeah she's still cute andet
yeah I'm going to snuggle with her after
this and fall asleep no
baby the little one my little ones I
love
her yeah I love love ghost for them I
love ghost cat he's a good boy he's so
he's so thin not not thin but
like it's because not anymore not
anymore chky now now he's a big chunky
boy Big And Chunky what have you been
feeding
him well I kind of had to change up his
diet just because you know he was
starting to get I think he got kidney
stones once what um KY St it was KY I
don't think it was it wasn't a kidney
stone it was um it was a uh an
infection um who like a a urinary tract
infection how you notice what was cuz he
sat in the litter box and just meowed
over and over and over again oh oh baby
no yeah and so I took him to the vet and
the vet said yeah yeah he had he has a
UTI you should probably change his diet
and so a what the hell on some new food
and now he's getting kind of
plump
baby yeah that's okay though he he was
able to pee and now he's very happy and
Ganky and running around
so I I would be happy
to if I was able to pee but I'm an idol
I don't pee and therefore I'm just
always like you
know like I drink water and it goes
nowhere I have to it out that's the only
way I can lose the water in my body
dancing just from dancing all the time
that's why Idols dance in the first
place because they don't have the
ability to pee and they must get rid of
the liquid somehow so they dance that's
the real reason
Bingo
lore oh true write that down someone
write that
down the TRU or crying crying and
sweating L of crying
lots and lots of
crying every
day oh I'm standing here and the stuff
is still going into the chest
amazing yeah cuz I'm I'm taking a bunch
of stuff out at the same time M and now
it's probably going to start building up
again though Idol science yes oh yeah
all only gets rid of some of it by
drooling is it is it effective for her
seems to
be seems to be but zombies may just have
a a different system in their body
anyway yeah for sure did you did you you
didn't play the the O dating game right
I haven't played it yet I want to play
it on my own sometime
[Music]
soon what did you think of it it's not
what I
expected oh yeah some twists and turns
maybe it's very much
torture oh in what way I
wonder so many ways is it a difficult
game oh it is very difficult to rise her
it's like everything is working against
you and it takes so long to even get to
ollie my mind was going
crazy I see a rather demanding game it's
just Mind Games
yeah it's more fun that way the Dark
Souls of games
yeah true kind of
sleepy I shouldn't be I actually I woke
up before the stream cuz I was up like
to 6:00 or 700 a.m. oo cuz I've been
changing this my sleeping sleeping
schedule for this project a little bit
but then this one started kind of early
so mhm ooh dragon's
breath
yeah what if I just drop this it will
fall into the chest right yeah yeah yeah
yeah
shut the up let me get out of
here it's so hard to get out of here oh
now you're tired you don't have to force
yourself to stay like super long just
saying oh yeah I mean I'll stick around
for a bit longer it should be fine yeah
it is it is about 2 a.m. is are you
going to play
tomorrow yeah I'd like to what time are
you thinking I don't know about tomorrow
morning cuz then that would mean like
four hours of sleep but yeah um but what
I mean is the the following day probably
waking up early in the morning to play
okay I think put it in your schedule so
I can see I've been noticing by the way
you put something in the schedule
Minecraft right I'm like okay I will put
my Minecraft there so Celly isn't alone
and then I put it there and then you
moved it and then I moved it again to
towards you and then you moved it again
and I moved it again towards you and you
moved it again and I moved it again
towards you no I'm not trying to get I'm
not trying to get away from you do you
have my calendar on though do you see
it yeah I do it's just it's a little to
like the right so like I have a bunch
there's like a bunch of other ones that
I added like more recently that are like
kind of in the in the way before yours
so I I only see it if I look really hard
and like try to like measure like okay
that's you were not running away from me
purposefully not what I really thought
anyway I was just like this girl can't
make up her mind when she wants to
stream
Minecraft no there's there's just a lot
of um things changing behind the scenes
and other recordings and stuff like that
so I'm like mhm just a lot going on is
this one new wall Mall ooh diamond armor
for horse nice yeah that's pretty
cool let's
see oh I wasn't
new don't stack huh music is so chill
yeah I feel like I could make the other
book now but I feel like we're not using
the
books uh not quite yet I
suppose that's okay we don't need them I
guess I just like try to keep everybody
up to date in different
ways yeah he what does dragon's breath
do um it does some cool things but I'm
not entirely sure what okay I'm putting
it in the final chest anyway oh for
splash potion
oh Ling green Potions all right I'll put
it in there could make a chest that's
like for potion making ingredients like
blaze powder and so on red
stone that could be a good
idea oh my God hard to brief right now
for some reason oh you good
yeah
somewhat no so sometimes I can't
breathe don't die on me Kiara you're we
need you for this please we need a
leader I don't know what I'm doing I'm
just organizing it's very chill though
leave the leading to
[Music]
meing bur no wait again I guess what's
wrong with the back there there are
torches I don't know what the problem is
here very strange is there not enough I
wonder why
it can't be because of the nether brick
right you don't think it attracts no no
no no but as long as they spawn over
there in the corner it's not so
bad yeah hopefully it'll be all
right oh did you just plop an egg I
heard it but I didn't see it where did
it go where did the egg go my
friend oh wait I did pick it up
immediately okay gotcha
the egg got raid is so bad what the hell
yeah not very good I mean I got one my
second throw the luck went
there yeah it should be every Pro for me
I know right you are the mother
hen mother
Phoenix mother
Phoenix precisely very strange
[Music]
those chickens don't know who they're
dealing
with oh that might have been not right
how dare they disrespect you y how dare
they they should love me like like their
goddess treat me like a
goddess okay yo where's the worshiping
ready for some more breeding cows oh boy
oh here they go oh yeah
baby baby cow two baby cows oh
God is in
control you know those fluffy cows those
are so cute right like IRL I mean oh
yeah there's some fluffy cows especially
the ones with fluff around their hes oh
you do o I got feather falling uh
feather falling oh that's very
good
yeah in the
book put it in the book chest oh oh wood
what oh it's wood ohian it's obsidian I
guess I can't see
it yeah real dark it's a coal block is
it oh that was four they say sorry I
don't know how to read oh it was just a
normal cold block feather falling four
so that should be pretty
good sorry I'm illiterate I don't know
what's going
on feather falling four
yeah feather falling for
sick yes go I wish you could like copy
books like make a copy of it cuz the fop
falling we will make use of that I
think oh yeah yeah the diamonds right
it's kind of useful for is it for
the also we really do have a ton of
diamonds I wonder how many we need total
for like full armor sets for everyone
too much May might not be able to get a
full diamond armor I don't know although
all we really need is one goddamn
Merchant then we give him the right
job which is uh the the envil one I
think or or the other one and then he'll
make us diamond armor we can just buy it
with the emeralds that's all we got to
do that sounds way easier than just
hoping for diamonds M it can be a
combination of that and our own built
diamond armor I would
that'll be the most efficient
probably yeah oh that donkey's wigging
out going on or
also n in the in the nether we can get a
lot of gold easily we can make a lot of
gold armor but that's really not
[Music]
helpful but yeah maybe tomorrow maybe
we'll go to the
ne yeah chat if we were to go to the
nether what do we really want from the
nether oh yeah what should we gather
there cuz we're not trying to find
things for the
weather oh dear what the hell is this
marshmallow
fish do not hurt
me Callie is literally GM Reaper she
will
no hurt you back Guardian oh
yikes this seems not good at least your
stuff is still there right oh there a
bunch of them what what was that how do
they do that hey what's that spoon I'm
I'm being spooned
cie you're being spooned what what does
the spoon mean stop spooning me stop
it oh he's got that whack that tail is
just him Whack Him I'm trying I might
can't dig but that's all that one block
is about I died
no why is he so strong [\h__\h] Elder
Garden my stuff oh please leave me
alone come on no wa food food oh please
let me out oh please I got
these and lots of good
stuff I could have drank into the
mushrooms too mining fatigue
what oh did he fall down the cliff by by
any chance perhaps let's go oh what a
big dummy stupid dummy idiot dummy but I
wanted to slay him I feel you but
sometimes we just got to cut our
losses what are you doing here
bear okay dolphin still thriving that's
nice to see Emerald blocks too nice good
you always slay I totally slay
especially now Kelly do you like my
favorite night
outfit I love it yayay there's so much
much going on so much going on really I
thought it was rather simple but Oh you
mean like not in terms of detail there's
there's a lot to look
at that's what's going
on yeah the students will have you know
much to look at I
feel you
know yeah not popping
off feel like we can plant a tree here
which one will it be just a small one
maybe I love the hair especially yeah
ponytail so shiny
yeah a pretty ponytail for a pretty
lady good very cute fluffy hair like in
the 70s and the
80s
a oh yeah okay oh yeah oh
yeah there was like one fan art of
um like the whole myth ladies wearing
like a fever night inspired outfit you
saw it I thought like oh this is this is
where it's at it was cute yeah 7s 8 I
had a shirt that said g workout attire
is the best wait I'm still fatigued how
do I get rid of the
spoon uhoh chat
spoon specifically a spoon y milk oh
okay perfect we have cows m
choose a spoon seems very random
bottle bottle bucket
bucket bucket so many different
containers to choose
from does it not go away on its own or
is it just really really
long to wait for
[Music]
that meow meow meow meow okay iron
iron piig takes long 5 minutes wow
egg okay here have some beward
seeds
bye oh I hear some strange spooky
noises now they're gone oh wait I didn't
I didn't I hope our Dolphins though do
you think do you think I saw it just
like a moment ago it's very much
alive ch still alive
cool he will live until the end of the
server
sheep okay okay okay okay okay uh I
think they like wheat too let me go grab
some wheat oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah we
could put it where the chicken is for
now maybe oh nice idea hey buddy where
you going this is is this grown
don't go too far away please we need
you yeah wheat will also work says
chat wheat and also what else Works
where's the Sheep where the Sheep right
over here the Le my eye on him yeah yeah
yeah Le could also work yes but yeah see
look that's fine hey Kelly do you want
to make a little sheep
shed o that's a good idea just a small
one would work for now out of Terra
Cotta of course or just a wooden fence
would do but oh true
o
forgot okay let's make a sheep area then
um a finally the sheep that we wanted
but actually we don't I mean yeah we can
get some beds out of it two more
beds yeah but not entirely necessary I
don't know but it's good to have some
options in animals good they have
options
indeed okay let's make fences get some
grass for it oh right we got
grass can I take this no how many do I
want oh we need
sticks you can do it can
we sorry I'm
sheeper make the sheeper the sheeper
make the sheeper a a shed so it can wrap
in
PE wrap in
[Music]
it needs grass oh just grass blocks like
like this just dirt blocks then
or
M let's see should we put him dir blocks
where should we put him I wonder cuz the
that area is really kind of what if we
put him
here do you know if we have oopsie any
more dirt blocks somewhere
I mean we should yeah they should be in
um well your stone box that you kind of
set up
right and also I have a I have a place
that I've created as well um it where
did the Sheep go uh in the storage shed
too I think um maybe we can extend the
area not necessarily make a oh oh you're
doing it there okay that's fine yeah I
think this is enough
shut them
down that's really small
actually je I mean there's just not a
lot of
room it's just really kind of seems
cruel where of a sheep jail it's just
you know this this thing right here is
kind
of way I wonder if we should put it
somewhere else like
a if we should put
it in the forest no maybe like around
here like right here
that won't work damn
it what if we we can put him in front of
the storage
maybe grass wasted share it now it's
okay it's all right oh okay okay here
look we can move it you must connect the
dirt with the green dirt H okay Callie
can we build uh can you take those yeah
let's make it in the forest or like yeah
sounds good connected to the forest like
what about here
or here behind the bum boo
maybe
yeah of
[Music]
this okay tree out way
tree with the sheep on my leash right
next to the
edge it's a good idea right we only have
good ideas sure why not
of
course this will definitely be enough I
feel this
area area will be good just a little bit
more around the house maybe oh this tree
is encroaching on the Sheep's
crib just getting rid of some of the
leaves that should be good nature we
want the Sheep to feel good right so you
can put the fence at the edge of these
blocks I would say oh like right uh here
is yeah and then around the put the gate
where the void is the gate yeah good
gate good
gate yeah and we can just don't forget
torches yeah don't worry don't
[Music]
worry oh interesting I guess that works
what I uh Le the Sheep but there's no
need to leash the Sheep right H maybe
I'll also make a little um roof for the
Sheep too for safety we don't want
another all sheeps and cows die kind of
disaster sheep can jump on the corner
block is that true oh maybe if torches
on
it oh maybe still yeah let's get rid of
it feel free to okay here replace it
with okay give me back the
leash yeah this should be good okay uh
Chad will the grass grow on its own
chat I mean not the not the dirt blocks
into grass blocks I mean the actual like
fluffy grass will it grow it will slowly
okay just got to give it some
time yeah little by
little feels kind of dark here
yeah some torches might definitely
help egg it's time for me to go sleep I
think oh that's fine thank you so much
for your help no problem I'll be back
for the next installment early morning y
early J
morning yeah next time okay I mean
doesn't have to be that
early it's cool I want to I want to okay
maybe just keep an eye out on each
other's schedules let's do it that way
yeah sounds good to
me yeah you want to say goodbye to your
viewers bye everybody bye tired sweepy
sleepy
e what's going on tomorrow um I was
supposed to do the 2.0 thing tomorrow
but they asked me to move it a day later
so it's going be the following day oh
yep yeah so I think I'm what am I doing
what I check's calendar there's a lot
going I have a lot of different there's
so much going
on let's see you doing a jackbox collab
right yeah yeah Tuesday I think uhhuh
Tuesday with a just anyone in Ian I
think I'll be there
too cool that'll be fun yeah it's a good
time for me actually so yay yeah jackbox
late at night
jst uh all of Ian is invited so that'll
be cool and uh and yeah I've got Elden
ring coming up as well at some point are
wead I haven't decided yet but whatever
one I guess everybody has I'll have to
ask around we will figure it
out faor nobody only you have to have it
for jackbox oh yeah that is true
actually never mind I'll think about it
if everyone has a favorite they like to
do and I think it's going to be an off
uh it'll be an off collab for one Member
One memb coming to my house I'll keep
you secret for now though yeah one
there's a member coming over only one I
think someone who who wanted to to come
to my
house yeah yeah so that'll be fun just
one a singular
one okay I'll see you guys later
everybody continue enjoying uh Minecraft
with kiaha and H live English
myth what a myth what a myth hope you're
about
bye-bye everybody byee I can't forget
you a I can't even remember to forget
you that's a song oh my god wow that's
complicated my mind is trying to do
gymnastics trying to figure out the true
meaning of that I'm not very smart um
everyone take care that's okay that's
why we make a good team yeah two not
very smart people equals smart right
that's that's that's F that's myth
that's just myth that's myth that's myth
well see you guys later good night
byebye everyone good night
byebye bye take care
yeah
g bye-bye gaha enjoy the rest of your
stream bye-bye kfp thank
you peace see you later and and talk to
you later when
I'm yeah
she gone she
gone
[Music]
going should I get rid of this tree
chat I say yes I say yes to
oh Mar happy
what
[Laughter]
w that is a surprise just kidding not
really it was kind of right
there thank you
[Music]
ka
damn I have the honor to be raided by
the
korei I say yes to give me so fny you a
she left with a smile wasn't it so funny
okay if you only uh if you came into the
stream later then please watch um
Callie's VOD where I was like pranking
her I was pranking her oh man that was
so funny to
me yeah cuz she didn't notice I would
totally notice because I always have
like my OBS window pretty visible to me
and then I have like the the other
window where I see myself on also like I
see myself like double I would have
noticed when somebody like shows up like
around me in the room put more torches I
want to but like where do I place them
on the
ground oh yeah the top of the roof too
yeah let me get up there
oopsie but yeah I was like showing up
she was still in the beginning of the
stream trying to like figure out
everything and she was was like oh what
do you mean Ki is here cuz I just joined
the room I Was preparing for my stream
cuz like I started half an hour after
her um and
then I showed up in her life Tod room
cuz I I was watching her stream a little
bit just to like see if she needs help
or
so damn
it and then I showed up in the life to
room without saying anything and she was
like confused because the chat was like
ah wah W wah wah wah wah and I was in
there quite a long time in the beginning
and then I left and then she after I
left you noticed the chat saying K's
here and she didn't know what was
happening that was funny oh wait why
line up the roof no it's slabs or is
this
because Is this different because it's
somebody said something about the top
slab yeah they so saw it too
yeah oh okay that's okay I'll light it
up that's plenty
and then I showed up again and she was
like what do you mean you guys are
trolling
me I was laughing my ass off off
screen I came in like five times until
she noticed
me
now I'll put one here that's probably
enough I one
here I should be good okay so the grass
will grow very slowly you guys
say but it also eats wheat right but it
needs another sheep anyway in order to
breed but I could Shear it now and make
the rest of the
beds although we might even have enough
uh spider webs again to make it out
spider webs
too C web
[Music]
string how many were
necessary oh my God so many
pandas webs a I guess I shouldn't waste
all the string cuz we might need the
string for bows to yeah speaking of bows
maybe I'll make enough bows for
everybody how about that
bow what the
hell bow bow
is sticks and strings not
there
Sligh slay so now that I'm alone I'm
going to try to keep this
running I don't know if anybody will
still join me m it's still early in the
day there's a maybe a chance said Ena
could show up I don't know she has a
alen ring stream today I think
right she could show up before that
maybe and Amy if she's up for
it please girls say hi to
me visit
me yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah good on Cali
we were free again I'm actually
surprised you know I thought there would
be more like more solo play and more Duo
Duos but uh it's actually been going
quite well in terms of that
so everybody just jumps in when they
can U what am I doing what was I just
doing what was I thinking of doing ah
bows um I wanted some sticks and some
more strings yeah
yeah wooden chest sticks maybe a few
more can't
type okay good good good good good I
want to mine until I find a freaking
Merchant is
that very ambitious
perhaps does it have to be done
yes I it has to be done and if we get
enough uh iron for an anvil I could
repair this bow and it would be pretty
good wait I think we have o i could make
an uh Anvil but the the fear is just
that if I use up all of this then I
don't have enough iron to make pickaxe
but we still have pickaxes so we might
be okay wait why why can't why does it
not show up the
Anvil what what's the recipe
oh it has to be iron blocks what how
many let's make one then it will
probably teach me
right free iron blocks a
okay huh and four ingots okay okay let's
see is it on the bottom or maybe it's on
the bottom
no four ingots four fre where wait where
like like
[Music]
here
what free blocks the blocks at the top
three blocks top one Ingot middle three
blocks one in the middle
ah ah yeah okay that's the shape of an
animal all right wow
finally an anvil where should I put it
I'll put it somewhere else cuz it's
really crowded over there I'll put it
kind of want to put it here
[Music]
I think it's nice to have it placed in
the middle not all furniture has to be
like positioned at a wall
right so now we can repair things and
combine things that's super nice
progress
Baby Progress
baby messing with fuy no improving the f
Clank okay I have no more sorder now
that's um going to be a
problem but I'll manage somehow for
sure
a do I still make any roof we could make
another roof above the cows for
safety I'll make it the bottom slab how
about that like here you like that you
like some shade feels hot right to be
hot in the sun in the middle of the sky
I'm sure the sun is really strong here
so protect our
animals at all cost I don't know why we
have the alpacas though like
it's it would be good if you could Shear
them and that would make so much sense
cuz people do use alpaka
wool tell me guys tell me please
surprise me with the fact the fun fact
that you can share them in fact indeed
tell me that tell me that
thing tell me it's possible don't
disappoint
me I mean in Minecraft
only possible in is possible Ed what
you're just saying that because I told
you to say it
right you're just saying
that damn it I told you to do that now
it's my fault it's all my fault it's all
on me okay I'll come back guys with some
more blocks don't worry about it it will
be finished although for some reason
they always like to stay close to the
house maybe it's good to have it like
partially if they want some sun they can
go there if they want some shade they
can go
there the cows don't need grass under
their feet
right oh let's go to the chicken I need
to remember to always go to the chicken
and check how's it going egg where the
[\h__\h] are the
eggs where are the
eggs you're not getting out until I have
50 eggs from
you they don't need it but maybe it
would be nice for them they like it well
now that's just that's just like you're
just saying that because an IRL cow
would like it
right that is not my problem sounds like
a cow
problem I'm hungry damn it that sounds
like a WWA problem
right ah no
eggs doco for
Real where are the eggs where are them
eggs what else am I going to do today h
what am I going to do I want to find the
merchant and another chicken would be
nice a second sheep would be nice
nice but I got to be real
lucky I'm got to be real lucky it took
us like ages to find that one sheep and
that one
chicken So
Random chances are really
low I put in my own bgm cuz this stuff I
can't if I'm if I had a DJ you
know but I'm doing this alone I'm
multitasking let's put in
waa music let's put some chill Cafe
music do you hear
it
okay
ah you know three I think three days or
two days ago
I mowed my lawn and even now my right
arm I feel it really is so strained it's
it hurts I thought it would go away
after a day I feel like last time it
went away after a
day yeah I wanted to buy a lawn mower a
proper one maybe I'll go buy one
tomorrow I wanted to buy like one
secondhand but the last time I tried
[Music]
that
um it's like hard to find someone who's
not like an idiot on those secondhand
websites uh what am I doing sorry guys
I'm really slow
brained you have to bear with me there's
too much to do
you want to sell me one
really don't you want to gift it to
[Music]
me come
on I know you have the urge
to now could you also transport it to me
cuz that's also a pain in the
ass that's also one of my
problems well I might just buy a new one
they're
not I don't have to get like a super
expensive one
right they've got a family to feed and
I've got a long to M oh double chest
heart of the sea what does that do again
just you can just swim faster or what
was it or you can uh
breathe if with that with com combined
with some other things you can breathe
on the water was it
that I yeah breathe m okay that's not
going to be very helpful for
us I don't think we'll be needing that
but we'll keep
everything everything could end up being
useful and if we don't have it because
we threw it away or so we're going to be
like what the
[\h__\h] now we have to mine for hours and
hours and hours to find another
conduit gas or electric I've been told I
should get an electric one
couldn't care less for a freaking
skeleton
horse your bones are more useful to
me than your
horseness is this
full
[Music]
no you've always used gas I guess
they're stronger right gas lawn
mowers but I don't want to like Buy buy
gas all the time either especially with
these gas prices right am I right car
driver
people am I right cars any cars in the
chat who understand the
suffering I know I've been bringing up a
lot of controversial topics today but
the gas talk just reminded me of um a
video from um John Oliver I just watched
the other day about like basically gas
gas gas
replacement on the bottom of the ocean
did you guys watch that
too vroom vroom honk oh we got some cars
in
chat not
[Music]
yet gas replacement yeah deep sea mining
that one yeah yeah yeah which also seems
to be a little bit controversial
controversial but I found it an
interesting topic because like I I want
to learn about why it is controversial
you know because the fish could be
damaged
by the machine that Goes Vroom Vroom
under water uh it will like spit out the
things that it doesn't need and that
will be like all these particles Dusty
Sandy particles SW SW swo swooshed
around in the
ocean uhuh and that's just not
good that's just not good cuz some fish
may like choke on it or so apparently
yeah it's like an ocean
Roomba but if you think about it it's
cool that we did find at least
like something that could be used
instead of gas down there I forgot what
it was called
though forgot what it was what was it
[Music]
sh yeah I don't think they've even
tested it have they so we don't really
know Cobalt a yeah the batteries yeah
yeah the
batteries
mhm something for the
batteries m
not a h I like to be
informed about these
things W learning wa expanding
brain I honestly don't understand how
cie has the brain capacity to sort these
things like maybe also because she knows
where the things are now cuz I don't
know what she put over there
but I'm going to break apart before I
manage to mine these things
[Music]
properly what else do we have here
nothing sandy stuff okay that's the sand
box
oh that's kind of it seems like she just
put things together that are light
colored oh
uh doesn't seem to be an actual theme
going on
there oh that's a second ocean box okay
I can put the heart of The Stone Heart
of the Ocean heart of the
sea
mhm and then we got some
Stone different Stone the Cobblestone
can go into this Stone
box ooh I have Ender m uh-huh uh-huh
yeah this chest I kind of
understand oh powder stuff powdery o
okay if I'm looking for coal you know
where to find
it do I have anything for these
[Music]
chests sting by color is so smart I
guess well you could do that
wait okay let me put all the why do I
have so many trees tree saplings what
happens
[Music]
mhm I'm going to keep
these how's the Sheep doing you're doing
well I see the grass has grown but well
not the real grass you want some flowers
well give you a rose bush just don't
hurt yourself
pretty oh wait let me give me some
flowers here too
wow I want to put it like further
away can I put it there
[Music]
no nice a donkey in the grass and the
wheat field that's kind of aesthetic
isn't
it kind of beautiful
why do these things not grow at the same
Pace
yo be
careful danger Dangerous very very
dangerous
[Music]
careful yeah too much lesbians no don't
say that when we have a lot of unusual
viewers today who don't understand our
Insider joke don't say that it's
confusing to
them like what the [\h__\h] what's her
problem with the
lesbians we'll have to EXP explain it
maybe this will be part of the kfp 101
series one
day oh that's actually a good idea
that's one of the things that should be
made into a video someday to explain to
the newer
viewers what we're talking
about what's kata's problem with the
lesbians well I I I yeah I mean I do be
having problems with them like looking
for them years
ago and now it's like too many of them
first I look for them then there's too
many of
them it's just you
[Music]
know cow love yay make baby make baby
cow cow cow cow make baby make baby cow
cow oh oh no oh no close the door oh the
cat got out that's not a bad thing you
can have some of that too a
baby I wanted to kind of say that
yesterday I think in some situation
something like that but I was surrounded
by cute girls and it didn't feel
appropriate to say it around them but
when when it's just you and me Chad then
I feel like like I can maybe maybe
perhaps make a joke like
that not my favorite kind of joke though
generally I was like I don't want to
even think about that kind of joke it's
not funny but then crony did it and then
I was like okay crony does
it I might change my view on
it let's [\h__\h]
go
yeah a you make me so happy
gr does it need time and not only wheat
seeds I thought I thought it just needs
the seeds or do you need time as
well maybe it needs
time
okay I know it's not like I'm wasting it
because I have so many wheed seeds oh my
God it's the gift that keeps on
giving
nice [\h__\h] why am I so
tired you know those times where you
don't feel tired but you just yawn
constantly oh my god oh the blocks okay
we should do some
sorting I can't even look at this K we
come back please come back damn we got
so many
books oh wow wow wow
wow I think the potatoes we could throw
away or is there any use for the
poisonous potatoes like trading them is
that a thing you can trade I don't think
we'll get that kind of merchant
[Music]
crazy I think this whole place came from
a single block right it's actually like
amazing and it's all Patchwork literally
it's useless [\h__\h] sheer sheep okay
should we make a
sheer sheer
oh precious
[Music]
shears I have come to release you from
your
fluffiness you look so funny oh my God
it's been a while since I've seen a
sheep like this a Minecraft sheep never
really paid attention you look so funny
you look like a
poodle oh it looks
sad
bye-bye wait I got chisel quartz block
out of the
sheep it looks like the wool a very
fancy wo
cool nice I feel like that was a win
just kidding I know it wasn't it was
obviously
this maybe we can make a wool chest even
though I don't think we'll have enough
wool to really have a good reason for it
[Music]
but is there a glass
chest this is the glass chest
now yeah ah terra cotta I got some terra
cotta all right what you got what you
got give it to
me whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoo whoo
whoo whoa whoo whoo whoo wo whoo whoo
wo so much stuff
[Music]
sorry this is so boring now I'm sorry
I'm sorry but I got to do this
otherwise okay it's not so good that the
these chests are so far
away here is this goes here right this
goes here this goes
here this goes here
does this go here oh it does go here
whoa does this go here it does go here
okay cie all right all
right I I I feel it I'm starting to feel
it uh this does not go here this
probably goes wait this has wa we have
another ocean chest we got to put it
into the ocean
chest
mhm okay okay okay m coal I saw coal in
this one I think yeah yeah I remember
[Music]
oh do we have another wood chest by the
way here cuz the other one's filling up
quite a
bit doesn't look like there's another
wood chest so far you you you you you
you you you shall be the new wood chest
hi there you go or maybe actually maybe
we don't need it for now we can probably
put the wood into the other wood chest
it will
stack it will
stack okay um dirt where do I put the
dirt for now for now let's put the dirt
just here so I know where it
is I
[Music]
know how did chicken's doing grown grown
congratulations on your
growth
a they're
kissing can't be kissed and they made a
baby I forgot so it was a thing they can
make babies with each other it's not
just the
[Music]
eggs all
right kfp
is growing
well I'm such a farmer
wow damn any babies down here I can't
see oh there
there you guys are too greedy give the
cows the babies some
space I feel like I just heard an egg
plop let me inspect the egg
situation oh I heard it indeed I have an
ear for it you know
will we get
lucky will this be our lucky
ink I'm so excited by such simple things
it's been a while that Minecraft excited
me with such simple
[Laughter]
things wa not bad not
[Music]
bad 4K
V that is pretty good okay
[Applause]
[Music]
sortation like one chest I want to put
into
the into the uh chicken
coup or maybe in front of it or no here
is fine so we can put some some stuff
here to feed
them no should I should I make a beach
Ro field I don't know I'm not really
feeling the beach roots that
much not really feeling
them I think bread is just so easy I
mean it doesn't heal much but yeah yeah
no you guys are great good good good we
are on one
wavelength okay what now uh um wait one
one thing is here
mhm M concrete concrete uh not concrete
uh terra
cotta that's kind of rough alone it's
kind of rough having to do like all of
it but I don't have to do a I can just
like you know stop you know and just
wait until it's more people again but no
I want to make progress I want to make
progress and if I want to get a villager
I will have to mine a lot
that is just the
[Music]
reality solo Grind Time yeah but I feel
like I've already been very very helpful
to my own project of course feel like
I've I've done some good stuff I've made
some good stuff I may not be making like
Farm uh like U not not Farms like
automatic things like the cobblestone
stuff but I still think I'm I'm
doing something
good
right
s
s okay
no we're getting there we're getting
there we're getting
[Music]
there the blocks now damn we got free
blocks of diamonds one is nine diamonds
okay
actually the Final Phase isn't so bad
because I don't think we got blocks of
diamonds and blocks of gold and blocks
of emerald in any of the previous phases
I think it's just now
unless I miss
[Music]
jumping yeah only now right mhm post
game blocks so they added even more
blocks to the already possible blocks
that we could get great thanks game that
that's exactly what I
needed but no it's useful it's useful to
an
[Music]
extent this I could go
burn
[Music]
MH can put my bucket away I'm just going
to put it
here do you want to make a place for
villagers first before getting one now
that the house uh yeah guess I
could just a normal house will do
right
y okay wait let me just get rid of all
these things I still have and then we'll
make a little villager
house for those villagers we also need
more beds right and then o what was it
three villagers makes one Golem so
that's also a goal I I really want an
iron
farm I really want
one I really think we need it because
like what if we die and we lose all our
armor and
yeah you need a lot of villagers to do
that I think free yeah only free and if
we have two we can make the third one
so currently we're at zero
brain slow brain
slow
[Music]
oh nice o nice 50 obsidian so much
obsidian okay um what should I build it
with these never bricks look
nice what would a good
area I
think maybe over
there yeah let me get some Cobblestone
for the for the ground at least make a
big nether
portal I already could I guess although
I need fire though to light it I don't
know if we I have a way to light it do I
[Music]
villagers zombie villagers and zombie
okay so ah yeah yeah that's why yeah you
need you need enemies right yeah yeah
yeah
yeah so this so that the uh Golems have
something to
protect
hello you can make flint and steel but
you need Flint I think I have
Flint so probably flint and iron
together mix flint and
steel if you got gravel from the one
block you can keep breaking those until
one turns into Flint I think we legit
have Flint
though I think I've seen it in the
chests hi kitty
kitty yeah yeah can't you force sprid
villagers by having beds and give them f
food yeah yeah yeah I
mean uh getting more is no problem after
we have two of
them and then we can give them jobs
that's the end
[Music]
goal
okay I guess I'll already stop by making
it relatively big considering how we
could
then try to you
know get
more but then eventually do we have to M
I guess once we have a couple we can
make just a few for the
PPP and then put them into boats and
then move them
to the PPP location
[Music]
oh I don't have that many of these
blocks after all but it's
okay W you need a lot of beds that all
of this is no more problem I have Uno
sheep or what's sheep
in Spanish Spanish or Spanish
I think I can find a few more of these
blocks
right where could they
be where could they
be why do I hear a
helicopter o o OA
OA OA is
sheep but then it's not Uno right it's
un un OA
we should have more of those blocks no
way we don't only have this
few una a una
OA but that means it's a female sheep
what if it's a what if it's not a female
sheep
right are those the same
you know what I want to decorate it a
little bit actually I want to I want to
mix we'll do like one layer of those
bricks and then a different layer will
be different terra
cotta these are cool but why so dark why
so dark right why not go
brighter
pink don't know if I like pink but it
has to match with the
red or
[Music]
or maybe this this kind of fancy
right the brown brown can be
utilized in all kinds of
ways so I'm thinking bottom layer these
bricks of course also windows in between
don't fall down what the what the [\h__\h]
interior designer time no this is still
exterior though I'm an
architect okay so now I have more blocks
for the base
again what the what the
hell I want to do the same kind of like
door fan that's happening over there
that's really fancy the way that am I
think am built it right the way that am
did it the am
way how so
big terracota flow would be cool ah
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah maybe smoo one or pattern
one what do you think for now
[Music]
I guess I don't have that many of these
maybe each wall will be a different
pattern or at least I think I can do
this and then windows will replace some
of
them anyone joining tonight oh two of
them already joined good on cie joined
before so how do you do this would you
do a
door door door door door
door I think I saw it dark oak doors
yeah okay wa can do
this and how do I put the other
one at here maybe
no maybe from from
here yo but shouldn't the handles be
like together in the
[Music]
middle oh let's go let's go
pretty okay open the door let's get ah
glass I know where the glass is I made a
glass
box and
actually these colors we don't I guess I
used a lot on the basement floor that's
why we don't have so many of these M
could try to make a pattern somehow with
brown
colors that's gray but I I feel like
it's
brownish and uh above ooh I'm going to
go with this one ooh oh
we're going all out on this
one did we go to the ne already no no no
it's too early and I kind of want to
give them another chance to all be there
but if if it's too difficult then we
might just go in a in a group in a
smaller
group hey
nice
hey fancy
[Music]
blocks kind of want to make it all in
this
one
[Music]
wait at least like this layer but it
might be
difficult just got to make more windows
I
guess this one doesn't matter no one's
looking at that
side
uh oh oh that doesn't
match does that guys make does that make
you guys scared if I jump like that if I
jump around like that
I'm out of I'm out of I'm out of
glass
no and I'm out of this pretty terracota
but it's okay it's a work in
progress just a bit more and then I can
make the second
layer maybe how about there will be like
double windows
no you're hardcore veteran oh you got
the trust in
[Music]
me oh this is this is a little bit
scary it's going to be a pretty
house I think I hope I chose the colors
wisely nicely
yeah I don't know what to do about the
roof yet but it's it's probably going to
be um a not a pattern just a normal
nice
color maybe like
yellow looks pretty thank you will you
do like an exercise stream for your new
outfit in the future well the thing is
it's 2D and I already got good 3D going
for workout streams if I ever want to do
that again like ringfit or so oh no
don't go
away so but yeah I think I I wanted to
maybe do like a walking kind of
stream that I think still makes sense
with this outfit because walking is just
one
walking but anything more than that
speaking of I haven't been using my
treadmill the past couple days but I did
do other
stuff kind of so
H I'm not going to have enough blocks
for this to look nice am
I and I should go on the treadmill today
though M yeah this is not going to it's
not going to
work I'm going to do like some kind of
sand half blocks Sandstone half blocks
right that works like the ones I just
got rid of red Sandstone slabs that
actually looks
nice is nice
is can do checkerboard patter yeah even
for that though I don't
know can I make
half blocks of
this
not it's
okay smelt never rack oh is that how it
becomes these
breaks how does this work again yeah
okay
that's good enough for at least a
floor oh this looks nice
[Music]
actually careful
now putting so much effort into our one
block
world I'm I like how the others as well
have been trying to make things look
relatively
pretty it's not just all a big ugly mess
just because we want to rush through it
no
[Music]
no no that's a kiaha color hell yeah
orange it looks a little bit like it
could be a
carpet with that texture on
it thank you for the Super
[Music]
Chat okay that looks
decent haven't had like enemy panic in a
while have
we need some more enemies to bamboozle
us
[Music]
H where to put the
Torches
oh this is
fine okay let me eat this Yum Yum Yum
Yum Yum more good
time didn't you die earlier wellan but
it wasn't as panicky as
yesterday
right should I make the roof out out of
the same stuff or I think a lighter roof
would be nice like the the light sand uh
where where do we have
it I'm thinking
of
M I'm thinking of just normal
Sandstone I feel like oh maybe it's over
there in that light colors
chest sand
Sandstone mhm
can you out of sand you can make more
Sandstone right but also I need to smelt
this to make more
glass 50 that's good that's a good
amount I think we're done
with ah where is everything
ah here
I think I'm done with
these 2 by two sand makes Sandstone oh
really oh
okay well I'm
putting some sand in there for some more
glass don't want to waste all the coal
for it but
yeah okay okay okay okay okay let's jump
up here
M yeah
[Music]
I wish I wish that this pattern it was
upside down I want the bottom to be
smooth to be
honest I don't like this can we have a
smooth bottom
somehow maybe maybe I'll go for a
different Stone after all
smooth Sandstone I need a a stone cutter
for that though
right how do you make stone cutter
again stone
cutter oh this is manageable Stone
normal Stone normal
Stone how do you make this Stone again
you smelt it right smelt the cobblestone
I think so
mhm feel like we might have some more
Stone somewhere else but
whatever just need one I think and then
the
iron y yeah
yay stone
cutter wow it's like gelatine cutter
when do we put it m M maybe cuz the
Anvil is there we can put Stone clutter
there
too
no and I was going to put the Sandstone
slabs
no you want the full thing a ah but I
can can I I can combine them back
together
right oh
yeah
okay my chat died Let me refresh you
guys
nice
okay because it's chiseled you're not
going to do it
bro wait is that the right
thing I feel like it's not
[\h__\h] damn it wait it's okay I have
plenty of sand to play
with is it like uh this
Sandstone what do you mean cute
[Music]
button now let's choose the smooth one
right oh wait maybe it was a smooth one
cuz this one has a pattern I see it now
actually it may have been
fun s St s smell
what oh Al I make the sense Stone
first the smooth one and then I cut
it oh my God I was going to mess up
everything
[Music]
oh okay close close close
call what does this one look like from
[Music]
below oh that looks
okay but not smooth enough not smooth
enough
not
quite I guess this one's the same to cut
Sandstone
laab my butt
nose let's check out the let's check out
the chickens can't forget the
chickens 1 2 3 four egg
thanks that was a bad egg try
again try harder
make baby make baby
yeah W I need bab
boy I another bubble wof I want to see
the baby's face yes I it needs to see me
to know that I'm the
mummy who's the mommy now
huh
oh no way no way here have some
food first food in your life let's go
no don't follow me ah what you little
[\h__\h] no no no no no no no no no why did
you how did you
escape
chicken come here are you
stuck
Jimmy think he's stuck
he'll be even more stuck once he grows
up and is thicker then he'll be stuck
forever break the stairs I don't want to
break things why are you like this
Jimmy you just stay here for
now he belongs to the alpacas now he
thinks he's an alpaka
maybe uh wait got some
glass he will die that's okay I can make
more chickens
there's more where that came
from okay I do need more glass after
all
okay okay we got the smooth
Sandstone wait I made all the did I no
wait there's more right I think there's
was it that more GL uh sand
yeah a little bit more sand chisel you
can have that you can have
that and then let's cut
this smooth Sandstone slab or I better
be smooth as
[\h__\h] there you
[Music]
go uh I I got to jump on something
woohoo I'm on top of the
world should it have another layer of
those brakes though I think
yeah I think
yeah or or slabs actually maybe slabs of
these would be nice
oh my God I'm such an
artist I can make them half right do you
get more if you do this in in the the
the Stone
Cutters then if you do it in a normal
workbench yeah oh okay then smart
decision
nice okay now how am I going to climb up
huh like
so oh actually yeah no
yeah uh yeah let's make this these
Corners
first ah might not happen enough I might
not have enough but then I want to make
the ceiling bright wait wait okay how
about the inside of the SE oh yeah I
think cuz it it it finishes it closes
off nicely if you know this is the same
as above but not as thake but then the
inside and this is how we're going to
save
materials is going to be this this is no
this looks exactly like the chiseled
ones
bottom o thanks for the thingy thank you
you this isn't as smoooth as I thought
it would be and I need
more damn
it damn it stop the glass production
stop it no I couldn't stop it in
time do we have
[Music]
anymore wait smooth no it has to be
Sandstone maybe we still have
Sandstone doesn't have to be
sand what about here
no reliable Oak wooden plank rectangle
house
yeah you do you you do you my friend is
it going to look different actually if
[Music]
I oh you won't let me cut it but what if
I do it
here oh uhhuh when the sand when the
stone cutter becomes
useless this looks like it has the same
bottom and top surface it's just that
the edges are
different very much so such is the case
use quartz yeah it's okay I've been
working on this now so I'm I'm kind of
committed to the
Grind what am I doing I'm so hungry I
only had like some cereals so
far oh there was more sand okay there we
go now we
know this block looks like a command
block this
one what do you what are you
doing oh my
God
[Music]
quy n n n n n
n do you guys want some hay want some
hay make baby make baby
yeah nice nice baby give me the baby
yeah you like
[Music]
that how the chickens
doing
precious see how horny they get
wow is is hay like you know like those
um
those one of those horny
[Laughter]
Foods hey is an
aphrodesiac I didn't
no
egg give more give me more but we're
definitely increasing in size in
Workforce I love
it maybe for chickens
maybe this is not even so worth to be
careful maybe I should just like get rid
of all and then replant
all I don't know how do you guys do it
in this kind of
situation actually these are where these
even some of these look different to me
I don't know it's a light probably
destroy all clear first then plant you
just get rid of all of it even if only
some of it is grown
not all of
it buffer for
[Music]
reproduction no
no
sorry W screams at
everything time to fix some of those
spots I'm actually so happy right now
that I'm like I'm playing Minecraft and
I have things to do cuz that was my
issue like I wanted to play Minecraft
but I have nothing to do just like with
Hardcore Minecraft that was a blessing
as well in that sense as it gave us a
reason to play Minecraft again and now I
have given myth a reason to play
Minecraft
again which is so nice like I feel so
glad that even these mundane things like
creating a farm again from scratch like
I never thought I would do that again in
Minecraft yet here I
am here I am making a a farm from my own
hands it's so inspiring isn't
it yeah everything's done and then
things are automatic and then you know B
they done
that
H limited Minecraft events have been
wonderful right I I'll think of more and
I I do want to also do the Minecraft
server touring like just find another
server like the Disney one and then go
there and check it out with some people
who want to go
oh I'm so hungry [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] I'm
so hungry
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] I'm so hungry ah I could eat
some fruit I have some neck nectarines
is that how you say it in English
too and I have some cherries but the
cherries um I don't know if there's
still good ones in
there although it's not that one
nectarine isn't even
that
filling yeah they're in season then I
might go grab one in a
[Music]
minute all right I got to put some
yellow blocks
here two two Yellow
Block perfect I have exactly two
[Music]
or do I need two how does this wait if
the doors are closed how does it does it
look okay like
this I mean when the doors are closed it
doesn't look necessary but when the
doors are I feel like from the inside
yeah unless I make them towards the
inside I
guess make a pillar pillar
I'm not sure I I guess this is
fine oh damn it what have I
done it's not the same you guys are
probably trying to tell me it's not the
same but on the picture it looks like
the same on I it's probably cuz only the
top is the
same only the top is the same
D ah stop
that I think I'm just going to mine it
with the sword
because if I mine it as a pickaxe I
think it comes back as a full
block yeah I don't know man this
material is not doing me
favors it won't
oh hey a little little roof do we like
that maybe
maybe why can't we have glass slabs you
want the ceiling to be see
through N I can't reach
I feel like all in all the choices I've
made are beautiful but it's just going
to be difficult
to
like find the rest of what I
need damn it
okay okay okay okay maybe I'll go back
to mining a little bit and see if we
just happen to find more of the things
that I need like uh basically just more
sand Stone H I guess I could throw some
sand in there okay okay okay okay or do
I need that wait wait wait wait we had
sand do we also
have what it normal
Sandstone this is cut up
huh wasn't there more sand somewhere oh
here yo
okay ah so
ambitious keep a boat on you in case the
Villager
spawns yeah I mean yeah I could
melt and then
[Music]
cut Alla just Revisited your song for
you to sounded amazing
together that song is so
hyp yeah I was watching that stream for
quite a bit because I was you know
waiting for my turn so I could tell you
guys that it's my
turn yeah and she chose so many hello
project songs made me quite happy cuz I
am a big hello project fan and Aura is
too that's kind of you know what we get
along uh with
[Music]
about damn I'm I'm I'm making so much
nice progress
wow y alfit makes me want to ex but my
posters are on can you correct it for
me you know I'm not like into Yogo so I
but I guess this could be like a good
yoga instructor outfit
too how you guys doing
huh but my posters is always [\h__\h] too at
least like I mean I don't know if my
posters is [\h__\h] when like working out so
to say if you can call it working out
but my poster is just [\h__\h] in
general actually this this chicken once
we have the these chickens then the
bread might be not so important anymore
but it's good to have a of a little bit
of variety right but we can roast the
chicken we can roast the
chicken juicy roasted
chicken let's
go don't be scared KY this is just a
game this just a game
let
[Music]
me oh I have four DMS what's happening
oh
oh now uh W this looks so nice
[Music]
actually it do be looking nice I think
this does bother me
I yeah I
will place it
here yeah that's
okay yeah yeah yeah yeah I do like the
extended
roof maybe I could extend it everywhere
when I have more of these blocks I don't
know looks nice right w w rarely puts so
much effort into building structures
like even in the Ian
server it's a rare
[Music]
occasion I will never open the right one
on the getg
go the gas is going to love it whoa whoa
whoa whoa why why why why why why
it's not
burnable wait the sand well it's okay I
can cover the top of it I just wanted to
inside to look like that I just realized
I guess the sand will burn right is that
why you're saying that okay I can cover
it with something
else yeah and I mean the guest it won't
go for the house right like it will
normally it will aim for where people
are at and I will not be at the house it
won't just randomly shoot here
right welcome to the Villager House of
the future they'll feel so comfortable
here we need beds
too we be
okay wait do you think it actually will
not burn
oh oh
oh ah wait I can't put torches cuz uh
lower block half half half blocks so I
guess nothing will
spawn it's good it's good somebody said
I should do it so I I was going to do it
but wasn't necessary but around here
around here is
good yeah yeah yeah
yeah y y y okay that's a real creeper
that's not just the head of a creeper
uh first of all what the
[\h__\h] let him let him roam around let me
go get my
arrow when he's oh God oh God oh God oh
God okay okay okay yeah keep on going
over there yeah yeah yeah
yeah is he coming no right do I have
arrows though I do
okay got to make them
count oh damn it how do you how do you
cancel it scroll right ah
boat sudden
boat oh is that the same creeper or
different oh there's
two oh man
[Music]
okay well the other
one don't have
arrows use
[Music]
this damn
it yeah come down I'll give you the last
hit Yahoo didn't even touch him let's
sleep let's
sleeping
Glo oh they have bodies
now they got bodies hey I think this is
my first time sleep it's my first time
sleeping oh
damn yay my first sleep I did
that I did
that
okay nice
[Music]
ni okay white concrete would also be
decent but yeah
um shall we
mine I'll make another pickaxe though I
think sticks I
have let's mine a bit
that's what it's all
about okay I have sorted everything I
have built the house for an upcoming
villager we're back to
mining extend the basement yeah I I we
we
will at some
point ler
we we we we Japan Expo I'm coming for
you
hopefully got to learn some French for
it but I think from my from what I
remember I've been there many many years
ago and there were a lot of M
International people there from all
around Europe still probably majority
French people but that was a good amount
of non-french
people and yeah I think in places like
these French people will be so kind to
speak English right for for for just you
know for us for
example just use that French phrase you
always you saw how they like that they
will like that
they for sure W like that
one oh looting impaling what of all
these impaling books impaling does that
make sense on a sword maybe
maybe not the best thing you'd want
right
[Music]
it's only on trid Dan well
then well
then that sucks see it's kind of the
same tune but I changed it up a little
bit hope you like the the cafe
music so many Trident enchantments and
no Trident I really wonder how do you
get a trident in
this cuz like you can't I guess you
could create yourself an
ocean if you really wanted to you could
make your own ocean with a lot of water
and sand and then make it deep enough so
that drowns could
spawn or yeah there could be a drown
spawning from here but will will he have
a try Okay chances are like probably 0
point
[Music]
something could C maybe but if you
captured zombies and then put them into
water so they
drown
uh will they then like in the moment
they turn into a zombie does it then get
decided by gacha if they will carry a
trident and when they turn they might
have one or not no they need to spawn
[\h__\h] okay so no self make Trident so you
would have to make your own ocean or a a
Dr spawns here with a trident but that's
like
0.0 probably I think it's more easier to
make your own ocean to spawn you can do
that
right if you make a big body of
water should work
[Music]
right grass sea grass damn
it has to be a river biome
well but there's no such thing as like
set biomi here we have to make our own
biomi so I guess probably a trient farm
in the right place is there biomi
here I don't wait
normally I yeah here Minecraft
planes but that's probably maybe just
everywhere no matter how far out we
go I wonder I
wonder n it's too much effort there will
be no Trident I'm pretty
sure it's just too much
effort but those enchanted books can we
uh like break them and return them into
normal books at
least that be at least
something yeah okay well that's just
something let's go sorting
[Music]
could you trade for one an already
enchanted book I feel like no feel like
they don't take that
[Music]
[Applause]
this one looks like roses the red glaze
terra
[Music]
cotta welcome welcome member Yahoo
welcome to the party decay of
party
Dam I don't know where the Soul Sand
goes I'll just put it there for now
[Music]
uh thank you thank you for 11 months
yay let me sit on your new egg no I'm
the sitter I'm the eggit sitter hey
don't take my
job can I just put the bones here I
don't know and spider web
uh I feel like leather armor can you
make lever armor back into lever then
I'll do that no then I'll throw it away
I don't I mean what the hell are we
going to
do move
[Music]
it bye
trash this outfit I can't believe
there's still so much fan out going on
like normally with a new outfit okay
there's like a little bit of like an
influx of fan art and then it will cool
down it will chill down but it hasn't
been chilling
down hasn't been Bing chilling at all
and I mean that's that's nice you know
it's really
delightful but like I'm so unexpected I
didn't expect that much and it's like
really good
stuff I'm so happy so much new thumbnail
material Thank You artist thank you
blessed be the
[Music]
artists yeah it's so popular to draw the
Wawa let's go let's
go I think these ones you can trade but
really depends on how many Merchants
we're actually going to end up with if
we're ever going to end up with any of
them
wait I made a glass did I make a glass
CH yeah but I I took the glass again
didn't
I
just
[Music]
m there you are it's so good that you're
always in the corner
so
good who wants this one who wants it who
wants it fight for it fight fight fight
here small one I'm so I'm
so
so what's the word what does benevolent
mean oh babies oh oh oh wo wo wo chill
chill oh so okay so that might have
actually been the word I was looking
for
kind gracious okay that was what that
was what I was looking
for happy birthday
chicken wait are you the are You the One
Stop
panicking
okay mhm
no okay you win some you lose some oh
you want back
in
a what a well behaved little
[Music]
chicken good chicken it has manners it
knows rules
[Music]
okay back to mining or there's actually
I probably
should not going to be mining for long
with this although I would hope that
some things would stack you
know I I'll mine I'll I'll sort one more
time
yeah
okay I don't remember was it did we
yesterday I remember asking or like am
was asking if you put a second chest
there if it will like split into the
other chest too and I think the answer
was no
right no one wore a diary for yesterday
Nor today yeah no it's not
happening if maybe if I I kind of get
them all together in one big group and
we kind of end at the end I'll try to
remember next time to tell them but at
this point it might not make any sense
to force them to to write Diaries it's
okay it's okay I I have an overview it's
really just like for them honestly but
if they yeah I don't know they'll be
lost they'll be lost lost little
sheep without the Diaries but it's
okay it's going to be fun F I don't even
have my own book yet yeah cuz I was
going to have you know have them have
them at least have them have them have
them have
them was the chest for these things
here
no but I got this oh wait wrong chest
wa what's with
this this is the one yeah this is what I
was looking
for
um
oh are you guys not bored by me why you
guys still here I'm so surprised you
guys are still here
thank
you are you just waiting for other
people to pop in not sure if it's going
to happen to be
honest go
here you love me you here from
me love
[Music]
kfp and you're enjoying the Minecraft
comeback
chilling while browsing what are you
browsing my friend
hasht
oh
[Music]
Miracle wait why did it cuz he exploded
in water oh my God it's as if we as if
I'm
like planned that like as if she knew ah
even if a creeper spawns like nothing
will happen for sure she didn't know for
sure she was not taking that into
consideration but
wow I thought this would
explode oh thank
God I was so terrified just
now I was so scared I didn't want to fix
it I didn't want to have to fix it
wow the AR way so it was good that we
put water there so that it
flows
genius genius genius
genius ah you little
[\h__\h] it's [\h__\h]
trolling
me oh
[Music]
[\h__\h] it really looks like it's trolling
me with that
behavior oh my God there's so many like
living things spawning right now ah
[\h__\h] let me out let
me
okay can you get out
you're free to you're free to
walk you're free to walk yeah yeah yeah
you're not in police
custody don't
worry he's thinking slowly like where
the [\h__\h] am I where is my family where
is my ocean where is my ice is this the
world
in 100 years or what
all the ice has melted all the like
floor is gone the oceans have become
smaller and smaller and became this
puddle he got isite no he he traveled in
time kitty cat can you get
out
go oh I'm so
benevolent post-apocalyptic future yeah
this is preparing us for what might
be can the Bear kill other it will only
be ah no I saw it killing a fox so and
that was actually
welcome I welcome
that cuz I saw animals like foxes and
wolves kill other farm animals before
yesterday or so and now
it's that was not good we don't want
that to happen again another cat yes
protect us from the creepers please do
it
protect cat
protect cat eat a snake but cat also
protect and Cat sometimes attack when
she
protect oh for a moment I thought you
were drowned but no you're just a desert
uh zombie
[Music]
huh I don't know for a moment I thought
maybe we should capture the zombies too
for the PPP in the future or no they
will just spawn on their own right in a
dark
place it's okay
love the new outfit thank you box is
full it's okay I'm hoping for it to just
stack at least to some
[Applause]
extent give it some
time only ones you might capture would
be zombie villagers if any
eh but I didn't understand that sentence
cuz my brain is not
not matching your
speed expand the hopper trans no no no
no no no I am not capable of such things
if anything Amma has to do
that I'm not going to [\h__\h] this up now
I'm not going to make
this messy
whoa oh nice Easy
E mhm so do we have
something oh see it do be stacking it do
be stacking here and
there that's it that's
it there we go we stacked it a bit it
um let me at least take the Terra Cotta
cuz I know where it
goes I know where that
goes and this one I can take and this
one
yeah this pretty chill I'm
chilling having a good time right now
just relaxing right now ignoring my
Hunger
but I'm
[Music]
good MH oce second ocean
chest ah ah ah ah
second ocean
chest
pumpkin how do you make pumpking p
pumpkin pumpkin soup is it just pumpkin
in the bowl pumpkin pumpkin a pumpkin
pie sugar and X SE like where the [\h__\h]
are we going to get sugar from we have
never seen sugar cane before I think
like [\h__\h] these
pumpkins no need for them but I'll put
it
there who hurt the
chicken who heard the
chicken
what
huh was it the bear could could have
been the
bear
H bear can't enter doors
right sus could it been a could it have
been this
cat no right it wouldn't do such a thing
such a heinous
crime but it's not a normal cat that one
cat is not a normal cat right it's
a special desert cat it might have done
it so sorry guys I have to report to you
that one chicken that was outside that
we were hoping for to come back at some
point it died sorry for the bad news but
here's some good news new
chickens
Yahoo can we have a moment of chicken
silence or do you just guys just can't
stop clucking huh can't stop clucking
and can't
stop well that's you know it's a city in
Austria so um maybe they're just going
there oh I'm out of seats there you
go the chat sumary said Jimmy
suffocated let's just say that that's
what happened yeah yeah yeah
yeah Love Love Is in the Air Love is in
the coop swoopy [\h__\h] baby is out of the
T Yum Yum Yum Yum
[Music]
Yum nice these things look like chickens
to me sometimes when I and I just walk
by oh
it's not even red thanks to the pinky
unknown thank you friend
friend could it be a
friend it is
possible and
broke so many things to work
with now I'm wondering how did the how
did smoke do it in 12 to 15 hours I
guess they just got everything they need
in in the first phases um like without
cycling into what the state where we are
now and then Protected Their animals and
all that and Protected Their villagers
without having them
die I suppose
[Music]
I think they had a plan and played some
solo before they were speed running
maybe
Gamers it's possible to beat the Ender
Dragon without armor to which is very
risky yeah I mean I don't think we need
like fullon enchanted diamond armor but
if we can get that that would be great
but I would also just go in there with
like half iron half diamond armor to be
honest I
would if things are dire
[Music]
where the [\h__\h] did the honey go I feel
like there was some honey somewhere
here maybe
there was never ever
honey po
po you know what I'll put the honey
block into the food
[Music]
chest mhm
don't need the jombie
flish oh let me put the
chicken here for now later if we have
more we can we can cook
it roasted chicken let's
go where was Flint
Flint stone St I can put this
here put this
here here's that stupid honey block I'm
going to put you into the food chest
now I saw Flint
somewhere maybe it has been moved
Ena can make infinite wor of chicken
farm if she can then she she's welcome
to do it any kind of farm to make these
processes easier for
us
[Music]
anything maybe the coal where is the
coal what I I'm going put it here for
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
sake ah we make we got to make
another free was it free
to and na a pickaxe guys is am I am I
losing more iron than I'm making
or no right no also sometimes we get
blocks like
these iron farm
doco
please I don't think so you don't think
[Music]
so yeah I blew a lot of it on the Anvil
and that was
like iron that we accumulated for a long
time but I think it was good anyway
I'll get more
yeah oh not you again it's always things
I don't
need that's
cheating oh that is Che that's
cheating stop doing
that what the [\h__\h] is that Moon Sun is
it uh eclipse
no Kiara
collap you you don't want to fight me
HH come here what it's so interesting I
didn't notice ever that it turns like
kind of red when it's attacking
it's like you know the veins when
somebody gets really angry and their
face gets red and then like in anime or
so they will draw their veins also
really red and then their whole face is
covered in like red and
veins that's what that looks like where
did it
go fight
me yeah yeah
yeah I'm not going to go underneath just
for that but let me go grab some food
boat his ass the
Vex can you put that one in a boat
too fascinating boat
mechanics
yeah
what no way
we don't need any more
obsidian this looks good ooh Golden
Apple
yeah boats solve a lot of problems yeah
but no it just kind of pushes the
problem
away hey hey yo hey yo hey yo why is it
the same one so several so many times in
a
row no boat is just like you you put a
problem in there it's not solved it's
just
like like paused it's a paused
problem
lag maybe how many of those are in here
or did H did they not they just break
right
[Music]
put him in a boat and kill it while it's
defenseless it's not even that strong
it's just because it flies around but it
only needs like two or three hits
actually not a big
deal silk touch at this rate with so
many books I wouldn't be surprised if we
get a silk touch
B but wouldn't even be really worth it
why do we need the ice why why would we
want to go out of our way to mine the
ice like that we won't need
it what's happening why is it the same
block over and over
[Music]
again water water
I didn't notice I didn't even
notice oh all righty
[Music]
using the pickaxe for
dirt but switching in between is so
annoying I don't want
[Music]
to oh hey yo sweeping Edge free sweeping
Edge
too
W matching
books wait if you combine you have
swipping Edge five
right swipping Edge I think is not the
worst it can be fun can be helpful a
little bit is that the the one that
gives you like knockback or is that the
one that kind of gives you more of an
AOE attack so to say cuz the reach is
bigger so how is it
ah 2 plus three is not five in Minecraft
okay that's fine three is Max okay we
can just give someone a two spping Edge
and somebody gets a free spping Edge
it's the wide swing
right spping Edge is sword AOE yeah yeah
yeah yeah okay that's cool that's cool
don't need to aim so
hard don't need to
be a hard aimer aim hard
[Music]
what do we got today on the
menu I
think I'm not going to get really far
here on my
[Laughter]
own efficiency doco
[Music]
oops
see you doing
great at least I mean I definitely have
been making progress in terms of like
food
sources Merchant House is ready to
go good
stuff is there any topics to talk about
what could I talk about
make this a little bit less
mundane
socer I mentioned it yesterday already I
think a little bit in the Super Chat
reading tomorrow well maybe I'll even do
a watch along for tomorrow depends on
how yeah but it's 900 p.m. it's kind of
and how long do those normally take like
it can take two to 3 hours right
[Music]
if I watch it it starts at 9:00 p.m. it
could be finished at
like 11: to midnight and then I could
start a Minecraft
stream what I don't
know I want to see when cie
plans what what
what that'll be too late no starting at
midnight I mean I don't have to play for
6 hours I could do like a 2our 3our
session with maybe gooa or so whoever
can show
up but I don't know we don't have to
watch every one of them I'm I'm not like
I don't feel the need to watch it
all slime block I know it doesn't go
there but you
know what else do I have I
have yeah I'm I I was just hoping that
we would finish this before the next
Austria
match that's my goal and that's why
tomorrow we shall go to the
ne maybe maybe one more thing I could do
today is build the nether portal already
or at least a space for the nether
portal I will now make little
pform let me make it slabs so nothing
can spawn on it
Euro yeah yeah I want to watch the
Eurovision EUR
European football
soccer championship that's happening now
but only the Austria
matches I want to do it as a stream
watch along
[Music]
around here should be
okay too bad that I don't like football
well I'm not like a big fan I'm not a
fan at all but um I think
still it could be
fun we can just
is that what gooa Oro had
on yeah I'm not a fan of soccer football
whatever you want to call it either this
is not like a thing
like GIF and
GIF yeah not a big fan
but you
know it's it's different you know when
it's your own country you you suddenly
are a little bit interested perhaps you
know it's just a nice opportunity to
have like a chatting stream as well and
you guys don't turn down my chatting
streams do
you you like those I know you
do I'm going to run out d
damage
no
okay no
don't want
it if La is there we will be there yeah
in the end you know whatever I stream
I'm never forcing you guys to watch it
if there's something you might not like
I don't know it is what it
is it is what it is we're just going to
do one and see how it goes no no
complaints no complaints I accept no
complaints wait I have another damn
it I did have another one
you had a choice well depends on how you
see it you know it's like a class half
empty half full kind of thing you
know it's more a Time problem well I
mean that's just but it's just my usual
streaming time pretty
much you
know so can't do anything about it
except I will I will do
it I will do
it is that
a you guys see that dot I think that's a
bee I see the wings flapping a little
bit and I see like some brown and I
think I see a Yello is thing going
on oh man that's so depressing like
imagine being a
bee and just flying into nothingness and
you're looking for you know
honey or anything looking for other bees
you find nothing you should have just
stayed on our Island
man should have just
stayed this is
Paradise I mean compared to the rest of
the world it
is rest of the world in Minecraft I mean
on this server cuz the rest of the world
is only
blue so much blue the bee might be
thinking it became a fish maybe the
things is under
water too real you might want torches I
thought nothing spawns on slabs that are
put
on the bottom part was it the bottom
part I think oh no this is the top a
damn
it this is the top isn't
it
okay no problem can do can
do
scoobydoo what's your favorite seasoning
on
chicken well I feel like normally I
prefer to have chicken that's like in
some kind of
sauce so rather than seasoning it's more
like what sauce I prefer I would
say I know more like light
creamy creams rather than like tomato
based creams or so I think my those are
fine too
but lemon lemon stuff is also great but
I feel like every time I make it it's
rather weak even though put so much
lemon lemon in there well last time I
made like a lemon soup uh sauce it was
pretty good pretty good actually turned
out pretty
decent
M but still could have maybe been a bit
more lemony just just a bit
more I a fan of hot wings no cuz I
people call me hot wings sometimes s but
ooh fire charge let's go but
I can't eat spicy
food no spicy food for waa I know it's
so
lame I know but I think my
tolerance is maybe a little bit higher
than I thought it was because oh hello
oh no oh no we're not [\h__\h] with you
today no no um I remember yeah my mom
who has a supposedly a high to of spicy
food you know I think I told you about
it when I ate something and then she had
bites of it too and she was like oh yeah
this is spicy and I'm like oh oh you
think it's spicy
okay not just
me but I guess like it may be spicy but
she also enjoys
it but I think she has definitely a
higher spice tolerance than me cuz she's
been eating spicy food for a longer time
in her life than me
some people love the pain I just don't
like it when like the spice makes me
feel like you know it's just the food
will feel even hotter than it already is
and like makes you makes you feel
like like everything's burning I don't
like that how can you like that I don't
get it how is that
Pleasant how is that
Pleasant I want what's the point yeah
like a little bit it's okay but like to
the when when it's like little little
bit tingly you
know these are the ones that you place
right these are the ones that you don't
that you throw think so yeah um but if
it's a little bit Tink tingly then
okay but
like anything past that it's like why
why are
you but I guess like maybe you really
don't feel it like that anymore when
you're really used to it then it's not
suffering anymore oh know I can't guys
tell me people have high spice tolerance
does that does when you eat spicy things
you just don't feel it anymore or
what that's why you need more and more
spicy
things yeah couldn't eat a red chili at
all we can still feel it I feel it but I
enjoy it what the [\h__\h] masochist
yeah you bear it my Korean Bros with the
spicy
noodles it hurts good you know I like
pain when it comes to like massages and
so on but I can't relate when it comes
to uh
food I don't like every kind of
pain just certain types of
pain
H interesting Des
I don't like pain and
massages weak but I feel like when you
start getting massages eventually you'll
want them to be stronger and stronger
cuz you're I feel like this is I guess
it is like with the the spiciness
but you'll feel
unsatisfied I think
wait that's a [\h__\h] block of
iron whoa do we have more of these
somewhere I didn't realize we had we
have did that also did that also Spawn
from oh
my that's good that's very good um
H H freaking block of iron more of these
please more I want
more quartz pillar no no more no more in
here
wait wasn't there more dirt yeah oh can
only take a
few not so short on iron after all well
yeah I mean it's nine nine right they're
all the same these kind of blocks
they're all nine n n n
nine why are you saying no are you
saying no it's not
nine in German it's nine is no you're
giving me confusing Vibes again chat
thank you for the membership thank
you uh think waa think oh why is that in
there I'll take it I'll take it what is
this in there
[Music]
oh where did we put that I'll put it
here
though
wait gifted membership thank you shear
the Sheep
ah yes oh my
God sheepy Shippy
CH no grass here yet
huh but a kitty cat has
been uh chilling with you huh oh three
pieces of wool thank you I feel like
last time it was just
one or did I already have two pieces of
wool in my inventory just
now hey
yo Tipp T
taaa memberships thank you for the gift
D you guys are so benevolent just like
[Music]
me yay
okay
W you can sort after all I'm getting
over my sorting issues finally sorting
things out with my sorting issues wow
wow wow wow wow wow
hello please go somewhere else
hey protect me polar bear do something
ah oh oh no oh that's that's so bad that
is so bad that is so bad that is so bad
that is so
bad y I hurt the bear oh it's actually
chilling there
still it's it forgave my
my my actions just for a little bit hey
there's so many
eggs but when I go back it'll probably
be mad again I'm
scared I can do it I don't have that
many valuable things out here anyway
[Music]
but let me just get back to full
health will attack
me gifts gifts gifts thank you thank you
nice eggs nice eggs nice nice eggs nice
eggs nice eggs eggs eggs eggs eggs
eggs oh oh okay polar bear you don't
care oh you don't oh thank you for
forgiving me so so
sweet okay wait I was going to do uh I
made the I extended the underground okay
you know what one more
thing m
one more
thing and then one more thing and then
one more thing and then one more
thing I'll try to make it look somewhat
cool I think maybe it's okay to put it
like behind this house for example what
do you
think let me get
some stones
for the
ground
M maybe I can build it on the bottom
slab This
Time come on waa you can do
it B ships yay you guys have been so
sweet again wait this is uh huh
wait oh this is already a bottom slab he
y I thought it was a top
one then it doesn't need torches but I'm
still going to put them there I guess
because it looks nice if it's lit
up that's a top oh okay well I'm going
to put torches
anyway we
good those are tops slap Dam I might
join the trend what trend the trend to
join my membership he yeah yeah come on
come on become a chicken don't worry it
may not sound like a really like
respectful like cool animal to be like
other animals like I don't know tiger or
so no it may not be as cool as that but
thanks for the membership oh 10 of them
oh oh thank you but you guys can evolve
into hybrid
phoenixes and you know other people's
perception of chickens may be you know
small unimportant but think about how
much chicken we
eat in the world every
day very valuable we should we should
think of things that we make much use of
more
valuable
valuably Cows as well all those kind of
animal we should trade them
better otherwise one day when they will
take over the world hi B oh my God
there's several
ones all those dots down there are bees
now when chickens take over the world
and we weren't nice to
them the pecking order will be different
then bang for the memberships oh my God
what's happening
guys it's one of those moments huh you
having a
phase are you having one of those phases
it's not a phas mom okay
okay pecking order
yeah nice gifts Christmas it's
Christmas or maybe it's early birthday
gifts my birthday is soon so I decided
what to do
actually for my birthday because so my
my birthday frd live once again it's not
being uh streamed on time sadly it's
going to be more of an anniversary
live um but the whole summer I'll be
like super super super busy with all
kinds of things so rather than you
know
[Music]
um like trying to get a whole another
life going and commissioning kind of ubu
to help me put it together and all that
no I'm not going to do that um cuz the
anniversary life is already costing me a
lot of money to like put together
things um
but yeah monthly wallpaper check it out
we're also having weekly membership
streams right now it's watch along
alongs but still it's pretty cool
normally it's not always watchong it's
just now for bakar but anyway yeah so uh
one thing I've never done
before actually and a trend that I have
been noticing for the past year year or
so that I think I really uh like
is
how uh members have been doing like
these Koke streams where other members
sent in pre-recorded ones
right pre-recorded uh versions of
themselves singing a song and I think
that's really
cool and I really like the idea of it
yeah so I want to do one of
those so I'll probably do I'll be in
Japan for this and that's
yeah that's why streaming times may be a
little bit weird but we'll see I'm I'm
planning to do a
countdown now which countdown am I
choosing not Japanese countdown
because uh I won't be able to use the
studio at
midnight so I'm going to do I think I
was planning to do ES
T was
I was I um no maybe not I'm not sure
some kind of countdown is
happening
uh for my birthday I'm choosing some
random
time and for the countdown I going to do
Callins as well and then the other thing
will be the Koke in a separate stream
which is probably uh in jst that will be
the seventh already the countdown will
be on the sixth in
jst
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah or should I do this
[Music]
Thea it's it will be archived yeah yeah
yeah I I made a whole list of songs like
I think it was like 50 songs or 60 songs
or so I made that yesterday and I sent
it to members to
choose songs of their
Ling I basically invited all of ID and
all of
Ian uh not all of them will participate
I think but like almost all of them
[Music]
maybe Dam
it and yeah they will pre-record it and
I'll sing live to the video that they
sent
me thanks for the memberships I think
it'll be fun cuz I never did that before
and that way you can have like so so
many members in your stream without them
having to make the time to actually be
there this stream is not pre-recorded
no oh perfect isn't this nice so
far okay wait let me get the obsidian to
think
about I know how how much
space where is the obsidian
here that means no Ana I think there
might be Ana but it doesn't count
because uh it's pre-recorded so it's not
really oh
creeper what the
[\h__\h]
bro bro at least I didn't
die oh I need torches run away hey y'
chests the chests not the chests oh oh
oh no this place is fine I
think
um put the
Torches and I should maybe just
sleep you might want to explain the any
your joke well do you need an
explanation just watch the the newest
video not short not stream the newest
video video that I put up on my
channel that's all you need to
know no did I lose one piece of
stair come
[Music]
on okay I'll fix it at some point
TDR there's a joke that we hate each
other it's really funny because we never
collab I don't even want to expl explain
it
man it's such a a difficult long
explanation explaining a joke kills the
joke too yeah but we don't want any
misunderstandings but I think you know
if I just say we say we hate each other
but we don't that's all you need to
know and we never
collab and and like originally it wasn't
on purpose but at this point it's on
purpose that we don't collab at least
not oneon-one at least not oneon-one
that's the
point
so we have so much obsidian we're going
to make it nice and
big although guess we have to like jump
in here
[Music]
like this
big and then I'll surround it with these
blocks wow gives off some light too
bye-bye I
oh
[Music]
no
yeah no
yeah a ah
no y
pro pro
gamer now I feel like the stairs should
we we'll need end up needing more space
uh more stairs if I make it wider
but I think it should have one more
block around
it right so it's not like all too close
close and tight so how
about how about this one cuz I haven't
used it
yet
yeah I I see the vision do you guys see
it
[Music]
too maybe for now we'll play sit like
this and then the sides
H maybe no need for the sides unless I
find more of those
blocks
yeah looking
[Music]
good looks so cool right I mean it could
be even cooler but it's already more
effort than than basic NE portals
[Music]
mhm incredible red pathway red
paway from where from where though from
where Alo then I would have to replace
this floor again I don't like that
idea are these top slabs that means on
top of it I I could put carpet right if
we ever get that much wool speaking of
wool
speaking of
wool that's just one I think I did have
wool in my
inventory before
that snip snip snippity snip
[Music]
mhm wait where did I put the wool did I
make a wool chest over on the other side
probably now with a fire
charge can I not already turn it
on let me see
w
w w cool I'm not going to go in though
I'm not going to go
in not going in just preparing looks
cool with shaders hell yeah I'm proud of
my accomplishments I love
Minecraft I love Minecraft oh so it uses
it up okay cool cool cool that's that's
a good way to use it I think
M oh no wait pick it up let's put that
in the chest over there can you go back
I missed my
screens wait I I'll take it in front you
can wait you can have me as part of
it I also took one
got
it already more advanced than the one in
the Ian server no no the one in the Ian
server the old one it has like you know
it's not as big but it has the the the
surroundings of it are
nice it goes hard you could make gold
helmets oh yeah let me prepare the gold
helmets
M yeah yeah yeah wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait what are we I asked this
question today already and I don't think
I saw the answer uh what are we going to
really be looking for that would help
us helmets or
shoes shoes
maybe blaze rods for ah for the for what
for the
huh for the eyes oh you needed to you
need blaze rods to combine them oh okay
okay that means we have need a fortress
ooh that I mean actually do we need it
there's several blazes spawn who have
spawned so far we only need four wait
did they ever drop a blaze rod though
did they ever oh we have four how many
for an
[Music]
ie Eye of Ender eh do you not make it
here 12 one rod can make
two
oh oh yeah we could we could Farm
Enderman in in there too yeah one Blaze
Rod gives two blaze
powder why does it not show up though
my
what did I never touch this before
ah one two did we have another one
elsewhere look we
did yeah one more one more only one easy
easy easy cuz down there I if you guys
didn't see the stream yesterday U then
you wouldn't know but let me show you
the situation here is that here one 2
three four over there's another one
missing so we only need four to make
this
work one block one block beaten
already should I make some
stairs should I should should I make
some
stairs normally normally I'm fine
though normally I'm
[Music]
fine do we have more ender eyes I feel
like we might have no maybe not
actually wait I was going to make
something um shoes or shoes or or
helmets it's this is four pieces and the
helmet is five oh I mean we don't need
to save on gold helmet okay yeah they
look
fancy 1 2 3
4 okay let me put them into the chest
that's over
there
uh do we have more torches somewhere
oh wait I think I put
torches
somewhere sorry just picking random
things right
now to put them kind of
together
uh ah here okay what was I going to do
what was I going to do bra Brain Brain
Brain
Brain ah wool chest I was looking for
the wool chest I was looking for the
wool
chest wool chest wool chest
here
five yaho
maybe I wonder one bed needs free we
have free beds already I need one more
wool right to make beds for everybody oh
my God can I really is it okay for me to
do so many things
to oh there were things in here already
some fancy things why are they back here
why are you is somebody hiding this does
this belong to somebody one of the
girls this is five helmets for us
yay secret
stash looks cool to place them next to
each other
fire fire
[Music]
can you believe what I'm doing right now
oh my God as if it
matters doesn't but it matters for the
beauty
contest which I will
win W it looks so much
nicer one three 1 2 three 2 three two
three
two
three must be corrected at some point wa
this
one's I'll fix it
eventually one two three
why am I doing this why am I doing this
why am I doing
this
WOW hey I'm kind of getting into this
I'm kind of liking it when things are
neat I'm kind of liking it m spicy
[Music]
okay it's the brain worms really
good what what you can put torch on top
of fence yeah yeah I know I know I know
but it shouldn't be on top of the fence
to continue this pattern you know it's
got to be on the
ground okay nice nice nice nice nice
nice I want to take another picture it
looks better
now I look so small when I do
that this looks good aesthetically
pleasing let's take a picture of the
other thing we
made I'll update the the girls in the
chat and show them hey I made this just
so you know what it's
[Music]
for
this Chee
W I have no diary w w w kind of gave up
on Diary okay I could make one but I'm
going to tell them with screenshots in
on this looks
good hey what the [\h__\h] is wrong with
you I'm going to tell them with
screenshots it'll look nice I don't need
a diary it's okay I give up would have
been nice was funny as a joke on the
first day on on the second I guess when
I read
it a golden sea yeah you know wheat
fields and sunflower fields any kind of
like Fields they're so aesthetically
pleasing really aren't
they such a beautiful thing beautiful
sight to behold
this always feels like I'm making music
cuz the beat the rhythm of
this you could totally like use this and
make a song out of
it use this as like the the top line for
a song The Melody
you jam to
it beat does go hard actually ooh it
goes hard EDM EDM EDM
EDM so dumb we're so dumb I'm having a
good time with you guys though I'm glad
I stayed longer for you know T time with
my
chat The Stomping sounds The Stomping
sounds are
the of my
dreams ah the Sheep let's take a picture
of no I didn't take a I should
I should have taken a picture when it
was all gold maybe I'll force it to grow
but or we can take a picture of both at
the same
time kind of hard to see let me get rid
of this
tree chop chop time is up for you
just have patience that took so long and
even then that one piece of seeds didn't
want to
grow freaking
Rude the tree can go back here
afterwards but for now I just wanted to
be empty for the sake of the
picture uh actually the wool chest could
be here right let me take that wool and
take a chest you know I like when things
are uh in the place where it's a
associated
with don't you love that
too this one's
empty yeah yeah you having a great time
too yay you can take a screenshot from
the VA yeah but it's not shd it's not
captured in
4k this one I mean yeah maybe it should
be up here too
okay oh it's already wow you grow your
hair fast W teach me your your secret
hey oh wait this time it was
free oh is it because you ate grass or
what wao so sometimes it is free
oh secret is grass damn we learned so
much about hay and wheat wheat being
like
aphrodisiac and grass is like it's all
in front of us guys it's all in front of
our eyes why do we ignore the things
right in front of us why do we go for
expensive things to make our hair grow
and and expensive aphrodesia ex like
those what what is it clams or
whatever but it's right
there oh my
God you really don't want to be naked do
you understandable have a nice day
[Music]
okay did I take a picture yet I
forgot I didn't did I I
didn't oh the shears can go back in
there too actually M I feel actually I
feel so organized and proud
heyo hey
sheep goes
hard sheep do be going hard I'm not even
bothered by this being on different
levels are you guys bothered by it the
only thing that bothers me is maybe that
and
[Music]
then although that's a different [\h__\h] it
fell down
huh is that worse no oh it's up
there give me give me
huh pick it
up there we
go only goes back when you really When I
Look Away I would believe you
it doesn't work I've waited I've given
you time oh but the grass already grew
back
oh
W close one close one close one it
worked it worked
believe believe only two this time
H
interesting right let me make some
[Music]
beds push the Sheep around ah give it
time give it
time oh oh oh
oh
oh oh oh oh
oh oh so [\h__\h]
ready let's go so what is is there any
reason to go into The
Nether is there any reason to even
go not really
no never right no maybe maybe if I'm
really bored and the others just don't
have time to do the finale yet if it
like for some reason delays a
lot no for potions yeah like uh NE warts
right well okay we might want to do
potions yeah yeah yeah
yeah okay never WS will be something we
want content yeah
yeah pigling gotcha what do they give
you lava for food a yeah buckets of lava
that's I forgot about that we don't have
to use all that coal what the
[\h__\h] I
fot now if we don't want more lava we
can just always go back or into The
Nether is this this does work
does this
work will it work lava limited n we're
going to the
nether but it uses up iron or the the
bucket never disappears
right the
bucket it will vanish as it Cooks yeah
the lava
right okay [\h__\h] stage okay
[Music]
am doing so many
things Wow
Bow wobo woo wowow
woo wow makes you go
wow good
could put some fancy enchantments on it
too yeah I'll take a picture of that
because maybe they want to see that we
got a [\h__\h] ton of books
today uh ah
I like the
word it's just a cute word sorry
[Music]
villager house wow wow so
cozy why is the Villager house better
than our no not better I think this is
really creative but the inside is kind
of messy what are these Soul sand blocks
doing there you know actually it's not
better than the Villager house that I
made no it's not I take back what I
wanted to say cuz I was
wrong was very
wrong
nice feel like this should be
can it be on the Soul Sand the girkin
[Music]
no
oh how to make trapo or so
uh how what should I put it on the what
the girin
pickle in in uh German is
gu gu in particular vinegar vinegar
pickle but you write it g u r k
e why do we put it on top of I guess
we'll
just put it there oh well
so we got
beds we got so many cool things wait
I'll take a picture of the
beds
nice anything else that's of important
let me take a picture of the inside of
the chest
maybe uh
just have to dye the beds
[Music]
next purple pink well yeah Ena
cie uh what else could I
make black no we I don't need black I
mean black could also be Cali but
no or or or wa we have sunflower
sunflower for
am right somehow I can make yellow dye I
think uh an orange we have no orange
flowers I
[Music]
think lapis for Goa yeah that works that
works how to make die
again okay I can make a yellow dye but
wait but I already made the bed don't
you have to can you dye it when it's
already a
bed red and yellow is orange oh let's
go you can to do it after oh my god
let's go okay um
bread like got this one for
example and then this and
thisy
Su oh I'm so delighted I'm so delighted
I'm making everything bra
oh make it nice color
yellow
[Music]
blue
pink that's kind of a magenta oh well
purple
and
orange it's myth fets myth fets and they
they will all be next to each other
[Music]
okay I would like to
be sandwich between all of them
please all of
them thank
you where did the girkin go what the
[\h__\h] here
[Music]
small smart smart Baba red for C you
think red will be
nicer o
or black I see like when people put make
the myth hearts in chat so often they
make Callie's heart black but her image
color is not
black it's also not red some people
think it's red too oops
see shouldn't be pink this is supposed
to be pink but more magenta but if you
compare it to the other purple then this
is less purple than you think but okay
let me see what I can
do
M there's no light oh oh red and white
oh okay okay wait the Roses could work
over here oh and there's white too
oh okay take
this oh you want to be sheared you want
to be
sheared I can do that for
you go eat and look
away you can't readed on I'll make
another bed
[Music]
then I can make another
one what the f was his fa I heard a
creeper fall down from the
sky um
[Music]
oh wait this is light
gray white
[Music]
Dy bone meal oh okay easy
easy bone
meal uh I think here oh wait we have so
many we have we have pink isn't that
going to turn out
pink
[Music]
yeah all
right can't do it
right
okay yeah this looks nicer
oh God [\h__\h] creeper sounds I swear to
God you guys
suck I don't want a parro YouTuber after
all now this will age badly if someday
we do get a parrot YouTuber to join
us don't don't don't don't don't make it
age badly
please I
stop oh my God
all right so I I did so much oh my God I
made beds in our colors because that's
important for one block Minecraft what
would we do without that
right couldn't survive without
that but also I made a lot of other cool
things so it balances
out yeah Porta but portal wasn't
difficult we already had like so much
[Music]
obsidian come
on is it the
bamboo go
go so what do you think
[Music]
guys I mean we could just
go into the uh end at any point now but
I think do you think it's worth it do
you think it's feasible even
to find another
Merchant uh uh villager yeah I think it
will be really difficult yeah I need a
lot of arrows indeed so oh we can get oh
see my chickens make so much more sense
now even not just food source but food
source but uh uh um feather
Source
oh possible but very rare yeah we might
just have to go without any Traders but
I I hope so cuz I built a
house I want
to make it
[Music]
happen potions yeah okay so we're
definitely going to do one or two days
where we go to the nether get stuff for
potions what else do you need for
potions Redstone uh NE
warts what was the other thing thank you
for the Super
Chat Blaze o oh
okay blaze powder no
not blaze rods but I know blaze powder
comes from blaze rods
but it for potions you need those really
okay are pigling in this version I would
think yeah maybe
not you think this all started with one
chicken it was hard and honest work I'm
telling you that a lot of happy chickens
yeah oh my
[Music]
God but I I'll have you guys look away
at some point there might be less
chickens than before you know but it's
for the sake of the greater good you'll
be doing myth a service a good
one it'll be so worth it you you guys be
honored for that
purpose not again not again we can
repeat history we can make my my stream
screen really small
again just like like three over three
years ago over three and a half years
ago repeat history
[Music]
M I want to put actually edible looking
food in a different chest cuz this feels
like a
mess what is this doing in
here wait with these mushrooms I might
be able to make some mushroom soups but
why would I do that when we have the cow
is there anything
else oh well I'll put these I put these
in
here need more gold apples oh yeah oh
that's what we need the gold for and
apples you just can get from bonking the
trees right do you shear them too I feel
like I remember you got to Shear them
you are not a sheep I've seen many sheep
in my life yeah he's also doubting your
sheepish existence this is not a sheep
this is definitely not
a arrows that let's let it's time guys
it's time
[Music]
ah but I can't I can't move all at once
it's annoying I'll just make this
one uh chat oh
oh no you know how good I has expendi is
I have small
leitis oh
no oh no how did this happen how could I
become so
small oh I have no
idea oh one of these sounds is is this
like a part of the smaller figh this I
don't understand oh oh no I feel like
some baby chickens are also crying oh
today is a sad day a very sad
day for
rain oh but well for some reason I'm
getting more and more feathers and and
chicken meat in my inventory I wonder
how that works where is that coming
from oh my God it's like I have sweeping
Edge on my
freaking oh no
on my on my sword why am I sweeping so
hard I'm not doing anything I mean
[Music]
uh Yum Yum
Yum it hurts me too it hurts me
too I'm sorry they're look at they're
look at me like come their
mommy wait
sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry sorry sorry can you forgive
I I mean I didn't do anything but can
you forgive me can you forgive please
yeah yeah
yeah it's for my it's for
[Music]
[Laughter]
my oh hi hi oh I'm cured I'm
cured I have been cured why is the
screen so ah oh yeah
[Music]
because it's a
miracle it's a miracle what does the AI
say what does the AI summary
say what it's pretty much same mama what
do you mean
here just same same
amount where's Jimmy this is Jimmy and
this is Jimmy and this is Jimmy this
they're all
Jimmy they're all
Jimmy some timmies in between but mostly
jimmies a chat conversation about a
YouTuber named Kip momy brutally
murdering ticket inside your M really oh
it wasn't
me I'm off the bed a sorry sorry sorry
I'm off the bed I'm off the bed
oh it was Callie it wasn't me thank you
AI thank
you Kelly has been
framed you guys going to be mad at
anybody it's not me it's de it's death
it's just the Grim Reaper makes sense
[Music]
right I put on some sad music but it's
not even sad enough for what just
happened is it wait where was this
creeper oh yeah over there behind the
fence right okay okay
okay um I'm guessing you need
sticks for
arrows
oh what do you need a a
r why do I have to come up with the
recipes on my own huh wait probably oh
maybe a piece of iron or so
sticks Flint feather oh [\h__\h] Flint for
arrows I don't think I've ever made
arrows
before um okay now I got to find the
Flint for real for
real have some
[Music]
coal make it from gravel mine gravel y
go but I feel like we had some okay
where do we have gravel is there gravel
in the stone
chest yeah then I got to make a a shovel
though this almost broken
[Music]
shovel I guess a wooden shovel suffices
wow a Minecraft stream never
[Music]
[Applause]
ending always finding something to
do that's just Minecraft
what stop lagging
around Co I don't want to hurt you oh my
God I got one Flint but I need more no
but maybe I get more like two or three
arrows out of
one recipe thingy that would be nice
because it feels like a lot to do for
one freaking
Arrow one Flint four arrows okay okay
well I want more I mean while I'm at it
you
know might as well make
more enchanting table and make a enchant
I don't I've never made an enchanting
table for that I guess we need a book
books are a bit
difficult and what else though what else
honestly I've already made so many
things today I feel like I need to leave
other people something to do I'll write
enchanting table on the to-do list how
about that obsidian
oh book two diamonds obsidian Oh that's
oh that's not so
bad and then is there a reason why
people put like bookshelves around it
always or is that just a stylistic art
aesthetic choice because I was always
wondering is that
[Music]
necessary uh oh it increases the power
of the enchanting
table
oh I'm not a hold
[Music]
interesting I never knew that
huh that's why they all make it that way
wow yeah to work hard I'm working hard
yeah well you are hardly
working nice
64 and that's just like the first little
session of
getting getting
those feathers
[Music]
too 68
actually too busy being murdered by CI
use pickaxe on gravel for Flint it's
been working so far is pickaxe better I
thought it was uh thought it was
shovel stream's still going yeah I want
I've been wanting to end it but I'm I'm
chilling and I'm having fun as long as I
know like oh I have this to do and this
I could do this I could go
forever one guy
okay well I'm out of
[Music]
shovel ah I wish it would have broken on
the last
one um
[Music]
chicken oh this is going to be some
tasty ass meal let's
go all right all right all right all
right all right all right let
[Music]
me where is where do where are we where
are we putting coal
generally don't remember
[Music]
I might be
blind shle
Gore just going to I'm I'm just going to
top it off
here oh well okay we replace that with
lava all right I didn't want to use that
much coal anymore because torches but
yeah I think we're fine I think we're
fine we're going to be okay
[Music]
ah I think one of my bowls went into
this
mhm I've got an egg for
you did that birth one or did I hit
one F felt very aggressive just now
didn't have to be like
that should I put the dy I I'll put the
Dy in the
[Music]
chest oh actually it kind of fits in
there but
no thank you for the membership welcome
we're gaining so many members today
uh oh God I don't know why I will never
remember which chest is which one I mean
I could probably guess if I used my
brain a little bit
more
but I put an extra bed here why
[Music]
not okay
now it's time
to
kill the
enemy don't you dare touch my sheep
anymore so I guess it was too dark
here let me
go and try to take some of this coal
[Music]
I know we still have some torches
somewhere but I'm too lazy to look for
them all that for a creeper yeah I mean
but in the end we still need arrows in
general because we were out of uh arrows
but yeah I mean for now but you know you
got to think the big picture the big
picture the big picture think bigger
that's your problem chickens you just
don't think big
enough don't you realize
H what the [\h__\h] where did it go where
did that go
sorry bird brain too small Horizon too
small hor Horizon that's the word that's
how you say that Horizon too
small future too
sad just think and dream bigger
[Music]
[Laughter]
ah I was like wao whoa wao second sheep
how did that
[Music]
happen oh that's kind of cute maybe it
was looking for
company big sheep
it literally wasn't there a second ago
how did it
enter there's a
fence name him
[Music]
sheep this is one of the many things I
am now capable
[Music]
of well
yeah I mean we're kind of wait wasting
Iron by using the Anvil for stuff like
that I will never do it again
[Music]
okay worth it though I'll never do it
again for something so
stupid can the Anvil if it breaks I
forgot if it breaks it breakes or can it
be repaired with a little bit
iron I think it just breaks right thanks
for the membership gift why first you
became a member and then you no you were
already a member right no you became a
member and then you gifted five what the
[\h__\h] thank
you w wa oh whoa whoa whoa am I dad
Charming
today can you right click it with iron
like with a with a with a go Golem Golem
Iron
Golem can
[Music]
I'm always
ding
[Music]
y okay here working on it
um gunpowder I don't know might be
good what's if all the clay
[Music]
oh MIP thank you thank you so
much
ah H
uh I'm so relaxed
[Laughter]
[Music]
bgm is not so sad actually this bgm is
pretty
nice bit of a waste of coal no that's
[Music]
okay we got more here oh and a Lea cap
oh but Lea
[Music]
W mine some
more W mine more W cannot stop playing
the game thanks for the pinky although I
really should soon because I need to
cook before the fish's two days expired
one day we we said we will accept but we
don't want it to be two days expired the
earlier I cook the better the lower the
risk I'm
hungry m
oh God oh my God it's almost 11:00 p.m.
the
[\h__\h] but I mean 11:00 p.m. with my
current sleep schedule is still like
middle of the
day but I'm I'm just kind of happy you
guys are like observing what I'm doing I
feel so flattered you guys are just
chilling with me even though there's no
other no other girls
around got to say I'm kind of
kind of
excited thank
[Music]
you always fun to watch you play
Minecraft yeah I missed it I missed it
it's good that Hardcore Minecraft
happened because I think that's where I
really got the idea
to oh [\h__\h] sponge I mean I had the
idea a long time ago to just do one
block with uh Ena possibly but the idea
to do it with myth was kind of a a
recent idea inspired probably by
Hardcore
[Music]
Minecraft
somehow it all came
together is that a honey block Yum Yum
Yum yeah I think it's good that it
evolve to full myth like because there's
not with Ena would have been nice too
but we don't do enough things as myth
anymore
and everybody loves Minecraft
so it's good to have a group
[Music]
project no no no no no no let me I'm
going to okay I'm going to sort these
last few things okay I mean I don't
maybe I should leave something for Cy
right
but I'm going to sort a bit more baby
maybe maybe may
[Music]
maybe where the why where do I put the
sponges I can just throw them away
honestly please fix water
[Music]
orange cat behavior oh I don't want to
push you out stay away stay
away you are no damn it
you you are the one here is where I put
one of
them ah sand sand was different
one sand was here
op chest 2 seconds ago oh my God that's
beautiful no look at the sun open chest
2 seconds ago already forget what was
inside wait I have this and this
and you love spontaneous collabs well
this is the perfect project then
[Music]
don't know don't
know wait there's nothing I need here
anyway uh
[Music]
ah oh there she goes there goes kitty
kitty
[Music]
Terra Cota Terra Cota Terra cot Terra
Cota Terra Cota ter
[Music]
ter these are easy to sort these these
are not so
bad
okay tear that card up tear that card up
M I'm happy having fish today but it's
not
C close enough let put this
[Music]
here I think my brain is fried by now
anyway it's a good point to stop because
I I'm looking at these materials and I'm
like what the [\h__\h] am I looking
at I don't know what I'm looking at
anymore what is this what is this
cuz like normally even when I play
Minecraft I don't like deal with so many
different kinds of blocks for hours and
hours
right that's not normally what you're
doing I mean yeah Block M Minecraft and
blocks go hand in hand but not like
[Music]
this sand chest which one is the that
just
here block over lord yes one block
became over 9,000 blocks probably in
total we might have
no close might be close I don't I wonder
how many blocks I have can I see it
because like I can't see it like this
they the others can see my name but is
there any other way to see it maybe here
[Music]
ah oh wow okay five 4,000 blocks okay
all right all right yeah we might be
over 9,000 combined with the
others that's my ping no
[Music]
no no
no can't think I can't think
[Music]
oh honey
blocks putting them back after
all actually since I have this pressure
plate in my
inventory is there another one on here
um no there's a trap door ooh trapo
that's what I was thinking
[Music]
of do we have any more gerkens or like a
pot wait with Clay I can I make a pot
with
Clay Pot
no um um what else do I need
bake okay let's try baking it with the
[Music]
lava wait this turns into bricks we
already have bricks do I just need the
[Music]
bricks huh okay well might as well why
not there it is
I want to make some
decorations why am I doing
[Music]
this it's another use for the flowers
what about the with but it hurts right
it hurts I think it
hurts oh wait we have some NE warts
cool Minecraft now let's go to the
garden flowers
flower flower flower
[Music]
flow yes
technology does this work though I
forgot if it actually
works might not work it
works I am very excited in case you
can't tell
[Music]
white beds white flowers
OMG this is like an
Airbnb this is legit an airbn
be oh my God oh my God I'm going to die
I'm going to die I'm going to die I'm
going to die I'm going to die
this is maybe the most fun I've ever had
with
Minecraft finally I can release you from
your suffering gerin I'll still use the
girkin I think but
um
no
yeah it's just it looks like an empty
vase
really okay if we have two left then
then you'll get a little nice dinner
[Music]
table honestly in this case they could
be empty and they could be like bowls of
food if I can ever place them there you
go or whatever I don't know yeah they
could be cups okay how do I make how do
I make
chairs what's a nice way to build a
chair I think I've seen some nice way
before but I don't
know ah stairs I guess stairs always
work I've seen nicer versions but ah
trap doors next to to the stair right oh
can I hug a stair with uh fences too or
does that not can it not like touch
[Music]
it oh science can work too I want to see
that
yeah I like
it my mom must be so happy with the
stream
too I [\h__\h] love it
man all they the same color I didn't
even do it on purpose
oh
[Music]
man creme de La Creme right here right
here isn't this sexy oh I can't even do
it in the
back
oh this house was
built while wa was filling
herself oh my
God what's wrong with me no I want it to
be a different color I think it looks
nice the contrast is
pretty I mean I I've heard oh cat let's
go cat makes house even
better no I've heard people say that
when they just like think they're pretty
and and sexy and all that and just
vibing wait I want to capture the all of
the this is good
me with the
cat oh my
God I'm going to live here I'm going to
actually live here nice air Beam Beam
man the cat it even has has a cat no
Airbnb is better than an Airbnb that has
a cat like unless it has a cat if it has
two cats then it's better than an Airbnb
that has a cat but you
[Music]
know I'm I I am
moved I'm so moved maybe let's put a
chair in here
too a chair and no more trap door wait
we'll we'll figure this out what why why
is this here is there a reason for this
is there a reason for
[Music]
this I'm going to clean
up lanterns yeah but lanterns use up
iron we I'm not going to waste iron
[Music]
little seating
area iron make iron that's that's one of
the hopefully we can make it kind of
gos it's just wishful thinking but I
don't
[Music]
know how's this going
wow that burns for a long
[Music]
time how to make trap door just
wood m
[Music]
maybe this color just to differentiate
it a little bit from the other did you
leave the house the Airbnb is not going
to sell well without
[Music]
you
that kind of no no no I mean I if it was
like a garden chair and table then
yes but uh the the gaps in indoors mean
no like Outdoors yes indoor no no no I
guess we go we'll go dark after
all chocolate
yeah two two will
[Music]
suffice chocolate table I'll bite into
it oh hello
Cat yeah it matches that's good that's
good can I like do something here
no no okay ah hey yo but then that works
too interesting h
[Music]
well now you're in the way not that I I
find it interesting like combining that
might be good for some other kind of
construction whatever you want to
[Music]
create I feel like I can't do it anymore
oh there it
[Music]
is yeah but maybe like if you enter if
you want to make it so that you enter
from the other side for some reason like
you want to give this Vibe of for some
reason it's there's wood there to I
don't know there could be things like
that
move F fence under the table makes it
look like a leg
really stop giving me
ideas
ew I have fence gate fence Oak fence
[Music]
how don't think it works
actually end rods work
too fence and the pressure plate put the
fences first I mean if it doesn't work
I'm happy with you know wall mounted
tables that's fancy
hi it
[Music]
works I'm going to end up making a whole
kitchen here guys if you don't stop meum
[Music]
it's like a wall light like
outside oh why is it floating oh is it
Ah that's why you guys said you can't
put anything there now that's okay
that's okay actually that's
okay I like the wallmounted
feature I like that if only we could
light it up but I guess that's why you
would get land
[Music]
LNS H stop wa stop it stop
it stop making things
[Music]
don't stop don't stop just go your own
way there have so many
chests I feel like we're we're going to
run out of wood uh I'm just going to
quickly mine the big tree over
here wood is good
[Music]
maybe drop some apples who
knows right I wanted to test that if
that works with the shears right right
right
yeah see I I originally had this already
in my to list
so la ah it's 11:00
p.m. I need to cook I need to cook food
wow I super cute ah lesbian let's go
lesbian woohoo
where are the
apples where are them
[Music]
apples careful lesbiian careful
now sorry this is a Insider meme if you
don't understand I know it sounds weird
I know I know you only get the leaves it
gives leaves on
ah
y
okay
but
decoration no okay
[Music]
no a fish is getting slime no no no not
the Slime they'll make it
slimy I I there's too much empty space
here but it's okay it's okay it's okay
it's if I space out the beds I could you
know but my airb be is a bit more work
oh my God it's so
pretty it's so
[Music]
pretty I want a lantern I want to put a
lantern on the
[Music]
ceiling less is better less more they
say in
German well that's going I decorate
[Music]
though H not
matching hi
Kitty you thought it was time to go oh
no oh
no let's make this more friendly oh but
my torch
[Music]
all right torch is worth it for this
sacrifice thanks for the membership
gifts
it's like a whole Secret Garden up
[Music]
here I pickaxe doco no
pickaxe I did it fall down no
[Music]
never Garden never that sounds fancy if
you ride it with
[Music]
v wow it's the same as on the other side
now or is it no actually ah it's kind of
different
[Music]
aren't the leaves going to thec I don't
think so they're flammable that's
okay I take it wait how do how how did
I ah
here
here it's worth it cuz it's
pretty should I put it around here too
no no no no
[Music]
okay there's no wood chest here okay
remove that one which
one wait that one is such
a vague thing to say if you only put
small lights in the leaves that look
amazing if you you mean are you saying
something that is not possible in
Minecraft can I make one
Lantern just
one wish you could make it with
[Music]
gold oh
can the cat come back
though I need another updated
picture raw fish on it I think we had a
Cod where did the Cod go is it because
I what did I do did I rip it
bu a
[Music]
fish use a lead
a works on cat question
mark cat wait how about oh you oh you're
right there
Hi it's I don't know if this is an
OptiFine bug but it's not on its
[Music]
head come here with me into our home no
careful careful come
careful how cute the way it just looked
when it walked in it was like oh is this
my new home is this my new
[Music]
home right I want to make it sit
though oh it's
sting how do I let go there we go okay
sit
[Music]
sit this [\h__\h] thinks I'm a dog what the
[\h__\h] oh my
[Music]
god
wow
[Music]
wow you good cute
I think something's wrong with me I need
to this is this is bad this is
bad this is
bad thanks for the membership we you all
yeah it's called
[Laughter]
toxoplasmosis okay did I take pictures
of everything that's
important I mean another thing that that
we kind of did that was is new is the
dolphin enclosure but I don't think we
need to photograph that um well this one
needs one more
photograph and one more
[Music]
light the final one oh it's very
greenish I think am would would like it
here the the green and the wood is
probably very aesthetic to
her
[Music]
cheese try placing Music Box near Birds
hey yo why hey yo explain
yourself do they play the
music random nether block yeah I kind of
want to fix it I was looking at that too
they Vibe with
it even when they're in the boat
[Music]
though Play That Funky Music
birdie no
boat not in boat but then I have to let
them
go but it would be nice to have the juke
box here anyway I don't know
it's a nice little piece of
[Music]
furniture I still want to lose them you
know but
okay they
seem hypnotized
they not is this the wrong track like
they don't like this one it's not
exciting enough oh cat don't eat the
birds uh
restart oh they seem like that kind of
did something to
them oh cat left the
room she wanted to see the the bird's
party but she realized oh nothing
happening here I think they don't like
the track or is it the version yeah is
it too old surprised there's parrots
anyway
oh yeah no I don't don't think it's
[Music]
happening
well back into the boat you
go please please go back into the boat
oh is it because they're sitting right
now do I right click them
oh no I don't think I have the power to
do it
though they eat seeds too a okay that
one's
set wait I don't think I taped them with
seeds before it's not my birds anyway
but it will go there eventually probably
now I I I will end it
here I will finally end it okay okay
okay okay okay uh Super Chat reading
probably not going to happen today maybe
tomorrow yeah I will I will I could play
longer but I shouldn't make too much
progress alone
yeah I will
cook I will cook some salmon with some
potatoes and there was something else
potato salmon a girkin salad no cucumber
salad like with like a interesting
dressing sounds premium doesn't it cuz
it is
premium thank you guys so much for
watching today I will continue playing
more Minecraft tomorrow so although
starting time will be different I'm not
sure yet when I will start I'm got to
think about
it got to hit up the other girls if
anybody's like available at any time
then I might adjust to whenever they're
[Music]
available football
tomorrow
the depends I don't want to like do two
streams so close in a row so probably
not but I'll I'll probably be watching
off stream or if we are streaming
Minecraft while it's happening then
we'll just keep an eye on it how about
that just don't keep an eye on the score
but I don't think I think France is
pretty good I don't think Austria can
win against France I just have this
feeling that France is decent right any
any uh European soccer Geniuses who know
I think France is decent not as good as
Austria France is top two in the world
oh [\h__\h]
okay where is it happening by the way
what's the location or is it several
countries I think usually isn't it just
one country and whatever is it like the
soccer uh World World Championship
where is it Germany
oh Germany's
hosting oh right oh wait yeah yeah wait
now I
ah and it's in it's a different CI okay
one of them is dled off right yeah oh
now it clicks in my brain now it
clicks
oh
[Music]
mhm okay well well
well uh and say love you guys see you
tomorrow wah wah wah outo wah out
hopefully tomorrow we'll play together
with some others so I can Flex my
accomplishments to
them yeah
byebye yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah
[Music]
oh