[Music]
N
voodoo
[Music]
uh go
to
me
Hmm
hmm
[Music]
Hmm
[Music] N
pandan Yeah,
good, good, good
[Music]
Moody
Hmm
[Music]
tnd
Enter
ana
[Music]  ]
Hmm
[Music]
Uuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu
this show
is!
[Music]
wh
me
[Music]
t
ni nare
me
eeeeee
tan
[Music]
Yeah yeah yeah
[Music]  ]
This program is brought to you by the sponsors you are viewing.
true
tut pr
Ji support senpai 3 has been muted
pane
Niki stupid woman
wow ha ha ha ana lagoon morning french pen goods mohe other than people
Join Fine, how are you all?Japanese people, please feel free to comment in Japanese.I'm
Sian-senpai, so don't worry.Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Well, first of all, let me explain this talk program again in English.  I
want to think about it
Video s a My mother with stage 8 is in trouble Watch
Patter's house invites Pusha to the toilet seat beauty salon
Life chance l I'll be in the prestigious club
rr 2 vs match house sam derose views Let's
play Wow healing  Banyu House
This is an interview talk show for Takanashi Kyarahoru and Kohane's English polishing for overseas audiences.The
purpose is to let people know more about Japanese talents through live interpretation.My
husband is, of course, my Takanashi character.Western
Confectionery DistrictCome
on.  All of you are real people, Sach.
8 So, there's
already a cat here, but before you bring that cat out, everyone, please take care of that.
Hey, I want Ross to win. Now, when I solve it, Akasha Ross Woohaa p
1  The
tree is 130,000 yen, so let's go to Hasegawayama prefecture.
Fish c 8
Nujutsu boa Child's life rapper me
Let's take the exam see csn dba Date
Shion-senpai seems to be awake, but somehow he's awake
Kamimae bye
new life aaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
[Music]
porn
Avatar
Kiki
me
Ohayohayo 8 It
's early Nya Nya Saya Iyo
2 The only blue bee-wielding chick that matches 6
ana That's so
cool Great
taste and English 4 Surprisingly thoughtful zepp I have no choice but to become fluent in English too
Outdoor hot springs are cooler
Cyan  Thank you for coming, Senpai.Actually, I was really worried that you would be late.Ahaha, I think I would
be late if it weren't for Yara-chan.Yeah,
well,
pandan personinde
re then breasted asti cardwirth h star 3
moon r asb to do  in forever Copper r Yesterday,
I was in bed. It's
my first time broadcasting since 1 o'clock, Senpai. Did you listen to that girl who was swinging
? Well then, this is good for you.
Honda's sleep.  I was thinking of doing it, but it wasn't raining, so I had to wake up early. I
guess I didn't think I'd be able to oversleep. There are so many people
here, haha,
but I'll stream on that discord too.  While I was planning something, I was on the 2nd floor.That
fresh singer asked me twice if I could get up to sing such an amazing song.If
I had to say it myself, the singer had passed away.  I'm seriously
worried. I didn't want to bury it. I
dared to do coarse up to do as I dared to do. Well, I'm
glad. I'm glad. I'm a good
girl. Today, I'm talking about the total abolition of Zion,
or
something like that overseas.  When I asked about it, the information that was known about that spring
was that the Red Minecraft was at war with Aqua Senpai.  I
recently learned about the Ness song, and I was like,
oh, you're a head, you're a head, Sugai-kami, so even if you pick it up from here, you can see it a little bit.Then, the
scene looks like an onion that looks like the sky, and I wonder what he's called.
When I asked about it, I was
told that 4-chan is called Garlic.Japanese
people don't listen to it.Everyone doesn't appreciate it.I
won't say
it.Well, there's a possibility that High Rock will be called "Garlic" in the future.  I
don't want to go, I
miss it. Garlic is delicious. I don't want to leave it behind, so what happened?
ii Chode Down White 3 seasons en us Mon Spain Oily Innova
Gay Site Minecraft 4 s Back Ah Senpai anh Head Gaa Wig c 3 e  5
e 9 server touch breno 2 japanese nkaaha xcg
kun p jellyfish oarsdriver aer I
'm going to go to Hawaii, but actually, I'm
also being told that 3 is being said a little bit.I don't have a hat.  Ours is also
said to be an orange-colored ball running away. When you
open the temple bell, it really looks
like that. I'm not going to take it off, but I'm not going to take it off, and I'm not going to guess. Wait a minute, I
can't show you anything.
This time, I'm doing this so that I can learn more and more about my 4th senior overseas.I'm
not an expert.  What
is it, I
can't help it Ah, what's going on with Negirapori?
Y beauty kaiser
Kayo buy it right away nater to buy it right away nater in Chungwoo support John year is also a little prefecture
apex up Hey
Abu-chan you guys too ever seen senior city profiler too
ever 2 that's right yesterday
a
hatan also separate from the pass  I'm going to turn on the spring again in the same city. Yeah, that
girl's hot spring pineapple rice is a little bit. My
self-introduction is simple, easy,
detailed, self-alienation, and I swore I was a radio regular when I saw something strange on ACOM right now.
A work  Bumper Rudy's rewarding housing complex
Bach
a Please introduce yourself in detail Egg book model
in Japanese It's okay in Japanese Power scoop last live 2nd generation a Cute witch girl Neko
mini a Our company Murasaki Shion
[Music  ]
Understood cleaning asoka
rar
cac sanjusangendo r chi zoom generater
coner fa
as the pure idol 4 nenga cpr patch 2
abu apparel fish in zumoon c the
why big ppe
aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa to to to  It's also the ward's hose, etc., so
after all, I thought I had to learn about that guest, so I did a
little research.I
saw a lot of things.Haha,
can house, 4, rin, poupe dinnerware watching, etc., Fins,
options, senior mistakes.  Good
REESE Lachi is a spice. 9 Fe I
saw the debut distribution at that Zion Senior
Sir, I'm sure I should make it public.  It's
different from the last day, isn't it?
barena
name Shitara Never Today's card holder ring
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa After all,
good eggs and whatever it is
Well, it's time people
belen deforide lenco aderin aderin specter
4 sp to do scene
agricultural tool favor
Is there a reason why you don't talk now, even though you used to talk in honorific language? Is there a
reason why you're starting to get used to it? Everyone is saying to Asuka that it's okay.  I thought I wouldn't be able to talk about it, but
maybe. Well, as
long as I think it was the first broadcast of the discharge after that, I don't really care.
Booba was good, more ooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo sooooooooooooooooooooooooo sooooooooooooooo so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so so such  Ah, it's
white, it's history. It's white, and the rainbow started with reporters and masters. It
's white history because I grew up in the hair. Nemuro is pretty
cute. oh is cute, but it's a lie.
Cyan pile with booby ah. I want a good bird.  Naaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa went into
Patty's release
yesterday, I was the only person in the English language club for about 4 times, and I bose to English-speaking people, and I was
completely out of control with everyone who has a Japanese brain.
Wow, I see.
When I finished, I searched for that question and asked, but that's right. According to the above and sister agreement, IA, the new
10th round of sex and space, 9 Ford, s 6, Nekoi, Sake
Brewery, Korehato.  So the
first question is, what kind of activities have you been doing as a tiepin?
Really lately, I
played a knitting turn game called Doki Doki Literature Club.That was
really strong.It was
really fun.I'm with a cute girl.  Dub love, the sound is
great, Shion is that girl and that happy sweat, it's a peaceful game,
appendix happiness is really good, you
should get used to it.
All that time, I know the truth. I'm a little scared.
Masukyuru-chan
must be a luer. I'm a strong girl. I'm not good at hora, so I'll say that I'm really bad at hora. I'm not good at it. It's effective.
That's right, yeah, Seahers finger
Uttoka Doki Dokimo Chuomachi Chocolate Opening
Hirase Pointer 3 Thumb Arm 5
Boo Boo SA 1 Helme Barrel Eade Eighter Leader and I liked it Well, I
think the name is Tsunami.  Please remember that, that's
what Jaguar was supposed to be doing in the summer. If you say that, it will be dangerous.
At the meeting, Monica will tell you that the doctor has loved only the moon for a long time.  I feel
like it's going to explode, but Arima,
someone tells me that he's
r f 0 f 5 a trender movie
motor ap still romen daimon cars
this is os Everly stopped example 3
Saaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa is also a bra day program her [ __ ] setup
game's  Save
Scary Scary Scary I wonder if that one is angry and sick as well. Why is that so funny?
Natsuki, the person who appears there, is probably
sick. I don't know because I played with her, but the
first one was amazing.  It's not neat.
[Music]
If you boo, you'll be fooled. Even the lure is 29 sen be to do on eyes
away putin ice cream koc have to do
anger I see.
That's what I did. I was also looking at the basics of the fog a little bit.
Ahh, that's amazing
Steve Khan It's
a little bit good that the family members who can only say rice from Atsugi were also doing it.
Lately, I've been in the type of person. Yes,
what happened? I saw you crying while watching Pekora's live performance.  Error I was
trying to figure out the direction and making some seeds.
wai
Is Usopp serious? He said it was cute. I
was cute. Ch is the Spanish Lime Scrying Bag Run exclusive. The catfish is dead and it's
complete.  voodoo
file No. 4 down walk, Haru-senpai's is Vienna Gabat. Now, the
next question is, I'm sure a lot of people are curious about it, but
Mr. 3, how did you find the moderation, or how did you get started?  What was that
?
Well, I was trying to use a Showa skirt, but I got a call from someone like that. Ugh, the
shop was just like a sweet maaika effect.
What a person who really likes things.  NakataIt's like that face.Gah,
that's the end.It
's decided by the um, but it's not decided whether or not to include it yet.  I
don't know if I'll give it a try or not.I don't know if I'll give it a try.It's okay to buy something like that.It's the first time I've felt
like I'm pure.I've been doing it for such a long time now.  Do you
think it's a good thing? I think it's
really changed my life
hmm
a
usa sosus raden audition beso nonce air conditioner
teraso aa me as she wants to do so are
lecture
nu do
en wedding star wars good choice join a day
cheese  And r iphone Pleakley, there
was a lot of rumors about it.Ah, it's
nothing.I was conscious of the existence that I was already aware of, and I moved.Hmm, I
knew the diver by default, but I do
n't know.I was thinking of going home, but I didn't want to go home at all.  Eventually, I found an application for an audition for a rural English-speaking country, and
from that moment on, I started thinking, ``Maybe I should get in,'' and I thought, ``
Oh, I should get in.'' Well, I'm ready, I guess I should go in.  I guess I had a lot of feelings about it,
but first of all, I thought that my autograph notebook would be a good fit, so I applied.I felt
really passionate about it and decided to try my best
to get in.  That's good, and the dimensions have changed.
Hey, it's serious. It's true. It's really true. It's a teacher. It's a competition for sponsors. It's a boss and a 3 a n
Derby spin. Come to Antigua. Turbo star is here. Zoom in with the funk. A little big
star palmy bar.
IOS Good Baba version. R abeno  Cheer on Butter Rice for 3 minutes
Addition
on danse be sure to do as to win the
audition me up nippon Chin 5 smooth pou dou dou
After all, if you
get into 5, it's Chinese food, something's okay I'm
planning to stream something like that every day  Well, it was
n't so good that I was robbed of stories like, ``How many times should I do this on Fridays?'' Well, I
thought it was so good that I didn't get a single response from someone like ``Maa-san,'' or something like that.
But long ago, Arthur did something else that made him so passionate that he did it every day.He
was like, ``Well, please read at least the episode, I'll watch it, and then I'll stop.''  That's
right,
moresale arenas are you doing
After all, it would
be fun if the investigation were to be included in the comedy. It's not
fun, so the story is fun.
So, the next person to ask the question was Khan,
Aeton,
Edo language.  There's something I've wanted to convey to people overseas for a long time, without a home due to restrictions in the United States.Ah,
I was able to
really speak English while having fun.I
guess the power of the live performance allows us to talk about other things.  I can
already talk to the listeners who are watching overseas, so I've been saying that for a long time.It's
already been a great effect.Well, I should have done it properly.I heard that they were
having a send-off party, but I don't know what to do.The
people who are going overseas and watching are also in Japanese.  Even though I don't understand, people are
looking at me and I want to do my best to be able to speak the same language,
even though I don't understand it.  The width is better, but everyone has something to say.
Hey Hayaba, you graduated from Starbucks, so have you ever lived overseas? Yamaha has advanced, but aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa I
graduated from a long time ago, Chikisu Nanban and Sasakawa did their best at Harvard.  Hey, sister, if that's the case, it's
not in the script in Japan.
Yeah, I heard that you know that. When you say virtual Bach, you mean Harvard University.
9 Hanyu, who
graduated from Harvard University, is like that.
Hmm,
cats are killing each other. Well, that's amazing. It's a love school,
but it's a little long ago. Even so, it's a huge piece. I
can't pull it out. Haha, I guess it's
going to go
down a little.  I'll conquer it
useragent kremer enoden oon download as
co wither soa patty acc zulong riding door
saa book going to work
ringspipe hmmm
[music]
voodoo
chain jsaa rb harem
inu format no soko garp f Eikura-chan or something like that I can collaborate with Grachan already  Yes,
that's right
. I need to practice a little. If you
really want to talk about money, you
should ask Mr. Kihara to teach you. Nanaka Eikura,
male. Yamaha. If you're a BA graduate, Anu.
Press the word once.  Just try to memorize the
more you can get aol
aso carendar ender car teacher red pou dou
dou
aso please help 6 ef 4 h club ascanty that push pim matsue
branch man booth you voice
a little bit.  You've already told me this in the English-speaking world, so I'm
going to teach you some difficult words now, so I don't know if I'll be able to memorize them until the end of the rebroadcast course.
Ah, I'm a
writer enjob pot fb Then the last sound of my cheeks is a face. Yeah,
well, the fur is amazing, but it's really difficult.
Ah, wow, both of them are
idiots. I can say it's nice.
It's a bit full of life, and I'm at home.  English is not my native language, so I'm going to make a bunch of
cone woofer faces.
OK, let's just use normal
[music]
in normal words, so I'm going to
make you remember it. Yes, I'm
confused about the pronunciation.
Hey,
how many planes are waiting for Ono Machop?
Petit artwork
Ono Raccho Parents and
Matcha A pair of macho keys that can be seen and Miyuu Auto
Now onomatopoeia
[Music]
Eh panamera
a The meaning is onomatopoeia
Onomatopoeia Eh, I
wonder if you don't know Matsu? That's why I can't put it there in the past, but in the past Yamakasa regulation r canopri But in the end, I remember the reason and can't do it.
Ahhaaaaaaaaa  If you are a graduate, you can
afford Onuma P Large Pdat Infus Zardi JAPANESE line,
total 4 damage butter cotton cotton cotton fabric shorts, oils, oil, oh, oh,
oh, oh,
oh, oh, that's the
best distribution of Yama.  What's the point? For example, I enjoy the distribution of benefits the most, like Operation
Game, Cats On, etc. Oh, I
like Maintenance Club, but I really like them all. I also like Gyūbankai because it's fun.
But recently, I've
been really bad at singing, but I can't sing.  I
used to like singing in front of people alone at karaoke and other events, but I
got nervous singing in front of people and couldn't sing very well, so when I played cherry blossoms, I felt kind of sad,
but now I'm getting better.Wow, I
feel like I'm growing up.  Nu, a little fun song has a big stinky breath
Oh no, it's giving birth to old evil people. Is Hemana my boom? There's
no reason to be worried before distribution. It's okay. They're idols after all, so they probably don't sing a lot.
Introducing equipment for idol battles. Yeah
references to  do paper burner lady say bubu bubu her
in dream water color green
usd e to do not to do this piece key fun
tsusukyu
What do I like most?The location is still Subaru's sound Shion is kind to Senpai This is Shun  It
's nice of you to reply to questions even though it's a stream where you ask Senpa questions.But
if you're curious, it's my first time talking canter, so I'll go first.There
aren't that many golden karaokes.I feel like I
can do it without having to worry about small talk.  That's why I like fun salt tongue, so
maybe we'll do karaoke too Ina-chan's solo Iccho
[Music]
h su1 s 4 s my perry Turn steam but let's play 3
Karaoke day recruitment Aron up When will I go to Bar Chiba?  Take more and far away
8 virus ana
stone lobby a
sas to ASCII box new wonderful old tag Pinir senior Shinsuku Tamakiuchi is cute That
face I guess he cares about the family too
ab 5
lick it to you early
ran
later  I don't know, I'm ranked number 5 in that spa quick-read stream, that
Nagaitsu Intermediate Spa and read stream, but I always end up talking about something else,
so I guess
that's what I'm talking about while I'm reading it, so that's 30 minutes.  It took me 3 hours to read
it even though I was supposed to finish reading it. It's so funny that I read Supa-chan's comment and it makes me laugh. But that's not the case. The
investigation makes me really happy, so I guess it's okay. Is it
pants? It's
just like Gara. Are some change pkg eyes on?  me 10
people matchy
and burn
chatters flooded next question Eighter's originally non-incisional festival ended this week
with a boom It feels like a long time ago already, but I've been training a lot It seems like it's been a long time since I've been training
Hey, the specs are 10 times higher. That's when we
set sail, right? The house did it.
Hey, you pulled off a perfect performance.
How do you feel now after the live show you resisted? I'm
sure the earphones section will be there many times.  I've talked about it so many times, please, Charka. I do
n't need to talk about it. I wonder
if it's true. 6 It felt amazing to be able to do everything.
Even though it was only recently, it feels like a long time ago.  I
taste it, but I'm still on the left.I used to sing in front of people in the karaoke broadcast, but I was
nervous about exercising in front of people, so I wasn't good at it, but I
can't sing or dance anymore.  It's just that my
feelings have changed quite a bit.When I
was in character, I was
nervous that it was still pretty good.I
was
actually really nervous.
But then again, it's this year. It
feels like it's been a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time since I've been in the middle of a long time since I've been in the middle of a year.  The
filling is
also a play plax, so I'm trying to outdo it in the garden.I'm still worried about the separator,
so I
want to do a concert or something.  I
want to do it, I want to do it, I want to do it,
falorni starfish, Kureha Barbaker,
Core on Stage Ogura Uza, unfinished k pop.  Isman
voodoo moe Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa goods chive live to be a lure archer
22 star steaks are always a bit strange.What
was the most fun or the most difficult thing about preparing for Welch's 8th card festival?  I'd
like you to understand a little bit why it took a lot of effort to do that road.Ah,
I see.Darth is my
sister.Isn't
it Pearl that I went back to the song that Kosan Option sang like this?
Hmm, I'll
make it a little easier than that.  I asked him to come up with the choreography for me, and I
did that Besson, but I still did my best. I don't usually dance.
Well, it's difficult if you're not anxious. It's difficult. Hey,
how long did it take you to get that choreography in your head?
But anyway, I wonder how long it took me to memorize everything. It's
been
years since then.
Well, all those songs are amazing. Not only today, but there are also Bach compositions.  It
took me a long time to really burn through all the questions. I
did it with everyone, too.
That's how many times. It's been a long time. It's been 2 months. It's amazing. I've been preparing since A.
That's why it seemed so difficult.  Even right away it was hard.
It was hard, but it was fun. Ah, that's nice.
Muscle pain is amazing.
Muscle pain is
amazing. Muscle pain is amazing. It's amazing. The first time was already too much.
Hmm, I guess. That's what I'm saying.
Car  forever to do armor ua nuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuwb white
blue pawn
booby erde morenote manometer erleph half fare
masu
At the Biker Star Shoin b The loser batch Hana Ga Paan unless I run away to my Niihama grandparents
ap sing for mature Fei closeness is so good it's fun.
a I
have some kind of memories of that practice time,
ah, I wonder what it is,
because the next day I forget most of
what Inoue did
.  Give some salt to the teacher who teaches miscellaneous goods.
Hey sister, this is what this is like here.
[Laughs] It's
weird that there's no 8 Lister. Neo. It's okay if you tell me. It's heavy, right? Let's go
to the beginning. If that doesn't work, I'll go to sleep.  It's a bit dangerous,
hmm, but well, if you do it all over again, you'll probably get stuck in your head more and more.2 That's
right.
Drunk Topia aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
name a massive code see branch school bag dress the
next coo bad announcement Jindo arson is the queen of making a rakusupin bakery
nb bear dog dobe pile teacher in den price waving do
ba boss darts angel without putting in the hot water of impa in Korea and China  It
wasn't that big
me
rear bass eset nod Zaboon
dere nore Boon to do in film Oh, I see. Let's move on to the
next question. Yes
a Not all members of the Japanese live show will be participating inside the next Bloom.  Please tell me how C-Oto-senpai
came to be under your umbrella.Actually, I live in that Shion-senpai's Khan.Hmm,
Japanese fans were curious about the cat's question, but
what about Axion-senpai?  I'm
saying it's really that good, but I'm
still trying to say it, but I don't know what's going on.It seems like I've never had the impression that I'm doing anything.Yes, but why
are you here?Now, I'm also participating in Bloom.Is that what you're
thinking of doing
?  Ah,
well then, I talked about it yesterday, but aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaling  Yeah, it's going to
take a little bit of time for me to worry about
that too much, and I'm going to get it right.It's really hard, so I was really confused, but I don't know why.After the
live performance, I thought, ``If you
have one big goal, that's what you want to achieve.''  Nikan Val Jean Nelly That's
it. It's really fun and exciting, and the feeling of accomplishment after it's over is
amazing. I
really like working hard towards a big goal.
ua Drink while you're doing it.  I
thought I'd smoke a hoodie ano onna son den den den
carabe iphone 5 au dodo
boo boo sr to do ri aan sakuraya
village ca 6 c 5 ea vale hoodie
carus way
andere 50 re so mare fuzz dondon watch
haizam complex wear these bid headway staff  I'm
going to facer pou dou dou bread with big After the rant,
this is that town Hollow I
saw the second face - when I looked at the clock, when we went together at the same time, those guys were
talking about Noon and making him stronger.
That's why when I was doing MC, I made it more lively for the English-speaking people in South Africa who were watching it with me,
but
at the very end, I said something about my impressions of today's concert.  You
said it in your voice on stage, and
I've
already translated it, but at that time, I was sure of Care.Until
now, even now, I
didn't really think of myself as an idol.  I would
be happy if everyone would think of me as an idol.When I
did that, I said, ``You said that, right?
7th generation.''
Why, I've been doing this for two years.Why?
Why, why myself?''  You wouldn't think it was Airo.I
guess I'm a
girl who thinks she's an idol.Hmm, I
'm close,
but I think she's an idol, so I attack her and do my best as an idol.  I guess
it's because I haven't been to many live shows,
but it's the first time I've ever been to a vacant lot and there was a Kaneko live show, and everyone
told me that I was an idol, and that in my opinion I was a really wonderful idol.
Even if you don't think so, everyone will have money now. Hmm, it's a
good thing, so it's nice.
Hey, can dir en Watch is also big-eyed
ais earmo can you do
voodoo arc en en us ide Are you home? bos
aside  A
tefcas aether fighter not earth ev's up to do
fighter
arm shisaada
west cd star s with charm and fan psb joint season fincar
position
senses char of bno reeder others eca fighter
maaaah boober right now  Branch Ponchaninator cheese yeah good pants
stick glue four eyed palm stone Sapira bar ping pong sevens edition
pass
hey want you the ground sun is great for spin guitar too my house is also in the
middle of the beginning or should I say at the time of bar 5
so much  I do
n't really think about this as part of my job as an idol. I
guess I just think it's meant to be broadcast. I'm playing a game with Nee-san, so I know it's a price tag game, so
this is just a shade,
but it's also part of my job.  Well, if you ask me, you're
already what I call an internet idol. That's
right.
Price hikes, pik. I guess you're a virtual idol, aren't you? You're a virtual idol, aren't
you?  I was able to
push it.
Hmm. Well, that's true. Even if you don't realize that you're an idol,
everyone these days likes the complete abolition of Shion, so if you're too conscious of being an idol,
things will turn out to
be hard.  Don't give up on
me, so I'll take it, sister. From now on, I'll just
stay like a cat. Dodge. Yes, if you're going to seriously become an idol, I
don't think you're suitable for today's world of broadcasting. Oh, that's right. You're
probably going to be the main focus of that live show.  I have to change the way I speak in the middle of the day, and use
honorific language. I'm not good
at the Japanese calendar. I do
n't speak on the bell. 4 I don't speak
a
roa some star.
Kakuban Yuga is farming tomorrow Life-san is already touched by Pet Pass Nizumi da
webtoon en Female doctor smartia degree two pieces of pi Dosu
party
Muju I became a service fan and helped Ah yes
No, it became a deep story.  I can't go back, so that's what I'm looking for in this talk,
so I'd like to talk about it.Yes,
this is good.I'll
go to the next question.I'll ask you a
cheer
or ever.Officially, it's okay.
But I've never seen him raise his muff at all.Tune
Senpai, please show me some magic.All
of them are animal gate firefly puffs.I'm
sure you can do anything with exponent 5 programs and 3D streaming.Mutsu  It's
a bit tough without the power of Arda Maid 3D. It's a
bit tough if you don't become a woman hunter.
Can you do ned? I like Finland as much as
Rockn Doc.  Hasebe Kung Fu do you search by
rules, I'm a cat girl now.
He's a princess with negative equipment symptoms, so it might be a little difficult. I'm
going to have to ask him about it. It's in that costume. He's
making me do it. Ah, it looks like he's floating. It's no good.  What
's the point? He's such a professional. Eun-seo is like that, isn't he? He doesn't want to destroy his image. [Music] Option to say boo-boo Gru Shiina's name view Enjoy After all, it's not punchy, it's the reason why Philly case 7 is good.  Okay, I understand. I'm
not sick.
Yes, I often embezzle and drive around in my car. My new senior's 3D broadcast is also for his license. I
see. He
was using magic here too.
That's right.  It can be used, Kanuma.
I can certainly say that. I was using it.
And then that moment every 22 seconds. Well,
those panties were completely visible. I'm
aiming for
anus, oh, oh, oh, Dale Arch, Finn Ahren, who do up the fighter, the
author.
Char japanese bathing 213th ah
rear xtender would do do butts barter color
suse suse Hahn Gardener 7 If the hot water shakes p I got it so my sister is already
struggling
If Chihaya's clothes
were definitely selling Ran club
skirts  It's a bit swaying and it's amazing.
It's my sister who is tearing up the catch. It's
difficult, so it looks like that. Low is the magic.
Does anyone else know that? Maybe it's like that. Even though I'm shocked when I do something like that, it's magic in such a situation.  Yo,
hey, that's what happened
because I was so shocked.Raku was
selling a lot of bones, right?I
'm going to translate that for the time being.I was in
a hurry when I saw Xian Fuji.Ah, I want to
take a moment to remember the story.ran ah
ah
ran
naite iru meb  Shaun Yu png water the mars apks
well placement fields for ever sealer 2 pass borders well ge sebas
ah
well it's a pity it's a little disappointing that I can't rain much at the store right now and the Agato plan is
sorry sis Naode
Naode strangers are a party  I have an unfaithful neighbor at Waseda University.
ana b 1 day uma gkn syndrome.
And now,
but... Hey,
Avaspick has prepared a spelling quiz about the fresh-faced Vera.
[Music]
Yes, question board
Um, what's going on?
cf 7 I'll get you to answer right away. Okay, don't think about it at all.
John Sweets Barco Lottery is so cute. The housewives are good. Tess order Maedate Renko 1 piece.
ep A
museum tour that becomes a related costume in another
Danbatch that seems to be the
original Hume maybe Male volume Uwaeka Papa Eyes Bimyeon Caster & Chasteberry Signature
Well, I haven't thought about how to translate this, but
Wada It's too early now so I can't help it.  No
, let's do it. Well, I've prepared some music for that. Ironaba Yasubei 24 a
Ober
Rush
Jobi Bai Ika
Osake The
enemy is a cold target
a Cold book Carment Dawn
Gus and Kansai de au
What a great figure
Taiko  In the past,
girls reader
Ah, I definitely couldn't keep up with ran
Ran I'm stuck
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa We'll
do it at the same time I
can't do it at the same time Climbing
Okitsu Tsuki 8 mountains?
Yeah yeah Well, how about
that run? Quick
cocker Sekine, it's
pizza, Pirak.  There are a lot of Jesus
KOK Senior Aika, 10 Paikorone Seniors, which are
open, is already a ska tonight.
So Ryoko, or famous or traveled in a big city,
10 medals to travel, fill in the pin, stomach, one leg, that blizzard, old sharpeners, urine,
a
rain, this 7 that that that glass is half full, is it half full?  It's so
good that the nest is Rugby Lagrass and the water n a is half full of mother.
Ah
7 Bar Family Family Girl 7 Kasbah Actually Rosso
Fan Nyah
Wow I'm
going to text him or go to the bar in front of him I'll give him a big present or get it  Or
a I want to get to the one station that I want, and I'm going to take the Arkaden Chale. I
wonder what color my pants are. The end of the Big Way is 1st class. I looked at the color of my pants. It's
not pink. As expected, I'm a cute princess.
Aaaaaaa,
no, I'm mixed.  I was told that I was being bossy when I opened that File Kirk, but I
chose the big one.I
love everyone, and I have free time,
and I'm getting married tomorrow.
If you're going to get married tomorrow, you'll have skin
[Music]
Boobahre I
couldn't translate it, but
aaa So, on this day, the question is, are you a negative person from that positive city?
4 Isn't that a lot in Japanese?
Hey, I thought you were talking about water in a glass, but when there's three-quarters of water in the glass, you're
saying, ``Oh, you know, car miscellaneous goods.'' Is it color?  I wonder if it's from Ninsaagakara.
Well, it's so foreign that it doesn't convey well. It's
as negative as aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa's-sssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssssss of of of being a country person to me. They
didn't even say that they were included at the meeting.I don't know.It
tastes like what generation of that computer it is.  Half of the story about what's inside the cup is half of the story, and
Omi Honoho is half of the story, and Sarada is half the story.If anything, I think I'm negative.I'm
negative.I know a little bit.The virtual version is still cars.Come on,
perseus wedding.  Nagu gangland argument ano
porridge beijing nude japanese came you do it's a
good idea don't throw it at the other fans Sky's amazing
line I see.
It's half-color, it's English, it's English,
hey, it's a
U-style bookshelf doctor, it's peeled pizza, I do
n't know if I can find the pineapple roux, so I pasted it up with flowers because it's
delicious,
e re the final, just cool.  It's more delicious if you eat it,
isn't it? It's delicious just for a moment, but I guess it's not very popular in Japan,
but there's a lot of war going on overseas. Ah, I wonder if it's
allowed to wear clothes like Peter Lee.  Ah, is the
ship full? This was a war battle, on Twitter, well,
at the time of my debut, I
took a survey, but really, it's
half of the time, and the number 10 is 10,000,000 Bakkart,
and gradually the good people are also administered, and the other
half.  It's really amazing to ride on the
rear guard pipe big demande anti-fog 5 the voodoo
Boo Boo Pineaporone I've
eaten it on pizza
ni ko Samorana then it's a branded
bar I've eaten it for generations that it's okay for professionals to put it on.  It's never happened before, right?
At the meeting, it's so far away that it's far away. I
can't say anything about the ticket. Oh yeah, it's going to be fun from now on.
Yes, Earth FC, it's Chirai in August. It's a peace facility in the 5 Paidapu zone.  The ridges are also blooming. Because
of Ebi-chan's tape, it's 4 Nataina Pon 3 P. I'm so happy that I used it 102 days ago. It
's really refreshing. It's a
quick taste, right? You're a major fan.  It's really delicious,
but I'm going to try it. I've never eaten it before,
and I'm seriously thinking that I should try that. I
'm sure there are people who don't like pineapple when I say pineapple on a large pizza.
8  I
also learned that Japanese people don't talk too much about that Thai 9, well, that
pizza doesn't really happen that much about Tainan's professional pizza.  That's
true for
Japanese people.Bread and pizza aren't that popular in Japan to begin with.I'm a bit of an
idiot, so if someone suddenly says something like that to me, I don't know if I'll ever see them again.I don't think it's
good enough.
That's pretty much what I've been saying,
Yayoi C. I get excited when I get a tropical feel.Ira
Darcy sites to do boots and die of natural causes at a harsh festival.That time
when I tried that food.Tell
me what you thought.Ryu Anately is good now.  I've finished the cross speed quiz, but I'm going
back to being a normal wife. I'm going to go back to being a normal wife.
Feather, papa, papa, this way,
legs, a. No, it's
wrong. 3rd place in the room.
Method
putter, all the agents. Re, Abe Zumukan.
Ah, this is ok.  Asaki Hodo,
Air English, Kokoda Sky Japanese, I'm reading it in Japanese, ah
, I'm a little confused in my head, but the water is
poisonous, and then I'm Astispi-kko, and I'm the Future Leader, with 3 colors,
Pension, as I
mentioned earlier,
Shion.  My senior has been expressing his distaste for Instagram for quite some time,
but when I looked at his surroundings, he turned into a perfect base girl bar, and Instagram was good for that role.
But it's impossible to hate, so I don't really want to hate it,
but I
guess Instagram is the kind of content that is woven together by cool people.  Well then, it's
not good for the committee members to carry it. It's a lie to think that there is some kind of situation at the Sakurai store.
No, I see that it's a dark root dark rice. Wow, the
customers have come in. The
ridges are also worms. As I just said, I like the human translation 3
caso.  deinem r stingray t ender ender
rasen usa reer reer enea reac car
blinker push-up bar
PR Bye-bye-bye Fiscard appointment push then that's it I'm
thinking for a moment Why is Twitter ok if that Instagram cherry blossom is not okay?
Everyone at Suneo's fishing star is using it. I see. I
like the one without wiping or turning.
[Music]
2 Shunsen
What is it? Lonely Garn.
Hey, I
think it's tough at home.
Then, Inushikura, what's wrong with that?
rc thunder ir advice earena game phrase kc sound place
4 f 4 sne line ota ku number
pearl pink cre per hour 6 move tour adventure
pa
But recently, Twitter has become a bit like Instagram.But
what?  Give it to me, Preet. Yeah, I really can't forgive it. There's
no need for a certain Watase. No one's fine with that. It's
too bad. Seriously, what kind of series are you trying to do and it looks like it's going to be fine? Then,
seriously, no.  4 Nyan Moment Island It's the
one who doesn't
know what to do, it's something that should be quiet Ah, when it happens, it
's so hot that it's Maru.
Spain, eh,
use me to do, do you like what I'm sending?
ani
he ran,
Bach Yoshii, that's what I wanted to hear from Yugami Sepa, who is a little like that. su,
dark carnep, 5 rows from Harukawa, chain
stake scene,
ee 6 e, ah yes.  It's
been a long time. Well, before this happens, I'm sure you know that the first foreign minister in that hood talk was Marin-senpai, but I'm sure you know that. It's already been 9 years since I said bye-bye.
When I asked you if you had anything important to support your seniors, you could talk about your memories with Shion-senpai.I'd
like you to take a look at that scene.Yes, I understand.It's okay if you look at it.It
's a haiku.
Well, I'm just looking at it.I'm going to show you a little bit right now.I have a lot of lower back pain.I
wanted to eat ROC, so go ahead.TBS, I'm
going to do Anna.Hey,
why, Shion, when I
was next to the person in charge,
what happened at night left an impression on me.I wonder why it was
.
Support week Glick Sharna sister
sexual ander push smart 4 s 1 c
delicious audio 5 minute app sa dena 1
with me mmf 4
3 minute suction morning pete dangerous lead senpai It
's long but actually it's that sepcial
night thing is shiontan  I'm pretending that it didn't happen
a It's been covered up Yes
z I don't know if you're saying it's retribution
Hahahaha yeah on the pine Sakushi-chan then the range is
2 minutes Hasher  No, ana, let's gather the values ​​in front of each other.
Birch Arc Ichimura's pin half body close-up.
Since we saw cows, scrapes, and biker eyes, Shion Kondo-senpai will also be on the talk show. Let's
read and listen. It's fine if you
listen directly. Please listen to me, please.  Eye View Gyachiyon Senpai Information Company It's a Big Problem Asuke Hatsu
C Sensei Appen
Yes Yes Yes Yes It's weird so I'd like you to tell me a little bit about the truth about love.What
happened?Well, it didn't
really happen.
At the meeting, I was a little curious about something,
so I looked into the difference, and I was
wondering if he was touching something.  Gaa degree Habyu
n one to do 3 items
window you say you have to do ni
Fielding Christine
Darby Harper's product Isn't something stuck?
Nothing ee Ah ha 4 There's nothing to answer. It wasn't
there anymore.  I
'm going to say that I like Sebu, a mountain road with a pinata pen and a staff who didn't have any skills. Do you say that you like Cebu, who lives in Aisai City and is sweet?
No, it's
true that my seniors, picture books, and Chong are true.  In the
middle of a mysterious battle, cheese synth Bezos seems like last month, but in my battle with 9 button multi-claw season,
that's strange, isn't it?  Is
that so? That's right, a
fan. It
's natural to hear that. Cheesy, you always prepare two
can you do the oscars. Strong.
Hmm.
Naoko. Now that's it. Well, that means that you were making out with them. Hey,
save yourself the trouble.  No, that's not okay,
Tanai-non-chan, Yu-o-porridge, etc. That's
right, so I'm
going to Oshio Prefecture.
Exercise size
voodoo control and other wired by Atowa
Shi faction side if Sunsun 2 b Wife is about to get married Come on,
Nara,
Emai-senpai
Was it Aso? Star-shaped eyes Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaasebeancellaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaay
Did you think it would be in Aso if you played with it?
Nabegoro
johan Then you or Athena Paint went north to Barb dissatisfied spoon ingredients. It
's a loss to play with that feeling. Case 2
Daijiko I think it's Mr. Kampf Shiun-senpai or someone like that.
No.  I
know Ruel to both hairs apb Hanyu's API number
Hey, I can't erase this because it's recorded that kind of thing that can't be erased.My
heart is in the radar star.It's
okay.Don't
look like a criminal.It
's Eightman
re 4
Yeah,
yeah, well, until it happens, this
will happen to Marin-senpai, so I'll ask for an avocet. Jawase, in other words, was
born by 2000 times. He's not doing anything anymore.
But we slept in the same bed,
right?  That's right, this Pad Zeniba cc is 2 strokes behind Oda Petty Pon in 9th place
Private area
But some people paid for something, but it's the head. I'm
also 3 seniors in Iito no Fuku Lab.
When I was supposed to do it.  There was a story about that, but when I stopped and stopped, I
stopped reacting due to my poor physical strength and bad ability to leave, but when I was being childish about it, there was a
story about how I ended up in the same house and bed as Mayu-senpai.  It turned
out to be Boo, and I was a bit worried about that, so I was sitting on top of it, and Una looked at the market price or something and told me about the furniture.  There was
no off-collaboration hahaha
re an rora me to do for seniors ea are
ide
amane j rem # ncp 2 good 6 action for
nec working
poor Kakashi Renu app anime and the senior couple Mine senpai is that kind of
buggy  I
want to do something wrong with Meowth, who is trying to plant trees in a clean house.The scene where he goes on a rampage like Pinata's.Ee, the
owner of Fink is in love with the toilet and the pen.I don't know what happened, but everyone is better.  That
's what I think, but
let's do it like that for the time being.I'm
going to ask my sister and Edge student Shinsha Matsuki.Here's the
medal.It's
almost the end of the year.
End It
's over, but do you have the most important memory of 2020? I
asked my seniors this question a while ago, and the story that came up was that story about Shin 1000x.
The corner where I was sitting, the
station, etc. I took that with me and thought about home too.
Tehayan
Sabai Disc Sank is a pop star 4 scene senior bar back pjs acquisition
too big big 3 items TPI Nemo Ushino then raise the bottom and go to the hot springs a little
more I want you to have a good story so that's it.  I don't think I'll tell you a story. Hey, yeah,
that's right. I wonder what 2020 really was like.
All the pictures and
all the things are still in my memories. It's been such an intense year, and it's already
gone so fast.  It's 2020. I've
had two live shows where it felt like that, and I can't believe it anymore. It
feels like before, but the
live shows have gotten bigger
.  I
think it's good that the new students have joined us.
Well, they must have been here for a long time.
Everything is new and it's memorable. There's
something special about this kid's broadcast. Even with this project, I can't use it.  Is there such a thing as
Planning Mother? I wonder
what it is. I wonder if it will
be easy.
[Music]
Think about this project. You can't get the role you want unless you write a book recently. That's how I translate it.
Yes, it's a fantasy-like story.  I came here to see the
cat.
Yes, it was the day I came to the city. It
was really fun to meet everyone and see the cherry blossoms melting away.
Oh,
the center is so nice. That's all.  That means you can meet me too. Let's
go to the oil painting. Woooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo gonna
meet me the rainy season ummmmm
prime shin
voodoo
for you air roaster special force charlie
and Tomikawa Kameido 4aaaaaaaaa swinging John Irving us waaaaaaaaaa
6 ea s see her to do sports
Schwan am papantsu
some mummy land house mcu enter chiasoi blanket panpipe serie toto
3 selection meeting etc. cuc  Donation Wiki Curve Amarone
Burner Meeting Monow Moni Surplus Azabu AB 9 Pin
5th Party
Not only those 4th generation students and 5 songs, but
also guest Indonesian 2nd generation students.
No, it's really a zone. No, it's
gotten bigger already.  It's 2020.
Well, next time, it's a little bit more than Kaa. I saw that the relationship with that lady was like that, but I
fell in love with her a lot four years ago, four years ago,
yeah,
well, that's so much.  At the very beginning of the episode,
Sora-senpai caught my eye, and that first year, Gober,
Shion-senpai was already there, but for some reason, it seems that the image showed
how many people have increased every other year.
All of them
were filming there, and as soon as I saw it, I
felt like wow, the original 6 had gotten bigger.
No, that's true.
As a new senior, I'm glad that more and more people are surpassing me.  It's a bit serious to cut it down, give me a break, is
n't this what you're talking about?
Oh no, it's impossible co
saitar racer semester day
urban open 4 ag 4 a scam good luck No. 8 Ender Sora Senpai
nandemo ap pojo nodus cero good moon
usi arm perseus  fc wife in place for a
Picard future cp 5 owners are you doing
Together we've become a big family.
Really, though, I
think the size of the current folder is just right for me every morning and evening.  I
see, it's definitely full already, that's right. It's
a bit dangerous if there's a collaboration at all with this Momo burger. Ah, there's only
4 for the Suke group. All of them are really big, so I think we can't get any more than this.
I was already in tears Ranran What happened Masu Kozumi
This is about
it I am just right
Byrne
Emma and Calm
Well, I'm happy to have any kind of people,
but I think the current number of people will make it feel more like a family. Yeah, it's true that if there are too many people, there won't be any
live shows. It's
okay if there are no modes.  3 d Well, I might not be able to do it.I think
next year, there will be Indonesia and other parties participating.I think it will be
three days.I might buy it.The
woman and the star.In
advance, by karin.The inscription is also peep.Damme bxx.Come on, mirror.  I'm
watching Boom Mappy in Kansai, and I'm watching a sweet pea-like muddy selection in Paris.Hero Wing
Shirley Majer's cauldron major
zun.Phoebe Mabe opf.Eraser in Kansai style.Oh, I
'm looking forward to Chinese originals.  I'm doing that audition with a feeling of
R Fun Fabba Ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
But I want to do this because it's the closest.
There are 6 rooms, so here you go. I
want to do my best. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to do it. I want to try it.
Now, I
also want to release a song that says I want to achieve this,
1 million people
, right?
[Music] I
won't say
that. It's a good thing that the Shikai passed away on the exam. Let's all register.
[Music]
Thank you.  I
hope most of you in Okinawa will register as well.
It's Shinobu-cho, the hidden entertainment shadow. I
want to be a married couple.
Hmm, I hope you see it. I'll do my best to speak as good as I can. It's
just right.  1 It's cold and first, the new Daisuke's total extension
Hey scene Chesou Pina Menu view dog pointed out good looks
A Watcher cafe expansion and Baikin pannugender Sai
Renge Aizu Aburikko pointer Resher with my tongue
Line jersey boom  First of all, I'm really looking forward to the Underground Bloomba this time.Well, it seems like they're going to
do it not only on the internet, but also on Layered.It seems like that
scene is
good too.  I
'm trying to tell the staff what a good day is and what they're going to tell me. I'm going to get caught out. I wonder if I'll get a seat to take a breather. Written by Mr. Minami, who used to be a castle. I
'll definitely go. I don't have time to do the same demonstration this time.  I'm going to watch the finished version live
from
rerere se blue du b
ameblo 4nah pper we are so op pop were to
do
Saito Zebu Akan-chan
horizontal screen is 3 Bokan birch full y-san  Step 1
But 3 I'm looking forward to seeing Cyan-senpai's idol-like appearance
Hey, Dorsey's sister Good luck with your training I'll do
my best yeah
3 Last question, but this is not a
moment It's okay, but for Shion-senpai, it's an unlimited club.
[Music] It
's been really since I've been to this live show that my life has changed and I think it's gotten brighter. I was really feeling cloudy, but I think it's because my life has started to drive and I'm having fun every day. Thank you very much.  masu
no
accare noire
life free chain to do scene
cars forever s 4 s and I'm totally good show power
, it's really going to change, isn't it? It's
really good, it's a tower flavor,
it's good, shunsen, my real place
today,
thank you very much,
read the gum  Lee
Jan Electric Road Sleep Bird
Horn Horn Horn Thursday Room Challenge In the Room Challenge Finally,
A memo Everyone is a small amount of energy on the amount ono
[Applause]
Ono again, the actual machine business
Ah,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, Japanese theory, Japan.
can use 20 det er jab ager big seam
Song Ha is the number of possessions on the team
Harvard bench screen How are you doing is
true, Harbor Harvard Well, it can't be helped since it's overseas.The
Japanese language is more of a problem.To the good kids.  It's already amazing
Who is Dow
? ana anh I can't talk Eibach
andere noreen japanese soup love anos in
japanese ah
That's why even Omi, which has already been introduced in Asia, is api. What's wrong is that the new starter at the station is the snow and the sea.
That last lever is
always Germany.  We greet each other in Japanese, but
at the end, we say, ``Ao Bida Hussein''. It's
like a place filled with sunlight that supports the Ao, Ni, and Ryu three scenes. Thank you everyone for today.
Thank you very much for
growing up.  Jump Store
ooooooooooooooooooooo
[Music]
Venture 3
Nwaaaaaaaaa I
can't get the fossil
hao
I'm vague I'm going to sleep with both of them now
Yes render
Aaaaaaaaaaaa
[Music]
Ta
Yeah
[Music]
me
ana
[music]
me
tee
[music]
th
e 7 a
[music]
dea