foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
me too today's photo karaoke today I
will be singing a lot of songs we'll be
celebrating where we'll be doing karaoke
with some of my friends
[Music]
um as you guys can tell I kind of
started the stream early Meetup
[Music]
um there's a few things that I want to
explain to you guys which is why I kind
of started this thing a little bit early
Mary Mary
hello welcome welcome welcome so let me
let me explain to you guys how this
thoughts of karaoke will work because
you know
Ollie you're going to call people and
have them do karaoke wouldn't there be a
delay no actually I've already planned
this for quite a long time uh how this
will work is that first of all I will
um
so first of all I asked all of my
friends to send them a pre-recording of
their karaoke with me daddy only the
bloom harini although that means
America I'll only be singing to their
pre-recorded videos
[Music]
yeah
that's how it will work the thing is I
uh
for this year there won't be that many
people in my toots
[Music]
yeah
um
was it like 60 or 50 people I forgot I
invited quite a lot of people
um
for uh last year but for this year
um I only have limited slots I only have
limited songs that I can sing hence uh
there won't be that many yeah um
foreign so
[Music]
happy birthday thank you
apples
and I also have one thing I'd like to
explain so I will be dividing today's
segment into today's uh what is it
called today's
today's event into two parts yeah into
two segments
segment yeah
life member yeah so so
there will be a segment for Holiday
members and non-allife members because I
think it's going to be easier for me to
list them off as much as I want to mix
them like the holiday members with my
non-hollow friends it'll be a little bit
hard to keep track of all of the videos
so yeah I'll be dividing them into two
but don't worry
it'll be cool the the non-hollow life
members it will start at about 7
00 PM ish
is it no no no it'll start about 6 p.m
got a guarantee
there's no guarantee to these videos but
it'll most likely start at 6 00 p.m my
time for the non-hallalife uh friends
yeah yeah gym people are seven exactly
yeah how long is this gonna be uh it
won't be too long last year we were
going on for about what five six hours
this year will only be going for I don't
know four hours
foreign
yeah
he'll be playing everything
so I'll I'll be singing and it'll be
pretty cool and that's about it now let
me show you guys a little sneak peek of
our first gift
foreign
I'll be showing you guys the first gifts
[Music]
I mean silhouettes of them there's one
two three four five six seven eight nine
right yeah nine people
they will be our uh quote-unquote
opening act
um
[Music]
I wonder who they are well only one way
to find out are you guys ready for the
tatsuki
cause I know I am
well without further Ado let's get into
it
five four three two one
[Music]
Little Things
my mind
[Music]
foreign
get done
breaks
[Music]
[Applause]
no more
break
it's Halloween
you ready
[Music]
time
machine
[Music]
attack
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you so much for letting me sing
with you happy happy birthday
thank you so much only for always being
the sweetheart that you are without you
oh this place would be such a dark place
thank you for being who you are keep on
doing what you do and I wish you all the
best much love to you love all
thank you
enjoy your special day thank you
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
today
[Music]
Let's Dance
baby
yes
[Music]
good night
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
happy birthday to you happy birthday to
you happy birthday
oh
happy birthday to you
today
[Music]
me too I am very happy to be able to
sing with early Senpai yeah
I wish you a very wonderful day
[Music]
let's sing together
[Applause]
Mommy
bye
[Music]
let's go let's go
mommy darling
[Music]
well yeah all your loves lollies
foreign
[Music]
send me something
never again
[Music]
foreign
la la la la la la
happy birthday
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
hi happy birthday
[Music]
foreign
I'll see you again
[Music]
bye
yesterday
[Music]
get it
foreign
there you go wow
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
today
[Music]
come on
you clean it
clean it well that's it we'll climate
fails
[Music]
anymore
Uganda
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
because
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
bye
happy
[Applause]
um
okay
okay music
hey ladies
[Music]
have a nice yes
thank you
[Music]
baby
relax
foreign
[Music]
United
[Applause]
[Music]
happy birthday thank you
hey
audience
[Applause]
today today
is is
singing together today today okay okay
yeah yeah yeah yeah only until it's not
do you understand
and do think with me singing together
I understand yes
[Music]
and do
come down is that okay yeah fine
two
one
music could fails let's go
[Music]
he died
[Laughter]
he's dead
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
together
[Music]
[Applause]
here we go
[Music]
foreign
you ready
happy birthday
[Music]
okay bye bye bye
tomorrow
foreign
[Music]
for me
[Applause]
[Music]
you're welcome
circulations
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
so sorry
foreign
[Music]
and now you're here
foreign
[Music]
this is
foreign
[Music]
Ginger
thought you guys tonight
[Music]
take a selfie
selfie selfie
[Music]
[Laughter]
people
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
together
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
hello
that was it so to put it simply
um those are the pre-recorded ones yeah
so I got I got yelled at my M10 she told
me there's no way you're going to be
singing this many songs in one stream
pre-record some of them and I said okay
ma'am okay
um
good call gotta take care of your voice
he was the one who inspired me to do
this she was also doing her own it was
like a Christmas special she also did a
like a Halloween special wait wait the
sad is oops
yeah it was a Christmas special and
anyways um let's not talk about that
we're going to move on to our next
session let me just move myself a little
bit only uh
so we already had our first nine people
um
these are going to be our next batch of
people
there's about one two three four five
six seven eight nine nine people happy
birthday thank you
yeah yeah thank you for with me
oh I wonder who'll be singing next and
the thing is I'll be singing live for
these people
live
hopefully we can get through all of them
uh smoothly so without further Ado
um
let's get into it go go
oh wait I'm sorry uh
I'll adjust my my voice so that I don't
overpower anyone else get my Reverb on
Playa
okay
first song
I'm still big
Empire
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
tonight
all right
together
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
how are you
[Music]
and that was the first
um karaoke live birth
I'm sorry if I butchered the song turns
out I don't I I have the lyrics with me
it's just that I'm just a little bit
nervous like hopefully the next one I
won't be so nervous so let's get into it
I
am
[Music]
done
thank you
[Music]
foreign
is
super good
[Music]
yay happy birthday thank you
um
oh my God how how long ago was that um
[Music]
and let you know okay yeah yeah we shall
definitely Place something together
um someday soon
yeah let's let's collapse something I
heard you were gonna play Rust if you
have any question about the game feel
free to hit me up on DM anytime thank
you so much for singing together with me
thank you
song you weren't doing so well thank you
and hopefully you will enjoy the rest of
your birthday
Ollie I can't wait for the merchandises
um if um yeah I don't I'm not sure if
they get they're like announced already
before the karaoke
are they yeah maybe future me knows oh
really thank you so much for having me
early and happy birthday
and that was my lovely done mate uh just
a moment next stop getting ready for the
next one the next one I'm actually very
nervous about this one I think I think
this one okay last song I kind of
butchered but I promise hopefully I'll
do better on this song no
Honey Senpai happy birthday thank you
for invite me today my pleasure I hope
your happiness in this year and please
collaboration collaborate with me yes a
lot okay okay today we gonna
sing sexy sexy sexy sexy sexy
sexy my outfit is for yoshima
[Music]
foreign
don't know
[Music]
foreign
it is
[Music]
foreign
tonight
[Music]
oh
my God
[Music]
I love you
thank you Louie
yeah so how did you guys like it
with Louie I'm sorry about that that
part I I just had to add a little bit
spicy you know make it a little bit
spicy
here comes the next song you guys ready
good morning afternoon evening everyone
[Music]
happy happy birthday Ollie I'm so happy
I could be here for your birthday
celebration
yeah he's fun so far I am it's so fun
[Music]
well I hope you have a wonderful
wonderful wonderful year with a lot of
happy things lots of good food lots of
fun fun fun stuff yeah thank you anyways
I fully we're gonna be singing the uh
song together yes right that's right
ah what are you guys think oh yeah yeah
we're gonna sing
Alien aliens yeah we're both not aliens
gonna be for yeah three minutes yeah for
the song yeah okay let's go let's go
[Music]
go go go go go go go
go
[Music]
surprise
tonight
[Music]
huh
hey guys
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
that was good yay yay
I hope I did uh good job as you do it
partner Ollie hello it was more than
great happy birthday again
uh I'm gonna give you a big big hug
through uh I guess uh
I'm giving you a big air hug right now
okay I'll give you a bigger hug too
and that has been uh Nino my inami's
Senpai hmm we sang alien alien together
and next up we're going to move to a
different uh
can you guess who's our next guest yeah
hey it comes
hey Ali happy birthday and I hope you're
having a good one oh I am I just wanted
to tell you how approachable friendly
and sweet you are and you're kind of
one of uh yes hype women
of hollow live and that's what I really
like about you and
you know if you're interested I would
like to collab with you again yes it's
not like I want to collab with you
but well anyway we have a song to do so
let me pull up my imaginary mic let's go
yes
well there we go three two one
hi how many people say all right
[Music]
hey it's amazing
foreign
[Music]
it's not a crazy guy no song
once again thank you ollie and
I hope you have a great one thank you
congrats you all from curling eyes she's
she's very sweet makes me happy Hi and
then uh not far from crony we got our
next guest coming up
let's go audience
[Music]
Daddy
numbers
[Music]
you're working
again
[Music]
you're a king
Anthony
[Music]
oh he's just so cute I'm sorry if my
voice was a little too high for you Puma
[Music]
foreign
spicy if that's not enough hint for you
guys let's go
[Music]
to another place
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
mm-hmm
the goddess of
so you guys will know who
it's going to be the same song
yes we have limited songs
I hope you guys understand
let's go
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
um
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
I I gotta look for the
uh lyrics
[Music]
[Applause]
tonight
[Music]
you're working
tonight
[Music]
you're lucky
thank you
foreign
all right everybody let me drink just a
little bit next up we'll have our second
act so we had the opening act we have
the first egg and next up will be the
second act let me just scoot over over
here and let me show you who's
in it who's in the runner-ups runner-ups
is that away
[Music]
and FYI these are going to be
pre-recorded I'm going to rest up a bit
after this so uh what you guys are going
to see next they are well yeah
I wonder who whom well only one way to
stop only one way to find out tomorrow
[Music]
responsive
I hope I said that right you did happy
birthday Ollie I hope you are having the
most amazing birthday ever thank you so
much for inviting me to sing with you
we're gonna be singing order by other
yeah and I'm really excited are you
ready is everybody ready I'm ready I got
my echo on I'm ready you ready I'm ready
and
then
okay
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
having an amazing birthday and get
spoiled because you deserve it oh shut
up yeah I love you too okay bye
okay
let's go I'll leave let's go sorry
[Music]
foreign
come on
hey
hey everybody
sorry for being cringed on your stream
no you're not
suit them away
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
hey hey hey
hands up
[Music]
I thought you guys
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
yes thank you who are always caring
about a approach
and we are greatly helped by origin by
kindness and we have a lot of respect
for origin pie today
it is
or you do be wondered
everything about with me hi
it's a new doll
let's go hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey
hey hey hey
yes
you want
[Music]
oh one night I
we can't say nothing
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
yeah yeah
super machine
[Music]
my sister birthday
foreign
[Music]
oh
this is
[Music]
foreign
whoa
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
thank you
okay wanted to say a little bit sorry
for the last one apparently the volumes
were not balanced at all I'd like to see
a very very big sorry
[Music]
I don't know what to say
we can maybe do an encore later and we
can redo it
it's hard because everybody sends in
like different frequencies different
volumes of videos your submissions are a
little bit different so but I'm still
very very sorry for the inconvenient
so to be honest we still have a few more
time until the next segment and I don't
know what to do oh I want to say thank
you too I I saw a lot of people there
was uh Kyla there was rainy I saw there
was Dad aka Cali Senpai there's also Rio
ryokan was also here but I didn't get to
greet you because I was I was doing
something else behind the scenes
checking everything up and then uh there
was also magni right this man was also
here yeah yeah yeah and Mary's still
here
hello wolf that's how Mary talks like
hello yes I am Merryweather woof
Kayla yo
I still have four songs to go before we
go to the non-hollow segments
maybe we can sing one song first
one song so that we don't waste too many
time and then we can get into the
announcements
segment coming up but next up I guess
I'll be singing one song and once the
timer hits five five five then that's
when we go to the announcement and
promotion area so allow me
so the next uh batch of people will be
oh very a very con not really contrast
but it's like the same species of color
who might it be I wonder
will only be singing one song from them
because after this I'm getting kissed by
the schedule man I don't know
heightened up uh let's sing one of them
starting from well well
is everybody ready
next week I gotta get that lyrics first
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
tell me that me chanisms
hi hi hi hi
hi hey
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
hi John debris
like at home
[Music]
happy birthday I'll listen bye I love
you much I love you too thank you for
the cake I really loved it a lot and
that has been okay now we really need uh
it was fun singing with Zetta but we
really need to get onto the schedule
we're getting chased so let's go back
here
you guys know what time it is it is time
for announcements pew pew
so first announcement that I'd like to
tell you guys is but bam I'll be having
my own radio showy I don't know this is
a semi-weekly semi-monthly radio show
where I do radio show every uh uh once
every two weeks
not really we'll be reading fan letters
and whatnot it's basically those FMS
that you guys listen to when you guys
are in your cars it'll be my own radio
channel
thank you so much lovely lovely Lego
bam I'm sorry if it's only
we're getting chased by the time
so if you guys have seen your icon frame
is actually a very big spoiler for the
um what is it called for the goods that
I will be releasing yeah
yeah
hi let me let me move myself a little
bit over here okay let me show you guys
what's in store
so first of all we no no no no this is
this is not okay it took hi so you guys
will be getting five items if you guys
buy the full set there is the rubber mat
there's also uh this is what you guys
have been asking me for uh a necklace
version of my sword yeah the sword's
name is
which means path of sincerity
yes Indonesia and then we also have
Royal protection for your iPads for your
pen tabs for your laptops yeah you can
use it for quite a while and then we
also have a bath bomb whoa a bath bomb
yeah so you can actually smell like me
once you take a bath
postcard illustrated by The One and Only
lovely
my style let's take a little look see a
little more that there will also be
voice sets back a lot of voice certified
so we have the behind the scenes behind
the scenes is only in Indonesian
behind the scenes
this and then we have the situational
voice in the name of Justice
bit this we have a Japanese version and
an English version uh the Japanese
version I think I did really well on it
so please do look forward to it we have
bonus voices too we have the
bonus voice and we have script made of
eat voice recordings
yeah very pretty
I really like this I'm going to I'm
going to use this as my profile picture
later hey
and then here's a little little more
peek on the rubber mat and there will
also be a postcard with a handwritten
autograph and message I did that by
myself I wrote I literally handed it
like a lot of them so I'm hoping that
you guys can get it the link is already
in the description below I updated just
now so be sure to look it up yeah
um
the link is in the description below and
here's the Bundle sale here's the merch
set there's a voice set there's
individual sales and whatnot coming in
even the packaging is so royalty like
it's
these are this is actually very cool
wait until you guys get this thing
because
like when you peek inside it's like a
whole new world you get to see me
there's like a logo inside it's a very
very uh fancy I'm sorry Lily I need to
get your bath bomb in such a great
concept right please
please the link is in the description
below I can't wait to hear all of your
reviews everybody
and then we also have
there's a little sneak peek there's a
little wooden uh charm that you guys can
take off and on on and off so so you
guys can literally put the wooden
anywhere in your necklace it's pretty
cool
I love the necklace so much I know super
cute isn't it it's silver too a bit
heavy but hey we can finally have the
same sword you guys have us have the
same sword on your neck I have the same
sword on my head it's pretty cool and
yeah this is the rubber mat it's it's
super cool I love the illustration and
that's about it please do check it out
buy it it's in the link in the
description below I told you guys to not
super chat before this moment so that
you guys can get it today thank you so
so so do that
and that's about it
yeah we're going to continue singing now
that looks so good you'll buy it right
you'll buy it right you'll freaking buy
it right
yeah it's better because I put a lot of
thought into it and all the stuff worked
really hard so it can come true fast mom
rubber mat there's also what was it
there's also the necklace
what's the other thing again
and and the other thing
absolutely sold out that item's so cool
is it
yeah
the link is in the description below
put it tonight
[Music]
I really really love uh
picture drawings illustrations it's so
amazing you guys will not regret buying
it because it's just so beautiful it is
royalty themed and yeah
now back to karaoke I'm going to
all right next up
we've already seen the preview so let's
just get into it shall we no not here
everyone's here
all right
instance okay
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
you live with me
thank you
[Music]
foreign
hi hi hi hi
yes
[Music]
Hallelujah
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
bye-bye
and that has been fun with me and gura
bye
I wonder who
um
[Music]
laughs
yeah
[Music]
let's go
laughs
foreign
[Music]
let's go
do do
foreign
[Music]
la la la
la la la la la la la la la la la la la
la
la la la la
la la
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
well me too um
uh confirm you guys give you guys a
disclaimer that was pre-recorded
uh she's
um she got the virus the C virus got
thing how much I hate that c virus and
let's just hope for uh
for her safety for the best of her
health let's pray for her so that she
gets better soon okay
[Music]
section
I want
there's a but how do I explain
this is going to be the final
Hollow
karaoke before we get into the
non-hollow one I saved it for last
because it's just the best
and I'm just so proud of them uh your
set doesn't deliver in Europe I hope the
people who can get it enjoy it though it
looks amazing thank you I'm so sorry
that it doesn't hopefully one day hmm
yeah this is I literally saved the best
one for last I'm just so proud of them
uh they're my they're my pride and joy
everything they do inspire me also and
I'm always wishing the best for them
they put a lot of effort into the next
karaoke you guys you guys will know once
once I play it
yeah so uh Feast your eyes get ready
ladies and gentlemen for the last but
not least
hello Tempest
[Music]
[Applause]
your your
[Music]
s
enjoy
[Music]
wait was it double the audio I'm sorry
was it double let me play it again okay
it has to be perfect
there we go
[Music]
happy birthday
my goodness
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
so he's dead
yourself
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
I'm so proud of you boys thank you
now tell me that wasn't fire tell me
that wasn't so cool so
oh my God
so so uh here's a little story before we
get into the next segment
I asked the boys one by one I asked them
individually hey I'm doing this happy
birthday even now
did you see how tempuses cover karaoke
of snow and lotion okay so here's let me
tell you let me spill the tea I asked
them all individually hey do you want to
be in my tootsukara Yoki I'm planning it
for my birthday I'm inviting a lot of
people do you guys wanna be in it and
then they said yeah sure but then they
figured out by themselves oh my God
we're all invited we might as well sing
as one let's sing snow halation because
we're almost no uh not snow halation
love life uh fans and I'm like oh my God
you guys want to sing as a group and
you're like yeah and so we distributed
the lyrics and then they started
recording they even had it mix if if I'm
correct coroni helped them mixed it like
listen I told everyone you know if you
guys do you guys want to come to my
thoughts of karaoke it's for fun you
guys don't need to take it too seriously
we're just going to have fun singing and
but no they took it to another level
they had Corona mixed it uh Desmond was
the one who rendered the whole thing
it's just amazing
and I'm just so proud of them ah my my
little mums kitties
say I'm very very proud of all of them
but please do support them and everyone
else who sang with me now after this
will be the non-hollow segment
I'll be singing with all of my uh
non-holiday friends and
um sadly I don't have the previous to
who I'll be singing with
but it'll be it'll be awesome I I
promise you I'll introduce them all one
by one before I start singing and all of
them will be song live
no pre-recorded uh pre-recorded for
non-hollow yeah you got this whoa thank
you
[Music]
gosh there's so many people here all
right so let's go here
all right
our body ready for the first song
the first non-hollow
karaoke I I'm excited all right
what
is huh is is hello hello can you guys
hear me
hello
everything good
we're back are we back
don't do this to me YouTube come on it's
my birthday I'm just I'm just a little
guy and it's my birthday can't you work
well for once come on work
work okay come on we barely started
I wanna I wanna start the non-hollowing
or are we goodness is everybody okay
Papa
come on it's my birthday
let me introduce you guys to our very
first non-hello she is the one who
inspired me to do this she is so nice
she's super kind full of energy she's in
basically an inspiration she's she's so
fluent and and a great singer and well
well and she is also an ambassador for
play Asia everybody give it up four
obake Palm
[Music]
come on
foreign
[Music]
tonight
again
everybody
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
picking yourself
nothing
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
I am sincerely thank you so much it's
just it's amazing to sing with you and
you know again like I said she also took
it to another level C put Harmony
in it goddamn did you know Harmony
so it sounded super super cool
she's poggers really she went exactly
she went the extra mile thank you Palm
[Music]
now next is from a very very
close friend of mine my favorite elf
she uh she she comes to the comments
section quite a lot I bet you guys are
very familiar with her get ready for Rey
levere
day oh my God can you guess it's been a
year no are you happy I I hope you've
been happy and as your number one fan
all right guys
I'm very excited to be with you here
today can't wait to sing together and
the crowd is not gonna believe what
we're gonna sing without further Ado and
no time wasting because it is the big
birthday girls
special day let's get started in the
music in three
two
one
[Music]
me today
no Pandora
[Music]
he be there
tonight
[Music]
foreign
together
[Music]
exercise
[Applause]
[Music]
I forgot sometimes
there's Parts where you sing and in
Parts where I say so I have to hold back
by singing But like because I don't want
to oh like how do you say it I love this
song so much and I know you so I feel
like because we're Filipino 11 fans
Sports because it's such a fun song
Thank you for inviting me to sing along
with you and I hope you have a very
wonderful birthday I will be like
already and I hope everyone here enjoys
Ollie's birthday as well you better or
else
thank you thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
isn't she just the cutest that has been
Ray levere everybody might get elf
friend and and you know we're both
Inazuma Eleven nerds
and I'm so happy I finally found someone
who I can just vent about another one I
love you no I freaking love you more and
I think I saw excellent Zeta in the chat
hello the cat and dogs are here what up
guys
did you guys see your party you both
sing snow halation
I'm so happy bro the godhan POG exactly
I love her so much I love her for
singing this with me
and then next up we have a song
also about a very good friend of mine
you guys are definitely familiar with
him if you guys are not familiar with
him that means you guys are not
subscribed to my channel if you yeah it
is and hello
me song I think you guys will like this
next song I love it as much as my
um
water tastes good make a look yes
so
you look at it
next song
oh bam
[Music]
oh sorry about that let's go
you ready
[Music]
Hallelujah
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
better like that
yo kokoro tomorrow
that has been
from Japan
if you guys
followed me for quite a long time we
play Apex together we're really good
buds he he's awesome yeah
it's awesome how he agreed to sing the
song with me I was like is there any
song that you fancy and he's like ah
yeah sure
really good sport please do check him
out next up I also have another guy
friend
um you guys don't see me and him
interacting that much we didn't track a
lot in Twitter
not that much on stream but he's a
really good friend we DM each other a
lot he always checks up on me
a very sweet guy he is a demon his name
is otaku Maru bubs
oh shoot wait let me birthday Ollie I
hope you're having a wonderful day today
I'm sorry I forgot that I said I'm sorry
that was not intentional
all right I promise you guys we have a
platonic relationship there is no need
to to oh my God
no no we're we're buddies I'll make it
he's taken anyways
so anyways let's go Bobs
happy birthday Ollie I hope you're
having a wonderful day today on your
special day yeah
it's like it's our turn so let's get to
it yeah what's wrong with my avatar
yo yo yo oh you're making it's weird I'm
sorry I'm sorry you promise
[Music]
come on
sunny days
[Music]
something
good night
tonight
[Music]
thank you
sunny day life
[Music]
foreign
yes you're a lovely lovely wiggling feet
yeah
you're going to show me more right
that wink was a yes right right we're
going to see more of those feet right
bubs answer me sunny day line sunny day
life
[Music]
foreign
oh
[Music]
happy birthday again Ollie thank you for
the year of uh oh it's happening year
round we love you thank you love you too
platonically good buds yeah
let me spell it out for you guys
otaki with o t a k e m a r
uh space
b u b s sometimes I mistakenly read his
name that has boobs I'm in the knees and
give me a break
ready welcome there's so many people
coming to say hello on my birthday if
this Thrills me with so many happiness
I'm so happy and and I'm still here
I'm so loved I'm so blessed I'm just so
I'm just so happy to be here guys darn
all right next song
running on a schedule we can't uh as
much as I want to continuously introduce
you guys to Bub's oh fabulous toes we
can't do that and run I hope you're
having a great day I am I am it's been
so fun and um next person
uh someone very dear to me someone who I
care for a lot she's a fellow zombie if
that's not a big enough uh spoiler
I'm sure you guys have seen her before I
was also in her birthday stream we were
playing Apex Ian will be singing
[Music]
let's go
Anita what time is
um
foreign
ah
wait not yet this is opening
hi
sick
[Music]
it's a zombie Club nice
is there any zombie lips here I'm so
glad I get to sing this with her
keep the zombies
[Music]
baby
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
I love her so much
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
I
she's adorable I love her and um here uh
there's a little reminder from M10 M10
told me that
um so that so that yeah
I'll be uh pending the oh shoot
okay uh just a moment
I'll be pinning this
these are the what is it called the
links to my birthday merchandise if you
guys forgot I have a rubber my hand I
have a necklace I have a
I'll read that that that a protector
holder thingy
and then I also have the bath bomb and
postcards
already sold out what do you mean
it says 404.
that couldn't be true your internet just
sucks there's no way it just sold out
sold out what do you take me for
hi yeah
[Music]
um
it's not a broken link
404 it's not found I wonder why what did
it
I'm copy pasting the same thing though
weird
but I think it's also in Twitter so
please be sure to check it out yeah
Hi and then next stop
is also someone that I care very very
deeply for she's been an inspiration
before I debuted I I I used her as a
reference a lot we're both sisters she's
the closest sister that I have
and her name is
[Music]
this
you put Three Links together that's why
it's uh
oof okay um that happened I'll change
that after this song I'm going to have
fun with my makeup
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
coming up come here
foreign
[Music]
from the use of material lifesaver thank
you I'll be putting your uh comment
instead
[Music]
I was super super happy that I got to
sing with you I I I've always thought
that that song matched our Vibe and I'm
just so happy that we got to sing it
please do check out he's amazing and
very very cute she also has original
songs it's really dope you guys really
want to check it out I'm not leaving
lying you guys won't regret it hi next
stop is a
is a
friend
from the Philippines
Philippines
we're going International we're going
from Japan to Indonesia yes
this is from a bread girl
very very cute bread girl I've always
been I always lurk in her streams a lot
she's super cute and today I have the
biggest Joy of singing with her
please give it up
from the Philippines pan V tuber
hi aliens only thank you for inviting
the Filipino bread to this collaboration
and happy birthday
I'm so happy that you're here
you see nothing but the mess you're the
most amazing and here we go me and the
zombies bread collaboration let's go
[Music]
foreign
give me well either
[Music]
[Applause]
is there videos
[Music]
do that
When I Dance
[Music]
tomorrow
foreign
[Music]
from the Philippines and the YouTuber
she's amazing she's a great singer I am
freaking in love with her she's a please
do take her out she was in the chat she
gave a Super Chat even so you guys can
check her out there yeah awesome All
Right Moving On
next song
um
let me hear you go Baba
come being
yep you guys are right it's
Indonesia let's bring her in happy
birthday
on happy birthday
thank you
[Music]
um
Young
[Music]
because
she died
[Music]
foreign
it says
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
let's go
thank you
foreign
[Music]
and the lyrics were down there
so I'm gonna change the position if I
look weird singing I'm sorry I wanted to
look weird singing before anyways hi and
the next will also be a K on song hukago
tea time from a doggo who really likes
eggs
[Music]
you guys smell
hi that's right next up it'll be Connor
karate individual from Indonesia
I'm
[Music]
happy happy happy happy birthday
[Applause]
[Music]
birthday happy special holiday oh my
gosh thank you so much for inviting me
today my pleasure
hi oh oh my gosh yes I wanted to to wish
you
happy birthday of course I I wish you
the best birthday of all birthdays on
the entire planet yeah
[Music]
I hope another year is gonna be filled
with joy and laughter and happiness and
wives I mean subscribers I mean more
more subscribers
[Music]
I hope all that you wish for comes true
this year and you'll have another year
full of fun
okay other than that yes how do you feel
about singing another song tonight oh I
would love another song
it's it's I I've prepared a song
actually
um it's called
you know it
um
perfect perfect I swear it's a fun song
okay I I can promise you that
okay let's let's get started and have
some fun shall we let's go
[Music]
foreign
imagination
[Music]
[Laughter]
one of the best best things to have for
lunch with rice
you'll never guess it's like the best
absolute best what is it
[Music]
stay welcome
foreign
[Music]
again happy birthday to you your special
day thank you so much for being a part
of all of our lives and what would we do
without you no
I hope you have a wonderful wonderful
one wonderful birthday tonight for sure
I'll see you later okay see you later
bye
bye bye always
bye bye bye she's adorable I love her
please do support her kind of tomato
everybody in the beach bear from
Indonesia
haha
I'm not blushing you are
uh
I think it's about time I change my
clothes I've been wearing this for quite
a while let's change the mood a little
bit let's let's go for ah let's go for
Miss Mafia
how's that sound I'll cover the whole
screen with my fabulousness
am I right
Hi and then next up speaking of fabulous
we're going to bring a very fabulous
person
in she's a singer she's also a YouTuber
now
she she has she only has one night
though
purple here you guys know who I'm
talking about right
coming from Indonesia let me introduce
you guys to Richie
[Music]
Zombie Birthday
I'd ask how old are you but like yeah I
know I don't think it's appropriate plus
you're like Undead so like it doesn't
really matter
yeah thank you so much for inviting me
to your birthday celebration I have a
little bit of a request for you I I hope
I hope you can do this I wanna I'm
seeing something with you today
hopefully we can sing something fun uh
can you can you guess can can anyone in
chat also guess what we're gonna sing
hint I really like Deco Nina
don't tell me it's zombie that's right
it's she knows those goodbye declaration
yay
you think it would be zombie right now
now because who else would I go crazy in
the town with except for my good pal
crazy Ollie
Jesus anyway
um well uh I I hope we can have some fun
and sing along and stuff and um I guess
without further Ado let's let's start
let's go okay okay let me get the music
[Music]
Ally hi hi hi
foreign
[Music]
that's another one
she's my friend she's amazing
school she has a Teddy a very just like
me too crazy
[Laughter]
[Music]
thank you
let's go
[Music]
yeah
thank you
[Applause]
yay
[Music]
exactly we go crazy in the town first
there's also that one part where it goes
[Music]
um I hope you got lots of cake
um I hope you get to sing a lot of songs
today and oh this is it over now thank
you
and that everybody is a mystery she is
an Indonesian
she's talented she uh what I like about
her the most is that she does this toad
voice
and it's
scary very similar she she sings a
little voice you guys wanna check her
out happy birthday
thank you for the Super Chat I
appreciate it a lot all right next up
you guys know who he is
we've collapsed so much he's he um
people compliment me a lot for for being
friends with him apparently
[Music]
um
the with the voice of a seiyu that
sparkles in a glimmer of night here we
go
to Bear are from Japan
happy birthday thank you
thanks for inviting me to karaoke
together
um
foreign okay
I
sorry music
yourself
[Music]
let's go
um
[Music]
show me
zombies
[Music]
foreign
show me shoes
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
it's a very difficult song but I'm glad
I got to sing it with him yeah that was
fun hi it's uh moving on next one oh she
she is just amazing uh she is an icon
she's ah she's ah
she's very kind uh you guys have seen
her in Twitter she keeps on greeting me
she was there on my account down she she
replied to me she gave me a present and
now she's going to be singing with me a
very good friend of mine from Neapolitan
Japan
let's
do that
[Music]
hi hi
foreign
[Music]
I might get to know you better let's
play together again sometime today
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you
that surprised me
she goes down and then she goes back
again
she plays Apex she's amazing and singing
she's the sweetest heart that you guys
will ever meet please do check her out
too
please stay please hold don't go
anywhere
foreign
[Music]
oh yeah
me is it
we still have one two three four five
six we still have ten more about ten not
exactly 10 but about 10 more
should I change my clothes too so that I
don't get in anyone's way I'll do that
actually
so that um
I don't know
you know block people off my ears
ridiculously big so I'm going to stick
with this one honey next up
also from the Philippines I'm sure you
guys already know because he promoted on
bullets Youtube Community he tweeted it
out he's a very cool guy I'm like BFF
yes it is time let us
um
bring forth
a d
uh wine of Shania I'm sorry what was it
again he's just a really good voice
actor he's also very entertaining of
YouTuber give it up for coming you do
oh hi it's everyday Filipino from Tamia
your um best friend yes best friend wink
Wong
and before anything else I would like to
say happy birthday Ollie thank you I
can't believe you're turning birthday
too this year oh my god
um congratulations on your
birthday oh we grow up so fast don't
they they turn and this year and they
turn next year oh man oh how time flies
really and uh it really means a lot to
me being able to celebrate it with you
on your birthday
but anyway
um I wish you nothing but happiness this
year thank you and today I'm going to
sing you a very special song called
Is This Love Is This Love how about it
Ollie are you ready oh I'm ready
satito
Hajime
for our friendship
all right there's a lot of things I want
to say tonight
can one of them being is for a birthday
girl
Ollie yes will you take my hand by any
means
[Music]
let's go Jill we got this it's in a bag
foreign
[Music]
good guy
foreign
[Music]
call me off guard there God there
the soul
but yeah that has been
BFF
come here dude
yeah he he's a he's a really good
support check him out to his channel you
guys just missed it he was also a
moderator you guys can quickly check his
journal out he's a really cool guy
yes hi nah next up this is going to be a
little bit weird
with the song choice and everything
but but but next up is um
one of my Apex codes I'm sure you guys
know her she is also my niece she's the
daughter of rpr there's a lot and
somehow
aniki is involved with her kind of the
aniki of her but he's supposed to be an
uncle the family tree goes both with a
lot of ways
yes next up will be singing with ditto
are you guys ready and the YouTuber
family is a little bit complicated it's
oh
hello hello Ollie and everyone happy
birthday Oli thanks for inviting me
today
um I'm so glad that I have a chance to
sing a song with you yes okay that song
that we're gonna see today is Let's Be
Friends
I want to be more than friends though
okay we lady let's go let's go
[Music]
let's be friends
all we gotta do just be friends
It's Time to Say Goodbye just be friends
[Music]
just be friends just be friends
this again
[Music]
all we gotta do is be friends just be
friends just be friends
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
just be friends
let's be friends
[Music]
thank you honey thank you next time
thanks for singing with me today
[Music]
bye bye love you
okay so I know what you guys are
thinking God damn Ali knows a lot of
Japanese YouTubers but a little
disclaimer a lot uh a little disclaimer
alert she is not Japanese she's just a
very good at Japanese her Japanese is
just so bad up at a level she is
actually Thai
Thailand
[Music]
so that was uh a little from time
cute isn't she her model is just super
duper cute
all right we got a little sappy but I
think it's about time we pump it up a
notch don't you guys agree
how about we get
a little crazy
sing a little something that boosts
their morals up I know I know what you
guys are thinking God dang it's almost
been what four hours she's still going
at it I'm getting tired okay here's a
song to boost your energy up I'm singing
it with a very uh
a very good friend of mine uh she's from
Incorporated wait what is that how you
say it
yes
Play One and Only
crazy unit
I
know
happy birthday
foreign
[Music]
I don't know
email
[Music]
s
foreign
[Music]
to thank you
again
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
the times
happy birthday yay
if you can't already tell I am in love
with that woman
autism
she just she just knows how to pump up
the mood you know I I strive to be like
I strive
happy birthday
um
I like the Shin-chan part the mouse
Hi and then also from a
yeah that was uh
so I forgot to uh promote Dallas
from anime please you take her out she's
a Vegeta bear from the premium
foreign
Japanese agency we uh recently became
best friends
and her name
is
yeah
where is she
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
I have this beautiful seat for you so I
hope you're sitting down now oh it's
lovely this is the beautiful seat that I
just got it ready for you so I the
birthday girl needs to sit down it's
okay if your hair is maybe covering me
I'll make sure to leave the back course
so they'll be fine don't worry and yeah
happy birthday
and I think I didn't introduce myself to
other Ali's viewers hello my name is
and one of our friends introduced me and
Ali and after that she became my BFF for
besties now I really didn't have any
friends that spoke English so I was
super happy when Ali was very friendly
to me she's a wholesome person you can
never meet she taught me a lot of memes
I did naughty memes no no no no no no no
no no she's good I mean it's good to
know I learned a lot of memes guys it's
so that you don't say it on stream yeah
[Music]
um
okay
um I think I should stop talking now I
think I'm talking too much where Ollie
no no no no no am I good you're very
good yes maybe I should sing now you can
um
I can talk yes can you talk you can talk
a little bit more
sure can I tell him can I talk you can
do both let's just sing let's let's sing
shall we shall we I love it
I'm in love
music please music please music music
please please
one two three four
guys
[Music]
anonymity
the money
foreign
[Music]
thank you
happy birthday
[Music]
[Laughter]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
I hope you have a great great fantastic
amazing awesome birthday
a hill already
really sound from Vivid
yeah Japanese
[Music]
foreign
wow
okay
again
the next one is also from a Japanese
agency
oh you guys know her she has the voice
that will melt any hearts she's the
literal it came in the in in the very
Beach
she's like
you guys know who it is
from Sugar lyrics
it's
[Music]
like oh happy birthday
celebrate again this year I love all
these big laugh and he's cute little
town oh thanks for inventing meter this
great collaboration today oh my
Pleasures have fun and sing together
[Music]
let's go
sorry
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
happy birthday so yes everybody that was
from sugar lyrics774 Incorporated lyrics
[Music]
she was so cool
Johnny
no
moderates
yes you are very
nice clear secretary
next is
you guys know him
he this is a very big giveaway he makes
comics
he makes lots and lots of comics he's a
really good writer a really good friend
oh you guys know who I'm talking about
yes that is right we're going to bring
in Merryweather into the table Mary come
on in
it goodness
[Music]
hold on
oh
[Music]
my God
yes
I love you a lot
oh he disappeared
I don't know let's go okay
[Music]
I love you baby
oh I'm so sorry Ali I'm an awful singer
no but I tried my best just for you my
dear Ollie oh you were amazing thank you
very much for inviting me it's having
you here I tried so hard to practice but
I just could not get it right I'm sorry
I am very sorry Ollie no no no no next
time I'll be better next time I shall
have a voice of gods for you my lady ALU
yes thank you for inviting me
I love you oh
hello
but he was so good
he was doing so well wasn't he
yes woof woof I'm sorry Mary a fire I
want to say sorry if I put burden on you
I'm sorry if uh the karaoke kind of
stressed you out I promise just having
you here makes me the happiest I love
how he used the that particular model
that has to be my favorite model of
yours thank you Al you're welcome I love
you too
but panicly
um
it got blue it's not that I'm cutting
their
um messages it's it's already loot we
were already at the store you know love
you sister we'll love you too I love you
too
[Music]
um
before we get the next one the next we
only have two more songs it's going to
be the finale after the two songs I have
an announcement so please be sure to
check that out just a moment let me let
me know
yeah a little bit sad that we only have
two more but yeah
[Music]
next also from the Philippines oh you
guys already know because he already
shared it on his social media as well
[Music]
who could it be who could it be
another one
he already had his turn this one is a
different guy
yes it is
Filipino right
I'll be very I'll be very very uh
I'll be very embarrassed if he's not
yes
a cool shades
maybe is it okay oh
foreign
[Music]
this is the highest the volume could go
I'm really really sorry everyone
Gaga
[Music]
computer
wait can we can we restart this one I I
don't I don't want to do I'd have been
like this we're going to restart
listen Okay
um all of the videos they have different
volumes something that I can control I
already maximized all of them to the
most
so I'm very sorry if it's a little bit
too low please pump up your own volume
okay I'm really really sorry I apologize
but there's nothing I can do to boost
the volume without cracking the real
audio okay
[Music]
hi
thank you
[Music]
everybody
foreign
[Music]
you won't say what word
[Applause]
what's nice
[Music]
continue
foreign
[Music]
thank you so much for inviting me to
your birthday I wish you more to come
you're one of the nicest most kindest
YouTubers I've ever met or seen heard
um or whatever
um but yeah I hope you enjoy your day
you deserve it
um and yeah
[Music]
yeah
he's such a sweetheart yeah
very very
wholesome
check him out he sings a lot
yes there's a lot of songs that he sings
it sounds super good he he I just can't
stress just how good his voice is please
do check him out
I want to hear your proper collab cover
that would be amazing out of it you're
down are you here
Hi and then next the last one
last one
it's from
you one and only
glug glug man
need I say more
yes this is the last one
it's
from mahapancha Indonesia
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
I wonder if we can boost the volume
but if we do this
can I hear it
ah
I'm hoping that
I'm hoping that the sound is good
yeah hi happy birthday Ollie hey
[Applause]
um
okay
[Music]
yeah nice
um
[Music]
foreign
inside
the moment yeah
[Music]
what are you doing what's the man doing
look at this
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
[Applause]
go up this street
we couldn't
do
[Music]
foreign
that has been good
[Music]
hi
I am
August
well I guess that's a great way to end
the Stream
okay on to onto our previous overlay hey
yo what up people
whoa
we're back here again should I yeah
[Music]
wait did you have any announcements I do
have a few announcements uh-huh
so
um
this is a
Okay so
last announcement for the day before we
wrap up my birthday
celebration holy
okay
[Music]
um
hi so I've been singing a lot
I've been singing for like what four and
a half hours
yeah and this will not be the last time
you guys Hear My Singing In fact
I have a cover coming up
zombie I also featured myself in it I I
signed the course a little bit in the
original and I'm finally coming out with
my own coverage
ah
for those of you who kept on asking oh
my God where's the ollie ah it's right
here no faces
ah
hi it's going to come out soon
and uh I can't I can't tell you the
release date yet
should be soon yeah that's all I wanted
to announce is
foreign
[Music]
I received lots of love I received lots
of wishes received lots of support I got
a lot of
presents from you guys I I still haven't
checked the hashtag for leaders like
this hashtag for presents it's hashtag
holiday presents the the INE being 13
because you know hey my birthday
I just want to say thank you for all of
your love I I know I know don't get
tired of me saying it everybody says the
same thing every influencer every
streamer every YouTuber every YouTuber
they all say the same thing but
seriously from the deepest part of my
heart
thank you so much I wouldn't be here I
wouldn't be celebrating
my birthday so I'm wearing for you guys
I've never celebrated my birthday this
um extravagant before I'm hoping that
next year I can celebrate it even more
like
a lot more extravagant I'm really
looking forward to it thank you so much
for all of the presents wishes love
kisses I
um I don't have any other words to say
other than thank you I'm literally
speechless
I heard that there were songs made for
me there's like what four songs five
songs
six songs I forgot how many songs there
were I bet the ollie graveyard like
um
pays a lot of attention to it there was
a lot of songs being released in
combination of my birthday haven't
listened to them but I'm looking forward
to them every single super Ted every
single uh gifting membership every
single
um donation every single comment every
single reply every single retweet
they mean a lot to me you guys still you
guys just don't know
sometimes I feel like do I really
deserve this I'm getting so much love
but what what what do I do I I literally
just stream I play video games online
sometimes it doesn't make any sense but
I really appreciate everything from the
bottom of my heart
you really do like I see ya I absolutely
deserve it
I love you guys so much I love you thank
you I love you and thank you that's
literally I sound like I sound like a
parrot I keep repeating it like a broken
record I'm sorry
but yes thank you I hope you guys
enjoyed the karaoke one day I hope I can
have my own silicon shirt
hmm I can't wait like this might be a
scuff karaoke session now but one day I
swear it'll turn into a solo concert and
you guys will ball your eyes out
yeah
I know I'm not the best at singing but
one day I'll be everyone's
um Idol for sure
I think that's all for today
[Music]
YouTube Community I'll be telling you
guys when the cover will be up so just
just put your eyes out yeah
thank you so much everyone for coming to
the stream this has been crazy Ollie
who just had
her 17 season three
and I am signing out
I love all of you
so much
signing out
bye
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]