[Music]
so
my
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
oh
[Music]
huh
hmm
my room is so hot
uh
ah
why the why is it so hot
i'd say
progress 12
oh my god they're mocking me
they're mocking me hello i just want to
start off by saying i had a
bad dream
had a bad dream i forgot already most of
it thankfully but part of it was
like i was like
dealing with this
weird
evil guy
who
um had like a [\h__\h] ton of
cats
but mistreated them like like just for
fun he like when there was a batch of
kittens
he would take them one by one
and throw them down um
like a hole in in a apartment where it
was like
six seven eight stories high or so he
would just pick him up and throw them
down
and i was like crying because like you
can't do that
[Music]
oh
and i wanted to save the cats
and then it was also like kind of
um
like dangerous for my own cats
because i feel like he was going after
my cats too
yeah what the [\h__\h]
he just dropped them
into this really big hole and the poor
poor kitties
just
died
yeah
i was so sad
to kind
yeah i was happy about waking up man um
oh oh and and and and another part of my
dream was interesting too i
i
went to
some kind of
beach
country
um
and then i i
i was supposed to perform as a stand-up
comedian
in some kind of
venue small venue
and turns out the venue is kind of like
connected to a school
so backstage i
uh first of all i i was i was so stupid
like i had my whole thing my whole
program planned out
um but
i didn't have enough time to really go
through it and i was really nervous
because that would have been my first
stand-up comedian thingy
um and then i
i needed to take a shower but there was
no shower i guess so i took a bath in
the
in the ocean in the beach uh and then i
needed time to
uh dry my hair because that was like so
wet
um
and then and then so i went back to
backstage but my my turn was gonna come
up soon so i was like [\h__\h] can we move
it like i need to dry my hair man
um
and and then and then and then i don't
know like in the waiting time uh i
figured out that my um
that the school that we were like
located in was
a school
where apparently i used to go to because
um all my old school mates were in a
class there and i walked in i was like
oh my god
oh
what a coincidence
and then i look a little bit further and
i want to say hi and all that and i
noticed that not only my austrian
ex-schoolmates are here but also a
friend of mine who is from a different
european country
who like a real friend that i have was
also for some reason in that school like
undercover and i was like what the [\h__\h]
are you doing here i thought you were in
and and it was like all weird and blah
blah blah blah blah and then and then
and then i was like yo you gotta you
gotta watch my my comedian um act uh in
in a little bit it's starting literally
after your class so please come by which
i said but i don't know why i said that
because i was nervous about going on
stage because i didn't know what to do
because i didn't have time to go for my
act and all that so anyway then then it
kind of started but i don't know for
some reason i changed places and
um
[Music]
because i i couldn't practice my act so
i would have had to go like
spontaneously
off the top of my head and i wasn't sure
if i could really do that so i was
thinking uh
uh i fought up one joke
okay here's my joke
um that i would do i apparently on stage
if i completely forgot my act and would
have to
grab
randomly ramble something okay
so
so i was walking
in a parking lot having a little walk in
the park and then in front of me uh
unbelievable they were they were three
or three
kids teenagers and all of them had a
like a free meter long [\h__\h] selfie
stick you know those kids nowadays it's
[\h__\h] annoying yeah and one of them
was uh vlogging probably for youtube
yeah he was like oh yeah look at what we
do you 666 and then the second one yeah
he was
she she was making tick tocks yeah with
her cringy ass dances
unbelievable unbelievable and the but
the third one you know what the third
one was doing with their selfie stick
and she was she was skyping with her mom
who was scolding her that she didn't
clean her room
wait that worked so much better in my
dream
[Laughter]
ah the kids these days is [\h__\h]
annoying with their selfie sticks
why
i guess i don't use skype
that's unrealistic it couldn't have been
skype
facetime facetime
but the joke was that you know the
they're all doing some kind of social
media [\h__\h] but then the third one with
her selfie stick she's actually getting
scolded by her mom um to do something
proper like cleaning a [\h__\h] room and
not be out there taking [\h__\h] tick
tocks and youtube vlogs
[Laughter]
is that not um i mean if the the
delivery could have been better i think
probably if you if you improve the
delivery then um
we could get somewhere with that
seinfeld bathroom please
um
yakuza um
[Music]
so i'm running some dms
ah
all right
am i not supposed to am i not is my
future not looking very bright in the
future of uh stand-up comedian
i think i dreamt this because i was you
know watching um
uh marvelous mrs maisel until a little
while ago and i was so mad that it was
only what eight episodes in the new
season like what the [\h__\h] i literally
finished watching that in like one day
what the [\h__\h]
um
unbelievable
netflix these days it's not even netflix
but
man
if i if i don't have a future and stand
up comedy and what am i doing here
wait that was funny nope was that funny
maybe a little bit
um
right
uh
that was that one was funny okay
[Music]
spoiler alert my i will i will probably
be [\h__\h] at playing this game today again
because i don't know the controls again
probably i'll try to get back into it
yes i pay
but please bear with me
and
also thank you guys
uh what are all these super chats what
the hell
ah
atf korean yes i saw your tweet
thank you
fighting
and we can talk a little bit about the
new girl
but let's see what we're getting
ourselves into it right now we might
have some story to
go through first
um
yakuza 0 presented by
[Music]
oh wait you don't even hear that
okay
now now you should hear it's probably
too loud even
[Music]
let's see
continue
[Music]
ah i didn't he could get a key what the
[\h__\h]
okay now i said it
still waiting for a joke shut up get out
of here where are we why are we here
wait did i not save
no i did i did that oh my god it scared
me scared me [\h__\h] scared me for a
minute
uh
well i don't uh i think i'm gonna
have some story very uh soon
uh
what is this place again ah this is the
the the massage place
the chiropractic
he's gone
where the hell did he disappear to all
all full of holes what
uh for people who don't uh recall what
happened
um last episode was mostly kiryu
but at the end of
his part we sneak peeked into what
majima's side was uh
uh looking like
and turns out he did not kill the cute
girl um it was kind of obvious that he
wouldn't do it yeah he's too nice of a
person and then
[Music]
yeah
now we're here
[Laughter]
but turns out
i think the girl kind of knows why she's
being chased but uh she said we should
ask the
the guy
who we first thought was named makoto
but uh he wasn't
um right
am i
am i recalling this correctly
um
yeah
so now we're looking for him so i guess
because we want him to explain to us
well what ma why makoto is being chased
yeah oh my god i forget controls but i
don't forget the story hallelujah
oh
oh [\h__\h] hide hide
small footsteps
who is this he just wants a treatment
[Music]
it's like a
i feel like i feel like this
this accent is supposed to sound like um
i think a chinese person speaking
japanese but it more sounds like a
japanese person person trying to sound
like a chinese person
trying to speak japanese
you
why are you putting him into a nap hey
hey i didn't deserve that what the [\h__\h]
the place was called jambalaya vajang
parlour in chauffeur west the big guy
with the bullet holes should be there
okay
okay we're go go uh the map map
map how to order oh there we go it
didn't work the first time i pushed it
i'm going here around the corner
basically
yeah i basically woke up today and uh
pretty much immediately
i started watching the debut of
the third gen of whole life indonesia
the first girl
they don't they have one per day
is it is that how she wants us to
pronounce that
oh
side story
hey be careful you can't bear it for a
crowd like dad
yeah i'm sorry i'm in a hurry that's
fine what's the big rush i have to go to
the conbini the one over there
yeah i got real problems if you need to
hit a convenience store that bag
what could it be he ever wants to use
the convenience store toilet
or
or he has a girlfriend at home and he
needs to get girl um things for her
quickly um because she was
already yelling at him like
um well i don't know what could it be
what
what could it possibly be
lip balm
that doesn't seem like something very
urgent
yeah
and nipple i'm in the harry so i have to
run by
hmm
up are you in some pain lip pain perhaps
oh yeah my feet have been sore are you
gonna use a lip balm on your feet
why don't you slow down a bit and go
easy on yourself
maybe he's just the kind of person who
runs to everything just just because
just because
if i don't run i won't make it in time
it's getting real cryptic what do you
mean
i'm sorry i really have to get going
bye okay
must be a real emergency emergency to be
on that kind of tear for lip balm maybe
his lips are like sandpaper or something
yeah but even dent
even then
uh
i know
[Music]
thank you oh thank you everything's so
pink pink pink pink
um am i supposed to go in here yeah
i think so
okay let's let's go in
um
i'll tell you what i thought about her
debut later
there he is
[Music]
to punch that other guy
yes
[Music]
i don't think it's much different from
anybody else but i suck at it even more
than you buddy
are you going to teach me how
to study
it
foreign
is
[Music]
um
so
get well soon
and those people are actually trying to
hurt her unlike me
[Music]
um
you're welcome
oh no goodbye salami stick ah
oh no no
um there's like two buttons i need to
push
there's so much [\h__\h] lying around here
oh
was that
we'll get better at this
[\h__\h] cat hair on my salami steak
today
[Music]
could have really just stopped wasting
our time
[Music]
hard to talk about i suppose
um
all about money
[Music]
it
foreign
um
[Music]
tell me
um
[Music]
in japanese what a cat says when she
person
meow
whoever that lee guy is here's a piece
of work nothing i can really do now but
to go check on the girl i guess
right
yeah yeah oh my first my first
impression of the girl
zeta
was
before even hearing her i really really
like her design i think it's my favorite
um
uh although rather than seeing her
seeing that design as a youtuber i see
that design popping up in a certain
tower defense game
[Laughter]
you want to fight uh want trouble
therefore it's 100 my taste i love i
love white hair and gray hair characters
and
the design ah i love it i love it and
the art style is cool too
yeah i really like it
um
which side do i get there
did you hear that
ah look at them kitty cats
what a yonky nicole
oh
wait that one had a funny face look at
that did you see that funny face let's
see that funny face
look at that funny face
oh it's about to get down
between those kitty cats
yeah yeah and then and then and then uh
holy [\h__\h] she has a really really uh
sweet
voice
yeah i'm sure all of your hearts went
doki doki the moment you heard her voice
yeah it's my first time i heard it too
it's not like i have any contact with
the new id members beforehand no no not
at all um but ah really really uh sweet
soft voice
i didn't i don't think i quite expected
that voice from like looking at the
design but
yeah
it was very cute
um it sounds so
sweet and natural i don't know really
cute like a little princess and i
my fault about her being a princess grew
stronger and stronger after hearing like
all the things she can do it makes it
sound like she was
like trained for her whole life
to be like an
uber human
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh oh the game tells you what to do
eventually um because you know what she
speaks like four languages and she says
baby level but it was really good
and and and
uh she can apparently probably sing i
didn't hear anything yet but probably i
assume so
and then she uh can probably dance
because she was talking about dancing uh
in 3d who knows probably i just assume
she can
uh
wait what else was it uh
she likes to draw don't know how good
but i i assume it's another thing that
she can do well
yeah she seems like someone who can
really um do a lot of things um these id
members are crazy man crazy
ah the art in the mv i i had to um turn
off the stream in the last couple of
minutes to prepare for my own stream but
uh i did uh wonder if the art in the
music video she did herself so she did
not
know
uh
i don't know but she just seemed very uh
skilled in a lot of things and makes
made me feel like
she probably was trained to be in
ubermensch
damn
yeah very cute
very cute new member
um
oh that would be
[Music]
don't cry
oh
[Music]
no we'll bring you food
um
[Music]
root for stranger nah
nah it's not about being rude i think
even as a stranger
[Music]
i think i think she trusts him
and
i don't know i would just want to hug
um
i thought dealing with professional
women was rev
let's get you some food takoyaki
[Music]
i'm not really a big fan of takoyaki but
for this girl i'll get her any of him
[Music]
all the way up there i could take a taxi
too
so temporary street east okay
so then
oh
there's some
pretty boys there again
oh they don't want to fight okay
wait i forgot i used this one okay
um
well if you want to be kicked by cali
rather than me then go to her stream
[Music]
please uh twenty takoyakis girl seems
hungry
oh piping hot takoyaki more more one is
not enough what the [\h__\h] mom
okay
a batch of what how many six
did i get it i guess i got it oh hello
what are you doing do you give me a
pocket tissue oh
i'm a telephone card collector got any
cards i could see i just want to take a
look
um
i used to collect them myself but after
i see a card for the first time i just
kind of lose all interest in it
that's why i don't mind just admiring
someone else's collection makes you a
pretty odd collector don't it why don't
you just drop the hobby
i can't give it up i couldn't go on
living without reveal reveling in
telephone card collections i i need them
to reach his own fine i don't mind
showing you my cards
don't bother with incomplete sets though
only full three card sets really do it
for me i don't think i have that do i
you know how cards got a b or c on them
it's cause there's three different cards
for each girl when you complete the set
come and show me you're a picky guy
ain't chucky
it says kill you
it says kill you there i'm majima
let's go i'm a game journalist i will
report this to the
right people
just kidding i will ignore this forever
so i probably don't have anything for
you uh
does he mean those cards from the girls
that i pick up in some places
where am i right now i need to go back
down there again damn girl make me run
around the whole city
yes yes okay
i thought so
okay taking another cab taking another
cab wait what is this can i enter here
too
come benny i love convini i love company
i wish we had convenience here proper
ones
maybe we need stuff oh yeah we do need
some stuff we haven't although i maybe
shouldn't buy it here
looks yummy though
special yakisoba
mandarin orangey
no i should buy it somewhere else where
was the good stuff again
pharmacy yeah where's the closest farm
you see
um
you know what focus is the big round um
out here big round fish that goes like
poof
and is poisonous
yeah yesterday guys i
finally got my
butt up
i finally
got off of my butt lazy butt don't don't
don't don't don't look at me don't i
need to no
what
i guess i'll go downstairs
and i cooked something
i cooked the japanese style curry
mi hong
yeah kong
yeah
[Music]
finally
some good curry man
it was really good yeah
i mean can't really do much wrong with
curry okay
it runs away
where are you going where are you going
where you going
where are you going
bye-bye
type a
yeah and i also i bought some uh
japanese panko
uh and some
uh
some meat some pork meat
some filet because i wanna make like
yesterday i only ate like a normal my
normal curry but uh i want maybe
tomorrow i want to make a katsu curry
so i'm going to try
yeah i'm going to try it
but
i never made
japanese katsu before on my own but it
shouldn't be much more
much more difficult than you know making
schnitzel
it's basically the same thing just a
different uh angle different different
breading
yeah yeah yeah
abilene
oh
wait interesting you you only
uh were interested in me after i
bumped into you okay
before that you weren't even on the map
i forgot how to do
don't mind i'll figure it out it was
probably triangle
i was an idiot he says yes
that is correct so where is that
the yellow one
[Music]
sumimasen
oh it's so colorful in here holy [\h__\h]
madison is so colorful in japan
[Music]
die hard
uh wait
does it even have yes okay what do we
want what did you guys say
heat toughness
uh
ah this one
or this one this one is a bit expensive
try to help your health and heat
significantly
okay sounds good i'll wait more
[Music]
i'll buy a few royals too i guess
but they're so expensive
oops
how much more one two three four five
one two three four five
sixty
holy [\h__\h]
yeah okay i'm good thank you inventory
is full
money is no problem yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah
yeah yeah majima got those super chatos
um okay wait now we gotta go to the girl
let's take the taxi again
because money is no problem for our boy
majima
um
down here all right
mr shake down is here
don't tell him don't tell him i'm close
by don't tell him
are you doing side quests today i don't
know
i don't know i always like to um
progress in the game quickly
[Music]
thank you i really need to
step up my korean game i um especially
after watching
the new girl
i felt like damn kiwawa
damn kiwawa where is your korean huh
um
but i've been so busy man but i will i
will i'm once again motivated
oh i'll try
kill two birds with one stone
[Music]
did you feed her
tell me you fed her
oh no
huh
another
[Music]
does he not want her to work worry too
much
um
[Music]
oh
um
[Music]
the music is nice in the background
though
piano
[Music]
it's
oh it's so pretty
love that piano track
oh yeah
[Music]
m
just gonna get it fixed right
he's
just he can't he he loves her
mother
it's gonna surprise her with the tune
foreign
can i join
[Music]
um
it's like his little kitten dead he gets
back to after work and takes care of
oh
[Music]
loving kia is just natural at this point
oh stop
maybe i'll drop by a cabaret club like
yamagata han suggested on my way to
check in at the grand huh
i might have seen one in the whole
hoganji yokocho area maybe it's worth a
check
what why what when to study or what
uh
bikers i see what's up
wait
wasn't r2 the focus button or was it r1
r1 maybe it's r1
is it i don't know
it doesn't always work perfectly either
way
i want
i wish they like
would turn after i kill one
just automatically turn to the closest
one
i feel like the focus in this game
uh the focus function is not not the
best i'm holding it down constantly but
like without a break i i hold it down
permanently but it doesn't work so well
[Music]
apparently today
is something you guys
were looking forward to some job for
majima
hello club sunshine
[Music]
really
i didn't know there was a spotlight just
tucked back in this part of the town
not quite this
this is the time where kiabakula just
starts to rise up
number one
yeah the difference was that i think
kabakuras are more small and like one
and
more one-on-one or like
yeah i don't know just smaller
yeah
i've been into livelier graveyards than
this
not as soul in here besides me but um
who is your number one girl
i'm curious
[Music]
you're just gonna
for this club's top girl she's pretty
low-key
oh okay
there was a reason why she was free okay
she hasn't been doing this for very long
ah
is this lady seriously the best i got
uh here you have no self-confidence
don't ask but i mean that's rude
are you really the number
one like
kind of a rude way to ask it
technically
so
[Music]
down
everybody clap your head
[Music]
everybody clap your hands
do
[Music]
i want chocolate
i can tell you something i watched i've
been watching so many
videos um
recently
um
[Laughter]
uh of like
like like
cringe um
pop culture moments and
um
tick tock people and all that
anyway so there was this one clip that
showed um baby metal being
interviewed overseas and yeah they have
this cute song right that's like
um oh no i'm not watching tick tocks i'm
watching like
tick tock like cringe compilations of
tick tockers being like on tv or
whatever
and yeah
anyway
so so there was a baby medal being
interviewed overseas in english and they
ask like this really serious question
question like oh your song give me
chocolate is about like eating disorder
right
and and then the main girl she's just
like um no it's just about
wanting to eat chocolate
that's all there is to it
just
it's just
it's just an innocent idol song about
gaming
[Laughter]
they wanted to paint this really serious
image or something i don't know where
they got that from like um oh so serious
song
yeah yeah yeah i totally get it
i i
researched so much about you and my
conclusion is that give me chocolate is
about an eating disorder
what where did you get that where did
how did you where did you do your
research
what
yeah there must be more to it they were
probably listening to the song and were
like
there there's no way that j-pop
sing like j-pop is all about these
super superficial cute things that are
not serious at all no no no there must
be deeper meanings they're hiding it in
between the lines surely no no j-pop is
most of the time really like that
most of the time j-pop is about or like
idol songs idol song specifically is
about
ah oh i'm so nervous i have a date uh
i like this boy what do i do what should
i wear
ah
stuff like that
or
oh i want to eat some yummy food or
drink some good coffee morning
famous morning muslim song morning
coffee
let's drink morning coffee together yeah
i am
it's just bubbly songs
[Laughter]
deeper meanings oh i'm sure they do
but i just thought it was so funny but
them trying to read so deeply into it
yeah
yeah the message the message there must
be a reason why you're so famous and
your songs are so popular it can't be
just you singing about chocolate now
speaking of
i was just reacting in japanese and then
imagine says the same thing
[Laughter]
[Music]
here
looking like that
looks like his mom dressed him this
morning
[Music]
how can you let yourself get bullied
like a guy
by a
if his mom finds out and scolds him a
little bit
he'll never come back
oh
[Music]
okay
i can't even take it seriously
he still speaks in polite japanese
though
would you kindly mind being careful sir
[Laughter]
foreign
write it down with pencils
[Music]
foreign
in tokyo we have the problem that they
want to
buy up all the buildings and here we
have the problem that they want to buy
up all the cabarets
foreign
[Music]
thank you
don't much care what happens to this
town but he thought of
beeps like that doing whatever they want
pisses me off i'm their fault plus if i
let them go now there will be trouble
for the grands bottom line down the road
which means trouble for me if i'm still
around
i'm curious about the cabaret club
business too maybe i'll try to learn a
bit more by helping out around here a
bit
beep
he's such a good guy
such a good guy even to end up being a
yakuza um
[Music]
so weird how he turns up being
so crazy later
two different
um
i'll manage this place
this is the back office looks nice
it's most it mostly serves as a staging
area for the staff i organize things
back here manage your girls that sort of
thing speaking of what would you say to
take over as a manager
would you mind it
what
just like that yes there you certainly
have the experience and i fear sunshine
can't reach its full potential under my
direction i give you total authority
oh okay
of course i'd still be here supporting
you in any way i can as a floor staff
will you do it sir
well if the money is uh looking good
then surely
all right if you're that serious about
this i'll do my part too leave it to me
thank you so much i'm at your disposal
manager manjima
now if it's all right with you i'd like
to jump right into an explanation of how
a cabaret club is run
that said there's a lot to cover and i
know you're busy man let me know when
it's a good time for you
the hideout you can now use sunshine's
back office as your hideout which also
serves as the key location for your
business
as the story advances you'll unlock the
ability to switch protagonists using the
hideout telephone as well as change
clothes into any outfits you've earned
okay
gotcha
so tell me more
i was thinking this might be a good time
to run you for the basics of the capital
yeah
okay
i'll do my best to listen lay it on me
lay it on me
come on
how do you even say that
you need to operate your club earn money
uh and grow your clientele and
ultimately crush your competition your
final goal to establish sunshine tsar
okay
as the undisputed top club in sultan
buri you can open a club as well as
manage the girls who will form your
active lineup by talking to yoda inside
sunshine as sunshine's popularity
increases and the clash with your rivals
clubs heats up drama will unfold drive
those rivals out of the business and
you'll unlock new combat techniques and
majima can learn to become even stronger
so bring the fight to them as
aggressively as you can
by driving sunshine's popularity up you
can transform it into a source of
tremendous tremendous profit and
anything you earn with the club is yours
to spend however you wish grow the club
smash the competition and become the
true cabaret club
and get filthy rich in the presses yes
no i get that
i got it
in that case the next step is let's have
you actually open up the place and do a
round of crap this is the sort of thing
where the quickest way to learn is to
actually just do it let's give it a try
i'll chime in with advice as we go
all right let's do it by the way i'm not
really voice acting today because
i'm not feeling like it
top menu you have free options in the
top menu prepare to open select staff
for the shift change their appearance
etc okay
oh i can i can change their clothes it's
like a barbie dress-up game
open for business open the club for
business and start raking in the door
hmm cookie dough rival battles enter
showdown showdown with arrival club okay
okay so far so good
statistics
each hostage has a different set of
statistics ability various stats showing
the horses ability to entertain
customers
looks physical appearance goes a long
way in this line of work
funny you don't want anyone to look
funny do you
the better the values the easier it is
for hostas to ensure her guests have a
good time and spend lots of cash in the
club mm-hmm your game is experienced by
working shifts and undertaking training
sessions okay
uh only platinum hostages can undergo
special training during a special
training during special training
sessions majima will sit down with a
girl for for a practice conversation
or take her out on a mock date
and the cardiology buyer for example if
training goes well the hostess will earn
a lot of experience plans looks good on
her resume too
you can only train one girl one time
before opening for business on a given
night but a well-trained staff will give
your club an
edge over your rivals hone their skills
to crush their competition flat
makeovers ah you can freely change the
looks of your platinum staff by choosing
different outfits or applying new makeup
let's go
it's the best part of sims
new hairstyles dresses and other items
need to be purchased the first time
afterwards changing between them is free
of charge but only with the girl for
whom you bought the item change a hostas
looks stats by modifying her appearance
which will help her appeal to your
customers various tastes
can i have like them all uh maxed out or
is it like a balance thingy like some
things will be better some things will
be worse i wonder
choosing a house choosing hostas for a
shift
uh
what do you guys say yes
free max not a hotel so let's ignore
funny no one wants to look funny
use the duty roster to assign hostages
to work the next shift pay close
attention to each host's condition as
this will affect their performance if a
hostess is hired then a smart move is
often to give her some time off of work
and to rest and recover hostas with more
skills and higher levels cost greater
wages which can affect your overall
profits while operating the club
opening a club for business once you
have finished any preparations you can
open the club for business first choose
which areas customers you want to target
the more rival clubs you defeat
the more uh areas will be available
areas okay
as you gain more fans in an area most
more customers will show up and more of
them will be big spanners after each
shift you will gain more fans in the
targeted area according to customer
satisfaction
oh
that's it okay oh
let's go i actually understood all of
that and
for once entered my brain
without leaving in the other ear
nice um
okay so we start by preparing
um
can we start with a makeover
wow
okay
i don't like the dress your dress is
[\h__\h]
it doesn't look like something we should
wear wait so right now it's beauty and
cute
[Music]
oh different colors
that's cute i like that one
that one looks like a pajama but okay
cute definitely something the guys would
like this looks like a princess very
cute i see the cute goes up
belted bear top
people like off shoulder dresses yes yes
oh that looks very kyabakuran
the music is too loud
[Music]
listen to the lyrics
every night drink wise and talk every
night
[Music]
me
wow
[Music]
okay
it's like
like in theory it's a good song but the
lyrics are so specifically tailored to
what this part of the game is
how is this not sexy i think this is
sexy but okay
um
i like i think this one was like a
personal preference maybe it does give
me two circles
uh
this one also gives two circles an x
another thingy okay and this one kind of
switches it around
okay
you will wear
this because you're our queen
oh i have to buy it oh no money bye bye
hope you like it
oh
[Music]
oh my god
this looks like
with her face and the hairstyle she
looks like kusumi kuwaiti from uh
ex-morning muslim member
look up kusumi kohara
[Music]
ho hai
oh my god she looks exactly like her
from this angle of that hairstyle
oh easy
holy
but she used to be and not solo but in
an idol group called money musume but
she sang baghdad
[Music]
wow
ah it goes from cheap i don't know this
one is cheap too
this is the most
expensive uh this
mature hairstyle is a favorite for
younger girls as well
[Music]
it's
it's worth the money
[Music]
looking at the stats
this helps us with regaining our
sexiness and beauty is like even higher
but cuteness disappears but maybe we can
get that from something else
[Music]
let's buy this for now even though the
top part looks kind of funny
color oh
wait we can make kiana out of her
although another it's not really an
orange why is it always lagging orange
but okay
[Music]
i think
this
suits you well
yeah
okay okay okay
now with makeup we want to make her look
cuter does that not change anything
let's see eyebrows
oh my god i love this
oh this is this makes her look really
cute but it doesn't change the stats i
like this one
[Music]
yeah
eyelashes
oh pretty
girl
girl you have so much potential
eyeliner
you know kyabakura girls usually have a
lot of makeup on
[Music]
now this is okay
eyeshadow
there's ah only two ah but then the
color we can change it i guess um
none is okay actually
let's give her a karaoke
was so surprised as someone who is
really bad with um
like having lenses in in my eyes
um
because my eyes dry out immediately and
it gives me a headache and all that i
really [\h__\h] hate it
um but in japan
like
every [\h__\h] girl i meet wears uh
lenses
to not because they need glasses but
there's like color lenses that rather
than changing the color make the eyes
bigger by having like an outer circle
only and that's what you call uh
a circle lens in english but they just
call it kala kong
um it's like a big business there like
like all the teenagers too
every idol everyone wears them
[Music]
you probably don't even notice because
some are more natural than others but
um
yeah
like almost every girl i meet in japan
has a kayak and i wonder how the hell
will you do that because
my eyes cannot tolerate lenses at all
[Music]
times
usually it's just like a brown or black
outer circle but some of them have like
a slight color in it too to give them
some slight slightly green or blue eyes
or whatever
or gray or so
but usually it's just like an outer
circle
so the they are a bit bigger than
a bit bigger and a bit thick thicker
than normal
lenses that you use instead of glasses
which makes them even harder to wear
but yeah
um
[Music]
i tried like lens fluids and eye drops
and all that but it's always painful for
me always
[Music]
hold on
i kind of like the gray ones on the hair
though i don't know why
[Music]
but something something not too strong
yeah yeah yeah yeah nude lips let's go i
love this is this what you guys thought
i would like because this is my favorite
thing now
wait let me try to change the color
contents again
i'm not happy i like every every color
ah green green's so nice
green's so nice
yeah
okay i'm done with you i want i want to
make over more girls i need more
platinum girls
oh accessories so we're not done we're
not done
oh no glasses hair accessory maybe yeah
yeah
what's 800 000 that's like 8 000 bucks
kidding me a t-hour on top of that
[Music]
no it doesn't suit your current hair
stuff but wait it does change the stats
not really in a way that i want them to
be changed though um
earrings
oh nice okay it's weird that it like is
on top of the hair but okay
can
we ah
this way we don't lose anything we only
gain sexiness uh i only want to gain
something not lose anything
the circle ones would make us gain some
cuteness
okay okay i'll go again
okay okay
no
no pain no gain
you gotta
get some holes in your ears
[Music]
this one
would be good
[Music]
and i'm gonna go with this one it's a
nice necklace indeed
i'm gonna run out of money
buying all this [\h__\h] for this girl now
some cute nails would be good
i only lose beauty when i do that
[Music]
i don't know
cute nails though
how about we need nails we need nails
[Music]
maybe regain some beauty from somewhere
else if i buy these nails for her can i
also use them in the future on someone
else
[Music]
yeah no
only on her
okay
but those pink nails are nice
now we just need to regain our beauty
maybe we have a ring
oh
yes
[Music]
okay perfect
okay
[Music]
i don't have a cute watch
a perfume
that lifts the spirit of its wearer
maybe another time
okay we can't get maximum cuteness i
guess
oh okay
wonderful
look at that makeover
recommend it okay
[Music]
[Applause]
after i end it
she's hotter than yukiya excuse me
[Music]
okay
oh yeah okay
[Music]
yeah okay
done
yeah let's let's do a training session
ah oopsie sorry
so i guess i go to special training
and do you why can't i not train the
others though
i want to try
she looks gorgeous now
[Music]
now taking um
requests for makeovers
come on to kiwa salon
only because they're platinum yeah how
do i get the others to become platinum
though
i still little conversation training
i offer myself as a victim
test subject
thank you for your help with this
what's up john you're nervous or
something
no no i wouldn't call it nerves it's
more like battle butterflies battle
butterflies
i guess that's encouraging enough all
right you're ready to pretend i'm a
customer
yes
hello customer
i'm yuki i look forward to a fun
conversation with you
[Music]
you sure you've got this
oh i made
she looks so good
oh man she looks so different yeah
some different hair and makeup and all
that and doing your eyebrows differently
and all that can change so much you
don't need plastic surgery for
everything
you can really change the whole
look of a face
in crazy ways of makeup and hair
you wouldn't believe it but here is the
proof
yeah
okay well let's start with an easy topic
tell me about some hobbies
oh my god she's cute
time to think about i don't know much
about you either let us use this as a
little practice to get better
acquaintances
[Music]
huh
maybe her hobby is having no hobbies
if you want to be a hostess that kind of
talk ain't going to cut it you just
flatline the whole conversation
try
well mr star what do you write about in
it
[Music]
where there you go there that's a hobby
wait wait back up a bit bonsai that's an
obvious hobby
wouldn't you think that attending a
bonsai would count as a hobby exactly i
bet your older clientele would love
hearing you babble on about that
i made her look so cute i'm falling in
love
are you saying i look dumb you could
tell anyway why didn't you mention your
bonsai hobby in the first place
[Music]
well i think it's pretty amazing eight
years is enough um
[Laughter]
stop looking at me like that holy [\h__\h]
those eyebrows are so strong
those eyebrows
blue chian thank you
thank you thank you
thank you so much
you really climb up when the guest stops
talking don't jump
tough girl to collaborate with yeah
impolite that ain't the right idea at
all our customers are here specifically
to talk to the girls you can tell you've
got to lead them with some topics mm-hmm
i would say rather than talking about
yourself you need to get them to talk
about themselves because then they will
feel better like you know make them feel
cool like when they say
they have done something that's not
really that cool you gotta be like so
guys so good wow you're so amazing wow
wow tell me more about that and then
they'll bubble bobble bobble and spend
i'm the perfect manager
[Laughter]
and try to exactly try to compliment
them
even if they're not looking good you
should tell them they look really good
like just pick like something like oh i
really like your beard or i really like
your tie
[Music]
if you're drawing a blank on something
to talk about try a compliment ain't a
man in the world who would turn down a
compliment
make them feel better
[Laughter]
yeah
yeah yeah
his face his voice his personality if he
looks even a little well off try saying
something nice about his closest shoes
or hell even his watch exactly
anything
[Music]
[Laughter]
is going to be long and bumpy for you
you could uh
she's so cute i forgive everything
what else is a good conversation starter
do you have some kind of talent maybe on
the second spot scratch that
lonnie's
what is it
doing
tongue twisters or something like that
what is it
ah maybe circle
i would like to say that's a talent but
we shouldn't roast her i guess which
it's probably circle probably circle in
that case
or
um i don't know this one's a tough one
square
oh older gents i don't know nothing of
this really says much
so the old guys fancy you today i
suppose you do seem a little like a
grandkid
makes sense but that's actually a big
plus in our line of business yeah yeah i
could let you handle all the grandpas
who roll through the doors
there we go
[Music]
i feel like i'm playing a different game
right now
nice
all right let's change gears why don't
you tell me about a weakness you've got
instead anything come to mind
i'm just messing with you well if you
got a lot how about you pick one for me
anything's fine
um
well that's gonna be a [\h__\h] problem
girl
that is going to be a problem
she probably wants to get better at it
um
uh
why is that because i'm such a
supportive and considerate guy
[Music]
without even trying
no effort rudeness
holy [\h__\h]
she insulted my manly hood
[Laughter]
yeah apologize with those cute eyes
and those cute
eyebrows men wait we didn't get the full
one
we didn't max it
oh man
max said thank you for watching surfing
good job so let's see
good lesson
well done yukichan that went better than
i thought it would actually you might
just make it through this thank you i'm
so glad keep it up and you'll have these
customers melting like chocolate on a
dashboard
i want chocolate
you really think so i don't feel a
little more confident i'll do my best to
work a lot harder
[Music]
okay can i do another session
immediately this is all we'll do today
okay i guess not we gotta do um
yeah uh i'll run from first
uh what's the club status i guess look
at that
moon area
so we have no fans anywhere yet at all
[Music]
okay okay
okay
uh
and hostas list and then look at that
did i no i didn't
makeover okay then cast on duty
it's like that's the lightness
okay
okay so they're all selected
okay are they all selected i think they
are yeah
okay open for business
we ready
target club mars area customers
and chris fanbase here
for business yes let's go
[Music]
oh my girl is looking like from a
different planet man the club operation
screen your objective is to make as much
music
money is possible before the shift ends
when a customer comes in and takes a
seat assign them to a hostess different
customers have their own preferences
when it comes to looks or ability choose
a girl that manchester tap and they will
happily spend the fortune in your club
serving customers gradually tires of
hostas out lowering her hospitality
points without hp she will be unable to
provide high quality service to let her
rest until her hp recovers oh damn this
reminds me of one of those um browser
games where you had to run like a burger
place or something and you had to like
remember the ingredients and and and
serve them really fast otherwise they
would angrily go
home your dino dash stuff like that
[Music]
hopefully it's not that fast the club
operation screen on standby uh-huh
talking busy uh-huh
or poor does it say poor because they
are poor or the conversation is going
poorly
wants to talk short session prefer sexy
uh i didn't really remember
the other girl's stats does it show me
that too or do i have to know it by
heart
money gosh
and party time the money goes at the
bottom right corner of the screen shows
how much cash your guests have spent in
the club at that time it will show you
okay
receiving orders from customers also
fills up the money goes
press r1 when it's full to cut loose and
trigger part
time yeah
wow
will put customers in the favorite state
people
that loosens their inhibitions and their
purse
purse strings there are plenty of
benefits party time like hp restoration
processes oh charge up the money guns to
higher levels to make party time even
more effective it's all happy hour
without the discounts
[Music]
press triangle to approach a customer's
table if any trouble arises it's time
for the check or if a hostess calls for
your help you will be shown several
options making the right decision can
boost customer satisfaction or pacify
any troublemakers
checking in on tables is an opportunity
to lend your staff a helping hand
waiting too long and you may wait too
long and you may lose your chance so
keep your eye open and hurry on over
when you spot a signal okay
okay
extensions and requests
oh
if a guest is happy with his hostages
when it is time for the check you can
try suggestion and extension and the
customer will stay longer and go into a
fever stack spending money like there's
no tomorrow
getting mega rich customers to agree to
an extension is a foolproof way to boost
sales and keep your girls smoking the
golden cash cow as your club makes a
name for itself some customers will come
in requesting a specific platinum
hostess
shift the girls around to fulfill these
requests as they arrive but even when
they're still talking everyone's got a
favorite
two results two result screens appear
after closing up the first displays your
profits and the second one shows your
staff's improvement for the day okay
okay
your club will earn more fans depending
on its performance
to progress the five-star storyline we
need to reach a particular number of
fans in each area okay
let's try this oh god i'm not ready uh
poor and what does he like
how do i know what he likes
sexy [\h__\h] i'm not so fast i'm not
[Music]
wait
here just take her let's go take her
and she's uh she's sexy too [\h__\h]
[Music]
uh
prefers beauty
average
[Music]
okay
you get our best girls
[Music]
guest on the table is upset what how
wait wait how how do i what
trouble
[Music]
ah it's a bit
not very well made okay wait what you
wanted something [\h__\h]
travel trouble again okay travel trouble
trouble
[Music]
i'm sorry
there's a gift
this moon has improved okay okay okay uh
sexy
oh you want beauty could not seat gas
due to lack of girls what what what
what
oh there's a new guest waiting what what
what what
what
what what's going on what's going on
what's going on
you can go now right okay bye bye
check please
[Music]
no i don't really want no
thank you
[Music]
we need the girl
hi help please okay okay what's up here
once the party long session prefers
beauty oh what's your problem she's
perfect
[Music]
guest glass please
okay
what does that mean
[Music]
uh wait what does he want not that i can
really give it to him okay
here
mighty i'm sorry
check please how about you stay longer
[Music]
how do i know how my girls are doing hp
oh yeah okay oh hp is low [\h__\h]
money money money money
oh [\h__\h] they're all gonna die soon
uh
what's his problem
what's latest glass okay
[Music]
oh he left okay beautiful
can i like make her rest
[Music]
and i want her to rest is she resting
now when she's just there
is it going up is there hp going up yeah
okay
um okay uh are you first
going to like
he's poor just uh
thank you
bye bye
guess left satisfied okay
and
wait
did i get the money or what
uh
what i don't know what does she want
preface beauty
oh she's not beautiful
she's still happy though
did i get the money or not
from the average guy
[Music]
what's your problem
why did it take so much time to tell me
[Music]
we didn't have party time
uh perfect prefer sexy
okay here you get this girl
[Music]
ready party money party
oh could i have thunder fever time oh
damn okay next time
when i'm already stressed out with the
first session holy [\h__\h] later when
there's gonna be more people i'm gonna
have a problem
two million yen
okay
level up they didn't level up
what the hell
[Music]
last area plus 110 okay
can i do another run can i do another
one
okay use it okay
not too shabby so we're short on guests
and girls is there no way around that
outside of daily grind if we wanted to
hire new girls i suppose scouting them
around town is the quickest way
um
trading in cp from the completion list
at the temple
uh-huh it'll be hard to outperform the
competition with an empty roster so try
to fill it out as soon as possible
uh word of mouth from everyday business
is one way to bring in new customers but
i hear cigna signing deals with other
local businesses is also effective
some of sultan body's shops will sign
partnerships deals with you for a price
partner businesses will send their
clients your way growing sunshine's fan
base in a hurry
and now it's getting too complicated
more advanced means more customers which
in turn means more profit so sign deals
with any hotspots you find out does it
do i get a sign that it's some place
that wants to sign with me
like a signal
scout for girls partner up with local
shops got it looks like i'm gonna be
busy outside the club uh-huh
the whole city is our battleground
there's a lot to do but good luck sir
thank you
we do need more girls
there's the girls over at the ground i
got from odyssey in that trade oh
long as we got nozomi recovered at the
ground should be fine if i bring the
rest over here what
i'm putting the call now off
[Music]
can we make her can we turn her into a
platinum one because i need to fix her
bangs like what what are what are those
bangs what what
i'm amazed if that surprised much my son
hard to believe that was your first time
keep that up and we just might really
manage to beat those brains back
there they showed up right when we
talked about them
you know
i'm here for your answer as promised
well ready to sell this problem to me
yet i told you before the answer is no
i see and i was so hoping to do this
admirably
all right you alert
ah fight fight fight fight what are you
doing teach the stubborn fool the
reality of your situation
oh are you sure about that you sure
about that we'll see which comes first
you give me what i want or you die
either way i can't wait do it no no no
no no
what are you supposed to be
name's manjima yoga son asked me to take
over operations here
and as long as i'm standing nobody's
making trouble in my shop
mm-hmm of course
you it's a wiser choice of letting a
demon like you to keep putting the stone
kill into the ground
you seem like you know your way around
the fight so you're the boss actor
around you clever choice for an idiot
i'm first truly you want to sell fight
huh
okay
i'm going to being entertained as i
watch just how far you managed to crawl
after making enemies of the fighters
yeah yeah yeah sure sure
you are lucky today mother son imagine
myself well why don't you try your best
if i get bored i'll drop by and swat you
down like the flies you are
porky enjoy watching your robbie little
house of cards come crumbling down on
top of you i hope your ass is ready to
get buried
oh we'll see how long that big tall
class i advise you've got to take the
five stars lightly
bye bye porky
[Music]
ponca
don't worry about the real bad ones just
starting we're gonna whip this club into
fighting shape fast if we want to take
them off
i don't give it all i've got majima
anytime you want to open the club for
business just let me know anytime at all
yeah i'm busy can't be here always but
okay
well that was a big introduction into a
side game
go to majima cats nice cats right next
to her head
things are about to get interesting huh
ah
i'm starting to get why yamagatan told
me to check out cavalry clubs but that
ate up more time than i planned yeah
it's been uh two hours
since i started the stream and
of those two hours was this game
i should get going back to the ground
okay
i'll i'll definitely play this mini game
more than the one from kiryu i think
um
i have a question like later on when you
can change between kiryu and majima
whenever you want does the game still
like kind of force you to
choose certain a certain protagonist for
certain
things
and is the money then like
interchangeable can you like send it
over to the other or switch it or
yes the game still does it okay
that happens post sorry oh
oh okay you can't send money to the
other guy no you can't can't switch
money
you can send money in between which one
is it you can send money okay it looks
like you can send money mostly
um there's a money wire but is that also
post story or
is that still
possible before story
you can vote later uh-huh the money
thing isn't poster okay now
okay well for now that was a long side
game let's go to uh
do some main story
a piece of crap excuse me
that was that was so
fun i like the
the makeover aspect the other part of it
is kind of
difficult because it's really busy
oh pocket tissues
yeah this is my item box
huh
yes
you also give me pocket tissues i
already got some just now no don't need
yours
like a character green and yeah
you can really like give them a glow up
of the century
hey hey hey mover
welcome back to my beautiful place
man
majima
you can't be so proud of yourself
[Music]
wait can i go grab some chocolates give
me chocolate
can i grab some chocolate
stretch yeah
yeah
chocolate
you
mm-hmm
um
i'm running out of chocolate
unbelievable where is all my chocolate i
thought i had more
where is all my chocolate and yes i did
get distracted by chunkers
i found there in my closet sleeping in
like a like a kind of a box you know
those foldable box i have some
um
stuff in there but chunkers likes to
hide in there because it's like dark and
quiet
yeah i leave my closet doors like a
little bit open
usually
so john grace likes to sleep in there
and she also always hides there when i
turn on the
the the vacuum cleaner she
zooms runs as fast as lightning speed
into the closet and doesn't come out
after
like
like at least 20 minutes after the
vacuum
cleaning is done
yeah
poor chunky
she's such a chicken just like you guys
yeah
chocolate
um
[Applause]
okay
it's pocky time
where is he
aha ah looks familiar
i think
somebody
[Music]
um
oh it's a doctor that we punched in his
stomach
[Laughter]
man
background
left side kirara i thought she came to
my other place why is she still working
here
kirana
nani stone then
um
okay
[Music]
we have a fanboy
this is our new fan
okay i that's it that's all we came for
okay
watashi
i'm not that dicey yo
i love you too i love you too man
massimo
you
he doesn't remember
what happened with your forehead
is
foreign
they're baseball players can i get an
autograph
[Music]
i am actually somewhat of a baseball
player
myself and i only get home runs
let's go
[Applause]
wait
[Music]
um
there we go feeling much better
stop stop stop his attacks his attack
chains are oh
are so long
can you not what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
with me
oh no i didn't want to see your [\h__\h]
face today
jumbo
with the big earrings
it's not my fault
um
he's a handsome man after
majima didn't go home last night
right i was headed back home at least
gotta be watching from somewhere
okay
really that's it we're not gonna talk
anymore of sagamon
he's just gonna let us go like that
kushkatsu
wait where am i going
ah down here
sumimasen
sorry i'm a lost child in this big city
help intervene
haven't uh saved in a while i hope i am
not gonna get my ass kicked
[Applause]
i think they got their ass kicked
instead
real sorry sir we will be causing you to
trouble again thanks you really saved me
i'd like to give you something in return
maybe this will do
slightly better stamina
a rat
perfect
we are literally a hero
for humanity
making this world a better place
oh you're right i live here
oh hello
what
[Music]
um
it's
underground
um
foreign
i like that you're using the tinfoil
emotes nice
uh first off i gotta try to figure out
wherever i'm being watched time to play
cool like i'm just strolling around and
try to stress out where they're watching
from
oh slip through unnoticed
how
how do i
go about that
do it
how do i
when i do that
wait isn't it huh that's not mr
shakedown but
oh walk normally
we don't need to go
to the bottom
[Music]
oh okay he's one of the ones watching me
hmm
okay i was just trying to go
not the obvious way
ah
can i go this way
looks like it's fine
oh
wait let me see
uh
what what what we're here here i haven't
saved at all
very casual
wait should i be
walking should i not run really
oops why no why is know the default
welcome egg thank you for the membership
yeah for him it's casual
all right
but this is gonna take ages if i walk i
don't have time for that
he's watching me
guess the bastards got everywhere i
might want to go on lockdown
very in character for me at least i like
to go get massages hopefully i keep i'm
thinking i'm still inside a while long
enough to find the store and get gone
anyway ah that reminds me um i went to
get a massage again uh a few days after
the after the concert a few days one or
two days or so
and um
i was going for the massage menu
and
um i forgot that the massage that i was
about to choose welcome to the
membership was the one that last time
was so um
intimate
i forgot it was that one
and um
yeah the handsy one
yeah but it was a good massage and um i
actually
um this was like my third time or so
at that massage place and up until now
it was kind of like always really
awkward
um the lady
who works there is uh is chinese and um
she's nice and all but we don't really
like talk
and i i always felt like she was a
little bit
a little bit scary
but i'm supposed to find a hiding door
yeah okay
a secret passage
lady god hands she has
really really
strong hands even though she looks
fairly weak yeah
um but this time
we actually
had a long-lasting conversation
um
because
i started the conversation
and and she ended up being like so sweet
and nice we talked about so many things
like how she got to austria
and it was really interesting she had an
interesting backstory that was a really
intricate and detailed npc
yeah yeah yeah
and um
told me about her her daughters and
and uh
uh
yeah blah blah blah
and i told her a little bit about myself
i guess but i was i was a bit
embarrassed because when she was
like touching
some parts of my body i was like
[Music]
um
and then sometimes she would say things
like oh cute cute and
wild
while touching my legs i was like
i want to um i want to say this is the
the fault of her not being 100 fluent in
german but
um some some some things were confusing
to me
um
oh yeah
but
okay what's the matter with it but we
did have a good conversation and
and i feel like finally i i don't feel
like um
i don't know like i'm
unwelcome in that store
i think she
she's now also
more
um
happy about seeing me and at the end at
the end
when when we're done and and i went to
to pay at the front counter
her other colleague was there
and
the colleague looked at me
and she asked me in what year i was born
and i told her and she said yeah yeah
yeah yeah uh in chinese something i
don't know culture or whatever um we say
that when you're born in that year
you're uh you need to drink more water
you're really lacking
hydration that's like okay
i mean that could be true oh
shake down mr shakedown was there
yeah
apparently apparently that's the reason
why i
have problems with my throat probably
and with
my skin is a bit dry too you know so it
makes all sense it makes all perfect
sense
[Laughter]
and and then and then and then um
they
uh like helped each other translate
something trying to tell me what was it
i just i think they wanted to tell me
that i look that i look cute
so it was like up until that point it
always felt very like a cold atmosphere
when i was at at that mustache place but
then
after i started a conversation and we
both opened up to each other now
suddenly they're like my fan girls and
they're like oh they're so cute
oh and yeah
i was i was wearing a coat and all that
i was dressed up pretty warmly and
outside it wasn't even that cold but
when i was about to leave they were like
are you okay are you okay you're dressed
like like so so um coldly i don't know
the words
you should dress warm and you're gonna
get a cold and they were touching my
hands and they had really warm hands and
they said wow you have such cold heads
and they were like holding my hands to
make them warmer
i feel like yeah they suddenly treated
me like their daughter or something yeah
suddenly treating me like their daughter
[Music]
is
yeah
they both ended up being big fans
oh and they really they really really
really wanted to know my job
um they wouldn't stop asking
so i ended up telling them i'm a voice
actress
and once they
were able to translate that on their
phone on google they were like oh wow
wow that's amazing wow so cool
thankfully they didn't ask any follow-up
questions
yeah yeah but now
now i feel more
comfortable about going back there i was
actually scared and i was like feeling
like i want to change
my massage place
uh my to go massage place because i felt
so unwelcome there but now they're so
maybe actually now they're too nice and
the lady is so touchy
she's so touchy
she's so touchy man
yeah
oh man uh anyway what were we doing if i
was being when i'm clean now to haul ass
to where the girl is okay
whole ass what the [\h__\h] does that mean
okay
should we go bottom and then right
they hopefully lost track of me
eh there's eyes up ahead what
they ain't see me i'm gonna keep my
distance i'm gonna go a different path
okay
here too
oh you guys are matching your colors
that's cute
there
[Music]
it always disappears so fast
now it doesn't come up anymore
i'm out of heat
i forgive you
oh yeah there's do you guys ever go to
massages there was there's this one
thing that i really hate when
massage people do it but it happens so
fast i can't tell them to not do it
um you know when they like kind of flick
your toes and your fingers like one by
one
they grab it they grab them and then
quickly
eh
and then quickly like
like not really pull them but i don't
know you know what i mean
it's so strange yeah i don't like that
because it feels like they're tearing
off my toenails or something
no not cracking they just like
it's hard to explain you like that it's
for circulation
you like the flicking thingy i don't
like it
never had that happen
i don't know they almost they do it in
almost every massage i go to
mention it beforehand that reminds me of
another massage story that i still
didn't tell you that i wanted to tell
you
um you know when i was on that uh
ski trip
uh
yeah i booked some massages there and it
was always the same lady doing it and
she was like
[Music]
i was kind of um disappointed
because for the first time like i've
i've had so many massages
everywhere until now in austria in
greece in japan no matter where i go i
always get massages um but this lady
pissed me off because um
like i would i would tell her for
example uh like i would get in there and
like normally in japan
uh this is what i like about getting a
massage in japan they
for example they would give you like a
sheet um with like a body drawn on top
of it and you can like circle the areas
that you want them to focus on and you
tell them
or you have to fill out like a form
where you feel pain strongly and
where you feel especially exhausted and
so on
um so that they can treat you better
individually right
um so they don't really do that in
austria at all and no place that i've
been to until now ah except
i think they might have done a
kind of uh in in that place i went to
with my bff
that place was more professional um yeah
they had a more professional massage
thing going on but anyway that lady she
um didn't do that and i went in so i
thought okay i will tell her uh vocally
then because when there's no form like
that i like to tell them that i am
especially
um exhausted in my shoulders and in my
neck so please go stronger there and
focus on that rather than the lower body
because it was a full body massage and i
said maybe focus on the upper body
that's all i said
i actually said it just with a few voice
i said um can you focus on my upper body
or something like that
and she was like
like um i'll we'll see about that i i
know what i'm doing
that's
what she said and that intimidated me so
i was like
oh okay
and then with while she was doing the
mustache like one time i asked her can
you do um this like here a bit stronger
can you
grab a bit stronger and she was like
i know what i'm doing and i'm like okay
um
okay
and then she goes to my butt
and i told her i don't really like um
but massages can you not
and she was like
but the but but
uh there's like so many emotions running
through that i know what i'm doing i
need to do this
so like i could literally
not change anything and
like she was so confident in what she
was doing
that even if when i say i don't like
something she would still like do it
like
what
what the [\h__\h]
i've never experienced that before like
what you're supposed to
adjust to what the customer wants you to
do
and then what really pissed me off i
have kind of something like massage ocd
it's like for example
normally
massage person does one thing on one
side and then they switch to the other
side and do the same thing the same
amount of time
but this lady sometimes would do one
thing on one side and then don't do the
same thing on the other side and in my
head it would really bother me i would
be thinking like
you didn't do that one thing but that
actually felt good why did you not do it
on the other side i actually needed it
on the other side i actually needed that
on the other side that's what i mean it
ah
yeah yeah
so first of all she was not like
listening to
or
cooperating at all with like what i was
saying and asking her to do and second
of all she says she knows what she's
doing but her massage wasn't even that
good
um but i had um
one more massage and and the full body
peeling um
with her so i had to see her two more
times but honestly the first time it
really really intimidated me so i just i
just didn't didn't bother with it
anymore even though it pisses me off
because massages are really expensive to
get so i think the least you could do is
listen to at least
where i want you to focus on
because i know my body best as much as
you like to say you know my body best
um
i would like you to listen to where i am
feeling pain
yeah i was pretty bad
um
i was not really happy with that service
that was the first
time that i had
an experience like that no i didn't
leave a review or anything um
at some point i was just like
so
annoyed by that lady
yeah
it's weird i should i should maybe tell
the
yeah
two stars on yelp no zero stars on yelp
yeah my disappointment is immeasurable
and my day is ruined i was really
looking forward to you know getting a
massage after a long day of skiing and
all that being really exhausted
yeah i was looking forward to that oh
well but i have to say that the the
peeling the full body peeling was good
the massage was um bad
but the full body peeling was good
um felt really nice smells really good
too
yeah anyway oh no no no no no no no no
skip no skip
uh resume one more time
therapist ever
pictures pictures of you pictures of me
do you
m
[Music]
is that supposed to look alike
huh
[Laughter]
oh
switch them out
uh
hoping that they'll both get away by
killing that girl that's why he said
they'll all get away but it's not a nice
solution
so we still have to kill someone
[Music]
well maybe maybe he will do the
finishing blow for us
it works
[Music]
what
foreign
um
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
oh wait i'm not even healed i'm not even
healed
okay
let's go
yes
uh he got me there he got me there
let's go
don't need to press something
i refuse i was waiting for that i had a
feeling that would come finally i didn't
mess it up
[Music]
uh
yeah baby holy [\h__\h]
i
[Music]
get
my babies one day
don't take that away from me they'll be
what's with his poise man
he got quite some points
okay that was pretty good i would say
i was very focused
[Music]
on
i get that we both need it we both need
it
[Music]
he's right
if his problem is killing that girl but
we're gonna end up [\h__\h] up her face
anyway
how about we sneak into
um one of those places where they keep
dead bodies
then just take one that looks somewhat
similar because i mean we're not using
the same person anyway and then [\h__\h] up
that person's face and that person is
already dead already so
then the problem of having to kill
someone is gone because that person is
already dead
no
the police would ah i guess it's already
registered then we gotta just i mean
we're yakuza we can probably get
somewhere in between
before they get a dead body and bring it
to what's it called the morgue before
they bring it there we just kind of
um
take it from them
before like where we we sneak in between
those two steps before before they take
it away but after someone dies we'll
find the dead body first
but okay maybe that's too big brain
um
[Music]
he really needs those photos
[Applause]
so what are we going to do majima i mean
cool that you're not so against killing
someone
but what are we going to do
have you thought about that
no
no jump
hmm
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] it's on your suit
okay
[Music]
um
i wouldn't throw that away so publicly
like that
who is that was it
ichiban ichiban was wearing a suit like
that yeah
but he's not even um
born yet at this point
um
this makes three days didn't wind up
changing much if anything things are
worse now number four
dick's up as soon as saga will find out
i'm keeping the girl alive
can't risk heading to the storehouse now
better play cool and head to the ground
like normal
hmm oh he was at this point really
okay
but he must have been a baby
hello baby was that
button popped up
maybe it was my imagination
all right
uh we are going to give um
up there okay
we are going to the grand
[Music]
get some work done
the ground
grand wrong ground
wait why is everyone always so
aggressive
welcome
welcome and bienvenue welcome
my spin the wind
welcome
what am i supposed to do here i see no
pink sign
how about we do a little gig on stage
i can't go up
it's my place i can't even be on my own
stage really
okay let's go upstairs stage upstairs
thank you thank you i'm finally
finishing yakuza zero oh
how far ahead are you hopefully
quite a bit
so that
me
playing this won't be a spoiler to you
i am going into the back room
ah shiny ohio
the hell does he want after what
happened last night
straight
gasoline needs to talk says is waiting
for me at hokashi kaikan
okay
we always come here just for like one
second and immediately already have to
leave i want more like stuff
could be going on in here too
i want this gorgeous place go to waste
[Music]
it sounds like a trap i have a feeling
that the the person with the purple suit
will be waiting for us there and it's
just
acting as lee
well maybe maybe i'm wrong i'm probably
wrong
oh man
all the way down there again let's take
a cab
taxi taxi
we are going
that way
safe okay
yes i unlocked sunshine
already spent quite some time in there
i'm not sure if we're gonna go back
there today
but
i have it in the back of my mind
wouldn't you safe
moshimosh
mystery caller
these sub stories always show up when
i'm in the middle of doing something
answer
how do you even call a random phone
booth like that
hello
wait wait a second let me get my special
effects
[Music]
hello you answered at last
this guy sounds awfully trippy trippy oh
okay trippy trippy's more like
yes it's you i want to speak with
who the hell are you what do you want
with me yeah
oh i am doesn't matter i don't know who
you are
you wanted to talk to
have to me you anyone who picked up the
phone would have been fine
but in the end you are the one who wants
it
i can't let's say i tell you no doubt
about it
listen man they have telephone clubs
we're just kind of very good into the
mood to get sweet talked here
ah you're rejecting me already
no funny business where i'm hanging
right the hell on
i want you to play and play with me
this sounds like funny business
just bring me the item i asked for it
what do you think
first thing i'm gonna say is what's in
it for me
page 413 of the phone book
um
open it up
oh
i got cash money
it's not much though
if you win the game i'll pay you an even
bigger reward
how about it
still think there's nothing in for you
are you in the habit of leaving that
much cash and phone book anybody could
bump through you're real nother
i liked it i'll play your game
i appreciate it
in case you turned me down
can you say that with certainty
it doesn't matter if you believe me or
not i don't need to trigger it anymore
are you crazy [\h__\h]
well what is it you want me to get for
this game of
about you bring yours a nine millimeters
automatic pistol
i don't even know what that is
uh what the hell are you gonna do that
i'm doing with that um
oh i wasn't concerned this stuff was
what i needed for
i ain't a fan of getting put to the test
but i can score that for you no problem
have to catch ready
okay
i don't have no idea where i would get
that but i know it's a gun i just mean
like nine millimeters and all that [\h__\h]
i don't know the difference
i'm not very well worth versed in guns
excuse me for not knowing my gun abc
what a shame what a shame on me
please don't fight me again
not that i would lose
[Music]
no the guy with the purple suit in it
is
know
[Music]
foreign
huh
[Music]
they're watching me
assuming that that guy did that for us
how did he know that we wanted that lady
to be dressed in
those clothes
maybe he just logically concluded to it
but it wasn't that clear was it i don't
know
foreign
i know you want the nine millimeter gun
i know
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
dark escape 10 million completion bonus
we finished the chapter
uh let's do another one
holy [\h__\h]
yeah
what
yeah thank you darla can save
[Music]
he's not meaningless
yeah he's not an elder ring player
i'm not a big fan of ellen ring
oh my
god oh my god
he's got the ladies on the control he
probably
uh
threatened them
with a good time haha just kidding
tug of war chapter eight oh
ps5
playing with ps5
i don't know i'm cool
for doing that
i knew that was stupid
foreign
[Music]
okay this is very interesting
thank you for the membership welcome
welcome guy who called me said he's
waiting at the ground let's go meet my
newest customer
go to the ground
thank you venom thank you
okay i'm going all the way back up here
taxi time again
taxi taxi mr taxi taxi taxi and trick
sweet trucks making six
[Music]
old song
old as hell
or they're waiting for me
oh what's this side question
it's a side quest you don't have time
for this now what the [\h__\h] but nice suit
nice suit
hmm hold up a sec oh yeah
are you the guy who runs the ground
it's me
so how's it going making mad moonloo
and all right how about you
oh you're really gonna ask him
you're the one who brought it up smart
guy
tell you the truth i got serious cash
money problems
the back of my mine's closed sorry
no no the trouble is i got more cash
than i can use
come on
[Music]
you earn all that from tips with some
kind of guitar my strong
oh this one is online i hand it out to
people who listen to me to play
that's that's that's a way of getting
people to listen to you you pay them
yeah yeah yeah yeah
what a big brain system you got there
yeah
oh what else am i gonna do no matter how
much you spend i can't get rid of it
it's like unlimited money
i took it to a bank but they said they
haven't got enough room in the world
what
i can people take some of my hands if i
play them a song or two
yes just skip it out like that
oh you got me there i see why they call
you lord of the land
what's that got to do with anything and
you're really that rich feels more like
you're yanking my chain
oh it's my weapon obvious i try not to
flaunt it too much but when you're the
can you got the aura bling
ain't no way to hide my high ball of
vibe
i hate to break it to ya but you look
more like a cross between a launch
singer and a used car salesman
it's a good example
[Music]
seriously the sleaze is just oozing
right off yeah
what
well you're nothing like the type who
shows up in my club and throws money
around that's for sure but we can maybe
get come on majima business business oh
big guy in the back watch my business
man don't call where is your business
spirit
try to get him as a customer
oh
oh yeah i thought you might say that
so you're admitting it it's been
stressing me out i really am rolling in
dome but for whatever reason people
think i'll i look like the human bottom
end of a gutter i'm good at makeovers
let me try to make you over then
all right try to tell a soft story
because it ain't working what i'm trying
to do is find a way to show my wolf
that's what i
heard you gotta wear gucci man
and valenciaga
sojambo is loaded tonight majima first
time i saw you on the street guys and
girls were falling over themselves left
and right to get into you good graces
i don't exactly like all the attention
but you don't seem rich at all
i mean that's that's a good thing yeah
so you don't get robbed or whatever sure
you look flashy on the outside but it
feels like an act to me i could see the
veneer peeling off oh i hope i'm not
offending you or anything
i guess you got some steamy after all
never mind tell me
why is your ghost stopping me on the
street if you think i'm faking it
yeah about that i was thinking maybe you
and i could be friends
no
i want you to show me how to act rich
and what makes you think god do that
once again for me money money obviously
don't know what to say to that let me
ask you that what's the difference if
you look rich or not
it's a huge difference when you look
rich you can hit on girls without them
screaming and running away they might
actually listen for a change who knows
maybe ladies start trying to talk me
into marrying them i could build up a
whole harem huh
so you're just another horn dog chasing
tail after all pretty damn pathetic
how the hell did you get rich in the
first place i don't understand this word
sometimes
when it comes to money i got all the
luck can you join the uh virtual agency
called whole life yeah yeah that's where
it came from i was really popular
streamer number one yeah yeah
okay now you're just being a creeper
how about this sin if you help me earn
some green i'll be your pal
wow
you know always friendship that'd be
something you give away for free
she's so he's got double standards man
now you're gonna take the moral high
ground if you're not rich you may as
well buy a few friends
so friendship can be bought
all right
i'll buy you money how much will it take
for you to hang out with me your sneeze
is making my skin crowd
if you got pockets that deep just come
to my club as a customer exactly that's
that's now we're talking
okay
if that ain't gonna fly forget it no
cash i walk
oh no it ain't bad i don't want to go
just steam's not have a hard time
spending much cash in a cabaret
you really think so the grant ain't some
pop-up dive bar pal those girls have
you're paying through the nose
what does that mean
what does that whole sentence mean
don't worry i've got the money i'm gonna
say i like that thing with the money
shower before am i to give it a try at
myself one of these ah
are you learning that skill now too okay
okay okay okay now we learned that too
i know how about you investing no fun
then you'd be making money on over first
ah now that you know he wants me to
invest to [\h__\h]
investment fund
me another wealthy people around the
country share info and take
contributions from investors we got the
smarts to make the money away from us so
you're gonna be sure it's gonna pay
dividends what the [\h__\h] where are we
going with this where are we going with
this cyclist
what do you want from me
[Music]
i'm gonna make any profit with loose
change right i have to invest big
of course anyway i'm talking enough for
today let's go over this some other time
okay you got to know tanyoka that was
known as mr moneybags interacting with
him will gradually fill the friendship
cause you can check the status of this
cause at any time in the pause menus
completion list
the way he just stares at me
saying nothing just playing his guitar
all right
oreno
oh god the big guy is always in the
background
he's got one more band-aid
[Laughter]
they're making a fool out of him
it's gonna be a mummy yeah
mommy yes mommy
yes mommy
yes mommy please mommy
oh interesting scene
they actually sound like they're
enjoying it
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
no no no not here
[Music]
damn
and yet the girls were around when you
called me
let me sit on that pile of money instead
now
that chair is way too tiny for him
haven't heard of that before
again
foreign
my
just a girl
oh no
please know
no
yeah he doesn't fight in here
[Music]
you
oh
[Laughter]
foreign
they were role-playing he's into role
play
he
[Music]
oh god
oh
he's got matrix
[Music]
that move is
it still hasn't got a hit on me though
[Music]
what are those moves man
holy [\h__\h] get up get up
oh oh he scares me
quiet buzzy
yeah
oh buttons buttons buttons buttons
got it
[Music]
that's that tickles
oh stop stop stop stop stop stop stop
i i i i i wow
oh
oh [\h__\h] no no no no go away go and go go
and um by the way let's hear
the fun interesting fight though
[Music]
he doesn't do it unless i get closer
does he
huh
[Music]
oh he's doing it again
awkward
[\h__\h] insane
what if i should use a different mode i
always use this one today
yeah
okay
okay yeah i got used to it so i'm okay
with it
[\h__\h] weirdo
why don't we let him out of the mental
clinic
well those guys
really like um being [\h__\h] up
foreign
um
i'm so confused
oh wait in the office okay where's the
money pile it's gone
where did my money go
try finishing my majima's cover race up
sorry i can get that i heard that i
could get something big from it yeah
oh
i'm disappointed in you i
i can't
grow
what is it
if you do that for one of those guys the
others will expect it too
and this is not that kind of a place you
know
you can get his number and i don't know
meet up privately
sorry
is
[Music]
[Laughter]
the logic of that is indeed kind of um
um
[Music]
because he was groping my girls
that's all there is
[Music]
so i'm getting back into my
yakuza
alliance
the fake body is only gonna throw soccer
off the trail so long hell he may
already be wise i gotta talk to leanna
hurry he should be with the girl
yeah
well i'll save
[Music]
he seemed to believe
me
but he was also asking interesting
questions but he still seemed to believe
me
question is just for how long until
it all comes out
he knows
you think he knows
um
[Music]
[\h__\h] i'll upgrade
yeah
shut the weight just to wait
shut the weight
oh
nice
[Music]
foreign
where's my stream on youtube
[Music]
hello doko
hello
do you hear me don't call s-e-a losing
losing connection we're back fine for
you okay okay thank you for the
membership welcome
youtube
go to the odyssey warehouse yes well
that's where i was going and oh yeah uh
abilities
i've been using slugger a lot oh we
haven't done anything with breaker
we gotta do something
at least the basics
uh-huh
let me take a look at slugger
what's the next step um increases the
poverty rate
okay 15 50 million
holy macaroni
yeah i was really enjoying breaker style
of majima i want to play that too
oh two million
two million is okay
okay spend some money now we're good to
go i think we are going to go all the
way to the bottom again so let's take
another taxi
taxi taxi
and i have to play with cabaret soon
yeah
um yeah
maybe maybe i know i always say that but
maybe i'll play it off stream
i just don't wanna because it takes so
much time i don't wanna like spend a
whole stream on it you know
i feel like cause this is gonna be such
a long playthrough anyway
since it's a long game
i
i don't wanna
like oh cats
i don't i don't want to make it
too much longer than it needs to be than
it already is
um
i'll definitely show it at least one
more time on stream but i don't know how
often i can do it
um
hmm
[Music]
second half much shorter
um
but obviously the main story is the most
entertaining
the story and i'm
anata
[Music]
it took money
that's why it was like eh i don't care
about the medicine
[Music]
who are these people though what the
[\h__\h]
oh
[Music]
what's with you guys
what
huh
is the people who are watching me ah
yep
[Music]
no
friends
oh
[Music]
foreign
let me show you more
my beautiful dance moves
on the yakuza dance floor
but these are just winklings
[Music]
if we kill these eyes then they will
have no more eyes on me
it's a
[Music]
is that all you
get is that all you got we clicks
oh
i mean he sold us out but i still feel
bad for him
foreign
well we can
if we can we gotta save him
[Music]
and get him to play some man
that's the right thing
m
[Music]
it's okay
go go
i just want to save you and all of you
um
is this like a
kill chapter situation where we have to
know
[Music]
for the whole city
with these people in our life
that was [\h__\h]
hell on earth please now
oh [\h__\h]
no not again
[Music]
in that case the bat might be a wrong
choice because
i always have these moves that i can't
interrupt
ah another escort mission
which in theory is fine with that time
limit
is kind of tough
just oh try not to fight uh
hide okay what's it looking like
uh this way
uh-huh
go back go back go back
and now there was no time limit but in
others there were time limits
[Music]
oh
it is kind of your fault but
um
hi okay
what she's blind oh wait yeah so
so wait what what's the point what's
your point what did i say
oh we wait didn't we have this like last
time too
wait last time
did we
did we escort a blind girl in last
episode as well
wait was it the same girl i thought it
was with kill
so confused
i'm so confused
we just run through here
when i first saved her
i thought that was like
from curious chapter oh but different uh
i'm getting confused okay i'm paying
attention shut up i am paying attention
it's just a bit confusing okay
they are doing similar things after [\h__\h]
run button
oh no
i press the wrong button out oh man
i can't press the wrong button
because maybe not everyone knows all the
controls by heart on the controller
especially when playing sometimes with a
[\h__\h] switch sometimes with a ps5
sometimes with whatever the [\h__\h]
maybe i'll remember everything in the
span of one [\h__\h] second excuse me oh
yeah sorry i snapped it's always this
this mission that makes me snap
but i can't i just cancel the
expectations of some people
okay so this i will have to fight here
okay
it's gonna make me so aggressive again
i'm gonna [\h__\h] go crazy
wait no no no
get away
just gonna dance around here nobody
i hate this so much i hate it so much i
hate you so much
oh he just killed me
okay thank god what a [\h__\h] deja vu
[Music]
hands off my girlfriend
who's that what was that move
[Music]
have a um feeling
bad feeling
ah bad feelings
oh my god lisa
[Music]
lisa
oh
[Music]
she's
um
foreign
got it
it looks like italian mafia
new god
oh [\h__\h] is he from the korean mafia
trying to get the girl back
[Music]
finished the chapter that was that was
fast
i was fast
[Music]
why you gotta save a million times ps5 i
will never understand this
what's up
[Music]
[Laughter]
song poor guy
chapter nine ensnared
what does that mean
[Music]
back to tokyo
[Applause]
would i be walking around so obviously
i wouldn't i would not
extend
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah
of course
[Music]
well do you have a phone number how am i
supposed to tell you
can you kill you is you it's you oh no
our home
baby no
[Music]
it wasn't me
is he not actually stupid for going to
his home doesn't he think that people
would like be having an eye out on his
home
damn dogmas goons torched my apartment
just to tighten the noose around me
i can't risk wandering around here i
need to find a place to lie
low and wait for word from tati banana
uh
i just hope i can find someplace that
will take me in
find a place to hide
okay
game not telling me where i just walk
around okay
um i said two chapters per stream but i
feel like this was kind of short
four and a half hours very short in kiwa
terms how are our items looking oh dear
um is there a yakyoku
yakyoku
they probably won't even let me go to a
[Music]
oh there's one there
you probably will stop me before being
able to go
uh
we'll play a little bit
if the quest if the game allows us we
could do some
side stuff but i'm currently not really
like aware of what we even can do
[Music]
what are the the exclamation marks for
is it telling me that that's where my
side quests are that i have already
accepted or
or the cyclist that i still haven't
accepted
uh sub stories that
new ones that i haven't gotten yet
the active ones okay
oh god uh one of them is in
the disco
i like going to the disco
i wouldn't mind going to the disco
[Music]
no but i feel like i have i have bad
days and good days when it comes to the
disco mini game
it might be a bad day
i don't know
i don't know what style i want to find
[Music]
let's do this
yeah i do enjoy rush but
rash is so fast that activating the heat
skills is kind of
slow not again
this fight is unnecessarily lengthy
um
my attack is a little low i think so too
oh we have a lot of money we can do some
upgrades
um
[Music]
money spent another hotel
ah wait take a moment
i don't really use this one that much um
let's go to brawler
will i really ever even use that
increases the power of
regulation now i have to i have to get
it though
r2
you've got to rise when you i will
probably forget using it a lot you guys
are welcome to remind me
[Music]
i don't remember any of those moves
which is the amount of people when you
wait that's acquired uh reduce the rate
that the heat gauge drops over time
uh too much okay
let's go that one then
throwing yourself an enemy okay
i will not remember that
um
can i still do one more no
no
it's too expensive
here
also everything's 30 million okay
okay
uh
docile what should we do i feel like i'd
rather do some normal side quests then
i'm getting a headache now
crispy mug
yeah i fixed it i fixed it sometimes the
audio sound
gets the audio the game audio gets weird
because of the game capture card
um
i wonder though
at this if i end at this current point
and then
play off screen if it forces me to
continue the main story at some point
but if i ran around here
it's friday night oh it is friday night
oh no wait it's thursday night
oh [\h__\h]
oh my god these people are absolutely
insane
hello
yes
[Music]
uh
okay okay i'm in the room i'm in the
groove i'm in the group
this is what they like to call
rip someone a new one right yeah yeah
that's what they're trying to do i don't
need a new one i already have one
i already have one
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] is the matter with these
people
[Music]
okay
now i currently don't have enough money
for more defense upgrades unfortunately
uh
what the hell even are all those
surpluses one thing down here
let's see if the game stops me from
doing something though
i'll try
huh give it a try
i'm not kidding you i just look a lot
like him
let's hang out no no
[Music]
i'm managing to run for the city pretty
freely though
doesn't seem like much of an issue
oh
what's this
the cat's in my family office oh you're
thinking about staying here
if kasiwagi's son took me and now the
kazuma family will have officially
betrayed patriarch dojima
all that does is make trouble for
kasiwagi-san i can't come running to
okay
i i wasn't going there for that purpose
anyway
hello excuse me
[Music]
[Applause]
do you guys get a redhead as well when
you drink a lot of alcohol
[Music]
i don't drink so many people are saying
they don't drink
but you'd say you don't drink often or
you don't drink at all is do i do i um
bring in the no drinker people the
straight edge fans
do you guys like me because i'm just
like you
hashtag relatable
don't drink at all wow that's so rare i
feel like
that is like actually a really rare
thing but my whole chat says they don't
drink
you sure about that
yep
my beloved
um
[Music]
okay
be careful though okay
be careful
be chiata full go to serena
serena serena so close okay
serena shut up
it's not me how many times do i have to
tell you
wait i shouldn't ah don't follow me i
actually i kind of want to oh buy some
items oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] you
no
for real those wait a second
um
i want to go to
they're so far away yeah
and where is that here's a drugstore
that's so far
let's go to the convenience store for
now
man no let me please buy
[Music]
hi girl
i um the best we can do is buy a couple
of those
and
i'm not done i'm not done girl
maybe
food heals um better it doesn't say how
much each item heals unfortunately
um
but i would assume
this should bring
a bit of health
it's fine bentos are good
how about the drugstore it's too far
away
well that's that's the only banter they
have i wonder if they count yakisoba as
a bento too
nice okay we'll just buy
[Music]
a few more
last time i drank a jungle i ordered 3
000 usd in magic gathering cards oh i
thought you're gonna say in in drinks
oh oops ellen do you regret it i didn't
read until the end
three thousand
damn
okay so can i enter from here
may i
and any healing
okay
okay okay this one no higher
this one this one
mommy
that means
i heard people say that a lot at some
point
where did that come from
is
oh
[Music]
uh
foreign
ah
oh
no problem
i'm ready get yourself
no free people can't hurt me
all right
smile slimy faces
you
oh they're getting more oh oh
oh god
[Music]
he was already back up but i still got
that one
you want a new nose right
i'll give you one
get up get up get up
[Music]
ow
what just happened oh i killed him okay
i got one hit in
he get a kick
no time for
in a prison cell right now
it's an ideal
reality
[Music]
is going to ask her out after all this
is over
and then marry him
oh okay no romantic here
no romance no no
or not
[Music]
sir
it's okay it's daijoubu don't worry
about me girl
ah hello
mo niggarin
um
i can't deal with the frustration of
that mode at this moment then
we just gotta get it over with quickly
hope for the best
[Music]
i always try to not have too many
enemies in the back
so they don't interrupt me
too often
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
oh my god
mine is
[\h__\h] fasted
[Music]
is
okay
hmm
[Music]
is old okay please leave him alone
watch it
[\h__\h]
yeah oh it's already gone that felt good
though
down
[Music]
damn
no no you guys happy now
i am an uber human
yes run away
cockroaches
run away
and tell the others
that i am too strong
you can't handle me
oh no but wait there's more
um
uh
bro
but you brought
[Music]
there must be some
kind of rescue now right
dance before
um
[Music]
no not
i can't do
[Music]
no this even have people helping them
out
no
don't heal
first get these [\h__\h] down
um
[Music]
[Applause]
[\h__\h] i'm so [\h__\h] up so far
okay but we already cleaned up a little
bit
[Music]
no let me pick something up please
i hate it i can't walk around like it
takes me five million years to reach the
thing that i want to reach and then they
interrupt me and i can't [\h__\h] reach
for it
and then it's just a [\h__\h] kettle
that's all i [\h__\h] get a
candle so sick of this
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay it's just us left just you and me
okay
who's that you're gonna regret coming
back for me
[Music]
broke so early
you'll belong in the trash cousins
[Music]
oh
where the [\h__\h] did that come from
[Music]
now i brought you this present
it's your lucky day i have so many
presents for you
is there something here
i'm like a dog i i picked up things and
bring it to my owner
yeah
i'm so proud or like a cat that uh
brings the dead bird back to its owner
back he's not really back but
now are you in front of me
oh [\h__\h] get up get up get up
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] sick you won't let me get one
punching
i'm trying to
[Music]
what do you mean you don't want that i
really really put a lot of thought into
that present
[Music]
man this guy is insane
oh
[Music]
there's a flag
what do you think about this beautiful
flag huh
and welcome back with some ramen
no really
i would
wouldn't mind going for some ramen now
he keeps on refusing the ramen what's
your problem with the ramen
[Music]
wait chill chips
back
[\h__\h]
[Music]
it's a love story between me and kuze
he says it's not about the material
things i'm not a material girl
just want your body kid you
want your body
what
[Music]
oh come on in order to have that kind of
control over that
that's true unrealistic
okay
never seen so much emotion in his face
before did he turn robo mode um
[Music]
[Applause]
wow
his finger oh that hurts me to look at
it
you lost him again sucker
dorif doll
don't lift all gas guys guess
[Music]
i was hoping for something like that
like a helicopter or something would
have been nice too
would have been really impressive but
the car is nice
[Music]
she has a name
um
[Music]
before
foreign
[Music]
i think in real life most people don't
have someone who would literally risk
their life
[Music]
foreign
what happened with
[Music]
for you buddy
thank you for the membership welcome
unwanted
hd turned on
rtx
oh
[Music]
what happened with him he was just
driving a car what happened before that
chapter that was a short chapter two i
was trying to do such stuff but it just
happened so fast man
i wasn't even trying to finish a chapter
i was just waiting for a good moment to
end the stream
to end the gaming part
no that he wasn't shot they didn't they
they didn't get him
he got the car sick
well we still will have to look at a bit
more uh story i guess
or we end it right here
[Music]
you
three chapters man
chapter 10 a man's worth
okay but we'll stop it here we'll stop
it here i don't want to see a second of
it no no no no but i'm curious ah
i'll look i i i will take a look
i'm curious my curiosity
is too strong
okay he's fine
um
foreign
a pun in japanese just now but okay
he had to add that
single-handedly
[Music]
foreign
you got
it sounded legit
oh that speaks style with chinese
his voice actor definitely sounds
from what i've heard so far more
japanese like his japanese is perfect so
i could understand if they just went
with a japanese actor
the batatu oh [\h__\h]
i was too immersed
oh
okay
that is
not acceptable i will never play this
game again
you can't do this no
no
no no no no no no no
no no no no he's bad man yeah that's the
conclusion he's batman
no i mean
come on
i mean
since the beginning tachibana didn't
really seem like a nice guy even though
he's kind of nice to us now
his whole vibe in the beginning was like
kind of like darth vader or something i
don't know
song
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no no no
chinese doesn't
and i still heard that that was that
sounded like a japanese person speaking
chinese
uh
ah
yeah
okay
we had a surprising revelation there
must apart me too we're gonna read super
chat still
yeah and i have a surprise at the end um
but yeah
first of the first first before we do
that i will go to do an idle meeting
intermission and pet cat intermission
very important also i just noticed my
hands are really small today
even should be like that
surprise it's not
much of a surprise anymore at this point
but
[Laughter]
yeah thank you guys for watching today
more yakuza next week we are zooming for
the game at this point surprisingly
and uh
yeah tomorrow i think is
wait what
what day is it today
no it is
it is friday and i so confidently
told someone
that today is first day
and it's
just
it is friday night who did i say say
that to
yo it's not friday it's first date you
got me almost
so thursday
friday
is friday okay so tomorrow is ttipuji i
was just wondering like isn't tomorrow
ttrpg huh
but how's that possible if today is
thursday
[Laughter]
[Music]
i lost track of the days
i thought you guys were just joking
because haha friday night haha there's a
song in the game
with
okay okay okay okay so tomorrow ttipg
and sunday we have um
and
my real card with you guys
yeah
now hold on
it's a little bit of a pun moment okay
finally i realized finally
so
uh i will
go to the intermission for a little bit
a few moments a few minutes please be
patient and i'll be back soon
automatically
[Music]
see you in a little bit i go afk okay
thank you for watching today
very very interesting story progression
today as well um
yeah
[Music]
do
all right
all right all right i got some smoothie
cuddles
yeah oh
how do i end the game
return to title
yeah
[Music]
this movie is so soft how does she do it
how does she do it
maybe gravy isn't the
the best way to get soft
[Music]
let me fix the chat chat
chat
okay
oh welcome back to the office
also i really like having burp on my
head
cute
we need some music
what are we feeling like so quiet right
now it's so
dead quiet
oh
[Laughter]
hmm
i sent
i said mummy something and she was
really amused by it
um i asked spirit snare
can i show this i'm just going to show
it
[Laughter]
i asked spirit snow yesterday because i
was so inspired
to um redo
the logo of mummy song because he made
the logo for her song
a new start and i asked
i asked to remake it and i sent it to
mummy
i just died
[Laughter]
oh the mad lad
what a mad lad
it's because a new start
really sounds like
and and and i was watching just recently
i was re-watching um
arrested development
and there's in the later really late
season
thank you in a very late season they uh
um
there was this car
that what's what was the character's
name again i forgot um
uh was it i forgot
but he wanted to have a new start but it
didn't fit it to be tobias yeah it
didn't fit in the plate of his car so he
wrote
this
[Laughter]
tobias yeah he's just such a weirdo
um
this is the kind of humor that i like
ah i already sent it to her she was very
very amused i don't know if she's going
to use it though
[Music]
we've been also planning something for
april fools as a group
so look forward to that
by the way
uh as always
last minute because whole live
holo myth is only ever able to do things
last minute apparently
i'm so sorry to the people who have to
work with us i'm so sorry
we're always like doesn't matter who's
planning it but it's always last minute
although i do try to
keep things that's so fast
oh
sorry
um
[Music]
i'm sorry
okay what do we have uh audio stock what
did i save uh i saved something
yesterday oh yeah this one was cute i
think
wait
both of them tropical i'm feeling
tropical today
[Music]
tropical
oh i can't wait for my vacation
[Music]
yeah my your sunshine vibes
i love it
we should play super mario sunshine
again
[Music]
yeah it could fit in there as well
let's
did she really just say that
it's like um
my traumatic memories have been wiped
out
because
[Music]
it's just the positive things about the
game
are
overwhelming you know
but kirby kirby also could be nice to
get into yeah
i want to play more games like that in
any case like more like mario
games um
or anything in that universe for that
matter
yeah i want to try some of those mario
games that are um
not 3d
like those side scroller mario games
where you jump jump jump jump
i want to try some of those
i'll be really [\h__\h] at it but
yeah
super mario world i guess so i don't
know
one of the newer ones though
um
mario maker yeah well maybe look into
mario maker as well
you beat or you can beat anything thank
you so positive
[Music]
because
that's one that i have i don't have the
playlist station one but i have the
nintendo subscription
[Music]
all right um
i have to read super chats from today
only hallelujah
because i was a good girl and read them
correctly
uh correctly until
the very end
not not exactly but i read the rest of
them privately
so thank you everybody for your kindness
and your patience
thank you very much
kfp
too generous way too generous
[Music]
i'm so proud
wow good girl mm-hmm
[Music]
it's
i still have the pictures up i don't
want to take them
uh
you know what you know what would be
nice um
putting one of these in the frame eden
are you listening
let's put some of these pictures in the
frame
i want i want one of them down here or
maybe in the back oh maybe up here up
here i want a frame i mean it could be
doesn't matter it could be like a png
and i put it up there
i put it here wherever ah but then it
covers up the chicken huh
if it's up there
[Music]
i need to
i need to make my office bigger
maybe
yeah i guess i guess here or
on the side i could like put it on the
side of of this uh wooden wall
or we get rid of the menu ideas and put
some in there or we get rid of one of
the tvs we don't need all of them i
guess
[Music]
yeah we could instead of menu ideas we
can have like a couple of pictures there
although i do like the idea of having
many ideas there you know because we are
a restaurant thingy after all i think we
got to think about
menu ideas be innovative but for now
i'll put that there
wow look at look at look look at your
boss
ignore menu ideas for now just look at
this stuff yo
inspiring
[Music]
yeah so proud
i'm not on the menu
thank you everybody
[Music]
we're at a restaurant yeah
and maybe maybe maybe i could have an
option
for sometimes if i want to put up
pictures
it could be for pictures but then at
other times we can put back the menu
yeah yeah yeah yeah
anyway
what's your reading super chats
from today
rachel
you know what i was thinking when i was
watching the new girl the new indonesian
girl
uh
her
is her rigor the same as corolla
because her face movements
really made me think of kuduli
[Music]
was so similar the way that the mouth
moves and and like the way her head
moves and all that
it's really interesting
to see how
it can look so similar
is it the same
[Music]
although partially sometimes her smile
also reminded me of
uh
abe or utto
i i wanna i wanna do that too i wanna be
able to
cheese
but i don't have teeth most of the time
but i feel like that looks so cute
i love how ame and uto and uh all these
girls
they have like proper teeth and they can
be like cheese
[Music]
it might be really weird in the
beginning though getting used to me
looking like that
i need bigger teeth i can't even cheese
[Music]
debuted
that was cursed
[Music]
i feel like something like this i would
i would have to
wait uh
a long time
to make it possible
um because i think then the base art has
to be
adjusted as well
and that's not something that just
happens
like that easily
all of these things take a lot of time
and there's restrictions and stuff too
[Music]
there's a lock around her neck bay has a
key
down the line yeah in a million years
probably never happening so
[Music]
has been announced as a character
designer for rwby
for
a new anime
[Music]
but it's not really like
not really saying it's his fault that it
will never happen
i ruby
right that was announced right because
that's why i saw it
with shuffle door
shuffle i can do shuffle doll
it's the shaft angle
yesterday yeah
so
it's gonna be uh he's gonna be busy i
guess but that's a good thing
having some work
i mean to be honest realistically at the
stage of it being announced he probably
is already done with the work though
because
it's
just the character design
and that has to be done pretty early
so i would assume he's already done with
it and already working on the next thing
but i don't know i don't know i don't
know egg
egg
[Music]
let's read some super chat though so i
don't fall behind too much
because you guys are crazy
[Music]
thank you thank you
oh don't worry we'll we'll we'll make it
happen after
uh april 1st sometime
i'll try to make it happen within april
maybe
yeah yeah
sad electrobuggy thank you
[Music]
are you writing in japanese because
you're embarrassed to say this in
english
because everybody will know what you're
saying
be proud no reason to be embarrassed
[Music]
but
it was perfect it sounded really good
[Music]
thank you you watched my performance on
the big tv screen rather than just on
the on a
small monitor nice
nice but let's hope that
you'll get the blu-ray because on the tv
screen with a blu-ray would be the ideal
situation
yeah
no bitrate problems
that would be nice
thank you sadeshobaki
thank you so much for your sweet and
loving support
thank you
from the bottom of my kokoro i don't
have a blu-ray player but you can play
blu-rays and uh on the playstation right
or maybe if you also don't have a
playstation then how about you just get
an
external blu-ray player
um
i don't think they're expensive you
could like just not send one super chat
and then buy a external blu-ray player
i have a ps5 well there you go don't
don't ps5 play uh blu-rays as well
um
yeah
that's that's what i uh
um
what was ps
three two even
was always famous for right because they
have a blu-ray player
[Music]
it's a sony format ah
ah ps2 was dvd
[Music]
korean virtual dancing typhon oh my god
oh my god
typhin what the [\h__\h]
thank you for
a [\h__\h] ton of red super chats
oh my god
uh one out of three i wanted to take a
bit to look back on your performance
before i send these so here we go
i've never been proud of someone i've
never met but after watching you these
past months and knowing how hard you
worked i can always say i'm proud of you
for all you've done i've said you are a
star so many times and even with my
expectations probably set to an
unreasonably high level you left me
speechless and honestly missed the eye
oh dear oh dear
you keep continuing to prove to me that
i made the right choice to stay and
support you as much as i can well would
you guys have
still
been proud of me if i did a shitty
really shitty performance up there if i
was just like really really bad at
dancing and just was like
noodling around
i hope so you guys say yes
[Music]
not proud but i would say
if you did your best then yes okay
[Music]
would have laughed at me
where was i you keep continuing to prove
to me that i made the right choice to
stay and support you as much as i can
everyone did an amazing job over the
weekend but you blew me away
you showed everyone the reason kfp
decided to follow you the passion and
love you have for kfp and for this job
truly shines so bright during that
performance wherever you start may rise
uh no we are proud of you and love you
so much
ty
new sweet potato
thank you
thank you thank you thank you
that is very very very very generous and
very kind thank you soon
i'm glad i could
i could make you proud but yeah as i
just said i wonder if you guys would
have all been really proud of me if even
if my performance would have been not so
you know
amazing
um
i would like to think yes but
it feels good to have everyone um
be so
how to stay um amazed and impressed and
stunned
yeah
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you so much
for your support typhon
i i sway more than i deserve but thank
you
thank
[Music]
i hope i can show you more
of my 3d and more of my dancing
in the future
yeah give back to you guys
so please stay
so that i can provide more to you hmm
[Music]
monkey scent of rainbow
rainbow
thank you
dear mrs takanasi kiera allow me to
offer my congratulations and gratitude
for your spectacular performance the
exuberance i experienced watching you
sing and dance was without doubt
unparalleled while my reactions may not
have been physical as physically vibrant
due to my general lack of energy why is
this so politely written
your appearance truly touched my heart
emotionally and flooded me with memories
memories of the past your debut the
beginning of kfp the joyous days as well
as the hardships you faced i have always
admired your strength to never give up
even when the fates themselves seem to
conspire against you and not a single
day have i ever entertained the notion
that you had let anyone down
thank you when i watched you run across
the stage greeting the audience as you
soared into their hearts and minds it
truly felt as if this moment was the
culmination of your journey thus far as
a journey i sincerely hope um will not
reach its terminus anytime soon
you are truly indubitably a marvelous
entertainer and inspiring leader and
forever an idol in my heart since
julia's jake gets monkey
i definitely did not sneak in the
wrinkle i was
i was faking what it said
never gonna
what never give up
where did you sneak it in
where did you sneak it in i didn't see
it i was thinking about it that you're
gonna switch suddenly and turn it into
the song lyrics but you didn't
let down
[Music]
i don't see it i don't see it you may if
you did it then you mix it in really
really
nicely so
it's unnoticeable
man
[Music]
ah
never give up even when fates themselves
seem to conspire against you and not a
single day have i ever entertained the
notion that you had let anyone down
i mean
it's just a tiny bit
it's so small it's fairly noticeable
i don't even take that as being rick
rolled no no no no no no it's a bit of a
stretch
but you tried
thank you so much jenkins monkey
there have been a lot of a lot of tough
times
like in the first couple months
um
where things just didn't go well ever
but somehow
every day streaming so much
these memories are like so far back in
my head
that i barely i barely can even like
remember
how i felt
back then even though it's not that long
ago
but you guys remember that it was tough
and you still supported me for all of
that
also today watching that debut i had to
once again think like damn how do these
new girls also holo ex and so on how do
they manage
to
have such
non-cringy
decent
good debuts
and i have my debut with a shitty
microphone
shitty echo in the background and i
don't know it was it was just not that
good
ah
how
you always wasn't cringing your debbie
wasn't cringing i mean there were better
ones and i remember getting a lot of
[\h__\h] a lot of slack
right in the beginning
um
so
i'm just
everyone's doing such a great job with
their debuts it's like they're they're
like they don't they're not even nervous
or something
[Music]
how do they do it plaque not slack yeah
how do they do it
how do you do it how do they do it
like
i
it's not like i
i was really really really really
nervous even though i have experience
with this kind of stuff
it's not only me being nervous it was
other things too and and some partially
undeserved things as well but yeah
anyway
[Music]
they're nervous you can hear it in their
voices i didn't hear it in zeta's voice
today
um
she didn't i mean i'm sure she was
somewhat nervous
but it didn't come across that way to me
she did a great job she was really cute
really curious how the other girls are
gonna be like
[Music]
also
do
people in indonesia all
know
three to five languages so what the [\h__\h]
is up with that
i know that in certain countries also in
europe as well
a lot of people know
like three four languages it's not that
uncommon
it's not that uncommon but i'm surprised
that every member that joins whole live
indonesia
since at least since second gen
is fluent in at least three languages if
not for
i think in europe i understand it
because there's so many like
countries back to back side to side
uh that all have a different language
but yeah i don't know much about
indonesia it's just to me it's very
fascinating
i need to understand how how do they do
it or do they just have a really good
education system but like them learning
japanese and korean is mostly on them
out of their personal interest
i would say
[Music]
that much not that common and whole life
just whole life indonesia just gets
really
lucky with auditions gets really great
people auditioning really talented
people and picks the right people
maybe it's just the people that make it
into whole live indonesia and the rest
are not really like that i don't know
but
yeah would be nice if it's their
education system and good for them
[Music]
but like anya anya learned it herself
right
i think i know why dana knows japanese
well
ali is
japanese self-taught too i would say
i mean hers is not the best but she's
she has some basics down
[Music]
how she learned it but her japanese is
really good
damn
and you know they say japanese is a
really different different difficult
language
and they all know it
damn respect anyway jackets monkey thank
you for the beautiful rainbow thank you
[Music]
happy to have you aboard and please
continue supporting me
i'll be very very happy to have you
around
[Music]
yeah need to study more korean
okay
[Music]
coco
duolingo
it's it's um
a good way to
study a language on stream but in
general as a tool for studying a
language it's not good
so i don't really want to rely on
duolingo for learning a language
properly
um
yeah i want to take private lessons
but i haven't had the time yet
i'll i'll try
i'll try but you know learning a
language really needs commitment to go
through with it like weekly several
times
in a week
not only like
once or twice in a month it really needs
commitment
[Music]
otherwise you forget it so quickly
that's the problem when you're busy
[Music]
i'll i will i will try yeah if i find
some time
i think in the next couple weeks i
i should have more time
there's not that much going on in the
next couple weeks
i'm on the side working on some things
but they're progressing slowly as
everything is these days
everything is just progressing super
slow
[Music]
um and also i'm just not
as
um
adaptive as i used to be
like when i was younger and learn
japanese a lot of a lot about a lot a
lot of uh me learning the language so
fast is on me being so young or
me
well
i was young back then yeah
now i'm old phoenix now yeah my brain is
not so spongy anymore
it doesn't soak it up that nicely
anymore
it makes a big difference
[Music]
i'll try anyway
at least i i just wanna do some
daily conversation like saying how are
you my name is blah blah blah i am from
blah blah blah my hobbies are blah blah
blah yes no thank you goodbye uh i like
you
i mean some of these things i can
already say but i just want to be able
to have like a simple exchange
that's all i want and i think that's
manageable um
[Music]
where's the library why why are you guys
saying that
i don't want to know where the library
is that will never come in handy
never
[Music]
oh my koreans are coming out of the
shadows
they were hiding and suddenly i said one
thing in korean and they're here ah
people here
[Music]
korean bros
how do i say
are you tired
[Music]
no
really
um
[Music]
one hour one hour
earlier
[Music]
summer time summer time
thank you summertime
okay let me continue read super chats
and mystic has big stun cushion
your legs straight up
yeah wait that's so that works
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
just just like literally a leg
that's a good idea are you about to
commission that
[Music]
thank you for the pinky
hmm
[Music]
thank you for the virtual hugs thank you
thank you
thank you thank you and private
homeowner says in the pinky super chat
sorry inspiration struck in a nap i'm
egg
nutrition and life incubated by phoenix
i hatch life or is this a
poem small and yellow i'm nurtured grow
big i'm employed live
life live life live potential i'm fried
free of mortality and food live again
hashtag guilt
guilt
you only
uh love
to tiara
the chimpkin creed
that sounded like a really cool poem but
why yelt
you only
maybe i maybe it's not a reference to
yolk but yolo you only live twice
i guess so in my case
at kfp my chickens only live twice that
is true i thought it was a
a reference to hashtag yolk okay okay
that's probably it yeah that makes sense
nice poem
i read it uh
in a way that it didn't do it justice
but thank you nonetheless
inspiring
thank you
channel
[Music]
top
and it was a huge honor to represent kfb
at the expo
[Music]
thanks for being you viva la
i'm saying that
speaking japanese out of nowhere while
always speaking english
is so scuffed like if i if i spend let's
say a week in japan i think my japanese
will be back to normal but yeah
i have been
uh
lacking opportunities to speak japanese
getting rusty really getting rusty
i need to do more japan collapse but no
not a whole week
um
koretoni collab is happening soon
finally i think we settled for a date
[Music]
haven't really been
in contact that much with
people
overall
[Music]
but i've been trying i noticed a lack of
collapse next week so i quickly
um
smoothly slid into other people's dms
and i was like hey hey hey hey hey hey
hey hey you you and you and you
let's call our bow
[Music]
uh i think
not next week but the week after
[Music]
yeah it's really difficult to coordinate
everyone's um
dates
it's really difficult we have two two
people who are
especially prone to be busy these days
it's the one where i already have the
thumbnails ready
um
that garlic phone
[Music]
ah i was thinking about that that it
looks like kind of like a penguin design
to me as well but nothing says she's a
penguin
is that just a coincidence that her
outfit ended up looking like a penguin
i feel like i would be more relieved if
she was in the pangolin because we're
already so many in honor
it's already [\h__\h] difficult enough to
coordinate them
her name is kind of like a penguin from
a movie oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] oh kowalski
[Applause]
i heard that somewhere before indeed
maybe it's just a jork
we will have to wait and see um what she
says
in her debut
[Music]
if she's as much as a penguin as crony
is a crowd then we're good
[Music]
all right well we'll see
super running in this soda subaru or
soul
yeah how about we kick out somebody just
kidding i would never do that but i mean
if i'm if i have too many birds in this
group
wouldn't it be logical to kick out the
one person who is not a bird
[Music]
she is
a duck no matter what
yes
yes what
she has reached acceptance
she's too deep in it she can't get out
of it now um
tony nina
[Music]
is a penguin a bird oh
yes penguins are birds although there
are flightless birds lots of people
think penguins are mammals rather than
birds because they can't fly and we see
them swimming on the water or rattling
on land instead
but they are buried apparently
[Music]
they're cute though holy [\h__\h] baby
penguins are the cutest thing ever
oh my god
[Music]
i fly when i want to i believe you i
believe you
[Music]
they lay eggs so not everything that
lays eggs is a bird well that's a weird
argument guys
but they lay eggs well they lay eggs
not everything that lays an egg is a
bird is a snake a bird huh
yeah
i mean i might i may have missed
something there is a turtle a bird is
this a bird
is is this a bird
is this a bird
is this a bird i'm thinking about about
the meme
is this a bird
[Music]
we are bob
is this a pigeon
is this a butterfly
[Music]
i don't lay eggs and i'm still a bird
not in my current form though
phoenix does not lay in my at least in
my world at least in my story phoenix
does not lay egg no no
but still amber yes
you said you laid one no i said i
hatched one
i hatch eggs i do not play them you
should know that very well you've been
here since like the [\h__\h] beginning of
time
and yet you still try to mess up my
stories here
no i no
no
no no no
[Music]
i will burn you alive guys if you don't
shut up
like i burnt that stage
just like that
yeah
[Music]
is
careful now careful now
thank you cocoon for the pinkies uh
[Music]
uh
[\h__\h] google translated japanese again
right you know what if it's
if this is you i will not
this is from google translate now let's
have the google lady read it for us
[Music]
might as well have the google laney or
the google guy
anata
this is how you sound
anatomy
okay i reply in japanese that's what you
get for writing in japanese
tomita
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
and violet apple card and duncan
you think this is better
[Music]
violent evil garden
you little [\h__\h]
i will i refuse to give you your number
i refuse
i complained previously that you're
making that you're you're uh having a
profile picture from someone else even
though you claim that i am your oshi
and now you claim that it's me but
that's not me i don't know who that is
i don't know what that is
not applicable duncan asami have knight
dunkish in her line danger and have a
line dangerous
petsy duncan
thank you oh my god oh my god one two oh
my god ten
ten orange super chats wait how much is
that twenty
fourteen
60 80 hundred
is it 200 wait yeah wait wait thank you
i think
20 times 10
20 times 10.
[Laughter]
[Music]
stop judging me so much
out in stock
[Music]
autistic
out it's dark
[Music]
golden stock
audi stock
[Music]
boating stock
body stock
oating stock
[Music]
onto stock
autistic
[Music]
out is dark
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
i know it's a bit late but for today
today today i have prepared to find this
orange carpet for your attention ah
that's what that is
i was so happy to see you reaching your
dreams finally
but i'm too big
[Music]
and
this was one of the big moments that
everyone was waiting for really proud to
see you performing on stage with your
senpais and gem mates yeah
not quite together but they were
somewhere there
the performance was absolutely stunning
it was beyond my imagination and it was
such a breathtaking moment thank you
you absolutely blasted that stage with
your singing choreography and your
lovely expression was really something
that cheering and calls hyped the stage
so much more as well
thank you
yeah it was really really [\h__\h] hard
everyone like jumping up and down and up
and down it was beautiful
also the 3d model oh my god it came out
so good you think so i'm glad you think
so
[Music]
and this whole concert made me emotional
and left unforgettable memories
especially the kick at the kick was
first of was a force to be reckoned with
i can't wait for the full fest next time
and hope to be there to cheer you on
from the sides finally let's go orange
boys pop that uos as if there is no
tomorrow well i hope it would be loud if
it's not allowed then
don't do it but
proudly shake that normal pen light
yeah
thank you so much for amazing
performance and and i can't wait to see
more live 3d performance in the future
and there's some korean
jindo
hangul
and
thank you so
much happy to see you again you've also
been here for a long long long time i
think for the long time kfps it's
something especially
precious that moment of seeing me on
stage
[Music]
let's hope that there will be more
moments like that to celebrate together
and to make memories of
thank you jean love for always being
here thank you
uh-huh
then after that good side because i
wasted anyone using this real adventure
i got them phoenix thumbs up
does it look like that too
in what ff14
there's apparently a skill called
phoenix dance does it look like my
phoenix dance
[Music]
i'm curious
i love my german kfb i just feel
uncomfortable reading german
out of nowhere
may i explain
sure
please do
it doesn't without the kickity kick
uh-huh
it's nowhere near as majestic
cannot get to my level
get on my level ff14
get on my level
where is the explanation
i didn't say i love you what did i say i
guess i did say it
okay i love you too
he took that very very um personally
[Music]
he ran
he's gone goku
[Music]
maybe he'll show up again
a good night good night
mr pier
good night
the game mccree donkey and jeff started
thank you for the pinkie
hi tanja i'm gonna tweet to ajf korea
every day oh yeah i saw you already at
day three
and you saw them and made me so happy
let's see where this goes today was day
three love you and let's have lots of
fun today thank you for trying i i don't
know if maybe it's already too late for
this year that could be i don't know
when the convention happens this year
um but yeah even if it doesn't work this
year let's try again next year or try
for other conventions that's okay too
but agf would be really cute and really
cool to be part of
[Music]
and honestly it's just an excuse for me
to travel to korea
[Music]
i wanna go to korea
sport yeah gotta um connect
things
yeah smart bird
thank you pong fighting
doctor professor danke sun
kfp
[Music]
then
autumn
it's a question in the name
thank you for the red super chat
i wanted to see the stream i listen to
music when i go to work and get off work
you mean my music
i like that there are a lot of fun clips
too these days i'm happy to watch clips
after work there's still korean clips of
me i have like barely seen any
of them recently popping up in my feed
i saw one yesterday
but that was the first one that i saw in
my
recommendations in like
weeks
[Music]
which is a bit unfortunate i've seen a
lot really
really i've barely been getting anything
in my recommendations before it was like
everything was filled up with it
korean clips
well i hope they didn't forget about me
yet
i hope i hope they're still there
[Music]
yeah yeah
um
i'm running for you a lot i'll do my
best to see you more often watch only
cronie every day ah
you you messed up my hashtag
it changed woke
from kiana to crony my heart is
shattered into a million pieces
[Music]
oh it's dark
is
[Music]
now
could
[Music]
yeah
okay
[Laughter]
okay okay the song is over so i'm happy
again
thank you mama
put up a little show for my korean bros
wrestle free thank you for the pinky
where's my bgm here
[Music]
yeah yeah potential congrats on your
performance last week i have a problem
in the kfc kitchen to report though
we have a giant orange rubber band
holding the ice cream machine together
and ever since last week it's all burned
do you know what happened
no
wait should i know is this a reference
to something a giant orange rubber band
holding the ice cream machine together
is this a reference to something
[Music]
i don't know what happened wait
is it
wait giant orange rubbermaid is it my
skirt
my skirt wait this is are you talking
about my skin
what what
what why
what what what
why
why why
why it's not a rubber band give me my
skirt bag
my skirt bag what the [\h__\h] i'll give you
something in exchange i'll send you um
kirby and then kirby you know have you
seen how kirby like
um can attach itself onto like a [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] car
yeah you can just put kirby on top of
the ice cream machine and it will hold
everything together
might as well be a reference
but it's not
thank god i have more than one uniform
but what the [\h__\h] how dare you just use
that like that
disrespect
man
oh at least kirby already looks like
bubble gum ice cream
yeah
did they also make a mannequin with you
is that is that where you got my skirt
from
after the cleanup from the convention is
that where my uniform went to from that
mannequin
that they had at the convention at the
whole live expo
they had mannequins of all of us
it was really cool to see like um the
council outfits put into actual clothes
as well because
i can imagine those are kind of
difficult to recreate but they're um
looking at them they don't really look
that handmade they look like most of it
was printed on the fabric so that must
have cost some money
rather than just uh
i mean that could still be handmade but
like most of the patterns were just
printed on so it looks very much like uh
like a company was in charge of making
them
they could just like
treat those as official cosplays and
sell them
uh in a store
yeah
whole life sells their own cosplay
clothes wouldn't that be
cool i think a lot of cosplayers would
be very very very very grateful
[Music]
that would be cool
like i have a whole production
whole live production
cosplay
[Music]
instead of having other companies
sell um their unofficial cosplays at
least these ones would be officially
approved so you can be sure that all the
details are accurate
[Music]
thank you for the pinky i'm really slow
today plumptail giving me various
feelings by the way
what kind of feelings by the way
attention yesterday was my first day
dawning on the uniform what does that
mean and start work in kfb i didn't get
to send you the sign on bonus because
super chats were not open can i have an
employee number sure
let me check uh your number is uh
uh
five zero
[Music]
nine
congratulations okay mike you got your
uniform huh is it does it fit well
i think you look fabulous in it
thank you for proudly wearing my uniform
yeah
i can't fit uniform
thank you
yeah
yeah write it down so you don't forget
it again you silly little chicken
also thank you for the pinkie
gracie
[Music]
wait why are you talking about abe
weissman
from oh oh i guess i mentioned marvelous
mrs maisel in the beginning a little bit
oh did you watch it too
you're probably gone by now
beginning bear are you still here
i'm happy to see other people who
watched marvelous mrs maisel but it was
so short beguiling
beguiling
[Music]
probably gone man i wanted to fangirl
about the show
it's gonna take like a whole [\h__\h]
year again until it continues i hate
waiting for shows like that for new
seasons is
the worst thing
[Music]
i just want to watch shows that are
already like done
where i can like
binge watch
through all of it quickly
i wish i wish every show was like that
why does it take a whole year man
no
this is so
such a long time
and then only eight episodes they could
have done more than just what was it
eight episodes i feel like it was eight
episodes or so for the newest season
they actually had less episodes than in
the previous season
it was like over so fast
it didn't last long at all
it takes so long to make a show
i get it because like their quality is
really good the quality of the show is
really really good
and they have to film with things like
the sea thing
in mind so that's also tough i suppose
but
you know still
i cry
no i don't think budget is a problem for
them
it's just a sea thing probably an excuse
for it but
uh
[Music]
when i was younger in the pre-streaming
area had to wait an entire way to watch
the next episode yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah that was also [\h__\h] that was also
really [\h__\h]
i would most of the time forget so most
of the shows when i was younger i just
watched like
randomly in random order
and missed a lot
back in the day
and then years later i i would watch a
show like that for the first time ever
in the proper order from beginning to
the end and it felt so good it was so
satisfying ah
yeah
somehow we survived i don't know how we
did that
um
i didn't even have a vhs to record i
didn't have that
[Music]
i didn't really watch dvds when i was
younger no i just watched normal tv
back in my day
i need to read super chat i'm so slow
today what the [\h__\h] why am i so slow
i'm taking so much time
unknown thank you for wanting free
pinkies
so pink
i was wrong about you being the son of
her life because you shine even brighter
than all the stars in the universe
combined
i know get out of here
words can't describe how proud i am and
how incredible you are you really
deserve all the praises and much more
you cute silly chicken
that was probably the hardest i've ever
cried you seriously did so amazing how
hard are you gonna cry when i have a
full concert and not just one song
and then have some up and downs of some
exciting songs and some sad songs you're
gonna cry when i do a sad song you're
gonna fall apart unknown
you need to become mentally stronger
until then
you need to become stronger
train for it now by re-watching that
concert a million times
you're so sweet
everything about your performance was
absolutely divine exquisite uh it's
definitely the best part of the whole
concert i'm extremely proud of you my oc
i mean
you're the cutest most amazing most
incredible most wonderful person ever
existed you are just perfect there
really is no one else like you chiara
your river place is loose
you say this a lot but i seriously mean
it you're the absolute spout
i know you're so sweet
like whatever you say i never get like
annoyed or sick like of what you say
like i mean it's very very cheesy what
you say
but i only feel
love
in the sweetest
kindest way ever
[Music]
love having you around thank you so much
lord of the top looking for the top
language
oh congrats oh nice
choco
no mono come sign me down for the red
super chat
hello it's really nice to see you at
this time
midnight in korea
you're welcome yeah we started um
at a good time today by now i'm
surprised you guys are still awake but
thank you for staying
thank you for watching my streams
oh you followed up with a pinky actually
that was beautiful i don't remember what
was beautiful but thank you
and i forgot what was it i don't have my
memo anymore but it was something like
she chung
you
[Music]
ah come sunny dogs
i don't remember the full frames anymore
[Music]
thank you
for
watching
[Music]
i guess something like that
thank you thank you thank you
a patsy duncan
[Music]
thank you
another one
thank you for making this week one one
of the best weeks that i'll never ever
forget i'm so glad to be your fan you
will always be my wanna know me aussie i
love you more than anything ever love
you forever
i can't love you
what do i do with you huh
you're sweetie
[Music]
love forever
thank you for being part of kfb
needs more people like you
[Music]
although everyone everyone is so sweet
everyone is so sweet
[Music]
so cute
you guys are so charming
how are you guys not all married huh
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] did i open a wound did i pour
salt over a wound i hope not ah you're
just waiting for me right
waiting for me
to marry my cats first
remaining less
okay i guess eldon ring
kind of helps us accept that
proudly maidenless hell yeah
are you guys
you're gonna be just fine
with such
a pure
sweet loving heart that you guys have
you beautiful chickens
y'all are gonna be fine
[Music]
say yeah um
that's not going to happen
i'm telling you now that's not going to
happen i'm sorry
crashing your dreams but i think so you
say sampai would crush it
herself anyway
a dream
no
[Music]
no something like that shouldn't um and
i know that you just
i know i think you don't take it that
seriously anyway but i think there are
some people who take this kind of stuff
um so serious that it holds them back
from
actually living their life
and um
creating real
relationships or neglecting real
relationships so it's not not like
thinking about them at all anymore
um like like when it gets to a really
really really really really really bad
level
of being
intoxicated or i don't know what i
should call it
so
um i'm not sure if there's
anyone
here who feels like that could be them
i would like to
assume that
at least 99 of you guys are not that
way
[Laughter]
well you still love me very much which
is understandable because i love you too
but i want you guys to become happy in
the future
everyone deserves happiness in life
and whatever
brings you happiness doesn't need to be
love i mean some people maybe don't need
that in their life
maybe some people need other things but
i just don't want um people to be held
back by something like that
uh and and like missing out on things in
real life
and forgetting how how it feels to have
like
these kind of
things happen to them and real life in
the first place because after after all
of that
see [\h__\h]
i think it's understandable that a lot
of us are like so locked up at home
um
and just
haven't had much interactions and all
that for like possibly two years at this
point
and
maybe you are at a point where you feel
like ah i've made it for two years you
know what i'll never go outside anymore
the the virtual life is the better life
i
i hope i hope that if someone feels like
that
you can um get out of break out of your
shell again at some point
[Music]
and enjoy what life is really about
um
as much as i appreciate you guys being
in here always at any time
there's so many beautiful places outside
to visit so many fun things to do
some in some places
and friendships
friendship is what life is truly about
yeah
[Music]
so don't forget about that guys
i don't like going outside much either
so i have to first myself too
um but also like in in austria like i
don't really see any fun activities for
myself outside like in if i were in
japan i would go outside more i would go
to karaoke and meet up with people and
all that i don't really see that that
much in austria either so i have to
force myself to go on vacation or
something somewhere else
because that's what i enjoy
going to the beach or something
that's fun
i have to force myself to i don't want
to go outside either i'm i'm quite uh
yeah the hikikomori myself for various
reasons but
um
we gotta enjoy nature and life more all
of us all of us
right now i'm like so focused on life
on on work
um
but i think
i think eventually i'll have more time
and and
[Music]
be able to focus more
on other aspects of life
yeah but right now i really need to
focus on this because also i'm
enjoying it too
but don't forget about the real world
both you guys and me
[Music]
stream outside the internet is [\h__\h]
outside
and no privacy and acoustics are [\h__\h]
too
so no thank you
going outside requires money no it
doesn't
just going outside doesn't no no no you
can you can see so many beautiful places
for free outside you can climb climb
every mountain as they say inside of
music
or go to a nice lake or a nice beautiful
park or i don't know whatever
it's definitely beautiful places outside
that you can reach
without spending money
although yes some things maybe need some
money but still
[Music]
getting there requires money not
necessarily unless you live in the
middle of a [\h__\h] desert
[Music]
if you do then okay
i'll give you that
[Music]
are you telling us to touch grass
not necessarily immediately but just
don't lose sight of it that's what i'm
saying don't lose sight of it
[Music]
hmm
yeah
[Music]
joke's on you my cat's name is grass
that's wonderful go touch your cat go go
go do it
do it touch your cat i support that
[Music]
i support that
the other day or yesterday probably
yesterday i saw a fan art of that cute
new pokemon cat red the green grass cat
and i thought it was a fan art of
smoothie
so confusing man
i really thought it was a fan art of
smoothie
why why why why why more fan out of this
movie please more fan out of my cats
please
i require it
chaplain lee duncan the gamer creed
thank you and sugar hasaga thank you for
the pinky congratulations once again for
your 3dw from holofest i legit was
crying and was happy to dance with your
performance but your kick made me laugh
so thanks for that it made you laugh
it should have been an awe you should
have been speechless
continue with the hard work tension viva
and kfp
first time able to see live stream what
and able to super chat this week ah this
week okay this sounded weird to me
sorry for any delay to send a super chat
to you no problem
thank you for watching the concert
and enjoying it so much
thank you yeah you should fear the kick
at a kick that's right that's right
thank you glad you enjoyed it thank you
for the support
okay of penguin thank you for the red
super chat
okay shut up now
thank you congratulations on a
successful concert about the concert i
have a small question accounting too
coming to lammy and pota and their
clothes were stripped
and was on display by staff on that day
did gemma do the same thing to you when
you naked until the show begins
now
as you know if you look on the right
side of my office
as a potential i need more than one of
my uniform man
i work i work seven days a week yeah
if i were to always use one uniform
it would be really stinky i have uh yes
attention would have multiple uniforms
that is true
they had one on that mannequin
but
i have more than one i have a couple
yeah
so i'm not enough i don't know about the
others but that doesn't happen to me
thank you for the red super chat though
mwah
thank
i'm sorry i got a translator i'm kfp
working in korea thank you
i was confirmed with
19 today oh [\h__\h] it's really hard but
i'm holding up while watching the
manager's
stream
[Music]
and
kiera
oh i hope you get better soon i hope
it's not too strong
uh
get well soon
[Music]
okay
take it easy and fighting
thank you blue chian thank you for the
pinkie thank you i'm so proud of you the
3d life was so amazing and wonderful and
impressive i'm dead thank you forever
i'm surprised people are still still
sending reactions
today it's been almost a week thank you
thank you guys it never ends it's never
stopping
thank you tian
thank you for your love and support
final flights of fancy dancin
a korean name
[Music]
the money
thank you for the red super chat
congrats on fulfilling your wishlist
tanjo i'm so happy for you today is my
birthday oh and i'm almost a kfb bucket
you bring me so much happiness and
energy during this year thank you for
being part of my life i'll always
support you no matter what thank you
happy birthday
what
happy birthday to you
happy birthday dear momma
with every clap there is more cat hairs
flying around it's funny
thank you please make it into
a great year okay i wish you all the
best take care of yourself
your precious chicken
thank you all my love to you
finally i reached you thank you for the
red super chat hey
missed the previous super windows so
here we go i'm just so proud of you
seeing the crowd go wild to your amazing
performance was a very emotional moment
for me i expected good stuff but you
still impressed me feels good that my
osha is an absolute star
thank you you're too sweet
thank you
i'm glad i could leave an impression
like that thank you thank you thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
[Music]
soon
big kiss for you
for the red super chat thank you for
being so generous and supporting kfb as
always it was such a great moment
it was it was that's why it's now on my
menu ideas how about we put a concert on
the menu ha ha
ha ha
dan barnacle
[Music]
foreign
and gd i don't think that matters at all
you just gotta have a talent for it
and show off your skills
where did i just stop reading
i need to refresh
[Music]
there we go english you can do it after
all
you're extremely cute i really really
really really really love you boss
you're an incredible content creator so
good thank you this is much better
your performance at third fest truly
impressed me your choreography energy
and singing absolutely entranced the
audience and viewers like me at home you
saw my heart kiana when you decide to do
a concert i'll try everything to be
there you rock thank you
thank you
i
i i really hope i can deliver yeah
planning a concert is a
big big big thing
[Music]
i've already heard some things
from colleagues
is it's quite quite a quest to take on
but i'll do my best but first we need
some more songs yeah yeah yeah i need
more songs
you want a solo concert like aqua yeah
that would be lovely hmm
i want a cute idol outfit too
yeah
chris cheese man duncan ruffian
[Music]
for being the phantom's debbie but only
started chatting here a while ago oh
what what got you out of your
eggshells huh
been a really fun time wanted to say
thanks for all the streams keep up the
great work thank you i'll do my best and
you're very welcome here please continue
being an active member of my community
we're happy to have more the more the
mariah
[Music]
dan kitchen egg nice to see you here
and thank you also for staying for so
long since the beginning
a beautiful round shiny egg
so beautiful takayama
[Music]
yeah
penguins don't count they can't even fly
wait never can chickens yeah we already
had that discussion
i think i think if she says she's a
penguin then we have to uh put her into
horitory
otherwise it would just be it would just
be like a like one of those popular
cliques clicks that you can't get into
we would be like the mean girls yeah
um i can't be like that
although i don't want the group to
become bigger to be honest as i said
it's really hard to organize [\h__\h] man
and then when you do something with some
of them people will always be like but
what's with this girl and this girl why
did you left leave them out
and i'm afraid of that
yeah and now we are five
five
[Music]
which is a good number honestly four
would have been the best because a lot
of games are four people maximum
five is still okay manageable
but if it's six then they will like for
almost every game there will always be
people left out but eventually if we can
get more and more and more then we'll
reach a number where we can play amalgas
with holoburps only
[Music]
so worst case we'll work towards that
oh hold a toy concert
eventually
[Music]
we could play with six but that's just
not really
gonna be fun is it there's so little
people's brother with like i don't know
10 people nine people
[Music]
yeah
then
thank you for the pinky hey boss i'm
taking some unpaid time off i'm going to
see some mountains for a week perfect
literally what we just talked about that
you guys should be doing i hope the
mountain view will be as amazing as you
girls on the hula fest stage love you
lots hench i'm intention
yeah but that's wonderful i'm happy to
hear that just uh
be careful okay don't slip on the
mountain that wouldn't be good
i hope you have some good mountain shoes
touch mountain not grass in that case
but yeah that sounds amazing i don't
want to climb a mountain that's that's a
little bit too far
uh that's taking touch grass a little
bit too far
but definitely we'll get a nice nice
view from that and a nice refreshment
i'm sure of it
[Music]
don't sleep or don't slip don't slip
sleep is okay
sleep is okay slip is no okay
okay of penguin
[Music]
foreign
attention i love you for the performance
and you're kicking the kick and i have a
gift for your chicken nuggets
wait is the gift chicken nuggets
is it your own chicken nuggets
thank you i love chicken nuggets
i wouldn't mind eating some chicken
nuggets now
but today i'm gonna eat
more of my japanese curry for dinner i'm
looking forward to it already i'm kind
of getting hungry
[Music]
also thank you for a red super chat
shortly after your debut i watched you
talk about how in the past despite your
hard work it wasn't paying off but in
the end you succeeded at that time i
thought it's time to stop dreaming
uh your words made me believe again
thanks for sharing your flame with me
seeing you on stage made me happy and
proud
ah
it's it's
it's always great to hear when like
other people are feeling similarly and
feel like they can relate to my story
and
that i made them feel hopeful again
that's wonderful
i'm glad we can have that kind of
experience and and yeah i want you guys
to be able to relate to me that's why i
also
try to share so many personal things
even if sometimes it's maybe oversharing
but i mean we're spending almost every
day together
how can i not overshare i'm actually
really like fascinated by how other
girls are still like
like so secretive
i don't know how they do it i just can't
hold back it's just it's just all
coming out of me automatically
but yeah thank you dental
you
should never stop dreaming
if you have something you want to
grasp a dream you want to make come true
i'm sure you can do it
judy duncan
[Music]
sweetie
i don't wanna i have this problem you
know i don't wanna maybe if the new
season comes out
and now it's been so long i don't even
think about it anymore
[Music]
if you can tell me with all confidence
that
the last episode of season four
handmaid's tale
is a good episode as in it's a positive
episode
[Music]
then you get me interested i just don't
wanna
no that whole show is just so painful
and i don't wanna go back just for one
painful episode
[Music]
but i think that's
partially
the reason for me
not finishing
a certain game
i kind of wanted to finally finish it
yesterday but then i was recording and
stuff
um
um but yeah i also just don't wanna
have it end like i have this with tv
shows and smooth games i just i just i
don't want it to end but not playing it
it's not really a solution either
it's
but i don't want to end cause then
i don't like replaying games and then
yeah that means that it's over then you
know
[Music]
i know i need to finish it
okay but it is on my list of best games
in the 2020s i will
i make a promise now
i make a promise
i will finish it
by
the end of april
[Laughter]
yes
[Music]
i promise
um
[Music]
have a good space and time to enjoy i
get that too yeah yeah yeah yeah i get
that too
[Music]
i'm not gonna get called out in my no
no no no no
no that's enough time i'll finish it
i just
really didn't want it to end
cuz like the next the next big tales off
game
is gonna take a while until it comes out
and i always need something there you
know i need i need to have in my mind i
need to have the option
available
to play
a tails off game otherwise i live in
suffering pain
[Music]
ah i can't it's just painful to have it
in the back of my mind that there is no
tails off game for me to play i mean
there are some oldies
that i could play but
i don't know the new ones are
prettier
and more accessible
[Music]
mostly also more accessible most of the
ones like that are on playstation and
gamecube and
playstation 2 playstation free
um
yeah and so on most of them i've played
it's just still pretty old ones that i i
would need to buy some console for
anyway
[Music]
yeah tails of graces was great
right i do i do have the option to play
uh
the
sequel
of symphonia
[Music]
didn't didn't i even own a copy but
what console was that for
[Music]
i'm not sure anymore was it ps3
ps2 ps3
okay
we
do i have a copy for it on on the
way and i need to buy a wii first
i was planning to
like maybe this is also another problem
as a streamer as a game streamer you
want to keep certain games
for streaming it like you start feeling
like not streaming is a waste
and i'm just constantly waiting for
permissions on certain games
yeah
there is a ps3 version maybe i have the
p3 version i'm not sure
but yeah um
yeah that that is uh i heard other
streamers talking about that too so it's
definitely a thing it's not just me
but
yeah when you play so many games
on stream
then
yeah playing outside of the stream feels
like a waste
partially
like oh i could play this on stream
and it would be more interesting because
people would like enjoy seeing it
yeah i should play it on stream i should
keep this to play it on stream
yeah i want to share my reaction i want
to share my passion and excitement for
this game and all that
it's like giving up content yeah like
especially let's say i play a game off
stream and it was so amazing that it was
life changing then i'm gonna regret that
i played it on my own and not on stream
to capture all those moments
yeah
so
i don't play games off stream
yeah
it's a very common thing
and not only that but also another thing
is just like when your job is playing
games then your desire to play games off
stream is
i think for a lot of people at least for
me not for everyone but for a lot of
people very small
and that is
probably also a reason why i haven't
been going back to tales of the rice
that and me not wanting to end it
yeah
it's like if your job like you guys your
day-to-day jobs
you wouldn't wanna
normally i don't believe you if you say
yes i do
normally you wouldn't want to do the
thing you do as your day-to-day job all
the time at home as well
like i don't know repairing a car or or
being a plumber you want to do that all
the time in your free time do you do you
even if you were so passionate about it
before getting the job or at the
beginning of your job it's still like
once it's your job
it's
just
yeah you want to do something else after
that
i think that is i think that makes
sense yeah
oh yeah
i think
for
yeah yeah i've heard things about like i
mean the cooking is just a part of
everyday life but if if being a chef is
your job
then
yeah you you may not make the biggest
masterpieces
at home you may just cook up [\h__\h]
spaghetti bolognese and call it a day
if anything
or just throw in the pizza into the oven
or order pizza
or have your partner your life partner
cook something up
because you cooked all [\h__\h] day i
mean being a
cook in a restaurant is [\h__\h]
stressful
really really stressful i mean maybe not
if you have a restaurant where nobody
where there are no customers but i know
i've worked with um
with
kitchen people
cooks chefs all that before
and i know they will always really
really stressed out even though
in our case we weren't even that busy
[Music]
i think we understand each other
did you cry in the fridge
um
you mean in the refrigerator room
uh i
i like to forget traumatic moments but
there may have been a time where i have
uh
hidden in one of those refrigerator
rooms for
a moment to gather my senses maybe
i i can say that possibly
during my time
working in that jump
[Music]
possibly i like to really forget the
traumatic uh
moments so
um
or somewhere just somewhere somewhere
hiding somewhere
oh wait i remember working in um
i remember working in a kitchen for a
while
of a restaurant it was part of my
training
and
there were some little
teenagers who were younger than me
but
were doing
um
a different kind of training they were
training to be um
chefs i was training to be something
else but my kitchen training was part of
it and anyway it was like um this
this
one got i may have told you about it
before
i feel like i almost feel like i did but
there was this one teenager who was
really [\h__\h] spoiled
from what i've heard
and he was like
uh
like kind of he was big like
intimidatingly big
and thought he was really
cool and
yo yeah
[Music]
and he was like during my time in the
kitchen i remember being like bullied a
little bit um
i think i remember food being thrown
around
i [\h__\h] hated him so much
i [\h__\h] hated him
i was so happy when i was done with that
this is so long ago that i
barely remember it but i remember
complaining to hr and all that and hr
uh was like
that [\h__\h] [\h__\h] we always have
problems with him never comes to work
anyway i was happy every time he would
just not come to work and play sick
[\h__\h]
being mean to
calling girls
and and and not taking your job
seriously i hate that
[Music]
now my hr department was pretty nice but
um
yeah
most of the time i didn't have to work
with him anyway because he usually did a
different shift than i did
but even even just seeing him the moment
sometimes our shifts would overlap a
little bit and the moment he would walk
in there into that kitchen feeling like
something better than me
feeling like he's cool or something
and and and i don't know
being rude to me
that moment already soured my day ruined
my day
[Music]
i've read did he have the thoughts and
not the hearts oh my god he did he did
uh
definitely um
uh brag about having a lot of girls but
i don't believe a word of that
but he comes from a rich family
apparently so he was really spoiled
talking about
having a cool car or something i think
but
yeah
yeah a tool
it's actually mainly probably yes
[Music]
but
i've in my time training for that job
i've met a lot of those solgaki
kitchen
trainees chef cook trainees a lot of
them and they're all [\h__\h] like him
all of them
[Music]
i went to a school where a whole class
was filled with what 15 16 year old boys
who who want to become
a chef
because that's all they could think of
and they were all [\h__\h]
and they constantly would get in trouble
for
um
being under some kind of influence in
class
[Music]
yeah
constantly and being [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
only causing trouble not coming to
school
yeah
it was like like
my class
was like
our our category
was like the
like the normal people
where the teachers would be glad that
they were
with us and then the where's there was a
class of of waiters like they would be
taught how to become a waiter
and then those were those were like in
between but the worst ones
were the [\h__\h] kids that wanted to
become
kitchen chefs
those were the worst
people ever and i i've never wanted to
see them like thankfully most of the
time i didn't have to deal with them
never except like in the breaks that's
why i always stayed in the classroom uh
during the breaks
now
i'll always always keep as much distance
as possible from them
[Music]
i respect all the chefs out there who do
it as their job but those teenager
trainees
they have no respect for anyone no
respect for life no respect for teachers
or people anyone
they don't even have respect for their
own job because they don't take it
seriously
but what do i expect from [\h__\h]
teenagers this is like we have this
system in austria and germany where
instead of going to high school
uh you go to uh
you you choose a job that you want to
learn you go to the job um 10 months a
year and then two months a year you go
to a school
that teaches you even more about that
job in detail yeah it's called lehrer
and the school is called
yeah it's apprenticeship and the roof
that kind of school is very well known
for
having a lot of [\h__\h]
yeah
yeah i did it a little bit later than
the others so i was kind of um
older than the others
mentally more advanced
so
i felt
it's it's generally a good idea because
[Music]
it's not always the case but often
the kids who go for that
choose that direction because they can't
make it into high school or they just
don't wanna
go to school anymore
yeah
um not always though
or if you just need some money
then you would start with doing that
or or yeah if you just don't aspire to
become anything super big in the future
it does count
as
like a kind of a
[Music]
what's the word
it does count as a
it's make it's it's a
[Music]
what's a word
in a replacement or something somewhat
um
on the same level as a
as a high school
diploma but it's just more specific than
a high school diploma so
um
you should really
only do it when you plan on staying in
that kind of um
business job equivalent yeah that's what
i was trying to say it's kind of like an
equivalent
because you do it for a couple years you
do it usually three years or sometimes
four years
and then at the very end you have like a
like a big big big test that you have to
go through and then you kind of get a
diploma but like kind of for that job
only
and it will help you to get into a job
like that that's similar to that um but
for other things you might have a few
problems
but you can then actually what you can
do you can do additional ones you can
do
one of those trainings for a different
job a different category and then have
more options if you want to or after
getting a diploma for that you can also
still choose to go to the university
afterwards if you want to
[Music]
yeah
so
it's like
it's
[Music]
it's kind of an equivalent but not quite
like people still see it
a little bit like
below
a high school diploma
here
but it's not really frowned upon or
anything like it's normal you can easily
get a job if you get that you can easily
get a job of that
so it's really just you're kind of
limiting yourself to one
um
one category one
uh
business one thing i can't find the word
anymore
that's that's a bit of a problem but
yeah
[Music]
it's a specialization yeah
so if you do one for becoming a chef
then in the future we you will have no
problems if you want to become or if you
want to stay
in that profession career yes industry
that's the word i was looking for my
throat is dying
i think the system is good though i even
had like in my in none of my class in
the other classes there were some older
people like one person was like in their
40s
one person was in their 50s
it's very very
um
open
system
helpful if you want to change
your direction
[Music]
and for me when i did that in in my case
it was
pretty much
like i chose it because i needed the
money
i did it after
coming back from japan
and um
living with my
parents with my mom again was not an
option
i had to live on my own and i had to pay
my rent on my own um so i had to make
money and the money that you get from
that is [\h__\h] by the way
especially in the first year
but yeah for me it wasn't really an
option to go back to normal school i
needed the money so yeah yeah
that's kind of why i did it and
it's not i don't i don't think it was a
bad choice because um at least the the
particular
genre
industry that i chose
is um
very very big like i can i can choose so
many different jobs i feel like if you
do this for becoming a chef then you're
more limited than with what i did
um
i don't want to talk too much in detail
about it but
yeah
basically i did something
that's really really really
helpful if you want to work in tourism
and yeah for tourism there's like so
many jobs you can work in a
in a travel agency you can work in a
hotel or in a flat
[Music]
in an airplane thingy
or or you can work in a restaurant too
you can work overseas uh you can work on
a on a
on a cruise ship some people go on a
cruise ship working there yeah it's
really easy to get a job anywhere in
tourism there's like really so many
choices hmm
yeah that's why i learned some italian
there and it's only
for tourism
yeah
yeah yeah
[Music]
i enjoyed
um
working in tourism
i did i did although the most annoying
thing was
stupid-ass karen's
yeah
i'm glad i don't have to deal with that
kind of [\h__\h] now
i probably won't go back to it anymore
in the future
um
[Music]
well i thought i thought about it and i
think
i'll probably just um become
a landlord
i think it's
a
smart thing to do
i'll just
become someone's landlord rent a
apartment
out
it's pretty easy
yeah if you if i i would say that's like
the most chill way
to continuously kind of uh
what was weird
they're the opposite of active
non-actively make money
[Music]
you're evil then no i'll be night no to
be honest i don't want i don't even
passive yes i don't even want to be um
the landlord
i don't want to i'll have a company
do that stuff for me i'll just be the
owner basically
yeah
yeah and then and then
with that i will secure my main income
in the future but on the side i can
still do some small things for example
if i want to get back into art
i thought that in the future i'll
probably still not ever be on the level
uh where i can really live off of art
but i could still like do some little
work
here and there if i am lucky enough to
get some work inter like with art in
that industry
um
but that's okay because i'll secure
myself with something else
[Music]
and i can still be happy by doing um
something that i always wanted to do
when i was younger doing art but i don't
have to completely rely on it
yeah
that's
[Music]
yeah kind of
kind of my plan
i got more time then i want to focus on
that and it doesn't need to be super
successful because i'll have something
else to back me up
[Music]
yeah
yeah i'll be drawing
uh in in my house by a lake maybe
maybe
chill with my cats and draw and draw and
draw and draw
and maybe sometimes sometimes someone
wants to buy my art maybe maybe
maybe
sorry that was a lot of real talk
i hope that wasn't too real but but at
least you can be relieved that
i i i have a plan for the future
[Music]
i'm i'm okay yeah i have a foundation
and and i'll i'll be secure yeah
if if need be
if it's really necessary one day i mean
i just get a normal job as well
um but i think the way i i have it
planned out i think it works yeah
i can yeah i have a plan b in case i
really need to work i can just go back
to tourism
[Music]
could work as a translator no i don't
wanna
maybe like
small
translation commissions i've done that
before
yeah maybe small ones but not as a main
job i would need a proper um
training and um
certificates and all that kind of [\h__\h]
for
being a professional translator that
stuff by the way i have a friend who's
like who does that um professionally and
first of all
it's stressful second of all it doesn't
even pay that well in third of all most
of them do it um
freelancingly
and it's kind of tough i think to get
proper jobs all the time lined up as a
freelance translator
um
yeah and i really have
a lack of time
yeah
so
no i don't really see that as an option
no anyway let's finish up these super
chats okay
mitchell doesn't shut up why did we even
we went to this tangent from the
question whether or not i would watch
the last episode of handmaid's tale
[Music]
oh my god
wow
it has a super tangent
there's absolutely nothing to do with it
anymore
nothing
a tangent of a tangent of a tangent of a
tangent of a tangent of a tangent of a
tangent of a tangent
[Music]
wow
whoa
[Music]
change inception
it went places
yeah um arch ellen or arc ellen thank
you for the rest of the chat i'm so
proud of my aussie the performance was
so good you were burning like the sun on
the stage
nearly too bright to watch i am looking
forward to hear 3dw and i hope that
there are many pretty streams to follow
because my osha is just too cute please
play actually a selfie too
i kind of want to
it's been looking really pretty
the visuals are just so nice um
not on stream though i don't think it's
gonna be ever a stream game
um
i think
maybe maybe
i'll give it another chance if another
completely new atelier releases maybe
next year or whatever
but not planning to
stream actually a selfie too but but but
but
i'm not giving up on atelier completely
as a streaming game because i really um
remember the times fondly
of when we
played raza
on my channel
[Music]
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah uh
sophie too yeah true we didn't play
sophie one on my channel so that would
also be a little bit of a problem
um
yeah nostalgic very nostalgic
thank you arch ellen
mistress duncan tonali no nico
motion thank you wiki tunes duncan
pudding challenge
thank you
see this is where this is where i would
have been done reading super chats but
your
your theories kiara had to
take a lot of time with it so i have to
refresh again and add some extra ones
onto it
it's my own fault honestly i could have
been done oh but it's not so many
looking for the top duncan
i was thinking about that before if i
could um because alisa john is so cute
if we could somehow
somehow get her
to work for us in some way or another
because i really really really love her
beautiful
kiwawa
cosplays hers are like the best quality
i've seen out there and she makes them
herself with such hard work yeah
and so quickly and so much details
genie duncan have a line dungeon
[Music]
ah have a line
eight
one
seven
that's your employee number
you're welcome i'm on ears
oh thank you okay okay okay let's finish
it together today
snooper super snake mario thank you for
the red super chat hey i've been waiting
wanted to share my feelings about your
3d performance but you haven't had a
chance till now you look so beautiful on
stage your dancing was so majestic and
your singing was absolutely divine
you truly lit that stage on fire so
proud love you thank you
next time they better use real fire
though
thank you very much i did my best i'm
glad you enjoyed it so much
hopefully hopefully you burnt it into
your memories forever and ever
[Music]
don't forget about it eva
thank you soon
[Music]
start a fire today
might be a safety concern no no no they
did use fire for different songs
i don't know which one it was but i
think they used it for
someone
i saw it i saw it for me they used like
red uh fog
[Music]
i probably kept it for like the end um
ungrouped it didn't foundation for the
pinky i just rewatched your concert
performance when you were on kitty break
i was on kitty break
oh you mean it's a normal day off yeah
that is actually a great description of
that don't expose me like that thank you
for the membership welcome
would you like to nerd out more on
talking about dance moves also when you
ran across the stage it was during the
instrumental section
do you intentionally have them for that
i think i kind of talked about this
before but um
i
definitely intentionally
chose that part
to like hype up everyone uh and ditch to
the dance break
but also these these songs are like
hinotoni and heart challenger are very
much like
[Music]
not made with all of that in mind but
it's just like the typical pattern that
j-pop songs and idol songs use
so yeah it's not not maybe not 100 on
purpose but it's just how these songs
are built
have a structure yeah
and
yeah often when i am
when i like uh
[Music]
listen to my own songs i like imagine
like how i would perform them
on the stage
yeah
we have
i have some thoughts and dreams about
how i want to perform them
and and and for hinotori finally i was
able to do it
[Music]
and girl didn't dance
you're welcome
and sirek thank you for the pinky last
one a very late congratulations for your
amazing performance during hulu fest it
was absolutely fire so much fire in fact
that spawn crashed what i've seen the
vod to see it uninterrupted again okay
look it crashed during my performance
that is devastating oh my god can't
reach the [\h__\h] room spawn
read the room
atmosphere
not bad time that's the worst timing if
that's true
what the [\h__\h]
it's too powerful yeah
at least for me it did wow
oh my god
it was too powerful
anyway okay i've already like it was
sorry
eight hours
yeah long shift today tomorrow is ttipg
on i think cali's channel
um so i'll see you guys there and
probably be pretty long
and yeah
i will take a nap beforehand i think to
survive
yeah yeah
normal length
i'm hungry
[Music]
it will be
it will be uh early in the morning for
jst 10 p.m for me
did i write that correctly on the
schedule i hope so
ah and now it's time the ending is
finally completed
yeah yeah yeah
maybe some of you guys didn't see it
uh yes the day before yesterday i gave
you a sneak peek of the new ending
the beautiful new ending
made by
the same people
actually the whole team is the same
people as the previous one but the
previous one was like basically just fan
made and a present to me and this time i
was like i'm gonna commission each and
every single one of you
so we have the same artist we have the
same animator and the same uh person who
like pieced it together
are you ready
are you ready for that beautiful art
from akinasam oh my god it's just like
eye candy
[Music]
and by the way uh the song that you will
hear is just an audio stock song that i
chose i ended up just
going for something from audio stock
rather than using my own stuff because i
felt it would fit better maybe in the
future we'll have something um from my
side and we can switch it out
but for now it will be that
adios
without onion stock
and in german we say
auf wiedersehen
oh perfect perfect perfect
[Music]
do
you