[Music]
oh
K I was like oh oh I better start right
awayy good morning sorry raspy morning
voice oh my God I'm so tired no I'm not
tired actually I'm not really tired
anymore I I get untired really fast um
thank you for coming to the stream I
normally don't stream at this
time uh but today I am sponsored by
Square Enix to play Star Ocean the
Second Story
[Music]
R I'm a
pirate and it's my first ever Star Ocean
game I love J pgs but Star Ocean is my
first yeah only ever like heard a little
bit about it oh my God my voice
[Music]
I have tea with me but it's not ready to
drink I going pour a little a little bit
of cold water in
here oh no please don't please don't
start the Bam Bam please don't start the
the opening video cuz the the song was a
Bop but I don't think I can play
it no no no no no stay
[Music]
then let's get into it I say because we
want to get some stuff done in a short
amount of time I'm really
curious as to what expect me just saying
again this stream is sponsored but you
know I'm an honest person but I do love
my jrpg gam
so so let me move my chat over here
there is no referral link as far as I
know of yeah it's just like normal if
anything normal download links you
finished the demo a few minutes ago
really fun game nice the game is coming
out uh depending on your time zone today
but like it's on the 2nd of November I'm
playing it on PC as I received a code
for the PC
version uh wait what what
what was
that okay okay here we go this is how it
start uh oh we
choose let's
go of course I'm choosing the girl like
who do you think I
am oh
y Rena landford a Carefree stere eyed
17-year-old girl with a big Magic ation
she's great at martial arts and also
possesses a mysterious healing power
what is it like is she a
Phoenix from the Southern Village of
Aria on the planet
expel has she been expelled from the
planet yet what let's read this too just
out of uh you know does he come if you
don't choose him does he come up in the
story does anyone
know I know it's new but people play the
demos so yeah okay so it's important
let's read it the only Claude C Kenny
the only son of ronx J Kenny hero of the
Teran Alliance Earthling oh oh alien to
Earthling unsure of what he wants to do
in life he's been going along with his
surroundings he's a 19-year-old student
at an officer school with a lot on his
mind like girls girls girls he likes
girls girls
girls he's learned hand to hand combat
at school however
what what what kind of cut off is
that
who what what how what what no what huh
what that really makes me wonder she
doesn't have a dot dot dot
ending
h however however he's scared of
fighting so he actually doesn't fight at
all he just watches the fights of his
teammates
or are we going for the
girl uh I can change the name no we're
going with this
oh help
me wait there's different
voices playing with PlayStation
controller ah oh it's
Japanese okay Japanese voice kind of
cute ah because I resarch
Japanese ah for English it's only that
voice I
guess yeah oh okay okay Nar uh
difficulty
galaxy universe earth
oh I mean it's a sponsored
stream I don't know maybe we go easy so
I can get faster through it I don't
know okay 30 difficulty
[Music]
names Galaxy is easy well then what is
Earth easy easy easy Earth is easy
that's what I thought yeah this obvious
from left to
right let's go with Galaxy satisfying
normal mode relaxing easy mode brutal
hard mode it says on the bottom left n
beat DM version Arrangement
[Music]
original
oh I mean for this track maybe it's not
as noticeable but I do notice a
difference that's cool should we
go ah original is from the original game
cuz it's a rem Master REM
make
so let's go arrangement though because
it's all about the
horor display event
art oh a you could do it without okay
remaster remaster
remake it's based yeah it's based off of
the PS1
version okay let's go with this this
game us an auto save feature
okay let's
go planet
Earth Earth Earth Earth Earth Earth
Earth Earth you
RF from 25 years ago I feel so
old me too
W
Earth Earth Earth Earth oh something's
Falling Down is it Rena being expelled
from her expel
[Music]
Planet wow what is
it aliens coming to Earth
[Music]
Earth the music is so dramatic I love
it oh it's
[Music]
pretty nice
HD
[Laughter]
earth I'm leaving bye
bye oh
wow hold on just a minute that was
scary what Mommy sorry Mommy Mom what
Mom don't you what Mom me how about
taking a break for once today you were
just there yesterday and the day before
that where was
I I know but it's just that being there
makes me feel so calm yeah it's uh still
2D for the characters the rest is like
super HD but I think it keeps the charm
of a 25-year-old
game come on why can't I
[Music]
go cute because I said so because I said
do I have to remind you about all the
crazy things going on since the sorcer
crashed down on us as long as you're
living under my roof and eating my
food sorcery Globe sorcery Glo just last
night we had a huge earthquake the
animals are all going wild and attacking
people it's too dangerous right now what
kind of sorcery is
this besides there's also
a I don't care what you're
saying ah wait a minute nuh-uh oh that
child what she sees in the sacred Forest
is beyond
me yeah cuz you're Boomer she's just
zooming let her zoom in
peace that was close why does my mom
always have to harp on me like that I
better get to the sacred Forest quick if
I want to make it there left or
right oh basic controls move open Camp
menu
confirm talk open chest close Okay
shortcut menu uh-huh current location
okay allows you toer your location or
destination while
exploring mini map icons ooh Town
dungeon scenario main scenario marker
okay we'll be looking for
that wasn't there 64 plus endings
[Music]
what we are next Bell right
now in Guild Etc cute cute okay
okay damn I don't think I ever played a
game like this where it's like HD
environment and then pixel characters oh
but it moves really smoothly I like it
left or right left or right wait
actually it the exclamation marug is at
the bottom of my map but we were like
looking that way
so wait where did
we ah the camera I can't move the camera
is
fixed yeah seems like Square Enix liks
to do these kind of games can I open
these
chests probably not it's going to be
stealing
oh where is it can be found inside
Treasure Chest be sure to open any chest
you come
across oh oh there's a five different
types spiked enemy symbols will appear n
what you're really letting me open
this
what the equip wizard it automa equipped
gear you find that is better than your
current weapons and armor accessories
will not be equipped can be turned on or
off under
settings I mean
[Music]
yeah I I'm a lazy girl oh is this the
money fool
fall hello little girl I'm not supposed
to leave the V cuz it's dangerous out
there that's so
boring yeah I'm not really supposed to
leave right now but I am going anyway Ah
that's a safe Point some safe points
only record data While others also
restore hpmp
oh how do I see the
difference
okay now this isn't the way okay
then ah wait maybe that way because it
leads us like all the way
around such a pretty
Village oh we could enter some of the
buildings
too get the good ending you think I'm
going to get an an ending today
wait is there really so what there's
really so many endings now somebody says
there there's
168 in the previous
game oh my God it's really
pretty oh do you see fish oh my God Is
there fishing in this game important
question there we go that's the
path
oh something about the sacred Forest
just makes me feel refreshed I think
I'll try going in a little further today
she looks so small compared to the
forest she's like an
ant or are the trees just
huge excuse my voice guys I it's like 7
a.m. here I just
woke got to read H got drink tea what
that's odd the first sounds different
than usual it sounds
[Music]
different
oh here we
go there's a speed up
Buton now this my mother would't worry
so much about me this place couldn't
possibly be any safer well she's 17
right
no well I guess most most parents would
still be very worried even when they're
17 look
out huh is the guy the clawed guy
wa oh what he clapped me what a clap
back wa just it's just clapped it right
in my face oh oh CLA CLA thank
you oh what was that a gun or something
good thing I made it in time yeah no for
real for real who is this guy he's
dressed all weird and what was that
light he killed that monster in the
blink of an eye so
true good
observation you all right that was a
close one by the way if you don't mind
me
asking what don't get so close wait wait
wa why am I
running ah
girl that scared me you didn't have to
get so close to me like that all of a
sudden
but maybe it was rude of me to run away
like that yeah what like that wasn't
that scary you just encountered a huge
weird stone rock Golem mob who was
clapping at you but then you're scared
of this dude what he noral tell me to
wait too yeah I guess you don't know
what that word
means hope he's still around maybe look
it up in a
dictionary now now now she changes her
mind and she goes looking for
him this
girl I was hoping you'd wait for me what
is the meaning of Cho mate
huh I'm sorry I ran away like
that what what what do you call
impulsive decisions yeah ran for 4
seconds and then like
M you know what maybe I shouldn't run
actually I respect that like changing a
mind and then like like not feeling
embarrassed about you know just running
away like changing your mind at all
normally I would be like well I started
running now I'm determined to continue
Running Oh no that's okay yeah admitting
your mistakes is
hard it's just that everything happened
so quickly I was really
shocked this is how love
begins scary
huh yes little still I'm really sorry
about all this you saved me but I just
ran off like that no I'm getting closer
no don't worry about it besides you did
stop to wait didn't
you I guess oh I haven't introduced
myself my name is Raina Raina
Lanford cute girl oh and uh I'm Claude
clae claudy Kenny claudy Kenny hi cl to
Kenny cl to Kenny nice to meet you Mr
Kenny
Mr Kenny so Mr Kenny was there something
you wanted to ask me earlier I bet his
second his middle name is also Claude
his name is Claude Claude
Kenny oh right it's nothing that
important really
but uh where am
I so he came from Earth to
expel are you a
traveler uh something like that
yeah was he the sparkling thing where
are you
from answer
answer from from
Earth Al so he's aware that he's on a
different planet interesting it looks
quite like Earth but maybe his Earth is
very modern where is that actually and
this this expel is far behind she does
look like clothing wise already
different well uh how can I put it it's
it's really far away from here really
really far away mhm probably probably
how did you get here a far away place
that's really amazing spaceship yes well
not
really no it is amazing traveling that
far it's not something that we can
currently really consider doing in Earth
unless we're
our space
people by
job Mr Kenny once we cross this bridge
we'll be in Aria
Aria Aria is that where you live if I
picked Cloud I would have seen how if I
just bar J oh Dam I want to see it of
course it is besides I need to repay you
some oh sorry no please please don't
worry about it I didn't do anything that
special you don't have to be so modest
it won't be much just the least I can
offer you so please what what what are
you with money or with food better to
not tell your mom though what you
encountered she won't let you go anymore
everas
a
oh oh oh we are a
party let's
go let me introduce you to my mom
already so early but you know I feel
like this is fate come follow me nice
handsome young lad from Earth so funny
he says he's from Earth H he's so
confused wait this is where I started
are welcome to Aria
wait wait so the house I just
realized I was right at the exit all
this time I just made a circle around it
so pretty oh oh is it well thank
you I thought the house was right like
behind where the camera ends ah it's
such a nice place I like it a
lot listen would you be able to show me
around the village yes of course I don't
mind it all
I don't mind doing another circle around
town ah this was my home
right oh well there's like six six uh
Quest
markers oh this is the home of the mayor
of ARA he's really no guy but he doesn't
seem to be in in right
now w w big table nice fireplace nice
the
kitchen oh the the the cooking place is
not as modern looking as the other stuff
interesting maybe I should get a stove
like that oh storage place can I go down
here oh oh wait that's the entrance huh
oh that's the other entrance okay nice
house Mr
[Music]
Mayor who's this
place is the home of the Town Carpenter
of his family he's got a big job in the
next town over right now so I don't see
him at home very much he says Ah carpet
making person so the two kids are here
by
themselves that's right those poor kids
I try to visit them and to chat as often
as I
can well we're standing on the carpet
and this house seems to have many
carpets so it's obvious that he makes
carpets that's pretty nice of you Rena
oh not at all I try
ha what oh come
on
chest strawberry Jem
M hi kids hey lady oh
Rena is your dad working today oh wait
I'm saying
this yeah he hasn't been back in 2 weeks
but don't worry I'll look after my
sister while he's away a he looks
younger though cute I'm not lonely at
all I've got my brother and you always
come to play with us too is that a cope
are you going to tell us that
story I'm sorry but I'm a bit busy today
maybe next
time okay you promise
y
cute okay let's go to this like item
shop looking
place this Ary are Goods they sell all
kinds of useful things for
everyone certainly smells good those are
the herbs you're smelling actually those
are the herbs you're smelling the
herbs medicine that heals WS you know
can't leave on a journey without them so
true so true and some some Revival stuff
hopefully you didn't no
nope I'm amazed you're so
alive how are you doing going shopping
with your boyfriend oh don't don't don't
say that ooh okay so the healing items
in this game are called aqua berries
blackberries I know this is MP
okay blueberries Resurrection alexir
cute lavender for oh 3% HP only but it's
used as a compound for item
creation oh oh they have spectacles they
have
spectacles
to analyze to get stats oh okay okay I
see I understand you I I get your jam
sandals oh cute a simple pair of sandals
made of wood they don't look like
they're made of
wood oh hold I'm not buying
anything next place is this
house buy them yeah I know they really
important I can guess this out way with
they're so in love with each other it's
almost a to watch
yeah
oh let me check out your house while
you're flirting and secretly steal stuff
from you wow
nice the way the the light enters is
also really pretty ooh healing items
nice wait they have a little a little
kids's bed in
their
own
uh split rooms
please
please let's have some
privacy don't have to share everything
oh
church this is Ving church we hold
wedding ceremonies and things in here
father Marshall is very hardworking man
he's always there for us if there's
something we need to talk about
a sounds like a wonderful man oh yes
everyone trust him oh that sounds like
that sounds like a flag of him being
evil in the end I don't
[Music]
know ah my voice is
so not warmed up at
all oh oh nice cool cool cool and
another floor
W magic canvas wait I want to go up here
too
no wait I'm I'm liking the visuals of
this a lot so
far search in the video g game you never
know yeah I mean I can see how you know
the church people end up being the evil
people in the game like this maybe who
knows press expert icons appear to learn
special information about that location
aha
investigate on the Watermill a water
wheel a handmade general purpose water
wheel that is an essential part of daily
life in Aria one used to see things like
this on Earth too yeah I don't think I
no wait I think I've seen one actually
even these days but very specific
location I
think special now we go to
[Applause]
Mommy well here's my house would you
mind waiting here a second I need to
clean up the place a
bit sure I'll be right back back
okay sometimes I do that too when
friends are coming over spontaneously
welcome back Raina after we went for is
something wrong for lunch or something
like that then I'm like oh [\h__\h] wait I
need I really need to clean my room or
check if everything's in order before
you
enter yeah I've made I've made then wait
maybe a few times outside only for a
short time only for like one or 2
minutes something big has happened Mom
this is serious but when I know they're
coming over then I clean properly
beforehand oh really now just what could
that be no it's really actually serious
I'm not exaggerating he's here the hero
has
arrived that's what we call him that's
what she thinks he is just by meeting
him for a moment and well he did rescue
her what but what do you mean the her
her the one from the Legends you know
the hero of light he's come to save us
well from anybody's point of view that
sounds like a big stretch but I guess
this is probably
true Raina are are you sure about that
yes he's wearing clothes like I've never
seen before and he has the sword of
light
oh oh
the sword of
light yes he used this unbelievable
light to save me in the sacred Forest it
had to be the sword of light so you
little [\h__\h] went to the sacred Forest
again Mama so where is he right now he's
outside right now so I'm going to what
why did
he this dude
hello just enters on his own wait a
minute
Raina h Huh he invited him
excuse me oh my
God rud is something wrong Mr
Kenny ah um it's been a while since you
left me so I was just wondering what's
up it's been 15 seconds oh my apologies
oh my God
clingy would you wait outside for me
just a little bit longer I was about to
call him in like in 5 seconds though can
we just keep him inside now sure do you
mind if I walk around a little oh please
do go
ahead no we're going to lose him he
surprised me no we're going to lose him
no no don't let him go was that him
ah
yeah are you sure we should leave him
out there by himself n no I I think
he'll be okay but he's going to get lost
no Raina tell him to come inside that'll
probably be better yes let's do that oh
my God these characters okay I'll go get
him you actually believed me Mom oh did
she really though of course I did Raina
you're my daughter of course I did yeah
yeah like I believe all you other
stories too
mhm thank you
thank you for giving me the confidence
of being
believed where did this guy
go no did
he oh oh oh makes me go here
[Music]
interesting wait what you want me to
talk to these
people H your boyfriend can't say I've
seen him speaking of which I haven't
seen
di flck in a while wonder the hell he's
doing you got another men how many years
has it been
[Music]
since di Diaz left earlier what what is
she talking about I guess I can
understand why he'd want to leave whoa
whoa whoa you're newly
went especially after that horrible
incident but still
[Music]
I I I got to go I got to go what a
confusing
[Music]
conversation what who
is who is
Diaz oh we're talking to ah there you
are could have just turned around but no
sorry to keep you waiting Mr
Kenny oh rain we didn't lose him
done uh yeah why what come follow
me I'm amazed that he didn't completely
ran off the other end of this uh the
village mom back look at that huge
chicken no that a turkey and some no is
that
melons and a big soup bread
[Music]
M Raina I wasn't expecting you two to be
back so early
just in time though I was just finishing
up everything nice finishing up me on
the
table is it you guys on the table all
right P thank you for your
services mom what's all this food here
for how did she whip that up in
like about 20 seconds
wow doesn't it look delicious I put all
of my best recipes out on the table for
you that's not what what I mean what did
I do something wrong I just thought I'd
thank Mr Kenny with a nice meal a wow
maybe she did believe the
story I understand that but isn't this a
little
much yeah I would say so he's pretty
young so I figured he'd have a big
appetite well who knows how long you w
hungry aren't you Mr Kenny how long he
hasn't eaten actually I am yeah yeah
let's dig in see a real man could put
all this away no problem so eat as much
as you like all right wait wait don't
say it like that cuz I I mean there's
surely some guys out there who have a
smaller smaller tummy like me and they
won't be able to eat
that they're still real
men oh
[Music]
Mom a nice
dinner he's he's a real man don't worry
man is the keyword he's a
boy oh an hour later passed out no oh
thank you so much for the meal but I
just can't eat anymore is
he uh this is a guest room are you okay
gu you didn't have to force it all down
you
know
I'm fine I'm fine I've got a cast iron
stomach cast iron stomach who says that
I'm sorry my mother made so
much it was all delicious though my
mother would never be able to do
something like
that a don't roast your
mommy thanks for the compliment I'm glad
you're happy I'm going to go downstairs
and help my mother clean up feel free to
rest up here for a bit all right sure
that sounds good
[Music]
good night new friend that I have
captured and put in a in my house prison
he's mine
now stuffed he said he couldn't eat
anymore so I had him rest upstairs for a
bit I say like he's I said like he's my
property in that case now would be a
good time to tell the mayor it's dark
out so be careful Raina okay okay I'll
go get him it's like I got a new pet
yeah he's he isn't he well yeah I guess
I guess so now he is like can enter from
either way I
guess hello Mayon son what all the
racket for
Raina sir come to my house quick there's
no time to waste we're having a party
about my pet alien just what is going on
he's the alien not me he came from Earth
this is not earth he's the alien the
hero he's finally appeared
oh what n it's true he has the sword of
light and everything the sword of light
well they're going to be real
disappointed if it's not true his
clothes are foreign looking too there's
no doubt about it he's the hero from The
Legend well I'm starting to doubt it my
goodness tell me Raina where did you
find him in the sacred Forest he saved
me from a monster using the sword of
light and right now he's resting in my
house sounds like what a hero would do
but I'm telling you the truth what's
more he said he's on a journey but
didn't have any idea where he
was he claims to be from somewhere but
I've never even heard of the place don't
you think this is more than a
coincidence coincidence I think not
indeed it is something worth looking
into Raina I know as well as anybody
that you are not the kind of girl to
make up stories either yeah you're just
the kind of girl to believe literally
everything you put in your head thank
you mayor so let's get to the bottom of
this first things first let's yeah yeah
go go come with
me oh you can go fast where
stick zooming where's Mommy I'm
back rain no no you pet escaped through
the window maybe what's wrong no way no
way way why you panicking like that
that's the first thing I thought when
she was like having these water drops
coming off of her head no it's just that
I've huh kiss my boyfriend tell me
what's wrong what did you do I said
it said
what I said the H
[Music]
word uh what you told him that so what
did he say oh oh hero hero hero she
mentioned hero to
him I don't think he understood what I
meant sorry Mommy please be calm
everyone it's all right he doesn't
understand what this is all about
either oh Mr Kenny wait in Japanese I
feel like in Japanese obviously it hits
harder they I feel like they must have
used it the same way cuz it would have
also been heo and
then this must be claudy Kenny then yes
yes yeah allow me to say I'm honored to
make your acquaintance well there's a my
name is Regis and ibly serve this
Village as its mayor in Japanese but I
feel like often they still go for the
English word
heo well who knows good to meet you
sir who knows allow me to thank you
profusely for saving our dear rea's life
in the sacred
Forest oh not at all sir
sorry I got stuff in my eye speaking of
which Raina has told me that you are at
present in the midst of a journey that
he doesn't really understand oh well
it's hardly worth calling a journey
really so tell me where is your
destination the kingdom of cross or
perhaps the continent of lur they do use
USA or they missed out on on a hero and
H pun there that we got well I
uh a curious traveler indeed not only do
you not know where you are but where you
are going is also yet unknown mysterious
let's adopt him and make him do stuff
for
us what are you trying to say Sir let's
make him save our world Mr Kenny if you
will forgive my rudess for a moment I do
believe everything you have told us has
been a
[Music]
lie
hey you are far from an ordinary
traveler if I'm not a traveler then what
am I oh my God this is
[Music]
so a visitor From Another World a hero
of Legends hidden under the guise of a
traveler if you say in fact even you
will agree that you are are the hero of
light who has come to fulfill his duty
as our savior Am I Wrong well that's a
lot of pressure you're putting on him
right now but I agree
surely what I uh listen what would
possibly make you think that I
uh if it's proof you need then let me
share with you a glimpse of our world oh
it has been told in our history that
when the people of expel are suffering
under the thr threat of impending doom a
hero will appear in garbs of foreign
make and with his sword of light he will
save us all this sounds actually really
fitting your clothes are nothing like
what we have and you carry the sword of
light what more proof do we need no
doesn't make sense what do you I don't
have any sword of
light of course you do you used a
blinding light to save me ear was it a
Tor no way cuz it actually looked more
like a
laser
that maybe he really isn't the
one no he's got to be yeah we'll make
him be that force him I think I know why
you're all confused this weapon of mine
it's not a sword of light although I'll
admit that it's something like one but
still carrying this around doesn't make
me any kind of special hero there's got
to be some kind of
mistake how can you say that well I mean
I'm not a hero I don't have any kind of
power like that I don't even have any
idea what's going on here it's deep in
your heart how you expect me to save
anyone at
all it's in your
coo you truly have no idea you really
don't know anything about the sorcery
globe or the
cataclysms damn let's let's throw him
back to Earth we're not talking about
something that happens in the village
here we're talking about the cataclysms
that have affected the entire world it
seems that you do not really know what
we are talking about please allow me to
explain okay it All Began 3 months ago
do we got a cut
scene oh yeah
baby on another continent Northwest of
this Village there is a kingdom by the
name of
lhm
no okay one fateful day a meteor crashed
upon Allura a town located within El's
territory oh
no at first people saw it as merely a
rare and remarkable Celestial
[Music]
event but before long a cataclysm took
place
cataclysm
oh great hordes of monsters suddenly
appeared in the once peaceful nation and
the Havoc they spread devastated the
kingdom of L yeah that is unfortunate
there has never been anything like this
before in our world not until the
arrival of that
meteor it only stands to reason that the
two events are related to each other
well if you say it like that that
implies maybe it's not
sus the meteor came to be called the
sorcery Globe a stone of pure demonic
evil so it's still there no matter how
you look at it that stone must be the
reason for the disasters that have
befallen the world wait we're calling a
meteor the sorcery Globe to me it sounds
like calling snake a danger
noodle
I love
that this is a full version yeah and now
just as the sorcery Globe fell Upon Our
Heads one day so you have also appeared
out of thin air if that stone is the
source of the chaos then we believe that
only you can cut through the chaos and
save
us
well still a lot to put on a stranger
but I'm just a
the cataclysms are still ongoing as we
speak strings of earthquakes like
nothing recorded before dosel animals
turning into fearsome monsters it will
not be long before disaster befalls this
humble Village
too it already has but I I'm not anyone
special like your story said how am I
supposed to deal with some kind of magic
meteorite with your flashlight if you
are not then where did you come from
and where are you going but he doesn't
know that he's a dense protagonist
that's I don't know how to explain it if
I did you wouldn't understand it the
only thing I can tell you is that I'm
here because of an accident and not
because I wanted to be here I just want
to go back to where I came from that's
all accident I want to see like his part
of the story you must have your reasons
but you must let us know more before we
can make sense of this I know but that's
on I can tell you very
well if you insist on it then I am sure
there is at least some truth to it we
will have to accept that you are not the
hero of light after
all how can this
be well I'm sorry lost lost this
probably not what you all wanted to hear
not at all it is our own fault forcing
you to be someone are not in the first
place yeah well um okay guys then I
guess that's the end of the story I'm
sorry about
this they'll just
die guess no
[Music]
hero where are we going
Raina I don't believe this he has to be
the one those clothes and that sword of
light stubborn child
[Music]
oh the next
morning good morning K
KY oh o oh self opening door is wow
magical such a beautiful day today you
ought to be spending time outside okay
is he out there it's probably like oh
sorry uh thanks for keeping me one night
but I'm leaving and I'm like no don't
go don't leave me you have to save our
[Music]
world wow he really went far without
saying goodbye oh my
God
[Music]
rude oh enemy symbols touching an enemy
symbol from the front will begin a
battle touching from behind or being
touched from behind by symbol will
trigger a back attack where battle
begins with the ambushed side in a
stunned State
okay weak strong normal okay okay don't
run into red
enemies let's
save I'm level three
okay
[Music]
no Treasure Chest purple blue purple
purple ah wait no wa is no why did I let
him do that okay uh well well move C to
normal attack R1 L1 use special art
symbology
okay wait what I already forgot uh what
was what was normal attack Circle
right
switch Target
L2 and move around okay uh r lock unlock
Target R free R free
okay the controls with switching can be
changed under settings list switch
targets according to the format used in
the enemy list during
battle
okay press X right in an enemy attacks
perform a perfect counter oh I'm not
good with those the Q is when enemies
will flash red right as they attack okay
okay x x successful perfect counters
have the following benefits recover 25%
of Max HP the lower the character's HP
the more MP will be recovered well MP
not HP okay the enemy Shield will
decrease by
one failed perfect couns will have the
following negative effects the character
will break rendering them unable to act
for a while the bonus Gods will reset
hey
okay
uh okay
uh oh oh oh oh oh okay y it I need
rescuing Mr
Hero what's
this Crush oh
yo good Crush Crush Crush Crush
Crush oh oh that's really
cool I wonder what skills what else she
has
[Music]
M Treasure Chest I love dead
ends fruit syrup should we do a Nava
fight let's
go you ready for
this heal oh ah that's the left one is
heal okay okay n
Nar oh oh only three hits okay all right
easy I like the the finishing music the
success
music let's look at the
menu uh wait
how this a
map ah there we go ooh Camp menu make
various preparations for adventur such
as checking your inventory for CH or
changing equipment and uh icon indicates
updated
information character comments depending
on story progress characters will
occasionally comment on the next
objective or situation oh
okay I don't want to look at my
equipment
oopsie equip weapons armor and
accessories or improve characters
equipment can be found at Shops okay
some pieces of equipment have elements
or Elemental resistances with the most
beneficial resistance taking presedent
precedence oh uhhuh
okay mm
mhm okay cool and then our
skills set special arts or spells for
use in battle there are three types of
special arts and
spells uhhuh mainly damages HP mainly
damages Shields damages both HP and
shields oo attack spell damage types are
all
balanced it is possible to skip certain
spell cutcenes the default setting for
skipping cut scenes can be toggled
okay ah we do have another one that but
that's just
antidote this is
[Music]
AOE okay not a not a oh I can
improve learning improving battle skills
so spend Battle Points to improve a
learn battle skills battle skills are
only effective in combat battle skills
can be turned on or off
oh okay
okay not why these are all battle
skills evades attacks increase movement
speed cast casting time cut E I wouldn't
know what to
take if casting at the same time as an
enemy and the enemy spell would go off
first there's chance your spell
interrupt theirs
oh I don't know maybe maybe maybe just a
normal boost attack
power or defense yeah let's just go for
this cheap one for now
oh I got an
achievement and maybe this one too and
so how do I use them we'll find out
maybe ah wait there's battle points for
this too ah now I already use some on
other stuff but they would have been too
expensive
okay you can hold up to 20 items
okay all right now I understand
[Music]
let's fight hot surprise got
en ah
it
bam getak that was an easy win I like
her pose she's like a
magician ooh great I love you ooh ooh we
got a lot of extra Battle Points but for
now
let's move on what I trying to
accomplish
here that's what I ask myself all the
time live life
questions father what am I supposed to
do I bought it cuz I saw you were going
to play it
nice glad you made that
choice
father what am I supposed to
do WS
[Music]
please keep your voice down we wouldn't
want Raina to hear us where's that my
mom that girl's passed down on her bed
now that she's finally had enough of
crying for her dead father I never read
her name until now was it there did not
just say
[Music]
mom it was there I sure this is just as
much as shock for you as it is for her
but you are her mother you need to stay
calm for her
sake stay calm how am I supposed to stay
calm my husband is
dead
Wester without him what am I what am I
going to do well that's I mean reason
the B reaction I still haven't told her
yet now that he's gone that's how she
finds out to tell her all by my Myself
by listening to their
conversation having to tell your
daughter that she's not your real
[Music]
child I'm
adopted I'm adoped I should have thrown
away that damn pendant why didn't I get
rid of the last connection to her real
parents she would have been mine my real
daughter that sounds kind of evil what
the hell
[Music]
so father dead but the fake father or
yeah the fake father
right
so and I'm
adopted and I just recall that so who am
I
then was I like pushing this memory out
of my brain until
now not trying to remember
it
Raina
yeah Mr Kenny
Kenny
morning good morning oh wait that's his
last name I thought she gave him a
nickname wait it is no it's Kennedy
Kennedy or Kenny WR you look tired
Claude Kennedy or
Kenny huh oh no I'm
fine oh Kenny oh I'm sorry about what
happened yesterday I didn't mean to
cause a scene like that so but maybe he
also gave him self a nickname from
Kennedy to Kenny maybe he likes it
more it's all right I mean I know I must
look really out of place to you all now
that I know the whole story it's pretty
easy to see how everyone came to that
conclusion yeah I grew up listening to
tales about the hero you know they
talked about how the hero would appear
in our time of greatest need and save
our way of life how do you know and I
mean a lot of lot of people are
desperately in need right now aren't
they all around the
world having you show up just like the
stories at a time like
this I just thought you had to be the
one that makes sense yeah it makes a lot
of sense I mean I wasn't sure but I was
pretty sure well I'm sorry I couldn't be
the hero you wanted
oh I didn't mean that Mr Kenny it's not
your fault I'm the one to blame for for
being so easily taken in by the stories
of the hero maybe she just also wants a
hero because of you know this [\h__\h] that
she heard about her family and she just
wants saving in a noble
way I still want to apologize though I
really wish there's something I could do
I wonder if they even had a conversation
about it or if she just heard it and
then like kept it to herself that she
knows
probably do you think she confronted her
mom you don't have to worry about it I
hope you can get back to your home
soon cuz
uh confronting seems like it I'm sorry
blow up would it be right if I stayed
here alone for a little while a well
Okay I uh I hope you feel better see
you
oh so he's still not leaving okay I'm
sorry Mr
Kenny I better get back home wouldn't
want my mother worrying about me what
you just said you're going to stay here
for a
while all right going
back but what about this path though
this path is looking interesting oh oh
treasure
death let's go
money no
maybe she's um what's this what's the
word
projecting she thinks she's looking for
a hero for the whole world but she just
wants a hero for
herself
man she has issues you
know back to Aria
[Music]
oh Alan
bro is it my bro cuz they have the same
color
[Music]
theme hey Raina you're a sight for sore
eyes how have things
been
good well
[Laughter]
great
Alan you good I've got good news for you
Raina I'm finally ready to marry
me ready for what no way no way the
stage has finally been set or should I
say our wedding ceremony is ready hey
yo how old is he huh what are you saying
Alan I was right he seemed very much
like he was going that direction oh [\h__\h]
oh he's being arrested already oh wait
what is he like a prince so he's like I
will Mar you what you're talking about
Alan whether you like it or not I'm not
getting married to you oh what he's like
forcing what
what you'll change your tune soon enough
Raina once you witness my greatness and
my power oh I'm a damsel in distress a
hero must save me from being forcibly
married off I love this I'm not changing
anything what happened to you Alan this
is such a dream dream story of any young
girl I mean for real
like I'm so wanted can't you feel it the
power that's pouring out of my body even
as we speak but what about love we
should be feeling love Alan what
happened to
you whatever take her
away Mommy
let me
go fret not my dear soon you won't be
able to live without me the stone has
told me
so who who who who whoo whoo hold on
wait
mommy what
the someone someone get Rees get
wer this took a turn yeah oh my mom
mommy well well quite the
reception mom help me Alan what is the
meaning of this let Raina go right
now can't do
that Alan have you gone mad and was he
not always like this Alan the power made
him
mad
move out of my way please I will not be
kind to
Interlopers
Interlopers let Raina go let's ELO oh oh
W the power pushed her back I will say
this one last time get out of my way or
I will make sure everyone here regrets
it
dearly the things he says are like
supposedly intimidating but somehow I'm
not very
intim let him through everybody this is
not the same Allan we knew I think he'll
do what he
says let's tested but Raina the hero
will rescue us I'm going to be all right
please don't worry about me I'm just so
popular
[Music]
man huh it would have been easier if
everyone just did this the first time I
asked off
then
what this is so sudden get
in oh why are you doing this Alan
chest nice bed though this is terrible
and what you did to my
mother cool off in here for a while I'll
come back back for you later and don't
even think about trying to
[Music]
escape so if you play the guy then got
to get out of here your job is probably
like you hear oh you yeah your your
crush was taken away and then you your
quest is to go get me out of here and
I'm I'm just going to wait here I'm just
going to wait for CLA to rescue me my he
just like any princess who's been
captured against her will would do ooh a
[Music]
Talisman defense plus 10%
nice okay well then let's go let's leave
cuz I guess the hero is not
coming or is
he
bye-bye oh
okay it do be locked oh
Chef H maybe through the
kitchen Miss Rena why Master alen
started acting strange after acquiring
The Peculiar Stone since then he hasn't
even been eating properly oh that's the
cook say what could have happened to
him oh so he's really like not normally
like this but he may have already had a
crush on me
[Music]
anyway what's this place there's got to
be a hidden exit
somewhere okay I know what it
is the statue move touch
yeah Chess at the kitchen wait does
didn't see wait let me go
back let me go back there we go let me
go back let me go back wait wa wait wait
wait wait wait wait don't let anybody
see that I just opened that door can you
move
[Music]
ah fried egg but okay wait before we go
that way
then is there any other rooms up here to
check out oh
hello the family made when I was walking
past the study the other day I heard
someone saying something about the
Statue thanks for the hint I already got
it though no chest here
[Music]
okay in
case you really lost there was no chest
here right okay
all right then let's use our new exit
supposed supposedly an exit oh where am
I I have no idea a tunnel like this
exists under a
miner I mean there's someone on the
ground m i n e
[Music]
r Bosman are you all right oh we know
him too no Raina why are you you here
that's what I was going to ask you oh
you're
hurt I'll be fine but what are you doing
here
Raina I was taken here by Alan he was
going on about a wedding in some kind of
altar ni see well Alan had me build this
bizarre room inside the Salva mines for
him guess now I know what the alters for
I'm afraid this all of this just built
by you alone something's wrong wrong
with that boy damn he's got this Stone
and every time he looks at it he cracks
this smile that makes him look like a
madman oh I was frankly too scared to go
on but when I tried to escape this
happened to me Raina if you're the one
he's after you better get out of here
fast I'm trying wait where does this
lean I can't just leave you here
Bosman I'll be all right I'll leave the
Mansion once I've rested up a bit m but
you don't have that kind of luxury Raina
yeah he's not trying to marry him he's
trying to marry me
but this Mansion is connected to the
Salva mines on the inside you might be
able to find your way back to town
through there now get moving
okay let's go let's go let's go oh oh
yeah
wo yeah let's
go and love
[Music]
this which way which way which way is
which way are the dead ends I need the
dead
ends all the dead ends first
please that's a dead end because can't
go for that path is that a chest
no meow meow oh yeah 10 is
K
nice yeah yeah that's what I'm talking
about we better be
careful oh bonus go collect enough of
the Spheres that enemies drop to trigger
bonus effects they can be up to free
bonus effects use them to gain the
advantage in
[Music]
battle
okay the enemies will drop spheres in
the following situations the enemy is
defeated a critical hit or the enemy is
broken spheres H breaks
Brakes in particular allow for large
amount of Spears to be obtained to
actively aim to break enemies when
possible the bonus G will break in the
following situations a perfect counter
fails the current character becomes
incap that dead battle begins with an
enemy back attack
okay
crash okay an enemy will break when
their Shield is completely depleted they
will be temporarily unable to act while
broken actively aim to break poses in
order to deal
damage
okay nice than I thought so the these
points I get uh to carry over to the
next battle it's I think from my
understanding an blueberries wait the an
I I can put that one on too
[Music]
offer some protection ah plus three
death okay no effect
[Applause]
though this is this a dead end too I
think so yeah I have a feeling for it
you know what you just have this feeling
after lots of experience in jpg games
man now this one is a
toughy okay the other one was a dead end
but then here is also a dead end but no
chest okay this is a back attack we got
enemies no okay
good what are these crazy
bunnies well I broke him just of a
normal hits
okay
nice okay weaker than I
thought is this am I doing something
wrong with the normal hits cuz they seem
like they're very like there's no combos
it's like so cut
[Music]
off there's no flow right
now just Spam Ren doesn't do melee okay
okay so her focus is just magic we just
don't have as much yet
[Music]
okay oh unique spot quietly gleaming
minerals the mining town of Salma is
home to Rich veins of metals and gems
that find their way into weapons and
accessories those small the gemstones
are highgrade and popular gifts
nice oh wait did I did I get exp from
looking at a uh unique spot like
that that's so
cool uh
[Music]
yes we better be careful pretty Rock
makes
SM but then it is it advisable to spam
[Music]
this I
wonder oh yeah limited MP of
course
good
excellent another level up let's
go wait now I'm feeling
like ah safe point you know what that
means go left
first why am I trying to Mid Max this is
just a spaed stream where I got to get
more content in in a short amount of
time but I need to I need to find all
the chest okay okay that's good we can't
go here thank you thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
we got enemies of course I'm enjoying
this I really like
it I mean I don't really have the time
at the moment
over to make a series out of it but I I
do want to play
[Music]
more
level six we are now
oops make mic PlayStation controller
confuses
me is it
connected did we go here before oh yeah
yeah it's connected okay that actually
makes me feel relieved cuz I was uh
thinking I'm missing out on a path on
this side
uh wait wait how do I see the map big
again there we go a okay so I pretty
much explored everything then
good didn't miss out on
anything old more chest way you ready
for
this crash
Crush Catman too fast got to break him
with my martial arts
punches I'm pretty strong even with just
even with the
[Music]
punches oh originally it was both on
PlayStation Portable and PS1 e really
damn back in the day when I had a
PlayStation Portable I should have
gotten this game I didn't know about the
game at all back
then
e if only I had the knowledge
okay this one's fast I don't know should
I
try okay okay okay
okay nice it's all
over I really enjoyed back then playing
with my PlayStation Portable
man I had a pink PlayStation
Portable it was pretty cute I love
bringing it to school too to listen to
music I remember
it was my my music device uh for some
time I used to have a MP3 player it's a
small one but then later on I just used
the PlayStation Portable cuz it looked
freaking cute and I thought I could Flex
cuz no one else had a PlayStation
Portable in my school okay maybe some
people did but mostly not oh what is
this place did he build a church here to
marry me and he didn't say an altar but
this looks more like a church
underground
Church
Chase ah my sweet bride God so wonderful
of you to make it to our little wedding
Dream wedding absolute goals in
life there she goes wait put the chest
we have to we have to open the
chest
oh nice music
kinky Raina my dear you should know by
now that you can't escape from me no
Alan what is wrong with you you weren't
like this before for real no I wasn't
I've changed and I have the stone to
thank for
that oh that
stone but that's a trifle matter not
worth killing yourself over Shall We
Begin the ceremony
Raina he came to my rescue he's a real
hero that's close enough I always knew
it so you're out let Raina go do you
have any idea what you're doing I'm
going to marry her not you if you'll
excuse me sir we are in the middle of a
holy ceremony in just a moment we will
be together as one it can't be
legitimate I would appreciate if you
would show some respect you need a
priest now then my Raina even if it's an
evil one doesn't matter Mr Kenny help
me ah this this is my dream stop it this
isn't anything holy you can't force
someone into marriage like
this I want to be rescued too Force I
think you're a tad mistaken here we are
in love with each other love with each
other love love love yeah he's in a love
Rush he's in a love love love Rush he
really wants to
marry love love love
Rush Love stream stream love with oh no
himself oh no ultimate power let's fight
him together Mr
Kenny oh he's foring
step back he's
moring he mored oh my God muscle guy
okay oh and now he's got an actual sword
he must have picked that up somewhere in
between
look oh my God okay this is bad you you
fight I stand back to do my rock attacks
switching controlled characters oh
R2 okay I don't I guess we'll do it for
the the sake of the sponsorship like
showing off
characters wait what did it say R2 and L
okay
[Music]
uh let's
go got you does he have also something
there no it's uh I don't know what that
is is that wait my is she hitting me too
oh thank you wait was was her was her
Crush hitting
me wait my h PE why does it get so low
finally
over w w w wo wo wo
W and when was he hitting me I didn't
see him hitting
me what he hits hard but Rena with the
nice backup thank
you he just gets level three now I
started off with level
three Raina are you all right the game
didn't level him up at
all yeah
damn what happened to this guy
Raina no idea man I don't know what a
freak ever since he came to Aria it's
like he was possessed by something mhm
but people don't just turn into this
kind of monster what's going on
here the
stone
Allan you were such a good person too
wait he's
dead Raina
why did this have to happen like for
real oh no okay let's heal him Alan oh
we did think he was dead though he's
still
breathing oh
oh I healed
him I'm so nice where am I
huh Raina why are you here sounds like
Raina
way alen you're
back what do you
mean oh my head's spinning she's
actually happy stuck in a dream for days
I would still be freaked out about
him I guess that stone was what caused
all this trouble once it's gone that was
enough to turn him back to
normal I'm so happy for
you really I guess let's go back to the
mansion we can figure everything out but
the chest though can we open the chest
no no what no I did all that no the
chest what I never had a chance to get
it they make me go back what no no not
I'm mad this is the end of the
stream yes you did I'm afraid why it was
a terrible experience my
ch
wow how can you do this to me I can't
remember a thing you telling me I had
Bosman build that Altar for
me yeah it was about 2 weeks ago that
you sent me the order now that I think
about it that was around the time I
started to notice you acting strangely
like you were in your own little world
or
[Music]
something it must have been that stone
whatever power that Stone's emitting was
enough to mentally transform you yeah he
built all that in two days but if you
think about it like he built the tunnel
too did he so I'm I just imagine him
mining in all these directions and then
stopping and going a different way cuz
there's so many dead
ends nah I guess the mining the that
system was already there he just created
that one room but it's funny to think
about him just mining all these
different paths and being like n this
not so nice I'll go this way and
extending his time of building even
though he's only got so little time I
think you're right about that the first
time I saw that stone it was like
something swelled up inside my head I
felt like I could literally do no wrong
that I was right and everyone else was
to do my bidding I don't remember much
after that but I don't think I'll ever
be able to forget what it felt like at
that single Moment I Saw uh two comments
in a row saying oh maybe he's the hero
of light Bossman um
he doesn't seem like he would be such an
important
character maybe side character but
no Raina I'm sorry it's okay I know I
was unconscious during that time but I
feel terrible for doing those things to
you really really do you don't feel bad
Alan besides you're back to normal and I
know the real Alan would never do
anything like that m maybe if he had
more power he would thank
you we better hurry back to Aria your
mom's worried about you
Raina yeah
understandable I need to go explain what
happened to everyone in Salva hopefully
they'll be
understanding
a or the small child St
too I still want to know about you know
if we have confronted our mom yet well
looks like we owe you our thanks once
again yeah you saved raina's life not
once but twice now we won't let it go
now you are the hero you just don't know
it every protagonist is dence AF so it
must be you oh no I hardly did anything
worth thanking me for yes you
did so is that what started this whole
little episode that little Stone he
found in the Salva mines
that's the only explanation I can think
of when the stone shattered Allan
snapped back to
[Music]
normal crazy crazy first you go mad then
you transform into a monster that stone
almost reminds me of the sorcery
Globe yes it does seem to be I was
thinking of it too but the two are
related somehow because the sorcery
Globe has different color and different
shape and all that I thought
the sorcery
Globe guess they are connected somehow
that's just something that popped into
my mind
anyway it sounds like the town of Salva
is in an uproar right now as if Allan
didn't cause enough chaos rumors about
the hero have made it over there as well
oh well
now can't can't get out of this anymore
I'm sorry I know you had warned me about
that H do not take that as a criticism
it was unavoidable with your mind
focused upon saving raina's life still
the story has spread too far now hiding
it any longer will prove to be very
impractical I
see would you mind investigating the
sorcery Globe for us Mr
[Music]
Kenny I know this is an awfully selfish
request but frankly I cannot think of
anyone more fitting for the task I as
well believe Allan's fit of madness has
something to do with the sorcery glob if
you could save him then perhaps you
could do yet more for
us nice Mr Kenny nice
nice nice flow makes sense all right
I'll do it yeah I'll do it you will we
got a hero in our back ah but but first
let me just remind you that I'm not the
hero sa world is just Way Beyond me I'm
afraid yeah yeah yeah yeah but I think
the sorcery Globe might provide some
useful information for my own personal
reasons oh why would you think that if I
can help everyone else in the process
then I figure it'd be worthwhile I mean
it might but why what makes you think
that like what what what what thank you
very much Mr Kenny we will help you out
as best we can
well I'm adopted so I'm going to adopt
him too just like I was adopted he's
mine thank you but I'm not to promis my
hero
[Music]
pet could you take me with you Mr Kenny
oh Raina yeah leaving home to go on a
world saving Journey you heard what the
mayor just said I want to help out as
best I can
but Raina it's going to be dangerous
dangerous I fully understand that but I
just know I will be of some help to you
along the way yeah like healing you
don't know very much about this land do
you's very low L too so you're going to
need some kind of guide in your travels
I could at least provide you with that
right
yeah I suppose so yes
but come on mayor help me out
here no he agree he a problem that's
right Mr Kenny why don't you take her
along if that's what she wants well can
we ask my mom though does my mom have
anything to say about this may mayor H
I'm sure she'll be a tremendous asset on
the road a prop
yes okay I got it but get your mom's
permission first Raina I'm not going to
let you come with me unless she gives
the green light mm yeah I know mhm in
that case you should probably head for
cross first that's a pretty large town
so I'm sure you'll find some leads there
you mean after I get
permission take care on your way home
Raina it's starting to get chilly so
don't catch cold now a cold oh I'll be
all right my house is right over there
you know yeah literally five
steps everybody so worried all the time
I'm not being a burden on you am I I
know I kind of forced you into that no
of course not um listen
[Music]
I
yes yeah it's not acceptable in my books
are you still here I thought you'd be
back home by now I love how in this game
like the the way the time passes seems
very different for these alien people
because
like after 5 Seconds everybody's always
like as if it's been 1
hour have a good
[Music]
night oh my God so funny to
me welcome back
Raina give me
some friendship level has changed oh
yeah I'm no yeah I don't want to go out
I'm just running around
um bedtime okay I guess I I'm going to
ask for permission
[Music]
tomorrow oh no never mind um
Mom
listen M what is it you think she dyed
her hair blue to make me believe that
I'm not adopted you know to make it look
natural Mr Kenny said he'll go check out
the sorcery Globe for
us yes no
maybe oh
really really but that's not all I'm
going with him and I'll marry him cuz
he's my hero I I was thinking about
going along with
him Raina why would you want to do that
cuz I'm
magical I thought the journey might be
too much for him to Handle by himself I
mean he doesn't know a thing about this
world it's my destiny I feel it but
Raina no please Mom her fake mom doesn't
even have Elven ears I know all about
wait I didn't no this oh my God that's
such a giveaway pardon my intrusion so
late my dear Wester could I have a word
you don't wonder if like as a child she
was growing up she would ever ask her
mom so why why why I have such long
pointy ears and mommy don't have long
pointy ears explain mommy certainly
thinking that she's weird compared to
her
mommy I'm going to get some fresh air
outside oh maybe she was told her dad
was an
elf or whatever that it's supposed to be
in this
world oh uh wait what where am I
[Music]
going map ah
okay and I wonder where there's a good
point to stop I hope it's
[Music]
upcoming the quest marker literally
showed to go
there I'm like oh it's dangerous to go
to
Forest maybe I was just looking for
him
what is this
device alien device still no dice guess
I'm too far out of range
M damn
it walkie
talking Mr Kenny are you having trouble
sleeping oh Raina no I just uh what are
you oh sorry sorry reflex well I told my
mother I'm going and um she was pretty
surprised I would think so did she say
no no but yeah she didn't say anything
but then the mayor came by to convince
her
oh listen Mr Kenny there's a reason why
I want to come along with you cuz I love
you reason what do you mean no cuz I'm
adopted and I want to get out of that
crazy woman's house now
she stole me it's crazy my
mom she's not my real mother yeah yeah
yeah yeah that's what I was
saying I don't think either of them
realize I know but I overheard them
discussing it a long time ago I told
you
yum oh
really so you want to search for your
real
mother oh is that my quest my personal
Quest
I don't have anything to go on besides
this pendant
a but the fact that whoever gave birth
to me cared enough to give me this
pendant I think she must have loved me
at the very least I think she did
yeah what about the mom you have now Wes
is the one that raised you I can tell
she has a lot of love and affection for
you what about her feelings don't be so
logical and reasonable and w w w w
[Music]
I I love her she's the only mother I
have so why all this
then just feels like I need to see
her I want to know what I really am
where was I born why was I in the sacred
Forest where did this power of mine come
from but more than anything else I want
to know what happened to the woman who
gave birth to me wait she's the hero of
light I'm not going with you because I
want to leave my Village May I'm going
because one day I will come back here
again
maybe it's getting late I'm sorry I
brought all this up always has been no
no
it's wait the always has been meme is
even suitable cuz like isn't it like in
space and they're in space
good
night someone must recreate the meme
with these people pointing at each other
always has
[Music]
been good night you can sleep on the
bridge or under the bridge however you
prefer the house looked like a cat to me
just now but you guys can't relate now
cuz now now that I pointed out it's too
late
already but the windows look like eyes
Raina for us Mr Kenny and like ears at
the
Top Cat
pill yes sir oh not going okay it's it's
a done deal be careful out on the road
let's go of course I'll be fine as long
as Mr Kenny is with me Kim I suppose
so Reina I think it's the other way
around don't worry Mom I promise I'll be
back soon uh like 5 years later saying
goodbye like this makes it all the
better when I say hello again right a
that's a nice thing to say yeah you're
right yeah come back soon okay Raina who
are you thanks Lucien remember to be a
good boy all right who's a good boy oh
who's a good boy okay come on now
wouldn't want to keep Mr Kenny any
longer than we have
to you'd want to reserve enough time for
the trip to cross no it's best if you
set off as soon as you can so the first
thing to do is visit the king of cross
at the castle right that's correct King
he will certainly welcome you once you
show him my letter of introduction
you'll be able to gather the latest
information on what's going on from him
well I hope he already has a bride a
queen because I don't want to get into
another
big crazy drama like just now oh
definitely I know the king pretty well
myself what if what if the king also has
a crazy stone that makes him
crazy let's go then Raina oh maybe he
does maybe that's what's going to happen
like we have to free so many people from
the power that makes them go crazy see
you later mom and more and more we find
out more about take carea Stone if
things get tough you're welcome back
here anytime you we calling the
BL don't forget that this is your home I
I I I mean I won't forget it until I
remember where I really came fromet
goodbye
mom best of luck to you Mr Kenny thank
you thank you
sir thank you D Al in as we say in
German oh use art to rotate the camera
on the world map press that button to
toggle mini map magnification try and
explore every nook and c yeah
as I always do every nook and cranny
fast travel in travel to any Town shops
or dungeons that have been visited
previously open the guide map with up
and then select the destination location
on the guide map can only be traveled to
if there is that icon uh fast Trav is
not available if it's like that
okay oh nice
Overworld
map very it feels very um you know like
familiar to me Like This Is My Jam you
know this my oh the water looks nice as
hell okay I enemies we can win this I do
think since this is a sponsored stream
that you know that was easier than I
thought I went longer than I needed to
cuz I wanted to but we should probably
like end it at a good point like
here yeah it's my blueberry
jam uh so can I safe
here
yeah
okay not wobbly water yeah I think it's
a the a good point
yeah
so that was oh my God I have DMS did I
do something
wrong no
okay and that was the uh sponsor sponsor
stream for H this beautiful game Star
Ocean the Second and story
are no no messages were all
fine it was a lot of fun yeah I'm
surprised I really like it the graphics
are really nice too like normally I
think you know you guys know I'm I'm a
bit
um hard to get
into uh like pixel stuff but this is a
nice mixture of HD and
pixel and I really like Rena she's cute
and the system the whole gaming system
you know it's really familiar so you
know I feel like it's the perfect game
for
me perfect Perfect sponsorship thank you
so much Square Enix for sponsoring this
for uh reaching out to me to get me to
play this game on my stream it was an
honor and as I said I don't really have
time to like continue at the moment but
who knows about the future who
knows I did want to play like generally
more Square Enix uh
RPGs um now that we're getting more and
more perms I was feeling like you know
checking out this or that nice game you
so did they give one a link no I don't
really have a referral link it seems but
it's okay if you guys are interested
game should be out um second today uh
depending on your time zone you're
already there or maybe not but check it
out it's on on Steam H it's on
PlayStation and I think switch too right
switch as well it's like everywhere so
check it out check it out check it out
it's out in less than 8 hours
ah
[Music]
n yeah it's it's everywhere nice I love
it when games are released literally
everywhere so I can make my own choice
where I want to play it
h so thank you so much I'm going to go
back to bed after having some breakfast
cuz I didn't have anything yet but man I
love sponsorships like this thank you
thank you really like bring it bring it
to me all the jerg sponsorships I'm your
girl bring it to me I'm gladly doing all
the jerp sponsorships it's my jam my
blueberry
jam
ah K Anin SK thank you jpg is best I'm
the JP Queen and with that I leave you
for today have a nice day guys uh it's
it's almost 9:00 a.m. time for me to go
back to bed not
lingonberry uh hope you enjoyed it too
guys I think it's like really really
cute and
Charming yeah I mean I I I made maybe it
seemed like I made fun of some of the
uh dialogue a little bit but that's just
because it's funny and cute and and you
know I'm not making fun of it I'm just
um teasing
it I I really enjoyed it I really liked
it I want to play more so who
knows yeah
straightforward I love the the first M
marriage
plot just like in my Roman itic
dreams so and in German we say I'll be
that's in thank you so much for the
support goodbye good night to whoever is
going to bed byebye let's
go
[Music]
happy