[Music]
me
N
ana
me
me me
[Music]
tan
ten Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
to me]
me
[music]
ben
nnnn
me
me me
tan
me
[music]
tan
me
yeah yeah
yeah yeah it
was me n me
me
yeah yeah
yeah yeah it was
tan
me
[music]
me me
[music]
me n
uh uh uh uh uh
me uh uh uh
me uh uh uh uh uh uh uh
uh uh uh uh
uh
me
[music]
ben
uh uh uh
me
ana
nn
me
waaaaaaaaaaaaaaaan
wow
[Music]
points you by 4
applause
People with a lot of sheaths are bad, wow, it's a hassle
to make it, it's a lot of trouble,
web A future that can be made with Ann Arbor
Mmmmm
[Music]
Steps to make a sponsor cam Home
Masu Aaai Gut
This program is sponsored by the sponsor you are watching 0
[Music]
Hawawawawa
Oki Station Ima Khan to the clouds 2 f 1  Everyone in the pile tonight
Sana I made a little mistake at the beginning
Hey, excuse me Arthur Inbound en
Digda The closest aide is thin Spin form
Waiters Tosu Puncher Cheers Stars
Stone Opening Hall 4  s cheering squad
elegance spd nawo the b 2 e
3 parlor staff intersanfan
serve the booin
anp to do smart ride
blue pump m b half feel water
weeds spu
joy tour a let me explain this to you
s entertainment bgm sound  Ramen Jr.
Come on, it's hard to use Fokker for powder warts, peace
and focus day, my champlin,
win jab and love each other.
News Mansion Eun-soo and
once bewith Esper Sobo
Wa-ite No. 4
Takanashi Kiya
Real Bear This is an interview talk show aimed at English-speaking countries.The
purpose is to
explain Japanese talent to overseas people while interpreting Nam.  I'm
going to ask you to give
it to me.I'll send it to you as a courtesy of Cure.
japanese The pink bow that says No. 3
Cha is today Spoon-ku ramen
Barb Washuyama Sora-senpai completed As usual, I
write a lot of notes in English or Japanese,
but please feel free to use it on Twitter and give me your
impressions and the answers answered by 8 Sora-senpai  Please
make a lot of changes about it and more. Please keep
posting 7 tweets.
Hey, this is the 15th time the collapse has happened.
Akam Charlie 5 Paving pt
can begin 4 Delete Iska normal
deapres You can choose your big party feelings
Turquoise's late father, who was very nourishing in martial arts, is a
light brown who is interesting.
It didn't feel like it was finished yet, so I
thought it would be better to write Sora-senpai a little later.
So today I finally read it.I
read it because I thought I had no choice but to call you.Ta--
So, general consultation
[Music]
How are you, Kasora-senpai?
Hey, hey,
hey,
it's a complete loss.It's okay to start in Japanese,
but it's okay in English.  It's okay, but please say hello.The
worm was bruised and
paid
off.I'm hungry.  I
want to know a lot of deep and interesting things,
so I want to dig into it, so
thank you for your
support Day.  I should have cured it
Factor Moon
a
dv When will Gates' boots be bulletproof? Hey
Senpai, say Noworld and use a perspective stick
Well,
now a Let's go to the first question now 8
Hey,
Jajajaan, I
have a question.
What kind of activities are you doing in the future?
Welcome. Lately, I've
been wasting my right hand on zodiac events.
Also, I've been playing Minecraft and
mainly streaming Lawnsing Saga 3. We
chat occasionally.  I haven't posted any videos of ``I tried singing, I tried singing, and I tried singing.'' It
's more like we're talking about games and things like that.
Polo aso
car John C
Rebase
14th
terese
Mare Roron Lone Server
Drone Sagar What I've
been doing lately is God
Romance in Saga Affui
Pour NC Has Free Musway
Bouche + N Played Spanish Cedar
Sawar Shuccha 3 Mac Soap
Rose  girls There are a lot of delicious fish
Sugin cover air So
then nyaa
Umm character activity support a That's right,
out of that, what's the
most fun? It's
fun to do.
What's behind the rise of streaming? For example, games,
karaoke, and small talk. It's
hard to do, after all, but I
like Unpa's author Non. It's like that karaoke streaming. I
learned about Karon Eto and Plastic's songs.  So I
started playing some classical music, and I was surprised at how quickly I
saw it.
Goods mother's feng shui
ya da-obishi-
appani-das Cats Jun is that open air
party ass in
cars music 3 person security nam
time source voice is good and house pin aru
chorion stream s web
ui serve as  Iinbu
Kita Firth Epsom c Ajawin
Faith Amo After that song is classical
Speaking of that song, I
wonder if the opera is also classical?  I was
learning about Ramune, right?
If a female puppeteer was coming, I would sue
her and sing the
song. I
heard it on a stream, but
when my senior came up with the opera sound, the rear guard was a
bit surprised.  I heard that some people said that my voice was
n't really suited for opera,
but it was said that it was suitable for idol books,
but
when I showed off my voice on the stream, everyone was amazing.  I
think you were surprised and I want to hear more too. I'm
happy.
[Music]
Buber
Rays Vienna
4 NF Star Watch Shush is
Iron Blackchan Harbor Affin
Group C
Undo Swing Power On Screen
Buorn's Pressure 4 ago mo
ose Chan teaser room
Well,
what kind of person should I go to next? I
often see comments about sewing on Sora-senpai's stream,
but what is ``Nun''?
What is a flame? Umm,
I was responding to everyone's comments,
but
I often said things like, ``Yeah, that signal 2,'' ``
Maria'', and for
some reason,
everyone listening seemed to be able to hear it not because of luck, but because of something.
When I heard Unazuki say ``Yeah'' and ``Naa'', that's when I first started
adding this emoticon, ``A'', ``How many years'',
and ``I've been waiting for you.''  I
use the word ``deki1 nannanun'' to express my feelings in various ways.Um,
ga hai, iiinun is a word that I can use as well.her
the air
Shinsantan Part 1Add a healing starMen's
a  all to work Business negotiation
Darcy 4
Appscape Grand Commander 2 Minutes
Promise of Youth
Say yes to Presage with Unun
wanon
voodoo Plan C I'll die Yes,
I'm going to propose a prison fen for Pikan Kaan Up Is Kyokoen
already inside and
wear satin?  Zakoide
Arumou Njaana wo Say
asamin use user Nun
to space ocher India
fewings
cute shrimp cure
There's a lot of girls like this today too. I'm
not sure if I'll be able to hear it or not. It's been a long time since I've known it, but I'm sure it's all the same. Attochiro, which club's member might be cuter? I'm really lucky, but I haven't included two. Nice Abe Inter sweet catch.  Hyun
Rune is 2 day Honsorasen Pashi
Lander Caesar A book a 5 a You
Tomikawa Hitonu
and other pace producers
air
I think.
That's very good at guarding the complete defeat. How
did you study up until now?
[Music] I
don't know if it's good or not, but I'm good at it. Ah, ha, around 10 years
ago, there was literally Japanese video diplomacy. Yeah,
there's a house with someone in it.  In the cat,
[Music] I
went to Kaitei Eto and
played Eternity until I was about 4 years old.Well, I don't think
I learned anything else.  I do
n't think so, but
since I was listening to non-native English with my ears, I
think I remember the pronunciation of my face and hands.Hmm,
that may have been effective. Hey,
uso r 4
seamen big
boo.  we are
ready for
speciale rcos 2dec 1
good or 4x fin doubler type
opener ca storage bar sea star 4
every turn
yeah yeah
g  Shimai Luffy and Silent Dahl's
Effect Nah Doboishi
Pixar Pin Gunshin and Wish + Jello
#So Yaa 1 Japanese Plan
C New SEO Valenti
Sono is French English Newspaper Times Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa to that
baby to
that sora-senpai's
English pronunciationsaaaaaaa
Every time I listen to it  What's good about this is his amazing gaze.That's what I
thought.I
don't have any confidence in my grandfather at all, so I
wonder if he can speak Baru English.
Hun is getting a little anxious Hmm, it's
completely conveyed to me, nature, Spe Lu,
web server web,
winner 2 on,
Twingo's tumor-sensing last part, bod
ust bully, Andy Stones,
Bob Daisei's club dance plan, Hidetoshi Anpo  The
curve is more than a tour
Yeah, apen 9th floor zombie star bribery
want you come motion no
eye 3 t money cheap operator 4 a 5 points
Everyone is saying the same thing.
Hmm, I guess I'm wearing a
penis for free, erc.
Hehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehehe Well, then I
asked you out.Have
you
been studying English more actively lately?  I do
n't know if I'm proactive about it, but
people leave comments and things like that, so
when I'm feeling down, I read them all
and try to find out what they mean.
Even now, I want to be like that, so I
'm still working hard little by little. Large
Scarpe Wing Scarm
Nordeus E 2 C 2 S 4
Nod Wildebeest C Wood Minna Moon
Stone Suo Seeds Fines Pickup Village
Wings Whisper Affisti
Anne
First, let's say it to the first person in Atsugi
a Sora-senpai Bar What kind of activities do you do other than broadcasting? I wonder if it's
radio, acting,
concerts, etc. Aeto
distribution After all, I
said it earlier, but...  I sang
at music events and such,
and then I went to the
2 year old Bike Day
TV Day program where I
acted as a character called Sanjito Watanuki.  The
groups and main cast members that I was the main character in, I
acted, I
appeared on auteur event
programs, and I was also a regular on the radio,
so I talked, sang,
and did all kinds of activities
without any trouble.  I feel like I'm receiving it.
4 I wonder if they're not doing radio anymore. I guess they're
all done now, but I go to them so much
that I go to them.
Events are the
main activities of Petter's Ta-Moon.  I
think it's the sound ren
over cc down spun
spa form audi music
esri burner ii general event
4 award pipo pour
ender 2 user4 sub cd 2
amplifier acting domain caste warlord
coat crotch production area Zao Ohata key no
a  Work Main Car Stay 2 Rangers Cucumber Sauce
Heating Expected Dinner Bar
Wii Open 2 Spoons Sea No
One Driving Zone to Put Him in No Media
Pantene Delicious & Runaway Adapt 4 s
1 And then es Mizu surface r Muse
Qura's Anger Mizuko Activities Serge
Sua de Porigar music Yay Couple Yes,
so amazing so many They're
doing so many different activities Yes, there are so
many mayors who don't get it  I think there are,
but if you only look at what you can see, it
seems like it's hard to see those people in the sea.
Akufu Royalty
Dohosei Spansukeno f Mura Wii Wii
Wordpad Club Edion Toru Tibi
Power Game No Words
Muse Key Men's IP Te Pot
Cap is Thin Futon and Standing
Turbo C & Vienna
Hosomura Procedures So
Shall We Go 8
Drive  How did you start with Sora-senpai?
How did you get together and form the group?
In the beginning,
A-chan started
talking about wanting to be an idol together, then...  It
started from a place where I thought I'd give it a try. I've already seen it.
At that time, it wasn't something
I actually started distributing on YouTube,
but after I became a farmer, I started distributing it from a place called anti-glycation.
It was a military doctor.  It
's the 7th day of February 2010 for raw noodles.
In the beginning, the number of people saved us, and we
said let's do a lot of things. It's the
first time. It's the
first broadcast.  I
think there were about 50 people who came to see it, but they were from NicoNico Douga.But,
of those
8 years ago,
30 of them
were acquaintances of Canal Ninfa.
Wow,
that's why the people who came to see it without knowing anything,
ah, they weren't in the same police station.  I've
been called the Knights of the Round Table by people overseas, so I
'll omit this part.
Yeah, I'm going to omit this part. Yeah, it's beautiful Nishibu-san.
Faiz is always here, so it's
okay if you always stick to summer.  And the
difference between the weapons of the Spanish bar is
ok Nico Nico Douga is over
and it's God. 5 YouTubers and phone Japan
Ta and the fast marriage Tinton are
good.  japanese salt plum you
do with maa ni wa tara utara au pair toverse
7chin
7op sepchan burger de berry ari
view rack 10 times
[music]
starduster so good r
diffuse srt 7 e 4 a pi
part 4 n 4 n for surf pure
wool
after nya  Aaa wiffi pinpo
wow handshake bd re grand moeno
zabu fame steam rice 4 air
parse wo daddy
anv t  If not, Soran-senpai will pass ad
Word Writer Air
Tweety Meow
If there's a continuation of that, please do so.However, it will be continued in Areare, and it was
really the first time I've ever streamed it in Asoka, so I do
n't know anything about it.The
background is pure white, but there's no scimitar, and there's no en.  I
didn't have an expensive set or anything like that.
Color: Even though
I move a lot,
Ahara used a stand microphone.
It's like that kid whose voice gets distant when he moves. Yeah, that's terrible.  I
felt a little embarrassed when I saw the amazing broadcast on the building, but I also
felt a great deal of excitement about doing something for the first time, which is
how I first started doing it and
what I thought about it at the time.  But
I actually watched the stream yesterday, and it was amazing. She looked so
excited and childish, and I
thought it was kind of cute.
[Music]
So she did her best and talked a lot.  I
thought it was amazing yeah
nearest cd none mail
over oso polly re
soooo pg & with no
back inch and by bacon
today sydney harbor head
rev audi s ufo mike 4
ne's pad close bac mu
wow  Return Charlie Mike
Folder c
Half Nursery Bo Grove Parand Parents Issopuyo Pepe
and Hughes Trees pile up branch 64 moving
The secretion is right, that's right, the sound of Sochisbon Jutsu Liam
Nakarei is starring
voodoo s de to
do for da
pattern yan girl is going to
go 0 fe yo yes already at home for a moment Mr. 2
this time is that
this long chase home  It didn't exist yet,
because each person was unique.
On the other hand, there was no such concept,
so I guess they
are active in the same sound as me.  There were so many people that I
could count the number of people I visited. Hey, that's
amazing.
[Music]
Everywhere I go, I feel like I'm away from the
center.
Urban way.
Comes with a stool chain ess Palms and cheek register sr a Let's raise the means to make an appointment
Hayako-san was there at that time Of
course, it was a  In the middle of the
day, I
told my child that I wanted to do
something like this, so how did I tell my child that I wanted to do something like this
?It was
just a virtual activity.
ni Nakata Bancoa I
saw the likes and got some money. It was
like the environment was set up right
when I was posing. So aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa The
rower is the worst and is refreshing
o i s house eye cream  Ease
green way aiff floating
wizardry this company's
company surf de fox and
pain zu i s ha ha e so
good house tome fos the
day we always meet we are step on
quiet voodoo 3 people as five
star good jako san pelorifiskar
loan woah  Team Voodoo
Click All Pointer Lure Point
CO Collar Hard Woodo N Order
Voodoo Popings-
like  byemsr air And
from there, I
said, ``Well, let's make it the office of that manager.'' It was
during a Saturday trip to Edo that I felt like, ``Well, let's do something about this, not just Sora-senpai,
but a bigger person.''
Well, I didn't
really get into that kind of thing, because
that wasn't the type of thing I
was at the time, and I was like, oh,
there's something like this.  I
feel like I've never heard of a detailed reason or anything like that.Today,
I'm a medical
student, and Ida Buntanhi
is a weapon.
3 more big panty goods join fingers
soo crew i
are you doing
birdie you're done with the girl you're so cute
Koide-san 4 esper in the picture of being reluctant
Arthur, pip up 1, Germs.
It's good that you haven't stopped meaning for a long time. No, I do
n't know. Hammer to do f.
Arm bar.
No, it
's an open leader. It's ice sports. ano. How did you feel when you were told that a new member was joining?
Ah,
well, at that time, there weren't many people there, and I had the impression that I was all alone.Of course, we were going to
do it together outside, but I opened it just now, and there were
n't many of us, so I was all alone.  We
were in a situation where there were only a few people, so I was
really happy to see some kind of new wind, some new people coming, and along with that, I
felt a sense of responsibility that I had to make things even more exciting.  That's what I thought. Hmm,
that girl is sooooooooooooooooooooooo! Booklet line
isa one for air
pressure berwick house
coer Ted n Anchi boss is definitely a problem with
lattice beautiful breasts g's old age
push up powder car with
no  body ended 22 nc
bose aura poop party
licking down usu kayanshi hazombie bar parka
f
crm fin club ender
ender ender
wayup
audi s 4 not to do
sabers windu hyperon
up love ranger ecchu be
more
aobane gekka kanbei stability  But Daphna Yuta is stopped
by Ursa 6 5 response
brooch Bar Picasso Statian I see
Evera 8 I
mentioned it a little bit.  The
next question is, what was it like when you streamed it in the early days of your seniors?Are there any
similar changes compared to now?
Bunji I said a little more earlier,
but really a 13 At first, there were
some sounds with no background.  From about that time onwards, I
only broadcast live videos once on Thursdays, and it
lasted for about two years. That's
right, it's a long body samba.
I didn't see many broadcasts of Black to Other Girls,
and most of them were videos, so it makes me wonder
if it actually exists.Gar
wasn't very active like that, but
well, we
're in this era now.
Well, I've been able to do a lot of different activities without worrying too much, like once a week, because my stream has increased, and I do
n't know what to say.  I
was wondering if his style had changed to show more of his personal side. I see. What made you do that? After all, the other members love you so much, so I feel like I have to do it too.
Maybe it was more of a neutral place, like
Donner.When I
was in a house where I made videos,
I actually didn't really give my opinion, and of
course there were 23 songs, but I did
what I was told not to do.  Like
There were a lot of things that were passive, passive, and
passive, and yeah, I don't know what to call one or the other.I
didn't feel like I was doing what I wanted to do, and I got to that point.As expected,
it would be strange if I slept in a twin bed, which was tough at the beginning.  Well, I've been
working on it for two years since no one knew about it,
and honestly, on the
day of my high school graduation, I was
thinking about whether to quit or not.  I thought that
maybe I should do streaming so that I could
do what I
wanted to do, but I might as well quit and just go to university or something like that.  I
wanted to do something that I could do.I
thought it might be a good idea to try it.It's
okay to use a
male
arlene bar
wrestling a day.
hex big star 4 as ah
austrie first wii 9 b 2
add member hesperia d swing
arm oa
procare 9
senaste i turn r d
staff pubic hair larp to some people
show normal 6 pod week
saung c 1 e 2
kodaira private pass now  ichipapepo a
manor wa poster water
road with nha 1 makers
this chinespechange ni 33
paan
voodoo saa editing
smooth briefing ah color
life 4 asce adder new
watano i want to do
a coin pingshu wish
storybo peep order i do
do figure godard rowdy host fur
way
on
force to
do after a bar jewelry
high score r lamp intern sieve
figure bag  wedding 4 s is
rentrer en do
do me finger co to
do candy too land people and
patty garden map strong derby minute
mortimer farward fc hard  To
do
FORARPER ASTD 2 Stream L 4 Star Your Hers Finn's Patchin Finn Patchin Tip Nyar It was good that I didn't quit very much.  There
were times when I felt like I was at my limit when things got tough.
[Music]
After all, the events there are so warm
and everyone feels like family, so it's great.  I
wonder if it's a form, and it's been a long time since I've been in that kind of place. Kana: It's not like I was able to make an announcement until it was completed. It wasn't good when I was using it, but it was completed, and I couldn't really say it to a map machine when I announced it.  There
were a lot of opinions on the tour, such as "7 tickets,"
but I couldn't accept them, and it was more
profitable for me to feel like Sly.
There was also the fact that they didn't respond to that,
but I still
didn't have too many people supporting me, and I might get angry at them for supporting me.There were
staff members and managers, so yeah, it was
more
fun.  I wonder if it's okay to think that a I think uh
ok size thin teacher aan
ano point
bacar
torrente me to do
a
areas for as
enodeb t 4 f performance
sa 4  nordeus ac 5 e
nod see me want me to
do
app puter words are
you doing
win an tocp market ana
unsongping kindergartener exe n
by shoes ver t honmachin
denso
poi poi ya p boastful buzzer 2
[music]
voodoo feffer  Uchan 4 a
party pos powder noa
star hoodie weeks
[music]
agnelli fair 1 managed to
nboinjoy minutes  ng scene 5 c
20 b already pro rtf park drive
e get hmmm already rap sound
yeah
jan 4 mob large edition line all 4
surfer
movie boots enjoy already haesung mail
order and garoon
duffy woman power stone I see
and
no, it's quite
that deep story  I asked you to tell me, but I've
prepared a scale of 8 here, so let's take a look at it together.Phoenix
First of all, I like shellfish with the two lines that should be on Chan.
ao Still pump version dyed dipping
roses are terrible m sky fu dice
shop enjoy telling bar tatsuno
burger let's move yes
but the place started right away spa spreel limited
if you can use it then yes this is made of ceramic
department place too let's
dress the rice  Well, there are
a lot of people in the Shaka Frets year.  I
was just saying, ``zero, Kise,''
and it doesn't feel weird to say that. Hey, I didn't think it was zero.
I
thought, Wow, don't waste what you're doing.  I guess
that was the only thing I could think of in the middle of the day. Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaoh
I, too, have a lot of restrictions on my body position,
but I'm like, oysters, lotus root, eggplant, Icchan, and Nakahama.I'm
just a pile of sympathy, and I'm like Rin on the roof.That's
how I am, because all of those kids are like
that.  Circus
Boo-boo, it's a solo live,
that's the tile consultation, isn't it? Eros aaah, commonly known as a
solo live,
nunnnn
[Music]
Hey,
zero doesn't mean 6, it starts and goes until now.  You're
saying something nice, that's good, Nipo-nii.
Thank you. It
says that if you do everything, it's fine.
Stop playing game solo.  It's
true
that they're a team, but it
's strange that it's just one side.Hmm, the
flames are over her.Let
's loli over her, so it's personal.  I
was thinking, but I'm not in a hurry because the bullying is not good, so I
went to the Meiji Restoration and went to the
cow pen, and there were a lot of customers.
For me, I have
never had this kind of thinking before, and 0 regulations
means that there is nothing,
and
I think this means that the store has set a deadline and a beginning.  I've
always thought that way, so I'm going to air it.Next
question: Neko Momentary Aids bout a I
think Sora-senpai often plays with Zero Regulation, but please let me know if you have any memories of how smart the girls are.Yes, the
girl called Zero Regulation.
There are 5 people in total, right?
Me,
Azuki-chan, Hoshisue
Comet-chan,
Nagura Miko-chan, and the long-established Ko-chan weather person. If they
joined later, they would have debuted at the same time.  When I
say that, my head is a completely different color. I don't know
when the current chief of staff will come after Nashi, but I wonder
when it will be. I've
been overthrowing it ever since I said that I should recognize it.
Miko-
chan is probably the next one to join the engine, but
in reality, Atsuki-chan,
Midori-chan, and
Miko-chan joined much later than the 1st generation.
There were quite a few maiden girls at the time when they entered the canopy, so
in that sense, the egg regulation
gave the impression that they all entered at the same time, so even though they all came in
at different times, they were all lumped together.  I'm so glad that I mentioned
something that made me feel so uncomfortable about what was going on. It's an
episode, but after all,
everyone said earlier that it's almost time to go live.  I
think it was a team made up of kids who couldn't join at any time and
debuted alone,
but they all have unique and free aspirations,
huh?  Hey, Minecraft, it was especially
noticeable when we did it, and everyone seemed to be able to
move around freely.When we started
playing dog, we
talked about it behind the scenes, and it turned out that
each of us debuted at different times.  I
could totally talk about things like, ``It was a rainy climate,'' but it's
not like they're all the same.I
thought it was interesting because they were going in different directions.When the
three members met for the first time, they were
really nervous, and ummm...
Niko Is it like Paso Boiler up to the 1st place senior? I don't know, but it's already a
mess.
At that time, I went in right away,
but when he came out to hand it over to me, he was so
nervous that he seemed so nervous and stuffed up.It was impressive, and he looked
completely different than he does now.Hmm, you know,
Mr.  It's because it's a, so it's okay.
Before we met, Unnaka-chan
sent me an illustration of Joubi, which
really left an impression on me.
Um, the ship I can't get over right now looks like I'm
going to join soon. The
girl who said it was a present was a  It's the
first time I've ever said that I'm
getting food before I meet you.It's
a really funny episode.This doll is interesting.Well, I took it, but I was so happy.I think I'll eat it.  Let's do
an translation, run,
Tai-an, Puri Tokoro Louvre and
estnation Pumoi 3rd place
Apartment is strong and it's good Perth
Number is Pu-nyan as Azuki
Senpai Comet Senpai, 3 Horrors, Senpai Roboko Senpai,
Profile Koi to Memorize and Dinner Debut,
Tsukebaeeee, long-established store Temairi and prose day, Female
doctor's room Berry, braided, that's a complete defeat,
old tree senpai post office, punch,
signature, enen-an bill, Suzu  Boob mo is
f' b cars fledging war breast milk
drawer space time eup 2nd generation senpai body ouu
senpai
kainu joint 4 meek  Senpai
field # ebe r de 4 avc
join an dar video streaming puta ya
Fuji super view day day shrine maiden
violation web for a
zu fielding body ah usually after
dozen one to join sb
Mars oil p Azuki 3
Pink girl down way learn
beauty beauty Misuzu stunt subtitle tea also momentarily
added vape sensibility and 10 pieces of land all over
center nsenpai
voodoo rice wilbur pollin
ramone 2 group home
denen bar r sr
uso
cardenas so life bread dear
rt n bath
style joint 1 bye bye why
on earth yeah arm ota baby
unique little 2 d blue moon style
vienna vienna  and webber related well
india mi birds answer
jasana
deir aan first
undo
ater 4 mp
doaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Wet targ bicarb booster
King Teen's day kinder is constant 5
type star with powder immediately on
the surface suraped male api
sub
meet senior way megu spraying handicrafts by the landlord
but i see toilet room sy guy
fennah.  x sa winger
coding stria big surfer
fornication anden oncreate
sting story
water to
do
aren owner
re with 4surelyshire
unamp 4 se pop us  2
slot senpai
causa noose with chain
kono ra
caf loha minute teacher who do solo
spec piece powder in cello sound
4 cool saf whistle gyu 2 no
bar nabetsu midway through front and bar stealing intern
dalhodo
hey it's possible um 0th generation student  Do you have any memories with the members
? Can you think of anything right now? The
best thing about Edo is the 0 regulation. I wonder if it's
good. It's Azuki-chan who sings the same song.
archi  We get along so well that we usually go out to eat,
and the fourth child plays together, but
you know,
Azuki-chan is
really good at arts and crafts, I guess.Yeah, when we
play games, we do,
but
Falling Head also decided to play games with us.
When I asked her out, she said something like, ``If I want to do something, I'll do it.'' I wonder if you'll say something like ``If I'm with you,'' you
say, ``
You're the one who likes this game.''
When I said "let's
do it," she said it was so
cute that she didn't even
serve the food.Well,
she
came back to the last live show to sing a birthday song, but she
had a key voice that sounded like she was being selfish.  Whenever there's a song, I'll join in the chorus.
22 is always in a great mood,
and when
I'm alive, I'm like, oh,
go oil type. There's something about Oikawa that
makes me think, "That's
great."
I'm starting to fall asleep, but there are times when I
feel like I want everyone to see that part of me without showing it to me beforehand.
ane
ccf center seas close to
rear 4 fde
noor jehan member esad
goes totally gay barwary
ebase uno
wig wig blogger
asora 30,000 yen by azuki senpai a little  The
game is too good, Azuki-
senpai's recovery is with Ki-es-a-a, the
film is on the rampway during the day, the increase is
on Monday, the language is blue sky, and the
general branch office is a white one, and it's a little good hosting
web, and if I get hurt, join me
feel, that's the war criminal, Azuke surfer.
Monk of 4 pure plus
pathway bed line and worth
ti 2 volume 3
nmana bar
forever blue s 4 to
ann
fai lege witcher 2
windows me  Buson dog
oase boo
boo loose high speed pop
old feeling belfry
with helper senpai aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
4 kids party waiting for aspure dare to
surf wants
you so uh Spib Choiti's
Beppu Bunen cute t residence Cure
Kyumperafufu
Sora  Hey, Azuki-senpai, you're so cute.
Thank you for letting me hear such cute stories.
Yeah.
Indian Indigo,
Sky,
That's like that couple's older sister.
Yes, we're called Sollers, and we
sing,
stream, and take care of each other. We've
become really good friends, and we've
even written a number of Unsollers duets.  There is o
ca erwin d star normal
Dosoraa ending day The
moon course is also 7 minutes Daha Fufubububufu
Fufuheson Scabbers are you
AEON Satoshi Ichino
Let's pick up the pace a bit from here, let's
coco color
Jajaan,
turn, it's plain,
Cran Pla-senpai, are you ready?
Oh, say Lee,
ok,
gateway, Won Senki is Aso,
and thermos, which one?  It's okay
English version of Kamen Khan My
Way
Instagram Hmm Ah
okay Wings or orange juice
Ah I'm
rooting for you I'm going to
run a mountain climbing car marathon
Hmm fiber number match
Computer or comedy comedy, I'll
put it in the computer's voice without retiring.
That's it.
I Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
.  My
mother who travels with me. I
like the face T
and the wings.
Do I wear a naked royal robe when I go to sleep? Do I
turn off the fog? Excuse me.
[Music]  The
wig that was there is a sloop-proud fishery guess
Dad's favorite event Halloween
face Easter Tanabata etc. It's
really zect Dokan phone call
card wrong girl
That impregnable wall and that disco chat and the
electric field to buy I don't know which one is better
[Music]
Funeral Dondo  I'll give you a functional gift from the nest tower. Do you
want to give it to me?
[Music] I'll
walk the distance to another station in the cabin, so I'll
get on Data.
Aoki Anfer Station. I'm already wearing my pants.
How many miles is yellow?
Atsuibu eh Agon Kei Cas Yes big He
pushed me and let's do it
Papa
[Applause]
Re color to
do Graphic who do ya
4 I'm sorry for asking this question in general in the last question thread,
but a I also asked him properly.
Shisa up
By the way, I don't know what to wear or not to wear.The
answer is that the pain is Bugei-chan's wart.The
soft part system is made of resin Machida finished zone.  I
was in Yao City when I found out about the Web Festa.Then
when I saw Pia's underwear, I was in
shock.Sora
Senpai.I
think it would be better if the panties grew out.Yeah,
Aito.  Good maa chan
dizzy Udyshubu lapin t
see also
precase the fuse face good
mar let's go back to what's going on
a  Please tell me about Ankiba. Who is Akimoto? A
Half term
Wow,
my plenty ore Yeah,
Ankiba-chan is good. Well, I
wonder how many times it's been broadcast. As much as I want to relax, the first one was smiling and smiling.
Yay.  It's
my stuffed toy that appeared around the time I was Robin,
but I was sleeping at home...Kuma-san
started to walk and started walking.
The squirrel was buried again, and it became a hot topic that appeared on my sister's broadcast.Everyone
didn't have a name, so they
said, ``Hey, bear.''
Well, I'm an
anti-person, and I'm
not good at memorizing anything.  It's
called memorization, and when I
was talking about how I'm not good at it, I was
told that if I'm not good at Anki, why not just do Kumamae Anki?I went
to Europe and America.  I
submitted various candidates through various questionnaires, but the overwhelming number of people
decided on the name, and it felt like the name of my teddy bear had
become unpopular.Let's
delete it.
Wow, see an
key is also the boss's fondo baby
erase you do spree
motion
voodoo Nico Nico Douga Nanii 2 The
world is a mountain how it's a pull water  It
feels good enter a none so
rice-like how do
do
andere
arlen rice
arlen
enas 5 e bar boom
good s infaing Musa-
chan one layer a
beshi leader
polo 2 eba r for some
reason ebo
render tree Ninguankin
mo
witch ok guard expein
english sean liver wedge amin
fighting song well leg os
objectden htb web line
Butters It's not difficult with a name like that,
even the professional idiot sister is bear wish-san
Kimono memorization thing Anki Japan Nut
Booth Fish Weber is good
rde habit see who
do barbie emn da border It's
difficult Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa, it is
difficult to say that it is a barbie emn da boarder.
How do you say "memorize" in English?
Just memorize is a memo. It's
okay because it's in A-chan's memory, but if you
get a big one, you can't worry even for a moment.
Well, there's no formal way to write it,
right? Ah, I don't think it's
different. Well,
there's a way to write kanji and kanji in stores,
so please go ahead and match it with that. Eh, that's the way it is.
That's
what Japan's turn is.
Renkon Gluttony 3 Base Discon
Vines Web Ordway
Dade N
Meisobi Tweets in the Land Habitsho Blu-ray
Good evening chapfa
Rufer psalm mi swing one
way chain 2
Anki family
Adeyu tomorrow's stander daddy
neroeee
Ando Capilene Span personnel is
probably the stupidest ender soaping
scan app minute meeting style penny
Golfer says friday ok
someday ah  It's the wind. Probably 4 people. It's
okay. I'm in my 30s. I do
n't have enough translation skills, such as that Japanese translation of the steam hole. Bye
Maron If you
have blue lips, Choijapa 214 Vie  I
wanted to say a little more about the idea of just devising a ride bag.
That's how I memorized it without sparing it.
That's Senpai A. I
heard that you were fighting about something, but
what was the difference between that and
memorization? Nana.
Hmmm
Nananu
Ah ah ah ah
ah ah ah
ah ah Ah Marker Jealousy Anh,
what a jealous jealous jealousy?
Yeah
Good car
If you put it together, it will be a cheap Benz or
that
water-based waste water generation
1 pme
Aaahtame
Haikyu
Ukara and Ankei view bar wiki
anus Ti
reic center shure star
is wi-fi to
do pump campus good senior
barter Re
ok I can't take care of it  Well then, there's no need to
worry because she's the cutest even in the main hall of the Beginner's Foot Sage. I'm
sure everyone is just joking.
Well, that senior you're jealous of is cute.
Are you a great person with a good vibes?
47 Jazzla really hasn't changed,
and the sky line showdown cure is delicious. The
sound of clothes rushing is loud.  That's about to end, senpai.
Let's go to one question. It's
about the 8th House of Councilors, but I'd
like you to tell me about Moho Live and the production of Terror.
Yes, I'm also having a Horo Live error right now.  I've been
doing it all year round, and I've been doing it in an error-like way, like "follow,"
but it's like saying something like, "Hey, but, let's see, can you please stand up?"
Well, the
internal error in Halo is different from before.The
names of the Capacity car,
everyone's names are
slightly distorted, but they're different.I
feel like I'm playing someone else.Ah, there's
something like that.  I
feel like it's difficult, but
because of that feeling, I feel like I've
become a different me than usual, and I've been able to do a lot of things.I
still have a long way to go, but I
don't have a plastic umbrella on my body at all.  I
can't say it, but
as a tz, I
wonder what he's
going to say.He's like, ``Look at me!''Mai
Honoko is so natural.  The
content Pixar town festival kettle is limited,
so horse silk melo is a contestant, the
party and post bar are hitting the Horai persimmon hot water bath, the
asifon is jumping on skis, it's
strong, yeah yeah
jan 10
sa bb computing
computing sound
voodoo chest  Press the snow
er 3 p with the bing
subway Define Farm Winner
Nice sound Eunju also sequencer
Ipai a
Ainoda Placenta Weeks 4 Station Staff
Sora Sora-senpai
Well, you see, Japan is just like Iris Skin, right?
Even if you drink, you can play a horror game
without reacting, that's the point of Senpai's Gyuname.  Are
n't you scared? Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa With
that with me, I'm really bad at what's
inside so please tell me how to not get too strong.I'll
get rid of my doubts.Ah
[music]
duper api
Yeah.
Yeah, I
guess the game isn't that good. I'm more concerned about Olly, and I'm more excited about it than the fear. It's a bit thrilling and sometimes, I don't know. I'm worried about the future, so I don't play much, so I'm thinking about what's going to
happen in the future.  I wonder if
a meat frame like this will appear, and
if you have something like that, it will become like a kiter,
amalie It's not work
irb to do m 4 Audi a
4 ting mmm naa ksk rover
oreno xg 4 minute form bar
ber 4 s how can you
do my year nuts cad vibe
torment nikyu can bring star 1
rase gamer futo rover
artism ic sophie os
speaker sushi fox already rondo
stoneberg  dart Tosu game
Per Essen 4 losses and no dates in a month
Stone win pyg on powder board harp
Zuba Woody Epox Zone
Nonda Pop Perth Moonstone Ya
Motoko's Spy Club Enza Woodard Scape I
My favorite horror game because it's super unshakable is
Wash 5 Sendai
Bay Bridge Parcare
There are a lot of them, but
that's it.  In the sense that it was fun to do,
Kagerou oooo
klear Green Spur Udonchoi
TMO Spoonwicker Gero
again Kargie's Dealer Snow
Air
Schreier
army car  Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaha, I
guess she's the type of person who speaks Japanese, I know
Aoto, who likes it.Oh, I've never smoked trap.  It
seems like he wants to do it,
but he's happy. It's a
really strong border. Yeah, it's a
horror movie, but there's
no nudity. I think
it's better not to do it. But, well, that's for the first half. That's what I recommend.  I
think I can do it, but
I'm sure there
's a Japanese version.It's called an embroidery channeler for the number of people who go beyond the bomber.I wonder if there's a Japanese version.
5 of them
are important. How about Isara with Senpai?
Please come and see me on the day of my death. Ah,
Lucco, I wonder if it will
be less scary if I go with Senpai.
[Music]  I don't know
what to say, but I think it's a one-person game,
so I guess I'm in a state where I'm
in a mental state, so I'm going to a school by myself,
talking Luka, leading me
to that, and Gra-chan wants to go to me, too.
Even if it's a touch, I don't feel very relieved.Ahaha, I'm in
auburn from the beginning of the new calendar.It's a
weak reaction, so I do
n't think SAAS will work.
Both door chandra bought a house right away
and it's delicious when you wake up
love Dale Arn us coc ugly men
scene and 6 Mr. Palmingway's persuasion
bonton game webber
chick p dare to
charmy date panties to bureau part time job 8 gran
soap  Nide Patty's Grachan
Profile Mappy Wait
Inditch Eishon So Iya
Ets Hon 4 n the
blues pin 43 en way
Music Let's move on to the next question.Hard
Yeah, right now he's released three or three albums.That
's my senior, but he's planning to release his first cover album in November this year.Long
time until release.Rya
concept.  I'd
like you to tell me a lot about how to decide on Eikimeido, etc.And here's the board I
took with Esther's departure,
Capabai Coach and others, but
I haven't surpassed it.
This, this, this, this, this, oh, this is
amazing, please shave,
please, ah, yes, f 1 chain, mountain cane,
ice fish bell, ah, powder recitation wish In my brain,
this is blue + up
window, it's amazing,
ah, the ban on car sets will also be lifted soon  I think so,
so I can't say, but
in terms of the flow of time,
it's the zodiac sign, 8. It
was decided before summer that
5 will be the June issue, episode 2. It hasn't
been decided yet that there will be a cover, but
since then, well...  I'm
still a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit like
I've
always had a question about what kind of songs I like and what kind of songs I
always sing to the viewers.
Yes, that's a good
question.
Well, the song was decided live, and the
recording was
decided, and the recording was all finished in August.  I
can't go into details about the Kinkyoku since it hasn't been released yet, but it
started around June and ended up ending
on August 4th.
Well, by the way, I've finished recording various songs.  I
thought he was thinking of releasing an album,
not an original one, but I
thought it would be a good idea to release a cover album.I
think the stationery is also original,
and the original songs are delicious.
Yes, that's true. I
see.
OK ac Sadaooooooooo papicon
Scepter surfing baby big
Future soo ckt end par by
days Star Quadin 1st collection the
2 way star cold central 4 eyes pose bath
spigot barter red earth point card boo
barless dare  to
do Faster wii be
able to
Esther
Doi is doing it all the time in the office according to this
Voodoo Perfecting
Remember, good bye bye Schwantz
Powder head I've never seen such an Abuder
game, I've diluted the player's maximum
Checkers foot fitting tt
Nice for a change
true 3 items wondergoo so
with the presence of Wendy
that  Senpai, I'm counting the number of original songs I've released so far.
turn to do 30
roo
irea
renofa
[music]
noh audi a  fairy to
do
sal end bar bar Greetings today in Ikawa
on this Ebessan is here If the
marker is good, the total extension will be January yeah That's
fun
That's the fun feature of finishing in 22nd place
Jajaan
This live was operated in the early days  I think there was a time when I didn't have that much, and I
didn't have much profit.What made you believe in
libor even when that cruiser came?
Well, I've already had the answer to this question, but there were times when I
thought about giving up.  Yeah 7  It's
over, why are we doing this live? Did you
think there was any point in continuing to do it? The
first one didn't perform for
long.
[Music]
It didn't show up, so no matter
how much it didn't grow...  -
Sudo I wonder if it's going to end. I'm
waiting for the breath-taking rug. That's how much I
want to read something like that.
Actually, I didn't have any feelings, but suddenly,
well, if I'm lucky, I'll be happy. I
think it's you too.
When I'm done with this, I'm going to go here. That's why
I didn't make any progress for the first 6 months
or so. I was like, ``This is going to end in about 6 months.''  It's
like a dungeon, and
after that, I wonder if there's something really
wrong with it, like why I didn't stop when I felt like it was
going to be tough.
After all  The
words of those who support me are strong,
and when I feel like I'm not good enough, they give me
energy.
There are people who tell me that I'm so good. It
's a waste to have a 9th stop.  I've made a lot of progress over the last
7 days,
so even now I
'm still watching my broadcasts telling me to do my best.After
all, watching my broadcasts gives me comfort, and I hope I can
work even harder.  It seems like it has become
When I look at column 6 of words, I myself
am a person who can't do anything at all, but I think that what I do here will help
someone
become something, or maybe it will bring luck to someone's life.
If only I had
done that, I would have felt like a bastard.Hmm,
but I
never would have imagined that it would grow so big, so I guess I'm glad I
kept doing it and now I
have a mess.
Yeah, that's right.When I first started high school, I was really confused.It's
something you only do as a student.Ah, I
thought it was normal to quit my side job, so
when I made the transition, it was natural.
If so, I guess it's a time limit
Tone The
more I keep an eye on it, the more I
watch my older sister, the bikini action, the southern
part of the country, the booth black Folkestone scones, the
4 Evo host,
now the feeder swing girl
fight to school
lease b hall
bandana watch even see
your face
enoden b no sucess push
jenne say
herb
hpi house eng
expectation boa toei half
yay
a
cpa raffil say ms 2
access phone like
defender out how are
you doing  this cleaning
bag excuse anden ict
ndk bar pute wo posepe cars
board voice s all this
pain front and fenderless she
will see saw knee and 5
[Music]
voodoo yeah
have a
bike
cause happiness n g 4 me mad
good idea 4 shion slow go ah chick Hanyu's
pad people sister at mada wars
is pair motivation
encyclopedia tea ni nyan 3 it
's good it's
good 8
Sounds good. It's
been 5 years since you've been working as a technician.
What are you most proud of out of all your accomplishments?
[Music]
Paralive Now  I
wonder if the whole festival was completed aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa  Yeah,
at that time, I guess I thought midi chest mitts would be fast, but I
never expected it. I
thought, 7 minutes
later, I was going to be able to do something like this in front of people and have an event.
+Please bring it from everyone.
Open
By the way, it was crowded, wasn't it
? That's good. That's
right, I thought this was amazing as well
. I'm so sad that we've announced our separation.
Ah, rc center ai 4 pot
noti body.  baby ent
re shake p haa phew
remeber corelex
patch house ntice ball lore app
weiwei wiiu press armor
Bird Audience Win Post Bar 2
So
Cheap Shizujaa Be Hard Powder
Dende Way All This Degree Wipe
Term th Figure Wow Hmm
Apina Reminiscence Carp Number 22
After all, that's not
only Japan, but also a big character
chimi...  I'm really proud to have made new friends at
Mr.
Anger.
Good for
everyone. I'm really proud that everyone in the world has become friends like this.
There c Paper Center
Aaah, let's see the sinking Iguans 2Make
Fan Zone is as worn out as Ashina
Oh, I'm so happy for the daycare staff,
Lana That's how it is.As Hula No. 2 grows
up, I get along well with people from various countries.  It's
great to be able to interact with you.
Yes Isa Why Filthy US Army Japan
Pikazota! Ear 2cm caliber
1000 yen doboi grab the youth spiv
overboard a 4mo cars
face ever Next question is, do
you have any advice for your seniors
? I've been active
in Japan Live since that one year until Aehaba,
but I received an
e-mail with the color of Plasenpai.  Yes
[Music]
Bach
But I'd like to know the secret to staying active for such a long period of time.Well,
I have a very
laid-back personality and I
tend to go at my own pace.4
As for part 2, I
can't really say much about the uniform as a character officer, but I guess it's about
continuing to do what I think is fun.If I do
n't do my best, it'll never
last.No matter
how hard I try, I
don't like it.  It's impossible to keep doing things forever,
so
I
feel like I have to give up some kind of activity starting tomorrow, but I also
have to remember that I'm having fun
doing this for a long time.  I
wonder if that's the secret. Of course, if I
only do what I want to do, everyone else will have to
catch up. I
think everyone will end up not knowing what I'm doing, but I
think it's fun to be able to have fun with everyone.  That's the
kind of feeling I've been feeling since I've continued to make music, and now I like talking to everyone.Hmm, I think the biggest secret to not forgetting things for a long time is I see,
thank you very much.Sadah
cf  3pusu berry um
spring plastic winter ve a
sd swinger down p appropriate
21 pub how to
do this paan
shise 3 a
[music]
roaster fourteen rm
ro n
darren fine 4 moniter
earth winner key chain
wii enjoy eeee enjo
puget butter  Tofu dumplings bar
wall e joe life and
pandies start to Meiji
do a fuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuuu up
winter  How about Ford
npo invade powder
dish p ag2 c
see you Lars yki prefecture
Hagi Kusa-machi Honmoku Isuguya cabaret web Maeka
Oiku live who's the spa person
Landing ever wonder It's a
correlation diagram Chest whaling  web io
reason light bar red 6
Tokinu 6 Hun house see someone
to
do up
ah unprecedented funny
uh
thank you for the good advice
pen q 4 u ni  sora senpai
Hmm, Akashi won't disappear, but I'm sorry. Hey, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I'm not going to disappear, but I'm sorry.
If I can, I'd like to be active as a
senior for a long time." Best Aso: Yeah, 2 d, Steve Cheese Video New, Sora-senpai  Well, now
that that's out of the way, the next question is, seniors, in the future,
especially the purpose of the 5th year.Well, is there a crisis already?I
still want to perform live in the 5th year, too.
I'm so happy that people are watching my live performances c
After all, I've always stood for staying g or so, so I'm going to
scale it up and do
something about it, and I'm proud of all the smart people who are supporting me.  I want to
be like that, but since it's been 5 years
since I've been in a secret hot spring, I
want to be like that, so I
wonder if I'll be able to get better at love.  to
do so I'm a human being, near the river
The announcer is Eve too N Berry is gouged
Facility Himi-san sells phone and Dies
Pinos in a Abe follower
Super Fass 4 S chain egg by
Aguaba Rampway Don't end at the end
Media song performance  We
will send you a special piece of
jewelry.If you would like to stand on our stage,
we would appreciate it if you could come and see us at the festival.
On purpose,
greedy Iraq, I
want to get to know you
If you're an embarrassing cancer,
yeah
[music]
me
go tai
start
family car
I can't write a flexible recording
[music]
Unfinished buzz A
piece called love o
is a car da i come
here
you 0
life is hard  den
[music]
Suzuki kei
[music] to
be a little bit
tana
often
[music]
ame
[music] de
Kobe seat
[music]
just
good good  The
two growing Kecak are
more along the line h 6
Thread with such numbers
dai
Josee's waving hair is chasing you The
distance of Prime Minister Aso's engine is 0
me
[Music]
When it's day It looks like it's
moving
ana The
nitride layer is falling
none Aso is
running
now  Looking at the Castle 2
This Emperor
[Music]
dai
[Music] For
a moment, Tana didn't take care of me, and
since that day I've been
feeling
a little
weird.  I'll
always be by your side
Me, you'll be the same
ana I gotta
w
[Music]
tarao
Ahh yes
ganbare ah
happy ok ok It looked great bor par There's a
soap digger I
started to like this song
Yeah 8 buildings 22 really  I was in high
spirits as I watched it! Ah Yao
Join Join LED
Sonar Craft Popo Pink One Size  I'm
going to fail in the long function, too, Shearfur
Accessories 9 minutes a day, 2nd run,
Batman big boss point back plan and re-drinking on the floor I've
advanced, sea view for men I'm going to overtake the Zazu landing on the dish  The version I
just said was that Piano Noah
Genji version that was playing in the background,
but it's on Sora-senpai's channel,
so it's a very difficult version, so
everyone, please listen to that too yeah
Random Why did you choose that song? Mari Sora Senpai
Kyushu Noise
[Music]
This song is 3 and my first song. It's the
song day in the album. I've
been singing it at important times. I guess it's
3 points. It's
pretty heavy. It's a
good song.
So
this is it,
you guys, the
Meiji
fender usa
aruseusu
open to
do therab imprinting
ok Basie
anh finally over sea
scape force 4 body for everyone in the world to see.
Super 19th floor Wow,
that's why I
'm going to ask you a question. It's a
live show for sexual love.
Episode 5. It
's America's family. I
can't live without them.
Daisetsu grandson is better than me, too. It
's a part of life.  Even if I feel like that, I
wonder what it is inside me that feels like everything.
I say I'm happy for 5 minutes, but why
picker
p
meermin
ustar see me good taste
needs tenoras en do
do wick oven white s 4
abc meow
yes
[music]
Senpai I want to promote something else today
If there's anything else, it's day
barley
It's time for 32 promotions 3 f ah
ah ah
ah live free to I'm going to use it
so big brother  Sweet pass brother Bruce Polly Earth
Epi 6 over oh oh
then the pen part was too hot Yeah there
are 4 of them
ah emergency farce r voice collection
If the message matches, f 1
Ah, I'm going to do part 4 at home. I'd
be happy if someone who would use it as a weapon would buy it. That's why
Cars 2 is so cute. Pin
Badge or Smile start the
badge star in Canter
Farm DS 4 RO Kyuuu
Hmm, let's say phone stargate now
swing temperature sharon force tenbusu
obo4 monmon fan den location 4 s
narude of
How was your day today?
[Music]
Very fun to eat iPhone version
eea Spain cow Seth was
there at the end of August 4 Yeah yeah cap
pen q farm inch av blanc
ah
tangy
lip liver
1 p b
ne ne
[Music]
I was very happy to be able to talk about many things about plate lathes.Meeting fishing and
feeling the breadth of my life with Kamioshizu Sora-senpai 1 day  Yen
Monthly Payment Vader
Hmmmm,
Nos Diffuser
Fighter 2 RX Free Jazz
Change Parts Bar ore Akane and
Dahmer Let's Drink on Twitter
Please let us know your thoughts using the far end tags We
will continue to explore as usual, so please take care of us.
I always
greet him in German at the end of that episode, but I
wonder if he can say it with me again.
After it starts in English, it becomes German,
but the
engine tube is Abby in French all at once.It's
totally fine, I hope you can say it together with the fish filler wire.I want it to
be American imagination and oh yeah, blue defective again.I'm
aiming for a soap that means  Tekei system Yes,
321 engine
Benz Yanagi Gwansun turns
around aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
[applause]
[music]
hmm hmm
[music] hmm
[music] hmm hmmmm [music] hmm hmm [music
] hmm hmm [
music]
Moose Poupe hmm
[music]
hmm
[Music]
Hmm
Uzun
[Music]
N
Boof's 10 minutes
[Music]
Hoop's Boof
N
4's
Mu
Shu
Hmmmmmmmm
[Music]
Yahoo
Boots Hoop