something
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
as if I'm gonna show you my baldness
right away we're not that close just yet
sing to me
baldy why
hello
open yes I opened the bottle
my beloved
[Music]
hi hi everybody
Cali Cali's just trying to mess with
your brain because she already saw the
new hairstyle I showed her when I first
got it same as she she would she showed
me hers when she got hers first
for some reason
the moment is got first added to our you
know
models uh we were in each other's
presence at both times
when I first got mine I was in her place
in her uh in her place here I am
and when she got hers we were I think we
were in that Mexican restaurant
um
what a coincidence right yum everybody
uh sorry for being a bit silent uh
uh and for no plan this week I mean
there is a plan and the plan is that on
the weekend
there will be Expo and four PES
and we are all very excited for it just
today it was announced that
you can cheer at the concert which you
know
we're still a little bit of a mystery
but for the longest time Japanese
concerts did not allow it at least not
in that kind of like big size thank you
Takoma and also I saw uh well let me go
back I saw who was that a red super chat
I can't go back that far I think no I
can't
simply about the blanket thank you
hey
the blanket
birthday merchandise from last year
blank is very cute right
I uh I've been
I I tried out the
Ina birthday I guess it was her birthday
merchandise right
washing machine
oh bag thingy
yo it has such a cute design man
I love having this kind of cute
merchandise that's also useful to
replace things or have things that you
never had before
pinky too thank you
an art block
[Music]
um
well I hope it gets better
but don't worry about it take your time
one punch Wallace
[Music]
well so I have to disappoint you guys I
won't be streaming for long today this
is just a short little stream to update
you on the long-awaited long time
announced
um new hairstyle
yeah and then tomorrow
because you know busy tomorrow
I will be on a Nina's Channel Nina from
because we're doing a little chitty
chatty collaboration over there
short eight hours no for real I'm gonna
do short this week short streams okay
but next week I'm gonna do at least
three Fire Emblem streams
and Metroid Prime
I hope that's okay guys you know shorts
this week because you know we gotta get
ready
for the big concert
oh snap Metroid Prime yeah let's go back
I want to play Metroid Prime baby
and it's next week release for
atalia ryza
maybe I'll do a little stream on it I
don't I don't think I'm gonna do I don't
know but you know once I get started it
would be weird to not do the whole thing
ah depends on how long it is but I
already have Fire Emblem running on the
price I don't know about right so I'll
do at least one stream on the new riser
and then we'll see how I feel about
continuing it but no promises no
promises I know
foreign
[Music]
it was rough man
damn I
[Music]
lost one unit on the way
but we're not playing classic soul is
good
oh my God thank you for the rest of the
chat Pony Clinton
yeah I'll be returning to my normal
stream schedule soon don't worry about
it sorry to keep you waiting but happy
happy birthday right
oh that's quite a while ago
hurry the [\h__\h] up
hurry hurry hurry hurry but for now
don't worry I'm just doing Divine
parallels
um until next week next week you know
I'm just I'm swimming finally a lot next
week so you know what you gotta do you
know what you gotta do
at least I'm not streaming much like
from like this whole week so it's not
like you were busy watching my streams
huh
well you also played well I said also
coming up next week
I do kind of want to make that
put possibly into a series
it's not gonna be that long right
which day which day is Bayonetta coming
out
it's tomorrow
[Music]
it's bad who says that just hasn't even
come out who can say that game reviewers
well they don't know how to play games
journalists
I like it
I like it from the looks of it you know
like
the normal Bayonetta games are not quite
my style but that one that's my style
man that new one oh I'm I want to look
into that for sure wow wow
it says the game I'm I'm I'm I'm a
better game journalist
received my copy today oh oh I guess
when you order physical copies sometimes
you get it early right
I'm Jelly full face watch along
um time wise it seems like I it's kind
of impossible for me to do a watch along
for the
second day on the actual like when it
happens because I'll be in on the same
day I'll be doing the tickle uh Nina
uh thingy which is before that so you
know I'll be running back and forth
between things
it's uh yeah
I mean I don't know I I don't think so
but we will do a
yeah I'm confused but um don't last one
but no this is not the new hairstyle yet
wait wait I'm waiting I'm you know we're
gonna I'm gonna get warmed up
ah I will be here at the Holo spy panel
which I think will be streamed on
YouTube on the whole life English a
whole live Channel thank you for now
what's going on got the red super chats
thank you what the [\h__\h] thank you
Studio raw thank you
so many things to talk about man yeah I
wanna watch day one
next week together
or maybe
as soon as possible
after it happened
um
[Music]
for breakfast
oh I want to eat that too yum yum yum
yum
[Music]
you know closer I'm so sorry I know and
I watched today I watched the
compilation
from Kyle carrot of all the courses I've
said in my last stream and I'm so sorry
but I think it was funny
I still love it and you know turns out
um Jenna you know during that stream you
know I wrote to her and was like I'm
swimming right now and I think then
that's when she turned on the stream and
she was watching my stream for the rest
of the time
um I hope I didn't say anything uh
embarrassing
a million times but turns out she was
watching it so the next day I met her
um her and another like staffer and they
both
were
like constantly
continuouslying at me and I was so happy
you know because I know some of you guys
maybe were a little bit fed up with the
amount of croissant that I have been
questioning
um but they were so happy
happily
and and joyfully sharing the croissants
with me and and Generals console is
really good I have to say so her
question sounds really legit
so I would say and then they would both
also with me say and we would love and
it was so funny thank you be faster
so that made me very happy to be among
people who like to castle with me and
we're not fed up with me
uh yeah I heard about Iris but did she
didn't get that from me
maybe only from the Tweet because
there's literally a zero percent chance
that she saw my stream
Iris watch anyone's streams
what
she wants my stream
what what but wait wasn't it just a
Super Chat rating
when did she want my stream I'm so
confused
why
[Music]
thank you for the pinky Jeff stop
yes yes yes yes yes sure
yes I am
maybe maybe yes
um
no no no no no no
I I can't no that must not be normal
that must have been like a once in a
lifetime thing that she would go into my
Super Chat reading
maybe maybe it accidentally
her YouTube accidentally redirected me
her to my stream
[Music]
oh well I'm happy to happy to spread the
croissant
[Music]
oh man iced tea so yummy
um
[Laughter]
well it's okay I have calmed down since
but I I still have a big love in my
heart for queso
so I saved a lot of
um
you know you guys came up with a lot of
uh ideas
suggestions for hairstyles
um
even though there was a short notice
[Music]
um
for uh drawing some stuff up last minute
thank you guys thank you
good idea
I should go to France for that
oh maybe I should really do that
maybe I should fly it over to France
that's another good reason for actually
I told you guys last time I think
already that oh what's
good what the [\h__\h] is
yes yes shouldn't you be sending it
after four Fest what's happening
thank you ghostbume you know I don't
normally hear from you I think so thank
you
are you like um a human
thank you
thank you I'll read this properly
another time but thank you
[Music]
are you a human
no oh no I'm just usually like oh oh
thank oh thank you for expressing
yourself I'm glad you guys like ghost
rule but now I'm out of the [\h__\h]
lost my train of thought what was I
saying
roommate uh egg my ex-roommate right she
I told you she messaged me right I did
tell you about that right right right
right right
I told you that right
do they say fall of train no way I said
train of thought this diamond right
okay I told you about women now did I
say why
fun
I said I read this okay okay
there Gaslight me
[Laughter]
I said train of thought
is that correct
now I'm unsure a train of thought
thought of train
you know wait it's straight no fun [\h__\h]
um oh my God that was saying about
mermaid right
um
uh so she messaged me right and she's
like ah I miss you kiwawa we should meet
up we should go on a trip or whatever
uh and then you know she told me that
throughout the summer she has a lot of
time to go on on a trip and I was like
oh hell yeah let's go and you know I
want to go on a beach trip and one of
the suggestions I made was you know
going to a country for Beach vacation
where I haven't gone yet you know but I
also would like to go to Greece again
and so on but but but one of my
suggestions was how about south of
France because I keep on hearing that
the south of France is amazing for Beach
vacation
so if I go to south of France wherever I
don't know where
and then uh I can I can do a croissant
review while I'm there
oh
um
there's so many places I want to go
I need to do some research I want to do
a couple quick
Europe trips maybe Quest Overview at
south of France let's go
too much
I'm happy I'm happy but get review oh we
can do that too oh
more trips good in my book and also good
in my book man
trips I know some kfb members or just
generally uh non-japanese whole life
fans are in Japan now hopefully having a
good time be careful guys and and feel
free to check out some places that I
told you about before in the past
make sure to get like a suika
you know one of those train cards
because by trying to figure out which
ticket you need and then buying a ticket
for each uh train ride would be [\h__\h]
um now normally you know the last time I
I normally I'm from my whole life
whenever I needed this weekend because I
lost one or so or past more it doesn't
matter
um
uh I would uh usually I I got it from
someone but if you need one and you
don't have anyone to give one to you I
think you can you know at any station I
think you can just go to the person at
the station and say please give me pasta
mall or should we call
um
and then you can fill it up at every
charging station
99 off I doubt that thank you General oh
you're going to unless you move lots of
people well hopefully that day will be
sunny because I I saw um two other kfp
went to enoshima
according to my suggestion and it was
chilly weather just like when I last
went which is the real experience but
but you should have good weather that
would be nice
yeah enjoy enoshima um
I feel like you could do anushima in
half a day
but you can also take your time but I
think it's it's okay to just you know go
early do half a day and Oshima and then
once you're done with the island
you could go you know over to the
anushima aquarium or I don't know I
think there's some more stuff around the
area you could probably take a train to
close by I think it's Kamakura I think
oh my
God oh my Nathan cousin thank you for
the pinky and Jeff so thank you also oh
yeah
yeah go through oh [\h__\h] man let's go to
Taco this will be
um probably like a
I think I might really just keep it at
one hour I want to stream longer but you
know
I should probably keep it like compact
it's just a hairstyle stream
yeah
I'm so so gasp I know
I know
I told you next week all back to normal
ghost rule yeah did you guys listen to
Ghost rule
I was really happy about the song choice
that I received I mean and a new
original would have been nice too
but I was happy about just being Chosen
and being teamed up with Luma is kind of
cool because she's a great singer really
and
um yeah that meant you know
Tony uh song cover that I don't even
have to organize for once no it's being
organized by other people and it's kind
of an official song cover because it
comes from the person who produced a
song
so there's CDs there's physical versions
you can buy but you can also listen to
it this time also on Spotify
Etc or if you just type in ghost rule uh
what's the artist
what was it on YouTube because you can
find it on YouTube even
it's generated on YouTube as well
um
what's the artist written as
we'll try both
they're um it's just various artists
yeah well I tweeted it out yesterday so
just uh check my tweet
it should be available now everywhere
you can give it a listen on YouTube or
Spotify this time you can actually
Stream It Isn't that cool order from
City Japan oh wait you can you can do
that from overseas
because I I honestly I'm not 100 sure
are you guys able to order these CDs
these physical CDs from outside Japan
yes yes yes oh
cool because you do get an extra if you
depending on from where you order I saw
that you get an extra and if you order
from City Japan you get a mume kiwawa
extra something so it would be
recommended for you guys to order it
from CD Japan I think there's another
extra for some other song
um what was that
[Music]
you also got the physical signed one
from you
I totally remember signing that for you
yeah yeah yeah
um the other one is okay oh yeah I think
I remember that
you get a bromide review moment oh
um
I think okay has an original song
does it no way that makes no sense
because I guess she's also on the cover
album I guess she doesn't have an
original song what was hers what's up
lizards
I don't remember
why is it on
wait is it one city I thought it was two
separate CDs
is there two separate cities
I'm confused now you can get them
together separately
it's two cities right and a big box oh
oh oh you have to buy them together to
get the extra or can you buy them
separately
special edition is two cities so if you
buy it separately you don't get the
extra
why am I asking you guys about this
is mean to you but hey we're figuring it
out we're figuring it out
too serious but the whole package for
the card
[Music]
oh
uh-huh uh-huh separate I believe they're
no good oh
you also get the accent
somebody else says assisting us
oh I I would assume that you only get it
if you buy the the special edition just
the package
what do I know if you're interested in
it just in it then just check it out
let's get to the bottom of this yeah
I'll leave that to you guys
thank you guys for the ones who already
you know got the special edition or got
the online digital
version purchased it thank you
thank you for the support hmm
so yeah we did Ghost Rule and you guys
have been praising me a little before
thank you there's one part that you guys
were praising me for and I was kind of
like um a little bit self-conscious
about
because
um
I feel like it sounds ugly the way I
sang it
[Laughter]
yeah the part that goes like Oh my God I
even I don't wanna I don't want to even
sing it
because there's like different ways I
could sing it
thank you
[Music]
that part right but a second differently
uh yeah I think I sent you know several
takes to Decor sun and just you know was
like use whatever you think is best
stream is officially past pregnancies
let's talk about yolk
but I will slowly start now with um you
know the actual thing that we're doing
it really I'm happy that we got like a
cool song I like cute songs I like cool
songs but that one's a cool song and now
you guys are praising me for that part I
didn't think you would first me for that
I thought you would praise me for
um
the the part where I was I was trying
really hard to sing like calmly
emotionally sadly you know
[Music]
you know
I tried to put a lot of emotion in it
you ain't saying anything about that
what's up with
it
all your parts sound Divine that's what
I like to hear thank you you did great
from starting to finish thank you hope
that she's singing a little register
more
um it's like it really depends on the
song Sometimes I have an easier time
with it sometimes a less easy time with
it
um
is this the one you do it with them yes
exactly
wow wow maybe I'm saying ghost rule
sometime soon in the karaoke
how about that
you know I love singing Deco songs
generally
you're probably meant for tweet was epic
ah oh that's a long time ago
man I like talking to you guys
I'm talking to you guys
[Music]
hairstyles
if you remember if you recall last year
on my second year anniversary
I said I will get a new hairstyle
um soon TM
uh I guess I didn't expect it would take
this long ah man well
I kind of did more or less but not this
long I knew it would take long but not
this long
um well it's been ready for like what
two weeks or so uh I guess I was just
waiting for the right opportunity I
don't know for the right timing I don't
know now and now I thought well I'll do
it here I'm just gonna do a short stream
anyway so might as well you know
what short stream could I do oh let's
reveal my hairstyle that's my train of
thought
yes
yeah yeah
um
yeah yeah yeah so here is one suggestion
from akanen and I like this one this is
not only drawn well but also I feel like
I've seen this hairstyle somewhere
before but cute I like how for the
braids you can see you know the two
color that my hair does
yeah and it's short shorts so a lot of
people have been hoping for short
hairstyles
[Music]
I guess Raza has something like this
yeah yeah I mean one side braid I guess
yeah
um
short yes love short yeah yeah yeah well
we'll see how short it gets
[Music]
I like it I like it I mean but you know
the thing is this hairstyle is gonna be
for this outfit that I'm wearing right
now it's added to this outfit
so honestly the one that you drew I can
imagine that with a different kind of
outfit maybe not for this one I'm
wearing right now this one you drew uh
more I I see it in a little different
design of clothes
I think well thank you
nice one next another short one from
elderflower but it's kind of different
because this one this one gets like
shorter on the bottom like less hair
volume on the bottom very cute also I'm
kind of naked on my shoulders yeah
again very well drawn and oh
you know a lot of people have been like
giving croissant references see this
foreign
um I don't know if like I would ever
go for a hairstyle like this as the one
main hairstyle for a new outfit
it's I feel like it's it's very you know
I don't know how to say it quite quite a
statement
it would have to be something that
really fits the outfit
hmm
I like it but it it would maybe be like
a second hairstyle option not the main
hairstyle option because generally I
prefer a bit longer hair on me even
though this looks good like it looks
good but when I do this as my first
choice probably not
but it's also like you guys know I like
to do hairstyles obviously that I
haven't done before
obviously like why would I repeat the
same hairstyles on every outfit why it
makes no sense and we don't have that
many more like obvious options anymore
right so
right well
next is wait did I say this was
elderflower next is
252 underbar Ayo
I'm a Korean bro apparently this is like
some kind of like
oh Korean Royal hairstyle I think
oh best one so far
I will a million like braids and stuff I
I don't think they would ever do this
with real hair though they surely like
put on some wigs I think for these kind
of like like special occasion big
hairstyles I think they're always
like oh
wigs
I would say this is more of a joke
submission
but it's fancy and there's a chicken on
top
um cute
nice earrings too but you know I feel
very
um it's not my brain what the [\h__\h]
I'm conscious about my about my forehead
very very self-conscious about my
forehead since I was a child because
people always make fun of me uh recently
I've been you know haven't been styling
my bangs much just because you know for
traveling I bought
um in Japan I bought this small USB oh
iron hair iron to like curl my bangs a
little bit
because I didn't want to bring my big
one from Austria because it also like
needs um a plug adapter
and it's too big it's kind of big so I
thought how about I buy one of those
small ones and then when I went there to
buy one they had USB ones and I thought
that's kind of smart maybe
because well I can plug it into a PC or
I can plug it into like a phone charger
whatever
[Music]
um
so I tried it but turns out it was
really really [\h__\h] weak it does
it's it no it's cute a small but yeah it
does not really get that hot
it gets kind of warm and it did curl my
bangs like a tiny bit but it doesn't
keep it like that like it doesn't stay
yeah so I didn't really use it after
that I feel like maybe for um
small accents maybe could work but yeah
I ended up not really using it so then
yeah
for like this whole month
in Japan I I I have been just letting my
bangs live their life the way they wanna
which means naturally
you know they're they are just you know
on the side doing their thing
very self-conscious about it but you
know I didn't feel so
so anxious about it around myth members
and and I also got you know I don't know
I guess
I guess going to the studio more and
more where you know I don't know
staff members are in the beginning I
felt kind of weird about
you know not being my prettiest self
that I could be
but recently I gave less [\h__\h] about it
hmm so but then again you know it's nice
I think it's nice to be able to let
loose and just
Don't force yourself to be like so 150
pretty all the time
I don't know what the [\h__\h] I'm saying
but sometimes I feel like
I feel forced to have to do that but
also it's nice it's nice to everyone's
in a while still you know make yourself
pretty
once in a while at least so that you
also maybe feel a little bit better
about yourself and then you remember oh
wait I can look cute when I try oh
forgot about that I thought I was a lost
cause
and the other day I did that when I went
out with an old friend of mine we went
to a nice cafe
what was it two days ago three days ago
when was that I don't even know Tuesday
Tuesday wasn't Tuesday
and I made myself look pretty because I
thought maybe we'll take some selfies
y'all and she said can Mama you're cute
no I was really happy about that
yeah and oh you know what I did
so I gave up on it well we're absolutely
testing so I gave up on the
um on the shitty USB mic right but I I
went to a donkey halter the day before I
think and
um
I found this item again that I've never
used in my whole life but I felt like
you know what maybe I should give it a
try because I see other girls using it
all the time
specifically this is this one is for
front bangs a single front bangs curler
it's like not so big they're like a
little bit like uh uh more narrow like
not the hole isn't so big and it comes
like it's not just the curler it has
like a little like a clip so you can
click it clip it click it clip it onto
your bangs and then kind of pull it down
and then curl it at the at the bottom
curl it inside and then you put you take
a hair
dryer so even if you don't have a hair
iron normally everywhere where you stay
Airbnb or hotel what they definitely
usually have is a hair dryer
so you should usually always have a hair
dryer with you
so you just like
hair dry blow the hot air onto your yeah
tubes yeah yeah yeah they like cubes
blow it onto your forehead on the on the
bangs
is
um
yeah so then you blow blow blow with the
hot air and then you just I just finish
it up with my hairspray what you guys
don't give a [\h__\h] about what I'm talking
about right but this wasn't really
really special realization for me that
there's this that this actually really
works quite well okay so I'm happy now
yeah um so anyway
okay next door
this is from Aldo greenberry so here we
have
an edgy
skunktail
kiwawa
of course with one eye covered
um
and I see you chose um
blue gradation for my under hair I did
have the kind of blue one kind of blue
right for my
uh fancy dress
um
it's not a face Mom it's not your face
mom
yeah
it's like always windy where I am it's
always windy that reminds me of Cali's
um
ponytail hairstyle right because it's
like side swept her ponytail goes to the
side at all times so whenever Cali has a
ponytail hairstyle I guess it's always
windy around her she creates the wind
but I understand as an artist you know
the problem is with like you know us you
normally we Face the front and even when
we look to the side well there's always
so sideways that we can get right so a
ponytail this was also a reason why I
didn't really do ponytails until now
does that mean she has a button though
um it's just how I how I say it I guess
but like yeah so because if you draw it
correctly then you will most of the time
not see much of it
but corn recipe for example has a has a
a ponytail that is not like constantly
in a windy situation
no it's just straight down it looks cute
too on her like it I I it works I guess
so
so you can even just draw it
realistically but then you most of the
time don't see much of a ponytail you
don't see it much
you know nothing guys you know nothing
and then and then yeah if you have it
like Cali when it goes to the side and
you've seen it all the time but it's
just kind of like stiff uh like you know
because it's always there it shouldn't
be there
um
or you do a side ponytail but I
generally prefer like a normal middle
ponytail
centered one because it's time for your
tail cute yes but
[Music]
nah
nah it kind of looks stupid often in my
opinion but
you needed to work with the right outfit
and so on OCD trigger
bro my heart and why not practical
well you know what's cute you know in
Idol Master enough attention in Idol
master in the OG Idol master I know
there's two twins or one pair of twins
uh sisters and they have uh side
ponytails and one has it on one side and
one has it on the other side it's kind
of cute that they you know have it on
different sides and that's how you know
which one is which
is yes
[Music]
um
you can't stop me from Talking oh my God
I'm like losing breath man
foreign
[Music]
emo hairstyle but you know they wouldn't
let me now this was from an owlette
I like this one because I feel like is
that kind of similar maybe I'm like
totally wrong here but isn't it kind of
similar to
um
from near automata the blonde chick the
what command or whatever she wants
[Music]
let me put this like in the back
is it is it I wonder am I mixing am I
like imagining things
what did her hair look like I don't
remember
you know what I mean though right
definitely I wouldn't say this is no no
no no because it's not a side braid no
it's just like you know the hair is
braided back on one side and then what
you see in the front on the left side is
just the remaining non-braided hair this
is not a dead mommy or something no no
no no no no
that's kind of right you have a good
memory about the new automata what was
your name what was that lady's name
called that character
let me let me check near Automotive
[Music]
it isn't Commander
wait what am I no I am ah no it's it is
I I am seeing it right it's even on the
same side but she has a ponytail so we
could assume that behind this there's a
ponytail
but also
[Music]
uh I like this
I I do like this I feel like it
it could be made into an actual thing
with the right outfit
okay
it kind of gives me like RPG hairstyle
vibes
the more cool and mature character has
this kind of hairstyle
often not a main character though
usually like an NPC important character
just like that Commander oh don't worry
I can go a bit longer but you know
it won't be that long maybe one and a
half hours
proof approved
I would like to see myself with this if
I wear like a slim fitted
long dress with a slit on one leg which
is exactly what the commander is wearing
I have exactly one image of what I would
wear to this
um
but yeah I really like it a slim
slim fit dress that shows the body line
um
design
at the beginning of the five hours no no
no no no no
why not to dance to the new hair
it's just how you do outfit and hair
reveals okay
I wanna milk it like a cow but also I
just need to talk about this
you know I just need to talk about this
one by one and if I so happen to break
out into a tangent I cannot be stopped
like I can't be helped this is just how
it naturally happens
it is what it is hi can we will We yucky
what do you mean yucky isn't that like a
is this yucky isn't yucky a you an
expression
how dare you entertain me
hi can we win we can we wear we that's
your new your new um name
no
milk did you get the milk
so I like this one go next oh so this is
really short this is even shorter than
the other short ones but damn it looks
so fluffy I will be honest I will never
get a hairstyle like this because I just
don't see it on me but I like it I like
the way you drew it it's very fluffy
maybe if it's a bit longer than this
like to down to the chin if you and
lengthen it until there
but feel free to draw it in like fan art
but you know I wouldn't go for this it's
from art pecoy art pikoi thank you for
drawing It Rock oh yeah
I guess oh yeah in like a oh oh like a
girl crush rocker outfit like lever
black lever outfit of studs run the
guitar in my hand
that feels so nice yes
hey that's actually a good concept let's
go
keep going I love the sound of this a
bit of lamp would be so good yeah yeah
maybe this plus a little a little bit
more length and then the rocker outfit
oh yeah oh yeah let's go all right let's
get to work I need that me too now that
you say it
thank you for this good art
feel free to make it a thing
and now we have uh from
bdh1816 that's the Twitter handle
Twitter account name I guess
hold on
what what kind of character would have a
hairstyle like this
um
it is pretty it is pretty
I I feel like I don't like this Gap
personally
it gives me bangs OCD I have like real
like strong Banks OCD I know that this
is a style Choice yeah
but it makes me wanna at least
if if we're gonna do this then I want to
at least you know do you see my mouse
here instead of going in a curve
outwards I would go for a straight line
here and then here
um
maybe another
strand that is like a little bit you
know bent the other way I don't know but
I don't like this o shape you know
that's just my personal bangs or CD but
I do feel like I've seen this kind of
Bank style before on some anime
character maybe in the past
Maybe
um what kind of character has this
it's interesting though because it's
very original I like it I like the
originally tea of it originality
yeah love the feathers well you know
that's my feathers
80s anime Vibes yeah
it is oh oh yeah I could see it on who
was that
yeah yeah I see what you mean yeah yeah
that that that kind of works on like 80s
um
what was that one
anime that also had like um
damn you guys gotta help me out here
again with my shitty explanations of
what I mean where I give you like two
keywords and you find out what I mean
anyway
um
[\h__\h] okay a lot what do you guys what
you guys are saying in the chat already
kind of makes sense to me that well
that's not what I meant um I'm talking
about
um
okay it had like a dating game
two that uh I played like online
um but you don't get very far online
because that's I guess there's a demo
whatever
um it's kind of Spacey not law peanut
but I can also say this in Love Hina
oh I can also say that I didn't know
today yeah yeah yeah yeah no no
Slayers what the [\h__\h] is Lance yes
Galaxy
[Music]
what's with my [\h__\h] tension
oh yeah oh my God
dear Lord
anime art styles from like 20 years ago
is like damn
oh my God somehow I can see I think I
think that's what I meant
did I mean I think that's what that
meant yeah it clicked in my brain
yeah anyway so
yeah
I think yeah this was 20 years ago right
20 years ago that doesn't sound like so
long ago to be honest but uh like
looking at the art style from it
it's like it looks like it's a million
years ago
man that 80s Show when she's yeah
because it feels like 80s
but apparently it was 20 years ago
huh what
it just feels way longer than that
what's the Japanese title
is
it's galaxy galaxy angel
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
back in the day and I was always so mad
because it wouldn't let me do the spicy
things
because I guess you had to buy the
actual game to do the spicy thing
so I just kept on repeating and
repeating and repeating
and Love Hina I think you had to buy
um smokes for just one character I think
damn I don't even I don't know man
what I was looking for in these games I
think you know I was young so I think I
was just trying to learn
[Laughter]
I don't know what I was trying to learn
but oh well next up
Christina Manzanita
I like this it's funny I will give you
that it's funny
I hope it's this one shut up
nobody really hopes it's this one
[Music]
I would never waste
an opportunity that I get twice in a
year
for a birthday and an anniversary
for this
I would never waste it
no
[Music]
no oh I wait
did you make your own or ah did you add
my ears
because this one has the
the the earring what did did you not use
my my base
or did you go for the trouble to add my
actual ears because you didn't like my
ears the ones that I drew and I added
huh
hmm but this looks like what I did you
just added the ears or what I'm confused
by the ribbon
anyway I have another submission from
Christina Manzanita in here somewhere
anyway uh
okay next
this one is from
Oreo and
a day with like croissant hair
which you know gives you Gothic Lolita
or
um like magic magician lonely girl I can
read zero right there's one that has
this but like way bigger
um there's certain types of characters
who can pull this off yeah
I love the Kotori like
accessories though so freaking cute I
don't think I can pull this hairstyle
off at least not with this outfit
yeah Beatrice Beatrice is my favorite
character from rain zero
um
so much
oh she's a she's the best
who needs Ram or Ram or whatever the
names are who is Ram what the [\h__\h] I
need some
yeah well I think I probably didn't see
like the most recent season fully I I
think I didn't watch that
it's been so long man it's been so long
I'm subscribing now we're best girl
uh yeah the character with this
hairstyle too huh
so
yeah well there's a lot of animes we
have like at least one girl with this
kind of hairstyle but it's always the
very like
eccentric characters
she lost she didn't only lose her hair
she lost her head huh
all right moving on
this is the other one from Christina
Manzanita what did you do with my mouth
why do I is that on my ear
my my one he's called again I forgot my
eyebrows
facial expressions it's like after
you're done with the hairdresser and
you're not happy with it but you don't
you're like too nice to directly say it
to the hairdresser and they're like so
yeah this is yeah I it looks great on
you and you're like
I'm like
really
thank you
thanks yeah
[Music]
no but I mean in itself maybe this is
also just because you're good at Art
when you're good at Art you can make
like everything work I feel like
it's like a little bit too high up like
my head looks a little bit too big if it
was a bit lower then maybe it would look
more natural to me
hair itself like it's cute
boyish
I think
being British and too awkward to say
this isn't the haircut I wanted and
living with it
it's a British fan
darker shade on the hair and more emo
makeup and you're good to go oh
no darker [\h__\h] now but but needs uh some
green or whatever hair gradation inside
looks mischievous oh yeah
yeah maybe like oh
fee for whatever you know it's cute
come on kill I like it
I like it [\h__\h] or cone hairstyle if
koala was a raccoon
cute kind of cute the more look at it
the more I like it also the expression I
wish I could do that
honestly I love the Espanol like I'm
loving this for you yes
hair
[Music]
okay go next
whoa bye
with bun hairstyle eventually which
means I'm not doing it this time but
it's coming
oh
yeah
I like it I like also the accessories I
like I like this egg one I need to
remember that I'm like the egg one damn
that's good
I would probably place it a little bit
further in the bag
but besides that it's freaking cute yes
[Music]
I'm glad you like it oh
what does it say a ghost feeling what
the [\h__\h]
what you can draw what's up with that
frog draw me like one of your French
girls Dan come on
uh
no I like it I think like eventually I
will for either a new outfit or like a
thank you
a new outfit on like a second hairstyle
for an old one I would probably you know
do buns eventually yeah hell yeah
hell yeah I totally wanna do buns
yeah I really want buns now
[Music]
isn't the accessory overload of Japanese
yes it's a dead cool
the cool
I forgot
something like that cool
[Music]
Dakota yeah Dakota
style they add like a million uh like
you know pins and stuff onto their hair
all over
no it's cute it's like hological fashion
um
you confusing me that's like three
things in one
minute
I wonder if you did that like knowingly
if you were trying to give me decoder
Vibes or if that was an accident
I wonder tell me oh
ah nice is that you like
that's also one of the things I like
kind of wanted to do when I was younger
but didn't really have like the the
financials for it because you know need
a whole new wardrobe for that man and
also didn't really have the confidence
for it I think also yeah I didn't have
the hair for it either I mean I say that
but you don't really need any kind of
special fancy hair a lot of girls do
that just with normal black hair but I
felt like I needed to have like pastel
colored cute hair
well next
[Music]
next is
I am your yoga night your name or I am
moving I don't know how to say that but
thank you this is very girly cute and it
has the same hair band that I'm using so
I don't even need to buy a new one
um
pretty I like it yeah it cuts off at the
bottom but I imagine it to be quite a
bit longer than this
it's like an anime where you know this
is the the girl everybody has a crush on
the popular girl in class right
oh and she's really nice too she is
actually really nice
[Laughter]
[Music]
girl yeah she comes from a good family
well raised
I know her I know her personally
yeah no I wish I was that girl
could I be this girl heroinda heroine
could I need me
she's me for real for real secret
yandere or could be it could be a Twist
yes I can see that
no no look at her not her
[Music]
so that's
oh and you know you know how you know
Japanese school uniforms
um
you know everybody has to wear the same
uniform but you can choose if you want I
mean even with this there might be
regulations in some schools but in anime
you know you differentiate depending on
the often depending on the the character
the personality the girl has
you know they would either have
um underneath normal socks
or really short socks like ankle socks
or over knee socks or loose socks or
tights and she
she is 100 the type to wear tights this
right here is a tights girl are you
agreeing with me on that
what I mean
could be more but this is the tights
girl yeah
yes
oh oh oh we need to talk more about this
kind of stuff man and now I'm kind of
feeling like watching a like a school
anime again for the first time in a
million [\h__\h] years
um
you know I used to love the idea of
loose socks you guys don't even
understand loose socks right you don't
do you know what those are do you even
know what I'm talking about when I say
loose socks back in the day yeah you
used to wear them but even non gyaru
would wear them but you know you know
the type of girls who wear loose socks
are kind of like
kind of a little bit like yunky kind of
girl maybe even uh or like you know the
cool girls the cool girls yes
yeah the super super super super super
super super super super
long stockings that you know you don't
pull them all the way up of course not
you make it so that it has layers and
you know how much I love layers
um
but it should go it should end under
your knee under right under your knee
that's not a sound anymore
as popular as it used to be but there's
still maybe some girls who wear it just
because
you know it it's something I even I
still see it being sold I saw it the
other day and I think a Don Quixote or
so had blue socks but maybe yeah
nowadays probably in actual schools you
might not not see that much just like
girls who you know go out have a fun day
in Harajuku or whatever
and they style a little bit different
than what they would style themselves in
school
so yeah maybe not for actual school day
but like just for a day out they will do
like yeah
loose socks
or yeah to go to Disneyland for example
I can see girls doing that for
Disneyland or for cosplay like of course
in general
um
[Music]
foreign
do not
how there
uh
Japanese people agreeing on me they
would probably only wear it outside of
school you know a lot of girls Japanese
girls
they love their uniform so much
apparently they wear it even when
they're not going to school like after
school you know or on the weekend or so
sometimes they still wear their uniform
and then just because it's [\h__\h] cute
they understand because they actually
have cute uniforms so it's worth wearing
them
and then and then when they're not going
to school they would do they would style
their uniform more the way they like it
um
yeah
isn't that school regulation what
you mean to wear your
[Music]
uniform like at all times when you go
outside
I wouldn't say so I think they can wear
what they want
but
maybe they encourage it
maybe I guess like I think I've heard
about that before at some places like
want you to wear it all the time
hmm
I might have heard about it you know
but it's not like every school makes you
do that
it's considered as a violation of one
outside here as well
oh we don't have school uniforms this
weekend so just extra minutes yeah
yeah not either
um
and I you know I wish we had but the
rest of Austria I remember if like one
time we would talk about school uniforms
back in the day in school everybody was
against it but
[Music]
but you would fix your school it was but
then again yeah it's not really like the
aesthetic that they want anyway
man
stop
from
zero nine a big fluffy side ponytail and
it gives me magical girl vibes
magical girl like
what else
the most
mackerel yeah
thank you
[Music]
um
no no no no
it's a moment
[Music]
oh I didn't watch that but now that you
said I think I remember someone having a
hairstyle like this
I'm having too much fun
um
maybe two hours
biker girl oh oh wait I
can understand
like a thinner version of this less
volume doesn't one of the the sisters
one of the twin sisters
have a high ponytail side a high side
for the tail like this
yeah cotton I love cutting I love
I say this about every character
[Music]
I love it so much it's like the best
anime ever
Pokemon Oh Yeah from uh sword and shield
right uh the uh the lady Professor has
this hairstyle really cute I like it I
love it
I always took you for tsuki girl
um
it's Ryan
if I had to choose been cut in and ski
damn
I think I like cutting more
I think but in general as I told before
my favorite in general is not a goal and
then uh younger shinobu Donuts age
and also sodachi yeah I think those are
my top three girls and so don't you such
an unpopular choice I think
oh yeah Karen has that egg a fried egg
on her hair doesn't she yo I love that
no wind don't they both and wait a
second what this one tsuki also have
another her hair where do they both okay
called in
[Music]
exit egg
oh
wait so tsuki was a phoenix what was
Colin she was in the Phoenix was she
even though they're sisters and
apparently they're both like what
[Music]
is she
right
forgot about that I feel like that was
never really like made into a big deal
was it
I feel like all the other things are
made into bigger
things topics themes
oh I can see it in her outfit yeah but
like
Karen B was an arc
damn I'm I'm completely like like
what
I don't remember that at all
[Laughter]
okay I need a rewards yes let's go
I feel ashamed why is that why is that
one thing I don't remember about this
it was nice well I mean I definitely 100
watched it but
a p arcade
[Music]
that was the arc name I'll remember that
yeah because
I don't even like that scene that scene
that is for you guys
not for me
no all the other ones
[Music]
that one girl was
gorida
salon
[Music]
oh man I want to watch it again okay
okay okay you made me wanna watch again
okay
I mean who doesn't like Cambodia she's
just dope
is so big and yet for years I've been
waiting for another adaption because
they did say they were gonna adapt
everything and then you know I've been
waiting like how many years has it been
since the last one man
nothing's coming
it's like is it even worth still hoping
huh
they did say they're gonna adapt like
literally everything
and I think they still they definitely
still have something left over man
adaptation oh yeah I mean adaptation
what about your new hair though
[Laughter]
man
hey like we're having a good talk here
come here
I like this I think I've done my hair
like this before but it it or like
actually I've definitely done my
hairline this before but it was a bit
longer at that time
um
yeah I like you know
doing like a what do you call it again
the brain where you take more strands
from like every time you braid it over
you take a new Strand and then yeah a
French braid I guess yeah it's a French
braid yeah I don't know stupid I'm
stupid
can't just lasted your whole lunch break
nice oh wait that's bad actually because
you got to go back to work huh
am I wait my chat dead Let me refresh
braid braid so hard for me to draw or to
do IRL
drawing look both my fingers I think
drawing is easier than actually making a
braid
um
well if you if you draw it you just have
to you know do these little like like
oval Circle thingies
it's fun I really really love drawing
braids
back in the day when I was still drawing
I loved drawing brains it was always so
much fun
it's so fun
they're both impossible Endeavors for me
[Music]
it's fun to do braids anyway I like this
one oh but no no not happening this time
oh this is why is it so big why is it so
big from the get-go
I mean here
I like this cute very cute oh cute
yes
kill it yes very balanced very cute I
like the not too much but still
puffiness on the bottom like the the
curve I like the bangs I like the the
frame uh longer bangs on the side of my
cheeks
where am I uh Wings though by the way my
my hair Wings this is something I don't
say it oh it's on my hair oh true I
don't know how to say it is but you know
I don't want to be like fuzzy and
annoying like you know picky or nitpicky
about it but often so often I see fan
art without my feathers and I just want
to say you know especially if it's good
really really good art I'm like this is
so good but why you draw me with no
feathers now I feel like I can't use it
because this is not me this is just some
random orange hair chick
hmm But I feel bad I don't want to be
like why no offenders but in my heart I
always feel like no feathers why so in
case any artists are watching this
please draw me with feathers like
they're not an optional part they're
like my eyes you need to draw me with my
eyes so you need to draw me with my
feathers
yeah
I feel bad like if I would say something
to most people
like you know if there is this like in
the kfp artist that draws me all the
time but then if it's someone who draws
me all the time then I feel bad to like
suddenly be like hey you've been drawing
me for like two years without feathers
[Music]
um
that
this is this is just you know the focus
on this one is just on the hair this is
from Moon LDL by the way so I totally
understand like you know no need to
drown my feathers but in general just
saying um
[Music]
foreign
people really don't get her hair what's
their name
they're not Mio's hair
but this is just the one thing where I'm
I'm like really like oof
some people also draw me with like pure
orange hair like absolutely no like you
know depending on which hairstyle I have
there's like less green and more green
and sometimes not green but blue Etc
um so you know there's no like like
fixed you have to draw my secondary hair
curl like this
but honestly sometimes I see a Chihuahua
fan art that doesn't have the feathers
and also doesn't have the secondary hair
color and then it's legit just a random
orange-haired chick
I'm sorry but please add some color and
add my feathers
[Music]
yeah sorry that had to I had to say that
once even though it's probably never
gonna reach the people that need to hear
it I don't think it's ever gonna reach
them but yeah just so you know in for
the future you know how important it is
to me
yeah uh but I'm not I'm not gonna go to
these people and say hey I love your
banner but I'm not gonna use it because
this is not me I'm not gonna do that but
that's what I'm thinking
yeah I'm sorry I'm that's it's
it's got the brand yeah it's like yeah
it's like you know as I said it's like
driving without my eyes
[Laughter]
okay
and Drew this one whoa
wow so it's a high ponytail with like
some extra long pieces and very like
like not not messy but like I wouldn't
call it messy what's the right word not
messy but
a little violent hair
this one looks like you will do a swords
I could I could no
no nothing's wow oh yeah Wild
Wild Hair yes I like that I would say
this is wild hair
I I don't feel like it needs one more
strand here
this is me as an artist
I'm commenting on what I would add but I
would add one more hair
but besides that I really like the flow
of it yeah like you had you're it you
make it go in so many directions I like
it like this one goes out there these
ones go to the right and these ones go
like up and then oh wow there's like
really a lot of dynamic in here it's
great you tried you did successfully
it's good
yeah but I think there's another case
where I feel like it would not look good
on this particular outfit this would
have to be like maybe like a ninja
outfit or like a more
fighter kind of outfit no
fantasy style outfit well still no hair
yeah
I'm keeping you waiting oh yeah okay
next is
another short one and this one is a bit
different from the other ones right so
you know very even with short hair
there's like so many different kind of
like cuts that you can do I like this
one too
I feel like this is very like casual and
maybe a little bit like pajamas I would
like it look casual one it's nice it's
cute that it has feathers let's go you
didn't have to but you did
I appreciate it thank you yes yes that's
all but no I'm not judging anyone who's
like leaving out the feathers and this
one is really just about the hair here
right so oh yeah okay thank you for this
one very cute I can say this is like
something like this um
that is important so true this one
so cute this is from okunin and I love
how like you know I don't know if you
did it on purpose but from the back it
literally looks like there's a cat
sitting there
[Music]
and you drew me some boba you drew me in
the Bikini what's up with Dan hmm
I like it it's so fluffy movies
foreign
I think they call this like wolf style
hair like I mean this is an extreme
version of it but I see a trend in Japan
it's in other countries but a trend I
see in Japan uh with like girls
hairstyles is beautiful wolf wolf
hairstyle
is like when your top layer is shorter
than your bottom layer it's generally
like it goes to shoulder length
on the bottom of your neck length
yeah it it looks
so good
on cute girls and cool girls
it's like the ah yeah it's like a mullet
kind of I guess
is there a difference between a mullet
and wolf hairstyle
[Music]
I don't know but it oh oh
girls live up
oh well
I guess even like in America and so on
mullet girl
mullet girl haircut yeah oh
yes girl yes let's go I mean some of
them I don't like and some of them I do
like but some of them
some of them no
not my time in terms of the way they're
styled their hair
some of them go a little bit too far
with it
in my opinion
I'm looking for pictures now
[Music]
but I feel like generally
there's
[Music]
Japanese girl wolf hair
can I find this if I Google it in in
English yes yo you can Google the same
thing see I don't know Google this
Japanese girl wolf haircut Google it now
and you're gonna have a crash because my
God these girls oh
usually they have like long pretty long
bangs too with this that go a little bit
over their eyes
oh
my oh my God
[Music]
maybe I should do that someday
maybe I could get all the whole life
girls to crush on me if I had this
hairstyle
oh my God I feel like I could
[Music]
how to make every whole life girl to
crush on me this is the way to go this
is the way to go I cracked the cold
after meeting with them when they got
killed go home and do a stream
I think everybody will be like huh
spooning over quinoa
Harem brought unlocked anyway thank you
for this one thank you
sight tail oh wait
what's up
[Music]
this reminds me of someone from whole
life actually
just remind me of doesn't someone have a
similar one yeah
I like it I like this science ponytail
too this one has like less volume
it's a little bit more like natural
looking
so you can probably make it work with
less like extreme outfits too
thank you pissy on the bar d-rw
did a good job I like the coloring too
thank you for adding that is so I'm not
naked
next is from last today so this is my
two submissions and I love them both my
God a double twin tail kind of you know
this without the bangs is
I've seen that uh I think also even an
idol master or Joe Sama style
um
but I personally you know have uh
you know I'm scared of showing my
forehead so I like I appreciate you
adding the bangs I love
you know twin tails you can do so many
different kind of twin tails and the
height really sets the theme and I like
this particular height very much too
even though normally this I wouldn't say
that's me but I like the me I become
with this
cute very cute
I love how you know they're like mostly
straight and then at the bottom they
like curl a tiny bit I love it
freaking love it nice well said hell
yeah
cute and then this is the second one but
I prefer this one
yo they're both good but I prefer this
one I love it
okay I might actually like adopt this
one in the future
oh oh this this one's so good
yeah that's 100 me like oh my God yes
oh just look at that
just look at it
gone
[Music]
it's difficult oh
hi everybody
um but I have to cut off the good parts
no
it's so good
this is the winner not that I'm actually
implementing this but at least not now
thank you it is so good please draw fan
out with me in this hairstyle thank you
and add the feathers please
[Laughter]
[Music]
very curly and girly curly girly
curly and curly what a combination I
love this like man the person who drew
this I think is must be a girl come on
because like this
is
this kind of stuff
um I feel like girls
can only think of this
I could be wrong but I mean this kind of
hairstyle you know I follow
uh on social media I follow
um like a hair salon uh which like
focuses on not on like dying and cutting
Etc
but focuses on like hair Arrangements in
Japan this is Japanese hair salon and
they do like stuff like this all over
the head in very intricate and if you
have like two colored hairs hair it
comes out so nicely oh my God why am I
like
I'm like dancing things so much just
like the purikura tangent [\h__\h]
but anyway and then you added like even
these like oh it's a little Pearl ribbon
accessories so cute I love it
that's so unlike I wouldn't say it's
unlike me
I think it's cute very cute
maybe even have it on both sides Maybe
be nice or like I mean you know I love
the curls down here though I want these
kind of curls like a lot of Japanese
hair salons do this with your hair
I feel like from my experience it's kind
of like loose uh wavy curls with like
some they put like some hair wax into it
so that you know blue blood blue I've
been to Japanese hairstyles before hair
salons before anyway I believe
yeah
he's a dude good job he gets it Sakura
more cheer
for real sauce
good job man
you know girly hairstyles man
job respect
[Laughter]
yes nice details okay next up
[Music]
oh that's one of my favorites
um I just love the way the hair flows
this is made just the key why did you
cut it off at the bottom why not we
extend it I can imagine where it ends
though but yeah it's like a really
natural
loose wave in the hair I love to have
this kind of side braid on the side only
one side too like I'm I totally like
would do this on a daily basis if I
wasn't lazy as [\h__\h] because of the curls
um
yes oh man oh oh I have a crush on this
Chihuahua I love her
I love her yeah
like it's a very like like realistic
hairstyle you know I'm like I totally I
see girls like this out there in Japan
[Laughter]
this is from streamer uh eager with a a
why a y as the e e at eager streamer
weiger yeah thank you
[Music]
this is from Skye thank you I had to put
in at least one of those a lot of you
guys were memeing thank you for all the
meme submissions
let's go
I have I have permission to say at least
10 times during this while I'm looking
at it okay thank you
tiny Delta ah hi Kelly's still here
tiny Delta
so this you know gives me it reminds me
of that hairstyle that Natalie Dormer
had in The Hunger Games Yes where she
was [\h__\h] hot right
she was so hot uh I think though the
shaved side
uh wasn't as bald back then for her I
think
but you know shaving it there and then
uh like whipping the rest of your hair
over to the other side
oh it's kind of hot right
um you could still give me some bangs I
would say though that would like I would
appreciate that and maybe like Let It
Grow a little bit more then I'm okay
with it but also only for a very
specific kind of outfit not with this
one
yeah you guys are saying cyberpunk
I'm surprised
[Music]
no hole I remember has like pulled out a
hairstyle like this yet
right
Cali with some something like this too
actually Kelly
or or Ollie but she would make it more
extreme this is too simple still
Skrillex koala very out there has an amp
lens for sure it's a hit or miss it's
difficult yeah you need a fitting outfit
um
you're right but still add some bangs if
crony did this oh
people would have even more people would
have a crush on her oh plus yeah
[Laughter]
okay uh that was Tiny Delta next one is
tips is drawing who even added like a
body to me and um
just came out of the shower I guess
I love the fluffy hair big floppy hair
wavy long I like it thank you it's kind
of messy well I like that too
yeah
it does have a huge
maybe I should grow in a hole yeah this
is what gura saw that morning
kind of
I had the blankets wrapped over my
shoulders not under but think what you
want to think
this is yeah it was a huge blanket
um yeah when I opened the door to gura
the other day
I was like so like what's going on
because I wasn't like I just woke up
thanks to the ringing
and I was like I need to open the door
quickly but where I don't know where I'm
like too you know
[\h__\h] up to put on clothes so fast like
I wouldn't even know where to put my
arms through
so I did that I need to hit her side of
the sword she probably already forgot
all right thank you this is drying very
cute
ah eh same person
nah I saved it was a different with the
same name as this one but I think it
should be a different
is this really from this person
okay with someone else but I may have
saved with wrong name but
um I thought this was funny
four
uh this one's funny my head cracked
literal Egghead
no ah that's for me
wait what's the other one not you maybe
did I mess something up
I wonder
sorry if there was like a mix up
a full for you then wow
[Music]
are both you
yeah
okay
wow wow wow two very different Vibes
that you are asking me for almost two
hours oh [\h__\h] okay okay well thank you
this is really cute and then we have
this uh snack snack bird Kotori nautical
Medusa hairstyle from uh
I just wanted to put it in because you
know the burps are snakes cute or the
snakes are burnt who knows
[Music]
is
so pretty my God
[Music]
put so much like work into like coloring
it even like what the [\h__\h]
it's so cute on
I don't know if it fits if it suits me I
feel like I need a really girly outfit
for this
but you drew it so well it looks so good
do you know
[Music]
no feathers yeah I will forgive them
it's just a hairstyle for this time
yeah someone has like the the prettiest
art style um someone actually drew the
current
um this month's members only wallpaper
which is also the background for the
schedule currently
so yeah that's the same artist it's so
pretty
um
[Music]
oh that could be yeah that could be one
of the hard Challenger cuts
anyway I think that was the last one are
we finally through
yes we are thank you everybody
it's time one hour has become two hours
who who would have fought
I just had too much fun chatting with
you guys
um
[Music]
thank you
well after all these great hairstyles
I'm really really nervous about it funk
damn it took him to surely
I mean there were a couple more
so you guys you guys can look at the the
hashtag new kiwawa but after this that
hashtag will be flooded with screenshots
I would hope please use the new hashtag
new kiwawa hashtag for screenshots okay
to be continued okay bye bye-bye I'm out
of here
okay okay
um
so the new hairstyle comes with uh
accessories and the cool thing is I can
compare combine the new hairstyle with
most of my accessories from this outfit
too like the cat ears for example which
is absolutely Divine so please stay to
look at all the possible
um um combinations it doesn't work with
everything like this headband it doesn't
work with this okay but with most of the
things it works so anyway
without further ado
let me introduce to you the hashtag new
kiwama's
combination
are you guys ready for this like are you
ready like come on here we go
let's go
wait I'll make myself a big a bit
smaller let's go all right all right
here we go close your eyes close your
eyes you're not gonna close your eyes
anyway even when I say it
[Music]
thank you
what's this
glasses I even though I don't really
care much for glasses I thought you guys
might want to see them so I asked for
glasses
oh I just realized there's something oh
wait I didn't check this one properly
this one's kind of [\h__\h] up
oh
I might get some things fixed here with
the glasses because I just noticed some
things are
okay that's a bit confusing something's
something is happening like this
um but yeah plus for the end yay
um it's confusing it only happens
sometimes
did you see that
for documentation so I can send it over
later
do you see what's going on here
all right screenshot so I can send it to
uh Steph
okay okay okay thank you documented
there's just some layering bug okay okay
we saw that I'm gonna send that over to
them later all right here comes
there's the glasses for now I'll show
them later again free
cute
[Music]
I'm cute look look at me I'm cute I went
for something girly and yes with brains
and then we have glasses oh
okay with glasses though when I'm like
this nothing's vlogging out I think so
screenshots
[Music]
I can also combine with the old glasses
and then
uh what actually came what I requested
to come with this is these cute pens
pins
with tankers and smoothies and some
other pens
I can't use the pins on my other
hairstyle but they work on this one
cute
I know
so it's kind of short hair it's like not
too short though it's kind of curled at
the bottom you see where it ends it's
like right behind my shoulders
foreign
let's go
and then
I can do now here I love this
combination
look at what
look at this eh
the countdown remember the cat tail and
then
oh my God
going out of the works guys
let's look
I'm a cat wow
[Music]
I can be a cat with this wow
yes that's right I can still be a kitty
cat killed my style
what and then let's say uh I take it off
um now of course I can do stuff like
this because this doesn't interfere with
my hair but let's say we take this off
and and then and then
oh my
God
you can combine this guys this gives me
such summer vibes I did not think that
this would be possible that I I didn't
ask for this but I can use my straw hat
with this unbelievable for doing it
oh my God I love this excellent like
works well together doesn't it
holiday style
I'm so happy
it's so nice nice and short hair you
know better for summer
and then I can I can also take off the
straw hat and I can also still use the
Louver remember the little Birdo
I
I up there hi
[Music]
I keep on forgetting about the existence
of Kotori in this outfit so I haven't
been using him much but maybe I'll use
him use him again in the coming days
because I'll be using his hairstyle all
the time let's go and then I can also
just do you know for example this I mean
I could even I could even do this but
who wants that that's weird but I feel
like this could actually like still work
because I do this sometimes with my
braids right if I want to you know mix
up casual with my default outfit a
little bit you could do this I want that
well I could also do this
foreign
I can do it but you know we have this we
have this we have this and we have these
pins
everything I can do pants
[Music]
and uh well of course I can still use
the bag and all that I can of course
also like this has nothing to do with it
so I could also
do this kind of stuff yeah yeah
or like or this
was my hand always doing this though
like
wasn't one hand just down when I
wait a second
wasn't usually one hand down when I only
was wearing one turkey
I don't remember this I'm driving a car
normally you know it's like this
okay you can put something else on my
hand there
[Music]
it was difficult to make a choice
I would have read because I didn't want
them to just be black
I made them big and round you like them
I feel like they actually look nice but
oh they're really buggy oh oh yeah okay
we'll get we're gonna get that fixed but
are they nice they're nice I think
they're nice
Kiana Potter
yeah baby thank you I wonder what
football standpoint I will say about
them
they look really nice with this hair
thank you they do don't they the big
roundness
nah
I would have preferred sunglasses well I
mean the thing is I do have sunglasses
and maybe they're not the kind of
sunglasses you were asking for you maybe
want like dark ones probably
but I've had these sunglasses for a long
time
um
[Music]
I'm glad you guys like it
I need to get this fixed ASAP
[Music]
that's weird
I was probably only looking at it on the
phone
oh well I love this though
what cat girl with glasses
oh my god oh it's looking nice
YouTube wait
[Music]
um
feed me and while you're at it give me
your credit card number please please I
need to buy a new country for myself and
more Kibbles and more wet food and lots
of treats lots of treats please
please maybe your security card number
two please
Social Security I mean please
[Laughter]
yeah
oh my God it's so cute look at me he's
so cute oh my God come on
[Music]
we can combine the nickel Mimi
cute
yay thank you everybody
I am cute
sorry I'm so cute right like my God
look at this girl
girl I'm getting rid of the buggy
glasses for now
thank you guys for the super Jazz cute
new hairstyle bring you right the cat is
my God I I also didn't ask for this one
I didn't think this would work like I
didn't think about it all the open like
the possibilities this is the good thing
about adding into something that already
has so many options but I also want to
add something to something that doesn't
have so many options yet if you know
what I mean so that it doesn't have more
options
way harder without the glasses I think
it's like you know a personal thing some
people really love glasses so I was like
I guess I'll take some glasses why not
thank you
[Music]
wait let me let me do a poll I want to
do a Paul
uh live oh maybe you know thank God the
glasses have no feelings because they
might be kind of sad with the result
with glasses or without a Time twist
away saying that because of
um
cat girl with glasses
I think that's what she says I don't
know anything I only know the things
that I know
[Music]
just in general your interest
such a classic right I love that whole
like I don't like ever not not probably
not every girl character but you know
some of them they say this and they say
it in different ways like everyone has
like a different way of saying it
right
let's see let's see what's it gonna be
thank you
oh whip oh
my wig is so bad
[Music]
Oh I thought it would be not that
obviously with glasses damn
um classical firmed for Kayla they will
be even cuter after they're fixed though
that's for sure we'll take a little
while probably
at least
two weeks I would say we'll see we'll
see
at least now I have like some video to
like I can show should be easy to figure
out what it is for them I don't know I
don't know how this kind of stuff works
so I don't know
but
[Music]
it wasn't drawn by hookah Papa uh
I actually
don't know who did it
um I was just like assigned someone
because look at papa wasn't available
uh yeah
um but I like it like they tried to you
know copy look at Papa's art style so
that it matches with you know
the art style yeah
um I I wasn't like told who did it
mystery Papa yeah just like Anonymous I
guess I don't know maybe maybe they'll
tell me who to credit and then I can
give them the credits that is due
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
no they probably didn't tweet anything
yet they might not even tweet about at
all I don't know I'm gonna ask because
you know I like crediting the artists
and yeah
but they did a good job at like making
it look I was really worried you know I
was worried when I was told Papa can't
do it and we have to rely on someone
else and I was like yeah is it gonna
like look like
my normal like is it gonna fit you know
and then they made it look exactly
like my papa's art style yo they're
really good at imitating that um
[Music]
what
well I don't know what camp we did in
the past life to always be winning like
this attention when you're definitely
the kids
also I guess we can add the poll thank
you guys
wow glass so popular I don't think it
would be that popular thank you Mr
Smith hey
um
[Music]
I said that was only the one hour well
here we are
thank you guys I'm gonna go to sleep now
to another Orlando yeah
ah that was fun so tomorrow if you guys
want to see more of me tomorrow I only
have time I think for that one stream on
Nina's Channel
um
[Music]
so if you're looking for me I'll tweet
about it I'll be on Nina's Channel
I'll be tweeting about it and maybe even
make a community board post but that
would probably be Shadow beeped because
uh YouTube doesn't like it when you post
YouTube links which is so real freaking
ridiculous but you know we talked about
it you don't get notified if I make a
post we will link to another YouTube
video on YouTube what unbelievable I
know thank known for the pinky
yeah so it will be I think uh 11 P.M jst
so I'll see you there thank you for
coming to my new hair show wait wait
wait one more thing which combination is
your favorite
so is it is it I want to know wait let
me make a poll for this one too
um
this is important favorite combination
um cat ears or uh nothing just the pins
or straw hats or
um what what was that
[Music]
I guess we can put mask on there should
we put mascot there it's kind of like
not
I have cat ear
none which just pins or like should I
put okay that's a mask up or default hat
because I can only do four options
okay
all right all right I don't know which I
feel like the straw had worked so well
and the cat I feel like these two are my
favorites
but I love that I can also do this for
example
chemistry straw hat with glasses with
which ones here I have this one and this
one and this one's
this one you know they're very versatile
so we're just asking about you know hats
[Music]
cat ears cat isn't winning right now and
the straw hat also very popular
oh
I don't know I like this too I'm gonna
use everything and same with Sky
musculine
and nothing I think is also nice
sometimes by the way I still have the
Hotel though sometimes I think this is
nice too you know sometimes I just want
to go you know girl next door because
this gives you girl next door Vibes
doesn't it
I killed right
ah Straw Hat straw hat and and Cat air
is most popular let's go
this uh
foreign
have one I wish it was a girl next door
like that I love the straw hat on I wish
you were the girls
[Music]
just normal like this and straw hats
nickel Mimi zambo skin
ah
dang boy girl I still feel it right
they're all good options right simple
Yorkies
foreign
if you guys see anything wrong with it
by the way
let me know
anything besides the glasses that I need
to get fixed like I I would like ask for
something but
besides that it's all fine
[Music]
I think
he can't say I love it thank you I have
a complaint too cute can't focus
what something that looks wrong you're
too cute
okay okay okay stop
them
no you
and left princess the bags are wonky
your left on my left
I think the
breads are
okay I mean I I saw something there for
like a Split Second
it's difficult it's difficult it's
difficult to pinpoint
um
it's okay no as long as I get the the
glasses I'm okay ah
ah Okay so
thank you guys and in Germany we say
I'll be dancing you're gonna have to get
useless hairstyle I'm gonna be using it
for a while
[Music]
um
my mind bye bye bye bye bye bye
[Music]
Oh wrong whatever
I feel like you know this one or the
grass it also works really well or
anything I kind of wanted to like
separate them to this one and then the
grass originally
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
questions
[Applause]
things
[Music]
[Applause]