oh I got to ask you next time I go if I
ever go again because the wobbly Waters
have scared me off away from the wobbly
Waters yeah the wobbly Waters what the
what's the wobbly Waters danger danger
the biggest danger of England or London
I stayed in a fancy hotel okay The Valor
atoria in London s fancy already yeah
it's from the Hilton like group and they
have a pool they have an indoor pool
which is kind of why I chose the hotel
so I could get a little swim in and then
that you finally reach the the pool and
it's like mold everywhere on the wall
and the towels that I got they had like
holes and some some stains did you
complain I mean uh did I I don't think I
complained because like what this is
just like how it is I guess no no no no
it's not not at all what the it's
because it's a uh company