e
e e
hello hello
hi
guys hello hello
[Music]
everyone am I am I on I think I'm on
wait let
me each one of us introduce
themselves yeah
we go by
ABC
yeah okay
whatab hello everybody I'm Amelia Watson
hello live and number one detective At
Your Service uh
uh you don't use that so often do you
yeah I thought is that a new thing I
like it was new thank you I thought you
add it into the um the
Club I was
watch next is
Callie oh howdy I'm next hello this is
cumori from whole live English what's
up all that good hi nice to see you
guys welcome I am recovering I was I was
a bit uh under the very under the
weather yesterday I'm doing a bit better
today though and very excited to play
with you ladies yay anticipating
woo
[Music]
yay who
who my name g girl I'm on gtic phone I
draw with a mouse
okay Mouse but you're good with your
mouse drawing so I'm well it will be an
issue no no no no no I actually draw
worse with a tablet believe it or
not I find that hard to believe yeah I
really understand that yeah I really not
used to it then yeah probably we all
have our tools of choices yes also I'm
eating chicken nuggets okay chicken
nuggets yum hopefully
no chicken flavor where where did you
get them from
um all all had a restaurant
[Music]
CH should have been C oh I mean I got
them from kfp
K yes of
course next up for introduction Iris
maybe could also be Ena but according to
Discord is IR oh okay okay Discord um
hiis it's Iris I
I the uh somewhat new um Holan project
hope V singer theyed uh last month yeah
for those who don't know me hi RIS uh
I'm very excited this is my first time
collabing with all my stop
laughing I'm
sorry Santa
sorry
sorry that doesn't work
apologize
apolog apolog that sounds yummy well
Iris how confident are you in your
drawing
skills yeah yeah yeah yeah I'm I'm just
SK seems to be a mystery uhuh yeah I
haven't I haven't drawn yet actually but
I've I've been telling people on my
streams that yeah I'm I'm Godly at
drawing but that that's just that's just
me um you know put giving putting a
really um strong face in front of them I
want to tell you guys the truth
now I I I draw with Mouse I mean I do
have a tablet too but like g i I can't I
can't draw with a tablet yes oh really
Mouse
drawers awesome art yes okay looking
forward to your masterpieces yeah
masterpieces I a question are we going
to like when we play We mute everyone
else like uh kind of an Among
Us that's a good
idea I think uh but since it's like the
first uh Hol full Holo en collab since
Iris joined I think for the sake of
having conversation we should not mute
okay as long as we don't like give away
what we're
writing yeah exactly exactly
yeah all right Ina
introduction what hello I'm n in from
Life
English
um uh welcome back
Ina yeah welcome
back but um yeah I I I like to draw I'm
looking forward to drawing a lck
today yes okay here welcome
back and
me hello K Tak Phoenix this H I've
played this game a lot now today even
today I've played it in a separate
stream and I'm playing it three times
this week so I would like to say I'm the
master of GIC phone um let's freaking
[Music]
go indisputable Undisputed and with this
stream I think we would all like to give
a big big warm welcome to Iris welcome
to H live English
I'm still I'm pretty nervous but
yeah welome no no need to worry to
much yeah we're here to help
you I think we should start it off with
normal and if we if we want to we can
cuz we're just six people so the rounds
should probably be pretty short we can
try some other things too but normal I
think is the
bestest funniest I trust you Kiara I
trust you oh
okay
start
we yeah oh I okay let's go three two
one okay interesting an idea
uh
okay
um oh I'm really on the spot now
okay I already thought of this one since
I was a girl
uh I have mine
[Laughter]
already I I a hint ble I feel like like
very wide broad s suggestions make for
funnier
outcomes when they're open to
interpretation but mine definitely is
not the phone is ringing the you okay
have a time oh my god oh boy wonder who
was
that okay wait did I just give it away
are you not supposed to
say wait did I I don't you didn't I
don't think you gave anything away wait
we got we got got fast huh I've never
played this sorry I don't know what I'm
doing I didn't do anything I didn't say
anything what we heard nothing G
anything I heard nothing I really heard
nothing yeah I was too distracted by my
lack of time I was talking about my
Roomba I think I left my Roomba going in
the uh the
kitchen
right you're using a Roomba I have a
Roomba I like to sit on
there five
six oh dear I don't know what I'm
doing we got I can't know what that time
is how much time is that oh my God we
don't enough
time almost half time oh
sh um this is the warmup round
right warm up round we have so much time
to draw so many different things don't
worry about it right
okay I got to warm up
my my drawing skills what the hell is
this what do you mean what the hell is
this
I I lost my drawing brain somewhere I
can't find
it draw the best things anyway come on
no this is a hard
one oh it's been 5,000 years since I
last yeah I feel so awkward drawing this
okay was it
y beautiful
um time is taking
girls a tip if you add a little bit of
color will make it so much easier to
recognize who you're
drawing I hope this is
enough also don't don't write anything
to your drawings writing is okay okay no
writing you tell me
that God damn it that Mak it way too
easy I can't put like an exclamation
like oh no oh exclamation I think
to
late why is there so many of me
oh all right uh well now I know the
rules is is okay uh okay this is easy
this
is um what is
this oh this is
adorable um this is what I get from
Dad time is sticking
oh you guys you guys don't get to see
what I wrote here one sec I'll make
we'll see it at the end just kidding I'm
excited why is there so much
about what the
hell
interesting I see I
see I don't know how to draw this
without being
God
uh
oh h
uh where's the oh on the right side you
have some tools right you can erase and
you can also go steps back oh steps back
okay oh you have a you have a custom
HTMI as well that's nice I'm going to
use
[Music]
this never mind it oh yeah it does work
I'm just
dumb by the way today I'm playing
Christmas music on my stream I hope you
I was going to put music on
Christmas music is so nice the bells and
everything ah made me feel so nostalgic
cuz it's music that I went that I was
using uh during the Christmas time so
nostalgic usual oh God I don't have
time yeah not a lot of time here
huh not a lot of time can you zoom in
music makes me sleepy uh no zooming I
think
[Music]
hey how to how to draw
her fan artists love this girl uhoh
uhoh
time yum
yum oh no uh hand facing this way
it would look like okay so there would
be fingers
okay um wow this is rough this is rough
you guys no no no you shut
[Music]
up oh yes
artist I mean uh I forgot what what
uh nice weather today isn't it yeah
that's it's very dark outside I can
barely
tell oh wait wait wait wait this this
are
now everybody will know who it is
right just
kidding what the
hell oh my God this is pretty right oh
no who drew
this I mean I like it I don't have a
problem with
it you guys can't oh I have my knee
blocked whoops what I want to make I'm
louder oh you can't see the game
Sorry thank
you oh I'm going to steal what I saw
from the
last are we supposed wait is there like
points you can get like are we supposed
to be guessing what people are drawing
like no in this mode there's no points
no no oh all right I I don't know what
this uh this means but
okay I am
confused so Iris how how does it feel
after one month in whole life
English I'm feelingly getting used to
everything yeah yay but it's everything
still doesn't feel Is that
real yeah it is actually not real it is
all a dream Iris oh wow this is one long
Hab dream wake up wake up there we go
yes don't wake up the dream is so nice I
also don't want to wake up I've decided
to never wake
up Wake Me Up Inside idea I can't can't
wake up can't wake up save
me save me
uh
right
right so SC how do you maintenance your
hair battling oh my hair yeah it takes a
good two two to three hours styling it
ready mhm yep I woke up super early for
this
Dam sounds rough I thought that was like
so set in place you don't need to like
you you wake up like this I wake up like
this oh it's even it's it's worse when I
wake
up oh God it's all over hey does it
tangle a lot do you have to like are you
string with tangling yeah my my my
hairbrush my hairbrush gets a lot yeah a
lot of hair just gets wanked off when
I'm brushing it yep have you seen those
videos where people clean their hair
brushes out after like two months or so
and the water's like brown why why only
after two months I don't know maybe two
weeks oh my
God don't well I think I'm this is
beautiful no one will understand it oh
we're done one before you start I think
um oh yeah it's already then and
actually we should do auto so we all see
it at the same time normally I do manual
but I guess Auto a auto SK three two one
[Music]
you
m giving a present to
ours didn't know we were supposed to
write I'm
sorry Merry
Christmas I hope you like this
Iris D is scared of hope I'm still
warming
up I understand this game now a stick
figure nice stick figures are Godly wow
this is beautiful are really good I like
theman beautiful you you guys can um
save save the album if you click on the
button to save it oh someone want to be
on Save Duty or I I will do it okay okay
okay okay shall we go to the next album
I draw the present
next
right Sant suspect descendant another
Sant
nice oh my God wait if that oh search
dominance and
Santa wait wait wait Santa dominance I
thought I couldn't think of anything
besides
deposing what this jingle jangle where's
where's
jingle jingle jle jingle bell
I'm wearing a
leotard very cute I wasn't sure if that
was even still about um Iris but I just
put her in there I guess I was right by
putting her in there I guess how did you
guess Iris yeah because of the jingle
jangle yeah made me think of Christmas
and I was like hm I guess I'll put Iris
in there cuz she loves Christmas so much
doesn't she that's true that true
right yeah
yeah you like it much more once you get
to know these five
Santas Santa us yeah become
Santa become as
Santa fear oh
noa's
album
oh that is very cute
you you understand it oh
no hey
Watson sorry walk in front of the camera
I like this one I see I
see that is so cute yeah C really
enjoyed that Bey uh manga that we read
together I liked the plot and it was
very dramatic I enjoyed it
right yes
next next album
MTI Dr you came up with that idea yeah I
was playing with the Discord thing and
it got messed
upack
uhoh
uhoh oh
[Laughter]
escalated a little bit let's
go Mor's album
us uh do you know what is I recently
know found out
yes oh no
oh my God said it was
Callie it
was finish mine yeah I don't have hor oh
my
God I didn't
notice beautiful there's a dolphin there
or is
that I thought it was a
dolphin realism uhoh sing ban accident
not
bad oh my God good you wanted the
CH I got that one yeah oh cute what is
blepping
mean I don't know what Bing
is oh my God I love these
beautiful beautiful everyone really good
was a nice first round
ladies fast we shall do
more should we do another normal
one I don't know what are you suggest
what are the other moons well the others
are partially pretty difficult um for
example um I think maybe sandwich could
be interesting people have been
suggesting suggest suggesting sandwich a
lot yummy do it want to do that one we
can try stop trying and keep drawing
Until the End finally describe the last
drawing we will understand when it
happens oh is it going to like layer all
of our drawings on top oh I think so
like a sandwich oh I see I get it so
stop I
guess
can Bo okay
okay um what is the suggestion
[Music]
I think that's good that's a good one I
think it's good I can't think of
anything yeah that's the problem I had
that lot
to I'm excited for your promps
everyone
yeah I mean something simple
screw it let's let's do something fun
let's get wild C doesn't have to be
something crazy doesn't have to be okay
oh oh
yeah I like this a I see oh God the time
time is taking so quickly oh God
[Music]
okay I had idea okay
[Laughter]
why would I give
up shut up Cy shut
up don't shut up Cy talk I can't let I
can't let you know what I'm drawing
uhoh I just feel like making it
cursed curs is spond do
cursed okay you bet you girl you betcha
[Music]
how it different from the other one I
think we will see starting from the next
round
oh uh
um I fit
everyone
H oh yeah art skills coming at
you yeah oh I'm so oh
yeah you're
going why does it not let you save your
color you should have like a custom
color Bank you can
save
unfortunately oh no I'm not going to
make it uh don't worry other people will
finish your drawing maybe oh oh that's a
good idea so maybe we should leave room
for others maybe oh probably yeah I'm
not
sure
uh gu she
[Music]
okay oh my God I'm Mist taking oh no oh
no no oh no no wait
no uh
oh
uh okay okay at least it's recognizable
I
think I think this is pretty it's not
recognizable
H yeah okay okay okay let's see what
happens oh this is
nice I
see oh God everything is going
turn ah this is really cute this is
adorable thank you thank
you wait what all right I got it we're
going point for Point
here
yeah oh okay I forgot the whole drawing
okay okay I think I
remember oh my God I don't remember I
already forgot I have a Pur brain okay
how am I supposed to remember that also
I don't even know what was going on
there uh-oh uhoh got to be fast oh yeah
he definitely
[Music]
got oh no oh
god um I'm so
sorry I keep wanting to control Z you
can you can't you can't control how many
people in such short
time oh my god I've been doing it
you can't pick a custom color you
can you have to click the big big Swatch
I see yeah
oh yo okay you me something know that
how do I there we go uh you learn
something new every day
[Music]
yeah there was some something like that
in between wait 1 2 3 4
I don't have
[Music]
space hey this isn't half bad I think
I'm improving I think we're seeing
improvements oh shoot the phone is
ringing
uhoh wait now you wait for me game you
wait for me or I'll be
angry I'll be angry you don't want the
no
[Laughter]
wait oh what's happening
[Music]
more second yeah that'll have to
do that'll have to
do is
this that
music wake up alarm oh my God what is
this wait does this time count as well
oh my
God what what okay okay okay what all
right this is a
no-brainer
what okay didn't notice there was a a
bucket oh wait it didn't work bucket
bucket
um something like
that this is really
difficult I like this
game I also enjoy this game yeah this is
pretty good Simplicity Simplicity is the
way to
go uh um what happened to
you also there's like someone missing
here oh
man now I actually still have time damn
it are we supposed to be doing this like
as accurate as we can or think so oh
yeah yeah yeah much as we can remember
right mhm and your artistic
interpretations of
so I'm so
[Music]
done I I captured the essence of
it I don't know about this one
I actually had it in it in early cuz
there was no no more to say I guess the
reference was just so simple uhoh oh
wait no no no no no no I'm not
done I really want to know what the what
the title to this piece of art is oh my
God I the time shorter and shorter
yeah it seems like is it oh maybe I'm
pretty sure is it sandwich I think
sandwich is like that sandwich all right
we're we're going in we're doing the
best we can with the tools we have there
we what is this that's adorable I don't
what okay okay it's hard not be able to
talk about it cuz I just want to make
jokes about what I'm
seeing okay I think you can make gra
jokes about it also after the on we see
it anyway
so write it down
remember
it oh okay
okay yeah looking good ladies looking
good beautiful and then there was
a Oh my brain power who is Asing right
now we can all do it if you want if you
desire that something maybe later
was it like
this I don't know what happened
here uh oh yeah can we get like a
Pur a different
color
nice nice oh cute wait wait wait wait
not going to have enough time uhoh
amazing feel like my drawing SK skills
are evolving through every single
round person who did this
yeah I'm going to be even better than I
was before I'm not going to have enough
time I don't know who this
is you you the time traveler out of all
people don't doesn't have enough time I
can't stop
time just go back in time and add some
to
it that's
cheating oh okay wow you're fair you're
Fair player huh mhm
nice she doesn't use her skills like
that I respect that
Iris I'm not going to steal that you
know came up with that it's beautiful
that was a good one that was a real good
one
OHA I think this is pretty accurate No I
don't know what happened
H there's one more one more thing to do
by the way five of the six so and then
then we'll
steal you're evil I hope you know
that I love it what oh oh God ow oh did
you hear that ow that was my hip
bone hi
bone Grand grandma
the have the same issues though I really
want that brace that you were talking
about I want a brace for my full body
yeah the shoulder brace to make sure you
don't hunch over like the hunchback yeah
be nice a good purchase you can get one
of those gamer rigs lay
back uhoh should we do manual because
it's beenin so fast actually want to go
for it slower let's do display mode
manually okay and you can open it up on
your own
okay okay I see here I detangling her
hair but getting stuck okay okay I think
I did a pretty good job that's cute so
cute so cute wow that's pretty cute yeah
she has a lot of things stuck in there a
lot of mas stuck in there wait so do we
all get the same
we same image I don't think maybe we did
at one I saw people's images I have to
memorize it and then like draw it yeah
that oh let's let's check out
gas oh good job that's good yeah
job did you know good that what was
going on when you saw that image did you
I idea I now I just thought it was
Iris singing
no yeah she has that hopeful expression
in her face yeah it was more of a the
scar look
but all right let's see
Watson's You're all going for the
singing
theme getting like the music notes made
it look like it yeah oh all right and
Iris draws
herself beautiful
oh my
conclusion saying what do has some dope
vocal
[Music]
cords yeah how about for each album uh
each person who led the album says next
next next and we follow that person uh
you know what I mean yeah sounds good
okay next is Ina
okay what did I write comments
is T
tomorrow tomorrow what shouldn't didn't
it just start today
again you know what happens when Taco
Time ends what what oh wait wait only
when only I can open it you guys open
sorry okay I'll open there we go
yeah
one
taco nice interpretation
tacos happier and happier went from y to
happy I think how I I know how this one
ends I see you right out of time there
uh yeah the Paint Bucket continued to
betray me over and over again have an
opening I can see
them hey
oh no it's dead it's dead I'm not sure
anymore if it was alive or not so I
ended up drawing it
dead oh no well that makes sense
according to the first
one oh no
inace this is what happens when Taco
Time ends I guess
so
[Applause]
okay would you like to read your pump
underneath no I don't want to read I
change my
mind
my what's under my desk who's under
there what could be underneath detective
desk I know it's underneath the
detective
desk oh no
dra
IR I got I got a blame Iris for this one
I got blame very confident I did it
perfectly I'm sure you
[Laughter]
did Bubba has got arms
bub and what I thought when I saw that
was good at
kill a beautiful progression of events
she look so
smug oh it's beautiful it's like rug
Red very good I love it all right on
next one what please read uhoh missile
being launched ready for
takeoff is a missile missile
oh my
God thanks it's my G
missile my G
missile scfb
for why do I look like Among
[Applause]
Us else
though Iris just no Ena Ena disappeared
from the drawing yeah I I didn't one by
one one by one gone I love way I love
kar's hat and iris's
joy well I count it very
simple
Bor
wait it was
rocket thing just disappeared I forgot
about the orange
Under I thought it was
Pac-Man what a turn we've taken an
artistic rition of
Pac-Man oh
wow creatures including
Amelia mytical creature I was going to
add in including the British
but there wasn't enough letters yeah I
love the face on on all of them oh my
God
especially accurate very well done
lady next
one yeah call
oh Ian pillow fight show it to me show
me what you
got drawing this
fight for pillow a
little I really pan
drawing six people your hair your hair
grew out look how long it tall
order long hair am I think my detached
from my
head I miss me some
pillows all right I had no idea what was
going on but all right I tried on the
floor there was no space so I made
really small dead I've been trampled
it's fine we can
move it's okay I think I think I saved
you I think I saved you thank you have
apex predator apex trbl predator
it's okay
yeah who how am I supposed to follow up
with this I
have maybe don't make a prom I didn't
finish I see you also time um it wasn't
it was these people's a lot have learned
my
lesson I mean technically that could be
correct because fights are
batt I was thinking
about would nevering we're hazing
you no good good ha fun
kind the fun kind
kind of are you proficient in battle in
B what what battle all kinds of
battle Yeah Yeah I have I have magic
powers how many have killed until now no
I'm hope I don't kill
people you need to leave that to
me don't let me catch you killing folks
I will have to get you for that you guys
are the monsters you're the ones who
kill
I don't
know all righty next up Iris Iris please
read your prompt you're a suspect I'm
investigation
okay
okay um I miss the Trident I
think the
Trident I forgot aboute your okay let's
go yeah this definitely
color oh no that is cute made it better
oh no so nice I can't
expain you
bur I thought on
fire a fire today don't stop don't stop
all right oh
was the spider yes I thought it was
and then my nuggets might come back up I
have to be
careful my stomach
hurts
power is that your power you got so
close I would I thought somebody would
interpret it afterwards so I just cuz I
don't
know she can harness the power of the
sun yeah
science exactly I saved them
all I will send them we all afterwards
we have um we have
that's we have
10 bit more I think we can squeeze in
another normal round noral noral do cuz
the first one was only 15 minutes
yeah all right okay let's do
it
okay okay um
think
[Music]
K Chad got any
ideas
copyight okay I'm waiting for some
suggestions
submissions I hope I hope some someone
really good gets that
prompt this is going to turn not amazing
thanks
Chad okay
hydrated party
[Music]
time I blew it I like that
a
oh oh uh all right I'm on it leave it to
me okay not great I ran out of time my
prompt is possibly interesting
oh no problem that's just that just
makes it better you know as I'm saying
maybe I left it really vague we have to
see what others come up with
[Music]
uh um
H oh boy what does this look
like
um so we have this here reference
picture um oh gosh uh and then this
one okay to write a letter in
this since this is a topic right wait
this this pretty much true
though and then oh my God
sh beautiful oh I feel I feel I feel it
I feel it I just feel it it's
beautiful
[Applause]
T I did not think out the composition of
this picture very well before I started
drawing it oh my goodness I wait to see
everyone streams after
this
uh um maybe should add some more color
to
this no it's not that ch
made
green I'm
panicking I don't know what to
doing okay I'm no wait no I need a
little more
time oh
no oh my
God that know was
thata yeah well I mean
this is pretty
[Music]
[Applause]
easy I wonder who got
mine this might sound better does this
sound better it sounds better that
sounds
better beautiful all right what is this
here we go what that
what does that mean oh easy oh I just
described what I um oh jeez
oh I need to Google someone real
quick
uh what is
that what what
is no no no no I'm Googling no no I'm
Googling this one but chat tell me what
is that what is that I don't speak this
language of
memes wait okay I'll draw what I think
is happening okay
um I think I know who this is
maybe and if I could draw this could be
really cute but I can't what's a turn
huh oh
um
uh I need to
drama
uh
okay okay uh uh uh
uh yeah
[Music]
not interpret
this what are you
okay are you good you're
good K's not good she's gone she's gone
she's gone car she's disappeared
forever oh no
oh God are you okay are you good okay we
need to call an
ambulance dying oh no Phoenix is
dying help do
something oh wait
wait oh no can't
what what what I don't recognize who
this is
what just playing my cards real straight
just playing my cards real straight chat
check it
out who is this is this okay okay okay
okay I got
this is that a sword I don't I know what
this
is my eyes are oh no I didn't have
enough time uh oh what does this mean
Chad what does this mean oh my God Don't
Make Me draw so many people again I
don't know what this means oh but yes I
do
uh of course I know what this
means uh
uh I
don't
um okay we can do this we can do this we
can do
[Music]
this yep all
right okay
okay uh yeah I think this my
be to Google
[Music]
this
okay um what we have to we have to do
oh
understandable
um I have given up
completely never give up never surrender
this is what this animal looks like I I
I don't I lost hope even though hope is
right next to me right next to you right
next to you
girl just look say I'm next to you girl
yeah oh wow I that wow that's I don't
know that's kind of
charming why is That's So Charming I
don't
know
uhoh oh
[Music]
no there everybody's going to know what
this is right
yeah yeah oh
no you someone than
usual lot of time lots of time we don't
have lots of time we only second I'm
done we go what's happening all
right oh my god well we starts out
with I expect greatness from
this that's good that's solid oh no like
I
know
brains shark sleaves and it turn that's
why you got cut off I don't want to I
think I know where this leads too oh
no you love to see it all unravel why is
G why are G and Amy always dead in these
things yeah why are I always dying what
good
want
real very real oh my
God we went on a little trip there can
we have aama laugh
please oh my god did you practice that
yes God
damn say I can hear this imagine it
sounds exactly like
that sound
perfect oh man okay
next yeah Lego
Lego I really just couldn't
yeah he looks like a looks like a Sesame
Street character
Muppet going wrong you you K that was y
I guess because it's the only male creep
person that we draw the position of the
Lego was a little weird to
me looks like it's about dominate
explain this this was the the one where
I started dying by crying oh no and I
also don't know I also didn't know what
teabagging
meant this is what
happened what what is I don't know what
he's putting a teabag I it laughing when
when I was drawing his face look like
a in a bag at a at a
supermarket wow that's yeah that's very
y go Bing
bro uh
so master of finances
this I thought you meant banking like
you Bank a turn I didn't think of
money it's okay this is what D phone is
living
for okay I didn't finished my
prompt this is the one you talking about
yes I my brain
um I leave it up to your interpretation
okay L room for
interpretation I mean that's pretty cut
and dry oh my God
[Music]
what it's the M it's
[Laughter]
Airy this is good
investigation this in her natural
habitat yeah I mean everything looks
normal to me basically good
[Applause]
stuff oh this fix the
turn I'm
sorry there's opacity in
this why
close oh well you know it it went it it
became so hot that they melted into one
body I some babies in a
monster I
misinterpreted monkey that is so cute
return to Monkey monke
around
cute oh
I love that love it I love it monkeys
look like
monke
monkey oh
sponge I'm just stating a fact saw in
the you come
that yeah just so we don't get in
trouble
the right person got that one yeah good
[Laughter]
job so good
smash
why nothing beats one
the
smash this is good this is a good one
smash
we
okay Ena puns destroying the world oh
this is a good prompt this is good uhoh
my brain I didn't know how to oh I
didn't finish
anyway I mean same thing same
thing oh that's a good one
same thing you understand each other
this is the the telepathy that we have
after almost a
year
wow it showed it actually showed all the
letters capitalized so uh I didn't know
that there was an Ena pun in there I
just guessed oh wow good guess my
intuition trained for puns pack a world
domination with Halloween
yeah with the homies
cute no time to draw so many people
again nice
one nice job
everyone that was a lot of very good job
I had a blast wow I will I will send
them to you afterwards everyone can pick
one to upload on Twitter or five or two
how many ever you want yeah yeah we have
a lot of lot of gifts gifts but okay by
the way how do do you guys say
GI G oh no oh no oh w a GI a Jer a GI
I'm a jfer my name ISF is
a what
is it's h it's GIF is it not hello my
name I usually say GIF when I speak
German I think and when I speak English
I tend to say gif
yes interesting I remember this being a
hot debate many years ago yeah it was it
was the pineapple on pizza before
pineapple on pizza was a thing the GI
for the
gift yet
okay announcement we got an announcement
we do have an
announcement we have one long long
waitting long long awaited announcement
from
the yes we have an announcement
everyone shall we open it
up
count
three okay who count
down you want to
down please sure sure okay three two
one oh no I covered everyone's p
[Music]
finally cration mascot plushies it's
almost one
year half year it's already been way
over half a year M will be one
year it's finally
ready so cute tomorrow it looks like or
later today I think huh like uh very
soon like h what's 15 minus
9 MTH whoa that was fast you did
[Applause]
that mathematical G who are you
what sorry gar is taking
over
imposter well uh the the Boo and gek
Jack page is got going up in
approximately 5
minutes and the tweet on Hol live
English Twitter is coming out in I think
20 minutes if they don't decide to put
it out earlier now but should be coming
out in 20 minutes right yeah
soones are uh quite
big seen them everyone can their other
details yeah show show show your your
ones guys I got death Sensei I
got for the individual check it out
Sensei 35 cm that's big you guys 35 cm
is Big yeah they're hug totally hugable
I heard they're really really
soft yes they're they're soft I can
confirm I have touched them
before question do we have a picture of
Yago holding them I wonder I don't think
least not
yet not yet but eventually hopefully we
in the fut so
round I'm so very
this is only because we need it for
scale for for
imagination no other reason wait we have
a picture some people don't think in
centimeters we have a picture do we I
thought you guys were talking about one
okay that's we not yet okay not yet yeah
H life's number one model you know what
these look like they would fit perfectly
in a T-shirt cannon they'd be really
good ammunition yeah you can shoot them
out oh we can have a pillow with these
plushies
oh throw them around batt of the
Gods no it does not come with Yago
unfortunately we're sorry but Yago could
honestly like just quit his CEO job and
become a model at this
point GQ is calling is that what it's
called GQ I think it's that I'm not
really
sure what's kikik I thought it's like a
like a magazine for mods I was thinking
D like d
que I'm craving a milkshake now ages
milkshake yeah that's a good point when
uh when we all eventually meet we need
to have a big pillow fight with
these stream it l are you down yeah yeah
yeah I'll stream
it don't really want to put them into my
luggage cuz they're going to be big can
you are you getting all of them are you
getting all them
M probably carry one as a carryer but
then they be questioning
you they're going to look inside they're
going to open them up and be like what
did you hide a bomb inside of
the then I have to cut them open it'll
be
surgery I cannot risk that
dissection oh no please
no wonder if there cotton in there
though is there anything else besides
cotton in there out I
guess
Cott are there beans in there I think
it's more like the soft like plushy yeah
they're really soft I've touched them oh
you tou yes I have I have held them and
I have touched them I want to squish the
face and distort it make funny yeah I've
touched those as well they're very
soft all right well Iris how how did you
like your first collab with live English
it was a lot of fun I love to play
gartic everyone's art art levels are
just out of the
world I like your thank figures have a
ton of Personality actually and that's
not me being ironic or sarcastic they
actually you did a very good job thank
you we are so glad to have have you in
this
collaboration thank you would like to
collab with all of you guys again yeah
yeah let's keep doing it yeah yeah some
of us just like me have not done a
one-on-one collab with you yet
yeah today was the first time for me to
collab with
you coll with half of you guys oh wait
yeah yeah let's do it soon
Iris Minecraft
Minecraft give you an official tour of
the Ian server so you don't get
everyone's buildings we'd love to show
you around yeah yeah let me show you
phoenixon I think you might have
actually already stumbled into phoenixon
but great is isn't it like the
restaurant the restaurant no no that's
kfp but uh I've heard you stumbled into
a big
Village Golems yeah oh oh by the way
Iris the hole that you fell into
now that we're all here um I fell into
that hole uh a few months ago several
times and lost a lot of things and I was
always wondering who made that who dug
that hole who dug that hole wasn't me I
asked my viewers and no one has any
record of anyone ever digging that hole
on on on stream but I I kept it open
because I was like well well I want the
person who dug it to F fall into it but
then Iris fell in
we need to know who the suspect
is was not g who did it maybe it was me
she's in the server M okay my own chat's
blaming me what is this what you mean it
was gura because you were like oh oh
uhoh or something like that you were
like reacting suspiciously suspicious oh
God we need an
investigation maybe it was hatama who
was said I wonder that hole of
death hole out of nowhere kfp like if
you go through kfp back to like
spawn
yeah I'm responsible for the the stairs
uh in kfp I will own up to that not that
hole not that hole different hole then I
don't know a different different hole
that's like one block wide but uh 5
million blocks yeah it goes straight
down it's out in the middle of nowhere
and when you just like there somebody du
straight down who would straight
down yeah do that someone straight up no
no it must have been straight down yeah
yeah yeah could be somebody that got
lost and they were trying to maybe just
uh make a a landmark or something or no
it's like really close to my house so
what if you did it Kiara you don't
remember W the others no no no no I I
knew nothing about this
I like this conspir this conspiracy
theory I guess this will continue to be
a mystery then it's a mysty does anybody
have are we gonna cover that hole or we
just gonna leave it there sign just
warning sign a sign there yeah it's it's
a memorial it's an important part of
Holan
history
yeah yeah yeah what were you saying um
does anybody have any like individual
announcements like maybe a stream you're
going to do or something like that oh
yeah uh so tomorrow um I have a Koke
stream with a special guest a guest who
is not in Hol live so I hope you guys
will come check it out we're doing uh
archived and also unarchived stream so
please
comeing thank you that's all I have
anyone
else um I'm going to
play uh
police officer officer GAA OH police
simulator yeah and we're going to
continue dou My Cry finally so that's
all I
got all right um all right then I'll say
next week I'm playing Minecraft with my
real mother uh on my
channel and it will it will actually be
amazing cuz for the people who don't
know my my mother is better at Minecraft
than all of us here is's really good and
she will teach me um some stuff and we
will go get never ride together yah I
need to see this I must she'll teach me
how to farm never ride it will be fun so
my mama will be on our server for one
day you guys are you guys are welcome to
join in for a minute and introduce my
mother
pleas Phoenix yes oh my God I want to
say hello I didn't say you guys were
want to do that oh I I didn't think so
okay go ahead please please you're
welcome of course you want to say hi my
mom knows about all of you she uh check
all of your streams out you got to think
of some embarrassing stuff to tell to
tell
yeah babyct baby
pictures no I didn't have manyu FS back
then it was n n n n
n n
[Laughter]
you okay anyone else with
announcements
uh I'll be streaming subnotica later on
today ring fit finally got
my ring
fit no no not your virus just some
healthy
exercise right we all need that I'm
looking forward to it
health that didn't work out anything
anyone else anyone
else no I have a a morning show that I'm
going to be doing hopefully week weekly
but uh I had the first one is going to
be on Sunday but I'll be gone for two
weeks after that and then when I come
back we'll do another
one morning
is the nameit that's cute
too Amit in the am in
the momy yeah smart title oh thank you I
will be watching it it might the archive
but I will be watching it
yeah you and me we are Orlando this
weekend yeah if anybody's heading out to
Megacon in Orlando Florida in the USFA
uh you can meet or talk to us or uh show
up at our panel I believe um mine is
tomorrow and Kiara's is the day after
yeah on Saturday you're on Friday and uh
oh yeah if you if you can't attend it in
person if you have a ticket then you can
actually watch your stream of it so you
don't have to be there in person but you
still need a ticket there is a stream
mm nice good to
know so everyone we're looking forward
to seeing you that is the the first one
that off the Holan in America
conventions America and Canada
conventions tour let's
go domination we're going on tour I
can't believe we're going on tour guys
yeah yes so cool Okie
doie shall we say goodbye yeah I think
the booth should be up by now question
it Bo is up now Bo and check Link in the
Des
I guess watching everybody hope you had
thank you
guys
[Music]
yay have
to okay Zan everyone say
byee
byus andus
[Music]
okay for