[Music]
n
for
[Music]
n
K
[Laughter]
oh K is back oh my god oh oh I mean I
know I've been like kind of back a
couple streams already but this stream
really is the
the proof that I'm back but for how long
well not for much
long I
guess
because
I I'm not I'm not sure if I will stream
on the
30f but the 31st for example you guys do
you guys know I will will show up on why
am I starting directly into tangents
like no time to lose let's go let's go
alarm alarm alarm like the fire fire
people that like go down the stripping
pole when they have an alarm and
stripping Pole right into just like me
for real for real right into the hole
fan yes
fan it's a stripping Pole
yeah yeah yeah uh do you guys know
though that I'll be in uh like a free to
watch as far as I know I think it's free
to watch on
YouTube uh concert
of
seemingly almost all of whole life
Japan like a New Year's Eve kind of
concert
m
yeahuh one of the reasons why I'm going
to
[Laughter]
Japan wait what some some didn't know oh
no I did not know oh well I figured some
people might have missed the
announcement uh yeah
um
myth okay I guess from Whole Life
English it's only myth but minus you
know
so uh me GAA Kelly and
Amma together will perform as a
group uh a song
yeah mhm yeah everyone with a 3D mod
yeah but without Ina but besides that I
think every probably in the whole life
Japan probably everyone's
participating um probably ID first gen
yeah yeah yeah yeah then they even put
up a
list of who's performing and I
think did they even include which
song I feel like maybe they
did I don't know why they made it
so so like why I spoiler the whole set
list
yeah had to learn the choreography but
um it's it's quite
simple I said we have to lower the the
Simplicity of the choreography quite a
bit not for me but you
know anyway pouring some
tea I said no no if possible like almost
no formations because
it's not going to work out
otherwise don't
trust like beginners to do formations
like
what
okay formation
AKB
48 you guys know that song it's a really
old um ak48 song where you know I really
didn't like it uh back then nor did I
really like it now U but they start the
song with one like without music one
lady screams AK and then they start
stomping and
clapping 48 and then they go on to like
Stomp and clap like really fast in their
choreography for
minutes and then I don't know that's the
whole thing with that song but I don't
like it no not like a cheer group but I
don't it's weird but it's interesting
[Music]
H what was the name
again see I I know some old AKB songs
too River yeah it's cool yeah I guess
it's cool but I didn't like
it yeah it's it's kind of weirdly
military style you get it oh mic you get
it you just get it the others wouldn't
get it but you get
it river river oh yeah yeah yeah one
reason I didn't like it is because the
song is called River but they always say
and sing
liver I'm so sorry
but I just couldn't take it seriously
I'm
sorry liver
liver liver
liver
liver liver H
liver you mentioned before no I don't
think I've ever mentioned this song
before ever buttered animal liver yeah I
have to think about liver the food oh
it's interesting how the first thing how
I describe it is food even though I
don't like I wouldn't eat liver uh the
food did I just say yeah Li the food
it's not first and foremost of food
[Laughter]
kiala organ organ it's concerning
concerning it maybe it's not concerning
cuz you eat it in a lot of
places
K smovie is currently trying to find the
P cuz I was eating Puro before the
stream and she was going crazy and then
I put it away and now she is looking for
it hoping to find it but I I I do think
she cannot possibly open the fridge on
her own I would hope
so
n I'm okay by the way it's just like
um I
uh I don't I don't produce I don't
really produce fum
anymore but uh I feel like my
current coughs come from a shortness of
breath which is why I was thinking they
should have given me an inhaler too but
oh
well so anyway I have tea I have water
and don't I know it's not good for my FR
but I have some Coca-Cola cuz it's left
over from yesterday and I like I haven't
drunken drunken Coca-Cola in a long time
it's it's
yummy minan let's go kill let's do it
until the
end which shouldn't be too far away
anymore since I split it into two parts
last time and off screen since I was
bored as I did some leveling and
[Music]
why is it so black
screen okay I also
tried what the I also tried to um
find some shinies and
outbreaks really just not really forcing
it anyway just trying to find it oh
there you are
by uh
yeah breaking up outbreaks no game audio
sorry there you
go mhm found a shiny yesterday was a
H well yeah I had no luck with
finding a shiny of course I didn't have
any luck with it but as you can see
we're currently around level 70 I think
I did like 10 levels or
so
so no way n
n ah there there you
go how
[Music]
now too loud too quiet that's over
really I you know that actually I didn't
even want to level that much that's why
I eventually stopped but this all came
from killing so many mobs at the
outbreaks I got like 10 levels from that
but that's why I think that we won't
have so much issue with the finale
that's not Overkill that's actually
perfect I was thinking so that probably
around 70 is probably
[Music]
desirable
little loud
really okay I turned it down like by
2% Okay I lied I still have a little bit
of flum but it's colorless by
now and it's not it doesn't come out
that often
St out you guys are so
[Music]
picky
yeah it it at least doesn't disturb me
so much
anymore and my
my my sniffles aren't bad at you anymore
the way I had to blow my nose when I was
sick was insane I feel like I was
blowing my brains out
H really like now compared to how I I I
blow my nose
now is back then was like insane I feel
like my snot came from a different hole
or from from the depths of Moria or
so where a Balck is
usually h
what is
[Music]
Moria yeah whole different store
second and I think I was probably like
blowing too strong but it was kind of
necessary Narnia no Moria the mind of
Moria m
[Music]
ah want to watch Lo of the
Rings yeah it just it was never ending
and I had to get it out because when I
didn't try to get as much out as
possible I mean I I still kind of had
constantly the feeling of you
know in my
nose it was
necessary it was
necessary I was blowing way too strong
long H yeah I think I want to listen to
the Lord the Rings audible yeah I mean I
started with the Game of Thrones one the
other one that I'm going to get for free
is probably Lord of the
Rings anyway
so um I did not continue the story I
accidentally almost did but I did not uh
I think we have to go to the
school
so let's get into it baby my brother by
the way has left the
premises I'm sorry to my brother but he
understands he's very okay with it and
um I don't know what he's doing he said
he wanted to watch Avatar but he's got
no one to go with and he feels awkward
going
alone I would go with him but I'm the
reason why he's being kicked
out for some reason I'm producing a lot
of fum right
[Music]
now yeah I don't think watching a movie
I mean I understand like I don't like
doing it either but it's not too
bad that's something I think I I can
overcome certain things I definitely
don't want to do alone but then there's
other things that I think are fine to do
alone that you don't have to feel so
embarrassed about
but yeah when I was younger I don't
think I would have had the courage to go
to the movie theater alone because
because mostly because seeing all those
like younger kids Young no older kids
older kids and teenagers I feel like
they would look at me and be like yo
she's such a loser and I didn't want
them to think that of
me yeah let's offer an eating at a
restaurant
alone that's interesting because I don't
have that feeling at all and I think I
think I know
why I think before I lived in Japan I
had the same feeling like I wouldn't
want to go to a restaurant Alone um and
I guess we're talking not about like
McDonald's and so on but like proper
restaurants um but then in Japan
um eating out in restaurants dining out
alone seemed pretty normal and yeah very
normal actually and I used to go alone
so much so
then I guess I kind of like got used to
that and now back in Austria I don't
feel worried about it N is
a
I guess honestly just you should you
should not care about it I
mean I guess going to a restaurant
where like a really fancy one where a a
dish a meal costs a hundred bucks and
people go there with their
uh you know Partners maybe that could be
awkward but uh yeah I think besides that
really not really not a big deal well no
need to care so much about it I would
say I mean I understand why you would
because I've experienced it to am I
going the wrong
way I'm I'm playing for OBS right now
cuz honestly in this game it doesn't
matter was it
upstairs what's up
dog
[Music]
off oh yeah I almost ran into it because
I wanted to do the the tests off screen
but then I saw that if I go there
there's a story time so I avoided
it wasn't this
wasn't there the reason why we're
meeting here a call saying from what
what was the
name what the name
uh what's the
name not
Clive didn't didn't yeah CA call us to
meet and well you know I for the longest
time POA was a woman but I did
eventually see a spoiler somewhere are
telling uh me more or less indirectly
that it's a heat and ever since then I
was pretty
pissed that I I know that now now I'm
not even
surprised sup
K you got it down you got the language
down now you spoiled me oh oh come
on well I was spoiling I didn't like it
but now you have but you would have been
spoiled eventually by watching the
stream it would have
happened director cl cl why are we still
doing this why are we
still
H all right I go with cl oh come on my
name's Clive remember actually no it's
time for me to bring this little
performance to end it's NE CL no Clive
it's CIO OA allow me to reveal my true
identity okay he reveals that first
being
clel I do apologize for deceiving you
with my
disguise but I'm I'm thinking now
actually still I still don't know I just
know it's a he so I'm guess guessing
it's him which is so
stupid and true the boy you knew as CLI
was none other than the director of Theo
Academy Mr
CL waa no
[Music]
[Applause]
way my mind is blown I've been quite
possibly BM Boozled oh H wow master
of
disg this guy is master of this
guys
wow Pikachu face surpris Pikachu
[Music]
face Sona
banana Sona
banana unbelievable
sh I'm in shock right I don't I know how
we will recover from this maybe I can't
stream this until the end today after
all I don't know how to recover from
this it's too
shocking so
stupid yes this must be quite a
shock my disguise was perfect after all
regardless there's still one more
astonishing truth I must reveal to you
oh here it
[Music]
comes
yeah that one pisses me
off the true identity of C you pay the
big boss of Tu star was me all along
well at least that one I guess is not as
obvious as the other
one that makes me angry I don't know
why I I wanted a French lady to be cioa
[Music]
but it makes no sense to
me it's not even like they hit it well
they forcefully deceived
us
why is there so much
fum I'm getting it all out
now I still don't know why you made the
connection okay no I mean it didn't
necessarily have to be a French lady I
just I guess I was just trying to make
the voice or the character sound
different from the
others and that was my way of doing
it now no one said it was a lady but
then they never they never gave it like
a male or female article anyway which
you
know obviously they were trying to hide
something this makes me so mad it makes
me so
[Music]
mad oh that's
impossible Hest to goodness when you
heard CIO pay over the phone that was
actually a pre-recorded voice oh yeah I
was just about to say that um even
though most of the time he was trying to
avoid
cioa I think there were Still Moments
where he was on the phone at the same
time and no yo why you actually claiming
that was pre-recorded no way
that's such a stupid claim that's that's
just because they had no other idea how
to do this script without him being
there sometimes at least without be
making it too obvious that it's not him
cuz that didn't seem like pre-recorded
at all it was just no no
no that's
that's no no no no no no I want
to go back on all the conversations and
look at them and then and then say that
it makes no sense because like they had
like conversations that you couldn't
have
pre-recorded I'm so mad
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah exactly
Kevin exactly that's what he
saying just keep going
what
h no I'm
angry I pulled it off using uh you know
one of those Hightech gizmos oh yes it
was very
clever
[Music]
so miss kiaba now you know I'm the big
boss that means there's just one thing
left to
do face me one final
showdown to deci side it all that's in
my title by the way oh it's happening
right now oh
okay oh trying to listen to the
music interesting you're challenged by
director clav AKA Clive AKA
Cil he has so many
personalities he should sing that
vocalize song I think it's called jumman
Soul or
so really like that
song it's about like 10 different person
personalities I Cay of Team star and
that prompt went away way too
fast h ah 10 levels below but I think my
level will be more more accurate or more
fitting later
on all right he has the monkey the
orange Guru which I could be honestly
too an orange Guru going to torch it up
baby torch it torch it I know it doesn't
do that much damage but at least we're
preparing we preparing a sweep
oh so much for preparing wait if I kill
him this turn do I still fall
[Music]
asleep but even if I would have switched
out uh to get a more effective Pokemon
he would have still made that Pokmon
sleep pul guys so a ghost Pokmon
I don't know if I I think I'll stay and
just unsleep
myself those your
onion if you swapped it wouldn't have
fallen
asleep no no I mean in the first turn
already honestly
yeah switch to avoid yeah I know Swit
avoid sleep
but I wanted to keep my my special vom
boom um I'll
keep there's a wake up uh item
no
Awakening
yeah wake up wake up wake up on a
Saturday night could be New York maybe
how would you London Paris maybe
toky
tonight tonight yeah tonight hey at
least he didn't attack me in the first
turn I was a bit worried because ghost
and
ghost well here we
go got us Shadow Ball y
oh yeah he buffed himself but he's 10
levels below me what the
[Music]
my only super effective attack now
is crunch
but crunch is weak as
[Music]
it will probably still cool
hopefully yby but I'm probably not
faster am I also it's just five levels
above this
one let's go yeah he's first Willow whis
was that it doesn't affect me let's go
okay well thank
God that was such a
waste what just happened AB snow Obama
Snow uh that's a snow Pokemon right oh I
wish I had my fire Pokemon right now
what else could I
use tell me tell
me grass ice ah fire would be like
million time effective
should I
revive I guess I will have to I I
will Dear Mr
President come take a walk with
[Music]
me
oh that's a cool attack for an nice
Pokemon
Aurora cool wait so I revived my Pokemon
didn't I okay well it's half Health
but should be fine
right BN also okay it's okay I'll go
with
box yeah kfp fire
okay see it does
nothing oh I'm going to start um pumping
pumping Pump It
Up welcome to
kfp okay
okay okay okay or Le enemies take half
damage what but I still one hited him
Houndoom ooh that's probably like a dark
Pokemon right
what's
effective psychic or so
maybe no psychic
oh I don't have
water ah I do have
fighting
okay okay out
guys
Hound all right oh ground is also super
effective guys I guess because of the
Fire H I'll do close
combat but this this this Hound is so
big just remembered cuz I'm watching Tad
lasto right now and I just got to the
second um season I don't know if you
guys watched it but oh
amongus ah it's kind of ironic cuz he
was the impostor
amongus but anyway in the first episode
of season 2 a dog
dies and by a soccer ball though sport
alert I'm wrapping a blanket around
myself cuz my PES are my fies are a
little
bit yeah I don't know it's like a kind
of ridiculous um moment when that
happens cuz apparently they have like a
you know taso is a little bit about
soccer very much about
soccer and they have this dog on the on
the field to get
birds and then the bird uh the the dog
goes runs to get a bird and he jumps and
in that moment it like happens in slow
motion kind of but they don't show the
moment when it
happened uh like the soccer ball goes
with full speed right into the dog's
face when the dog is
midair um and then later they tell you a
few minutes later that the dog died I
was like thinking he would
survive but I don't know is that
realistic
is that
realistic I would feel like maybe he
would get like concussion and
survive nope okay cuz I don't feel like
that is realistic even if it's a if the
ball is coming with quite a lot of speed
at
you depends on how hard he was hit but I
feel like the most you would get from
that
is
concussion but well it's a dog so I
guess it works differently anyway
amongus what what what do I what do I go
for
guys what makeup dog ah I don't remember
I don't
remember fir flying
okay I I
have I have only pluck in terms of
flying so even though Sparks is already
low HP I'm going to count on it now e
psychic also works ice also works what
the
ah this
thing
ew
ew h
H I'll go for flamethrower please kill
it oh it didn't die and it makes me fall
asleep again you little
you little oh ver Veil wore
off you know what I don't care I'm going
to throw in one
more what I already sleepy sleep I
thought I get one more
hit that's not fair they killed by
my start twice in this
battle the is wrong with
you ah sport gives a random status
instantly oh it's not always
sleeping
interesting we could
stop what do you mean you avoided the
attack what what the
[Music]
the
oh it is 100% sleep oh
okay ability to random one uhhuh okay
people confused quack Val or is that the
the the the quack starter the the duck
starter in his final
form H let
water
uh so I guess I switch to
dual so he did get the water starter
after all
H to think that I fa would be backed
into a corner like
this I'm trying you know it's been a
long time since the last time we played
it and I'm trying to make sense of the
story line
here
uh because there was something about all
teachers and the
previous um director of the school being
like thrown out right fired or whatever
or they quit
and then and then and then yeah he
becomes that but he also was part of the
ones who who made team
star makes no sense I guess he'll he
will still explain that one to me
right
hopefully all right wild
charge weird dancing
duck totally looks like oh wa you will
terize into
what just water
[Music]
right yeah okay water to
water you're not making
quite good use of the
terization but okay fine with
me works with me the the smart thing
about terization is using a different
time getting a different time so that
you can counter something
unexpectedly
anyway how strong you have
grown are you surprised are you really
surprised oh having the same time gives
you two yeah okay yeah yeah but well but
I think it's good to have more
coverage well now miss Kwa seems you
have grown quite spend splendidly over
the course of your treasure
hunt thank
you yes I
[Music]
have and here once again I must
apologize
what what do you
mean
what no he's joking
right no way I not actually C you
what though Clive and myself being the
same person was no lie mind you wait if
you're really not c p and I'm actually
satisfied but that was quite a BM
Boozle no why would you tell me that
then just for the funny the jokes and
memes why would did he do that like
what's his
problem what's his
problem ha
prank are you is he Doney with the
funsies is he
[Music]
done well then I really still don't know
who it is and I appreciate that
[Music]
true identity remains hidden but I
believe I can Hazard a guess as do who
they may be well maybe the the black
hair black suit lady but she's the
champ that but I feel like the name fits
her and my French accent fits her we
will see that is why I sought to spare
you from having to confront them in
battle their sorrows should not be yours
to
bear however Casa has settled on a
course of action and is determined to
see it through I'm so glad because it
would have made no sense for him to be
it but what's his
problem feels like a little prankster or
something trying to you know make sense
of it by telling me this the messages
are pre-recorded and
I'm so done with your
oh yeah Merry Christmas guys it's over
though Merry
Christmas I do not imagine any ordinary
student could hope to stand against them
and win so I challenged you to a battle
to test your skill yeah you really need
didn't need to have
to didn't have to change your identity
for that again if you had lost I would
have fallen to me to bring down cioa
such was my resolve but it turns out you
are as strong as you are kind if anyone
has a chance at saving that poor child
child it surely is you child child does
he just say that because he's really
old well then it's the the flat chested
girl with with uh the tech girl the tech
girl then is the tech girl but only if
he really means it's a child as an
educator it shames me to burden one of
my students with such a task but please
but she's too
young a
penny defeat Casa take on the big boss
of Team star and
win why though we've been helping Copa
because it didn't seem like they have
anything evil in mind so
far he's not even telling me why wa why
should I should I have a good reason to
do
it
do I have a good reason for
it I explain it later yeah but he can't
just tell me to defeat kioa and not
explain me
why I guess I'll do it because I am just
an empty vessel for you
thank you for the bottom of my
heart I'll leave this in your
hands you're not Casio be right it's
like I'm paranoid now you're
you're but I think the chat I saw some
being like it's it's really the
flatchested
girl you there what do you think you're
Doling oh Mrs time a pleasure to see
you it's no pleasure at all Mr
clel I can't here to investigate reports
of an illicit battle on school grounds
and what do I find why the director of
The Academy himself facing off against
one of our students no less what were
you
thinking uh no I could just explain you
see it is a rather sad tale oh spare me
you and your little bum Bo and pranks I
don't give a you need to grow the
up that's I guess true
it is
[Music]
true remember the big boss ask us to
meet them in the schoolyard after dark
oh I guess this was is this not the
school I guess but it's not dark okay
okay counting on you okay okay you write
a letter of apology to the students on
faculty art once and I'll be reporting
this to the chair women of the school
board make no mistake good gracious no
and anything but Dad I implore
you I have to go inside
[Music]
apparently
no can we still take the test
now at least one you guys said at least
one of them is
helpful oh heal
wait I'm
Healed oh which one is the helpful
one
history oh the history
Sor
okay this is R for
uhhuh I for fast travel don't we already
have fast
travel oh
wow oh I see we have some new students
here with us
today my name is rord I will be the one
to impart knowledge of the past to your
little Minds if you can manage to
comprehend it that is the lives of our
ancestors throughout history forged the
path to the present in which we
live sorry my my little strand of hair
has its own brain and mind and keeps on
twitching there's some ghost stuck in
there I
think oh my God look at
don't don't look at my hair please it's
embarrassing today you shall learn about
the most mysterious location in all of
Pala the great
crater as you are all aware the massive
crater known as the great Crater of Pala
exists in the heart of our region the
area inside this crater is called area
zero and research of its geological
straigh and material composition has
shown that the crater is in fact over 1
million years old n over
9,000
it drove me mad and play wait it's still
doing
it it was long believed that a certain
something rested at the bottom of this
mysterious Creator what what certain
what like her
necklace aha perfect timeing to make eye
contact Yi waa answer me this what
exactly was believed to rest in the
depths of the great crater oh you asking
me is
Snorlax oh I have to answer these
correctly
huh an adorable answer but to be sure
but were you perhaps fooled by my use of
no I was more fooled by the fact that
it's big a chunky chunky
[Music]
wonky I contact let's battle Yeah that's
not a thing anymore in this
game
treasure that's right some believe that
the treasure more valuable than anything
else in the world rested in the depths
of the great crater so much for dreams
of treasure hunting though as a lab has
been built in those very same
depths Oh and before I forget you would
all do well to remember that the great
crater and AR at zero are both off
limits to all but those who are have
official business there do not dare
entertain the foolish notion of
gallivanting what's that after to area
zero in search of riches it is no place
for children dreaming of treasure and
Adventure you should tell us to go
because if you tell us not to go of
course we'll
go remember the answers do I have to do
it again or is it just a test at the end
besides if it were at all possible to
investigate the area I would surely be
the first to do
so even from afar her hair does
that oh it's a time already I must have
gotten swept up and filling your minds
with knowledge this ends today's lesson
we will unravel more of histories
enigmas together next time okay so I
have to do this again
huh oh there are tests
okay Wick Wick type
Pokemon that would be funny
actually yeah the weak type Pokemon that
tries to sit on top of people's
heads that would be so funny and and and
and like an arena Traina could have it
as their like lead Pokmon and then you
know have it on their head the whole
battle until it's its turn and then it
flies off the head and then reveals the
person the trainer is actually
Bal a living hairpiece yeah that would
be
funny w
w
kind of like the car Pokemon no that
kind I think this would be really cute
what type yeah maybe ghost or
normal maybe
fairy if you design wise make it look a
bit more like
that it probably probably goes
tropy aren't Hatter Ren awake like
Pokemon what Hatter
Ren that sounds more like a hat hat
Teran ah no but I really mean one that
looks really just like a wig like a
fluffy hairpiece with eyes
is and maybe some additional details
but and that's not that's not what I
mean no no no
no just the
hairpiece C was the first user of
it yeah hatan isn't
that game freak you
listening okay so we have to take
history again huh okay so uh
treasure is one and then I guess we'll
learn something else
now oh I should close my my tea
container okay okay oh so
heavy
greetings my little students whatever
you did yesterday it is now part of
History oh wow deep Bro today we
will continue to unravel the Marvel that
history has presented to us thank you
for 10 memberships
all
than about 2,000 years ago this region
came under the rule of the pan
Empire historical accounts describe the
pan Emperor has been quite a
dictator this Emperor also jealously
believe that legend of the treasure that
rests deep the
legend
zero I must mention that the
civilizations of our ancestors were not
as developed as ours is today people
back then were far more likely to
believe in mysterious Legends magic and
beings Beyond human comprehension in an
attempt to gain the power to stand
against Pia's neighboring countries the
thank you the emperor sent people in
drugs to join the hunt for The fabled
Treasure of area at
zero perfect timing to make eye contact
again me she's bullying me she's
targeting me approximately how many
years ago was it that the pan Empire
began to rule this
region did she say
it cuz I was not listening
then
um maybe 1,000
two she said
it two
two even though I'm reading it out loud
you know sometimes things don't don't go
into the
[Music]
brain that is
correct even though you got the answer
by asking your your
classmates but I'll look um
P
de that's not you see it say it you're
surprisingly clever one aren't you I see
you are listening intently to my lecture
yeah look away look away H the answer is
about 2,000 years ago that is when the
Great era of exploration began however
it is said that not a single Adventurer
sent out by the emperor ever reached the
depths of area zero was it the punishing
Journey itself that buried their way or
perhaps some unknown creature the
resounding failure of this Great era of
exploration almost certainly heightened
the air of mystery surrounding the
crater oh what wouldn't I give to
explore area zero in its untouched State
at that
time I suppose I can only hope for the
Swift invention of a time
machine right so treasure and 2,
years is it maybe total of
three less
[Music]
I'm the same I was the same time of
student as you are now you think
so I won't be too sure about
that more like
eight
sheesh okay let me try to go through
this a bit faster six lessons two tests
oh my
God oh my God
H greetings little students today
whatever as you should remember from our
last class area Zero's Great era of
exploration began about 2,000 years ago
this ERA last 1,000 years maybe remember
that one but not a single soul was able
to venture all the way to the deepest
reaches of area Zer having poured much
of its human and Financial Resources
into exploration of area Zer for so long
the
P 200 years later or 800 years
ago so many numbers
the Empire and its surrounding Nations
united into one
entity this was the formation of Pia as
we know it
today MH mhm apparently established at
that
time 200 years ago or 700 years
a in fact this school building though
certainly having undergone repairs for
the years is just as it was when it was
built so long
ago
restructure is a piece of History ah
things of old are truly Splendid just
like Mr clubble when he's not acting
like he's a teenager I would
certainly prefer not to have the
Pokeball portion though a relatively new
edition she's a Pokeball
hater okay
um how many years
ago well I read it in
chat uh ah you only get this information
by reading a book in school AR
ahuh
oh
CH not my fault when you provided me
with it
no yeah yeah yeah I hate nothing more
than when a student only pretends to
listen this lady scares
me
85 years well 800 years wasn't correct
then this Academy was constructed
exactly 8005 years ago to be precise in
other words your Academy here is 85
years old duh at time it offered
state-of-the-art facilities and a
uniquely Innovative curriculum as such
people used to say those seeking
knowledge need look no further than the
oranges of palia oranges that's right
they were referring to the ranja academy
it is sad that this proverb of Swords
was even used outside of the Pia region
okay uh 800
years
uh couple thousand years no 1 million
and
treasure okay next lesson is mid exam
okay so free questions in the exam I
remember them I remember them oh boy
T I can do this I can do this I believe
I will not fail
school history
midterm okay let's do it let's do
it it's five
questions no it can't
[Music]
be it can't be
2 million it was 2 million no it was 1
million oh I need free correct yeah B
well
uh well I would say
a how do I ah the great crat of P ding
ding ding ding well was long believe the
res deps okay I
tryy how many years ago did the pan
Empire begin to rule this
region
M 2,000 years ago
maybe yeah
okay how many years ago was this five
five five
five those seeking huh need to look no
further ah knowledge probably hey I feel
got all questions right I didn't even
cheat
[Music]
I think I
all remember the 2K one was a little bit
cheaty wey but besides
that yeah easy
easy wow five okay at least four out of
those five were me shut up if you're
blaming me for looking at one
answer four of them more than half of it
the
majority who by Yours
Truly okay everyone who's calling me a
cheater I will I will time
out
[Music]
time
out time
out time out time out time out stand in
the corner you will have to write an
extra uh 10 pages
[Music]
10 pages yeah about uh why you were
wrong and why kiala is the greatest an
essay you'll have to make me I'm making
you
now I dare you time on me Sky you little
thank you for the red super chat Su
CHF is swiz right
Switzerland
Switzerland Switzerland I probably won't
get to your Super Chat uh until I am in
Japan but thank you already mwah mwah
mwah I think I'll do a super chat
raining like either on the first or
second of January
probably if I can't do it earlier I will
try to do it earlier
though
Switzerland oh oh lost
Arc you know I wanted to play that too I
think I want snacks but I have more
snacks my family ate all my snacks but I
put I bought them them for them to eat
them in the first place I have no snacks
guys Ki without snacks it's nothing it's
like a like a turtle without its
[Music]
shell I got like leftovers from
yesterday yeah but I'm more thinking
about like
chol I'm
St I'm like a naked turtle
s we do at least have like a chocolate
cake that you have to warm up you know
with um with a um chocolate like liquid
corn but then I would have to get that
and War it
up yeah know I will survive I will I
will I will I might suffer but I will
survive
looking forward to what I um will eat
for dinner later the remain remaining
pieces of beef wellington which by the
way was really
good the boyfriend of my sister made
[Music]
it that was a ton of meat and
apparently they made like four and they
had two of
those like like the day before with like
um my sister's boyfriend's family I
think and then they had two more and we
only even managed to eat one
though during the Christmas
dinner but it was it was really good it
was a ton of meat though that must
have been a lot of work and was actually
um they they did use the Gordon ramsy
recipe
apparently no no no they left us one
whole like loaf of beef wellington
here I thought they would take it back
home but no they left it there and and
and yeah now I I'm supposed to finish it
but half of it I gave to Mommy to bring
it home to her
place yeah he used the recipe for from
Gordon Ramsey it seems but he added I
think a lot more garlic was very
garlicky but you know can't can't
complain about garlic it was the first
time I ate that it was really
[Music]
interesting was really yummy then the
meat was really good and um it had like
a like a red wine sauce kind of and then
yeah some some roasted potatoes
potatoes even the potatoes were so good
even though it was just just basic
potatoes
it contains mushrooms
really didn't nothing really looked or
tasted like
mushrooms but yeah I thought it was
quite like British makes sense that it's
British cuz I feel like you know feel
like it's kind of a British thing to put
like a
pie uh around something
Savory to
eat I feels so British to me so
British and it worked so well together
had a meat pie kind of
[Music]
stuff I suppose changing
things so allow me to tell you an the
old fairy tale that has been passed down
in Pia for Generations once upon a time
there was a king who very much enjoyed
collecting treasure he was particularly
fond of treasures from other countries
one day a merchant from the East heard
rumors of this King and came to meet him
the merchant laid out four treasures
isn't this like a Jesus story in front
of the treasure loving King the four
treasures were as follows a vessel a
sword a set of tablets iPads to be
excited and a set of beads seeing such
Rarities before him the king leaped Joy
he showered The Merchant of gold coins
and claimed all four of the treasures
for
himself I don't think this was four
treasures in Jesus story wasn't it just
free not sure
anymore perfect timing to make eye
contact K once again it seems like you
you're the only one in this classroom
who has eyes uh what you think these
tablets were
iPads but probably not no way maybe it
was R
still
[Music]
but even though it was long time ago I
think it was probably still
Pokemon RM
probably
incorrect is that some kind of joke were
you expect me to laugh at yourself D no
no no I'm not piing you electronic
tablet and more freaking of a ROM that
was like I guess like described as that
but you she that's I I feel
insulted by her
reaction you
shouldn't I feels like so rude the way
she reacted to me saying something
[Music]
wrong
man these particular tablets were wooden
and used as a writing medium in the east
in ancient times as you may know they
fell out of popular use as paper became
more universally available for the king
to consider these paper substitutes
Treasures they must have been of superb
quality I used to always think that re
is super be when I was
younger that or perhaps they had some
amazingly profound teachings written on
them so the king obtained these four
treasures and on that very night it is
said that a terrible disaster rained
down upon his Castle reducing it
to Rubble by
Dawn okay so uh wooden planks that would
have been my other
answer
H all right all right all right all
right all right all right all right all
right all right all right all right
right right right right right right all
right all right all right all
righty more history
[Music]
oh by the way by the way do you want to
know what I'm planning for
tomorrow I'm going to do the sock puppet
concert
tomorrow
yeah so tomorrow my brother doesn't have
to stay out for like 8
hours should be
shorter I'm thinking 8:00
p.m. my turn talk poppet concert I got
permission from from
[Music]
JMA my gr captured the imaginations of
many including the former pan Emperor
200 years ago a group of explorers
claimed to have finally reached its
deaths the name of the team that
achieved this great feat was the areat
zero Expedition that might be an answer
to a question the team is said to have
been made up of Pia's best and brightest
skilled Battlers brilliant researchers
talented individuals of all kinds among
the list of team members was the name of
a man who was an author and a brilliant
natural historian
Heath after returning from the
expedition of to ARA zero he used his
literary talent to record the events of
the Expedition and publish them he you
going to ask me who it
was
ah I think uh this one
yet mhm record of their activities
written by the Expedition member Heath
can be found in bookstores and alike
even today this record is known as the
Scarlet book
w at the time the entire region of Pia
was absolutely buzzing about ARA Z the
sced book was so popular that
practically everyone had a copy back
then people were still reading books
unlik
today the masses began to call he a liar
even the truth of the of the Expedition
making it to the bottom of the crater
was called into question just like the
moon landing the Scarlet book was
condemned to the shelves of used
bookstores as just never a book of wild
paranormal stories there's a copy on one
of the bookshelves on the ground floor
of the entrance hall feel free to have a
read if you're interested
H her hair keeps on twitching what the
heck what the
heck is she okay is she nervous is it
nervous
[Music]
twitching one more I
think
yeah one more one more no wa maybe two
more I'm
confused what my hat fits
perfectly more or
less I it's a bit too big but
whatever I I'm back again I'm going to
class for
once yeah yeah yeah 200 years ago it's
not that long ago not that long ago at
all how unfortunate that our history
lessons must March so inexorably toward
the future would it not be more of an
adventure to March toward the past
instead she's a bit
weird to start from our present and
study history in
Reverse sure sure okay yeah yeah why
not yeah so you agree with me do you
kiaha however I'm afraid I risk inuring
the wrath of our dear director if I
Stray From the
curriculum I suppose I have no choice
but to let the flow of time carry us
toward the future in this last class of
hours I shall fill your minds with the
history of theal pH
phenomenon the technology behind behind
Terror orbs has its origins in area zero
even after area zero Expedition
supposedly reached the Creator's deepest
depths others contined to explore that
area and around 140 years ago Pokmon
cloaked in a mysterious light were
discovered there as you may have already
guessed these were in fact terized
Pokmon however when those who
discovered these Pokmon brought them
out of area zero the light faded and the
terral phenomenon remained remained
a mystery for quite some time however 10
years ago that might as well be the
present day a certain someone you have
definitely heard of unraveled this
mystery
Alexa okay what's the
question the name of the famous
Professor
hi
no no
wait maybe
not
uh
s
she didn't say though it's making me
[Music]
guess yeah I should have known that from
other stories I
[Music]
guess uh-huh so
mhm to think that you when you transfer
to our Academy could correctly answer
this question you must be
cheating approximately 10 years ago a
professor named Sada unraveled The
Mystery of the terrestrial phenomenon
she discovered that the shining crystals
down in area Zera or rather the energy
they emit is what causes Pokmon to
terize this led to the professor to
invent Terror orb technology and to
develop a practical use for it you're
losing me here you're losing me you're
absolutely losing me in my
focus rumor has a dad director clav was
one of those researchers on the
professor's
team Alis this story is much less
exciting now that someone we all know
appears in wow she's oh my God she's she
has quite a king for history but if it's
history from like yesterday she gets mad
about it modern history truly is dull
isn't
it I'm sorry that we recently are not
creating any exciting history apparently
sorry for disappointing you teacher
[Music]
son bring the wonders of History to the
Forefront of your minds in
[Music]
preparation you know yesterday I had a
weird phenomenon
where I was like I was feeling like I
was falling asleep and I didn't want it
want to fall asleep cuz I was kind of I
don't know suddenly terrified of falling
asleep I was wondering if there's a
there surely is uh a phobia of falling
asleep isn't there there surely is cuz
like I can imagine like it's scary that
you you're able to lose
control over your like your body there
you could like even die while you're
sleeping no I didn't never sleep
paralyzes
phobia yeah for some reason I was
feeling kind of scared about falling
asleep last night I did not sleep much
by the way because I couldn't fall
asleep by the way and then of course in
the morning you know even the slightest
noises wake me up especially cuz like my
mom and my brother you know they were
waking up and smoothie noticed did and
reacted to it ran over there and begged
them for
food and she meowed so
loudly and yeah that obviously all of
that woke me up then I had breakfast and
so on and blah blah blah but then
afterwards I took a long nap so I'm good
now took a long nap but I expected that
it's always like that when someone
sleeps over since they don't have the
same sleeping Rhythm as me
but they gave smoothie food and then
smovie
shut shut it shut up but it was too
late I was
already
[Music]
awake for some honey thanks for the
pinky oh than I'm sorry guys I'm so far
being like behind on it like getting
sick really me over cuz the the
recent streams I wanted to still go easy
on my voice and not read the super chats
until I really feel
safe my Mouse shows
up thank you guys I'll get there though
don't worry there's I think one stream
and
uh maybe the member stream was the
member stream the only one where I said
I will not be reading no I think there
were two streams where I said I won't be
reading them uh
publicly you guys remember which one
they
were I think the members stream and
Clubhouse okay so that's at least
something history final let's
[Music]
go
okay let's see I think my finals won't
be as good as my
midterms my mouse is
everywhere Twitter space oh oh I guess I
did get maybe one or two super chats
okay here we go here we go what is area
within the great Crater of Pia called
area
zero
right just making sure
okay how many years ago was this Academy
founded didn't they ask me this in the
midterms which one of these did not
appear in aalon Fairy Tale about the
four
treasures a folding fan
[Music]
which area Expedition member wrote the
record of the team's
activities
[Music]
he how many years ago did Professor s
invent Terror orbs I think 10 years
ago hey I didn't cheat
guys must the last question is too
shallow and ridiculous to be on the
history test but Alice the director forc
me
wow oh girl in 10 years a lot of things
can happen or like like 10 years
ago important especially she doesn't
understand because like for the longest
time for hundreds and hundreds and
thousands of years development of the
world was slow as but it's only in
the past 100 years or so where
development was like extremely fast
as h H and you should be excited about
that how we
suddenly figured out how to get into
electricity and and internet and all
that kind of that's actually like
worth of like 5,000 years of History
packed into a 100 years girl
[Music]
woman it's more than enough stuff to
talk about and get excited about what
what's her problem
she's she's just being a what's what's
the
word a contrarian she's a
[Music]
contrarian the heck out of her yeah cuz
she's a
weirdo she's a history teacher I don't
understand why she doesn't appreciate
recent
history we should be proud of what we
have
achieved if she's not happy with that
then maybe she herself should create
history that she can be proud of to
teach
about huh huh how about you create
something then huh R
for history
hipster
yeah I mean I find all the history more
interesting too just because I'm like
into the whole tutor's Dynasty and so on
but still I I will give credit to how
incredible our history in the past 100
years is there's so much to talk about
so
much or even in the last 50
years so how many questions I get right
five out of five
right so in total that's 10 out of
10 and we have the perfect emote for
that oh candies okay that's
it what about fast travel don't you guys
say something about fast
travel
[Music]
what or do I have to take a different
one now I wasn't there before this
one go to the screen and find it oh the
the
lady uh wait how do you do this again
here
that's
her do her social link what was that
again okay
hi damn those
pants ah you're you out from class 1 a
who got the 10 out of 10 totally not
through cheating no but really I didn't
cheat H the way you conduct yourself in
my class and the answers you give to my
questions I admit they pique my interest
you're quite interesting people I must
say she's going to completely ignore how
I roasted her the whole
time tell me kiaba given a choice which
do you prefer things of old or things
are new oh yeah totally older things
totally totally just so you like
me so you prefer the things of the past
do you the potential I saw in you was
real after
all yes this one may indeed be of good
use to me something what
[Music]
W what is that thing on her on the side
of her head not the twitching hair but
the I don't know
some weird accessory is this a Pokemon
like shape
thingy you can disregard that I was
simply thinking out loud I feel weirded
out by you even more now lady I enjoyed
our oh oh i r hello thank
you conversation today you have my
thanks
Ki I became slightly closer with
her that sounds dangerous to me should I
just talk to her right away again or do
I have to go somewhere else first yeah
okay okay no
problem I'll go and talk
to the
nurse why she looks so cute even in that
tiny picture who is
she
[Music]
what her her head is kind of too big for
her body but besides
[Music]
that feet you guys like feet don't you
she's cute she looks like she could be
the mom of what's her name not
[Music]
e hey there come on in everyone's
welcome in the nurse's office do I sound
like
fauna what brings you here today I don't
see anything super wrong with you or
your
Pokmon she's
[Music]
cute she's cute kind of weird body
proportions but
cute
o wait this is your first time here
isn't it oh
yeah I like the little band on her
knee
oh so I guess you transferred in
recently you must be Ki right
everybody's been talking about you her
mouth I've heard all kinds of rumors
apparently you fell off a cliff right
after hey don't bring back those
embarrassing
memories and even pick a fight with Team
star
[Music]
oh yeah you started your treasure H
thing right her mouth is so weird when
she just leaves it open like that like a
nutcracker come to tell me about
anything super interesting you find out
there in your adventures I'm kind of
bored just sitting in here all day you
know I don't have any classes to teach
and students only come here to skip
class yeah it do be like
that but
um she cute she's cute maybe she should
become a streamer like her
daughter so yeah drop by if you can deal
deal cute wa what happens if I get super
close of all of them we get a secret
kissing
[Music]
scene what is that Pokemon ah the
giraffe it
[Music]
moved it moves around so
wearly okay can we go back to the other
teacher now H she's somewhere else now
not in Persona you can do Romans with a
teachers that seems highly
inappropriate just hearing that it seems
highly inappropriate
guys it
is oh oh that's the best part because
it's
inappropriate so is it a dating
game well if it isn't Kiwa are you
perhaps interested in the rest of the
old tale I told you in class no but
yes don't judge
us PR of f many things Dating Game
included wow
wow that's the best act dialogue in the
game oh it's
meme character
okay no when I get back from Japan I
already have plans I have to play other
games Fire Emblem I'm so excited for
Fire Emblem at least the Fire Emblem we
can romance uh
schoolmates yeah no need to romance
teachers what the
convenient that you would take the bait
I presented in class a vessel a sword a
set of tablets and a set of beads after
obtaining these four treasures the
King's Castle was destroyed why you
ask because of course these VES were
actually for Pokemon I told you
it's a ROM maybe it's not though as this
Pokemon were passed from human hand to
human hand as Treasures they slowly
became tainted by
Hub I think you say it like that and
greed finally after coming in contact
with the rapacity rapacity
rapacity rapacity the is that
word rapper
City a
hopacity h of the king at that hand they
awakened as disasters and began to began
began to Rampage out of control the king
called for renowned Pokemon wielders to
defend the country and after a fierce
battle these incarnations of disaster
were
quelled weird sound it is said that
these four Pokmon were then sealed away
somewhere in
Pia
four it's not the four
it's not the the the the the
Titan Pokemon is
it did they look like those
things no
okay so what do you think would you say
this story is just make believe
no oh
mer
Moni thank you what kind
let in summer in summer to Hokkaido
interesting
choice any places I should really visit
well I have only been to Hokkaido once
and that was in winter so honestly no
idea if you're just in in
[Music]
summer I didn't
choose oh is it like like a little
semester or so and they they gave you to
a
specific like host family or so that you
have to live with have to do with the
holidays that I have ah cuz you only
have holidays in the summer oh wait but
that's amazing you get
holidays let's
go that's e the hey one Japanese person
says somewhere in Hokkaido is nice at
least that's actually possibly the best
place to
uh be in Japan in summer because
everywhere else I'm sure I don't I know
I I've never been to okado In Summer but
I know that the rest of Japan is humid
as and absolutely
unbearable especially if you're from
Europe and you're not used to it I know
I know in Europe it gets hot in summer
too but Japan is like humid as and
kills you it's terrible so hok
might
actually save your butt and maybe I mean
if it's a
vacation you can maybe also leave H for
a little
bit
maybe
right countdown
yeah
apparently in Hokkaido what Hokkaido is
famous for in terms of food is jingus
Khan is that also what you call it in
[Music]
English the food jingus and uh roasted
uh cor
CS Yuki
matuli
lamb
lavender oh it seems there's a big
Lavender Fields in in summer that
actually I want I could like I'm very
interested in that that sounds
beautiful you know big big big flower
Fields like endless flower Fields I I
want to visit
those that sounds pretty
hey favor sufferer nightmare ah I'm so
blessed for not having
that the song is it was oh we didn't
talk about it yeah I was so into
cleaning my apartment cuz my family was
on their way and then I missed the
premiere I I said it on a time that I
would be able to see it on purpose but
then I couldn't see it but I did watch
the premiere live chat afterwards H not
much really to see anyway cuz you guys
are just spamming
emotes but but did you like
it did you like it I I heard I read a
lot of positive feedback you guys seem
to have liked the song and and you know
those those weird voices that I
did um life here we
go yeah it's actually me
recreating the song um properly I wasn't
sure if I should like put that in or
not um but I I felt like this song you
know it has all these dorky
tunu sound bites and I I felt like it
needs it to really be
complete and so actually the the
producer who used at least used to write
uh pretty much all hello project songs
for years and years and years tunu his
really famous tunu son um nowadays he
still writes songs but not so much
anymore but like he's the he's The
Mastermind and uh kind of like the Yago
of Hell project and his thing is though
that he writes the songs and then often
he puts his voice into it as well and
this song is full of it and without it
it's just not the same so I I Tred to
make like a low
voice to impersonate
[Music]
him yeah like the JP whisper yeah but
sometimes
tasan puts in just like one word but
sometimes he puts in a lot of words into
the lyrics that he he then records for
[Music]
it you would do the
same it's it definitely G gives it a lot
of character that's why I didn't want to
Comm
completely um omit it but I I did not do
all of it like actually during the Cur
uh you know it goes
like even between there he does
something he goes
[Music]
like it says something there as well in
between each
line I I left that one out because I
thought that's a bit too much in the end
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah good
call just enough
honestly I think I had a good feeling
for it you know the l o e life I made
the the other girls record too but I
thought it would be too much of a
trouble to ask them to recreate all the
tungu
sounds
um uh because I wasn't even sure if I
was really going to use them so I just
did it on my own and then I was like
let's let's try putting this in and then
see if it works or not if it sounds
stupid or not I love it in I think it's
okay commissioner song I was thinking
about that too at at some point but I
think I'm pretty sure it would be
insanely EXP ensive
like not I would never get into the plus
if I did that um so I don't think I will
ever attempt that even though it would
be quite the accomplishment
but I I I don't think that is worth it I
don't think the investment is worth
it like once
you once you work with producers who are
that big then that the
dimensions of how much they charge are
Next
[Music]
Level well maybe I already did Ion
on very astute of you I have read many
historical disaster reports personal
Journal journals and the like there is
much to support the truth of the
story
oh well to be honest like
um I was also thinking you know uh the
the the subunit Bono from Hello project
yeah you should know by now who that is
guys they have some really great songs
that are actually not by Tusan and um I
kind of was wondering if if I could get
a song from those
producers cuz those
are I feel like those would be
more
M say they would speak more towards a uh
an overseas
audience but I don't know I don't
know they would probably be really
expensive too if I'm able to prove this
story's
veracity myself I'll will be sure to let
you
know I became even closer with her oh
it's getting dangerous it's getting
dangerous
[Music]
yeah okay we have to leave again and
then talk to her again I guess let's
[Music]
talk let's text the nurse again no
particular reason why it's a
[Music]
coincidence
Lucas we're
fine oh I like the detail that uh no no
I stay here that there's different
people and Pokmon in here
now wow what an effort oh wait can
I okay hey there come on in everyone
while welcome in the nurse's
office oh K have you toughened up a
bit
yes her
mouth Al so you know your tough stuff
huh but seriously you look a bit
different I bet it's because of all the
crazy experiences you're having on your
treasure
hunt you need to tell me about what
you've been up
to Okay blah blah blah blah blah blah
blah blah blah blah blah blah
blah wow that's so
cool I sure I'm jealous of you kids you
get to try out new things every single
day me on the other hand I actually
wanted to become a teacher I'm just a
school nurse you know I can't teach
classes or anything like that you could
teach um I don't know
like SE sexual education or right surely
she could or like I don't know like
biology uh or whatever it is when you
teach them about your
body not no I mean like telling them how
it
works guys why are you being like that
it's a normal thing in
school right I think it
happens yeah there's surely something
she can
teach we're just joking yeah you better
be
huh I couldn't pass a certification exam
to become an actual help ah well there
we
go I took so many times with no luck so
here I am stuck forever in the nurse's
office H the face she does right
now
[Music]
she
needs a kiss do we all agree on
that
a minute she I mean she's literally
doing a kissing face right now how can I
[Music]
not how can I
not I got you I got you
[Music]
girl
hi
Hi how are
you how are you oh that
face how can I how can I resist I can't
I must I
[Music]
must
okay I done my
[Music]
duty thank God for
3D couldn't have done this of Life today
all right
BRB po arm no no no no no no no no
you're imagining you're imagining
things oh
[Music]
you read my mind K how do you know
exactly what I
wanted thank you kiaa I'm so excited
please come back again
oh I definitely became a lot closer with
her all right now we got to the other
lady oh they're in the same place now oh
it's a showdown they're going to
make me choose kiaha who do you really
love me or
her you can't make me
choose maybe we can try
to get both of
them
but if I had to choose I would choose
her hi k sorry were you looking for me
I've been away from the nurse's office
lately did you need something from
me do you need something from
me are you Pokemon hurt no no no
no no they're full
health no wait I'm just trying to talk
to
you and and do improve our relationship
huh oh yeah I guess it it's pretty
unusual for me to be out of the N
nurse's office like this uh well I'm
actually doing a bit of studying oh she
want to she wants to take the exam again
maybe oh I try my best at the health
teacher certification exam one more time
oh you can do it
just so you know it's totally not
because I'm inspired by a certain
somebody working hard at their treasure
hand
oh you know I still have a of exams
coming up too girl oh she's asking for
it again I'm not going to change again
she's going to have to wait for
later but we can restart you
bunnies okay
later in between the bookshelves yeah oh
that would was a a dream I've always had
to get a kiss in between the bookshelves
just like in the animes yeah okay kiaha
see you in between the
bookshelves thank you kiaha love
you I said it on
[Music]
you oh I like that there's like all
these boxes hidden behind there's just
like oh nobody's nobody's going to see
it it's behind the bookshelf right yeah
yeah yeah just throw it back
there okay well the time has come the
cursed Treasures the poor Pokemon of
Ruin they
exist and I stumbled upon the truth in a
newspaper of all places an interview
piece of a carpenter no
less uhuh a carpenter the Pokmon
Whalers apparently use S sacred Stakes
to seal these Treasures of Ruin and
shrines there is a separate Shrine for
each of the four Pokmon in eight St
ah the big
[Music]
doors ah made Stakes peror driven into
the ground in the area surrounding each
Shrine keep the power of Ruin at
Bay ooh I only found a couple of those
so far
o in other words if all of the stakes
for a given Shrine were to be removed it
would release the Pokmon held inside
what happens if you find all those
Stakes
beforehand and remove them before
getting to those points guys
nothing birthday merch comes
tomorrow ni thank you for getting
it
yeah I'm I'm going to use a walk through
for that pretty
sure ah you can still Freedom the
teacher is optional oh it's just
optional this conversation and all that
you can just do it without all of this
that's kind of
lame yeah I've seen a lot of
Japanese Bros getting my BR merchandise
already
nice just in time for the cold winter
well not just in time but at least at
least the winter is not over
yet but the blanket is huge guys did you
see
I would gotten the mail yet yeah okay
but I think it will come surely
soon welcome back Tiana thank
you I want a
snack text told me tomorrow or the day
after
oo a saw caped can't be superhero
wearing
it yeah yeah yeah no no no that uh she
do be twitching don't you think it would
be nice to free those Pokmon from the
confin of their tiny little shrines it
sounds very
dangerous but I'll do
it is this part of the main
story kind soul I see you're proving
truly useful this kind of like the
fourth story line
now according to the descendant of the
Pokmon Whalers in the story you must
have a bond with Pokemon in order to
remove the
[Music]
stakes I've already been able to remove
them so I guess we're
good it's The Post Star Line That's
optional it's not necessary
oh oh okay h
huh if it's optional okay we'll focus on
the other things first and if we still
have time at the end then we'll do this
too I'm sure someone is Pokmon savus
yourself would have no trouble at all
with that you can choose for yourself
whether to believe me or not but I will
Mark the locations of these shrines on
your map are the doors oh I would
appreciate the the stakes more but
okay ra a go myself of course but
skipping out of my classes to go
adventuring seems to have made the
director a little suspicious of
me you can think of it as part of your
treasure hunt Treasures of Ruin are
still Treasures after all I hope you
will investigate these shrines if you're
at all inclined to do so maybe we'll
see well
okay n now we finally have this as well
I thought this would have been part of
the main story those doors and
Stakes I'm quite
surprised
TBH okay I I just want to see the end of
the nurse
story she probably made the exam now
didn't
[Music]
she how's it going
lady hi there uh uh the kiss between the
bookshelves was really amazing like a
dream come true H thank you so much oh
CL
[Music]
s have some good news you're not going
to believe this but I passed the health
teacher certification exam
o
congratulations thank you so much I saw
you pushing yourself real hard with your
treasure hunt and that really inspired
me of course most of the credit for My
Success goes to my own hard work
though thanks for giving me the pleasure
I needed to try again kiawa you're
welcome oo 10 Max revives let's go
that's really useful I only had
five but they tell me there's no room to
add new classes this year a maybe next
year then so I guess I'll keep being
nurse Miriam for a bit all right this
sounds good yay we got her a new job
guys I bet I'll make a great teacher I
can't wait to see you in my class
I think we did a good
thing than I
that okay
[Music]
uh
H uh we go to him now I
suppose wait no maybe not but I guess
we'll talk to him
wa have we been in here before or maybe
we have I don't quite remember yeah
we've been we've been here
before oh hello Miss K how is your
treasure H coming along having all sort
of fun adventures I
hope yeah yeah yeah been sick in between
but it's been nice it's been a good time
wonderful I'm glad to hear it to keep in
mind at the treasure H there is no set
course or criteria you must follow
simply go where your heart takes you
blah blah blah
speaking of such Pursuits there has been
something on my mind of late if I could
ask you for your expertise on the matter
I would be most grateful you see I
recently heard a word whose meaning
escapes
me he's trying to be hipster again what
is it this
time is that a real word that people use
in the real
world Chi or did he make it up and I
can add my own meaning to it
uh first
time I used it all time
[Music]
weirdly real word had to look it up real
word
h apparently is
that I'm learning
English I think I understand for both
speaker and recipient is not a pleasant
word I take it the words used by young
people these days are quite often beyond
my comprehension but when I learn the
meanings Behind these words I find that
I feel that much closer to my students
that much closer I most grateful for
your help on that front Okay so this is
also just like mhm something where I
gradually get closer to him but I don't
really want to get closer to
him so I'm out of here where is the
school yard a there it doesn't even show
that there's like a quest going on
[Music]
here now it's already
Copa
n wait C you're so young you were the
leader of the uh of those peeps
interesting are there's a game trying to
deceive me again what a weak weak weak
attempt how stupid do you think I
[Music]
am
thanks for
coming
oh oh are I going to do a surprise
Pikachu
face the
SM yeah I did to a surprise Pat your
face
unbelievable this must be quite a shock
for you the big boss cioa they were both
me all along well of course of course
she was speaking with a French
accent
because she was trying to you know not
sound like herself actually it makes so
much sense it makes so much sense that I
gave her a French
accent the big boss CIO be they were
both me all
along when I saw you make quick work of
those team star lackes outside school
that time the idea for operation starle
suddenly came to me my skill let me get
hold of as much LP as I want so I
decided to use that to tempt you into
helping me out after the operation
started I kept an eye on you as a member
of the supply unit and I had you battle
the bosses on my
behalf wow you look you're so
smart I hate that face that she's doing
right now
though all for the goal of defeating me
and putting an end to team star once for
all but still there's part of me that
wants team start to live on I can't just
roll over and let you win without
putting up a fight yeah makes total
sense this is the final showdown are you
ready it's not the final showdown It's
the final countdown didn't you see my
title girl pay
attention I'm ready
though she's about to get wiped I think
so
to I think my level is definitely
sufficient maybe not my choice of
Pokmon but we'll see I have decent
coverage I just don't have grass and and
I think also no water which is actually
quite shitty but oh well s sorry to keep
you the let of apology Mrs time had me
uh I mean preparations took longer than
expected that that voice are you
Clive oh they never met
huh Benny so it was you after uh no I
mean is that you
cop
In the Flesh I have a task for you Clive
if you'll accept it I want you to record
what happens next so you can send the
video to team star they need to see the
outcome of this battle for
themselves okay we'll
do and also send it to my Mommy cuz I
need to make her
proud then allow me to introduce myself
properly I'm the big boss of Team star
the name's
CA no Penny oh we're going with Penny
now okay bow down before the overwheling
mind of Team star's
founder which one these people can't
make up their
minds
oh
[Music]
music you guys like this one
it sounds like a hot mess to
me ah yeah this part's a bit better but
it pops up wait for
it can I turn it louder a little
bit
a
okay okay
[Music]
okay
oh okay that's pretty
good that's pretty good what did you say
also what's effective I don't know
should it just torch
it oh does she have an all Lady team
that makes so much sense with her
backpack I like that that's
[Music]
cute fire F will fire be
fine even though it's not super
effective let's go torch
song okay I like this part oh that's not
so good but we'll get
stronger ooh ooh that's super effective
but it doesn't do much damage we can do
this probably free hits
though I have to heal myself though I
hope she brings out out the water EV now
so that I have some time to heal
myself water please
Vaporeon uh was that grass or water I'm
not sure I don't
remember that's water oh nice ah perfect
oh wait no way not perfect wait I'm
confused I'm confused a
ah water
[Music]
hey guys did you know that what does
that mean what does that
me okay I deserve that
one you want the water now you get the
water yeah
but I I buffed I boosted myself so
much I can't leave
now is Vaporeon defensive or offensive
she'll definitely one hit me I think if
she attacks now so I should heal
nonetheless maybe she'll buff herself
the first
turn
uh 12 + 90 is
like something 10 or
[Music]
so
should I use he potion or Max potion
never mind I have this rpy mindset again
where I don't want to waste
items he myp might just go back to what
it is
now should I switch out but what did I
buff myself
[Music]
for I will be one shot no way
Y water water okay all right no need to
try to sweep it with one
Pokemon
M should have switched when she switch
though what a
[Music]
waste I'm faster though am I not okay D
that's a lot of damage for being not
effective
wow
oh Flareon
fire well ground would work but my HP is
low as
see I remember ground would work um
H
I guess I might have to heal I have
no water
I'll
heal and wait if I'm fast and I do
dig let me just try it I'll risk it it
should be fine I think it will be
fine
guys let's go don't get hit taka don't
get hit and don't miss
[Music]
yeah
y not wasting any turns no more
Leafeon okay I'll switch back to
sporks but Leafeon is probably
faster is Leafeon strong
though I guess maybe also ice should
work too no uh ice
against Grass I think is effective still
got full
HP okay okay then let's do it this way
then everybody gets a a
turn
H go go go frilla
go oh I love the design of leum looks
pretty in this
game
Poon oh it's faster than me but it just
uses baby doll
eyes I attack fell I do attack
physically don't die it avoided for
sake again
[Music]
ooh come on there we
go need two
hits but oh this time we attack
first does baby doll eyes have like
a go first r R
jolon is electric right so ground and
what else is
effective should I go back to Daka again
but Daka is like no HP we would have to
hope that I'm
faster just ground
o so even I I could I could heal myself
though because surely she won't do much
damage to me cuz I resist her
cuz I don't know if I'm faster I don't
want to risk that yeah jolon surely very
fast I have this image that all electric
Pokmon are super
fast surely not all of them but a lot of
them uh okay so I
heal
um and then I
dig Comon trade m
good image that's
true like just think of Pikachu Vol
absorb let's go she got nothing against
me
m uh Baby D eyes okay but whatever
[Music]
whatever
it's not a one hit o well we'll do it
[Music]
again l o
e that by the way is a a really common
chant not only in the song cover that I
did but like if You observe Jpop songs
like Idol songs specifically you will
eventually recognize
like Rhythm patterns where the specific
chance fit
in yeah and then there's
specific Parts when there's enough space
after one line you can fit in the L
someone
someone always has to be like
two two
uh
syllables syon which one was
that
Pon
very okay we blet with steel okay yeah I
can use my whole team nice
to I can't fault you in your bad skills
at all no wonder the bosses fell at your
[Music]
hands ah this cutie
PTI a t
Hammer oh you got to
tralize just into fairy I
assume right
R yeah okay then no
problem wait is she really
here I she see wait you showed up at the
perfect time when I talked about the
perfect perfect topic how did you do
that
how I I wanted to extend that
conversation and say
like like sunus son know the hello
project producer that I talked about
will purposefully write the
songs like that to fit in all those
chants and all that and always give like
a like intros and dance breaks where
they can go like o o o o and so on and
always just keep like some space to do
like
[Music]
uh and so
on on
purpose So eventually you will just even
if you hear a song for the first time
you'll be able to naturally just know
what to say and when to say it and what
happened did I I I right I can't do this
one twice in a row ah shoot why do I
press it again and
then I can't do fake out SK smack is not
very effective so I guess play
[Music]
Ra it it does the trick it does the
trick the fans feel like they're
performing the song too yeah maybe not
like performing but it definitely is
like one of the reasons why I loved
going to Idol concerts because it's just
like so much fun to participate with the
chance and and copying the
choreographies and so on it's just so
much
fun and it gives you this it this
feeling that everyone in the hall is
like
one one for all all for
one everyone knows what to do is so in
sync so much
fun and it's
exciting I wish we could chant an idol
concerts
again I think depending on where it is
you can do it
[Music]
already when are you going to be in h
have no idea
never I think I can go in if I wanted to
I don't
know yeah yeah I saw that NPC couple of
streams
ago if you just join
yourselfers why do you have to say that
why is that so important to
say so
everyone should know it is
important that's that's a private thing
why Wen you guys watching in the first
place it's a private
thing we were having a moment okay
anyway it's all over now well isn't that
what you wanted
[Music]
Penny what the do you all want no
one can make up their mind in this
game it's finally over guys it's
done she says as if she's like as if the
others are
dead
oh we're done here I think we should
call it
quits hold up are you saying we should
break up the team you got to be joking
we got carried away with operation star
now everything's gotten out of
hand yeah well that's what happens when
you round up a bunch of bullies in the
courtyard and make a show of learning
them some manners but we didn't fight
them in the end we didn't do anything
wrong indeed merely did we declare Our
intention to battle two for nail should
the villains persist in their tyrannous
oppression it was bloodless Victory we
assure
you
um
yeah
yeah I don't know this one's
difficult yeah they didn't even send out
their Pokemon they just blubbered and
apologized a whole lot our outfits must
have been spoke spooked them for good
must have spook but the police made a
huge stink about what went down and then
they all end up leaving the academy our
plan backfired epically there's no way
we're getting off scotf
Frey I guess you
right I guess you right this little
stunt the crank I'll fix this mess up on
my end just leave it to
me what are you
saying I'm the one who started team star
I dragged you all into this so I'll take
responsibility for
everything oh Noble and kind big boss
you cannot now that the bullies are gone
you could you guys should start going to
school again oh yeah and what about you
I can't go
back you know the the the the guy there
he looks like he could be a character in
dangan Luma to
me dangan Luma
H can you see it
[Music]
oh
right why there's no reason for you to
stay shut in your room anymore
right all I can say to you guys is
thanks even though we never met in
person you are all so kind to me pill
[Music]
come I imagine if you write in Korean
you can fit more no
[Music]
problem I'll read it someday if I ever
get
there stop right there BB why are you
talking like we'll never speak again I
need to go take care of some
things
what
privy privy speak to us what is thine
intent dude if you speak like this I'm
not going to answer you okay hey
big boss
[Music]
answers so
salty bye bye guys thanks for
everything a she was outside the whole
time cuz just opened the
window thanks for everything K and you
too
[Music]
CL so what
now I'm glad I could see this fruit to
the
end sorry sorry plug
them she get sent to
prison H I guess this is it for teamstar
and me
too hold that F Miss uh Penny I'd like
to check something with you first check
what why resort to something like
operation Starfall if you're the big
boss of Team star wasn't there any other
way to handle this I tried telling the
bosses that we were done once before but
they still didn't quit why not simply
order them to and now it's way too late
anyway our code states that no one team
has the right to order people around I
could ask them all to do stuff but I
could never order
them so it's back to the Cod once again
the bosses must have taken it very
seriously they did that's why I knew I
could use it to force them Force
teamstar to
disband because the bosses would do
anything the Cod C of them even leave
the
team yes and according to the code they
had to accept any challenge made to
them
ah it doesn't leave my
nose there's something in
there I'm not
crying
no this doesn't move me at
[Music]
all still not 100% he CH I don't know
don't worry it's um really really
[Music]
lowkey does sound like you're sleepy no
I'm
notm I'm not I got way enough sleep
but well a long stream I I yawn anyway
sometimes I want a snack
[Music]
though yes and according to the yeah I
read
that that's the idea for operation
stle CIO let me ask you one last thing
oh now he calls her CIO wasn't just
penny a second ago what does team start
no what do your friends and the team
mean to
[Music]
you there
oh they're my greatest treasure oh
wait
okay that's nice cuz it's all about
treasure
hunting and she already has her
treasure okay okay here we
[Music]
go what this whole life mean to you it's
my greatest
treasure Splendid thank you for
apprising me of the situation Miss
Penny what a come
on I know Pokemon games are really
childish always but but there's like
there's there's a limit to how stupid
you can make the
characters now young lady there's
something I should very much like to
discuss with you
hey quit it with the old cheeser act CLI
you're creeping me
out indeed well then before we talk
further allow me to reveal to you my own
secret I should Rage
Quit
no way
again tal of Hell unbelievable oh my God
just as CIO was your disguise the boy
you knew as C was
mine why yeah why why
why why me to B
why
why I needed a way to talk to team start
on equal terms students do tend to shy
from speaking their mind to their
teachers after all much more so when
faced with the director of The Academy
okay I get that part but maybe could
have tried a bit harder with your
disguise yeah but why do I even start
wasn't the outfit a bit much no it
wasn't
enough plus I have some big feelings
about that Weg I don't think that was a
wig might be quite insulting to him to
say that well that's quite enough for
that now everyone why don't you come out
oh oh same face
POG
[Music]
oh wait why does she talk walk normal
now why does she walk normal now
M she walked normal she learned how to
walk more like long time no meat right I
mean we only found out your real name ja
now
mie very least thy long hidden
countenance as s for
eyes so um I heard your real name is
Penny how you been all this whole
time 4y we found you at last you have no
idea how worried we've
[Music]
been a that's cute okay gang on the
count of free one
two hello penny
a the way Mellie moved is cute whenever
you watch
that take care bless you thank you you
too now then miss Penny and each of your
young bosses as well on be of the
Academy have to say something I would
like to say to
teamstar you all have
my sincerest apologies come again as
director of the Academy I let you down
my handling of your situation was a
dismal failure what I I still don't I
mean
[Music]
why you'll told me about your reasons
for forming team star and about your
subsequent actions ever since my first
day as a director all I've ever
experienced of the academy is an
environment blessedly free from building
that's kind of
no no no no don't a it towards us don't
worry I'm spitting it into a
cup big fum collection yeah yeah it's
starting to form into a Pokemon that
looks like that that one Pokemon um that
psychic or Ghost Pokemon um you know
that that's like a a big round floating
thingy with some spikes around the edges
it's it's kind of like pink and what
grimer no not grimer not
grimer no no I mean um the one that's
like coming out of something on the
ground no not
gasing no it's like a weird Pokemon
really weird one hi chunky
wonky no not M Spirit t or maybe that
one yes that's the one I
mean
yeah yeah
yeah Spirit up that's that's how my
flugum is turning out to
[Music]
me when you
collected the
cup I'm sorry for giving you that
image but I don't know this piece was
built on the backs of your hurt and
anger and of course your immense courage
in putting things to right and so I get
straight to the
conclusion the Academy's order for team
star to disband and my threat to expel
those who did not obey is hereby
revoked does that mean what I think it
[Music]
means a lot of fum today but it's not at
least has no color indeed team star can
continue to exist should that be a wish
but at least go to
[Music]
school woohoo Penny isn't that great now
we can all stay
together oh my heart is giddy with
Glee but but I betrayed all of
you you mean operation sta director CL
tell us all about it far as we heard you
only went free with it to save us from
getting expelled you were just worried
about us right not like we'd ever check
the team just cuz someone told us to
after all a our
style I cannot even begin to imagine how
you must have feared for us Lady Penny
Lady sorry for making you worry B we're
all okay now but even
so hold on everyone I have more to say
as previously stated the requirement for
a team starter to spend has been revoked
however there's still some unsold
matters to discuss allow me to provide a
few
examples your protected try your brazing
customization of school uniforms your
unauthorized usage of Academy equipment
your Reckless modification and
jeopardous driving of Pokemon power
vehicles do you even have a license need
I go on youve lacker and disregard for
school rules cannot simply be
overlooked yes yes if you go to school
you must follow this the rules okay be
be good everyone don't do such Reckless
things th as punishment you will all be
required to engage in community service
community
service like there're some freaking
prisoners what like picking up trash and
the
straint I did come here to service in
school what
what did you
do Penny actually come in his crimes
damn damn
girl I spit at the
idea spit of the
ver what a dramatic reaction from
me
yes yes I do not agree with
this she's
oh she stole
money holy wow that's actually
she's really a bad kid oh my
God damn that's actually quite like a
serious
thing if you think about it in the real
world she might
be the biggest criminal in Pokemon
history even the like you know
characters who are painted as criminals
usually are not really doing much bad
things most little
[Music]
time I mean okay there might be worst
ones javanni what did javanni do brand
and actual Mafia what what did they
really do Mafia like
things or was it just a tone down
Pokmon version of a
mafia yeah did they cut people's
fingers no I doubt it still Pokemon yeah
whatever that's just like Team Rocket
that's like whatever stealing
Pokemon I don't take that
seriously I don't take that
seriously that's not Mafia that's
cool oh
man they killed a
Pokemon did they I don't remember that
which game was
[Music]
that no you can't steal my cats that's
not in the real world you can't do
something like that no that's that
doesn't compare it's different
red and blue oh I don't remember that at
all and specifically I will be asking
you to manage the
stc's
what and that stands for the star
training
[Music]
centers I'm so upset there shall be
facilities for cultiv I think his voice
is making me like
more they shall be facilities for
cultivating Pokemon and trainers talents
I plan for the Academy to found them in
collaboration with the Pokemon League
the idea came to me when I saw Miss kwaa
battling her away for real basis the Bas
is construction as well as the Battle
Tactics employed by the students and
team star are remarkably unique and
creative I would ask you to continue
your team activities but henceforth as
STC staff members using your former
basis as training
facilities
and that is the sum of it does anyone
have any
concerns um no sounds like fun but so I
don't see how this would be anything but
a
win-win this may be a weird P to say
since SDC are supposed to be punishment
and all that you should totally join in
too Penny it's true we would most
happily have you at our sides my
lady we can go to school together too
that way if anything happens we'll be
there to protect
you
yeah this is definitely not
normal me admitting so much
fum I think it's the
voices but it's good get get that
out
there get that out there I don't
want it in
there get it
out we were talking about how great it
would be to have both team start school
in our lives that that would be sweet we
deal
man so what do you say you
guys W what do you
think I wasn't listening that much to be
honest I was just
reading huh but um I I just don't need
to give you respons at this moment Penny
do take some time to decide but so I
don't know what what they're they're
being asked to go to their world bases
and do what I didn't get that
part I'm processing none of
[Music]
it ah train
others please just mute no
I have to mute the whole time it's so
annoying enjoy
it appreciate
it okay so they trained them okay that's
really it okay wow
H so basically they're asking them to
take the school's
job but I guess not quite because the
school is only doing fearing and battles
on the school grounds are not allowed
right but basically they're taking the
school's job so the school has to do
less lazy
asses but now least I think our little
group should go the separate ways not to
say you should break up team star after
all I simply meant it it's time to
leave yeah of
course M while please stop by my office
later if you could all right all
right all right oh my little home
haven't been here in a
while it really is quite nice can I go
into the
bathroom
no what the am I supposed to do
when I need to
go ooh that's a big ass
table that's even bigger than my table
setup
I wish I had a table that big but I
would want it to be like different
color this is such a
dream apartment for a student like a
freaking junior high school or whatever
student it's way too big way too much
unrealistic okay I muted it this one
time and where did he say he wanted me
to go ah
[Music]
here yeah so
unrealistic
[Music]
hey ah here you are Miss kiaha I want to
thank you for your hard work and
resolving the situation with teamstar if
not for you I suspect I would have done
the team a grievous Injustice in my
choice of punishment for directions you
have my sincere gratitude oh who's
there no CL it's wrong you need to ask
who's there it's not going to work uh
it's
Penny um Miss Penny
coming hello
director about the stc's I'd like to
work on them together with the rest of
teamstar
that's wonderful news thank you very
much for your favorable response but um
I should be punished more heavily than
the others I think yeah I guess that's
true why so because of operation stfall
no not that because of the other really
bad thing I did oh he doesn't know yet
what would that
[Music]
be because I stole a ton of money
I'm a hacker man hacking into the gate
you know yeah I was quite illegal I'm
quite the criminal mastermind actually
damn well if you hack some more and give
me about like a million LP then we'll
forget about it
okay ah okay I guess I can do that is
that really the right thing to do like
ethically and so
on um it might not be but
you know I have to pay
for this the school's fees somehow
because I'm giving you guys way too big
apartments and not making you guys pay
anything it's not like the not like
we're getting any money from the country
so yeah I I kind of miscalculated the
cost of everything so I I actually do
desperately need some money
you okay yeah it did seem kind of crazy
on reason able to have such big rims for
all the students I do apologize Miss K
but I will have to ask you to give us
some privacy you didn't hear anything
did you no I never do I never
[Music]
do oh spooky biscuit that's an
interesting Theory do you think the
reason why there is so many adult
students here is because they want the
Sheep
housing could be
they ported me back into my room again
where am I supposed to go now I gave
them privacy but where do you want me to
go I'll
leave it's good
point let me see what JMA is
saying mhhm oh guys uh hold talk
merchandise got extended by two days
because uh apparently like I don't know
how long it was but there was an error
for a while where people couldn't
purchase it but yeah so I got extend you
get one last chance to uh
purchase until
[Music]
28th
yeah and oh yeah yeah some shipping
rates or whatever I guess were weird I
guess mhm I didn't really notice was I
didn't even notice it but JMA was on it
immediately yeah so if you want to
support Holo talks future then please do
am I getting some
merized I do
you okay
byebye if I ever get a
house I want Windows like
that with like you know like some space
there I don't know how to describe it or
with out this
platform um have this be empty but still
have it like as a curve there or or like
just I don't know a cut out space so I
can put like a a day
bed yeah a
Nook to put like some furniture there a
day bed or so a so far I think that's so
nice I really want that but I I never
see house or
apartments here who have that which have
that
Kaa Penny there's something I want to
talk to you about could you come meet me
in front of the school stairs you know
where we first met I'll be waiting at
the bottom or at the
top I'm coming oh oh
oopsie she's right there I
think I know she's there down there ah
that is where we first met yeah on the
middle level I remember long time
[Music]
ago
really dot dot dot
star the six of us fought up that cat
race back when we created the team it's
so cringy it's perfect you
know look at her
movement yeah it is
cringy selfawareness
important anyway about the lp thing I
thought I was going down big time for
hacking the leak point system but
they're letting me off easy what
happened the Pokemon League said they'll
wave my depth if I do some volunteer
engineering for them oh they even asked
me to come work for them after I
graduate if you can't believe
[Music]
that director clavell and that ga ga
lady kept complimenting me like a weird
amount apparently I have outstanding t
or something I'm like a super genius
don't
mute you want to hear it
huh sorry for calling you out here like
this I'm still not so great with people
face to face I never seem to find the
right words but um thank you yeah thank
you so much you save team star and my
friends along with
it I know words won't ever be enough to
prop thank you for all you've done so
here Draco
meteor sounds
strong
wow comets are summoned down from the
sky onto the
target record from this move harshly
lowers to use a special attack St does
it do damage too I'm sure you put what
that voice I'm sure you'll put this to
good use and one more thing I want to
repay the dep I owe you if you ever
think of a way I can do that just let me
know I'm great with machines and hacking
and stuff oh I'm sure wait wait wait
wait we were supposed to get her into my
team
right for going to the area
zero next time I'll be the one helping
you
kiaa
[Music]
oh complete Street
we
[Music]
we okay we finished that now what's
next what is next sua oh neona is here
she seems to want to talk to
me uh is there
no how do I get
there wait it's like
is there like a tunnel
here there's a gate in the
city wait which
way are we ready for that or should I do
something else
[Music]
first guessing oh wait maybe it's from
there
I'm ready okay ow okay should I give the
Draco meteor attack to my
frogzilla never mind it's not
here or you think it's not good for
him
no
no there it is how did I never notice
this was it closed before I
[Music]
wonder was closed okay
o
[Music]
hi level
nine if it was close until now then they
can put some higher level Pokemon in
here all right uh b b it was never
closed it was open okay what the
hell at this part was
open
a okay well
then so is this like really L level two
let
meow
14 what a
jerk que you would think you'd get a
little bit of like last minute last
minute training in here before going to
[Music]
neona I guess that ain't
happening this one is low but the next
one isn't oh that would be a big b
bamboozle for anyone who wanders in here
before they really should be
here that one over
there that that would be insane bambooz
though is he like suddenly like level 60
now thank you fire glass yeah I'm happy
to this back to normal I'm so happy I
was sick for so
long I really wanted to stream a lot
leading up to Christmas and leading up
to my Japan
trip so
ah the nuzlock
killer dear Lord oh well oh well not
effective
but let's
go sand storm
[Music]
did you guys watch
the the Epic sock puppet finale I even
showed it to my brother and my mom when
they arrived
yesterday it was a coincidence that
Bales the last one but the most cursed
one that I
made
was the one to deliver the the
speech was so
funny no no that was the finale that was
the finale
yeah yeah BS even looked even crazier
than she should because one of her eyes
was
stuck it made her look so DOR worky it's
not always like that though her eyes
aren't always like
that what the is that s ledge what
is
that
oh what is that
time H Ghost Fire ghost it's fire ghost
too I'm faster what it looks faster than
me but it's
not that isn't that like
um some special Evolution that I didn't
get to
do but um Scarlet has a different color
right Scarlet's evolution of that
Pokemon has like a a different one and
that one's the Violet one
right I've seen it I've seen it
I never got it though and honestly it
would have made no sense for me to get
that Pokemon because it it has a very
similar type right to mine even the
Scarlet one isn't that also just fire or
something I'm a
Rouge it's weird they make this special
Pokemon that totally overlaps with your
typing if you have a fire starter
h fire
psychic oh that one's fire psychic I
find interesting but if you get if you
get Violet and if you get the fire
starter then
well then that one is absolutely useless
cuz it's fire
ghost unless you want to give up on your
starter where's that coin thingy
whatever I'm not I'm never going to get
enough coins anyway at least not
today don't care I don't
care oh here we
go visual
preference in case you don't want your
fire starter but who wouldn't want the
fire starter with the with the fire BB
singing
hon what voice did I do for her
h h
a low one a low one
surely did I give her an
accent don't remember if I did she looks
like she would have an accent
though crony
voice hello
kiaha so this is it you've decided to
face the Pokemon link the final test you
must pass to become a
champion is held here here in this
building I wish you the best of luck
from the bottom of my heart
kiaha I look forward to meeting you
again
soon gosh her
hair her hair I think she needs to brush
it it has so much volume there I feel
like probably has a lot of knots like in
the lower
layers
I could brush your
hair am I ready I think I am wait so
wait I do one fight or do I do four
fights how many coins you got definitely
not
enough I have eight gym badges right
let's go Iuka
five four one
one okay plenty of downtime
hi hi aren't you one of the four why are
you sitting here like a
receptionist thank you for coming
today please do have a
seat this is
creepy this feels like a different game
right now I'm
scared kaai
this room reminds me of the entropy
Center if if I walk through that door
it's the same room again
probably no comment I aica will be your
interviewer let's get started with the
first portion of the champion
assessment
Fury let me see how many gym back gget
you have she needs a higher chair she's
sitting so
low excellent you have all
eight next I'd like to ask you a few
questions if you don't mind k please
think carefully as you may automatically
fail the interview depending on your
answers let's begin how did you get here
today well I
walked mostly very good very
good
please tell me the name of the school
you're enrolled
in what if I say something else mananita
Academy no
Naranja that's right so what brings you
to the Pokmon leak
today came to become a
champion sorry champion
champion yes indeed why else would you
be here I suppose kind of questions are
these what do you intend to do if you to
do if when you are what if and when you
become a champion yo this has never have
they ever done like an interview before
before you go to the those final battles
I think this is the
first I want to find
treasure I see interesting tell me which
of the eight gyms gave you the most
difficulty what I don't
remember none of them
probably one of them doesn't matter
anyway I don't even remember I think
this one was
Ice I don't remember which one the
others were ah C was maybe bug and this
was
grass ghost oh
maybe it did which one was
that
salty Mall this one
matters isn't that like such an
individual thing though well if mall was
the ghost one then I'll go for that it
better be right was it right oh maybe it
matters for who or what I'll be fighting
or so
I see and what was the name of the gym
leader you faced
there oh I see you're going to do that
to me huh rhyme probably was her name
hey
Larry did I choose the wrong one I
wanted to choose the the the the rap one
oh well okay in that case I guess it's
Larry then
damn
it I'm glad you seem to remember uh yeah
I totally remembered I have perfect
memory I have I ew I have um what's it
called when you remember everything you
see
there photographic me that's it
photographic memory
but do you remember which type of
Pokmon that normal normal normal that
one I remember wait was it
normal I think it was
normal was normal
right now I'm questioning myself but
yeah it was normal because he was so
normal
nice
unbelievable building the skills needed
for the champion assessment is no small
feet you must have met a lot of Pokmon
to get here
kiaa what was the category of the
Pokemon you choose chose to be your
first partner oh really you really
asking me that
huh okay you're not asking to test my
knowledge here right you're just like
confirming cuz you have to type it into
your system and all that like legal
things and so on
hopefully
very good very
good please how could I forget my
starter please forgive me but I'm going
to repeat a previous
question I what do I attend to
do treasure
woohoo was it the wrong was it the wrong
answer giving me a second chance
or oh no that's right okay what the
what's going
on next is the final question for this
interview so
weird you like Pokemon
um sure Pokemon the game or Pokemon the
Pokemon
whatever say
no why would I say
no
good job kiddo gu trying to manipulate
me I blew it no
way that about wraps up the
interview what a weird thing to do
here I passed the first
test I'm so
[Laughter]
confused you failed at why so I need
help maybe for the the the arena
question and which trainer it was H
that's the only one I feel like that you
can it
up on your first try too no l don't
think anyone's done that since
Theona anytime anyway time to switch
gears and get ready for the next segment
is it fighting I hope it's figh
him a we facing the elite ball let's go
I remember um in Pokemon uh shining
Pearl I had quite some problems with the
Elite 4 but really only with the last
one I think was it that
game yeah and hopefully this time we
won't struggle as much revive
tees we're the best El leag has to offer
you'll be facing us four in a row no
turning back this won't be a cake walk I
promise promise you dad make sure you're
all ready and then go into the room
behind
me okay please don't tell me it's the
same
room I can't
look trauma
oh I still looks like it could
be
okay
oh
interesting room design is still kind of
scary feels like one of those rooms
where you go in with like that white
jacket wrapped around you so you can't
do
now then let's get this started eh
let's good R be the first of elite four
to take you on take me on take on
me I
think go
[Music]
H it's a
beish I am starting with the wrong
Pokmon oh cool music I finally get the
valy I've been looking forward to this
so don't you give up too soon oh I won't
what it's a it's a water it's a
water right then I am a
f water
ground oh
[Music]
ohoh
doio I don't have I have I have bullet
SE why did I bring
caspers so
useless should I use
caspers let's
see if caspers will be able to manage
this
one
I'm pretty sure I wanted to switch out
Casper beforehand but oh well at least
we didn't take much damage that's pretty
good all right then bullets
it oh we go ah we go several times
nice wow okay let's
go let's go good job casers I didn't
expect to you at
all what's cam up that's the isn't that
the the volcano erupt Pokemon
thingy again I have no water fire
ground what do I do Sweep with caspers
what do you mean sweep what can I
do oh is huge
uh should we do population
bomb okay I don't get full 10 hits
though I don't have that item I get like
maybe eight hits or
so
terize make me
stronger I think I have I have a special
type I'm not sure I don't remember just
bum
okay oh oh yeah oh yeah
oh that did a lot of damage even like
the single hits I'm
surprised wow okay wait how many levels
am I above anyway don't fun well let me
try I don't know the type but let's
go ah
steal I got something super effective
let's go okay I'm like over 10 levels of
above thank
God one two that barely does damage damn
two
three
[Music]
okay
only W earthquake
y but we're fine we're fine five is Max
oh okay
okay oh yeah really high defense he must
have really high defense super
bulky seems
so I can't believe I'm sweeping with
C I was going to take him out of the
team but I forgot duck
Trio I think we can bullet seed again
right I've learned this now oh yeah oh
yeah
baby what is going going
[Music]
on
what
M Claire what is that sounds like a
ghost Pokmon but I'm not
sure can we do it
ground poison oh does she have a ground
Pokemon ground steel ground whatever and
so
on well
then impressive you really have
something else kiddo don't call me kiddo
I don't like that ah it's that one that
so cute kind of sad I didn't put it into
my
team H so bullet the population bomb
what do you
thing population all right let's make
some more mice
babies let's finish this go on cloud
shake things up it does he attack
first oh no she teriz is okay into
ground y that's actually a sick cut
scene I like the animation of her and
the
color
a
protect so my population bomb doesn't go
through oh you going to do that
every time you
coward really I expected more from a top
four the lead
form here we
go no running from
kiaha it's happening whether you want it
or not oh I could bullet speed now oh
because now he's most typ ground
ah oh toxic
no I'm poisoned but we're almost done
with this
fight we're
good all right bullet seat to the
end wow what a what a coward strategy
you poison the enemy and then protect
yourself until the poison does a DOT
kill you for
real that is a ridiculous Strat it's
just because she can't do on her
own let me
through there we
go stret a
stret
[Music]
all right one
more no we're done with that
one wait we went for the whole team with
CMAs
amazing
what I did not expect
that wow
wow talk about unfair no way I was ever
going to win that one still though what
a great battle felt good even to
lose not a whole lot of trainers have
the skill to make it past the elite test
but who knows I'm beginning to think you
might be one of the few that do kiaha
better stay on your toes though the
second of the Elite Four is stronger
than
me you're up next s
work
ah
com oh did you
L yeah I did she's no push ever let me
tell
you I'll be watching from the side
avenge me if you can
eh you bet I will no oh same
room oh okay uh
we barely have to
heal
[Music]
sick why is
then so I I don't know I'm not going to
ask you guys to tell
me what type of Pokmon she mainly
uses what could it
be what could it be something cute huh
but maybe surprisingly not something
cute
I'm just going to start out
with Sparks again and we'll see where it
goes where did your face poppy of the
lead for hell
yeah it's so cool you this
part when you say byebye me oh my
Pokmon super
tough your we attacks won't work on them
at all they bounce you right off you
see I I can't wait for you to meet my
friends so here they
come a
child she should be in
school wow big boy what type is
the probably a double type but like
which one is hers the main one go
on Smash
him
steel all right oh might if steel is her
like ongoing type
then we can stay in with Sparks and
sweep
again oh okay steel iser seems like hell
yeah all right all right all right all
right all right oh
no
challenge no challenge for
me this will only take like a minute
guys maybe enough for a quick toilet
break for you guys go go go go go
go someone bring me a snack maybe I
could make some popcorn oh that would
actually be a good idea but I'm thinking
more of a sweet snack to be
honest
ideally I'm not even I'm not even even
[Music]
looking hi big metal
bird byebye big metal bird was nice
seeing you for a second on the
battlefield
next
please can I even buff myself even more
or aren't we at the max
already supposed to let it win oh it got
sturdy
oh strong against special well I'm
already buffed so hard that it doesn't
really matter three times more okay
okay then let's go again although we
might need to like refresh the
pp of that attack before we go into the
next trainer
fight just in case we need it take a
time I'm not scared my last Pokemon will
turn things
around sure well
sure as long as you still are hold
holding on to the hope then I'm glad I
didn't break your spirit just
[Music]
yet thinking of just going for the
flamethrower
now it's time to get dressed up all
pretty Tinky Winky
n
t
[Music]
it's her favorite TV show she's just in
that age
group oh good try good try it was
actually super
effective oh
[Music]
see too bad I'm so sorry girl maybe it's
time to go back to school stop playing
games
[Music]
oh oh don't look guys it's critical
damage on your
COC oh
man look what you did
oh
[Music]
I'm
sorry I want to take the revenge on you
we pretty sure you mean take rench for
me squirt don't think I did anything
wrong by you hey to say it but you lost
puppy better call the next guy oh that's
right Haven time to do this in a long
time it's your turn Mr
[Music]
L
Larry did we know that it was one of the
elite
four oh wait oh it's because I said I
had the most problems of him
did I have problems with him though I
don't think
so is he going to use the same
Pokemon I should
uh do the
PE which which item was that
ether uh
okay
hey this always
him
oh oh so that's just a coinci well then
what were my answers
for okay uh I don't remember like what
we were using and what was good but
uh I'll just go one those
[Music]
Sparks
Ah that's right I I might have uh used
caspers a lot
huh it's noal use
fighting fighting was
effective
really really I don't remember he uses
flying now what his whole
team well I wouldn't know that if I
would play along so whatever
that's fun he's like I I guess I can
kind of see it in this tie did he always
have this tie he's reaching for
something more exciting now he wanted a
little bit of excitement in his boring
ass work
life I serve as a member of the L 4 to
yeah unfortunately for me not like I'm
already told you over worked you know
but at least you usually people don't
come this far so it's not like I do this
job a lot I use normal type Pokmon
usually since I have a lot of common
with me but while the boss told me to
use a different type here
uh didn't know what to do so I just went
with flying Pokemon I
guess hoping that they will pick me up
and then drop me off on some Island so I
can finally get a vacation
man cuz my workplace won't let me take
of vacation it's a black company man you
sick
gloves chance Spar of elite full did his
hairstyle change I feel like he has more
gray
hair which is
worrying well that's plant flying huh
I'll be trying my hand with flying typ
all right but plant I can I should
have gone in with Sparks
man ah well each bad L of
Str he's
just aging really fast because of this
game all
right let's see how far we get with uh
[Music]
sporks
get thanks for buffing fire
moves star
rptor some kind of bird but uh I don't
know I'll
stay can't be that
bad is that fighting flying or just
flying steel
fly there's sunlight oh Brave Bird oh
that's strong ooh but not so strong but
he does some damage to himself even
thanks for helping me out so
much
oh normal flying ah okay we
were thinking of that black bird didn't
you alaria dragon flying
right h i could switch to my dragon
Pokemon or I could attempt to
stay h
Shadow Ball I remember yeah this one I
remember yeah yeah yeah cuz I like this
Pokemon right also special so my BFF
should
help oh
[Music]
yeah I might have been a little bit
too highly leveled
overall it just kind of happened when I
was
sick I did Force myself to stop
eventually oric Coro what is
[Music]
that a the Cher bird so
cute H let me Grill
you I wonder if you taste like
[Music]
chicken okay FC
kfp someone say KFC but it's kfp man
Flamingo ooh Flamingo
strong Fire H fighting the
show well I'll
stay you stronger than before oh man I'm
going to get it going to get another
gray hair streak
don't even have time to go to the
hairdresser to to cover that up man all
right love it six
6 just a flamingo you guys always um
always talk so so positively about this
bird you know you're underestimating it
really I'll do another a torch song I
guess or maybe it wasn't necessary cuz
this is his his last Pokemon at the risk
of messing up my sua but it's time to
get some wind D bags oh hi he's going to
caresiz it into into flying isn't he
[Music]
a
okay
whoops great for earling game it
definitely
was it worked just
fine that's shocked
Flamingo all right one left
guys isn't that the left one the
dad another dad so many dads Well that
took the wind from under our
wings sorry Larry you can go back to
your other job now you're a lot stronger
than I recall no wonder L PR likes you
now then I suppose to final member of
the Elite Force
next H so Hof
[Music]
I don't think he heard you
Larry
hustle
[Music]
louder
hustle hustle you R
next this dude actually also looks like
he could be a teacher in Harry
Potter uh hello there light me to see
you there were you taking care of my
child well thanks guys uh I'm here now
so you can leave if you
want oh no we
watch
right ah well I guess he's a yeah but I
mean a teacher in the Harry Potter World
specifically so I wonder what he's try
raining so far we had ground steel or
[Music]
flying I don't know what could it be
Dragon
okay oh that that that makes
sense I was of course absolutely certain
you would make it to me eventually young
sprouts truly do grow with astounding
speed yes but I never for a moment
imagined we would be facing each other
so soon now teacher's duty is to guide
students and Aid their growth those
Stein skate eyes but I think I shall
forget about my role as a teacher for a
moment and wield all my might for the
sole purpose of defeating you I am
Hassel not Hoff the dragon guarding the
final Fortress of the Elite Test prepare
to learn firsthand how the fury breath
of ferocious
battlefields I hope this won't end up be
really really embarrassing for you dude
oh they all have matching gloves I just
noticed cool
cute
ah that one looks so
strong poison dragon
maybe show me everything you've got I
shall face you with my full
strength but ice is also super effective
20 attack from cling Pokemon during the
next turn cannot miss afflict double
[Music]
damage we can go for Rush he won't
survive will
he
ow oh that's the first time I saw that
animation I four
times I want to see glay for
us fla ah the Apple dragon's so cute
y though my my house is it is it Plant
Dragon or grass
Dragon apparently I've never foughten
before in this game ice four times again
all right then okay grass okay okay then
I was going to go for ice
anyway dor yeah it's true it's
okay did I miss did we both Miss what's
going
on what the
a waste of my
time you good can we both Focus up a
little
bit it's a serious
battle H Dr get don't know what it
is anyway
what the what am I
[Music]
doing what again I also super effective
this one's poison
dragon
H just use dragon attack d
k oh oh dragons are aak through I as
well we got so much Choice done we're
sweeping every single one of those Elite
Four with one
Pokemon kind of sad I was hoping they
would have like mixed types but I guess
they never do
huh I feel like at least for elite four
you should give them mixed types but at
least they can have double types but
still it's
lame I'm 15 levels above them
yeah
but you know I'm over
level that might
[Music]
be
nice but you know it helps us to finish
the game
today being overleveled a little
bit so I take it I need to finish this
today and then we can read Super Chat
those don't we all want that
I still even haven't told you my Navy
story oh wait it's the same it's like
I'm looking in a
mirror who will attack
[Music]
first I will how do you
know oh higher level
oh I wonder if clay Rush will
kill hey this one's only six levels
below
[Music]
me let's do it yeah let's do
it do it and do it and do it do it do it
do it do it and do do it do it and do it
and do it do it do it this is the first
time I saw the Dragon terce I ization oh
he's going to do it too huh come oh
great dragon and take a terit as your
crown I see I
[Music]
see what a perfect mirror
match for you don't get to
attack
yay
noise why so
sparkly
chill he's happy GG the mighty dragon
has been
failed is it the
end of the
tarians oh no oh
no it's probably better for the world
you really did it oh
wow the bull bull are you okay I was
crying so proud of
you no way she's going
to I don't Grandpa they're not really
related are they or was my my lore my
was it
[Music]
true no he's just
old well we don't know we never Cena uh
and
D NDA no DNA
test
confusing I don't know
sorry we work with a lot of ndas so you
know sorry about all this Ki the old man
can get like that
sometimes guess I've got to do the
talking anyway your result for the Elite
Test of champion assessment
is a pass no doubt about
it yeah you T
[Music]
Ste congratulations I'd say you're good
to go but there's actually just a wee
bit more to the champion
assessment this will be a final trial
neona see the do door back there our FS
Commander the final opponent Commander
will face for your test is waiting
Beyond it her skills are so amazing she
was able to do strong arm all of us into
joining the Elite Force
you won't find the migher champion
though I think you'll be fine kiddo you
beat me after all I'll patch up your
team on the house so don't lose your
here
BS Tas oh I guess it's the blackhaired
lady and then maybe neona and her
probably cuz you said one one
41 we'll see we'll see we'll
see evil baby dragon can breathe
fire what guess you got over your subs
huh you can do this we all know you
can I think so too I am prepared I came
prepared your hands may be small but let
them seize a great
Victory thanks guys so wholesome all
right then say Al
[Music]
suckers should I save maybe I won't die
anyway but just in
case a t but you're very overleveled
okay then I'm not worried well C sweeps
this one
really easy easy
easy oh we actually going into a
different room this time
then oh the roof
cool ooh I like this roof that's good
weather
too welcome Kwa it gives me great joy
that you have managed to make it all the
way to the picle of the Pokmon League
the final test is battle against me the
top Champion to pass all you need to do
is win but before we get started I
should apologize for one thing you see I
have a threat that some might say is
inappropriate for leak chairwoman I'm
utterly incapable of falling
back that's like oh that's so stupid
that's like when you go to a job
interview they say what are your your
strengths and weaknesses and you say my
weaknesses being so
eager and working really hard not being
able to hold
back I just can't take a break stuff
like
that I can't hold back
okay when it comes to Pokmon battles
maybe that's why nobody's passed this
test recently it's a bit of a problem to
be
honest but you you might manage
something wonderful like Champion nimona
did so are you ready for a final test I
want to see the true measure of your
talent she has developed since she can't
hold back she also can't hold back her a
anymore top Champion
G
justra wait does she she doesn't only
have one type right she has different
types Sur
right I do hope you can defeat me and
become a champion
[Music]
yourself again a new
track
a is very like positive
uplifting oh or does she do
psychic is that her thing she looks like
a trainer who would train psychic
[Music]
Pokmon yes that was the correct
decision in this situation please
continue I will I will sweep I haven't
even started my torch song are we are we
singing are we going to be singing AB
that's a nice Pokemon
right yeah okay now we can
sing
Y is that all you
got is that all you got but it seems
like she has mixed tpes kingom bit no
don't know what that is
we'll
see is this some di Pokemon what it
looks like a evolution of a Pokemon I've
seen
before is it
steel dark steals oh okay
TCH speaking of fire you know my Advent
we Reef
I was um you know I wanted to light it
for Christmas when my family was here
cuz it looks really pretty but turns out
one of the candles the last candle
actually has you know that the candle
thing that's supposed to go all the way
to the bottom of the candle it didn't
have that it was like a I don't know
product
ER the wick I didn't have that
so um like I didn't I thought okay I
guess it doesn't have it but I guess
whatever my brother and my mom tried to
um find the wick tried to carve it out
but there was just was no Wick in
there so what we did was we made a big
hole in the candle in the middle and
then I inserted I got a different
different
candle and I inserted it in the
candle in an attempt to you know be able
to use the candle again cuz you got to
turn on all four
candles it works
but overall it was a big mess and the
candle never you know looked really
pretty again the way it should be or
could
be
it was very messy but oh well I think it
added a little bit to the atmosphere at
least because I didn't have a Christmas
tree and I was very proudly boasting
that this was uh self me my my Christmas
Brie Advent free what the is
glamora don't think you've won just yet
what do you got what do you got
H I don't know that
one rock
[Music]
poison is fire effective against
that shadow B yeah I was doubting that
fire would be
good oh
well
Ro the this fire well
okay I'll give her one turn to play
around a little
bit so she has a bit more screen time
and can get some more fans oh almost
killed it
though oh I shouldn't have given her
more
screen it was a
mistake it was a little
mistake
[Music]
so much for that oh well okay what else
do we have then against Rock and and
whatever that
was BB oh finally we haven't used BB at
all so
far okay really no wait no people say
d water and
[Music]
ground
it's not poison anymore
mhm use grass water ground on gr okay
I'll go for C sorry
B oh thank you
harine happy birthday I guess oh in
December 30 oh okay that's still some
time thank
God and bullet see finish it let's
go
oh wait there we go I was wondering
where's my second
hit it looks pretty this Pokmon looks
pretty I like
it
e okay wait that was the last one wasn't
it oh I'm the new
[Music]
Champion
wow you go beyond my imagination so
easily I know it's
unbelievable it's just so
unbelievable I'm like a dream come true
such overwhelming power such amazing
skill it seems Pala has G gained another
wonderful trainer to be proud of
congratulations it's my honor to call
you Champion
kiaha sounds beautiful I like the Ring
of
[Music]
that congratulations it's right now I
can really say you're good to
go yeah you did it
Miss
congratulations
crying again
o let him cry I think it's nice that
he's so emotionally moved by how
incredibly stunning I am everyone should
be crying once they see
me like a proud dad
oh
oh your Pokmon you Pokemon trainers are
The Treasure of paa oh then I don't need
to go look for Treasure
right and amid that treasure Champions
are the jewels that shine the brightest
Champion Kiwa it is now your duty to set
an example for all of the trainers of
Vala now allow me to walk you back to
the entrance I'm certain you'll find a
familiar face awaiting
you what the why is there so much
fum coming out of my
throat kiaha
kiaha oh man I can tell just by looking
at you you did it right you became a
champion
no H you've got jokes but seriously you
did become a champion
right
no come on it's me I don't have to lie
just tell me if we
can't no okay wait you did become
Aion didn't you how many times you
ask you Champion
yes okay it stops here oh they give up
so I think I win the fight I win
[Music]
it sorry I just really didn't want to
deal with you today neona but okay I
guess
sure I knew along hey you were really
insisting on it I give you that I got
word from La Primera when you cleared
the Elite Test oh man Kella I'm a
champion and now you're a champion we
are
champions which means we're true equals
you and me both Champion ranked trainers
this is amazing now that you've made it
here I've got one thing to say you it
lets you and me be best rivals for life
I never felt like we were real
Rivals no
no oops couldn't hear you I'll say it
again unless you
me I'm in a mood
today sorry not going to stop this is so
worth
it until I hear her yes let's you and me
the best rap wait
she she's not going to stop until she
hears a yes she's forcing
me
can't even say
no okay wait you will be my rival won't
you
hey no let me go let me go I don't want
to consent what about
consent you me rbls yes wait is this
repeating already oh yeah it
is my
God I guess conent is not a thing in
this game yes TOA huh all right you know
what Rivals do battle their absolute
hearts out I'm going to hit you with
everything this time you ready do wait a
moment champion neona huh what's the
matter Primera Champion assessment has
only just ended I believe AR rest is in
order for Champion Gua skele and the
others Champions must be understanding
toward their
opponents Ry there I go getting over
excited again sorry kiaha and skele
that's not his name he has a name that's
like calling me or you guys or no okay
none of us but a human just a human hey
human I'm so sorry human for doing that
to you
human you want to want for your first
battle as true Eagles and Rivals H now
that you mention it that's a good
point in that case can we use one of the
Pokmon League battle
courts
[Music]
surely there's somewhere more fitting a
place with special meaning for the two
of you perhaps special meaning H let me
see anywhere to leave to M well maybe
the place where we first
battled out behind your house oh you're
right that private beach is basically
like her backyard mhm
mhm oh you way around that backyard is
basically a private beach for you
freaking
spoiled ha our beach had back huh yeah
the place where we had our first battle
might work but on the other hand to me
it just kind
of flex the
[Music]
flex stop flexing on me I'll you I'll
you'll pay for that I'll make you play
I'm on the Backyard Beach
too I have to move to Spain so we
got a backyard
beach to me it's just kind of my back at
you know a little ordinary I
[Music]
need she doesn't even cuz it's to
ordinary to her a Backyard Beach is too
ordinary to
her well that's s something about you
girl doesn't
it okay that reminds me Kiwa remember
back when director claval explained the
treasure hunt you know where he told us
to go in search of our own treasure well
I know what treasure I got out of all
this I found a true rival someone who
can stand up to me at my full
capabilities that's right I mean you I'm
so glad I got to meet you kiaa anyway
that being
[Music]
said are be waiting for you to battle
corn Miss go to Central Plaza Theater
H she's probably around 65 maybe
levelwise so think will be good still IR
respect you two share is palpable even a
bit inviable to be honest I am known as
La Primera but even when facing me in
the final test of her Champion
assessment Champion nimona nimona didn't
reveal her full mind and you I suspect
she has found someone she can battle
without holding anything
back I'm Thea
[Music]
myona heal oh maybe she did heal me oh
maybe she did she said I need a rest so
I probably need to heal myself my
[Music]
bolognia
I sang that song before on stage a long
time ago you know I think I never told
you that story you want to hear it want
to hear that weird
story it's really
weird I think I want
some why is it on the roof again I once
like kind of hinted where the is it
where is it I want to go up there
isn't it up
there
doel well well
well uh so once I worked for ah there it
is some
company just like a normal job in Japan
really normal like office kind of job
how many is that one not worth
it and I'm going to ride
mhm and the
boss uh let me try to remember this cuz
it's been a long time and I barely
remember myself but the boss I
think uh no one of the
employees uh worked uh or not not really
worked but like his thing was being an e
guitar player I
think I think and then also the boss who
was a lady she was on good terms with
some kind of Rich old
dude Rich old Japanese dude
who I guess just wanted to have his own
band
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah what so hard to
remember
and wait was he even part of the band
though but it was like his birthday
party coming
up and I guess like my boss kind of knew
that I like to sing and want to be on
stage you know so she asked me if I want
to be part of that band or that birthday
party which is kind of a PR occasion but
they rented out like a like a big uh
venue inside
venue oh there she
is and
uh yeah held a concert there and they
put together a band and like one of the
guitarists was that one at the job and
then I don't know there were some other
peeps I guess maybe the old dude was
part of the B I don't even remember I
only remember that you know everyone was
Japanese except for me and the lead
singer they got like uh some American
dude I think oh wait they're talking and
out of every single person gathered here
yes sorry sorry I'm the most excited by
a
mile suddenly
talking the stage is set nice cut
scene it's my all out
power versus your strength and
fation let's see who comes out on
tap is she looking for the
toab she'll never find it he in my
[Music]
chest oh I like his
track so basically it was a bunch of
normies creating a band and anyway the
the the lead singer was also so
Foreigner finally the thing I've waited
all this time for time to begin the
greatest battle of all okay let's go
let's go let me tangent
though oh
let's try Shadow
Ball ooh self
[Music]
frog yeah but the songs that they were
going to do were all like kind of rock
songs old rock
songs and and that's why I know some of
them quite well cuz I had to learn them
but I was mostly like a like a backup
singer like a like one standing on the
side you know with someone else me and
someone else I don't remember who that
was even we were doing like a backup
vocals and then the lead singer yeah
ACDC yeah we sang ACDC
too the lead singer was quite
good quite badass
yes she hits hard she does or form what
what is that ground I guess what do I do
what do I do what do I do Ste keep okay
thanks punu was real no rocku was
real my HP already looks pretty bad but
oh
well I'm faster thank God okay good
um yeah and then like I we went to like
practice several
times and had to do fun backup vocals
and then at the concert this was so
weird like I don't know I was like a
side character in someone else's
story oh doio I'll stay cuz I don't know
what to
[Music]
do it was an interesting experience it
was such a weird concert though was such
a weird thing it was just someone else's
birthday
party Dragon
oh the foreign exchange student
yeah yeah I was a s
character Andel The Rock oh yeah that
too oh
well oh I thought you meant the stealth
rocks meant something else
huh the rock
music oh that's going to kill me oh no I
didn't
oh
wa
Sparks holy
s BR Bo sing
[Music]
it I need my
ref
nauy is that not a ghost Pokemon I hope
I'm
faster ah no that weird thing what is
that whatever I'll switch out
um
okay
H to use Duma
[Music]
again
yeah anyway I don't know there's not
much more to say to it except that it
was a really really surreal weird
experience I guess the guests who came
to the concert were also really just
friends of
that kind of Moi rich rich dude who seem
to have like some kind of I don't know
shal
personality cuz that person even though
was a really old suit was
dressing in the in some
really
H eccentric
fashion it looks so
funny
P
wait
ah are we both going to dig are we both
going to
dig does he does the other one have dig
in their move set let's see let's see ah
they don't maybe they don't unless maybe
they do and they're just too stupid to
use
it oh it's
[Music]
survived
oh
man that big was so close to a one hit
man
okay I want to use
B are
[Music]
IP
ouch okay right Lina
[Music]
crash I I enjoyed I already forgot all
the
songs m
which one was the one that I was singing
like
maybe
[Music]
ice I can keep for you think
so
shirona ice can
work
okay okay
okay I don't remember the songs if I
would go through some rock songs
playlist fam rock songs playlist I would
probably remember
though all down to this my last Pokmon
we're going to fight with everything
we've got bring it
on the more I look at this Pokemon in
this final form the more I like it to be
honest shine BR my greatest treasure I
thought that was me what the but we
had something
[Music]
special it's not too
bad come on come on one hit come on
please
yeah
nice we did
[Applause]
[Music]
it once again kiaha slays oh don't
cry
cute everyone's like is she crying but
then she's super happy isn't she
you you did it this is leg just
incredible you're the strongest out
there like totally
Q I mean you knocked me flat oh God
getting Goosebumps I was giving you
absolutely nothing everything I
I oh man Pokemon battling am I right
it's so much better so much more fun
than I ever even
knew thanks thanks for that incredible
match you why is that gone so fast what
the
CL cute that was very emotional now
let's give ourselves a minute and have a
quick break QA before round
two
n which Pokemon should I bring out this
time decisions
decisions those
you a
that's
nice oh
complete man I feel like it's been 4
hours I feel like I'm kind of slowly
progressing
huh
y too much Tang yo arvan here okay but
now our team is complete huh whoa down
boy don't jump like that seems like
hearing your voice has all my all works
up one last
[Music]
section
yeah BR is
frezy I hope he's
okay H you remember what we talked about
before about going to area zero yeah
let's do it go go go go go go go
speedrun
run I need to read super
chats you assumed this would take me
maximum an hour until now what I did
until now
of course you do you little know it
all got a mind like a steel trap eh well
all the effort you've been putting in
around P has really helped you make a
name for yourself build up some Goodwill
that's for sure so I've been able to
secure two allies who want to go I have
been able to secure two allies excuse
me m
[Music]
the now we just got to go there okay
let's go let's go let's go waiting at
the zero gate zero
gate have I seen it before Oh no I
haven't looks like a space
station an hour left of the game
oh let's
go it doesn't feel like there's only one
hour left feels like there's more
left no wait can I not just go through
ah what wait wait wait wait
wait yeah and don't
call that
thing I know
wait that
thing okay let me go
[Music]
here what is that sneaking on my door do
you see
that you see that red
thing what's
[Music]
that looks like a Pokemon or
Pokeball Pokeball Place
holder another Pokball
bug it's a door
stopper okay uh do I have to leave this
building too
probably
let's go I mean I kind of expected 5
hours of gameplay I planned for
that so if it really only takes like
about one more hour then roughly
roughly on to the best part of the
game why why why do they make it so that
the best part of the game is at the end
of the game the whole game should be the
best part of the
game or like around the middle I don't
know the change of mood in the game
oh okay
[Music]
okay have I fought enough two only what
the hell okay never mind done uh
oopsie what about my Pokemon oh they're
doing fine someone healed them Theona de
huh okay
okay
uh let's go I should tell you about my
nappi trip man it's been so long already
I was expecting to tell you about it in
the Pokemon stream in the originally
planned schedule
date never
happened ah the
guys
you waited for me to come to the
city it's Theo City huh is it wait is it
is it though it it's not isn't that like
somewhere completely else is this just
random
you who are these
people who are you
guys planning this out perfectly
to bambooz on
me should we fight him let's fight
him oh that's the lar one
oopsie I thought I was wrong but you
guys just suddenly start an Neo
ra
noo right really didn't did my did my
viewers even
increase hi Tonky
[Music]
wonky okay okay just one Pokemon
perfect yeah I mentioned a few stories
but not not
everything okay okay okay okay okay I
mean I wrote notes down but let's see if
I can do it without no I shouldn't I'll
forget things let me open my
notes why the are you so up was
sturdy
again
[Music]
unfair okay okay
no where did
I oh okay
okay all right so I think I already told
you that we were both late and I had
troubles finding a restaurant we met up
in in salburg uh a little but nice city
in
Austria I thought it would be nice to
show her around there cuz I know the
city quite well and just by foot
you can really see
everything in like okay maybe not
everything
but in one day by foot you can you can
get pretty
far you see a lot of important things at
least so by the time I arrived I was
already late like sun was already
setting by far was kind of sad m I have
to go from
here oh seems
so hey over here sorry my tangent has
been interrupted once
again space
station this is the zero gate it was
made so researchers could try to observe
the inside of the great Crater of paa
what folks call area zero SAR TI it down
into the crater oh and speaking of the
crater you know that Pokemon up here is
the one I gave you ER here is apparently
where Kon was born or something like
that maybe it will be happy that it can
finally come back home not that I really
care about anything
huh why you about that anyway our two
new teammates should be waiting for us
since at the zero zero gate guess we
should head
in are they actually going to fight with
us or are they just going to be like in
the background cuz that's kind of
lame oh maybe we'll do raids because
four people are always in
raids that would make
sense like a space
station what kind of dark in
here why is there like no staff guarding
it or so what the hola
H Arin said there' be tons of strong
Pokemon so here I am when she heard you
get to battle awesome Pokmon she was
here in a second you're an annoying
little pest at the Academy but I guess
you could come W so honest spoking like
a guy who wants to get beaten in the
battle but more importantly why is it so
dark and where's the awesome Pokmon not
here
it is weird that the lights are off last
time I was here the electricity was up
and running but
now what
music well now the lights are
on but why well they were waiting for us
I I turned them on like a hacker just
turn on the lights switch to be honest
too seems like they were in power saving
mode h
I hacked into the system controls and
overrode the settings oh it was more
than just a light
[Laughter]
switch oh it's you the kid with a fluffy
Eevee
bag cute kind of kind of wi that e um I
guess my name's
Penny well hey we never got to actually
talk I'm Theona I'm in class 1a it must
be some kind of tech wiiz do you like
Pokmon battling too
you talk like way too
much do you understand what I've been
going through all this time the director
introducers us when you need someone
good with text she's a no brainer anyway
Penny also agreed in the second when she
heard it was time to help
K I'm not really the adventuring type
but I owe you kiawa and I pay my
debts she surprising oldfashioned like
that and of course everyone knows me
Arvin my loves include my buus and
cooking and no one cares biometric
identification in progress oh ah s hello
kava I've been expecting
you and it seems you have gathered a
group of formidable allies as well and
my
son uh sorry who are
you that's my mom
probably what do you mean probably
what that's Professor
s Lona student ID number 805 C1 and
Penny thank you for
coming oh of course Professor oh my gosh
it's such an honor to meet you in person
it's not really in
person Arin did you uh tell your mom
about
us why would I have done that to begin
with I'd like to ask you all to make
your way down into the great Crater of
Pia you can reach the lower lower
chamber using the elevator you can see
on your
right um
M please proceed below
huh you're not going to talk to you son
you had a
question must not
be W
okay well let me look around first I
can't move the camera in here come
only this
much okay can I tangent or is there no
time for Tangen thing
now no
time love while damn
it
H biometric identification in progress
identity is confirmed why is she talking
like a robot access granted to lower
level oh it open for us automatically
that quiet looks like to me like
someone's controlling this thing
remotely once you step through you'll be
above area
zero Kiwa you've brought cidon with
you I'm so te is and he's such a rebel I
do not believe that can be the case well
then why are you asking me if you
identified the Biometrics
anyway if you utilize kon's gliding
capabilities you should be able to
descend into the depths to reach area
zero
right what isn't there like an elevator
or something wait did you say k don't
can
fly when you reach the bottom I will get
in touch once again I hope your trip is
uneventful
right rting people into stuff just like
always I can't wait to see what Pokemon
Le down in area zero let's
go watch out for spoilers and trat
okay that girl is she like incapable of
fear or
what she has a little bit of Hunchback
doesn't
she
okay what do you mean I can't write good
I on here just told me
to what I'm supposed to just open it
when I'm falling like a like a
parachute
huh ready for the
worst yeah how do you know it's the
worst good that's all we needed to hear
get out the Pokmon of yours and we'll
be off h
best B GM
coming okay they wanted a cut
scene what's the matter with it or
scared get of Hearts that's what I sayy
how dare you ride my
Pokmon you too hey
hey I didn't give you guys permission
how does that logic
work hey that's so
[Music]
scary how
Reckless that's so
dangerous
pretty
should have taken the screenshot yeah
damn
it music
to oh I hear something really
faint
what
[Music]
hello and now I'm back here
again I think I might have died once or
twice
there it's okay it's okay you did it
we're on the ground now
yes L reset her game to take a
screenshot
what it chose to go back into into it ah
it chose to go back into it
po it's probably just hungry or
something wait a second where's the
student counc
neona oh where is
she oh everyone you have to see
this I it was
amazing don't run off like that it's
dangerous come on already I guess your
ability would be un Tempo
huh funny Pokmon
jerk condition satisfactory mhm vital
signs all within normal
range it appears you were able to make
the Descent without being
harmed uhuh yeah sure smoo sailing who
could possibly complain about a landing
like
that that is that is
good I had concerns in might fail given
the crudeness of the only available
access method you had a feeling that we
might die and you will just let your son
go down like
that
wow I think your mom's circus and
detector needs
fixing uh you are worried about us
that's so
sweet
you should now make your way to me at
the zero lab
oh in there in the deepest part of area
zero
however the entrance to the lab is
buried by four locks insalled on the
exterior which I cannot
unlock it's so quiet right now what the
freak four locks on your way to me you
must visit four research stations that
were constructed inside the crater
ahuh at each station you will be able to
disable one of the logs do so as you
make your way
down I hope you
succeed wait for the drop where there
must be music first for there to also be
a
drop
okay yes let's disable the four loocks
and get into the lab sounds kind of like
video gaming when you say that oh don't
break the fourth wall
Lona come on time to find find a way to
the deepest part of
arero Music going hard what
music do you hear something that I don't
hear hear the footsteps I hear really
really really really really faint what I
still can't ride it okay what the
hell I like this sparkle what are these
sparkles in
the
oh why is that why is that starting so
randomly
[Music]
what
oh are the Sparkles supposed to lead me
somewhere
oh okay okay okay now we're getting
somewhere who is
this so this is
inside what feels different from just
seeing it in our textbooks normally we'd
never be able to get in here to see it
for ourselves huh wait where did coron
go seems like it got spooked by
something it's hiding in his ball in
cereal that's not good can we even get
back got to the surface without it ah
should be all right the last time I was
here I caught a flying taxi out of the
crater oh that was come through why
didn't you just call the professor if
she's down here don't get along or
something none of your business pip
squeak please no need to bite my head up
what are you getting all puffy puffy
about okay come on you turn this
adventure have a good
[Music]
time it just goes away um on
automatically I wish it
didn't are they going to have a lot of
those dialogues popping up can I can I
tangent
please I will I will now okay so we met
up and it was snowing like crazy I think
I also told you that but because of that
we were freezing and I told you that too
and we were going to Christmas markets
right
so my plan was to go up there's like a
castle and like a little mountain in the
middle of the City I wanted to go up
there and show her like a nice view but
the um the cable car we wouldn't really
have enough have had enough time to go
there so kind of gave up like I still
tried to get there
but yeah I didn't want to rush and then
by the time we were somewhat close to it
was kind of late and then I was like
well na do you want to walk up there by
foot like I did it before but with all
the snow I feel like it's going to be
kind of exhausting and oh what why can't
they walk normal and I can't okay okay
okay
now and yeah so for us na was like yeah
let's do it that's fine so I was I was
planning on doing it but on the way to
the path to lead up to the the castle hi
sming hi meow meow
um and uh we walked for like Christmas
markets and all that and we were getting
really hungry and we were looking for
food but then no one took C so we first
had to find an ATM blah blah blah it all
took so long so much longer than I
thought ooh hydr
pump so we kind
of
meow gave up on going up there
eventually because even if we went up it
would have been pitch black dark we
wouldn't have really seen much of the
city so yeah so many people yeah the
Christmas Rockets were insanely crowded
but So eventually after we got some
money from the
ATM um we uh I I I you know recommended
what we should eat at the Christmas
pocket so first I got uh for Nai Mama
something like mold wine actually I
don't think it was mold wine right it
was something else can most what's most
in
English not quite mold wine but she
really liked
it so I'm
satisfied and I just got myself some and
Outsider oh some kind of Plum cider or
so oh that
hurt you did
music way to
quiet oh can I fall down here don't want
to and and and and then I got us like a
oven potato I
know maybe the photo didn't quite make
it look as good as it actually was but
naimo said that that was during her trip
here one of her favorite things that she
had eaten but I think the fact that we
were freezing our butts up um made the
potato taste a lot
yummier but I just generally generally
love oven potatoes
you so we shared one oven potato baked
potato with
um what happens if we fight anyway we
should try huh why can I not walk
normally
Fu
sake let me fight
someone I guess I'll fight
you
uh oh know oh 54 on on but so I fire
alone okay
[Music]
oh the fighting music is cool here
too but we only heard it for a
second okay so uh let me fight this one
then hi come down will
you yeah there we
go and yeah we got the potato and uh we
got roasted
almonds and she really like those too I
was so happy that was actually the first
thing um I bought for us I shared the
fro uh the the roasted almonds they're
really yummy yum yum yum
yum the sugary roasted
almonds love those so much ah we
snapped on those for a while but yeah
eventually want to see something more
proper even the potato didn't help so
much and I want to go into a restaurant
but as I told you I called like 15
restaurants and they were all full no
matter what time they didn't want not
want to give me a seat I'm so
sad so sad guys I really wanted her to
eat some yummy Austrian
Cuisine like she got me yummy Korean
cuisine in Korea you know when she
showed me around oh well I I keep on
doing that by
reflex
uh what was I
saying ah oh yeah and also we walked
into
um like some store in the Christmas
Market oh wait so Penny how' you went up
with friends like Kaa well uh I guess
she just really came what everything was
going out the rails school was big help
getting all that sorted
out so she helped you out too while she
was tackling Yo which 5-year-old can
read that fast K and I have classmates
neighbors is back home too plus I said
she should aim to be a champion and she
did so do they not want me to read this
so
ha
there are nothing compared to what me
and her went through our friendships are
another level uh nobody asked you stop
trying to flex on us guess we're all the
buzz with k club okay well feel
weird can you make it slower
oh yeah well
whatever I'm not pressing a s it on it's
automatically going
by I wouldn't complain if I was doing
it that gave me a
shock sneake
attack okay I'll try to make it slower
next time after this
battle
e
disgusting yeah voice acting of course
would be nice would be nice hi smothie
why are you
here what oh
yeah yeah no mommy is working I know you
had you had two weeks with me
alone mommy has to get back to work at
some
point
H I'm sorry
oh yeah wait I know that's not the wrong
wrong button here uh
options attack speed
slow slow I guess will that
help
man
okay okay okay I'm leaving her soon yeah
that makes me so sad
too don't want to think about it I'll be
gone for a while on you do be like that
um oh yeah we went into this little
store and I was looking at like I kind
of wanted her to look at the ornaments
it was selling like Christmas ornaments
and all kinds of stuff uh I was thinking
maybe she find something cute that she
can buy well then you know I was just
trying
to sell all the things promote the
things they had there and I was looking
at a little owl a white owl
thingy and uh oh should we go just fall
down
there should I follow the path I'll
follow the
path I can go for
it to exploring I want a tangent anyway
so to wait
and I thought there would be an item
here
sad yeah it was a little white owl I was
like ah so cute I love owls and so she
takes
that white ow and she says I will buy
fori waa I'm like oh n what really
that's sweet of
you so she went up
the to the store
person got it for
me now I got a cute little owl it's
really small it's like smaller
than no maybe about as big as the palm
of my
hand yeah
[Music]
yeah maybe I should have walked down oh
well it's a tiny
mum doesn't really look like M my sock
puppet looks more like
M but yeah and
then I think then we were at a point
after already kind of like going for a
couple of different Christmas markets
where you know kind of wanted to
go into a warm place oh how did I miss
that oh I didn't ah was looking at that
from up there what oh oh I bet that's
what we're looking for
yep that must be one of the buildings
the professor was talking
about possibly oh yeah what are they
called radish
rations no way research
stations well I was
close good try good attempt oh you have
such great memory
Penny it's quite obvious makes a lot of
sense don't you think the name research
station a SC is my Common Sense compared
to you yeah yeah that's more of a common
sense
thing train ah that
thing
cool yeah yeah Pokemon love primary uses
I didn't know that species could be
found in the great crater oh so did LA
PR get it from
here interesting take it on together oh
finally a double
fight she ran away though oh
neona
Lona a there she is okay she's just
really
far I thought she was going to ditch me
again look it's like a love triangle
H
H what choice do I
have
oh wow you're useful
unbelievable wow thank you for once like
Arvin was never useful in our double
fights against the
Titans she one hit that thing
are they going to be a lot more of these
rare Pokmon down here you
think I think that was something please
you've got no idea how terrifying area
zero really is so far it hasn't really
been
terrifying wow patronizing
much easy you too let's just head inside
the research
station m
okay let's go
[Music]
inside Pok Balls or something I miss
no okay what is
inside some books of LW inside
oh wow are these ancient ruins a a
ancient this looks ancient to
you girl yeah they look far to reason
for that uh-huh it appears you have
reached your first research station
without incident this facility was
constructed 87 years ago as a way
station for those surveying area
zero so that's why there's a bed yeah
not really comfortable looking though
looks like we can use this place to rest
up if we need to ah like a Pokmon
Center can M if you would be so kind as
to disable the first lock on the lab
using that Central panel okay okay
okay oh I got a dusk stone ah that was
in front of the door
right I feel like we're doing something
really dangerous here and by the time we
press the last button we're going to be
regretting it well done please continue
your efforts at the remaining research
stations in the books yeah okay okay
okay we've determined that this energy
crystallization is linked to the being
we call something
something the interlocking hexagonal
plates that compromise shell must
somehow cause this phenomenon which I've
dubed parest
alizing oh
thanks to my prototype Terror orb I
secured corporate founding fing for my
research and made a laboratory in the
lighthouse near kabo po someday though
I'll return to the crater and resum my
study of these crystal is is that just
what Professor Sada
wrote sounds like it was her what is
that wait what is that teleporting
thing yeah probably sound not h h h i
almost never saw my mom in my whole
life oh is it time for back
seem she was always busy with work
hardly ever came
home I C for myself clean for myself my
bus was the only one I had to talk
to P me so yeah I don't really know her
at all even if she's my
mom try not to think too much about it
tried to just be proud that she was a
famous
genius the truth is I would rather just
have a mom who was there even if she
wasn't anything
great haven't seen her for ages now
unless you count seeing her in the news
or whatever used to at least get emails
sometimes but even though stopped a
couple years
ago and then there she appears out of
the blue and tells me we got to come to
are zero some family
right oh but we're not here to judge or
anything and I'm sorry about earlier I
shouldn't have snapped at you like that
uhhuh I was also giving you a hard time
sorry uh Penny my name is Penny you know
you're actually pretty nice for a little
pipsqueak don't call me pipsqueak you
big
lunk nice spirit you
too okay weird banter going on there all
right back to K
[Music]
attention uh I went that way but I
wonder if I should have gone the other
way I'll check it out can I go over here
okay so oh yeah one more thing actually
before I went to all those Christmas
markets
um after I I met up with
her I realized I really needed to go to
an idol meeting and I was like oh never
mind I I'll be fine until we go to a
restaurant or
so um but you know we had troubles
finding a restaurant
and uh we were walking and walking and I
was like y s s I need to go to Alam oh
wait last time I came to great crator I
was trying to go see my
mom I got about this far and then I got
attacked by some kind of creature that
never seen before really what kind of
Pokmon was
it it wasn't even like a Pokmon more
like this crazy violent R rampaging sort
of
thing sure it wasn't just a Pokemon
that's a little more I don't know
rampaging an average like a Titan maybe
yeah I'm sure it was like a completely
different creature all
together and it hurt my bust really bad
so it's not like I just
forget I don't want to run into that
awful thing ever again did I miss one of
those
stations it was that strong huh and I
really got to say it that's what I
figured You'
say you will attack us sometimes deona
you know that what weird combo these
people really don't harmonize with each
other
huh there's one down here I'm good keep
crying okay uh I guess I'll fall down
here wait let me go
there
yeah no okay
whatever maybe later on I'll I'll be
able to use
um uh something done could I
don't later and then I can explore some
more oh that one's
pretty it's like a fire Mo right I know
it one's down there but let me explore a
little bit here
first um yeah yeah yeah you might be
wondering why I'm trying to tell you why
I really needed to go to an idle meeting
but stay with me
guys
so we're walking by this uh big big Saha
Hotel you know the one where the cake
comes from the Saha cake the chocolate
cake a famous one that we
also um I I give it out as a souvenir a
lot and I was explaining to her like
what kind of Hotel it was and you know
that the cake comes from there actually
I brought her the cake to Korea as a
souvenir so she had eaten it before but
you know I was like I'm 100% sure that
it's going to be full but you want to
check out the cafe and see if they maybe
let us
in you know for a little
snack and we went in and of course there
was a line of like 20
people absolutely impossible for us to
get a seat but not J was like wait but
Kila come come down here with me and she
she makes us go down some stairs to the
restroom and I'm like yeah we can't use
that we're not customers we're not we're
not using the cafe we can just walk down
there it's so obvious that we're just
Rand looking for a restroom feel bad
about it in this fancy hotel fancy
restaurant but
I don't know she insists on it and I'm
like well Happ if you go and she's like
well you know we can say I'm a foreigner
make a mistake
sorry I just kind of followed her and
then we enter the restroom and I was
able to go to do my idol meeting and it
was a really fancy restroom you know cuz
I didn't want to go in the in the train
station cuz train station idle meeting
rooms are don't want to go there I
wanted to go to nicer place this was so
nice was really clean and
fancy
so I was really grateful to navi for
pushing to
go to that
expensive luxury
restroom restro time as n likes to say
okay second research station is there
going to be another Pokmon though
[Music]
and it was even free guys the toilets at
train stations often cost money I think
just a little bit but still so we got to
a luxury
restroom which I didn't even need to pay
for but I would have liked to go enter
the cafe too so I was sad let's head in
and take a Brea I thought you'd have a
bit more stamina student council
girl I'm just full of
surprises that wasn't a compliment you
know what the
what the it's an alien
Jigglypuff
what happened to
it is that
[Laughter]
Sada does it count as a different form
or as an evolution surely a different
form
right what does it have a different
type
what it's an
alien complet what it's a completely
different
Pokemon
wao waa okay no relation but it's
obviously
like they they like tried to Tred to
create a Jigglypuff maybe and then it
turned into
this the is this
don't be scared why is your Eevee
backpack black
now she's so edgy and emo
now
what so dark really looks
black so
weird
okay
so she's using
Umbreon scream
[Music]
tail that's its
name oh whatever she used it didn't
affect me
nice and that was super effective I was
hoping for it
wasn't sure what it's going to be doing
but it works if it works it works catch
it oh too late but we'll probably have
more opportunities
right okay ah can't catch the story ones
anyway all right then see seriously what
was that Dar thing scared me half to
death it doesn't look that
scary this looks creepy like an alien
Jigglypuff or like a Jigglypuff that
people experimented on and it kind of
went wrong it was definitely kind of
ferocious for Jigglypuff wasn't
it no
kidding come on let's get inside already
one more jump scare like that and I'm
done for just like me for real for
real
wait but the other one didn't really
look like an existing Pokemon did it the
other one that we
met
all it's pretty much the same it
does seems like w Pokemon don't come in
here we should be safe to catch our
breath no need for it but okay
hey seriously what's with this place
that
Pokemon it's cursed it's cursed I've
been wondering about that
myself think maybe that Pokmon was one
of these NY
NY oh what's that
book book Monsters of area zero as we
descended further into area zero we
began to catch glimpses of mysterious
Pokmon
though we wondered if these huge
ferocious beasts were indeed Pokmon at
all one of our teams suffered a brutal
Blow from such a beast and was more
mortally wounded forcing us to retreat
for a
time a member of the servy team captured
this Photograph by chance I noticed a
passing resemblance to the Pokmon known
as Donan yet differences such as its
sheer size and the shape of its back
sets it apart as do its great Tusk wait
wasn't that a
Titan
so they aren't actually a
Pokemon uh I don't really
know yeah right so the Titans came from
erer well that's not a big
surprise what do you think
you I think oh both us just oh no wait
they're not I think they're just Pokemon
weirdos though yeah same I mean they
look different sure but they use moves
and batt just like the Pokmon We Know M
oh I suppose the time has come for
explanation
Professor some of the life forms that
you see residing now within area
zero our ancient Pokemon that lived in a
distant past long lost to us oh then we
shouldn't be battling
them because we need to preserve
them ancient
Pokemon what that's
awesome oh come on there's no way that's
possible the zero lab where I am located
contains a time
machine what it summons the ancient
Pokmon to this place
[Music]
oh so the thing my mom spent forever
researching down here she actually got
it
working indeed though the cost was cat
catastrophic
H human lives Pokmon
lives but a time machine you mean you
can actually travel to and from the past
it is theoretically impossible to travel
to the Past however for a being such as
a human it would not be possible to
return to the
present well oh you know who'd love to
go
there that one history teacher she
doesn't want to go back
probably let's just send
her
then she can stop complaining about the
current
state but then the past will be the
present for her so how's she going to
deal with that yeah once she's there
it's just a present yeah
H well that's
horrifying mom
you oh why' you call us here to area
zero as
sacrifices if possible I would like us
to speak when we can meet face to face
it will be easier for you to understand
once you can see the situation for
yourself well now then Kiwa please use
the central panel and disable another
lock on my
lab
S I feel like we still need like one
really evil
character like Penny wasn't really evil
so we're missing that maybe it's
sad well done please continue your
efforts at the remaining research
stations
heck you know that book she told me to
bring I think it's got something to do
with this place or more like everything
to do with this place but I'm not the
one she expects to fix whatever all this
is you are I think you should be the one
to carry it
oh thanks H nice book fancy
cover SC book got of the expedition that
the auor he ah
uhhuh Heap what this but the other books
in here are from s right the book has
the name s
written on in in his clumsy
handwriting okay just because s used to
own it right s is not like someone from
the past who Ed a time travel machine to
come
here that's why her name is on the book
it's her copy okay okay I mean she's
wearing oaba clothes somehow I don't
know her hair looks a little bit OAB
bonga to me
so oh
so maybe she's a c
woman we'll see we'll see
we'll
see the Crystal's power is tremendous
their unstable output made our corporate
back if we can harness this energy it
will open up research possibilities
we've only dreamed of at last Paradise
will be ours to
create
Paradise really at last I can resume to
work on the terror project I'll move my
research to zero lab this month my team
will be smaller but no matter the strong
influence of of the crystals makes our
experiments much more
unstable should I heal no I'm
fine maybe my fair was
right um what was I okay I am and
Christmas markets BL blah
blue what the what are you guys all
doing here there's the evolution the new
[Music]
one oh yeah I was so worried that Nai
would get sick because it was constantly
snowing like crazy and Nai didn't wear a
hat or anything so I was worried that
she would catch a cold her her hair was
like wet the whole time anyway H even I
know about your dad he's on the board of
the ROM phone company what wait how do
you know
that that's how she's she's so rich
everyone knows that he's famous and I
guess I looked into him for my own
reasons too so Mona's actually some ped
little princess yeah yeah we already
know that no no way that's so not my
thing though yeah I guess you could say
mother and father were like hands off
but in a good
way my big sister's probably going to
take over the business so they pretty
much let me do what I
wanted wait you called them mother and
father you little
for god
sakes yeah you must have been freezing I
was freezing
too I was I think I was wearing a hat
but eventually my hat was soaked as well
uh my family is unbelievably
annoying like super overprotective you
mean it's just my it's just my dad he's
loud and clean and makes up weird
nicknames for me like pen
pen he's the most annoying guy in the
world period he's the
worst man that's real down for you dead
having his own daughter describe him
like that yo these people really don't
harmonize don't you dare take your side
K how about you your mother seems super
nice oh yeah I guess she met my in-game
mom had a glimpse of an amazing looking
ah didn't think she was going to say
sandwich really I wish I could have seen
that I bet it tastes
great I'm so busy reading this damn
I can't even look at the scenery because
I have to look at the text the whole
time oh wait there's another one over
there H okay where was I we were
freezing we were wet we were
cold but I really wanted her to see as
much as possible from the city cuz we
already lost so much time but as I told
you before we ended up going to that
curry
place which was really nostalgic for me
but they changed so much they used to
have like daily curries and now they
don't seem to have that anymore
but it was fine had a good
curry and you know Nai made her really
really spicy as I told you last
time it's we need cow carrot
again nah n you don't have to really
really don't have to you probably
shouldn't people if you want to hear my
tangent you just have to go through this
ah all right another research
station which Pokmon we're going to see
this
time we got to chill for a minute no but
wait something's going to jump out at us
again 100%
[Music]
guaranteed H oh Penny such a worry
words
surprise
at least she didn't Penny didn't get
surprised even though she expected it
like I do sometimes when I expect things
and still get
bamboozled I like this version of it is
so pink and
purple B one of these before Arvin it
looks seriously
strong yeah well Ki and I are Old Pros
when it comes to tians leave this to
us it's not as
Titanic as the one that we fought
though like he's better than the
OG's now a version of Viet
[Music]
really what's down there is that a
spoiler is the world that I'm seeing
under the ground a
[Music]
spoiler spoilers on the ground
well can't be mad at the game for
spoilering me can
I A Whole New
World okay yeah so we had dinner and
[Music]
then I booked us some train tickets oh I
think naan didn't pay me back for those
yet oh yeah also like whenever there was
like a little bit free time actually no
pretty much only in the train I guess
but the whole train ride she was working
on her iPad doing some some work stuff
drawing some
stuff it reminded me of Ena ch in time
we also always have her iPad with her to
do some work when we were like uh on a
train or whatever when we were uh on the
way to
[Music]
somewhere always
working such Workaholics or not really
even if you don't want to be Workaholics
if you just have so much work then it's
not about being workaholic it's just
about being
overworked yeah they look straight to
grind
at least they have jobs
though in always working in yeah see
that Victor is
our maybe the one we saw when we were
searching out the urba mystica came from
down here yeah you too got to meet one
of these Pokmon before our crater get
together
challeng uh if we got we've got f from
literal ancient times roaming around
Pala that's a major
problem isn't Professor s doing anything
to keep them under control how could you
let this
happen just use some duct tape on the
time machine man yeah right cuz it's not
like OA brilliant Professor s ever
messes
up come on K let's get into the research
station yeah duct tape
when in da use duct tape or or glue hot
[Music]
glue and made to station number three
almost there how we doing after all that
walking and battling and whatnot anyone
need a rest
nah I almost honestly don't know what
the is wrong with my flum why am I
why am I spitting so much
out you're feeling rough
Penny uh no it's not that I've just been
thinking that's the problem you need to
stop thinking ever since the professor
mentioned that time machine ah there
have a Pokball on the ground around my
shoes you see
it the Pokmon here in area zero came to
our time from the past right so what
about Kur don't isn't it pretty likely
that it's also one of those ancient
Pokmon
yeah
probably I hold up all the cut
scenes
again I think you on to something it's
kind of giving off ancient Vibes even
its name sounds
pasty wait a sec I totally forgot hey
Arvin you had K's ball and you told us
about his forms in the first place you
must know something about it right I
still remember that from right back no
wonder you everybody's Little Star pupil
I guess I've got no choice then but to
tell you what I know that Pokmon C that
is it was found by my mom when she was
working on her time
machine I believe it would be best for
me to take over the explanations at this
point I don't want to give my son any
screen
time kland which I entrusted to kiaha
was the first Pokmon that was
successfully retrieved from the pass by
The Time
Machine
seriously through analysis of its
genetic makeup as well as its behavioral
Pence I came to realize that what I had
discovered was in fact the ancient form
of
cyoar well the ancient form looks so
much better than the current form what
the hell what
happened Pokemon still commonly written
in this region well that makes sense I
guess they do look alike many other the
Pokemon also came to this place from
across boundaries of time but I was
never able to bring over more than two
specimen specimens of
coridon you mean there another run
around here somewhere maybe the one for
Pokmon Violet
Edition what if their family the other
one could still be somewhere near AR
Zera waiting to finally be reunited with
our
Kon heartwarming family
reunion
exactly imagine how fa they'll be if we
can get the family back together after
all this
time Family huh yeah sounds nice if we
could proceed Kiwa please disable the
next
lock FU fumu oh there's only one book
here
[Music]
disabling
and one
more well done only one remains now
please continue on to the final research
station a doily wait a second our time
machine research has yield the Triumph
of Pokmon from the anient past I've
named he I was expecting one near life
to treasure wait no not he this blue
book was probably by solow right but
what Fortune to be blessed with this
gift as well h i wait no there's another
book here didn't see it I've
successfully brought more and more
ancient Pokmon to our time since the
first one she did it on purpose I'm so
close to creating a world like the one
in the book a paradise where we free can
live happily together forever I must
make it real dad mom and her
son and they're doing it because they
came from the past and they can't live
happily in this New World
maybe
[Music]
maybe you know
naban of course is also really into kop
just like me so we got really hyped she
was like K you still listen to kop and
I'm like yeah recently I'm like I guess
quite into new
jeans and then we both screamed we were
um walking through the city but then
suddenly we jumped around and scream
like oh my God yeah new oh my God oh my
God and then Na's like oh yeah hi boy hi
boy sorry I can't tangent they're
talking in they want to battle my
coridon so won't come out of its
Pokball oh all
right that was the first I heard of it
coming from the pass myself it was just
some weird Pokmon my mom brought home
all of a sudden one
day we all live together at the
Lighthouse lab for a little while wait
before I go into that hole let me go
this way my mom made me promise to keep
it a secret and I have to take care of
it for her
too that's why I knew so much about
it yeah but then one day K just went
nuts against some wild
Pokmon few of the folks living nearby
end up seeing it so the secret was
out once that happened my mom took it
and went back to area
zero yes that makes sense if it's a
Pokmon from a different
age yeah people found out it will be all
over the
news didn't see my mom and cidon again
after that for ages oh looking back on
it now it seems stupid but feel like I'd
lost my mom because of
coridon was the worst feeling ever just
hated coron and everything about it I
didn't want to talk about it poor
coridon being hated for something I
can't do anything
about you should be sorry you should be
[Music]
sorry great to know all that relevant
info before we got
here
yeah yeah but you know it's always like
that they they never tell you the full
story until when it's too late
last
minute okay I'll go into the big hole
now anyway anyway anyway
anyway yeah we made our way back and
then I saw I saw her
off and she went to her
hotel
and did I forget something from the
first
day oh the same
Pokemon always the same
one ah naan told me it's okay to tell
this but in the train you know she was
working a little bit but we were still
like talking constantly to chatting and
she told me about something and showed
me even a
video she told me that in her
school that she goes to right
now there was a talent
show and she participated in the talent
show by playing
guitar and she was singing along too and
she showed me a video of that it was so
cute I forgot which song She Sang but it
was an English
song it was so cute she was like sitting
there on stage playing guitar singing a
little song with a cute
voice in Her talent
show so cute I didn't know she could
play the guitar yeah I didn't know that
either well she
can unfortunately you guys will not get
to see the
video oh wait there's so many holes but
we have to go here first
anyway multi-talented yeah I wish I
could play the
guitar I can't play any instruments so
sad wait why is no one we didn't even
made a
Pokmon wait have we been in this one
before
oh how did I get back here
Hide don't okay
ain't nobody got time to learn a
freaking instrument wait where's the
next one in one of those big
holes there's one over
there but this one's so small there's
probably nothing really in there
right let me check it out though the big
one okay but I still want to check out
this
one before
what it look shiny what the I was
so bright I thought it was shiny
what on Earth that's so
[Music]
mean Y no
shiny oh I want a BM
Boozle you want catch it what which
one oh is that like a new form of it
what what is is a
new that one is that it's ancient
form looks
nice oh it looks really similar to its
like OG
form this will probably kill it though
won't
it I should use like
a
speed okay let me try to get the other
one
[Music]
ghost
Fairy Oh there's a Pok
ball well we all love Miss
dous so it's gone where there were
two let me respawn
them there it is
I'm going to get you I'm going to get
you whether you want it or
not happy it got a glow up it already
looked great before didn't didn't even
need a glow up I would
say um what was it
um quick Ball come on come on
please please yeah oh that was
easy flut man oh it does all these
ancient Pokemon have kind of lame names
like very descriptive names though no
like funny puns just descriptive names
huh I didn't quite have the sense for
ponny names back then yet
ah feel like that all of those ancient
Pokmon kind of had like their own
section
there how okay f with
describe now hold
on makes
sense
[Music]
okay now hopefully this is the right
hole
wait no okay I'm going
in maybe we will now have a big story
Revelation what can I go through oh yeah
oh crazy alien Jigglypuff I guess I
should try to catch that one too let me
try get
to you guys like this version more or
the the modern version of
[Music]
it red eyes scream tails are shiny oh
only the eyes are different yeah B oh I
didn't like I didn't like the
Pokball maybe a hyper voice won't kill
it this one's better Modern is less
creepy that is
true oh okay okay we can do another one
I think oh it's healing
itself no don't sleep wait up but that's
good doesn't that help the chances of um
catching it does it stay in sleep well
then well then well
done oh let me try
now it helps
yeah maybe a great ball how long does it
sleep oh looking good
okay so in order to make up for the not
so good first day at least in my opinion
like didn't quite do the things that I
wanted to do
um uh I planned out before I went to
sleep I planned out everything perfectly
for the following
day
I had like a Time plan a time schedule I
think we met up at like 11: or so I made
reservations for all kinds of hotels uh
restaurants going to try to catch this
one too uh uh and all good night lunch
and dinner
restaurants
uh for Austrian Cuisine I needed her to
try as much as possible cuz she couldn't
try on the first
day and yeah I planed some sseeing in
between and some more
um uh Christmas markets and I also
wanted to go ice skating as
well um but this was another snowy
really cold ass
day
and
so let me tell you with we're not able
to do everything oh
oopsie that I wanted to
do
but at least I
tried we
first uh on this day we were sting
Vienna first day s book second day
Vienna was doing Naruto
run and I I uh uh met up with her kind
of
like not in the city center but in the
outskirts and uh there's a there's a
place that's called uh
gloriette no wait not GL
yet wa I always mistake those
two wait wait wait wait wait wait I'm so
confused let me look it up I wrote it
down
ah maybe it was so
confused we find it
again ah there's a there's a big big uh
cast Castle Palace sh Bor Palace and
then no it wasn't glor yet if you uh
walk up like a big
hill you
reach something it's called a glor yet
it's like a kind of looks like a palace
but like a really Slim narrow version of
it and there's a cafe inside and anyway
it looks really impressive and up there
you get a beautiful view of Vienna so I
wanted to do that while it was so bright
we did that first thing in the
morning and this is time for this one I
didn't have a reservation but we had
like a maybe a 15 20 minute waiting time
to get into the into the cafe and I
think I was able to really impress Nai
with that Cafe cuz it's so fancy like
dining in a palace I already saw this
one this is no surprise to me
namona the rare dun spars oh did it have
more like um parts of its body than the
other ones yeah I don't care oh my gosh
look at all these huge gorgeous crystals
they go all the way to the
bottom oh the talization crystals
huh
SP only a two segment oh
okay one slip and we can kiss our short
lives goodbye yeah don't slip oh good
call what's your
step so the professor's down there
somewhere waiting for
us that's fine toally fun when you're
not really
fun all right team what your and let's
get to the bottom of this thing hell
yeah this place looks unreal maybe there
really is a treasure down there like the
stories
say wouldn't get my hopes up but we can
check it out yeah this place like
something from a whole other world makes
you feel like maybe you already died and
went
somewhere is just me or do the crystals
here give off the same glow as when the
Pokemon teriz there's got to be some
sort of connection smart girl only one
way to find out come on everybody let's
keep moving we've got all the way to go
down do a
flip maybe the real Treasures the EST
stranged mothers we've rescued along the
way I should not be really coming
H don't
care yeah you need to look it up guys
Vienna gloriette and then you know what
I'm talking about it's so pretty on the
outside and on the inside so inside we
kind of got like
breakfast AKA late breakfast AKA brunch
AKA
lunch and I I ordered us some yummy
Austrian dessert I thought this is the
time to order it oh
interesting so I got a
Ka one of my favorite Austrian
desserts and another one oh what was the
other one something with lots of vanilla
sauce never Austrian dessert we so good
and then we shared it and also I made
her drink
oh the Austrian
herbs soft drink pissy soft drink now
what's funny here was that we were we
were
seated next
to two other what why say other but two
Japanese people I'm saying other I guess
because me and Nai always communicate in
Japanese so we sit down next to these
other Japanese
people and we look at each other and
they're
like k
it's kind of awkward because you know we
could hear each other's conversations a
little bit oh came to our age through
the time machine then it lived here a
while with the professor along with
another one of its
kind that seems to be the
story so we brought it back home kind of
or to it second home at
least I guess this place should be
familiar to it
sure oh that's great a chance to unwind
and but ask into familiarity that
doesn't exactly jive with how it's been
acting all spooked since we got here
doesn't seem eager to come out out of
its ball anytime soon either really I
thought it was just scared CU we were so
high
up who said it was scared of heights
yeah yeah it wasn't that we've already
climbed plenty of mountains so even how
K was acting early I think something bad
happened down
here
oh maybe maybe the other C don't died
was the same for me when I was ignored
by everyone in class just thinking about
school made me want to hide away in
somewhere I saw I know how it
feels a
penny so maybe we got hurt down here in
area zero just like
aive can't know for sure but it doesn't
change in in into its battle form
anymore right so I think it's
possible that that's so sad we got to do
something to make it feel better I
already gave it so many sandwiches what
do you
want I'm not just saying that cuz I
super badly when a battle C out on
myself wait where am I supposed to
go jump down there no it's that way
right okay and another sandwich yeah
there's more sandwiches sandwiches will
do the trick surely Merry Christmas D
thank you to you too
oh
that's
the prevolution
oh yeah yeah so actually I felt really
social there
so I we had a conversation actually when
nappi went to the restroom I chatted a
lot with the other
Japanese women that was s sitting next
to
us that was
nice
that was nice but apparently they
weren't even tourists they were like
studying something
here so I was going to recommend them
the o d drink but they said oh I already
had it many times yeah yeah we know we
know oh okay but they were really
interested in why we were speaking
Japanese to each other because Navan is
Korean and I'm Austrian and yet we're
talking Japanese to each
other yeah it is it do be a little bit
weird but uh
I I told na her English improved and see
she she said she said that on this day
she wants to speak English but then we
ended up still speaking Japanese all the
time
oopsie there were a lot of Japanese
people on that day I met I saw so many
or like I heard so
many they're
everywhere
all right I know I have to enter there
but let me go down there first
for can't escape them they're back doing
tourist stuff touristy things I
guess
oh oh they forced me to go back okay I
guess that's spoiler alert okay okay
okay okay okay back up
right no wa this
way why did they teleport me over here I
was like all the way over there no oh
it's going down there they could have
just teleported me to go back right in
front of the
door maybe they thought I fell down from
up there or
so well that's we
the
that looks like an ice version of itself
but no in this light it looks normal
again
okay not shiny yeah not shiny oh this
one's
up oh what happened this place is a
mess it looks like something went
berserk in here yeah but
what hello
children go Prof fessa you scared us I'm
sorry why is everything in here all
busted
up I'm sorry hello CH that's so spooky
the camera moved come again I'm sorry
s she a
computer hello
chill is she a
computer is Arvin also
computer
what's happening hello hello I'm sorry
my children hello what the heck she's
bogging out stop that you're creeping us
out hello child children children
children
PR initiating restart what the
I thought she was oaba woman but
she's a computer woman robot
woman the professor must be having some
weird connection problems or something
huh no no no no no no no no no
no well it was definitely weird at least
almost like I don't
know if she meant it as a joke it wasn't
funny I still got goosebumps and all
yeah that was
freaky what the maybe she was being
controlled by a
ROM uh wait maybe let me read the books
first I need more people more time that
man walked out not long after the boy
was
born I need enough set of
hands but could they be trusted and how
long would it take them to even
understand if only there were two of
me that man interesting how she calls
the man that she conceived her son
with that
man and uh could it be that she um since
she says it would have been nice if
there was two of her she cloned herself
and that was that robot speaking just
now my new assist is intellect and
technical skills survival my own yeah
cuz it's you somehow a bit rigid at
times but I've got no serious complaints
productivity has doubled we even brought
in a second quem via the machine though
this one has proved aggressive
oh c hanger cuz I got to go to an idol
meeting
cliffhanger
see you in a
[Music]
second
for
I left you with a nice face on
purpose I got some chocolate snack
called the
hitos from a snack book
still have some left
over who is e
those let me pour some more
tea yeah chocolate it's like chocolate
waivers
sure pH are we close to the end I wonder
like going down here I guess I could
have maybe that it a little bit faster
if I wasn't streaming but I have to read
everything and also I have to tangent
I've been waiting so long to tangent
about my na Chan
visitation this feels like the big ruler
yeah you're
right okay who just let me get like one
or two
bites what does that mean who
isos who
isos
yum yum little
bones of course I washed my
hands why you questioning it
what's going to happen
[Music]
N I need I need an
animation a cut scene of her really
slowly going down with her finger on the
button really slowly pushing it and then
everything
exploding
dramatically ah she just pushes it
normally she doesn't understand man
content content entertainment value
girl she doesn't get it she just doesn't
get
it
mhm when said
hello
hello can you hear me
now please forgive my previous
transmission there seems to be some
signal interference
mhm it's all normal now totally normal
don't tell
her that's not what that was yeah that
was different that was very different
there was a difference between uh a
shitty Wi-Fi connection and you being a
robot in
Disguise what do you
mean the locks have all been disabled at
last please make your way now to the
zero lab which lies at the very bottom
of area
zero nothing excited H exciting happened
when I pushed the
button what is this by the
way oh ah okay another
teleportation
okay guess I I'll heal Sparks
oh ah could have just rested in the bed
oopsie oh
well this way probably
faster
okay that one now definitely something a
about the presses now right
mhm dramatic FL own jazz neona is so
naive
are you guys reading it you guys got to
read it yourself
now bed do PP too I didn't fight that
much
though I'll be
fine
yeah I saw the thing oh what is
this what is
that it's trying to censor it it's
trying to stop me from reading
it what the
[Music]
let me read
it I need to know the truth can't hide
it from
[Music]
me well love we can be sure you can you
can type then you can
read what is
this
no leave me alone is this like a
dragon I don't want to fight
[Music]
you yeah I know I guess I can't read it
oh
well Dark terce
[Music]
Shard oh yeah then after the cafe where
we ate a lot of yummy
stuff and and looked at the beautiful
view we walked down we walked this time
down walking down was way easier like
when we were walking up I was losing my
breath it's really exhausting it's a
long path to go up but we walked up like
from like kind of the outside cuz I
didn't want
her like to have to have the reaction
spoilered I wanted her to only see the
view once we're
up so we kind of went up on a side
street h M it was all all planned all
according to
Kaku
[Music]
and yeah going down was fine though and
then
uh I was originally hoping to get like a
little tour inside that Palace but the
times are set in there and there weren't
many times lot so I couldn't do it
because of the time schedule that I
created M yeah so from there where did
we go from
there I think from there we kind of uh
cuz it already like took so much time
more than expected I already had to
change my schedule a little bit and
cancel some things so we went straight
to lunch I think after
that and lunch was really good we were
there early but they still let us in
early it was really empty
actually and um it was nice it was cozy
and very austan looking and I made it so
that we ordered two different austan
things and then we share like we eat
half of each uh meals and then we switch
so that Nai can get as much different
experiences of Austrian cuisine as
possible very smart so I ordered a
schnitzel and AOS Braton schnitzel you
know what schnitzel is but maybe you
don't know it's um I think it's beef uh
or is it it's
pork no I don't know which one it was
but it's basically with a lot of
onions roasted
uh and then some like onion kind of
sauce how do I describe
sweet roast be with onions maybe
something like
that M it's one of my brother's favorite
dishes my mom used to make it for my
brother a lot when we were
younger it's really good I guess it was
beef yeah it's really really good the
onions are
M
superb and the Schnitzel with lots of
extra lingonberry jam and and and
parsley butter potatoes although I had
to say that the parsley butter potatoes
that my mom makes or that I make even
were a bit better I think those weren't
that impressive I think but I love
potatoes so
whatever lingo Berry Jam Yum Yum Yum
Yum so yeah I had some cozy lunch there
let me look up with it's been so long
already I don't remember any of
this uh
oh actually yeah one thing I forgot to
say for breakfast you know she was so
much craving for some uh cup Ramen she
was trying to find
a did I go in there can I trying to find
an Asian
store uh close by that would sell her
cup Ramen for
breakfast she was so so desperate for it
and she was like well if they don't have
cup Ramen then I don't want anything
else
I won I W eat breakfast at
all so she ended up having no breakfast
cuz she couldn't find cup
Ramen instant noodles for breakfast yeah
but it seems to be quite normal in
Korea she had withdrawals yeah I think
so have we reached the final deepest
part who made it ready to save those
Legends of treasure down here for real
yeah right that's just fluffly right to
fill in the
textbooks hello children you've done
well to make it here oh she speaks
normal again the structure you see
before you is at zero lab that's what
you are right
Professor but wait why does it look like
the whole place is being swallowed up by
crystals I guess you could take it as
that the crystals here and arader
possess a peculiar
energy this energy can alter the
functions of living things and optimize
the performance of Machinery it is the
same energy that allows Pokmon ter to
terize so this entire building has been
terized is that what you're
saying don't be silly
Arin the professor implied something
important about Terror just now they're
made from the crystals down in area zero
aren't
they well indeed not though not many
know
it since you have disabled all four
locks the gate to the zero lap should
now open for you but once you open the
gate you will quickly be confronted with
dangerous Pokmon
inside they will likely make a break for
Freedom that sounds like a problem
with the four of you working together
you should be able to wait are you going
to do like in the in the in the in the
in the in the camp battles again where
we just throw out our Pokemon
nah prepare yourselves well then open
the gate okay okay Like A Boss Rush like
a team star no okay you've got me and
Kiwa here doesn't matter what we're up
against we'll be
fine H well then that puts all my
worries to rest
really series of dual battles
okay time to save
okay really that
dangerous I'll just sweep through
it I'll just sweep right through it oh
there's your Pok ball over there I have
have to go
there first things first
no I can't help
it I'm already like probably missing out
on a lot of things like over there
there's probably
something it's hard to just ignore
it ah where's the door oh here sorry I
was looking at my notes should I press
this thing here
open the gates to the zero lab hell yeah
let's do
it come at me ancient Pokmon hold
it all we're fining on the cust of
getting into the lab look if it's true
that a bunch of really dangerous Pokemon
come at us and shouldn't we also have
Cordon help oh yeah but it doesn't want
it's don't
strike maybe with a sandwich we could
get it out
I want to see the battle oh but it
hasn't even wanted to let us ride it
ever since we came down to area zero and
it can't enter it B enter its battle
form in the first place well it's really
strong I know it is I know those mystica
we found too and it really matters I'm
sure it'll fight oh yeah like
a like one of these really dramatic
moments when suddenly someone really
powerful comes to the rescue in movies
or anime yeah yeah yeah yeah that will
happen surely
an ARA zero is where it used to live oh
you're so glowy dude you're glowing are
you
pregante if you bring it out of its ball
now maybe it will be able to find its
family too
right that's pretty that's pretty
sensible by your
standard I don't
know go on I don't I guess we'll force
it wait I should have said no again
yeah what the
let me translate for you all right
come on Ki now that we've got coron
ready it's time to open that gate okay
well let's hope coron won't disappoint
[Music]
us why is that in free
wait oh I was like why is our a up here
now but
oh oh oh it's bigger than ours
isn't it oh because it's in its battle
form a family reunit is happening oh
guys guys it's not like that probably
well no
way nope uh-uh a a happy reunion it's a
the evil
copy wait it's lagging so bad the the
sound
is
O why does the cut scene have
lag
the sound is way earlier than the
video I might need to restart the
game okay wait I I saved right before
right do you want to like rewatch that
without lag
maybe let's rewatch
[Music]
it I did save I did I did I did chill
did and even if it didn't work that time
it definitely had like auto save
somewhere I did I want to rewatch that
cut scene
properly I did I think before I picked
up the item
[Music]
though yeah okay item still there should
I get it again I guess I'm getting it
again m
I think after the lunch I think I
brought us to the Stefan D which is
interesting cuz I've never been inside
the Stefan do before it's like a famous
Cathedral that we have here in
Vienna I think it's our biggest
cathedral in Austria possibly and I just
thought I never thought about going
inside cuz I thought it would just be
like a normal cathedal I guess but the
inside holy it was crazy
you can go inside for free by the way
and
damn it look there's always lag in the
cut scene really oh well okay that's
sad but yeah it was
insane you can probably find pictures
from inside
but the inside was like wow I I I'm I
felt
like I was in a different
world that was one of the prettiest
structures I've seen in terms of like
churches and Cathedrals and so
on so we looked at that for a while we
walked around slowly and uh there's like
part of it you if you want to enter it
you have to pay we just looked at the
free areas but that was
enough I never had like in the cut scene
been because I play this game in
handheld mode uhhuh I see
oh we will see in a
moment and then right next to the um
Cathedral there was another Christmas
Market there's like Christmas markets
freaking everywhere in all the hot spots
at least there was also one up there at
the uh at the pal no not really up there
that was just just like just like one
tiny stall but then down there at the
palace it was also a Christmas Market
the big one that I wanted to go to
originally with her but time wise we
couldn't make it so I have to cancel it
H yeah but yeah we went to the Christmas
Market through the whole Christmas
Market at the at
the uh Cathedral and Nai Chan bought
herself a nice
sausage yeah like a dry sausage that she
consumed later in the
day guess she really thought that looked
yummy and uh and then also oh yeah uh I
saw some some Li uh what was that again
gingerbread some really classic nice
gingerbread so I told her that this is
this is typically like Christmasy here
like winter season snack not too sweet
you might like it so uh we got some of
that for her too she liked both of it
both the sausage and the and the uh
Ginger
bread did we buy anything else I got
myself like a
hot uh alcohol-free of course again mold
wine is it lagging again the door lagged
for
sure oh that was on time that sound was
on time at least that was on time
too yeah a they look
laggy what no way oh
step
oh oh yes better I
think oh wait oh now it's not it's
gone it's gone
again
okay was a bit better than before I
think but
still
H oops he spoke too soon oh well I I I
gave you I gave you an opportunity to
better
yourself you didn't want to have it you
didn't take
it huh what's
wrong are you bummed at your heart
Waring family reunion got caught off so
quickly you guys not get
it
are you
joking there was nothing hard roing
about thank God penny is
here that we were this close to getting
caught up in a nasty braw wait for real
oh my God why am I around these
people just look at just look at K poor
things terrified guess that other one
isn't exactly as pal yeah I thought
Pokmon was giving us some real bad
vibes not that you should worry a thing
about any of that once we get you back
into your battle form I'm sure you'll be
going Toe to Toe against that jerk if
you know if you want
to come on do it transform we need
another sandwich huh we need another
sandwich anyone bring a
sandwich I didn't do you think that
aidon was one of the dangerous Pokemon
that Professor W us to watch out
for they're all pennies principal flame
so true well didn't the professor say
the dangerous Pokmon would come out
from
inside you mean from inside the gate we
just oh wait that one looks like some
cake the one in the
middle you see how I see it as some cake
with like mint frosting and chocolate
and yeah yeah looks like a mint
chocolate
cake aose
cake you see it you not the only
one oh that's the other ones we've seen
before oh that doesn't look like a cake
anymore that's it only free what oh my
God that's
it that's all you got fre
Pokmon
oh wait there's more they're all the
same byy a lot of yummy cakes pretty
obvious they're not here to roll out of
friendly welome
M there's no way we can handle as many I
don't worryed unless maybe now Kur on
dramatic
transformation we got a little disaster
in our hands
here come on miracle time baby look even
that fellow's ready to play you I guess
it's my turn I've been
waiting
I no problem no
[Music]
problem true NAA that's a good
argument it's supposed to be an ancient
Pokemon and yet it has the Pokeball the
even the modern Pokeball
design this is supposedly more ancient
than Pokmon Aras
no cuz this Pokemon weren't in our
either
questioning questioning the logic is is
illegal
forun wish the camera was like different
I want to go further but I don't want to
go
up I want to go further back and see
everything I want to see it from the
side but see everything but I can't do
that oh
[Music]
well 10 five with the invent of the Pok
ball
ah I like like the amongus design so
much he based off of that where's that
Lord
from where do that come from Moran
ohas wow they're strong now this is a
worthwhile
challenge I'm glad you're on outside but
you're still really annoying when you
say stuff like
that go coming at me you help me out
here I want to fight next to that other
chick please help
K our is set 100 years
ago I just want to clean my
throat once and for
all Brute
Bonet
brute
hold
wait someone heal my Sparks
PP wasn't 10 just a second
ago one HP
come on Umbreon I paved the way for you
perfect I get Auto
healed I I didn't even notice not at
all very kind as if these battles were a
big big challenge for me the ancient
past must have been
terrifying oh chill chill
a screamed them away
and those Pokmon get out we're going to
have a g gigantic
gigantic mess on our hands we got to go
after them Penny what
me
[Music]
wait hold on Lona and why do I get the
family enjoying all this oh okay so
they're leaving to take care of that
H at least the crowds would F out now
guess it's up to us to deal with what's
left okay okay let's take up on this one
no problemo one Shadow balling is
dead easy easy
easy I don't remember all the places we
went to anymore besides the Cal actually
I think it really it really wasn't that
much cuz then we were freezing our butts
off again and uh I think after the
[Music]
cathedral I think we basically called it
a day pretty much I mean we were
planning to see some more but then we
kind of you know fell
asleep that happened falling asleep
while watching RI and morning and did
you go ice sking at the I wanted to do
that I was planning on doing that cuz
it's really pretty there and it's not a
normal ice skating ring it's like so
many paths intertwined and so on I
wanted to see that but
I don't know especially after first
after the first day we when we were
freezing our butts off I don't know I
just I had enough of it and naban didn't
seem to really be that motivated to go
outside into the cold
again uh um
so totally accidentally fell asleep also
naan before we fell asleep snacked on
the the sausage and the the uh
gingerbread
M
and I was an absolute
genius naian actually said that
she uh you know we we still had some
time to kill after we woke up from the
nap and we decided to just go to dinner
after that naan was like I I want to I
want to do K and I said
well I don't know how we would do that
but wait now turn I'm going to try my
best to make your dream come true so I
took my
laptop and I I logged into
the uh my cuton account that I have for
work
basically a big
friend didn't have any microphones or so
but yeah basically with my laptop and
and
uh uh kind of fun we we did a little
Koka session we sang like some K-pop
songs and a Christmas
song I think she wanted me to sing uh
that was this this one Christmasy song
from what's her
[Music]
name Adele maybe I think it was from
Adele We sang that
together and uh
a black pink song because she really
likes black pink we tried at
least there's a Christmas song from
Adele I thought it was a d maybe it was
someone else
similar sounds like I really gave her a
good time yeah I wanted to show her more
overall
though but then after that and know we
were kind of late actually so we hurried
to the
dinner yeah and dinner was
amazing dinner was really good sorry
what's going on yeah okay we're going to
have a fight
okay din is really yummy um again I
ordered like two things that we could
then switch
out uh I had uh some special Austrian
gulash
and what did what did naby have
ah no
way wait
no oh yes we ordered cheese sp sp the
ones that I cooked
before sorry H it's not like seeing you
cing and scared out of your wits makes
me feel any better about it
you've got amazing Powers if you just
use them and you've got us too so so you
don't even think about losing to that
jerk be brave set up and
fight is it going to do it
now what no transformation
yet oh he wants me to go in
alone dude it's your mom though it's
your
mom
really I have to deal with your
mom come
on ooh that's
weird I saw
heraa
woman who she
is come
on
human presence detected within the zero
lab is she
okay she doesn't look quite
okay
hello
creepy deactivating sleep mode
the
hello Kiwa thank you for
coming bro XD is it
mine you didn't show me that you didn't
even show me that oh no it's not mine no
back to your
ball what that one his far should I give
her a verbot voice now it would be good
if the game had voice acting right now
because then I would know the current
state I guess she talks normal right now
that one is far less distractable and
far more aggressive than the one you've
traveled
with yo could I on fled area zero
because it lost to the other one in a
territorial
struggle I'm afraid that there's
something for which I must apologize I
am not that true Professor
s then who are
you I am an artificial intelligence the
professor created imbued with her
memories and knowledge insured I am an
AI powered
robot the real Professor passed away
during the incident that destroyed
research station number
four and you did not care to tell your
freaking son about about the
passing of
your of the
mother wow
wow pass
away the Pokmon was not to be blamed it
was the original Professor who failed to
accurately accurately judge its full
power I believe the professor wanted
nothing more than for the coridon to
survive and thrive that is why she threw
her myself in front of your cidon in an
attempt to protect
it from the time I first reached out to
director clavel and asked to be put in
contact with you I was never more than
an
AI what a
bamboozle what a big bamboozle wa does
he know or does he not
know Ki the reason I asked you to come
to me is because I have one last thing
to do here at the zero lab and I desire
your help in short I wish for you to put
a stop to The Time Machine the original
Professor
created any questions can be addressed
as we make our descent follow
me he doesn't know he knew but he didn't
have
[Music]
proof so he was like susing
her it might be the case but not sure I
don't want to believe it because she
mom mommy mommy can't possibly be AI
everything's being replaced by
AI is that for
kuron oh is that no is it Terra
Chris's okay let's
go this elevator will take us down to
the lower level step
inside not for
on a for ancient Pokemon
ah kiala it trly is a great relief to me
that you came I will answer any
questions I like how you change your
name to AI Sal now is there anything you
wish to know what is an AI really an i
is a artificial intelligence created by
a human being the computer draws on the
original professor's knowledge and
memories to calculate all of my thoughts
and actions this is the future guys I
already have so many AI
things already
and
one can dis like have a long discussion
about whether or not it's been doing
positive or negative things a lot of
things are doing positive things surely
but then there's also AI that are not
very
helpful but this this might be the
future guys an AI
mom is that what you
want is that what you want is that what
you want so tell me what you want what
you really really want I'll tell you
what want what I really want I want to I
want I want I want to really really
really want really real
mom I want a real mom not an AI
mom you don't want an AI girlfriend or
boyfriend do
you want a real girlfriend
boyfriend no I'm not
AI I'm not a
robot no I'm
real the results of those calculations
are expressed by this mechanical B body
built to resemble the professor in every
way Humanity does not in fact possess
the knowledge to develop such a
sophisticated AI at present but the
crystals that make up the zerol lab have
made such a thing possible they are also
why I cannot leave this place oh is
there anything else you wish to
ask what happened to real professor as I
explained to you before the original
Professor no longer exists during the
distruction of the research station her
physical body received Grievous injuries
that left it unable to sustain life I'm
afraid that this fact may be difficult
for her son Arin to accept
o i now managed at Zera lab in the
original professor's place is there
anything else you wish to
ask H time machine is a device that the
original professor and I worked on
together it sends pokeballs to a
different point on the timeline to catch
Pokmon there and it can then draw them
back here to the present when she was
alive Prof Professor Sada had a great
fascination with Pokmon from another
age what you might call ancient Pokmon
even as we speak the time machine
continues to automatically draw Ancient
Pokmon to this
time so tell me what you want what you
really really
want naris what the
the original Professor had a dream of a
world in which ancient Pokmon might
live alongside present day Pokmon in
harmony why do we have to force that
though
why why do we have to like rip them from
their own timeline and insert them
here just scientists trying to force
everything for whatever
reason
what do you mean happy copy of course I
would help it of course I would flip it
over keep reading H but these Pokemon's
Powers seem to stem I was going to keep
reading anyway seem to stem from a
praval energy of the ancient past and
this energy has proved too
terrible their very existence brings
destruction to the ecological balance of
this Modern Age
the original Professor would say that
such such destruction is a natural part
of life at the present the barrier
around area zero is still working to
keep the ancient Pokemon from escaping
into the rest of Pia but we've begun to
see Pokemon appear that can break the
barrier such as great
Tusk eventually they will break free of
this wall Garden known as area zero and
run rampant across the POA region and
when they do the rich and varied ecosyst
of Pia will be trampled beneath their
coming I may have been created as a copy
of the professor and yet I cannot seem
to find the logic in allowing such a
tragedy to
occur but any hope of preventing it
would require overcoming the greatest AI
that the original Professor ever
devised kiaha you have become a
formidable trainer now use that strength
you have gained to
destroy the dream Sada once cherished
no this task cannot be done without your
strength you 13-year-old random child in
this story you are the one you are the
chosen one I beg
you we're already here so you got to do
it
girl whether you want it or
not wow it's like inside swarovski's
store Swarovski has like a place like
this I think somewhere in
Austria I've never been there but I
think it's like close to sou
sburg what the why is it like
this why stop doing that okay like a
Swarovski Swarovski world something like
that apparently you're not allowed to uh
take pictures though really lame
behold this is the time machine we
perfected using the power of teral
phenomenon now
saving wow
shiny
hypnotizing
nice good job
kiaha who the built this this is
not something people
built it was of course randomly
generated
naturally W okay thanks for the
pinky yeah you took took a break test
for this why to stop the time machine
you will need to use the professor's ID
which has been embedded within the
Scarlet book
oh it was very like the professor to put
the final key we would need in that book
of all places she loved that volume
since
childhood if you place a Scarlet book
upon the pedestal here you will be able
to stop the time
machine there's just one issue if you
try to stop the machine I will most
likely attack
you thanks for the
notice good to
knowk thanks for letting me
know son a fret oh no AI is going to
destroy us after all artificial being
that I am my own desires can be
overridden by the systems
programing once that happens I'm afraid
I will become no more than a battle
machine bound to defeat anyone
identified as an obstacle by my
Cod I don't know what to say about the
story I don't know man my battling
abilities are Peerless they are built
upon analysis of all the battles carried
out by the various champions of the paa
region having seen the bond between you
and your Pokmon however I believe you
can
Prevail once you have Reed yourself for
this fight please place the Scarlet book
upon the pedestal
pedestal paddle
stool okay
how ID confirmed Professor s initiating
emergency shutdown please wait please
wait
access denied oh
no it's gold now oh look at
her she going to have like red eyes or
so oh AI s switching to sleep mode
activating offensive
[Music]
protocols please defeat
me
and at a
last at Le my dream is within reach that
Pokeball looks
like something Wario Wario would own for
her
eyes let's
go the
master
creepy so creepy keep
a iada has initiated the
battle way she dropped it oh it's the
the fire Mo
thingy I'm also
[Music]
fire I don't know who you think you are
but I'm not about to let anyone get in
the way of my
goals C
Wing fire this unfor Al I think I'll
have to switch that thing maybe into
Dum
vibing
oh what was
that this is the power the ancient
bholes Splendid isn't it five
spendid she's speaking in lead
Speak doesn't seem to have anything good
against
D it's not fire it oh wait it's bug
fighting then fire would have been fine
right
F oh
sh not the same Pokemon well would any
of these help or should I
switch I you switch it I didn't know
that it's
bug you know that's hyping it doesn't
look God damn it all right I guess we're
going back
want
[Music]
waste H
nice all right maybe we can sweep a
little bit at least
for uh 10
levels 11 levels
above now this is interesting child do
you actually understand a an Pokemon
Pokemon's
weakness yeah a little bit not really I
mean not
really H what brute foret ah which one
was that we fought that already which
one was
it which one was that not the mischevous
one
right ah the amongus one okay okay
[Music]
I can deal with that I
think let's um boost one more
time probably a one
any hell
[Music]
yeah
Sandy
shocks ground Pokemon I would
assume I don't know if I met this one
before
though oh wait electric s ground
electric maybe whatever would be
effective against that I do not know
maybe
Casper assuming it's ground Electric
maybe bullet seat or ice ice okay
okay ah I was bued enough to take it
yeah maybe I should stay I should
[Applause]
stay oh wow we want to see more than one
Pokemon
right okay no I have not seen this one
before that was
funny the
legs
power
gem W it's got legs now do you imagine
you can beat be best the wealth of the
what just hard to read girl how are you
doing this in Japanese I wonder and like
other other languages with other writing
systems scream tail what the is
that
I'll say I'll just look at what it
is Ah that's I forgot about it at
least we know the typing already and I'm
you got some
Hammer Shadow
Ball how about we bring a bnk
then want to see some bunk
action
apparently in Japanese it might have
just been normal
[Music]
Katakana Katakana that makes sense I
guess because kakana usually is used in
Japanese for English words but also when
someone speaks like a robot or speaks
like they're not good at their language
what some sort of error has occurred
here recalculating for critical Dage
damage in Karine she speaks normally
what I guess you guys don't have
something comparable to
Katakana SL man was that the mous
one was
it I
think does he know it was
fluttering okay then ghost will be open
K we should have brought Arin here he
should be seeing
this I mean it might be a bit
traumatizing but you know don't you want
to know the truth about your mom holy
yeah ghost versus
Ghost myow ball is
stronger yeah
yeah thank you thank you
bom roaring Moon oh I don't think we've
seen that one
either Moon psychic maybe something like
that well I'll stay in I'll see what
wait my HP is really low though
everything is proceeding with my
expectations I'm afraid the probability
of you winning is zero what the
expectation was that I'll take all your
Pokmon down except
one a I've seen the original form of
that before somewhere but it looks
really
cool looks really
cool uh that's probably Dragon
right probably Dragon maybe dragon
flying or
so but I don't know I'm going to test it
out probably we got to
teriz probably going to
teriz that's just um no but I'll
die I'll
die if it hits me
again if it's Dragon then frog still but
he's already damaged a little bit
Also let's give it
try
ooh that wasn't even super
effective am I
faster probably
not
I'm going to actually try glaive
rush I W it I W it I W it let's go I
would have died one
hit let's
go I she didn't
thiz she did oh no take a picture for
Arvin take a picture p p p p here's your
dad dead AI mom
Arvin I killed your mom I'm going to
come out and say Arvin I'm sorry I
killed your mom but don't worry it was
your AI
Mom oh
man he's here oh K
kiaha the is going
on what what is
this you already beat all the bades
without
me okay out of it you who are you
really you see how she's
twitching maybe the teacher the history
teacher was also a
robot
malfunctioning cuz she was also lowkey
to switching her hair she was still
holding it back as much as she
could by the time we go back to the
school she might have
already escalated and be in the middle
of taking over to school oh no I'm the
save to school it's a robot take
over she's a twitch
bot that's why she's obsessed with
history
who are you
really thank you for everything
a oh man he never got to say goodbye to
his mom did
he time machine has finally she has
finally been stopped B
stopped you're really not my mom are
you oh look how big you've grown oh
a so proud of you
my sorry you were alone for so
long
Mom oh they got so many colors here
you
RGB Security System
Failure threats to time machine
detected who who what's going on
now there's another Army of Pokmon on
the way
here it cannot
be an obstacle is preventing time
machine from performing as intended who
is talking activating Paradise
protection protocol to remove the
offending obstacle what what's keeping
the time machine running truly all the
professor cared about locking all
Pokballs except those registered to s's
ID but who will save us we all know it
I'm sorry
children you must
run alada
disabled Paradise protection protocol
enabled o scary Oh you's going to fight
again
y not
fair you are not getting in my way you
are challenged
but this
funny that is not a game bug even though
you may be confused cuz you're not sure
at this point but that was I think on
purpose ah no we got to get
AAS
AAS I can't
battle what do you mean I can't I know
obviously it's true our Pok BLS won't
work how are we even supposed to battle
fist fight fist fight fist
fight
run would put
that what about
us to be in danger too some crazy
electrical signal is
chaming what do you want me to
do that's solely chaing and you call
yourself an
adult no she's just an
AI here I'll push oh I can I can do some
healing and stuff but we're fully healed
I'll try to run
again coridon how do I get my
coridon
n i d
it didn't glow up before
right it's time
cidon I thought it would come out on its
own after some cutcenes
there it is let's go oh it's also in a
poke ball though weren't able to lock
this one
huh
awkward without
voices so quiet there we go
oh it's evolving or is
it would you call it an
[Music]
evolution what level will it be
oh all right another mirror
[Music]
match
sunlight opposing turn to sunlight
h b in
sunlight 6 I'm 68 I don't know it's
level though well 68 seems kind of low
okay we got flame perra Collision
Collision Collision Force Power 100
accuracy 100 endure endures any attack
of at least one HP there's no chance of
failing why do we have this and Terra
Blast I think I want to go with the I no
[Music]
fighting
this is taunting
me wa that's
cool the head
Wings it Chang this battle form let's go
ground you got
[Music]
this okay that didn't do so much damage
let's try flame
throw you will follow your within this
Garden Paradise and achieve nothing in
the end or sorry nothing
[Music]
yeah I guess it will bring me down
really like it's
purposefully too
strong so I have to I'm going to be
forced to use
endur you will not be allowed to destroy
my Paradise obstacles my gos will be
[Music]
eliminated we need another Evolution
this is not enough
or I can't I don't have the option to
terize right we have to
teriz looks like it could be bad no
totally not hang in there
Ki yeah okay it will probably eventually
Let Me
terize Wait I should have done the other
one the other one's
stronger he
back
ohshit tapped it out so I wouldn't feel
sad thank you could have died there well
now I have a problem so I'm assuming
that it makes no sense to heal myself up
you took that hit like a champ you can
do this I know you
can he did take it like a
champ all right I'll endure
it plock
armor I brace myself brace
[Music]
yourselves
can we really not pull off a wind here
this doesn't look
good hey Kaa your Terror ORS
glowing it doesn't
work I know it doesn't heal I was just
trying to
[Music]
survive can I heal
myself
all right I'll I'll do
it and then win ter it's
ass I can use up all my all my items now
show him you won't get pushed around
time to resize and get in some super
effective
hits oh it terzes into Dr agon makes a
lot of
sense let's
[Music]
[Applause]
go first time I use that attack I think
but I know it always oh becomes the the
the element of
whatever whatever um type your
terization go for ATT toiz I'm already
doing it I'm already doing it I'm faster
so this should do the trick
right don't die don't die there we
[Music]
go we did it
we showed it who's the
boss oh Mommy sorry
Mommy I defeated the paradise production
protocol the
pppp previously pick
property M
mommy
mommy you did
it it it's not not going to berserk
anymore
how how very astounding to think that
you would manage to defy even the
original professor's final
protections are you bre to
normal yes a completely unforeseen
outcome even for an II possessing the
most sophisticated technology ever
conceived even on the brink of Despair
you children did not give in and instead
proved your
worthiness she got a fancy lap code
now I would keep that not giv and
instead proof your Ence showing the
wisdom to think for yourselves the
courage to hold faith in your friends
and the fortitude to do what had to be
done no matter how difficult your own
pasts may have been I believe you will
be capable of walking whatever paths you
choose for yourselves now with
pride m
rovy La code yeah thank you Kiwa I thank
all of you
children but I'm afraid that the time
machine cannot be put to a complete stop
so long as I am
here it appears I myself am part of the
system that ensures the machine reboots
when
stopped what what is that
mean I am
sorry you know when I was watching you
all on your adventures from down here I
felt a sense of jealousy I envied you
your freedom the way that you came
together working in League with your
fellows and caring for them the way that
you sought strength and to better
yourself throwing all you are into your
battles the way that you would face down
even the greatest enemy to save that
which you loved the way that you never
cease to seek nor to fight for a
treasure on your
own
AA and the way that you sort free for
the very skies on those wings of yours I
wish that I too might be as free as you
all free to seek out that which I might
treasure above all else not
bound your own
treasure as long as I remain here the
time machine will not stop for I am
extric connected to it so I've made a
decision I will use the time machine to
Journey to the world of the ancient past
that I have dreamed
of you're leaving your son
behind you can't just leave now right
when we finally reached you I'm not
going only so that the time machine can
be stopped I also cannot deny my desire
to see the ancient world for myself
you're an AI this is what it feels like
to have your heart race but the FR of
Adventure do you even have a
heart Arvin I'm sorry that I kept the
truth from you for so long I inherited
all the thoughts and wishes of the
professor and so I understand better
than any your mother truly loved
you you you can't can't just go and say
a thing like that
now no I suppose you're right I'm
sorry Arvin could on K it is a little
sad but I'm afraid this is
goodbye
[Music]
Mom
sorry Farewell My Free
adventurous i b you ad
you
hole oh there's a copyrighted song in
the credits o
okay how could you just go
mom man that's so sad for
him Arvin you okay
bud he lost his
mom I was never aware of it can't even
like bury
her what happened to her body did the AI
eat her the hell somewhere deep down I
kind of already knew
it a some other members kept it well
that doesn't necessarily mean that it's
like
safe I knew that thing was fake but it
when it said my name using her voice and
wearing her face even if it was fake it
felt real you
know so I just
uh yeah guys don't get too this too
disillusioned with
AI those whole life member chat Bots
they're not
us sorry I don't know what I'm
saying uh that's okay real to me
[Music]
yes I guess Kon is that
too oh but the battle form how cool is
that so
[Music]
strong if it tries to nudge at me for a
belly rub while it's huge like this I
seriously think I'm going to
die hey now uh now
hey let's not es skipe over the big win
here Kiwa and cordons just saved all of
Pia that that's right you both did
amazing thanks
kiaha yeah that's my B kiaha for
you you know Ian even though the
professor's gone I bet she's finally
having a real fun adventure of her own
in the
past yeah thanks
Penny not really helping much I would
say yeah
sorry what should we do now K how about
we adopt Ain we'll be his mommy or my
mommy could adopt him my in-game
mommy let's go
home you said it come on everyone let's
make our way
home
[Music]
not hold
on a that's
pretty we're all
like so
[Music]
depressed okay everybody listen
up Let's Take the Long Road Home and get
a little more fun out of this
adventure I I don't really
sounds great if we can load up on snacks
first I'm in wait who said that I guess
Penny he why will not you
[Music]
too all right fine I guess we're doing
this oh man it's okay to be sad Arin
it's
okay is it a song I
know ah I'm muting that I sing for
[Music]
you I don't remember this so
well
[Music]
Celestial yeah
celesa
[Music]
celestial
wowow make me
feel so
cesal
[Laughter]
celest
[Music]
[Applause]
clap
I'll go on and on you make me
feel Toby
[Music]
fox make me
[Applause]
feel make me
feel
guar you make me
fail
[Music]
CES
C
[Music]
celestial
a lot of German names
there
[Music]
amazing done with the copyrighted music
I
think
amazing um that took way longer than
expected
I told my brother to come back at
midnight and that's soon so we have like
40 minutes to read some super chat but
tomorrow I'm planning on doing the sock
puppet Stream So that itself will
probably just take like an hour or two
so then I have a lot of time for super
chats
supposedly there's a little more of the
credits
on you forgot about Roary how can you
forgot about him
there's more
story
y
yeah what do you mean there's
more can I skip the credits I don't have
time there's a bunch of post game stuff
I can do I don't have to do okay maybe
I'll do it privately then thank you
treasured friends I mean there's a nice
cut scene now and we'll watch that but
oh it seems to be
finished
okay birtill is
freezing calling to the director's
office Miss Miss n and Mr master master
Orin and Miss penny D clav would like to
see you in his
[Music]
office okay guess we'll go to the
director's office should
we should
we I feel like this is still like part
of the
ending time to get expelled yeah for
going to the crater when they told me to
not
go it looks like the hero is finally oh
it seems like I'm a hero would you join
us miss
[Music]
Ki thank you
guys no no no no no even if others
streamed it this song surely has yeah I
can I can see how it would be dmca I
don't think it's just because it's Ed
sh just because something is dmca
doesn't mean that we have to take a
stream down or so um sometimes all all
that happens is just we share the
monetization income or whatever I think
um so just because the other streams are
still up doesn't mean that it's safe to
do but anyway you just heard a perfect
rendition of me that was one onone just
like the original so I might get DMC
anyway anyway we're in for an eful AR we
guess we'll find out soon enough no need
for concern you two I'm not angry in the
slightest I merely called you all here
to discuss your fine achievements in
this year's treasure
hunt you shut down the professor's time
machine and thus prevented the ancient
Pokemon from running ramp rampant across
Pia your actions were truly outstanding
in every regard and I couldn't be prder
of you all though your decision to enter
are strictly off limit's area was
admittedly
regrettable you got us
there however since this was necessary
to protect Pala and its precious
ecosystems I'm willing to overlook that
particular
point so we're not getting raged over
the colds after all oh before I forget
Miss kiaha there's something I would
like you to have each of your friends
has received one already so this is this
one is for you
a master ball h a fancy purple one looks
like how do does that not look like a
Mario but Wario ball a mix of a Mario
and Warrior ball because of the colors
also it kind of looks like a like that
Pokmon with the big the purple Pokmon
with the eyes
bluk doesn't stop
yeah another game beaten by the game so
true and claim the game thank
youi ah oh yeah that's the purple
[Music]
one and about the Hall of Fame Hall of
Fame bad I gave you a short while ago a
gift is one we bestow only upon students
who achieve truly remarkable Feats I
expect you to all know what that bad
represents by striving always to serve
as a model for your fellow
students I'm guess I'll
try oh well I suppose you must be rather
worn out from your recent
Adventures Master Arin I was so sorry to
hear about the professor you have my
deepest
[Music]
condolences uh well uh it was pretty
rough when I found out my mom had died
what weirdly enough my head actually
feels clear now for the first time in
ages in a great crate I got to learn a
bit about my mom's research and what she
was trying to achieve down there I guess
if you're building something is
mind-blowing as a time machine that
takes priority over showering your son
with attention huh all I know is I'm
done feeling like some lost little kid
done Time to Say Goodbye and move on I'm
going to enjoy every last day till
graduation with my buds here and my boss
of course
we say it Master Harvin you truly are
your mother's
[Music]
son so was she not an oaba woman
though
[Music]
confused they didn't come from the
past that's
unfortunate that's unfort but they what
the
H she's now H she is now she's just like
their
fashion just a cosplayer
cosplayer I see she was already oh no
that was supposed to give away the
ending she was already
dressed at the start of the game she was
already dressed in the accurate attire
to go to oaba land at the end of the
game she was ready back then and how how
did we not pick up on
that yeah return to Monkey of course I
must remind you that you've now nowhere
near enough credits to graduate you'll
need to study frantic cl to cat up but I
have every expectation of your success
what and let us not forget the other
good news our Academy as a new Champion
yay though we sadly cannot make your
Valiant deeds in the great crate unknown
to the
public your new Champion rank at least
should be celebrated throughout the
whole
school oh I know how we should celebrate
we should battle battle battle Yeah Yeah
Yeah Yeah batt batt seriously could we
not
same classic
Noona a Pokemon battle contest you say
while your own vested interest in such a
adventure a more than a parent Miss
neona I think it's a fine idea well
please understand that a large scale
event will be quite Beyond us with many
other school activities to keep an eye
on after
all got
[Music]
it
ah pretty hair
lady the Pokmon League will of course
happily land a hand in organizing this
contest well well most kind off for
chairwoman
gah I do everything in my power to
nurture young up and coming Talent
though that's not to say only the youth
have promise when it comes to Pokmon
battles a former gym leader the
developer of the Pokedex app this
Academy clearly counts many skill
trainers of Pokmon among its staff as
such my suggestion is as
follows students and staff should
compete for the title of strongest
trainer at the Academy oh wow we're
going to we're going to own those
trainers and those
teachers going to show them who should
be the real
teacher w we get to battle the teachers
you'd compete too right
pra is that even allowed the chair wom
is not part of the academy
right actually I think she's a
chairwoman of the school board as well
as the Pokmon League wait for real I
mean I knew she was on another
level thank you I am a workaholic so I
really just enjoy doing all these jobs
we're glad to take up your kind offer to
compete alongside you all but I'm afraid
my schedule is already packed tied with
work that I simply must attempt to
oh
no h can't you free up sometime somehow
I suppose I might be able to
participative Champion Ki would agree to
lend me a hand with my work or is that
post
game where should I
start excellent answer much obliged
Champion kilaa to get straight to it I
would like you to go out and inspect
Pia's various gyms in my stad are they
fulfilling their duties as beacons of
strength and inspiration for all those
aiming to achieve Champion rank no well
has there a Brilliance started to fade
yes the find out I ask you that you
bring your full might as Champion to
Bear against each of the gym leaders and
test your prowers in battle I already
did that they're all trainers of
exceptional Talent handpicked by me
personally does she not know is she
lacking critical
information I do not expect you'll find
any cracks in their armor but well
consider it a formality have to do it
again oh they'll be scaled they have
bigger
teams
who
[Music]
nice
uhhuh Larry dying inside oh no
Larry this will also provide the perfect
stage for your first appearance as a new
Champion since all the gym leaders will
still be expecting me to carry out the
inspection I imagine they'll have
mustered their full strength I dare say
they might be more of a challenge than
when you faced them before you got you
got to have an another battle with jus
man I'm
jealous no it's always me let's let's
have neona do it she's a champion too
now then onto another crucial matter I'd
like to discuss with Penny here how to
patch the weaknesses in our leag point
system uh but there's a bunch of anime
I missed it I was just going to bch
thank in advance for your willing and
ego
cooperation I'll do I'll help
him I heard some like go go go go go
sound excellent we'll leave you all to
it then come now
Penny oh
man
this is awesome k chsp b I can't talk
anymore my throat hurts man so much text
much Tex
[Music]
T reading it out loud is the exhausting
part enjoy thinking up swing at the
gym I filling out the
the
oh sir it's wonderful to see you all
showing such
initiative he's glowing you have a
critical role to play Penny assisting
the league our new Champion inspecting
gyms the Mona arranging the event give
it your best to
everyone guys my all so obvious it goes
without
saying kind of rude just got
ignored what is his
role mental
Court
Well I obviously don't have time to do
all of that now and since we I guess
officially finished the game I might
never do it on
stream h ah he'll make the sandwiches ah
that wasn't so obvious to
me but okay well yeah clap clap clap
game
finito
[Music]
um I'm not going to praise this game to
Heavens obviously there were many issues
um story was okay but I personally
preferred Pokemon
arus I remember being way more like
excited and happy with that
game both during it and also at the end
of
it
was fun overall yeah yeah every Pokemon
game is fun
overall
yeah I don't
know the end of of course the end was
epic
but
well oh no not really my thing I would
say do I have to read it
o I don't think I can rate this
game I don't think I can
[Music]
read I'm not going to rate this
game let's go read some super chats but
thank you guys for watching my Pokemon
Adventure
[Music]
moving over here oh my sock
puppers AR Story character game that's
is true that's like uh throughout the
whole
game
like the strongest part about the story
was Auburn's storyline saving his dog I
think every pet owner was touched by
that everyone's here which car is the
real one ah me it's me tomorrow if you
want to see these in motion a bit more
I'll I'll uh play a round of these talk
puppets I think I won't put up the
reservation until I wake up though but
yeah what's the sound is my brother
back Nan if you're here make a
sound no what was that sound
spooky oh wait it was the game it was
the the foot sounds in the game that I
heard cuz I still hear the
audio ah no Nan he's following my my my
only guy my request of not coming back
until midnight I I good brother okay uh
let me save the game here uh oh
would you like to save your adventure
yep and
then
okay I need some bgm for you
guys we only have like half an hour I'm
so sorry guys I really didn't think it
would take this long man no one f
it I'm your cat's favorite V to
what a why so cute meow meow meow
meow I love
kettles especially if they love
me okay audio
St
um I will try to go quickly through some
super chats but uh someone like the day
before yesterday or so sent me a
screenshot of the Super Chat that I
missed like a long time ago
um but can whoever sent that to me send
it to me again
now cuz
like oh yeah I think it was
JD on
Twitter I need a massage I think I'm
going to get a massage when I'm in
Japan at least I think in Japan they're
cheaper
is the Yen still so cheap guys by the
way like it was like months ago where
everyone was like go go change into Yen
now is it still like
that it is who oo actually still have a
lot of Yen though in cash so I was
thinking of just using
that it's improving but still bad oh for
f ticket super
cheap Mak stop right let me Che twit
someone wrote to
me uh oh wait I forgot
bgm I don't hear
it uh
we finished another big game
guys want to finish it before I got sick
but things happen glad I got to finish
it before going to
chapando
whoa wait
properties oh that's loud I'm sorry guys
what's the next big game I be playing uh
finem I
think probably Fire
Emblem should be coming out end of
January right or like what 20 20th or
something around that
time
oh show last bit of
tea
20 I'm probably going to start a few
days later but still within
[Music]
January
oopsy yeah M mama
B's Mama made the art for that the
concept art I guess or so Main Art so
cool cute
PGM yeah I'm finally getting used for
the Christmas BM again that I was that I
downloaded last
year okay okay let's see if we can get
somewhere with
this H the picture that GD sent to me is
that all of them or are there still some
below that I have to
read or or is that just
those within the
arrow all the characters from past Fire
Emblem titles look so good too yeah they
do a fire emblem character
exactly from that point on
downwards
I'm
confused is it just those or whatever is
below as
well
cheating all of them well that doesn't
really answer my question I don't get
[Music]
it everything below as well
okay which stream is this w
what happened
my how much did I spill my whole PC mat
thing is
wet
okay whatever
[Music]
um the previous Pokemon
stream
give me a
second it's been a
while
[Music]
uh that one or is it that
one should
be a whole table is wet that's I guess
what you have these Mets for so that
they can so it
up no no not the spit
[Music]
C no no no I would be screaming if that
happened I I think I have the wrong one
cuz it Doesn't find Luna
Mor was it part five or part
four maybe that one Luna Mo okay that's
probably it
yeah okay okay here we
go scw oh wait I should put the
thumbnail
up so we know where the hell we
are um part four next
[Music]
one
uh hi since my birthday today could I
get an employee number also I don't know
when you'll be able to R but if you're
in ja B already almost almost fight
screw how did you how did you know it
would take me this long if I wouldn't
have gotten sick it would have never to
taken me that long so maybe maybe you
knew I was going to get
sick if you're in Japan already I hope
you're having a great time of collabing
with your sis and that everything is
going smoothly fried
scr happy belated
birthday I'm sorry it's so late I got a
feeling I also thought you would never
read no no no no no I'm sorry I'm sorry
I lost track of it but I wouldn't skip
it on
purpose thank you for sending the red
super chat for your support for a long
long time and I hope you had a lovely
birthday day time traveler confirmed
yeah you may be
a you may be a time traveler but your
title just says you're an R&D engineer
just a disguise maybe maybe just a
disguise but you want a number how
about
26 one
two you like that
number
[Music]
no particular
reason don't think that one is taken yet
looks
familiar no way no no no no no the date
is written 12
26 2022 no that's how you crazy
Americans write the date over there it
couldn't possibly be the
date how do I come up these numbers
well I maybe have seen them in a dream
or in my documents no surely in my
documents in my documents and they're
all in there I don't know why you guys
don't remember them it's your fault
anyway fried
screw thank you so
much yeah I'm sorry it's so late did you
eat some yummy cake I hope you
did next time if your birthday comes up
next year I will try my best to be more
on
[Music]
time
Phoenix
need May thank you for the red super
chat some funds for hunting
supplies wait what does that have to do
with hunting supplies what are we
talking about unless you want to take
down a deer or a board with your bare
hands but yeah find yourself a good
butcher it's a worthwhile investment
invest especially if you can store some
portions for the
future what is this
about it's been too long I super chat
this stream you don't
remember ah because I said I wanted to
do survival
stuff oh going fishing and in
general was that around the time where I
was watching those survival videos was
that so long ago
already
damn thank you m believe even though you
don't remember it yourself here's a
kiss
tasun and kak dun with that I get rid of
this one and now we go back to
where Minecraft done age of vampire is
done I assume Pokemon part five maybe I
don't
know do you guys
know part five also done ring fit how
about
ringfit no
clue ring fed look looks like doesn't
look familiar to
[Music]
me R doesn't look familiar to me was not
R
okay my throat
hurts bring a bit
in that H thank you for a pinky oo oh
here we go gim girls episode one
thoughts m Michelle is hilarious oh yeah
suk's cooking reminds me of kata's
kitchen except kiata has less accidents
but she's supposedly a better cook
though nervous Rory talks to Dean like
she's in a k me and great is already
giving up on Dean for Chilton we'll keep
watching oh that's so much happened in
the first episode already I hope you're
enjoying
it
I wonder how far you've come
already I I really like Michelle he's so
funny he's like that sarcastic angry
french
guy really like his
character I think a lot of people have
him as his fa as their
favorite only 20 minutes more yeah
yeah that could dang no dang Flappy boy
D for the pinky turns out I'm by far not
the only one watching his streams while
doing my exercise routine so glad you're
going to join us today as a gym
instructor we need jimins need to get in
shape and gain some meat for the menu oh
yeah but it shouldn't be too muscular
meat because that's going to be like too
stiff no your meat should be softer guys
I don't think you guys need to work out
that
much yeah if anything you should eat
more get more fat become thicker
thickening the
chickening begin the the thickening of
the
chickens yeah but if you want to work
out if you want to be a buff
chicken that's okay too I guess go ahead
go ahead show me the
[Music]
results
MK B Man Black Mage 666 D work D oral no
fan uh KW
J
Dom thank you for the red super chat 1.4
million children
fund thank you thank you I don't know
how to feed all these little children
chickens chicken childrens and I
have thank you with your donation I can
feed five chickens some
dinner no I think actually a couple more
maybe like 15 actually if I cook myself
if I don't bring them to a restaurant if
I just cook myself then I can do it
cheaper hell yeah going to be eating
some beef
wellington uh remains today you guys
want
some yall get fed hey I do feed you
guys yeah we Fe each
other or corn you can have as much corn
as you want we have unlimited corn
thank you
verus Will D for the red super chat as
well those kfb kids meals won't pay for
themselves
exactly look at them they're like
basically just
bones look at you guys you guys haven't
been eaten eating
properly I have to take care of you
every single day don't die thanks for
the gifted membership
St I'm famished no
all right all right all right you guys
can come over to eat the beef
wellington thank you real
adol so thoughtful so considerate of
you Randy RJ blue
D Jimmy Jim Tracy
Jimmy I
am need child thank you for the pinky
you're really hot today and then you
even played
ringfit but yeah it's such a great
stream ringfit with 3D is an amazing
idea you're so expressive and active
it's perfect with this kind of stream
top TI your energy want to see something
even more
amazing I'm has been doing for
Thanksgiving and for Christmas she's
been shooting things in
3D is that how you guys celebrate
Thanksgiving and Christmas I'm starting
to get a a wrong impression
here it's wild she be
Wilding looks like funa it's it's I
don't know kind of cool when she reloads
the gun and you see it in in her
movement
too it's like oh she knows what she's
doing yeah thank you thank you Unity CH
the
G Sai
thanks for the pinky thanks for the fun
stream B thank you for watching thanks
for being part of it and um I have to
say I mean I understand why you guys
were worried about it cuz I was also
worried about it um but I more or less
purposefully but
also kind of naturally made like OAB
boonga noises rather than other other
noises so I think it was just so funny
did you see the short that cow carrot
made out of it like a compilation of my
funny sounds while working out my
aggressive
screaming that I uploaded on my channel
if you missed it you should watch it but
I just can't stop laughing at it it's so
funny especially the part where I but I
run in that ridiculous way and then I
say pickle pickle pickle pickle while
doing it I just cracks me up every
time so um ringfit streams don't
necessarily have to be uh
erotic thank
God my Ringwood streams are
Justa yeah letting out all my stress and
[Music]
frustration in oaba
noises yeah super
kiaha so no need to worry let's do it
again
sometime Australian grunts pickle pickle
pickle
pickle and GD thank you also for Pinky
well than I'm very proud of you this
will probably Inspire more KF peeps to
do some exercise did it I wonder if it
did if it did then good job me if it
didn't then as I said you guys are okay
to just have like some wobbly soft
meat that works
[Music]
too thank you for the pinky great work
today thank you that was a big workout
really for me that was insane I I didn't
want to just stop it after 50 minutes I
call it a day I try to go as long as I
could M very exhausting I feel like you
know for the stream I just like when I
eat I like you guys to know that I'm
still here so I try to make noises but I
think if I was working out alone I would
have um used my voic less and then
therefore I could have probably saved
some
energy I'm probably could have gone
longer
then but yeah need to make OAB bonga
noises oh you started when I did the
Just Do It video wow I'm glad that had
some effects that's what it was
for
hi frat girl thank you for another pinky
Burger fun kiaha you deserve it m got to
get some meat to build muscle kiaha I
think I really did go out like really
late last minute to get a burger at
Burger King that night I got myself a
uh a crispy chicken I think I really did
even though it was cold as outside
I just really wanted to eat a crispy
chicken in that moment and I I just did
it I said it and I did was so
good 8 minutes left I wonder if my
brother is just like literally standing
outside the door now and looking at the
clock counting the seconds and
minutes
yeah he's
fine he's a he's tough he has been
toughing up a lot this
year he has endured things this year
that are crazy that have inspired me
to endure similar things
someday
what does that
mean what does that mean I wonder what
that
means
uh I wasn't sure if I I wanted to tell
you but I'll tell you cuz I'm proud of
him I'm so proud of
him even though he is not not
religious um he
went on the
[Music]
pilgrimage for several
months he went all the
way
from uh I think he started in
Vienna I think or maybe in I don't know
somewhere in Austria he started
somewhere in
Austria
maybe it wasn't
Fano but yeah somewhere in
Austria on foot
two what's it called again
[Music]
then somewhere in Spain what's it called
ah uh Santiago
Maybe
let's
see that
is Santiago de compostella
mm that
is
2,400
kilm and if you would walk without a
break break 500 hours if you would work
I guess
continuously like a human
can't 6
2,416 km in miles is
[Music]
1,500
1. 233
Miles I do it if he wasn't religious I
think a lot of people do it even if
they're not
religious
um well H I guess for him it was like
a I don't know I don't know how to
explain
it but it was incredible like when he
came back we looked at all the photos he
took like millions of photos and videos
and the sceneries are incredible you see
the most beautiful sceneries country
Countryside sceneries and so on but also
little Villages and and so on from like
Switzerland
France Spain depending on when you start
you don't have to start there and my
brother told me that most people um they
don't do it all at once normally a lot
of people don't even start where they
live they just start like where it
starts in
Spain and then just walk that part which
is really short and even if you do the
whole part uh from where you come from
then a lot of people just do like one
season like one month or or or two two
weeks three weeks or so for one section
and then next year they do more but my
brother did the whole thing from
beginning to end of no
break we just did it all in one
go and it was quite inspiring to watch
that um progress and
and yeah now it's like he needs to start
all over again of
course yeah which is why he's looking
for a job and all that right
now but looking at all the footage I
want to do it myself someday maybe not
all at once and all that distance but as
he said it's quite normal for a lot of
them to just do smaller parts or just do
one section per
year so kind of want to do it myself
someday
maybe with my BFF I already talked to
her about it do you want to do this one
day and
um uh stream it while walking could do
but connection will be shitty I think
you know you also like have to go
through some more depressing areas which
are not so nice to look at but most
things are really pretty to look at and
apparently you know it's really crowded
especially if you get to like France or
especially in Spain then it's like
really crowded and you look behind you
see many Pilgrim people and then you in
front of you as well and you make like
so many friendships and you you group up
with some people you dine together
there's like on the path there's like a
a a fixed path that you have to walk and
like there's like a little like
private uh houses who offer for
pilgrimage people they offer food and um
some beds and so on some of them do it
for free some of them do it for like do
whatever like pay whatever you want
basis and some of them charge a little
bit but not too
much and the closer you get to the
destination to the final go the like
more the more of those will show up the
more of those like
private like people offering something
in their house and so on
and it's just so inspiring listening to
the story that my brother has from that
yeah it's so inspiring he got to know so
many people he's got so many friends
from all over the world or like yeah
yeah even outside of Europe from Europe
but also from Asia he got like he met a
few Korean ladies he met some Americans
Canadian you British people all over
yeah making
connections yeah but it's midnight now
so I kind of have to go when you got a
tangent about my
brother yeah I don't know sounded so
inspiring I'm going to do it sometime
don't have to do it all at once and you
know my brother wasn't that fit before
starting it either like he trained
beforehand to get ready for it but
during it and after it he was much more
fed than he was before so it's not like
I can't do it if I want to do it I'll
prepare and then you
know yeah that's midnight let me
in oh yeah he said he'll gladly do um
some of the like he'll gladly come with
me for some of
it I know doesn't that sound so
[Music]
sweet
yeah and you know there's like so many
places where you can get a stamp in your
little book
and at the end of it he had had like
when you opened the book you know it's
like meters
long and it was all filled with stamps
and he had to attach the books to one
another the pages because one was
obviously not enough he used so
many it's so
cool no like Shrine stamps see I like
that
thank you for streaming k no thank you
I'll see you guys tomorrow and I think I
finished the super chats from that day
didn't
I wait almost uh no no no no and D there
we go now these should be
finished yeah okay I'll go have dinner
with my brother now on my fixed table
let's go on my fixed
table
yeah the concert will be archived yes it
will it will
be so happy with my table all right guys
and thanks guys for
watching I'll be using these
tomorrow I kind of have to fix good I
think cuz she's falling apart inside I
noticed I've been playing with her too
much
I was using her too
roughly I know that sounds weird but um
it is what it
is
bye-bye byebye
[Music]
bye-bye
byebye good
[Music]
night