[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
guys amazing
very beautiful beautiful
everyone kick it again and welcome to
the
first I would say full collaboration but
now we have Council so it's the first
almost full collaboration of Halloween
and Indonesia
[Music]
[Applause]
Discord comes out the Discord Fighters
actually you're probably watching this
is the tweets from Discord yesterday
with all the screens on Mario Kart
so we're glad to have the Discord
support today and hopefully also the
viewers support today because uh today
will be a very very passionate and
dangerous and fun and exciting even yeah
[Music]
yeah
great day
exactly
drivers bad drivers no we're not here
[Music]
I think we shall start with the
introductions of each member uh now
let's start with
melvisa from Whole Life Indonesia
[Music]
hello thank you for having me this is
the continuation
thank you everyone I can't wait what's
your what's your ikigo means
um
[Music]
[Applause]
okay what about
oh
oh oh okay
[Music]
tonight is the show you my practice I
guess
oh oh show me what you got
[Music]
it
next up how about rainy
hi professions
[Music]
yeah I've heard you were good you and
Iris have heard Goods good news about
you yeah had a good practice yesterday
right right
[Music]
hello my name is
what's the motivation for today oh well
I I want to be at least not on the last
okay
[Music]
oh okay we will see we will see we have
some competition today in your heart oh
the lost in someone's heart is that such
a good thing does it sound like a good
thing yeah okay next
Indonesia and thank you so much for
inviting me to this collab I'm so happy
though I'm so excited they go
my motivation for today is that I would
like to have fun though although yes I'm
not really confident but let's have fun
all right
[Music]
and Ollie
yay yay
zombies
Indonesia second generation hi guys
motivation I plan on ranking pop so that
you guys become my bottoms that is my
motherboard
that is on top I see I don't know what
else I expected from your motivationally
we won't be dominated that easily senpai
and I think wait did I get it all the
introductions from ID I think I did
yeah
yeah yeah
all right let's introduce the inside
let's start with Iris
oh yeah hiris it's Iris hello live
English project hope V singer here
um my goal today is to get first place
Victorious
thank you for participating and looking
forward to your driving skills thank you
so much for having me here so I heard
that you waited for yeah for me to come
on we were literally in the last
question that I needed because before
you it was we were elf unless that's one
that was German we were 11 people
thank you next up how about
um
today I'm gonna win probably okay okay
this is the I own I heard you only
played Mario Kart so far in the members
only stream but that's about it yeah I
won in that one too oh oh okay
oh then you might be the hidden winning
Choice
[Music]
a wild card player welcome
thank you thank you and next time
English
um
um I'll do my best I think we have a we
have a future competition to be not less
than to be first so I'll do my best
alrighty
thank you
you know I was also taking this very
seriously in her practice round so I'm a
bit scared of Ina um I don't know
still falling off my house it's fun oh
yeah it happens oh Kelly joined yes nice
thanks Kelly
[Applause]
thank you all right I'm here nice then
let's start and let's continue with the
introduction from
op Maury
hello everyone my name is Calliope my
parents are still asleep and probably
can't watch the news this morning Maury
nice to meet you I'm gonna be talking a
bit low because it's a bit early uh so
excuse me for that guys but I'm very
excited just to be here I really didn't
think this was gonna work but it's
working
thank you Kelly for joining even though
it's such an early time and to kind of
uh Troublesome with some setups and all
that I'm glad you're still here and you
know what you being so whispering and
calm might be a good uh thing for
driving because that way you might be
able to focus more
videos
[Music]
and I'm kind of sick today and if you're
watching on my side I just need to say
this now I've had some technical
difficulties very suddenly so I am made
of cardboard I'm sorry please well it
was not my fault it's out of my control
right now so anyway I'm PNG tuber Doma
summer does a PNG tuber Let's Race today
baby today
[Applause]
well you know on the screen there's
there's gonna be a lot of things
happening so your viewers should be
looking at the game and not you anyway
so I think it's fine I'm careless
ah we always wanted to of course
all right that leaves uh me I think yeah
I think we're done with everyone else
yes
welcome everyone I wanted to lose
tournament for a long long time uh I I
think my viewers have heard me talk
about it since months ago and finally
it's happening uh and I'm very glad to
have all these lovely girls here
together it's the first time we're doing
a tournament like this so I I don't
think anyone has to feel bad about you
know not being so good it's all fine
maybe we'll do it some more often in the
future so please don't stress yourself
out let's just have fun today
[Music]
[Applause]
but before that let me say thank you is
the hats and the cards are sponsored by
ninoma inanis yes
they look lovely so cute all right let's
uh everyone switch to the rules in a
minute please thank you
okay tournament rules easy there's not
many rules basically and all characters
all courses are allowed however if you
choose uh please do not choose random
courses please choose a certain course
that you want to actually race but if
that course has been used before like if
it has actually been chosen before
please do not choose the same course
again already
understand oh yeah
and number two items are allowed number
three we are racing in 150 cc with no
assist everyone please check if you have
turned off your assist I think you can
check by pressing y
EP all right
now okay
if uh wait a second it's if you press Y
and select your character at the point
where you select the card you can press
on a plus the plus button and that's
when you see the the three options on
the right side if you press l
uh if if there is a if there's a sign
that says no
then it's uh Auto steering off that's
how it's supposed to be okay
yeah it's supposed to be crossed out
exactly the other ones you can ignore
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
well then I also want to quickly let you
guys know yes I'm on I'm gonna be on
like Auto mute this whole time so unless
I have something to say I'm gonna be
muted don't worry if I'm a little quiet
I'm still here with you guys in spirit
yeah okay okay no problem no problem
and next row uh oh yeah then there's no
more rules there's basically it's just a
system we're doing the first cup all
versus all big mixer four races each but
then we get we will mute each other by
the way during the race and just to
focus everyone on what we're driving and
then we get back together and Discord
talk a little bit then we go to the
second cup which is en versus ID six
versus sixth yes yes that's when we will
separate each other in uh The Voice
channels by team this one in this one we
will actually talk with one another if
you wanna and then we uh give some
comments together again when we get all
back together in the same channel and
then we do the third cup with random
randomly thrown together teams no Ian
versus ID but like all mixed together
naturally beautiful
random random random we will just like
I'll count down and and then everyone
joins Eva voice chat room zero or voice
chat room one is this one
everybody wants to be you want
well then we're gonna have to do it
again and again and again
perfect and by the way just just so you
know the the those like team cups would
basically be
um like the same system as all versus
all the difference is just basically
like if you throw items like red shells
or whatever and there is a teammate in
front of you it will not go to the
teammate obviously it will go directly
to the closest opponent driver that's
around you so yeah that's how that team
system works I think
[Music]
is everyone ready to get started
who's that random dude
who's that wait a second
okay
all right okay
okay then everyone who's ready mute
yourself on Discord if someone's not
ready then I will ask you why you're not
ready
[Music]
wait guys
uh how do you go forward in the game
you can't go right now you can't move on
the world right now okay that's what you
mean gotcha all right understood thank
you thanks guys love you okay love you
too
[Music]
okay we're all muted it's just me and
you guys don't tell me how how do I win
I need your help
[Music]
well one of the cheat codes I can put in
gotta go fast gotta drive all right
still controls
all right here we go
[Music]
what should we pick oh I like Bowser's
Castle
[Music]
yeah
I
[Music]
practice one time yesterday
so I think I'm gonna do pretty good
[Music]
is this there we go and my wheel
castle castle
ah I was so close
should we be showing this
[Music]
time right
on the dress
[Music]
yeah yeah
my place has been covered I'm in fourth
place
tricks on my jumps
[Music]
now you guys at my place
your place
else
[Music]
[Applause]
get up
[Music]
out
in did I drift the wrong way
it's okay it's not bad at least we're
not last
we could still bring it back
all right we're still gonna go for
Bowser's Castle oh yeah let me move
[Music]
hats
is this a good spot can it be right here
is okay
[Music]
there's a big game on you already
like who got picked I wasn't looking
[Music]
oh who won who got him first
last game
of the beach okay
[Music]
did you check
hey
what's up
we got him I was in first for a little
bit that's okay we're gonna get this
trick here
third place I'm still covering it
we're in third place right now
[Music]
wait
damn I messed up that boost I got some
free coins I'm like no no no no no
trick
stuff
[Music]
it's a drink that's a place right now
oh okay I'm getting coins
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
okay
not personal
[Music]
no no no
okay
I always up this part drifting it's
kind of hard I just I guess we'll just
go through the water I'm in Ninth Place
I got we all got up
oh this sucks
this sucks I hate it like you I was in
first for a while
doing really good it was like at the top
and then just all of a sudden just oh
shoot
okay we got eighth place that's done
Mario Kart with items is lame if it was
just okay everyone do not use cheap
cheap beach or a Mario Kart Stadium
anymore for your race collection thank
you I'm gonna try and remember that but
I don't know yeah
nothing that looks like a beach and
nothing that looks like a fancy
placed right but isn't there multiple
Beach
uh yeah but the cheap cheap beach the
one that we just did from the DS version
not anymore oh okay okay okay are we
doing team wait what are we doing teams
uh we still have two races to go for all
this result
okay I mean oh sorry
[Music]
there's plane racing I'll be at the top
so much RNG
[Music]
old Harbor
all right
we'll catch up
trick trick
y we're catching up
foreign
[Music]
thank you
what does Hope taste like
[Music]
[Applause]
hahaha
my coin
[Music]
glass
bye
honey
I'm thinking it easy on this one but
let's go up the side here
[Music]
when the time comes
oh
[Music]
I hate items
it's a trick
oh my God
and if it weren't for items I'd be at
the top
no no no no no no okay
I finished the Ninth Place
what
that's BS
is
ping
that was a castle
it's all RNG
there's no skill involved when there's
items
[Music]
electrodome
I played this one
[Music]
I am
monster
truck
[Music]
foreign
makes you lose coins
guys I got disconnected oh
what do we do
have my problem
check
[Music]
Cali's in front of me
whoever's in first place I
drive here what the heck
can I get a Bullet Bill
[Music]
trick
foreign
okay about the disconnection I'm
I'm not sure like normally it seems like
in the whole of Japan tournaments they
automatically give the one like well the
like this qualification like last spot
if you uh oh well if you are oh wow uh
congratulations oh everyone cannot mute
themselves now oh yeah
[Music]
but she still was a fourth or what so
yeah
yeah I think that's just how we're gonna
take it it is what it is
so uh let me let me just uh enough was
number one right number one
congratulations
[Music]
I I thought you kept on selecting
Rainbow Road
you know no
you know
what yeah yeah she practiced on that one
a lot I think that's what she was going
for that
um
we'll get it oh okay someone has to uh
yeah wait uh wait who was number two
no problem who was number two though
Irish
[Music]
how did you how did you manage to get
number two today
I did bad on the first race so that
really pulled me back but yeah Ina
Senpai was very quick but I did my best
I did my best
you were amazing both of you
[Music]
oh thank you oh wait me and Elena were
thirds are we tired
good job good job oh wait wait are we
complete in the lobby right now one two
three four five six
okay I guess we're complete okay well
then shall we continue uh but Muna senpa
is currently unavailable
my battery is 100 but it's taking low
battery so I didn't know which one is
low battery oh
the ones that you're like okay
do you think you're fine to go or you
need some time I I think
um
everyone who needs coffee go get
yourself a cup of coffee
what about the caffeine shakes already
I was actually really surprised about
Emma's driving too like I thought you
know because she didn't like we didn't
see her practicing we didn't see her
play the game and to begin with um
[Laughter]
yeah whatever yeah no it would have been
a waste if you would have shoutcasted
how you uh suggested uh Amir because
you're such a good driver we need you we
need you
all right then let's uh okay only okay
okay Ollie is going to an idol meeting
no
that gives me really bad flashbacks I
don't like that
[Laughter]
is
picked last and I don't want that I'm
gonna go at my full power now because
now I'm fighting for the en ladies yeah
this is where we put our all in it yep
yeah
the honor of our teams
I was just warm up now let's now do you
mean and I think actually this is good
because
[Music]
two of the strongest ones are in Ian
wait me too no
oh my God hey I've proved that I that I
can I'm okay at not getting last place
so that's good news
is a good asset to have I want her in
our team hell yeah guys
will have to carry uh Indonesia's uh
back yeah it's okay I will I will
support Rainey
[Music]
split into teams by I think let's just
um Ian go to a voice Channel 01 thank
you okay oh
wait a second
oh okay okay okay uh just Cali is
missing did Kelly get the memo
ladies I'm back what is it always
strategy for winning against
IDs go fast
I've never played oh let's go Jack
before but like um you know for items do
they automatically um not hit our
teammates yeah it only hits like oh okay
that's really helpful nice yes
but I've never parted teams yet I'll see
how we can select that I think we will
um like every every participant will
have a choice to win which team they can
join I think that's how it works let's
see no more items no CPU all vehicles
race four races let's go
oh there it is
okay uh
I I I'm the one doing this okay uh
player was Ollie right yeah no no wait
no no no
no no no no
no no no how do I how do I cancel this
no
if I have to like you might have to
oh no problem okay it looks fine okay
all right
you know what to do girls
okay I mean just as a book I have I'm
creating a room right now
sorry girls I did a little mistake
because like I thought uh oh yeah you
know
I just opened the room again
you can join them again
okay yeah you can you can join in again
it's open again I think it closed once
you can join again now yeah
[Music]
you guys ready to drift
very much
do it as much as you can that's that's
how this works
yes but not overdrift you know you know
there they are oh God it's a scary face
the bald one is back wait there's two
Bob ones now
I'm missing one
oh they're finishing her full power with
the baldness that could be Uranus that
is that is raining I think
okay
wait I'm a complete one two three four
five six seven eight nine ten eleven
twelve okay I think we're completely
just doing a head count everybody stands
still
I think we are okay
no CPU all vehicles for races
yeah at least a little Baldy
so you guys know what my mom is watching
she's not gonna say anything though
are you sure you don't want to say
anything hey
good morning oh my God this is how you
do it well you have to press a
[Music]
one two three four five
ah this is uh who is that Anya okay okay
now it's even let's go there's actually
a random button there so for later we
can I can just do the random button we
don't have to do the voice chat thingy
[Music]
a new map a new map which one do we want
to use which one do we all have
confidence
I want to do Wario Stadium
um
music Park I like music Park so choose a
different one we don't have anymore
they're using a tactic you guys know
we're overloading them
oh no babies
wait we don't know
no I think those they're they're
definitely teams
because Kiara
I think today for us
oh nice we're blue blue
and here we go here we go okay okay when
do we push the go button on the tomb
yep
[Applause]
[Music]
it doesn't work with like the same
people oops I think it shouldn't really
I don't know Chad told me that it
doesn't hit uh your own people unless I
don't know it was it a green shell oh it
probably wasn't yeah I don't think you
can control it
it was red
okay I don't know well then you just
gotta be careful
they're fun oh I see someone right in
front of me what interesting I think
we're laughing
oh no no no no
yes
there's someone in front of you on this
road
[Music]
[Applause]
everyone
okay we got it we got it now
[Music]
okay no we did okay we did okay
I think
[Music]
or like the animal crossing map is easy
like easy as in it's like oh no you
gotta make it difficult
Stadium personally
okay
[Music]
no I don't like the cheese one no
that's the lactose we'll Rock It Anyways
bills will rock it Bowser no matter what
it is
[Music]
I have practice in that one
is on this one is a little trick yeah
just has a lot of traps and a lot of um
obstacles
dirty
let's go
let's go I was number one for one second
I love that one that was a good second
I am number one again
[Music]
I'm not used to this oh my God
stay home
okay who's in front of us
[Music]
yeah okay so everyone's Ian then okay
I won't use the shelf so what do you
think
wait that wasn't me that was protect
yourself
it seems like the flower does attack no
that wasn't someone
foreign
[Music]
no we got back
only happy accidents
let's go okay yes
I'm not bad at this map
[Applause]
it's hit me like a wrecking ball
whose song
Miley Cyrus ah
ugly
oh
should I throw the Red Shell right now
with Enon so that I can be number one
really bad timing oh I hate it when the
lightning hits when you're about to jump
and you just like I'm dead alrighty
let's freaking go
not bad
oh no oh no
oh no what oh no
what a play
Oh rain there moving off the rain oh
rainy she's taking it serious I feel
like they uh
I feel like they're definitely getting
tactical on us here you guys
they got nothing on us
[Music]
cheese versus rainbow
[Laughter]
it's
gonna be that one don't worry it's going
to be Rainbow Road and I hate it
um I feel like it's gonna be cheese yeah
it's too much cheese here
oh
ah
goddamn cheese man
okay please land why do they like that
one so much
[Music]
yeah hell yeah
just kidding
yeah
[Music]
he took a shortcut there
I didn't even know that was a shortcut
you know the shortcuts we're in trouble
they do they do
it's okay I'm still I'm still doing okay
it's so good we're still good
someone else in front of you which will
be number 12 I guess
it's gonna be a long road for that when
Rachel
I shouldn't have listened
oh
okay so she knows the shortcut I see how
it is I thought I I just saw it I was
like oh yeah there was a shortcut here
not at the very end
oh
thank you
[Music]
oh
no I'm going off track
okay only only irises ahead of me that's
good yep
oh Raina came through the shortcut no no
no no I didn't have a boyfriend to use
that shortcut okay she's first now okay
all right
give me something good oh no not a
banana
[Music]
oh yeah
oh God okay
guys together
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
oh my God oh my God
okay
I think it will bite Us in the ass but
we have Ina so okay yeah I don't know
I'll do my best
I don't know the shortcuts for this so I
don't know any shortcuts here but the
shortcuts just go down in space to Sana
areas through yeah
I
know the shortcuts for that
oh cool oh we're getting right oh
[Music]
we'll be good yeah yeah
like the lower rankings we're fine yeah
okay we're pretty ahead though
okay I will just chill with newest
just don't fall off the edges
yep
laughs
yeah I told you
okay
hang off
oh man especially for like for like Cali
for example I think she's not gonna have
a nice little mini Virgo here we go
oh thank God this is so easy
oh thank God
oh my God um please please don't do it
this is so slippery it scares me
[Music]
okay we are one two three right now yeah
it's all of us okay okay
that's fine
that was not me that was nothing
don't get too close to me I have a
retail on my back okay
and I'm just gonna follow you
oh okay
[Music]
okay
oh no always only went in front of me
okay it's okay one more night
[Music]
my hand is sweating
oh no blue shell coming
no
it was so nice
driving oh my God
no there she is
okay no no no no
okay we'll get here
[Music]
oh yeah I see it
[Applause]
come on
okay okay
[Music]
okay let's go
oh it's so scary there
you know I'm at me I think
I was like third fourth yeah
until the end oh it's okay we dominated
the race let's go one two three four
nice
hell yeah still in the blast still not
last
hi
[Music]
[Applause]
hello everyone congratulations
I expect hello guys hello
[Music]
yeah what can I ask the Indonesian team
uh what was their reasoning behind
choosing uh the cheese one and the baby
Road I like cheese because
was somewhat in control there because
like It's gotta be a road where Elena
knows the shortcuts and stuff yeah I am
yeah well
um
uh do we have uh some uh comments from
the winner Ina it was number one I think
uh yes uh I would like to thank my
generates
um
[Laughter]
for this opportunity because
I was about to be like yeah go let's go
okay okay
thank you
okay so we're doing random teams next
there's four more races so please
everyone be careful to not choose any
roads that have been chosen previously
that I would appreciate that
um
well even if you accidentally choose one
that has been uh chosen before don't
worry it will probably not be so like
that so let's just let's just try to not
choose the ones that we have uh raced
before then I will do the random teams
now actually there is uh we don't have
to do the voice chat thing because there
is actually a way to do it here
and then once the teams are selected oh
there it is okay so uh in voice chat
zero zero zero one we want uh gura
and your feet all right
baby
[Music]
in one team
yeah we're gonna lose
guys wait guys we still have hope
the pressure I don't I don't I'm not
really confident in winning against the
United what's your favorite map
my favorite map has to be uh probably uh
the airport right now okay airport
Sunshine airport yeah airport airport
okay oh then how about we choose the
iPhone where is it we haven't played at
once
yeah what is it on
hmm
oh
well
uh aren't aren't us like the the the you
know the the the top 10 from the back
yeah she's like yeah the other team is
is packed with like the really strong
ones I'm just like
there's a Kiara right
yeah
let's go
I'd like to apologize to you personally
because I kept bullying you in the
previous rounds I got Karma I did not
know
[Laughter]
let's do this team so we got this let's
go we got this
We Believe
together
ribbon Road okay okay where is
this wait I hate this map
particularly hard for me
[Music]
right in front of me right now uh okay
oh
okay
yes if the Hops not with us
at least I don't know wait we can do it
guys don't worry
did I just meet you what
no
[Music]
okay
we're doing good
what okay I don't understand
[Music]
I just realized this one feels like a
Toy Story
never give up
oh
no wait who's in front of me right now
Arena and Nina
okay
um
nobody in here I'm so far waiting yeah I
am
[Music]
oh my God
oh
that was close that was very close Okay
uh second uh
seven I'm seven
five four it's good it's good uh this is
fine we can still bring it fine it's not
that bad it's not that bad right now
yeah yeah
okay it could be worse yeah yeah
we're still we're still going okay we
can hit our friends that annoys me yeah
yeah okay airport the items can hit
airport yeah Airport please
it's okay guys
oh you could do it how much practice did
you eat yeah yeah
you are our home
how are you guys so strong I'm
a senpai can't you rewind time so that
we can like redo that and win isn't that
crony's job
oh yeah I can't do it for everyone just
me
Amelia is the one with the watch right
so yeah yeah she can go back in time and
practice a lot uh yes
ah what is it
oh what is this big blue I don't know if
I've ever played this one before what is
this this one is like futuristic water
parkish
oh
ah
okay I think what I don't like is that
the NPCs keep harassing me oh the ones
in the map yeah in the way
[Music]
oh I love this music though oh yes
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
yep I'm in the front right now but this
is very early game
yes
oh my God
[Music]
oh
there's somebody's actually flying with
bananas
well that's me
I'm gonna be careful okay
[Applause]
yeah Thunder really destroys my Pace
okay
I don't see Nina come on come on I want
to see Ina I don't know
so
okay
sorry I didn't mean to you I see her
[Music]
oh
he's using a shortcut oh okay
this chart could really help though
legit like I know any shortcuts I did
not make it uh
uh I should have studied more
it's all right
[Music]
I don't think I've ever played this map
number seven maybe I'm getting one of
these quality right now I'm being very
salty right now guys
airport will do Us justice will ascend
and be embarrassing though to get
airport and I still do bad at it
thank you
I believe
it's believed
oh everyone's choosing airport oh my God
[Music]
wait is this the third race or the last
race this is third right I think okay
we got it in the back yes okay we got
this we got this we got this okay
Sunshine Airport
[Music]
let's just hope that Ina doesn't really
know this map but I probably she
probably does
I think she does yep
do you guys know the items that we got
oh like what do you mean by losing uh
from like thunder and stuff there's no
way to really prevent that
[Music]
I got something
but we don't want to
how how can we
[Music]
trash
oh God there is some of the items that I
don't really like to use
it
come on
I don't really get how this music like I
have this like speaker looking thing I
don't really know how I'm supposed to
use it I think it's like oh it's like uh
if there are like a lot of people around
you you can just like honk it
okay and everyone's just like I'm just
gonna honk it uh
[Music]
let's just use it I have a bad habit of
holding on to items
go Ali
food
is good
okay
you win
[Music]
she's in third place
okay oh
my god did I hurt you we're doing good
we're doing good so far okay
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
just gotta make sure it's not yina
oh my God what's what's that yeah what
is that what I don't know I'm eight I
wonder
how pretty you got nerd
okay I wonder how this looks right now
oh yes
I kind of like being right in the middle
all right what's the next time
what is it yeah
what are we gonna do next does anyone
have anything that they're confident in
music like a very confident music
[Music]
Park okay yeah
oh no can I can I join before this ah
yeah I'll tell first all right run for
it it's not ready yet
right yeah people having children
there we go
wait I just realized the crown did you
get any yeah yeah we're like a head by
six points
explains we gotta keep this up it's a
very close race
we got this we got hope
uh okay that's my point counts ladies
not not the clock not the clock I don't
like the clock okay
[Music]
okay
and this one has a lot of drifting so
whenever you guys uh
do you know the shortcuts for this okay
there there are a few shortcuts but
they're actually pretty tricky so I
wouldn't recommend them okay yeah all
right let's go let's do this I don't
really recognize this place but let's go
I'm gonna win this
oh no I just got it
up on the beginning okay over here
[Music]
okay
in the front and then another one
[Music]
oh yeah this is a lot of Dripping okay
okay there's a shortcut over here but
it's really really pretty
shoot
okay okay wait uh who's first right now
I see Ina in front of me so I'm usually
second bring it okay
because I saw them
oh God and what I don't like this map
oh no girls in front of me
[Music]
oh you're our last hope right now I'm
doing really bad
it's okay
I've eaten a lot of your kind so we're
good
Hope Has consumed zombie meat a lot so
we're good
[Music]
oh no I see so many people in front of
me
[Music]
what
piano okay okay
oops
did accidentally hit someone
okay be careful
[Music]
oh no he got
who got disconnected I got disconnected
controlled
[Music]
Destiny is in your hands
sorry
[Music]
one of your
perspectives to see what's going on
um
okay I'm last so when I got
well it was a valiant effort ladies and
144 hey that's two fours in there if
four is a good number I like it I can't
say I'm unhappy
[Music]
okay so wait uh we did great I got
kicked out of the room uh
yeah
[Music]
and we had two disconnections so it kind
of doesn't count
yeah
and when I rejoined like my points are
are reset yeah
yeah
disconnected
I got disconnected like right before the
last lap oh no that was me and my Shark
friends
well that probably means that you know
the last round if if these two you know
got disconnected and the points got
deleted that means that the last round
uh final result is not really accurate
um but that's okay but let's just say
the last round was an extra Encore for
fun and yeah
um I would like to give out some golden
juggles
we all want a golden yellow right so
okay they're not showing up on your
stream they're only on my stream but I
like I would like to give one a golden
juggle to Ina for winning almost
everything
yeah yeah good job congratulations
congratulations
[Music]
and I would like to give uh another uh
golden Yago
um as uh to Iris for also being
absolutely amazing
another golden juggle goes to Dana for
being I guess the strongest in the ID
team holy moly
another golden yellow goes to gura for
being absolutely the speediest shark
I've ever seen yay
[Music]
[Laughter]
goes to
Ave for being super a big surprising uh
what do you call that wild wild card
damn wild cardio
never go goes to Muna
mooning because I
didn't see you that much on the race but
I think you were still shining brightly
as as the moon always does
the darkest time
and now the golden yellow goes to ollie
for being also surprisingly damn good
you were number one yeah
[Music]
for being speed squirrel
[Applause]
[Music]
goes to
amazing too thank you for participating
[Applause]
and another golden Yago goes to Cali for
actually really you know I don't you
surprised me you surprised me Callie I
was I was looking at you driving there
and I was like damn well what the hell
man she didn't even do practice arts and
she's so good
oh no my mom was playing instead of me
that's why I was so good
didn't I didn't get last place even once
guys that was my goal
thank you for cheering for me everyone
thank you I stopped moving don't mind me
uh chat I'm not gonna be able to fix
that now I think one two three four five
six seven eight nine ten eleven
wait who did I not give up
you were so surprising me too sometimes
I have I had an eye on you thank you
[Music]
the last one
yeah
thank you very much everyone
um I hope you all have fun
um can we get like a last one last
comment from everyone let's start with
Anya
oh me okay
um that was so much fun but I have to
practice more
next time I don't know maybe
maybe I will definitely be next time
yeah
there's always room for improvement
thank you
[Music]
closing comments
uh let's see my closing comment is Kiara
thank you for everything you made an
amazing tournament you worked so hard on
this you had a logo commissioned you
made all of this stuff in as well for
helping with the assets but like oh my
goodness you organized the whole thing
and it was a blast and I just wanted to
have fun with my friends and I was able
to do that because you organized this
amazing thing just thank you so much for
for working so hard on it because it was
a blast thank you I'm so glad you
enjoyed it thank you
[Music]
it was fun to organize
good uh closing comment please oh
thank you I want to say thank you also
to Ina and Kiara for all the hard work
you guys put into this tournament thank
you and I'm very I'm proud of myself for
not doing nearly as bad as I thought I
would and I would like to uh say that it
was probably because I fixed my switch
legs so I didn't have any lag let's go
games
no excuses I watched and I won though I
can use that excuse me
in a long time I think yeah no practice
it's cool okay let's go rock challenge
[Music]
ah yes so I'm just uh thank you for
organizing this and now we have uh
mishaps and some troubles uh Beyond but
yes thank you for this golden young I
will cherish it and talk to you okay
thank you so much
thank you too
okay I've completely disappeared I'm
sorry guys
okay Iris closing comments please thank
you so much for inviting me to this
wonderful tournament Kiara and thank you
so much Ina for the very very cute
assets and yes I will practice more so
that we can I can go against Inna
yeah yeah my goal is Nina yeah
yeah I'm really excited to do this again
hopefully one day yeah
thank you I hope yeah one day I want to
win against Ina too that's a big pickle
that would be a big accomplishment it's
not that big of a goal
[Laughter]
I'm so glad I'm so glad you joined Holo
Ian because that's what made this
tournament possible yeah I'm really glad
to be able to join this wonderful
Tournament being part of the cool kids
all right Ollie closing
okay I'd like to say a very very big
thank you to Kiara Senpai for organizing
this I've organized it once and it was
really hectic so I can't really imagine
the links that you go to uh
and even the thumbnails those must have
been hard and also for example if we're
making all of those acids so quickly
like you guys really um how do I say it
I really appreciate it a lot and I'm
sure all of us do so thank you so much
for your hard work it was really fun
playing with everyone and um I may have
not popped everyone but one way or
another you guys will um
I forgot about that goal yeah
you look at them someday only you'll get
them
thank you thank you all right stand by
closing comes please
um first of all um thank you for you
Kiara for organizing and no you guys can
stop thanking me stop I mean I I don't
think without without you organizing we
wouldn't be like this I mean it's it's
rare to gather all the whole life
Indonesian homes that's true yeah so I'm
so thankful for that and also
um big thanks to inatu for making the
assets it's really great thank you so
much and I hope in the future we can be
like this again yes yes
yes yes yes I hope so too definitely I
was thinking like maybe on on uh like
around Christmas or New Year's Eve we
should do something like this
foreign
[Music]
for organizing it of course I know like
organizing collabs and everyone in
different time zones and like schedules
it's really really difficult but you
really put a lot of effort into
organizing it commissioning like the
logo and everything really thankful
um and everyone feel free to use your
hats and cards like in your Mario Kart
streams in the future too
[Music]
and uh yeah thank you everyone for
joining us today like it was so much fun
like playing with everyone and um
Corporation this was a great
collaboration between uh kfb and Taco
Taco Bell taco eats stuff
[Laughter]
let's work
our fast food franchises are meant to be
together yeah we're speeding
okay all right
closing comments please
okay I know you said stop but thank you
and also innocent pie uh thank you so
much and I had a lot of fun
um there was a little miss out there
there was a little disconnection issue
but overall I had a lot of fun and I
would love to have this kind of
tournament again in the future let's do
it you are so good yeah yeah no thank
you
training so I'll get better yeah
[Music]
thank you
an example closing comments please
okay so it doesn't end there I would
like to say thank you
to everyone here also especially uh
Kiara and Ina like these are amazing and
also okay uh I'm really happy because I
could actually uh gather and play with
all of you guys here yeah yes like well
uh I'd appreciates more more more
collabs like this so if you guys are
planning to do so
I I'd love to I'd be I would be happy to
participate so yes thank you so much I
love you
okay
it's closing comments well first uh I'd
like to apologize
but if I was salty if I cursed it you
guys uh no yeah
[Music]
and uh yeah thank you Kiara and and Inna
you guys worked really hard thank you
guys and thank you everybody for
participating it was really fun I know
it's hard to organize these types of
collabs because everybody's so busy and
different schedules thank you and I had
a lot of fun thank you
[Music]
now that we have Polo Council we can
like we don't have to relay on these
exact 12 members anymore so next time if
you want you can do shout casting
thank you thank you everyone for
participating today
um I hope I hope everyone had a great
time even if you know maybe you were not
number one number two number three
that's fine I think today was really
just about getting together putting um
two communities to Fan communities of
hello Ian and hello ID together and just
feeling United definitely and I am
always glad to um do stuff like this
again so I would gladly invite you guys
again whenever you have time for it and
want to join and I'm sorry that you know
because since it's such an international
collaboration
um it's not gonna be an ideal time for
everyone so I'm so sorry for the girls
who had to wake up at like six seven a.m
or something like that I'm so sorry I
know it's
themselves
your mom enjoyed the tournament
what did I think she did I think that
she enjoyed it as well
well done with that I would like to
officially close to hollow Ian Holo ID
Mario Kart tournament everyone take care
of your golden yagos to polish him every
day he wants to be shiny and sparkly and
yeah I'll see you guys
peace
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
best place