[Music]
Thank you for your continued support.
[Laughter] [Music] [
Music]
[Laughter] The
countdown will begin, so if you
eat then you'll be on time
[Music] Hey [Music]
[Music] [Music] [Music] The second half is now available, so please wait. OK [Music]
Google
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter] I'm
here for an interview.
Sorry for the fall.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Thank you.
[Laughter]
[Music]
Thank you.
[Laughter] Let's do
our best, so Nedaruma-san fell
down. He's wearing pretty big shoes, everyone.
[Music]  ]
Looks like it's time to start the competition.
[Music]
Okay, so after today's introduction, we
'll start. Okay, here we go. I
fell down on Daruma-san, but this is a
competition for everyone. Yes.  If
you run toward the goal when the display says Daruma-san,
and if you move when the display says he has fallen, you will die instantly. Yes, yes. The
competition is for Daruma-san to run as close to the goal as possible by 321.
[Applause] Try
not to die.  It is also important to act carefully.
Yes,
Harvest.
Yes, it is an important competition. First of all,
everyone has a preliminary round, and after that preliminary round, the top 15
compete in the final
[music]
.
Since you said yes, we'll
start with the qualifying rounds in which everyone participates.
Well, this year, we'll be tweeting about a bit of a street area,
etc. Well, things have changed a bit
.
If you stop in a hurry, you'll end up slipping like this,
so you
'll be instantly killed.  I
wonder if the difficulty level has increased a bit, but
last year,
this year, the system has been
made to be more precise, so it
's quite tough.
[Music]
Well, that's right.
Before we start the competition, I
'd like to say a few words about it starting.
But can I ask Ei-chan, who made the announcement, that it's
starting a little bit?  Is it okay if I just say a few words? We'll
start now, so I'll just ask.
Okay,
everyone, are you
ready? Oh yeah,
okay?
[Music] I'm
sure you're canceling your entry or making an entry.  After all,
Fubuki says I'd like to have a chat before we get started.
That's what I'm saying. I guess everyone's golden apple has run out. I see. [Music] [Applause] Are you ready? [Music] [Music] I'd like to start. Yes, OK. [Music] Daruma-san [Music] Something's off.  New decision has been made
[Music] It's pretty
dead
[Applause]
[Music]
Yes
Yes and 12
Well,
Tomata
Event and
Toner
Azuki-san
[Music]
[Applause]
I guess we'll start with number one. Would you like to
listen to the interview?
[Music] Nata-san
[Music]
That was amazing. You
must have been practicing.
[Music] It's
broken.
[Laughter]  That's
right. Shiro is so harsh. Shiro is so bad.
In the 15th final, even the last place gets points. The
person in 1st place has the most points, so aim for the top as much as possible. But
please do your best to get as far as possible.
Of course.
Well, I think it's better to eat happily. I see, because there's only
one, and there's only one.
Certainly, if
you want to eat, there's that meat in the box at the back,
so it's
a call. It's a call. It's a call. Star Match Comet.
Hoshimachi Narcissus What did you do? Something you
often see at sports days.
[Music]
[Laughter]
This is crazy.
That's amazing. We get along so well. It seems like we
get along so well. I wonder how many points we should get.  I
guess this is
not the case. I
want to be in mpt3.
[Music]
That's right. I do
n't know what will happen. I
might be disqualified. Thank
you. Thank you.
Let's calm down.
[Music] I
really want to move.  Please do your
best.
[Music]
I'm sorry.
Also, I can't say that. I'm the only one who can say that.
No, there
must be a blue demon.
[Music]
Start
Why are
you there?
[Music]
But...
[Applause]
[Music]
Try your best, try your best, try your best, it's starting Try your best,
try your best -
What's going to happen?
[Music]
Come on [
Applause]
[Music] That's
not progressing That's not
progressing
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter] It
was also 41. Ade
503.53.53
No, no, no.  I'm going to
make an announcement, please.
[Music]
Oh yeah, some of the controls didn't work during the game, so I
was nervous, but it turned out okay. I'm
glad I made it to the Abune goal. [
Music]
[Music]
[Music]  ]
And then there's Annie
[music]
[laughing] You
did a great job, thank you. It
was good, thank you. -
1st
[music] I was
planning on taking first place.  that
Yesterday, I
was taught an excuse.
Thank you very much for this.
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Music] The
first place will tell you what's important.
Don't worry.
Lately.
I'm the winner of this game.
[Music] [Music]  [
Applause]
[Laughter
] [Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] I'm
being bullied
[Music] It
must have been
[Laughter] Let's get
on with it [Music] I'm glad the button was there.
Well, I'm
glad to have made a comeback here. I wonder
if you can hear me. Can you
hear me?
[Music]
[Music] I'm
back
[Music]
So Daruma-san is in here.
Just the settings
[  [Music] The
lag
may be a little less if you set the graphics processing priority in the settings.I also experienced lag earlier, so this
is the video setting.Thank you
for setting the graphics processing priority in the video settings.
[Music] Adjust the
drawing distance a little.  It's
better to make it lower. [Music] I've already set it to 6, but [Music] [Music] I decided to go for it, so that's one point to attack. [Music] Take the apple and give me some meat.  It's ok to put it in. I
won't eat that meat. I'll only
eat it after all.
Show me the next one. I
got mine to put in the big nose anyway.
[Music] It
's cute. [Music]
[Music]  When it's
time for the water, we
all play TNT from the beginning.The boss is
one person from the top, and the two of us are playing under the festival,
so we
can't do the water until that's over. [Applause] I'm nervous so I'll definitely start from scratch
[Music]
Inside, I'm starting to think about quitting. I
don't have the courage to compete at this level.
[Music]
If you go up, there's an exit at the top, right? Just
go down there. That's where Mel-meru comes
from.
Sensei, you've woken up. You're in a hurry. You ca
n't do anything. I
see. I understand that you can't do anything. But
basically, everyone
seems to be able to mess things up that much. I
think I lost the script. Maybe I
have it. I don't have the DVD either.
[Music]
My own.  I get nervous when it's my turn. I'll talk about it
later. I'm curious to see how well the white group's extra drama is transcribed right now.
[Music]
[Music]  That
's really all there was to it. That's amazing.
[Music] It's really hard to sleep on the left, so the right is full. There's a place where everyone jumps around together. There's no water. Hey [Music] [Music] It's
about time.
[Music]
Left  Enter from the
right to collect. It's
okay, you can go right.
[Music]
Subaru Cap
Sorry
[Music]
OkOkOk  Is the
rain okay? I'm
practicing.
[Laughs] The
characters are okay, too.
Wow, Matsu Muto is already
finished in red. He's a
red demon.
[Music] I don't like it. [Music]
Always be serious. Hey, die,
die.  Die, do your best. I
want you to relax and have fun.
[Music] Having
fun is the best.
[Music]
Mel and the others should go here
Subaru-chan, I'm on the wrong infection channel, so
please tell me what you're going to do.This is
where it fell.It
's streaming, it's
streaming.  I'm
practicing the relay,
but Chiara-chan and Ame-chan are also doing well. It's
scary. Just a little
more. Just a little more. Hey, please tell me if it's
okay. I don't want to go around. It's
making me nervous.
[Music]
[Applause]
Everyone now delay relay
practice practice no
[Music] - Do you
want to do it like a man?
[Music]
[Music] [Music] [Applause]
[  [Music]
[Applause] It's
just practice.
This is
good.
Too bad. [Music] Okay, here we go.
Ta  You're
moving and swimming, but it's amazing
[Music]
On the contrary,
stop being nervous
[Applause]
Freeze power
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
No mistakes
[Music]
Ok, then the
yellow one  Hey, let's go and support you.
[Music] It
looks like you're being interviewed. It's so popular.
Maybe it's okay if you include your voice. That's why.
What's going on?
What's
going on? What's going on? What's going on? What's going on?  I guess it's
because of the frame that I can hear.
[Music]
Thank you, thank you.
[Music] I don't
think you can hear me, but
yes, it's too scary. It's
scary. [
Music] Yes, yes.
When I can't run, I stay asleep. I take a little
detour.  It'll be dangerous if I do it, you
idiot. I think it's
better if I do it. It's scary.
Isn't it normal?
[Music] It's
scary.
Stick to the wall and
do your best.
Countdown.
OK, let's eat right around the beginning.
[Music]
Ah, it
certainly feels like there's no sound, but the
operation sounds are right, like I can hear them.
Eh, there's a lot of light. Even
when I go to bed, it's a little dull. Maybe it's
just that there's no BGM.
Everyone has started. Huh,
hasn't it started? There's
definitely no sound. I
forgot about Peko-chan's BGM. There
's probably no studio sound. I
forgot.
[Music]
[Music]  I can
hear your voice,
it's so deep
[Music] I think it's
Nina's number 3, but it
's a nice cat. This might be a one-shot.
Everyone is here.
[Music]
Mental Physical Punsion is 2 Peko right now.
What's going on?
[Music]  [Music]
[Music]
That's not good at all, this is it. It's just a cat. I
can't
do my best. I want you to do your
best. Yeah, do your best, do your best. Do your best. I'll
support you.
When will it start? When will
it start?
That's right.
This is the time when I'm most nervous.
When I'm waiting.
Stop texting me. It's
hard to kill someone.
[Music] That's it.
Congratulations.
[Music]
Which camp is this?
Good luck!
[Music]
[Applause] I'm going to do
this. I
'm going to go down. I'm going to
go up. I
'm going to beat everyone.  It's so
close, stop being so in love, really
in love, I'm
done with one more
Boss Boss
[Music]
[Music] Ah, it's
here, it's here, it's here
[Music]
Eh, don't call out to me, okay?
Let's try to be nice. I'm calm.
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause
] [
Music]
[Music] [Music] [
Applause] [
Music] [
Music] [Music]
[Applause]
[Music] The
team has separated properly.
It's a difficult place here Umai Matsuri Senpai is a bit of an enemy Lie OK I'm being shot I'm Matsui Senpai and it's almost over Nice Nice Okay, one more one has come down and two more to go Thank you for sending it to me It's a start This might be the end  Hey
[Music]
OK, let's go. I have to
run. I
want
it to explode. I have to.
[Music]
Good luck,
Uncle Cree Party.
It's the
last frame of the Creeper.
[Music]  I'm
really getting wet, it's stinging pretty
hard. It's
raining a lot from above.
No, but the movement was really good. It
's actually number 1. It's
actually number 1,
but
it's the best.
[Music] That's
true.
[Laughs]
Forgive me, I understand.
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] I
think I was there, but those
green guys killed me.
[Music]
Well, give me a little time.
[Laughter]
Congratulations on the unexpected result.
Thank you.
[Music] Thank you. [Music]
Thank you!
[Music] Thank
you very much. Next time, Begorra is in trouble. The
Red Team's
interview is also terrible. It's like the one
with the red hair, isn't it?
Enemy  I had it, so I didn't like
it. That's right, all three of them were really good at
it. It was faster than any other cheese. Seriously, it was the
fastest one, so I did it.
It was really crazy, it was amazing.
[Music]
Okay, I'll go back to the next one. Wait a minute, then I'll say it. I wish I could go back.
Hey, the
interview is over, can I come back? I'm going to go back to the
main topic.
[Music]
Yeah,
[Applause]
[Music]
But you've given it your all so far, so no
matter what your limits are, all you have to do is give it your all.
Please.  It
can be done here. Where can it
be announced?
So, thank you for the replay video.
[Music]
[Music
] Here it is. [Music]
Do you feel like you've got a complete plot twist?
[Music]
Most importantly, you're being eaten by that creeper that's being eaten by that creeper.  That's
what they say
[Music] I was
thinking, ``It
's faster on the left.'' Everybody just
walk straight. Let's walk outside. It's no good. The only thing we
can do is cut while practicing. [
Music]
[Music]
Please go ahead! I have some tools
left over. It's
great.
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
And it's amazing.  I'm
looking forward to seeing what will happen.The points will be distributed as 30 points for 1st place and
20 points for 2nd place.Let's
have everyone prepare a little bit.
[Music]
Wow, you're really nervous.
[Music] Please enter
after you finish your distance
[Music]
[Applause] [Music
]
[Music]
[Laughter]
Subaru-senpai kept the camera on until halfway.  I'm a girl who wants to do it,
so I
understand that you have to do your best.
[Music]
Thank you very much.
The third runner is a
red-haired crazy girl wearing
rental physical fashion.
And, oh, that's a
picture of the red team, and of the white team.
Reine and the other group are here.
Senpai
[Music]
And the golden group is Ozora Subaru.
[Applause]
I'm looking forward to it! [
Music]
Are you lined up properly?
[Music]
Sorry, I said it first.  Tokimasu It's
okay, it's okay,
it's okay It's okay to be the last event in the 2nd year of the Senbatsu.What do you
think about the red team?  It
feels like that character runs twice in the chat or something.
Because I've been called.
Yellow team order.
Kiara Heart. Muna
Pecola. It's
okay, it's okay. OkOk.
[Music]
[Music] [
Applause] [Music]
[Laughter]
[Music]  ]
[Music]
What do you think? Shaka
Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Shaka Sha For some reason, it
overlaps with Marine It
seems a bit like that
[Music]
Oh yeah.
Yeah, do your best. It's okay. I'm confident.
Don't wait. The
others?
[Applause] Hey, I'm about to
puke. It's
okay. Are you okay?
Let's sabotage the other person.
[Music]
I think
[Laughter]
[Applause]
There's a lot of meat.  No, there aren't too many.
What do you mean
? Just give me some support. You can do it. It's a quilt.
[Music]
Yes, so do your best.
Shiro and everyone else.
[Music]
[Music]  This is the
last event, so please tell us how you feel now.
Mental Musical Pension
[Applause]
[Music]
[Music] I
feel like I don't really know what's going on.
So, Akihara, what do you think? You've been
practicing too much.
[Music] It
's okay.
[Music]
That's right.
Just do your best. I feel like
throwing up, but no matter what the outcome is, I'm
going to have fun with everyone in front of me and have fun.  I'd
like to do that.
[Music]
[Applause]
What do you think of Pekona, the leader of Ng?
Yellow and yellow mobs were on a good ride, and
the first half was really good too. It's
possible for yellow to win, everyone.
[  [Laughter]
[Music]
[Music] I'm
sorry, but could you please enter again
? I'm really sorry
[Music]
[Laughter]
Well,
Subaru's spirit is too strong and it got to that point.
So, we're having a rehearsal. I'm so
excited.
[Music]
[Music] The
sports day venue was so excited
[Music] I
pressed the
other button. I'm entering.
[Music]
Please line up.
Please be
quiet. Please be quiet. Name.
Nekore, that's
good, that's good.
Thank you very much.  Do you want to do that
?
[Music]
Thank you
[Music] Hello, it's
okay. Hello,
thank you.
Hello. Is everyone OK to enter? Yes, okay.
Well then, I think it's time to start. [
Applause]
[Music]
It's okay for cats to enter.  Yes, it looks
like it's okay. I'd like to check with the management,
but it's
not there.
[Music]
[Music] Let's
have them do it for you.
[Applause]
[Music]
Let's go to the last two years of the Senbatsu. Let's
start
[Music]
Okay, okay, okay [
Music] It's good,
right?
[Music]
[Applause] [
Music] [Applause] [Music]
[Music]
[Applause]
[  [Music]
[Music]
[Applause]
[Applause] [Music] [
Applause] Let's
go to track and field. It's going to be a little
heavy. We
can
go!
[Music] [
Music] [Music] [Applause]
Music] [
Music]
[Applause  ]
[music]
[Music]
[Music] I
get the impression that you practiced nice.
[Music] It's an
interview.
Most of the time, I'm
crying. I'm so happy.
[Music]
Congratulations! Congratulations! [Music]  [
Music]
And then, about the NEETs who finished in the same place
[Music]
How was
it? Some of you were like that too.
Until the very end, we lined up and crossed the finish line without giving up,
so it
was really hot.
[Music]
Hello, congratulations, congratulations. Please
look forward to the final score.
[Music]
Yellow team, Okay, I
'd like to go listen to it. The last one is yellow.
Let's
go. Everyone,
[Music]
Thank you.
I think it's amazing that we were able to catch up and finish in the same race.
[Music]
Everyone was passing the baton.
Everyone ran really well.
So, in the end, I gave it my all.  Well, let's eat already
Thank you for being nice
[Music]
Thank you
Okay, so this is more than just an interview.
Now that the results have been announced,
all the planes are finished, so I'd
like to hold a closing ceremony.
Okay. [Applause] That's
why.
To everyone,
yes, this is the first half of the group.First of all, let's
all gather together.Let's have a closing ceremony.Yes,
please, please, yes, that horse
was over there.
[Music]
Yes,
sports day.
Subaru Ozora, the executive committee member, has gone
to the contestant channel.
Thank
you for your hard work. Thank you very much. I feel
lonely. That's right.
[Music] I
don't feel like it's over. It's been so
long.  It's been
really, really smooth this year.
[Music] I
think it was a pretty great match. Thank you for all the games.
Everyone worked really hard. Very smooth.  I'm
sorry I made you worry, but thank you very much.
[Music]
[Laughter]
So now that we're all here, we
'd like to hold the closing ceremony here.
[Music]
[Laughter]
So, yes.
So, I wonder if everyone's voices can be heard at the closing ceremony. My position [Music] Now, we'll be holding the closing ceremony. [Music] So, first of all, I'd like to
ask Subaru Ozora to give his correct greeting.
Thank you,
everyone, for today.  It
was fun!
[Music]
[Music] I
think it's because of the preparation. It was a
great sports day. Subaru had fun too. Thank you
very much. Thank you for your hard work.
That's why I said yes.
Thank you for your greetings. Thank
you. Now for the final details.  Announcement
[Music]
Hey
Well, let's start with the announcement of the last digit. First of all, let's see how the
red hair is laid down. If it's going to be all, then it's
all going to be out.
Sorry, let's go.  The
last digit of the red-haired, white, and TN teams
is right.
[Music] Well, I guess it's
not my fault.
[Music] We
might win, so let's
do a little something to see if we can win.
[Laughter] [Laughter]
[Music]
[Laughter] What is the
Red Team?
Cycling  The result was a twist.
[Music]
[Applause]
Thank you very much
[Music]
- You're welcome.
This concludes the Live Sports Day 2022.
[Music] Well
then,
let's all get together. Please take your food here or there,
but there's a nice line right now, so let's just stay like
this. If we get everyone
together, we'll take a
photo.
[Music]
Yay,
[Applause]
Even if we don't have to.  I'm a
Mackinkeen at heart, so that's what I mean.But
seriously, people were really excited about yellow.
[Music]
[Applause]
Let's put this to good use next time, next year.
[Music]
But where should I be
? It's reflected. All I have to do is
face
forward. Look forward. A little above me, maybe a little above me. That
red guy. He was from the Red team.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
[Music]  ] In
the
morning, we will have a morning assembly at the dais.
Cool.
Tiara's English is cool.
By the way, everyone used the rest room. Please
use it.
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] [
Music]
That's not a suspicious person.
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
Yes, thank you to the person who was in charge of that camera in the second half.
Thank you very much
[Music]