[Music]
I'm tired of the same song every day
like it's on repeat I need a risky
break oh
honey the night is calling don't need a
steady
on can you make it
origal take me away like it's just a two
of us I'm
ready do you feel the music
baby maybe underneath St like I'm alive
move my to something new I don't need no
drinks tonight
[Music]
so robotic so
emotionless but then I see you across
the Dan FL so now honey follow me I need
a feeling r
something to keep me up all
night don't look away now it's just a
two I'm
ready do you feel the
[Music]
music
bab me the drop light come alive move my
through something new I don't need no
drinks tonight
[Music]
in got
Shin Mak me wild don't's watching
baby
meath moving my to something new
[Music]
oh wait wait wait that's the
H haven't seen that menu in a while I
mean haven't shown it to you in a while
oopsie k
k
hello ah oh why is my my voice feels
kind of raspy what's
wrong dad opening this not the first
time I heard that remix but
she this the first I'm in a
while what two hats yeah I F today cuz
I'm revealing a new
outfit Jus this
once are you hearing the fite uh
instrumental damn that was so fire that
remix is so fire holy
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] ADM let's go
[Music]
right yeah it was kind of like aichi
Vibes for real for
real it set the mood yeah wow
okay uh I have
a unfortunate message I mean it's like
whatever it's just for me like
unfortunate because I wanted to do a
gimmick for the
[Music]
stream but I think my trackers my fredie
trackers are dead some of them I don't
it's weird I'll explain to you if you
want to because now we have to stall
anyway because my gimmick isn't working
out we'll just have a normal classic
outfit reveal with no like extra cool
ideas oh okay we're even we're even
still crashing like since
Yesterday since Yesterday the app has
been not working well it's because they
put without a new a new update
but yeah I think that's why oh well I'll
just continue restarting it again and
again and again and again that's okay so
how you guys
doing it's new outfit
time yo oh sorry my hats went away
because I did something are you sad does
that make you sad here you're
back k
you guys don't have to wear workout
clothes okay you don't have to wear it
anymore you can take it off and just sit
here naked
instead but yeah uh where do I start
uh okay I'll I'll explain to you what my
gimmick was was going to be and why it's
not working okay and then we'll go I'll
show you I'll show you the Polaroids and
then we'll look at some predictions and
then I'll show you the
stuff is that an order yes get naked
chickens or
else yeah so what was I going to start
with oh yeah the gimick I wanted to do I
mean you could expect it already cuz I'm
talking about 3D and I told you guys to
uh get dressed into workout
clothes uh I was going to do like a
aerobics
routine wava
aerobics I had a whole like choreography
setup I like watched aerobic videos from
the80s to get inspired what kind of
moves they do and then I made my own
Coro it was like an 8 minute uh kind
short you know because like just a small
aerobic
version yeah 8 Minute uh routine I made
an 8 minute routine I made myself a
whole video to like remind myself what I
was going to
do but it's okay I can still make a
wobic video like later on whenever my
trackers are going to work
again yeah as a standalone video yeah I
was thinking so too I'll just do it as a
standalone video and maybe I don't know
maybe I'll even commission like a a an
like a low poy or like a small version
of the new outfit as a 3D model like a
smaller lowbudget version I don't know I
was just going to do it in in my normal
3D eh what Rob aerobics aerobics what H
aob what am I saying it wrong I said
aerobics a I don't I don't [\h__\h]
know doesn't matter row like rope aerob
aerobic a
aerobics
aob
[Music]
arobics whatever W
arobics you're confusing me you're just
making it
[Music]
worse let me take a candy before we
continue my room is like my office room
is so [\h__\h] in terms of air even though
I've been airing it out the whole
day oh thank you for the membership
gift okay so I was going to dance in 3D
do like a aerobics routine 80s with 80s
music and all that I got some audio
stock bgms to uh fit you know I I I
looked for the best ones that give an
aerobics
Vibe I put it all together I made a
routine of
choreography and it was going to be fun
you guys were supposed to follow along I
even thought about like how to like
yell uh
motivating phrases and words and
describe each move
and yeah
[Music]
I'm just going to do it in a normal way
instead and the the aerobics routine
will be later on in when when this stuff
works again uh but yeah I think so
basically
yesterday I think yesterday I already
looked at the trackers and I noticed
some of
them won't turn on and I thought well
it's probably because I need to charge
them then today uh a couple of hours ago
usually you can do a a good full charge
maybe in 1 hour but a couple hours ago I
connected every single one it's like
like 20 trackers or so I connected every
single one and I noticed the moment I
connected them some of them you know
they already start blinking and some of
them I had to turn on with the button
there's a button on them um and then
they started blinking some of them
wouldn't turn on some of them wouldn't
start blinking when I pushed the button
it would blink once and then die
immediately and I thought okay let's
just like let it sit there let it be
charged maybe it will be fine later then
I checked again later and it was still
not working so I was hoping that
maybe maybe there's something else maybe
yeah I was I was also trying to
reconnect the cables and all that of
course like switch the connecting cables
from the ones that were able to charge
to the ones that seemingly are not able
to charge and even then like it it's not
the cable that seems to be in the
wrong some were charging some just were
dead from the get-go seemingly and even
when I uh plugged in the cables that
were able to charge
others those in particular were not able
to charge still even with other cables
and they are all like this one big pack
of cabl
specifically um made for for charging
these
trackers thanks for all the membership
gifts
yay so I think something's wrong with
the tracker battery like some of them
like free three of them or so but the
problem is if one tracker isn't
working the whole setup doesn't
work uh so yeah I don't
know I don't know I asked uh really last
minute I asked Kano cuz Kan uses the
same stuff if he knows what this means
when you push the button and it just
like dies immediately and he said after
hearing all my explanations what I tried
already that yeah something seems
wrong but how how can it already how can
they already die I haven't been using
them that
much oh well so that's that um that's
okay that's okay we can just do a normal
outfit reveal that's fine now let me
show you I think you've been waiting for
the Polaroids I've organized
some um limited time limited edition
Polaroid as you remember guys sometimes
the Wawa uh gives you guys Polaroids to
choose in case you want to send a Super
Chat uh of a certain color you can
choose um you can choose a a Polaroid
and I'll sign it and put your name on it
and then you have a nice Polaroid of us
together and you can print it out if you
want to but uh I've been doing that
several times now for special occasions
and I thought this is a nice occasion um
it's specifically fite
them so do you want to see the menu cuz
you already have been sending some super
chats but you did not know what you've
been sending super chats for here it
is Fever Night full aoid uh I feel bad
if I charge too much so it's just a pink
Super Chat uh giv you choose uh one of
these we have um a a DJ chicken yeah DJ
chicken we have a aerobics workout
chicken yeah perfect and we have a
dancing disco go chicken in a nice uh
what kind what what do what do you call
this kind of
suit is this an 80s suit I don't know
it's a shirt I'm not
sure very very laser suit oh it has a
name like that laser suit I've never
heard that
before and then we have a a a cool
stylish sunglasses chicken taking a a
selfie himself uh with a a flip
phone and all of them with a fever KN
night frame yeah so oh thank you yeah
you guys waited to actually choose uh
the one that you
want some people just were like whatever
wa just give me whichever you think is
good I think you can trust me because
all of these are good but if you have a
a preference and you already sent like a
super chat to say whatever you can still
send like a smaller Super Chat maybe and
tell me in a in a green or whatever oh
actually I want this one after all
[Music]
yeah so this is at least one special
thing that worked out thank you Duma for
uh preparing these kind of last minute a
couple days ago I I asked I was like M
can I have some faite fed H polars
please
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah oh wow so many
orders coming in thank you thank you
which one's very which one's the most
popular right
now are they four 2 two 4 two I saw some
one two
three maybe two and four are the most
popular I mean the two is like very very
adorable
M oh three four
1 now it seems
relatively well balanced wow thank you
for your red super chat
too uh one po of your choice okay you're
leaving it to me all right even though
you have this menu it's because there's
the choices are too good right you
couldn't make a
decision thank you guys so much thank
you for the support so the Wawa me I
have for released a song in case like it
would be so sad if you not aware of
fever night if you're one of of the
newer um viewers if you joined maybe one
or two years ago even then you were not
here when fite
released and maybe you never heard it
before so I thought I should sing it for
you because this whole stream and the
outfit is fever not themed
so maybe that is at least one good
replacement I mean i s it recently at
offy
but why not sing it again right
[Music]
uh Fe let's get the feite lyrics feite
lyrics Takashi
Ki thanks
Google when was this song
released when was this released 2020 may
may 2022
right and then it also became part of
the POV
album May 22 oh right before D me oo May
2022 that's yeah that's 2 years ago 2
years and one month
[Music]
ago I have a fruit candy in my mouth but
I think I can sing
anyways I think I'll be
fine I've done this before I've sang
with a fro candy in my mouth before or
should I no
I Sprint it
out thank you guys for Super Chat W
thank
you okay I I'll spread it
out okay I I'll I'll take a new one
later if I need one Gul no I'm not going
to that's it was still like pretty big
I'm going to choke if I no anyway let's
not say things that people can take out
of context I ready for the fite
rendition of today's present
Wawa sing along if you know the song
[Music]
hi hi hi
hi I'm tired of the same song every day
like it's on repeat I need a risky
breakdown oh
honey the night is falling don't need a
steady simple
Mel can you make it orig
no take me away like it's just for two
of us I'm
ready do you feel the music
Baby meet me underneath the straw
light move my feet to something new I
don't need drinks tonight
me dancing it R through me let this you
s take over me
D let's go chicken
DJ
wow oh
yeah oh oh he did that he just did
that lately I'm dancing alone so robotic
so
emotionless but then I see you I'll cry
dance floor so now hone follow me I need
aing
red oh something to keep me up all
night don't look away now it's just a
two of us
ready do you feel the music with me baby
underneath come alive move my feet to
something you I don't need no drink
tonight give me me dancing now is rap
[Music]
time you moving you got me shining
glowing like a pris that makes me wild
don't care who's watching so
baby make me underneath the straw light
come moving my feet to something so I
don't need no drinks tonight give me
dance me dancing feel it
right I don't need drinks
tonight
it
baby can we dance until the dayl like
crazy
about the sound I'm making of you
[Music]
yay thank you you guys are dancing in
those white Elvis suits let's
go thank you thank you thank you so that
was fever Knight fever Knight was my
third original single I think
so and M this MV I I really really still
to this day love it so much it's like I
think maybe my fav one of my favorite
together with heart Challenger my one of
my favorite non 3D mvs that I did or was
the fourth oh ah
okay because why was it my favorite
because Mone Drew so so so so so much
art back then for the music video video
which made it just yeah so aesthetically
pleasing thank you guys for still
sending polar art requests by the way
thank
you um yeah the art was amazing and it
was a whole vibe like everything
everything was just perfect yeah so ah
yeah right we got to talk about the
artist too so here let's let's segue
into the topic of the artist that is
involved this
time and so okay this outfit is heavily
heavily heavily inspired by um let me
try to find their Twitter while I'm
talking cuz I what was it again the
Twitter
eh wait I'm I'm actually I can't
multitask JMA are you watching
JMA oh Gemma is probably
offline ah the Mone ah the Mone yeah
uh ah she is she's online
yay
okay
so uh
Mone uh originally designed very very
cute beautiful outfits for fevera night
and um for the longest time I was
wondering man all these cute outfits not
just for fever night but like other
stuff like Sparks and so on wouldn't it
be nice to have these as actual life Tod
outfits and when I was thinking about
what can I do for this next
outfit I for some reason just thought it
is time it is time and I want to do a
fite outfit because I feel like you know
it has like a sporty Vibe and I don't
have um a sporty outfit yet I would say
and it can also kind of be seen as
something somewhat
casual and I just think it's like super
interesting um now I did uh not go with
like myone as the actual artist to draw
the uh life Tod outfit version of it
because um like I think the art style
would not have matched with the base of
me so we found U you know I chose
different artist because for a while
now for a while now we've been we've
been choosing uh different artists to
handle my new outfits uh for several
reasons but this has been resulting in
uh you know like different different
nice Vibes you know every every outfit
is a a fresh
surprise you never know what to expect
yeah yeah every Wawa is a new
WWA but uh it was still heavily inspired
heavily inspired by heavily heavily
inspired by uh the music video
so it's I mean there were several
outfits in the music video too but it's
well yeah it's like very very very close
to that he heavily he heavily yeah
Heavenly H okay wait Jemma is still
searching so let me just for now show
you guys let's go through the
predictions isan MO konato
let's check it out let's check out some
predictions so I think it was pretty
obvious that it was like what kind of
clothing it is but some people seem to
purposefully still go into a different
direction of what's most likely thank
you for
that oh let's start with I don't know
let's start with uh this one
oops what did I just move this one this
one is from uh I don't know how to
pronounce the name it's YK
o25 it's so cute it's so
girly I love that the leotard is like
sparkly and I did
not think about the fact that these also
come in these shapes with a big window
tummy window breast
window
I I didn't know that
man now I'm kind of feeling like we
should have done a leotard like
that it's beautiful I love the Sparkles
like I can IM imagine I can imagine I
can I can make the image in my head of
the
fabric and I like that you added like a
headband of the same fabric and the way
that it's like pushing the bangs back
and up oh I can totally like Vision
visualize this like in my
head but I don't have to because it's
right in front of me it's beautiful it's
so
cute a short hair yeah that this is a
question many people are like H is it
short hair or is it a
like a ponytail we'll see we'll see but
yeah this is beautiful I really like it
I like the the combination of the white
tights with the pink uh sparkly leotard
that is
definitely very soft kind of gentle
girly m80s aerobics
clothing yes absolutely nailed the
vibe 10 out of
God I love the 80s yeah hell yeah
honestly
until to this day I still am not really
sure like is it is it really 80s or is
it also partially 70s because if I look
up
70s like workout clothing or so or
aerobics this also comes up this kind of
style could it be like mix stories in
really 80s what do you
think anybody who who knows who was
alive during the 80s how old is someone
who was alive during the 80s 60
40 40 right 40ish
50ish but you would have been a baby
so sorry I immediately corrected
myself I immediately IED
myself ah it's both late 70s and early
okay okay that's what it comes up for
both I was never sure what to name it
because of
that now hold on I learned something new
okay let's look at the next
one next
one uh oh this one oh it's a j J fif
change to
jpeg Works jpeg always works so this one
definitely still has that 80s Vibe right
thanks I think a big a big 80s m point
is the hoop earrings to me to me I was
like I need hoop earrings you know so
the hoop earrings put some hoop earrings
on and wear anything else with the hoop
earrings you're giving 80s
Vibes yeah I love the skirt I don't I I
I don't know if that actually really
works with the silhouette that I gave
you guys but whatever it doesn't matter
cuz I like seeing the skirt version very
much and the chains you added around it
and the belt with the shirt tucked in
all of that I think is very 80s very
very very
80s I do think that you know the way
these clothes are styled like a a bulky
sweater with a big uh colorful belt
tucked tucked the sweater in have it
highwaisted and then a jeans or
something else but I think it's supposed
to be jeans skirt M tight one too tight
skirts I think were're very
popular so yeah perfect and this one is
by
rafhael kayi Rafael kagi thank you so
much for your
submission yeah I think I think we all
know that we're going more towards the
leotard uh you
know situation but I like to imagine
that this could have been a
thing thank you very much for
participating on short notice
yeah let's look at another one ooh this
is also
Jif Twitter why must you save pictures
as jith next one is from the
inosi I thought I had to stall a lot but
actually the time is looking good now I
stalled a lot in the beginning I guess
now maybe I even need to hurry who
knows oh oh my mommy is writing to me
about the the time period She says yeah
well she was alive during it I can tell
you that
much oh I wonder if my mommy was wearing
clothes like
these at that
time cuz I think in Austria certainly
this kind of clothing was also like the
80s kind of clothing that we're going
for was also popular I would say Okay so
this one M leotard chick belt check
colorful neon colors check hoop earrings
check what's interesting here is the
head uh ribbon band headband cuz can you
guys see they put my my my badge my
shield badge on there oh cute and chunky
wonky and smoothie are also
represented let's go I'm so happy it's
smoy and chy monkey are in this yeah
thank you for thinking of them they're
very important to me it's a nice touch
nice that you thought of them I think of
them all the time but I didn't think of
them when designing the
outfit but yeah beautiful beautiful also
you still uh kept the the uh
feathers but made them kind of shorter
now I will say we've had this with with
the fancy outfit I think the fancy dress
uh no not the fancy dress which one was
it I have a different outfit that
doesn't have my feathers are a kimono
the kimono right the
kimono that's where like I was also like
hook you know what we're implying with
this that we can rip out my feathers I
don't want to imply that I don't want
people to think that it should not be
Canon um now because of the hoop
earrings that I really wanted you may
not see my feathers in this outfit uh
but that that's just an exception okay
they're like I don't know hidden away
somehow tucked away okay they're just
tucked away whatever but I guess we
could have made them shorter like this I
I did ask like oh can we have like both
somehow or will it look stupid but I
think it would have looked maybe a
little bit like it would have been
cluttered I don't
know so yeah they're not going to be
there they're just tucked away yeah but
don't think about it too
much I found however this uh this was by
the inoi thank you for your submission I
found one submission that had a good
solution solution to that that I liked
did I save
it uh
a is it this one is it this one no it's
not this one maybe I can't find it we'll
we'll see if we'll still find it and
this submission is by turquoise
table oh that is quite the V window
she I am a vtuber after
all not this kind of YouTuber huh oh
yeah that's what I am yeah I I love that
it's a
onesie I love the onesie idea I think we
had a onesie in the music video
too uh some kind of onesie I don't know
if you couldn't call this a onesie too
it's a onesie
right these kind of onesies I think
they're also very 80s yeah beautiful and
the cut I mean I don't know if they
would have always gone this deep with
their V
Cuts back in the day maybe not this deep
but I it looks gorgeous if you have a
nice chest to show then let's show
it yeah I like it very much thank you
for the
submission man man man I wish I could
have made all of the fite outfits into
the live
Tod you know next
up um yeah thank you for purposefully
going in a direction that is very
unlikely com com
[Music]
com uh yeah um this is not what it's
going to
be a few people on Twitter I think
especially Japanese Bros were saying oh
I for a second I thought it was a
silhouette for a new outfit for pekora
Senpai because of the the ribbon and I
guess it could be a bunny suit because
leotard you know the shape I don't I
don't know um I guess it could have been
I don't know maybe the silhouette can
remind you of that uh good
try H but yeah no unfortunate thank you
Ido for an interest thing submission
certainly unique
yeah and
next is from Newton
art a
cute I love this kind of
sweater wait let me here the edges of
this sweater I love that I don't know
what you call that but I love these kind
of edges on sweaters
yeah and the pattern that you put on the
leotard is very 80s or 70s or even 60s I
don't know but yes yes I like it very
much thank you for your submission newon
art and even with a heart for
kfp on the chest can you see it cute and
I also see you went for the the short
hair version we'll see I think all maybe
most people went
for short hair so far might be wrong but
that's what I'm getting so
far thank you thank you thank you thank
you I feel like I have to hurry up now
so I'm hurrying a little
bit uh
next Exile Eden Eden
Exile has also given it a try and also
very
purposefully decided to go into an
unlikely
Direction and I so I think this is
supposed to be like a ninja is design
right
maybe I think I think that's uh what
what you were going for that's red it is
red it kind of like a maybe it is is
like a cyber cyber ninja
h no
well yeah I like it but it's not not
where we're
going thank you D Eden Exile also helped
out with the background there is going
to be a special background just for the
outfit reveal so thank you so much for
working so hard on
[Music]
that let's show you uh the next one how
about how about oh this this one I
showed this one I showed this one I
showed ah next
one and see
poooo wow you put a lot of effort into
this one
damn damn an ace pilot K I'm a
pilot W like you even put all those
symbols there and badges on the jacket
on the shield necklace
and my feathers are kind of incorporated
into the
headband damn my even my knees are
protected
nicely and
pilot thank you wow I even have a
microphone I just noticed
W cool maybe one day I will become a
pilot maybe one day I like what you did
with that first symbol on the top left
that's also on the jacket I like that
one that's really cool I should buy it
off of
you thank you for participating c pooo s
e a p p thank you appreciate
it and
[Music]
next let's let's
so sorry I'm just changing Jeff fifs to
jpegs
oops this one is from
Atomic
marshmallow wow this also looks like you
put a lot of effort on it how did how
did you guys do it in such a short
time how how do you do
it I love the colors I love how the
sweater is like layered like on top of
each other I don't know how to say it
and it's also not um what's the word I
can't say any words it's not centered
it's off center I love
it yeah and oh oh okay I have to like
zoom into that do you guys
see those Shadows around the
crotch ooh that's good those Shadows M
Anatomy an
anatomy oh and you also did for put the
feathers in there
m not giving up on the feathers I
see my feathers are fful to you m yeah I
love it really really nice I feel like
it gives me a little bit of a Spacey
Vibe maybe it's the colors and the I
think it's the because it's a a
turtleneck and then the pattern on the
on the blue leotard something about this
gives me a Spacey
Vibe H he 80s 80s but in space is what
I'm
feeling yeah thank you for this
anatomically correct
wowwa very much appreciate it and I have
two more and then y time is really
ticking oh my
God this one is from taku taku you know
the one who draws GAA a lot in really
cute small forms so maybe that's why you
you were inspired by GAA and maybe
that's why you gave me no bangs no
headbangs no hairbangs I mean uh exposed
forehead feels very
embarrassing uh but I like you also went
you know in into a kind of um different
direction than other people than most
people giving me a black leather jacket
like a
biker yeah and also some nice crotch
Shadows again thank
you although I'd rather not have my head
forehead
exposed so that's probably not happening
but not today not in the close Fe future
but yeah it it's um
those tights they look really uh very
thin
and almost sefr I don't
know dangerous tight dangerous get up
thank you so much for
participating and the last one the last
one I'm going to show I'm showing last
because it's just
too it gets really freaking similar to
what you're actually going to see
probably because this looks also very
similar to what you see in the music
video oh it's big yeah this is beautiful
thank you s r r e w
E5 for this beautiful beautiful fever
Knight W yeah it looks pretty much I
think pretty pretty much perfectly like
the one in the music
video Perfect 10 out of
10 thank you for absolutely nailing it
but it it looks like you also went for a
short hair cut huh
right looks to me like a short haircut
no we'll see about it thank you
guys sorry I had to kill a fly I think
it I think I got
it okay now it's time to reveal the
artist oh my God I only have like 9
minutes left he
yo hey
yo okay I hope I can show this I it'll
be fine should be
fine I'll show you because it's nice to
have a
visualization I'll show you a screenshot
of their Twitter just it's just nice to
see something so you can maybe maybe
you're are like oh this artist
[Music]
skle so this new artist is different
from Hook Papa different from who
originally drew me
okay are you
ready maybe you know maybe you're not
don't I I think I teased before to
members that it's an artist that was in
charge of like drawing something for a
game I played before on
stream yeah or a game series and you
guys were like already guessing who
could it be back
then it's this artist Yos
yos for taking the time to working
really hard on this outfit what do you
mean you knew it there were many choices
because this person worked for Fire
Emblem Heroes yeah that's where you
maybe have seen it before that's why I
was fire I didn't play fireemblem Heroes
but still you know close
enough and um also some other stuff
they've been working on is character
design for
yi and
Y and aain and other stuff yeah and they
have a really beautiful art style
is she s
this yeah amazing vup
yeah a lot of amazing things
and yeah a kns of azour
mhm yeah very talented artist that I
have
chosen yeah I feel like I wonder if I
would have given them like not such
a m
exact theme like I want to have this and
this and this you know I wonder what
they would have done with more freedom
you know kind of would would have liked
to see that too but oh my God we're
running out of time so and we're going
to move to the room that I have prepared
today
[Music]
perfectly timed absolutely perfectly
timed
okay let me move out of the way for now
for a
moment yay it's a fever night aerobics
themed Background by Eden Exile thank
you for working on this there's some
dead looking chickens over there there's
these like Steppy thingies that you step
on and then you step down and you step
on and you step down and so on there's a
super cool neon logo uh of kfp there
like it's my dance studio yeah here you
can take a phone number for learning to
dance at kfb dance school even though
you're already there I
think
yeah really cool I love it so much I
love it it's so cool and this is where
I'm going to reveal my outfit to you
guys
so are you ready let's get started I
can't believe I've already we're already
like an hour in I can't believe
it ah one thing I want to
say
before I show you
everything
um there is
an alternate skirt version of
this but I will not reveal it today I
think because of many reasons there will
be like a a
different like an accessory reveal so to
say at another time for now I'll keep
this other version to myself the skirt
already exists but I don't want to I
don't want to reveal it in its current
form basically
okay o getting
ready
o okay I'm in the
full 80s aerobic attire
baby let's begin I'm starting Straight
From Here normally people start from
like here okay let's go slowly slowly
slowly slowly slowly I already saw
it yeah yeah yeah the shoes are so sick
wow they're
beautiful why are my kicks always so
sick I love
them they look so
nice M they look comfortable I like the
straps they're very original oops
okay all right all right all right
slowly we'll be moving down we have cute
loose socks that I can actually also
take off but I think it's nicer this
way socks socks
socks
and we're getting to the knees we're
getting to the knees do you see the
shadow that's like happening when I bent
down wow we see signs of up upgraded uh
life Tod but only part
yeah we have pink leggings pink leggings
pink pink
pink pink and very
[Music]
shiny oh one more thing I wanted to say
really quickly I already mentioned it
like yesterday but I just want to point
out that uh the pose is completely
different for the first time ever
normally the outfits are drawn on top of
the base of the model and the pose
doesn't change but this time my legs and
my arms they're like redrawn from
scratch and put into a new pose that
looks more relaxed so I hope you can pay
attention to
that look how my knees go together and
maybe you can kind of see a five
wobble I don't think I ever had a five
wobble
before jingle jle Wile wiggle
wiggle shiny shiny yeah I I got like so
many different choices of what the
fabric could look like and I went for
this metallic look but there were
actually like uh many different feelings
to this fabric that I could have chosen
but I love I love this very shiny
metallic look the most
yeah oh oh
oh my God it's so
jiggly it's jiggly like
pudding okay now I want you to look at
the butt cheeks can you already
see the butt
cheeks you can see my but cheeks back
there oh yeah by the wait
pink pink so just like the pink super
chats let's go as if I have PL landed
and my fingers are visible and we're
seeing we're seeing some colors
here wow the leotard is becoming visible
hi
G yeah everything is
jiggling I I have to say my you will
have to look closely at the at the
cleavage because it Jiggles more than
usual to very nicely I must say I'm I
actually did not complain about the
jiggle it's good
now look at this wow wow wow I just love
this shininess all all all the folds and
yeah here we're getting we're getting
the leotard now it has a flower pattern
a little bit different from the music
video I
think and the sweater is blue blue blue
blue
oh
oh oh KF logo
that actually looks oh wait did we did I
mm I think I showed it to eat an exile
that's why it's the same as on the wall
I forgot that I did that oh and resting
my arm on my hip by the way that's new
too that's a new
[Music]
pose do you see this like open pattern
on the sleeves yeah very cool and here
come the
jigglypuffs here come the jiggly Puffs
oh my
god oh [\h__\h] okay I'm I'm I'm mesmerized
by it too guys it's it's okay like do
you see wow those look really real like
the I've I've I've I've made um I've had
the pleasure to meet some really big
jigglypuffs uh a few weeks ago that were
like this and I must say this moves
really
realistically
W do you see like this little squeeze on
the side yeah I feel like it Jiggles
there on its own differently and that's
nice now just so you know there is uh
this kind of
variation because it would be tucked
into the skirt and I I'm not going to
reveal to you yet and also there's a
blue tight version but I prefer the pink
one so let's continue with the pink one
wow
wow okay are you ready for the most
exciting part the face although maybe I
can't even say that maybe maybe the most
exciting part is already right
here I hope you're liking it so far
though I hope you're liking it okay here
I go hoop earrings
is it a short hair or a ponytail place
your bets you have five seconds five
four three
two
one
t it's a
ponytail a high
ponytail hi
ponytail hi ponytail how you doing I
love the hoop earrings so
much and my hair we tried to make it
very volumous because I feel like all
the hair in the 80s was very volumous
right so how do you like it
h how do you like it jiggle everything's
jiggling and shaking wo wo wo wo wo wo
wo oh I really like how the Hoops move
move
nice yeah I like this I expect you to
come into my aerobics class see I'm
standing on the let let's stand on the
podest let's do a workout together guys
come to my aerobics class I'm awaiting
you you signed up for it you can't back
down or back back back down
now you signed you signed a contract you
already paid paid for the classes you
got to show up now don't L around I'm
waiting for
you erotics no aerobics not
erotics ER robic I don't know I don't
know how to say
it please come here to my dance studio
dance studio W
robic yay
don't let me wait yeah okay I'm good I'm
good oh oh why is it like this a little
bit cut off there we
go new wa 80s we love the 80s wa in
the80s so in terms of like different
variation I can't I can't really show
you much like there's you know no ribbon
and then there's just switch with the
shirt I kind of want to show you the you
know what
I don't know I I the thing the reason
why I don't want to show you the skirt
is because I originally I just wanted
the skirt to go with
um uh fish
fishnet tights or bare legs and they
said no to it because it would not fit
into the theme
apparently uh but I can get it as an
access accessory for my anniversary
[Music]
so I have to wait until my anniversary
cuz I don't know I feel like it looks a
little bit weird with uh in combination
with the
leggings but that will be almost like a
new
outfit yeah so look forward to that and
let's show you the full body with the
blue version if you want also there's no
socks but better with socks yeah this is
the Blue version but I think even though
the blue works with the ribbon
isn't pink the best yeah it's like a DLC
later on you'll get a DLC for this
[Music]
outfit tight DLC can the top come off no
maybe in the future maybe I can ask for
that
too possibly I'll inquire okay for the
leggings and the top to come off and
then the skirt will go on Blue better
pink best blue
both oh can we have a can we have a pole
please an appalling pole
which which
legings I we need to decide which ones
will be Canon blue
pink for me the pink is Cannon to be
honest for this
outfit for fard I I would say you know
pink should be Cannon but if you prefer
blue you can draw the blue very if you
want to draw fan
artist pink blue I feel like the overall
balance you know it's just wow wow
refreshing oh yeah okay most people say
pink after all but blue can be nice too
yeah blue can be nice
too thank you thank you thank you thank
you the pink stands out more yeah
exactly you know we needed all of these
nice color is implemented and is the
best complete
version well well well well pink
wins yeah thank you thank you so much
guys I'm so happy about the new pose too
I think it looks way more natural in
this pose because if I would have had my
default pose then yeah now I don't think
um it would have looked so cool yeah I'm
so happy about the pose
thank you Yos Yos the artist for this
outfit the new artist for uh yeah
putting so much work and effort into
it and they draw really good boobs right
oh my
god
wow are we all are we focusing on the
same thing
guys if you get naughty then I'll have
to I'll have to do this yeah have to
hide them a little
bit
Yahoo the hair yeah the hair moves
nicely too wow wow it's so
bouncy I love love the ribbon yeah
ribbon is cute too it's not bunny
ears bring back the W don't hide
them
okay okay I like to see it too it's like
so satisfying it's like water it's
liquid they're really soft don't they
look so
soft yeah so this is new waa please draw
the new waa I want to see Fever Night
waa
[Music]
fan
artas water balloons
yes looking forward to it aren't we all
looking forward to
it how can a top even contain them
wouldn't you have liked to see me work
out in this
ehh man 80s workout clothes were a
blessing from Heaven why why is this not
like still a
thing why why is it not a thing this 3D
would be
mental would be nice right would be
nice I'm so happy you like it guys I'm
so
[Music]
happy will it enter your top three of
Wawa
outfits guys what do you
think tell
me we have so many now I have so many
outfits now yes yes
really oh top one number oh really is I
feel like if you see something new just
because it's new and fresh and fresh out
of the oven maybe that's why you're like
oh this is the new number one but maybe
you if you really feel like this even a
month later then then I'll take it
[Music]
wow really enjoy this aesthetic me too
me too yeah I'm so it's not like I'm
going to uh like turn all of my original
songs outfits into life Tod um but I I I
really thought for Fever Night the
aesthetic is just so good and the the
outfit designs that Mama Looney came up
uh with with back then are just Heavenly
so big shout out to mamaon who basically
designed this as well in a
way it it's very similar to the fite
outfit
[Music]
yeah a great combination this is
actually like free artists mixed because
the base my face is hook Papa the
inspiration for the outfit is
mamaloni and the new artist who drew it
is
yosu and then we have the rigger I
actually don't know who rigged this
maybe we'll find out uh later
on come alive moving my
something and now with that I'll say
goodbye I
suppose I think we should keep it short
like compact so people are not scared of
the the amount of hours the vault is
like my8 hours and 9 hour
streams you'll see more of this
beautiful fite laa in the coming week oh
wait wait I have an announcement oh
[\h__\h] I had an
announcement oh
M sent me I think she's watching the
stream or she has been at least for a
moment she sent me um a song from Olivia
Newton John Physical and told me to sing
it in A
Kar and I actually well I did before cuz
I did a' 70s 8s we got to do it again we
got to do a 70s 8s K again I did want to
try again sometime we did it like
sometime last year we did a unarchived
70s 80s K and that was one of the songs
I sang there yeah in fact I did okay
little announcement um you should
already know that this is
[Music]
coming but I'll announce it properly
now and next week on
on oh let me double check the
time let me double check the
time
oh next
week ah and Friday in like American time
but
uh 7 a.m. jst Saturday I think midnight
for me so the night of Friday to
Saturday and we are
[Music]
starting Hol my one block
Minecraft
yay do you like the
[Music]
logo yeah H I've been planning this for
not so long actually I had this idea uh
a few weeks ago that I have always I
always wanted to do one block Minecraft
with Ena um but recently I thought about
it again and then I was like actually we
should just do it as a myth project yeah
and it will start and I don't know what
what the uh American times for it are
but it's midnight wa time midnight from
Friday to Saturday and then Saturday
7:00 a.m. jst is when we start it's the
first but it will be a project that will
um it will take uh a week or two
weeks uh uh 6 p.m. EST there you go 6
p.m. EST for example 3 pm pstd is the
beginning um but it should you know be
happening over the course of several
days on different times we're just
starting this one at this time cuz I
thought you know I'm going to
start late for this one for the sake of
everybody yeah H what does one BL mean
okay one blog Minecraft is a mod for
Minecraft a way of playing Minecraft
where you start out with one block
there's no world you are building the
world one block at a time and the block
that you get is
random uh I think in the beginning you
just stand on one block too right like
in those in the middle of nothing you
stand on one it's like in that way it's
like Sky block block I
guess yeah you stand on like one block
and then you get another block and then
you get another block and you get
another block but it could be any kind
of block it could uh it could be
anything and we do this together and we
try to build our our way through
everything like we try to build a base
we try to you know get armor
and this and that and then our goal is
of course to kill the Ender Dragon
together once again yay it will be quite
the challenge I feel like this is more
hardcore than Hardcore Minecraft when
played normally this this this sounds
pretty hardcore I'm a little bit worried
but we're going to get through it with
teamwork and yeah it'll be a nice
project so please check it out uh the
first stream will be on my channel
only um but then after that everybody
will be like you know allowed to stream
whenever they want they can start a
stream or they can just join someone
else's stream if they're already
streaming and playing one block
Minecraft uh maybe sometimes there will
be someone alone possibly me and then
later joined by others or I'll join
somebody I'll stay up really late or so
um sometimes there might be two people
playing sometimes there might be three
people or four or even five people
playing definitely the beginning and the
finale will be five
people
yeah so because of this my stream times
will be a little bit weird uh while this
is going on but I'll be I'll try to be
like available a lot and online either
mostly during Japanese prime time or
like uh Nosh now starting like now and
then stream for like five six hours or
so like ena's ena's streaming
time something like that would be my
goal so that I can um you know hang out
with the
girls sorry Europe no it's not so bad
for Europe either when I stream during
jst Prime Time m and ena's time slot at
least in the beginning maybe the first
hour or so isn't too bad you know but
the streams will yeah be late later than
usual
yeah yeah I'm going to change my sleep
schedule a little bit for
this I just want to have fun with
everybody I want to I want I want us to
you know find each other in the game I
don't want to play alone you know this
is a group project so I don't want to
play alone obviously I hope that um
we'll be at least in in doubles in pairs
or triples triplets
triplets uh as much as we
can
yeah yeah yeah yeah so first stream on
my channel and then afterwards it's like
whatever Wherever Whenever Wherever we
need to be together I'll be there there
and you'll be here and that's the deal
my
dear myth my beloved indeed I've missed
myth Minecraft collabs yeah we haven't
played with all five of us
together in a long long time years it
has been years
maybe so I really thought it would be
nice to have a a myth only Minecraft
Project because I know you guys miss
like myth projects myth streams and you
know myth has done some collabs here and
there but they're often you know to
promote something or it's just once in
half a year or
so um although although we did that
really nice
k h on my channel uh in March you know
hyping up fest with all five of us that
was
nice yeah yeah yeah that was also not
for promoting anything just saying this
is also not to promote
anything this is just to have
fun well you know it's a little bit
difficult to get all of us together our
time zones are all over the
place
yeah been almost 1.5 hours yeah it's
time for me to go why is Ki so hot right
I know
I'll give you the full body one more
time in case some people just uh joined
us I'm dancing I'm dancing I'm dancing
I'm dancing I'm dancing aerobics
aerobics aerobics
aerobics yeah thank you for watching I'm
going to leave it at that so that it's
not awkward yeah we leave it at High
Point H thank you looking forward to the
fan art and uh Polaroids yeah polar
wordss thank you for uh
sending the super chats I will get to
them ASAP and you'll get another chance
if you missed it one of these days if
you
want and in German we
say oh I love this out oh the more I
look at it today the more I like
it especially in this
room I'll
daning oh yeah eh I should have said
this in the beginning screenshots put
them up on Twitter uh in the uh hashtag
fite is
real F night is real now it's real for
real for
real byebye what's
[Music]
going aerobics AO e r o b i
CS
[Music]
yay oh yeah no stream tomorrow I have a
lot of work to do but you'll get the
schedule tomorrow
[Music]
n