[Music]
so
[Applause]
oh my god
amazing
[Music]
but now we have council so it's the
first almost full collaboration
of hallelujah
[Applause]
[Music]
the discord support today and hopefully
also the viewers support today because
uh today will be a very very passionate
and dangerous and fun and exciting
even yay it's race day baby
yeah yeah
i was like burning rubber yes exactly
and bad drivers that's
but i'll drive you guys nuts
now let's start with
[Music]
hey
hello thank you for having me this is
anja melvisa from hello life i second
generation
thank you everyone i can't wait
again
what's my ikigomi um to not be on the
last last place at least
i'm trying i'm trying hard hmm
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
i read generation one
so my motivation tonight is um to show
you my practice i guess
that's all
[Music]
hi
attention please and favorite rainy from
whole life id generation 2. my goal
today is to be
number one in your heart and also not
that last year
yeah i've heard you were good you and
iris have heard good good good news
about you
wow yeah we had a good practice
yesterday right
[Music]
hello my name is
what's your motivation for today
well
i i want to be at least not on the last
okay but in the middle it's like okay
[Music]
riddle is okay at least not glass
oh okay lucy
[Music]
does it sound like a good thing
yeah okay next up
[Music]
hello hello everyone i'm alejandra from
whole life indonesia and thank you so
much for inviting me to this collab i'm
so happy though i'm so excited they
[Music]
my motivation for today is that i would
like to have fun though although yes i'm
not really confident but let's have fun
all right
that's the most important thing
[Music]
motivation i plan on ranking pop so that
you guys become my bottoms that is my
motivation for today
she wants to be on top i see i don't
know what else is
[Laughter]
we won't be dominated that easily senpai
thank you
and i think wait
all the introductions from id i think i
did
[Music]
let's start with iris
oh yeah hi
it's iris hololive english project hope
v singer here um my goal today is to get
first place victorus
thank you so much for having me here so
i heard that you waited for
yeah
for me to come on my friends we're
literally the last one
[Music]
hello amelia and number one hello live
and detective
today i'm gonna win probably okay
okay okay
okay girl i love the enthusiasm
i heard you only played mario kart so
far in a member's only stream but that's
about it
yeah i won and that one too
oh oh
okay
i see oh then you might be the hidden um
winning choice that the winner
dark horse a wild card player welcome
amazing
[Music]
thank you thank you
um
i'll do my best i think we have a we
have a fiercer competition to be not
last and to be first so i'll do my best
[Music]
i was also
taking this very seriously in her
practice round so a bit scared of you
know
i don't know
i'm still falling off maps it's fine oh
yeah it happens oh kelly joined yes nice
thanks
thank
and you start let's continue with the uh
introduction from cal iop maureen
hello everyone my name is callipe my
parents are still asleep and probably
can't watch the news this morning maury
nice to meet you i'm gonna be talking
about that low because it's a bit early
uh so excuse me for that guys but i'm
very excited just to be here i really
didn't think this was gonna work but
it's working i love it
so fingers crossed
you for joining even though it's such an
early time and kind of uh troublesome
with some setups and all that i'm glad
you're still here and you know what you
being so whispery and calm might be a
good
thing for driving because that way you
might be able to focus more
drifting
while whispering you know
everyone yeah
yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
please
english and i'm kind of sick today and
if you're watching on my side i just
need to say this now
i've had some technical difficulties
very suddenly so i am made of cardboard
i'm sorry please bring well i it was not
my fault it's out of my control right
now so anyways
i'm png tuber domo somebody does a png
tuber let's race today baby i'm the wild
card today
[Applause]
my dust
well you know on the screen there's
there's going to be a lot of things
happening so your viewers should be
looking at the game and not
it's you
i'm curious how close they want to look
at me right guys
[Music]
all right that leaves uh me i think yeah
welcome everyone i wanted to do this
tournament for a long long time uh i
think my viewers have heard me talk
about it since months ago and finally
it's happening uh and i'm very glad to
have all these lovely girls here
together it's the first time we're doing
a tournament like this so i i don't
think anyone has to feel bad about you
know not being so good it's all fine
maybe we'll do it some
more often in the future so please don't
stress yourself out let's just have fun
today
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you for organizing
i think we will go to the roof but
before that let me say thank you uh the
hats and the cards are sponsored by me
no my inna nice
please
[Music]
so cute all right let's uh everyone
switch to the rules image please thank
you
all right okay tournament rules easy
there's not many rules basically uh all
characters all courses are allowed
however
uh if you choose uh please do not choose
random courses please choose a certain
course that you want to actually erase
but if that course has been used before
like if it has actually been chosen
before please do not choose the same
course again already
[Music]
understand
number two items are allowed number
three and we are racing in 150 cc with
no assist everyone please check if you
have turned off your assistant i think
you can check it out pressing
all right i think i'll turn it
if you press
y and select your character at the point
where you select the card you can press
on
plus
the plus button and then when you see
the the three options on the right side
if you press l
uh if there's a
if there's a
sign that says no
then it's uh
auto steering off that's how it's
supposed to be okay
yeah it'll be crushed out exactly the
only way you can ignore yeah
okay okay okay okay
[Laughter]
i also want to quickly let you guys know
um i'm on i'm going to be on like auto
mute this whole time so unless i have
something to say i'm going to be muted
don't worry if i'm a little quiet i'm
still here with you guys in spirit yeah
okay
[Music]
and next row uh oh yeah then there's no
more rules since this is just the system
we're doing the first cup all versus all
big mixer four races each but then we
get uh we mute each other by the way
during the race and just to focus
everyone on what we're driving and then
we get back together and this floor talk
a little bit then we go to the second
cup which is en versus id six versus
yes yes gently we separate each other in
uh the voice channels by team this one
and this one we will actually talk with
one another if you wanna and then we uh
give some comments together again when
we get all back together in the same
channel and then we do the third cup
with random randomly thrown together
teams no he handles id but like all
mixed together naturally beautiful yeah
what's the random
random random we will just like i'll
count down and and then everyone joins
eva voice chat room zero or voiceover
one no who is this whatever
who's the real one that's not who is it
everybody wants to be one
well then we're gonna have to do it
again
those like team cups will basically be
um
like the
as same versus all the difference is
just basically like if you throw items
like reg tails or whatever and there is
a teammate in front of you it will not
go to the teammate obviously it will go
directly to the closest opponent driver
uh that's around you so yeah that's how
that team system works
is everyone ready to get something to
fix who's that
hey
is
[Music]
yourself on discord if someone's not
ready then i will ask you why you're not
ready
[Music]
wait guys how do you wait guys uh how do
you go forward in the game
you push the
a button you can't do that okay yeah
yeah
okay
[Music]
it
we're gonna be muted
i am muted yes you don't see my eye kind
of appearing oh really cool
really cool and um
i don't know what else to say other than
i'll do my best i guess
yeah so there's that
i'll do my best
got all this model
only small though i think i think
was beautiful i think what was better
than this
model that she's using right now
it's so funny
it's so funny oh yeah um
not a lot to use random i will just
close my eyes and
then um
close my eyes there you go sunshine
airport
i don't know if i've ever i've ever been
there before
i'm not sure
[Music]
oh god
my hands are shaking
my hands are shaking i can't do this
i can't do this what is that stage
mario kart stadium
iris switch
oh who is that
oh god
whenever i focus
um i won't be talking
i'll be talking um for too much oh god
i'm doing this again
i don't want to lose to these are senpai
at least
who is that
we keep on doing this but it's fine
[Applause]
okay
that's the same thing with the same five
was that
[Music]
um
okay
who is player is player only right
at least i don't fall as much
like i did um
in the
practice stream i jinxed myself
oh
i don't care the same fight will be good
at this
is here in front of me
[Applause]
is iris
at the top
[Music]
rainy
um
i love it
i wonder how many races will this be um
is it four
i think the first round will be four
four matches
oh can you just oh okay nevermind
at the top
did she just
train me
god
i really can't trust anyone when it
comes to this game
[Music]
then
okay
on the senpai only
oh god
[Music]
i didn't get anyone
and then
[Music]
oh
okay
i'm still behind
how's moona sing by better than me
god
okay
i'm gonna find that timing to use this
there you go
[Music]
god this is so sad
i had chance i had a chance to
the last okay and please everyone do not
use cheap tea beach or uh mario kart
stadium anymore for your
collection thank you i'm gonna try and
remember that but i don't know
yeah
nothing that looks like a beach and
nothing that looks like a fancy night
life fancy mario kart study right but
isn't there multiple beats and court
stadiums yes the cheap cheap beach the
one that we just did from the ds version
not anything yeah
oh okay okay okay okay are we doing team
wait what are we doing teams
uh we still have two races to go before
oh okay so it was
right okay
nice hat you know
she's muted okay
oh sorry okay
i love i love the way how innocent i
just answers that and she unmuted
herself and to just to say thank you
mm-hmm
oh
[Music]
um
oh god i forgot
gosh i shouldn't i shouldn't have went
here again
that was a mistake
it
magical
[Music]
uh
hmm
oh this is the last one okay
okay i'm not going there this time
i'm not going there this time
let's just use this
myself
co2
god i'm gonna bum into this yeah that's
what will happen
what just happened wait what
i was at the 10th place just now i swear
i thought she'll be as bad as me
can we say bye
john
uh
that was close
okay
okay let's go let's go we can do this
[Music]
oh god oh god oh god i'm gonna fall i'm
gonna go
ah
save
save okay
oh that one's so good
what am i doing
oh god
okay well that's not good
guys i got disconnected
oh no
it's the curse everyone
[Music]
i've never played in this map before
maybe i did but only like once
and i just don't know how to do
stubs
[Music]
yeah
i'm not sure like normally it seems like
in in the whole of japan tournaments
they automatically give the one like
well the like this qualification like
last spot if you
uh oh
if you are oh wow uh congratulations or
everyone cannot mute themselves now
oh yeah
[Music]
i was very impressed
i think that's just how we're gonna take
it it is what it is
[Music]
uh
let me let me just uh enough was number
one right
number one
[Music]
you know
everyone you know
what
yeah she practiced on that one a lot i
think that's what she
[Music]
okay
how did you manage to get number two
today
i i did bad on the first race so that
really pulled me back but yeah ina
senpai was very quick uh
but i did my best i did my best
[Music]
oh
wait are we complete in the
lobby right now one two three
yeah okay i guess pretty complete
okay well then shall we uh continue uh
but muna senpai is currently unavailable
yeah she's taking something
but i don't know my battery is one
hundred percent but it's a low battery
so i don't know which one is low battery
oh oh
i see the one that you're like did i do
that
do you think you're fine to go or you
need some time i i think i think it
should be fine
okay
sorry we're making coffee right now
[Laughter]
[Music]
everyone who needs coffee go get
yourself a cup of coffee
[Music]
i have the caffeine shakes already so
i'm banned from coffee
i was actually really surprised about
emma's driving too like i thought you
know she could she didn't like we didn't
see her practicing we didn't see him
playing the game
with them a lot i was like
in most of the races until the end when
i got silver
screwed over
his crown
i saw you go off the edge though watson
it was pretty good
as planned right it's all part of the
plan
yeah whatever yeah no it wouldn't be a
waste if you would have shout casted how
you uh suggested uh ammo because you're
such a good driver we need you we need
to
all right then let's uh
okay ollie okay okay ollie's going to be
picking teams are we picking teams like
dodge ball no like the winners pick the
kids
no that gives me really bad flashbacks i
don't like that
[Laughter]
again
now i'm gonna
pick last and i don't want that i'm
gonna go at my full power now because
now i'm fighting for the en ladies
kelly senpai i thought you were gonna
chill in the last places with me ah
this is where we put our all in it yep
[Music]
me too
[Laughter]
hey i've proved that
that i can i'm okay at not getting last
place so that's good news yes
is a good asset to have i want her on
our team hell yeah
guys
we'll have to carry uh indonesia's uh
back
yeah
i will support granny
as long as you don't get disconnected
again
[Music]
please don't let that happen
i hope you don't get this are we on the
break right now
god may have forgiven the disconnection
but i didn't
everyone uh please split into teams by i
think let's just um ian go to uh voice
channel 01 thank you okay
and i guess we're going to apologize
oh we're saying oh kelly is
[Laughter]
[Music]
so that's what you've been doing
moms here are famous for like their
super reckless way of driving
yeah
like mercy like
mom's supremacy i hate how that's
actually true
the auntie only very dangerous
yeah
you know
yes uh there's a problem with my
nintendo's actually what's up
oh
[Music]
yeah you know uh
uh should we join in here
okay
okay i'm gonna jump
yeah you can you can join in again it's
open again i think it's closed one you
can join again
okay thank you sorry
[Music]
are you gonna be okay
i think that i think that we actually
need to buy separate uh what is it
controller
[Music]
i was using the uh the normal controller
for the longest time and it had never
had problems
mine is good yeah
it happened to me at once
yeah when we were playing one together
[Music]
and the worst thing is that my
controller actually died so
she might want to be careful yeah
um
okay they say they're a full battery but
[Music]
[Laughter]
i don't like that
oh
[Music]
yes
oh
[Music]
how do i do this
oh
[Music]
oh my god
goodbye everyone
[Music]
district
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
whole idea only thingy like mario kart
you know
what are we going to do
again
i think you have to be at least good at
mario kart because this kind of
tournament is going to like happen in
the future
it will happen again
like a new mario kart tournament you
know i can't
[Music]
is
where am i supposed to go
[Music]
[Applause]
hey
[Music]
oh
yes
hey cursed
hi
i'm doing good okay somebody just like
stole my items
[Music]
definitely
guys
what am i supposed
[Music]
where is this
[Laughter]
i don't even want to know
who's born
good luck everyone good luck everybody
oh
[Laughter]
strategy
why did they pick that place oh my god
do you remember
rainbow because that's all sunshine
[Music]
um
i don't even know what are you talking
about but yes
we just like randomly screaming at each
other at this point all right
oh i was late
i don't even know
it
[Music]
is
i think it's okay
i i did hope it's okay though and i fall
okay
i thought
yeah oh cheers
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
yeah you guys get items wow
wow
like seriously like i'm asking you guys
got an item
nice yeah
[Music]
i believe i can touch this guy
no
[Music]
yes
again
oh god oh god oh god oh god
[Music]
oh god i had potential oh my god i have
potential and uh
[Music]
oh my god let's try topping top five all
of us
[Music]
yeah
especially this one this one is
especially hard
[Music]
i believe i can fly
i don't know if there is
[Music]
[Laughter]
so
is
[Music]
oh
do we stop here
like like you you know how to stop the
car like you think
[Music]
um
baby
[Music]
sorry
[Laughter]
[Music]
indonesia
no english english is not good because
youtube youtube ai is bad bad right
in indonesia
it's okay
just this
moderator okay
[Music]
i
expect hello guys
hello guys
[Music]
congratulations
what was their reasoning behind choosing
uh the cheese one and the baby road
i like cheese because
we liked
these
i was the one who told them cheese rode
because i like cheese
it's gotta be a road where reina knows
the shortcuts and stuff yeah yeah
do we have
some
comments from the winner ina it was
number one i think
yes uh i would like to thank pajamas
[Laughter]
for this opportunity
because of you yago i was about to be
like yeah go let's go
[Music]
okay so uh we're doing random teams next
there's four more races so please
everyone be careful to not choose any
roads that have been chosen previously
that i would appreciate that
um
well even if you accidentally choose one
that has been uh chosen before don't
worry it will probably not be so like
this let's just let's try to not choose
the ones that we have uh raised before
all right we'll do the random teams now
actually there is uh we don't have to do
the voice chat thing because there is
actually uh a way to do it here
oh there it is okay so uh in voice chat
zero
uh zero zero one we want uh gouda
yeah
[Music]
our iris and amen they are the two days
yeah
what is not dangerous just push her off
the push-ups
okay what are we doing what are you
doing what are you guys gonna do for
mount wario
oh they're going for the airport
okay
that one i think that's actually good
all right let's go mm-hmm we'll come to
that
yes
let's go
do our best
[Music]
i don't know it is kind of risky and
it's very risky right
um
ollie's over there
in front of me that means i have someone
to target
[Music]
yeah you're in hong kong that's fine
that's fine
uh
i hate you
me and my life
oh
[Applause]
this is the most adrenaline i've had in
a very long time damn my heart is like
[Laughter]
i'm like surprised like i didn't think
it would be this much fun to like have a
full tournament with everyone we're
having a blast man that's a little
airplane
[Music]
we should do something like this wait
hold on an airplane yeah
what are we picking
oh
possibly
[Music]
uh
the humanity
okay
this is
not looking good
[Music]
nice
okay this part i usually choke but
i can do this
[Music]
yeah i got the mushroom for the last
part
no i didn't get a
[Music]
oh
yeah
good job everyone
good job team um
you're so shaking okay
now what do we do
and before we get the time the clock
okay airport
okay since they want airports so much
that let's direct them in there yeah
yeah
oh is this the last one do we have one
more
we have two more i think we have two
[Music]
is
enjoyed that
instead i just got screwed over like you
would not believe
what happened i'm gonna come back
[Music]
let's go
okay
[Music]
this is not looking good
okay just uh leaving the rng
yeah
i don't know how to use the how do you
use
the paraglider
oh god you fly higher
oh then i can't hear
oh she blocked it okay
[Applause]
is
although something a miracle happens i
don't know
oh i'm not feeling this one yeah it's
bad this is really bad this is like
you're gonna lie to me but okay i have
never gotten a mushroom before i can't
come back from this
neighborhood this is unfortunate
[Music]
it's okay it's okay still got there
this is the last one yeah this is the
last one
someone dropped out
of them
i can't come yeah
i gotta come back how are we gonna come
back are we picking
seven what are you peeking
what are we thinking
drop down
wait
i did warriors gold mine
i don't know if she can join in time
what's up someone please don't join uh
don't choose a race yet if you can
okay yeah
are you able to
oh no i'm joining again
okay i was still on this oh it's
starting it's starting oh no it's
starting
[Music]
choices at least i didn't want to choose
the plot this time i don't like ollie's
ollie's me it's smug aura
she made it oh yeah she mean it okay
that's oh thank god okay oh music okay
[Music]
yeah this one's a little rough we can do
our best but i don't think i've ever
played this one let's have fun
wait what
is
[Music]
ollie's really good at this map
yeah oh was it the one with the bouncy
stuff yeah
yeah i don't know how to use it
i saw you disappeared
[Music]
i'm sorry if i hit someone
yeah okay okay i guess today i learned
that
how early fire is somehow
yeah
unfortunately fine
get me on the ground get me on the
ground cat and let's go
iris is behind i can't hear you with me
okay one more one more one more
go go
[Music]
that's garbage oh no
oh no
oh i did i couldn't get her sorry oh my
gosh i shouldn't hold on to that
[Music]
you deserve that watch
is
[Music]
oh my god of course hi iris
okay that makes i send sarcasm
number one
[Music]
let's go back on hey
i got disconnected like right before the
last lap
oh no that was me oh my shark friends
after the wi-fi cables
that probably means that you know the
last round if if riso you know got
disconnected and the points got deleted
that means that the last round uh final
result is not really accurate
but that's okay let's just say the last
round was an extra encore for fun
and yeah and i would like to give out
some golden juggles
[Music]
by speedy
and i would like to give
another uh golden yaga um as uh to iris
for also being absolutely
[Music]
i guess the strongest in the id team
holy moly
[Music]
the biggest period
another golem
goes to gura for being absolutely the
speediest shark i've ever seen
[Music]
another golden yogurt goes to
abbott
[Music]
damn wild cardio
i didn't see you that much on the race
but i think it was still shining
brightly as as the moon always does
the darkest time
and now the golden yellow goes to ali
for being also surprisingly big damn
good
[Music]
let's
thank you for participating
[Music]
[Applause]
and another golden yaga goes to cali for
actually really you know i don't
you surprised me you surprised me callie
i was i was looking at you driving there
and i was like damn well what the hell
man she didn't even do practice arcs is
she so good
my mom was playing instead of me that's
why i was sleeping
didn't i didn't get last place even once
guys that was my goal
[Applause]
thank you for cheering for me everyone
thank you they love you
don't mind me uh chat i'm not gonna be
able to fix that now i think one two
three four five six seven eight nine ten
eleven
uh
wait who did i not give her anyone
yeah
[Music]
you weren't you were surprising me too
sometimes i have had an eye on you thank
you
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
last comment from everyone let's start
with anya
oh me
okay um that was so much fun but i have
to practice more
if there's gonna be next time i don't
know maybe
maybe there's gonna be next time it will
definitely be next time yeah
thank you so much for improvement
thank you so much everyone for the fun
time thank you thank you
thank you
[Music]
kelly what's your closing comment
uh let's see my closing comment is kiara
thank you for everything you made an
amazing tournament you worked so hard on
this you had a logo commissioned you
made all of this stuff ina as well for
helping with the assets but like
oh my goodness you organized the whole
thing and it was a blast and i just
wanted to have fun with my friends and i
was able to do that because you
organized this amazing thing just thank
you so much for for working so hard on
it because it was a blast
thank you i'm so glad you enjoyed it
[Music]
yeah thanks for everything
thank you
nice
closing comment please
ah
thank you i want to say thank you also
to ina and kiara for all the hard work
you guys put into this tournament thank
you and i'm very i'm proud of myself for
not doing nearly as bad as i thought it
would and i would like to uh say that it
was probably because i fixed my switch
legs so i didn't have any lag let's go
gamers let's go home
[Music]
excuse me i'm sorry watched and i won
though i can use that excuse
me
even though you haven't played the game
in a long time i think yeah no practice
baby
let's go raw talent let's go rob ellen
sharks
[Music]
yes so i'm just uh thank you for
organizing this i know we have uh
mishaps and some troubles uh beyond but
yes thank you for this golden yellow i
will cherish it and talk to you guys
thank you so much
[Music]
okay i've completely disappeared i'm
sorry guys
okay i race close and common please
thank you so much for inviting me to
this wonderful tournament kiara and
thank you so much ina for the very very
cute assets
and yes i will practice more
so that
we can i can get go against inna
[Music]
yeah yeah my goal is nana my goal is
eena
i'm really excited to do this again
hopefully one day yeah
thank you
[Music]
thank you i hope yeah one day i want to
win against ina too that's a big pickle
that would be a big goal
it's not that big of a
[Laughter]
i'm so glad you joined holo ian because
that's what made this uh tournament
possible
yeah i'm really glad to be able to join
this wonderful tournament being part of
the cool kids yeah
yeah
yeah thank you
let's go all right
okay i'd like to say a very very big
thank you to chiara senpai for
organizing this i've organized it once
and it was really hectic so i can't
really imagine the links that you go
through
for like the logos and stuff
and even the thumbnails those must have
been hard and also for innocent piper
making all of those assets so quickly
like you guys really um how do i say it
i really appreciate it a lot and i'm
sure all of us do so thank you so much
for your hard work it was really fun
playing with everyone and um i may have
not popped everyone but one way or
another you guys will all be my bottoms
i forgot about that ghoul yeah
um first of all i'm thank you for you
kiara for organizing this thing and
thank you so
without you organizing we wouldn't be
like these
i mean it's
it's rare to
gather all the whole life indonesian
home and together so i'm so thankful for
that and also
um
big thanks to inna 2 for making the
assets it's really great
thank you so much and i hope uh in the
future we can be like this again
yeah yeah
yeah
yes yes yes i hope so too definitely i
was thinking like maybe on on uh like
around christmas or new year's eve you
should do something
[Applause]
amazing
please
yeah i'd like to say a big thank you to
uh chiara for organizing it of course i
know
like organizing collabs and everyone in
different time zones and
like schedules is really really
difficult but you really put a lot of
effort into organizing it commissioning
like the logo and everything really
thankful um and everyone feel free to
use your hats and cards like in your
mario kart streams in the future too
[Music]
thank you
and uh
yeah thank you everyone for joining us
today like it was so much fun like
playing with everyone and i hope we can
do it at the end
it's been a pleasure
thank you
oh yeah thank you thank you
operation this was a great cooperation
between uh kfb and taco taco bell taco
eats definitely
special thanks to you guys so well
together
our fast food franchises are meant to be
together yeah we're sweet
[Music]
okay i know you said stop but thank you
kiara
and
also inna senpai uh thank you so much
and i had a lot of fun uh
there was a little mishap there there
was a little disconnection issue but
overall i had a lot of fun and i would
love to have this kind of tournament
again in the future let's do it we're
still good
thank you
okay i'll go training so i'll get better
next time
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay so it doesn't end there i would
like to say thank you
everyone here also especially uh kiara
and ina like those are
amazing and also okay uh i'm really
happy because i can actually uh gather
and play with all of you guys here yeah
yes like
i'd appreciate more more more more
collabs like this so if you guys are
planning to do so
i
i'd love to actually i would be happy to
participate oh yes thank you so much i
love you guys
thank you
okay
[Music]
please closing comments
well first uh i'd like to apologize
if i was salty if i could stay you guys
uh no
that's part of my heart
[Music]
yeah thank you kiara and and ina you
guys work really hard thank you guys and
thank you everybody for participating is
really fun i know it's hard to organize
these types of collabs everybody's so
busy and different schedules thank you
and i had a lot of fun thank you
thank you
[Music]
we don't have to relay on these exact 12
members anymore so next time if you want
you can do shoutcasting
thank you thank you everyone for
participating today um i hope i hope
everyone had a great time even if you
know maybe you were not number one
number two number three that's fine i
think today was really just about
getting together
putting um two communities two fan
communities of hello ian and hello id
together and just feeling united
definitely and i am always glad to do
stuff like this again so i would gladly
invite you guys again whenever you have
time for it and want to join and i'm
sorry that you know because since it's
such an international collaboration um
it's not gonna be an ideal time for
everyone so i'm so sorry for the girls
who had to wake up at like 6 7 a.m or
something like that i'm so sorry i know
it's tough it's no problem it was fun
i just wish my parents could watch the
music and i'll be all behind you go back
to them
i hope your mom enjoyed the tournament i
don't think she did i think that she's
doing it as well
[Laughter]
well well well then with that i would
like to officially close to holo ian ho
id mario kart tournament everyone
take care of your golden yaga's polish
him every day he wants to get daddy and
sparkly and yeah i'll see you guys soon
[Music]
bye guys
you