[Music]
so
foreign
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
sorry for the delay
i
was busy
and now i was not busy with my cats for
folks sake
no
yeah i wish i was
[Music]
banana
i'm not really in a good mood right now
i'll tell you that
[Laughter]
um let's hope it gets better
um
it looks a little bit weird in that
angle
in photoshop i was able to turn it
um but i'll try
uh
[Music]
had a meeting before
the stream
and then
i went to buy groceries
and then i continued the meeting in some
way just before the stream because i
wanted to um
discuss some things it doesn't quite
know oh well um
yeah so now i'm feeling a bit frustrated
ah
yeah i see it needs to be a bit more
angled oh well
hello
i have a banana in my hand
i have a banana in my hand oh if it were
the other way around that could be like
mostly mushy
but this way it doesn't quite make sense
if it was the other way around
like
hello
moshi mossy
mojimo
gore knight yo i can't hear you
hello
the grip on that banana man
the grip
ah
no what same banana what banana with
banana what banana in my dream huh
what banana did i drink oh the bananas
are the banana that i um
pushed out of my body in a pool well
that's a while ago i don't even remember
that dream how do you remember that
ring ring ring ring ring banana phone i
don't know what that's from i just know
ding ding ding ding ding ding ding ding
ding
[Music]
me
[Laughter]
it's a cute old
yeah
finger five
[Music]
yes thank you for knowing it
most only japanese people know it
i sang this one before though i like
like a year ago or something i don't
know long time ago i um
[Music]
i sang i tried singing this in a random
stream before
when we were
trying to be a phone before
i mean you know banana phone as well
when you hear it
[Music]
let me see what if i just look it up on
google banana phone
banana phone song
rafi
banana phone is it which one is it this
is the same thing
let me listen
banana phone
i don't hear anything
my audio is broken
my audio's broken one second oh [\h__\h] oh
no
this happens
when
ah
wait
system
oh i hear it
what is this
i can't play it one second
uh-huh i don't know this ring ring ring
ring ring ring banana phone
i don't know this
i never heard this before
no
ring ring ring ring ring ring banana
phone i never heard this before ring
ring ring ring ding dong ding dong
banana phone
[Music]
never
okay what's even that funny about it
what seems so funny
because
it's a banana phone
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
i will i will fake love for you
[Laughter]
hi uh let's play
yakuza
uh yoga gotoku
let's continue
it was funny because early internet days
oh oh okay
oh maybe maybe it was
[Music]
okay boomer if if if i was a boomer
then and this is an old internet meme
thingy wouldn't then i enjoyed even more
as a boomer wouldn't i be in zoomer
because i'm not enjoying this huh
objection correct kiwawa you're
absolutely i'm sorry empress kiana
you're absolutely 100
[Music]
[Laughter]
let's hope that yakuza lifts my spirits
today
i'm currently not amused
but
yes i saw koba's message
but not i don't i don't need to like
every every single message
do i
hello
why are you here
boy
sorry
um sorry
sorry i don't
he calls me the d word why are we
didn't you already go all the way to the
end of this path
i went back to safe after we already
went all the way here but okay let's
let's look at it again
i did save yeah
but we're still going this path again
interesting
um
i was gonna say something what was i
gonna say
uh
i forgot i forgot i forgot i forgot oh
oh [\h__\h] i went i came too close
okay
oh yeah
actually uh
me and kobo ended up dming
a little bit
i'll tell you about it later james
jensen
[Music]
even worse than before
ah
he speaks like a [\h__\h] robot
this is how he's speaking
or like um
hello
this is my
uh
hello this is my
japanese
friend uh
can you
please please speak with
him this is how he speaks basically this
is an equivalent of how he speaks
oh my oh
it
what no don't skip let me hear more of
that shitty chinese
song
one second i want to raise my volume a
little bit why is everyone so quiet
[Music]
where's my phone by the way i left my
phone somewhere
damn i gotta grab my phone later why is
everything so quiet everyone's on
maximum here
ah wait i know why never mind you
couldn't know her
okay
it's quiet for you guys
we suddenly jumped back
[Music]
oh yeah we want to seek um
help and and stay in little asia because
we're being followed uh and and they
they can't get into little asia
because they they have their own people
that control it i guess they're kind of
safe there
um
but apparently they don't want us there
either yeah we're seeking
refuge
apparently
so that's
my chinese is not better
mm-hmm
um
[Music]
foreign
famous
[Music]
foreign
wow thank you so much yeah
okay next
i'll need you guys
um
foreign
do you get homeless in every yakuza game
at some point
the same in two games
it sounds familiar
not all of them
[Music]
is in general i do see like
like similar patterns you know about
but
but maybe that's just what yakuza is
about uh
like okay there's a
city uh yakuza heaven under control i'm
part of them but then i'm being kicked
out or something like that in some way
or another
uh
but then there is some boss there that i
look up to blah blah blah also where of
course we don't have any parents anymore
we were kind of adopted by them
yeah and then we need to hide at some
point because they're all following us
is it just that those two games are
similar or is it in general similar
always i wonder
the other ones are a bit different
each one story was supposed to be very
similar to kirill well that would make
sense for me if they introduce a new
protagonist and they want to have him
like have some
um
similar
story lines
yeah
that would make sense hmm
yeah now now that i mentioned it it's
similar really have you not noticed
they both start to story so that might
be a lie mm-hmm
foreign
a life of crime homelessness and tough
home lives etc is true irl look i don't
understand how that
connects with what i said
mm-hmm
it's a way of calming down people scared
of changing protagonists and gaming
styles by giving a sense of familiarity
i wonder if that's really what they were
thinking
i guess it would make sense
[Music]
i don't have any place else now that
i've been kicked out of malaysia might
as well take his advice
uh okay
okay where the hell is west park
oh right up there oh
i don't remember ever going there what
the hell
um
how's my inventory looking like by the
way
yup
um
inventory oh
oh yeah one i really wanted to go to uh
a pharmacy i think oh let's do that now
pharmacy was
here okay
so
pretty much straight
yeah
am i late for anything not really i
started a little bit late and oops
um
yeah nothing really happened we just got
kicked out of chinatown where we ended
last time
uh not chinatown little asia
they didn't want us there
so now we're looking for a different
place
where we can find help
shut up
um
you should check the shrine and use some
cp to make money gaining easier
aha
i guess i can what's
what's cp again how much do i have of
that
uh
stamina
um no no
[Music]
why do you not
why do you always always close
immediately stay open stay open
[Music]
okay
how's my health i'm okay okay
no no no no no no a good mix of those
two
you get cp besides injuries or you may
not have many oh [\h__\h] uh
i wonder if we can do
a side quest now you guys said the ones
of the
exclamation mark are the ones i have not
accepted yet right
in that case how do i find
like
my other
[Music]
how do i
is that all the details i'll get
that's that's completed but that's
that's completed as completed
um
what is that
mina's supposed to be around san diego
avenue okay how about we
they are the ones oh they are the ones i
accepted oh okay so for example one of
the uh exclamation marks could be like
this quest
sanyo avenue
shall we do some side quests first
uh
will
send where the hell is san diego avenue
logically then it would be by one of
those exclamation marks
is this any this is something oh it
might be here
okay let me check that out i don't
remember what that quest was about but
um
questions
did i bunk into you so hard that you're
like so mad that you want to kill me now
[Music]
chill
that girl
is that
isn't that mina who who who is mina
again what is that about
her boyfriend wants to know how she's
making so much ah
yeah right it was yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah that was the couple why the
girl was making so much money and the
boyfriend yes wanted to know how why
can i talk to you for a minute i'm sure
a new customer oh
a customer don't tell me this girl's
really selling herself
oh i'm sorry i guess not did you want
something and probably it's not that
it's just something else that seems like
she's doing that
no i shouldn't jump to conclusions
exactly i'll try to keep uh the
conversation going and see if i can
figure out what she's doing
just ask
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
oh
this is all new to me
she's so vague just ask what are you
doing
although
sorry this is all new to me i don't know
where to begin could you tell me how
this works
oh so your first time customer that's
why you were so unintentive i'm sorry
the first time can be awkward and
embarrassing they're doing this on
purpose
they're making it sound like this on
i think i managed to get the ball
rolling the girl's a little less weary
too
what would you like
i don't know
well
top or bottom
wait okay let me think what could that
be
top or bottom
[Music]
what could that be
she's selling something on the street
where you can choose from top or bottom
oh nails wait did you spoil me
is that the real answer because that
could be it she could i guess be
offering people outside
to get their nails done bunk bed oh man
oh yeah maybe it's like uh one of those
themed uh girls cafes like uh like a
make-up fade but in this case it's like
you get to sleep in a bunk bed with a
girl
because there are there are places like
for example where you can sleep on the
on the
on the thighs of a girl
and his makuda
that definitely exists
like pretty um
expensive probably but
yeah 30 minutes for
probably a lot of money
okay what do you guys bet i i will say
both of those are good the nails and the
bunk bed
oh this is something else
nah
is this girl talking about position
yeah bunk bed position sounds like she's
giving customers the option of being on
the top or bottom but i have to keep up
this charade to figure out if she's
really selling her body
um top or bottom which one do you prefer
a little
eh
i don't know
i never had my my my toenails done
bottom my panties what
oh she sells
wait really she sells her bra or her
panties
wait i thought she was
doing something way more ridiculously
innocent
so
andy's
[Music]
why your underwear i don't get it kitty
act along
i'm sorry if you misunderstood but i'm a
voodoo setup girl
girls sell gym clothes school uniforms
and lots of other stuff they've worn
before okay
okay well
i thought it would be um
more innocent than that
[Laughter]
okay
um the more you know
magika
monsica
in my case though i just sell my
underwear
yeah sure why not i mean probably got a
lot more to spare from that
yeah
you sell your used underwear
who would buy that and why i'll kill you
you
naive naive summer child
[Laughter]
why i guess when used them to do hurry
things what else would it be
i don't really want to think about it
yeah
okay
um
okay i get it you are doing business
with men who get excited over your
second hand skippies
don't chance you're the one here trying
to buy it no i didn't know what else but
i thought i was getting my nails done
no actually
you're not going to buy my underwear
then go away i don't want to stand here
talking to a pervert
[Music]
that's ironic
nutty
hey
okay she's totally shut down though on
the adult here i better set her straight
what's wrong with me
huh
what even are these questions
this implies he is a pervert he's not
whatever let's get to the point
would you admit to other people that you
sell your underwear can you be proud of
that oh
yeah i thought no it's not about that
you should just tell your boyfriend
maybe
you probably won't like it though
can you tell your parents siblings
friends or your boyfriend that people
purchase your panties
i
touch on right your boyfriend is worried
about you
you know
i'm gonna say one thing to this if
you're
um
of legal age then do whatever the [\h__\h]
you want with your underwear
but this girl seems to be going to
school
so
i don't
i don't think it's good but that's my
personal opinion
um
huh how do you know about touching
actually he pulled me up to this he
thought maybe you were selling your body
you wanted me to find out for sure
hot tub thought i would do that i would
never sell myself
oh right you're not selling your value
what you're doing is what was that word
again buddha said you're selling things
that were on your body
but whether you're marketing your
underwear or your body i think they're
still both about
selling your sex
i wouldn't agree with that
whatever or can you probably tell your
boyfriend you do buddha i mean yeah
you're probably embarrassed about it
aren't ya
i don't
i don't i don't want to do this either
ah
oh no i said the words don't thumb point
it out
um listen i'm sorry for getting all
emotional on you ah
good girl
what did you just say don't say it like
that i mean it was in the text and i
mean it's still another word for gender
okay
nice just stop don't don't make a big
deal out of it
don't make a big deal out of it
have you ever heard me count in german
i swear to appear from 6 7 act 19. 19
what do you say about that
huh are you now
sex swelling aroused by me saying the
number six
six
sixtuelly
oh are you
are you
one welly or two uelly aroused huh
or three you ellie or four you ellie
five you ellie
what how do you like
how do you like number
two i have three
four
five
seven
[Music]
eight
oh no
nine
[Laughter]
ten
i skipped another on purpose
this is like my
my pc specs asmr
um
uh rtx 3070
gpu
over 9000
um
make a giga drive
no things about pc
well that's some real dirty dunk
oh yeah you love storage you love
storage i'll give you storage
[Laughter]
you all start
out i'm actually kind of into storage
myself
yeah
that really turns me on
endless storage that also comes with
super mega
intense
online cloud storage for free
[Laughter]
[Music]
holy [\h__\h] they're throwing online
online clothes storage
let's go
okay okay chill okay everybody relax
relax
relax everybody
we're just talking about computers and
numbers
[Laughter]
honestly no one wanted to do this
buddhism thing was it for money
some of us are in for that but not for
me
i mean it's nice having money but it
doesn't make me happy at all to buy
things with money i got by selling my
own panties
i guess not
i'm just so afraid of such cool
sansko
sachiko who's sachiko
thanks guys i'm glad you uh
enjoyed
pc specs and numbers
[Laughter]
shut up
shut up chad don't make it weird you're
making it weird
you're making it so weird
i'm selling computer specs online i'm
not i'm not keep it out for free
it's all about love she runs things for
all the buddha girls in the area and
sachiko figures out where we should be
standing on the streets she also takes
care of things if there's any trouble
with a customer in return we all have to
submit a part of our earnings to such
school once a month
so there's a girl overseeing the
operation can't you tell sachiko you
want to quit
yeah
and that's impossible as long as she's
around i can't quit this buddhist thing
no i need my pc don't buy it you
high school girls around here all that's
close friends if i try to stand up to
her quit they don't bully me so you
can't quit i don't want to stop nowhere
it's getting pretty complex your
boyfriend won't be able to solve this on
their own
reena do you know where i could find
this at school
[Music]
i don't want to go back to your
boyfriend and tell him that you are
peddling your panties so i thought maybe
i could pursue it that's cool to quit
running the sketchy producer thing what
really you would do that oh my god
um
near the hotel the street she's a
long-haired girl wearing sakura zaki
akadami's uniform
sounds fancy
sakurazaki's uniform has a white collar
and a blue scarf
do i need to remember that sometimes
wears a cardigan but i'm not sure if
she's wearing it today a white collar
and a blue scarf okay
okay
don't worry about it where's the hotel
district
um
all the way over there of course it is
let's take a cab
a white collar
blue scarf white color blue scarf i
remember maybe a cardigan but
maybe not
oh yes
ah i guess so yeah because she's saying
it like that there's probably gonna be a
bunch of similar girls
okay okay
okay okay ah there are already a bunch
of girls here
and they all wear the same [\h__\h] uh wait
white collar blue scarf
white color different scarf
white color blue scarf as well
i don't see a difference between those
besides the hairstyle
that's cool is there more
what are these doing hey stop then
let's uh warm
up we need to warm up fighting
intervene
superhero
to the rescue
i forgot how to fight i forgot how to
fight i forgot
[Applause]
[Music]
because
r1 was focused right
okay okay i think i'm good i think i
remember how to fight get up get up
okay
yeah good weapon feels good to smash
them on their face
[Music]
although i feel bad for whoever's
bicycle that was because bicycles are
low-key expensive and
i'm sure the person who owns that
bicycle is relying on the bicycle
i'm sorry please don't need me anymore
[Music]
okay bye bye
my
job here is done
hey
and now
i will choose sachiko oh wait there's
another girl over there that also looks
similar
but that's it
shut up
i'm busy
is it that easier a ring
oh ring a ring wait it's not a typo he
said that on purpose because it's a ring
of people
oh
well well well i wonder who puts you up
to this
ah yes that's cool
ringling
ah
i am such cool is there a problem with
that
a big one you're forcing girls to work
in your buddha cellar ring and it's
making some more of them miserable
miserable they make a lot of money
selling used clothing why would that
make them miserable
[Music]
customers want what we offer and we're
not breaking any lungs why shouldn't we
do what we do
help us
is it
hmm
[Music]
think of your parents
is it
what if your parents were to find out
about your buddhist ring think of the
pain they would fail this is wrong
how could you be so cruel to bring up my
parents
my parents are long gone oh i have no
one who would be hurt if they knew what
i do some might better in the business
doesn't present the problem for anyone
well okay
well then it's a health risk thing i
guess
her parents are fine this little [\h__\h]
you don't joke about that
you can't even see for a lie that far
fetched good job getting schooled by a
school kid big mr adult man
oh your [\h__\h] breath soggy
it's a health hazard
it is trust me believe me source
me
or chat actually
it's a health hazard think about it use
animals unsanitary duh
duh
well isn't that exactly why men buy it
exactly yes
yes duh
so stupid what is this conversation
[Music]
besides if you're worried about hygiene
i'm only selling underwear that i put on
after taking a shower
so there you have it okay
what you're doing is selling your
there you go you're fooling around in
the world of adults when kids play with
fire they're going to get burned
well well i haven't gotten burned yet
we'll see what happens when i do it
yeah you gotta honestly for teenagers
who do stupid [\h__\h] whatever it is you
need to
wait until they
make a mistake otherwise
like make a mistake and then suffer from
the consequences otherwise they won't
listen and care
so
yeah
yeah you probably won't get her to stop
it but we need to get the other girl out
of it because she wants to stop
just get her out of that somehow
i don't know maybe get the parents
involved
i'm glad to hear that did you come back
for more
such good chill i love you
i love you
i love you lovely such
[Music]
i hate that because
i've had no not including the panties or
anything i've had an experience like
that
where
someone goes from
fan to absolutely
insane and like that
so
this hits
deep
like marry me i know you love me too
even though i mean this is real talk but
this is
it happens
like
even though
i like gave nothing
they're like oh i know you love me too
let's get married i love you marry me
you love me too i know you do
[Music]
oh sheep
mm-hmm
i made up my mind so john i already
decided i'm spending the rest of my life
with your panties because i'm a
prophetic piece of [\h__\h] and i don't ever
get any consequences from that but i
suck and i'm
[\h__\h] a useless bastard that failed
alive that's why i stalk girls like you
you're really scaring me i love you such
good job come on we'll be together
forever such good job
please
i
[Laughter]
what
yeah yeah i took him down don't worry
about it
wait a second
my chat is dead
that's because i'm not using hyperchat
today that's what i get for that that's
what i get for that
let me
hi project my beloved
there you are
hi pritchett
i missed you i'm sorry for not
using you right away today i'm sorry
it's because i felt lazy okay
okay
sorry you're safe now
who did you
don't get in my way such good job it's
mine okay
let's see about that
menacing man
probably is enjoying the pain that's the
disgusting thing about it
[Music]
are you right
i i'm okay i told you right you played
with fire and you got burned
i wanted to help me after all the
horrible things i said to you
i would never just stand around while a
high school girl got insulted in front
of me
thanks i don't
what is who's that guy
i'm sorry but i can't do this anymore
that's your boyfriend i guess i'm
quitting you put us in a group i'm
really sorry but she ended up being able
to say it anyway herself
please let her quit tell my boyfriend
but don't bully her for quitting your
group
hate to admit it but you were totally
right
business is too risky a game for high
schoolers to be playing i never even
thought about a girl like me or being in
danger from something i put together i'm
going to disband this buddhist
[Music]
you are really
yes really i'm sorry for everything mina
we're touching i don't know what's after
what yeah
[Music]
you made their day too
i just don't ever want to be that
frightened again there's no need to
thank me
besides
i think you should only show your
underwear to someone you really care
about
wait why don't you look at me like that
oh
okay
okay i got the right idea from dad she
was sending me a signal
is just too likable
all right let's go to
whatever quest that is ah is that where
don quijote is
the line of people you need to go to
showa street west
one side quest completed
here
so give a quick
is that a good quest
what a donkey's like in real life uh
huge nevro and they have everything
and they have
uh
always fun music playing
uh wait where is the donkey
so what is this line about is there some
new product that's super popular
i'm so glad i lined up first this
morning i'm going to be the first to get
it
oh this game i got a quest free
recording in line pal you have to play
by the rules and get back in line like
everyone else
i snuck off from work for this if my
manager finds out before i get back i'm
so dead
all right kid
yes what's going on why are all these
people here
did you want one too that's probably the
game in the background right
i'm really excited about this i don't
get the last one in stock what are you
talking about
i'm signing up for other quest three
i don't quit three
is that some kind of secret code
no it's another question the newest game
and not have good eyes serious
advertised there
yeah it's like dragon quest i can't wait
to read the instruction manual on my way
home
never heard of it so people are actually
lining up to buy a video
i understand buying a game and i
understand lining up for don quixote but
not combined because don quixote is not
really the place where i would go to buy
a game
but okay
maybe they had no uh
model for
a
a proper game store it's the most
popular game in japan right now i went
looking for it with papa but they were
sold out everywhere
and then my friend told me this place
was getting a new batch today so i
grabbed my allowance and ran all the way
here i actually don't remember seeing
video games in the donkey i've seen
everything but not video games in a
donkey
and i didn't have yoda camera
yeah i don't
know
if
you know
[Music]
to the rescue there are some where they
sell games as well
i guess i just never
went to the floor where they sell games
i always went to the food floor or to
the makeup floor and stuff like that
um
i made it just in time and got the last
reservation i'm so happy it's gonna be
the best game ever made
times are strange if it's just hard to
buy a toy sorry to bug you kids thanks
for the info
and now
wait what
what
what is the continuation of this quest
wasn't this a quest
[Music]
come back later
ah go in and out okay okay
[Music]
i have a full inventory though
oh okay
so give me a shout
squeaky armors
oh they're gone they're gone
big man is over there
eight million
oh wait okay
boy
did you not get it oh
is he stealing it from him what
slimy high school oh no
oh big guy
in the background
so we're still making me so nervous when
that guy walks around in the background
while i'm in this in like a cut scene or
something
what's the matter something wrong
my brand new video game
yeah i took it run away i spent all
morning waiting in line for my oh my
allowances
stealing from a little boy that's really
low
hey kate what's your name it's ikea
you
hand dried up here i'll get you came
back
so there's no need to cry
okay i won't cry anymore
that's showing some spine little man i
like that leave it to me
thank you
so cool
um pink street okay
a little kid i'm gonna show him who's
boss
don't you dare mess with my friend oh
wait is he also getting
bullied and also getting his game stolen
wait what the [\h__\h] was the name of that
club to the right oh dear
uh isn't that
yeah okay it's a chain i get it
well
not gonna say you didn't deserve that
for stealing it from someone else
you have the data for the game don't you
watch it to you my friend just came to
enough prepped and so leave me alone
now can do i'll take that
you took from making you are a good
every that's the last thing i want to
hear about right now forget it i'm going
to grind your ass just for the
experience
okay
i'll give you an experience
a once in your lifetime experience
[Music]
this is how it feels to get bullied
get into the trash
[Music]
okay i just caught the guy who took your
heart with it
but he doesn't have it anymore
i know
i told you i didn't hear it i got rubbed
away better theme
this jerk from a street gang busted out
his tower of stealing and made me give
it to him
how did he know that he carries it with
him though
i'm gonna be home leveling up but now my
unaccurate three is probably going to
some dude who's not even a fan
excuse me you're adequate of three then
it wasn't yours
you rob a little kid then turn around
and cry like a baby when you get mugged
how pathetic is dead
if you haven't learned your lesson yet
you want another class
[Laughter]
don't tell me that person is going to
get robbed as well
please
oh no
[Laughter]
mighty dare
boy
i i i i
[Music]
best dialogue
here we go again
how many times are we gonna do this
okay
kick
bye hit you
quickly kill you no kill your kick
sorry i still don't have your game bro
sorry
yeah i know
i've seen it
a yakuza
a yakuza still the game
damn
loves the game
probably not even a fan
i don't know you are also a fan
seems like
it was like everybody wants the game now
you should have pre-ordered it stupid
i mean i never pre-ordered games either
but
because i usually i usually just order
it like like an online version of it and
that's never out of stock
hallelujah thanks to online games
like games being available for purchase
online in online shops
yeah
indeed this day and age we can do that
but
wait wait
wait which street
here
yeah back then when pre-ordering meant
something
oh
my god
i thought you were the shakedown guy for
a second
[Laughter]
oh
you're finally my another question
my quest is complete
and the game you got there building
something like a five-year-old give back
let's do that for you one of the losers
who couldn't score another career three
that's some tough luck but you see
there's not a good belongs to us
if you want to live get off my street
and listen
don't bother looking for a place that's
still selling on a career free just find
a fool who bought one and take it
villains every last one what's this
world coming to
where'd you say boy
that adequate i'm taking it back
huh
let's go
i'm like santa claus
i have to protect the child
i will make sure that the child gets
the present
[Music]
but he doesn't know how to aim
out
this cannot be
give it to me
you're back
it was never yours to begin with
well i'm begging you please my little
boys
wait is he your son
what a plot twist
my old lady left me and took the boy
with her
he's been wanting autography ever since
he read about it we went looking
everywhere but there ain't none for sale
anywhere i just wanted my boy to be
happy fella i'm begging here yeah
gotta
let me have it please
i got the picture now sorry but i can't
do that you probably don't know this but
a little kid saved up his allowance and
went through a live travel to buy the
last copy of this adequate free
uh i didn't stick up little little kid i
took it off somewhere it was going yeah
but he took it from someone else and
that person took it from someone else
and that person took it from the kid
okay
i had to walk
and i came to get it back for the little
kid let's go back to the rightful owner
and now comes akio and then he's like oh
my boy my child and then he'll be like
daddy
and yeah
happy end
maybe not maybe got it no i think that's
that yeah
yes yes
papa
[Music]
he tried to shoot me and i punched him
so high that that his guts were flowing
out of his
mouth but yes
[Music]
okay
because mama always can smile on you
papa for spending money on golfing
go-karts and board games
i didn't want mama to get mad at you
even more for spending all your money
again papa so i tried to find myself
mr papa looks kind of scary but he's a
really really nice man once you get to
know him he took me to a bunch of game
stores just the other day papa's not
living with mama and me now i think he's
lonely so please stay friends with him
ah no no thank you
actually i'll kill your papa help me get
you all your career free back
i did in a way
i don't want to see you crying again be
careful going home with your game
okay
hey mister sorry i forgot who my papa is
i
you didn't give him the game well okay
just to apologize or to thank you for
teaching this for a lesson maybe
whatever i want you to have it
sunburst
a weapon
oh can i replace my back with that
[Music]
noise
oh i want to see how much stronger that
is
[Music]
it breaks what
what rolly what the [\h__\h]
wait i don't have a weapon at all
i mean brakes
that can't break
by the way i need more access where do i
get accessories i've been like i'm
halfway through the game and i still
have accessories
where can i get stuff like that is there
like a shop
after 22 hits
what
and wait do i have it now in every
stance
should i keep it for like a tough fight
sub cluster lockers
you can fix it oh can i repair it
okay um
but once i have it equipped is it like
always equipped enough fine
automatically once i once i put it in
the slot where i just did
down on the d-pad okay okay okay so i
need to kind of activate it during the
fight as well okay
and i'll just keep it
for now
okay okay and
okay now
we
go to the shrine
and then we go to the main quest because
that's all the
all the subs subquests i can see right
now
all right
[Music]
nice damage
oh
[Music]
me
and kill him
yeah
the last hit always feels so good
oh wait the taste is on the ground can i
pick it up
no
i was running around it but it didn't
give me the option
do i need to be a beast
where
it doesn't really do any damage
[Music]
okay never mind
why is it suddenly so many people huh
i just wanted to go to the shrine man
it is here
what
was side quest
uh
where's the producer without the show
for the location so today we're screwed
well he had a huge argument with the
director at the question remember he's
probably still buttered now i directed
something else you won't put in an inch
but even when they've been spreading
hands with the producer i heard a lot of
the crew that can't deal with him either
maybe it'll be a strike
uh whatever the reason if we try to
shoot on location without the producer
the director is going to going to really
you like this sad place
you guys said it about every side quest
maybe we can find someone who can stand
in for him
i'll show you someone who can stay calm
and cool while taking all the crap on
direct your kisses out
we need a guy with an hour of toughness
a guy who can command respect just by
being in the room i guess guys like that
aren't exactly a dime it doesn't
could it be me
well
show must go on
well how perfect we ran into another
side quest while we were doing cyclists
all right
yeah i know what you want you want me to
be your
director
or producer
same thing same thing
we're production group for a tv show
would a television crew want from me or
what
oh we're going to be shooting a short
segment at the restaurant here in time
for a gourmet food program
we're down to a man and we're desperate
will you help us
after i eat my banana which is never
because i can't eat it man it's just
it's just a png
you don't have to do it if you would
stand there and local fertility oh that
sounds good
i can't see you're always so bright it's
dazzling
oh please i mean it's true but
okay let's do it
let's do it
supposed to be here but something came
up this minute he can't make it so we
need you to stand for him yeah
[Music]
okay
i have no idea what i'm doing though
people will not faking it
no i mean
from your looks with that suit it's
already wait you're gonna change my
clothes
my clothes are fine
sure they do now let's get you looking
like a big shot wait can i keep the club
stand after this
um oh
i look like one of those rich people who
go to like a thingy like a club what are
those clubs called um
not golf clubs but yeah he looks like a
golfer too
oh
those are not yeah counter clubs those
are not really producer clubs
the producers i've met never wear
something like this
actually they all even wore suits or
like a shirt with uh suit pants
oh it's the 80s okay but still
maybe it was in the 80s
[Laughter]
okay
let's produce the [\h__\h] out of you guys
oh
oh director is on the way all we need
you to do is deal with him and keep up
his demands he can be a kind of a diva
he says some weird stuff but just try to
not send him off and you'll be fine
okay
oh looks like you can do yakiniku here
there's crayolas on the grills on the on
the table
director is here
act natural okay okay
i'm a natural
yeah yeah you look like a director
[Laughter]
um i'll buy that
ciao lovelies
good
[Music]
excuse me
gluten morgan to you too
don't ever change more chad i'm counting
on you today bling bling baby
what in the blazes where's our intrepid
producer where is my eater john
sorry you just sound cold and sick this
morning here's on here we'll be standing
in for him today
never heard of him made the real deal my
man
oh yes of course kids on does a lot of
work on location overseas this is his
first domestic shoot in the world that's
probably where you can recognize him
a very well and celebi
i don't care who you are when you're on
location with me everyone has to pull
the weight capisce
[Music]
you dragged this guy out of the river
riverboards
i guess what they say is true people in
television businesses do seem pretty
shallow
this guy is irritating but i better play
along so he doesn't get suspicious
and they're a
problem if you can't return a simple
greeting your history in this beast land
a proper creating is important in every
walk of life what should i do
adequate i don't want to just observe it
i want to be the eddy [\h__\h]
the rest sounds like [\h__\h]
i discourage disrespect this skirt get
goofy the goofiness would fit the the
guy
the the right director
i guess let's get goofy
[Music]
when in room i guess i have to do this
ride what
room instead of saying hey
yeah
let's get this [\h__\h] so we ran before my
next meeting
oh my god it's good and imitating
i love it i didn't expect that from you
but i dig it today's gonna be
i guess that went well
boy
so anyway where is the babbling bit of
window dressing she's on deck for our
dining report
what we know interesting is that tv is
your goal
yeah potato reported
and what the [\h__\h] are we here it was
your job to lock down the tail and you
did that didn't [\h__\h]
i'm sorry i'm about to get your schedule
in time she's on the way right now
you can come all incompetent in beside
if we go over and die we'll be screwing
over the restaurant you're a nice guy
maury but this [\h__\h] doesn't cut the
mustard
and the ketchup neighbor i'm sorry sorry
this director what a change from that
cheesy goofball a few seconds ago guys
got one short piece
oh
[Applause]
sorry i'm sorry i'm late
no problem a baby doll we're patient as
a pie
don't you look ravishing today
okay gang let's get this boy started
simply
a fantastic car to your max everyone
let's roll it
what the hell is this where is the
erasable
where's the food you mean
oh sorry we'll get it
[Music]
sorry can you son can you grab the
erasable from the table erasable
i can check what's on the table that's
the start
what
erasable and you can erase it because
you can't eat it oh that food
there's some pretty random things on
this table which one do i take
what's the something to do ah
the eraser
why why do we need it no that's that's
that's a trap
you would think they mean the eraser but
what would we need a bracelet for that
makes no sense let's take the food
she got
i brought the eraser book
yeah
yeah yeah i understand i understand
completely
oh thanks can you send it to the table
mm-hmm
wow
it's literally two-dimensional i see
like no dimension there it's so flat
it's like a paper of veggies and meat a
piece of paper
oh that looks nice thingy
oh doesn't it i want you to savor it now
let it linger on your lashes
this shot won't be my tour de force
there's no grill it's it's raw we need
to grill are you gonna notice it now
[Music]
i'm so glad you
i'm sorry you figured out eraser boys
what our crew calls consumable props
like food uh-huh
smarty
why why talk why say it exactly the way
it is like food when you could say some
fancy word that no one understands like
erasable
yeah
gotta have it be complicated and sound
cool like a secret agent by using secret
secret code words and all that
um
[Music]
i think that food is erased when it's
eaten mm-hmm i'm smart like that
oh brilliant just choose going smoothly
thanks to you
i might as should be useful somehow
is that really what they say
at least in in japanese maybe maybe the
direct translation isn't so accurate
because they had to make it work with
the eraser on the table
but hmm
wow that looks delicious
there's so much but it looks so tasty i
could eat it all in one sitting but
please grill it first please
apart and we get you down but we have to
still live that erasable later so would
you be a doll in grocery for me
sure
[Music]
uh uh i would say
i don't know
two
i mean yeah
yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah for the close-up
shot of the food
yeah
because i don't know what this means
either leave only the brightest i don't
even know what that means my my thought
would be number three if anything
but i don't know what leave only the
produce means
i got this
and that's a great looking grocery job
if i say so myself hey i grosser did
[Music]
brilliant really
it was correct is it
yeah that looks perfect to me
perfect png
my new feed they're erasable is anger
like a groceries display ah
like i guess yeah like in the grocery
shop
i mean at least
uh yeah
when you gross your crap it means it's
tilted at an angle like how it grows to
this place
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah of course i
knew that of course i knew that
honestly i didn't really like think
about that i just thought about how
japanese tv first like they do these
like close-up shop a close-up shots of
the food in these food reports where the
you see the the
the chopsticks are like shaking but it's
like so beautiful because it's like
there's like fog around the food from
being so hot
and you see all the details
it's really really really mouth-watering
what's the last ah gear
money cheer these props and strike the
set
punch
[Laughter]
um
i would say remove
i would love to punch them
pot
violence
kick them
but it's probably removing what does tom
dear means taunt ad that's like a there
that's what yeah would would be a direct
translation i guess but it's probably
i hope so i hope so
[Music]
you made me think there for a second
was obvious i knew it all along
you're welcome
thank you everyone thank you thank you
thank you that's a wrap the shoot's over
okay what's my reward those cloves
yakiniku
oh where's that place huh
can you sign you saved us you don't show
this lingo like a pro
and no problem i had fun with it also do
you think pink pants look good on me
because i feel like i'm rocking them
it's rare to see a producer who can take
charge on the location like you please
accept no thanks
and make that necklace oh is this also
um
like a throwaway thingy
or does it stay on my body forever
okay
uh
oh dear
did the shoots go down okay without a
real crew
with the devil why would you even bother
showing up
you needed on the teleprompter we're
here to beat some matters into you
this is for working as like slave flight
into the night who the hell do you think
you are
we got into breakfast and because we
love television but thanks to you we
don't have time to go home and watch tv
there's no way to live
what can i say it takes blood sweat and
tears to make a tv show four to five
gentlemen
big talk is always character who made
you so important that you can treat a
producer like this i've had it with you
that's why we boycotted the shoe today
we're on strike a boycotter more like
let your personal drama get in the way
of work you call yourself professionals
yeah boy you want is the last time we'll
ever see you so let's end this [\h__\h] show
on the happy nose for us
oh my gosh what do i do
i'm the producer i will protect my crew
let's go
[Music]
i must say you have a great fashion
sense
oh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
[Music]
i feel that huge [\h__\h] stick he's
about to uh
do one of those jumps over like a really
really high bar you know what i mean
like that sport
oh my back
[Music]
the small stick
my knee my knee
that's a meme that i know but you guys
are probably not gonna recognize
my leg
his knee
yeah yeah yeah yeah
family guy
yes
[Laughter]
yeah yeah thank you thank you you're
welcome you're welcome oh yeah okay
[Music]
killian john um did the best you could
do with such passion despite that
knowing a damn thing tv is not a gentle
mistress a single minute or even seconds
of footage can take distance to hundreds
of hours of hard work to struggle this
has to save real
the challenge demands an incredible
level of precision experience and skill
but there's something even more
important than those and that mommy is
passion
fashion
i believe tv gives viewers hopes and
dreams just like youtubers there are
people out there who can be inspired by
tv to change their jobs or even their
way of life
i think tv is a medium that has the
power to change people's lives for the
better
you might be right about that most
that's why we make progress of passion
no matter how hellish the process may
feel as creators we're the dream weavers
it is a duty to pass those dreams to all
to others
you're quite a director you know that
oh beast boss i'm just an overbearing
loser who can't even hang on to a solid
crew i want to bring the same bastion i
have in my work out in in them but i
can't seem to get through to them
yeah
all right
what you just said that moved me to
balco we have a lot of growing up to do
i want to do more i want to make better
programs oh yeah okay okay
chill guys
you're julia great producer
wait i don't know how to say that
oh bye-bye what
have mercy you're gonna record some more
i'm i'm not gonna be part of that
[Music]
[Applause]
from the top i don't know they're gonna
start from the beginning that's what
from the top means come on you know that
too
okay okay okay we moved away from the
shrine though i wanted to
i'll never get to the [\h__\h] shrine i
just wanted to go to the shrine
oh yeah i'm going back to the shrine
[Music]
and then we'll block the same path back
oh i know what you want
[Music]
what did i just get distracted with
again i can't just ignore that
[Music]
um that looks like another cyclist yeah
oh give me that sword
[Music]
the best cyclist in the game
really [\h__\h] cake
you need to learn from this
called
oh god
here we go again we're just gonna look
at the intro so that i have the quest
and then i'm gonna do it another time
punish me
hurry punish me when everyone can see my
shame
um sexy clothes you got there
um okay then
you
you're middle-aged man
yes go on
um um your lasting guy
oh i put your soul into it
please visit again you you customer
not very good at it
um
that was no good like nothing about it
was working nothing at all i knew you
were bad at during the role play but i
didn't expect you to be bad at just
saying goodbye
can you please tell me what i wait maybe
we can get her to work at uh oh no wait
that's majima's
part never mind
where do i start when i ask you to
punish me you said i was a middle-aged
man that's the truth not a put-down
i suppose that's true
and then you called me lusty i mean who
says that if i'm coming your life is
pretty obvious i think what's the joy of
being told what you already know
also true
or to top it off please visit again
that's proper business and you can't not
massage
center sm whatever
i'm so sorry oh man are you john you're
an s m queen a dominatrix you should
never ever apologize
yeah how did she get into this job like
um
how
like with
with the way
she's polite and all
she could have done a similar job that's
not about s m just fine
like one of those uh
cabaret clubs for example
why
what
maybe she likes leather
maybe she likes how it complements her
skin tone
[Music]
oh no are we gonna show her how i see
her ass crack
um another time girl
mata don't need to walk
[Music]
how many more times am i gonna be
stopped
before i get to the shrine man
how many more times
[Music]
wow hey
wait i'm gonna die
let's have a bento
um
okay no more horses
[Music]
so much for that
take it back
what you get
for fighting an unfair fight like that
oh he's mad
[Music]
you don't seem to notice that you need
to shower anyway so you don't seem to
need
are you sure what no
don't seem to need nose either
[Music]
or knives or whatever
get up
stop you little [\h__\h]
gotta work on your one ladies i know
i'm trying
okay bye-bye
i don't block okay just like an alien
ring you guys can completely forget
about the blocking option it's not what
i do
just forget about it forget it it exists
okay
i'm fine with just uh
which is swooshing from one side to
another that's my blocking i dodge but i
don't block
yeah it's not my way
not that kind of yakuza
[Music]
okay well do i have cp now
uh-huh
no wait what was this about
buying something with cp that was normal
money here
right on my cps ah 38 oh
that's for longer recover more quick
quickly that's the i'm dashing all the
time right
no no no no yeah that's not in the fight
that's just running right or is it in
the battle
ah look at those ah battle tabs ah
there's some expensive ones
get the golden pistol when i'm so close
to getting the golden pistol should i
get the golden pistol wait a bit more
and get that one
or
i have to get them in order
what
that's more likely to take a nap
good for him wait
until everybody's ready for collection
um business
i'll i'll take the first one at least
where's this
oh
[Music]
it's all about mommy
oh my god five left okay let's just do
this okay okay
thanks
very much
oh wait
uh can i have 74 million can i do some
abilities
what's the next one 30 million oh
ability acquired and this one i already
have that one
at least after being knocked down
after i'm being knocked down
a counter
when ketu gets up from the ground will i
get a prompt for that or do i have to
remember that
that's when i'm still on the ground or
the moment when
it's a heat move for when you're ah okay
okay there's a prompt okay so when i'm
on the ground i'll get a triangle prompt
okay cool cool cool cool
sounds good to me
and i don't really use beast much but is
there something for
10 million
oops
no
no okay
come send me out welcome to the
membership
and now
from here on out we'll do the main story
it's been two hours now so i don't know
we might only do one chapter
today because i did side quests and last
time we did three chapters
um but we'll see about
that okay
okay okay okay okay okay
um actually i wanted to say something
um yesterday
me and kobold
dm a little bit and
i must unfortunately
announce that the girl
even though i believed in her
pure
childish season-ness
that she does have kusogaki tendencies
after all
yes it's sad news but it is true
she has kusogaki tendencies very much
it was very clear to me
the reason is
the reason is she called me
chicken
and i said cobra basketball no
[Music]
respect mama and she said oh my chicken
sounds funnier and i was like no kabul
no
no and phoenix okay
thanks
alright so i think i got her under
control now but i definitely failed
those kusadaki tendencies
foreign
i'm sorry to have to let you guys know
like this
but it's the truth
[\h__\h] all up here
[Music]
oh
yeah [\h__\h] off
okay
nice pgm can i carry the mountain
not the mountain bike the bike
as a beast
[Music]
how do i pick it up again here okay i
thought he picks it up automatically in
the beast mode but i don't know
yeah
slash that motorcycle
[Music]
how did that feel huh
you feel good
if yes then
you're the right customer for an s m
club
picked automatically impressed square
how close do i have to be to it though
oh oy oh my what
wait that's one of the rich guys that
we're
able to see now oh
are they strong
no
they're not
they're only rich and weak oh [\h__\h]
how much did that give to me
i didn't pay attention
seven million
wait was i lucky or do they really
appear quite often
damn
they do it very often
this is west park hope there is
somewhere for me to sleep
don't look at me like that
uh
let me save
oh and money was weighing him down yeah
oh so let me get some stuff out of my
[\h__\h]
out of my item box
oh and the necklace yeah yeah
oh my god the saving process triggers me
so hard
i'm a little penny a phone trying to go
call
[Music]
defense one blade one firearm one
restoring your health while you stand
still in battle well i don't think there
will be many moments where i stand still
okay
cool
a place where i can sleep
maybe here
no
maybe one of those benches
pigeons oh wow holy [\h__\h] they really
occupy this place
oh i don't need to read
um
[Music]
we
wow why would i do that
huh
foreign
i mean for him it was probably like
worth a try
this is thank you but it's like like a
[\h__\h] house
wow
hmm
this has to be the shadow he mentioned
should at least keep me from freezing to
death
i guess in order to progress the story i
suppose i have to sleep once so
i suppose
it's free real estate
me
oh no someone probably yelling at the
homeless people in general
oh
is it yakuza
i would almost call that place a home
though
the one that he built
it's not much of a homeless man anymore
it's looking pretty nice
i respect that man
built himself a cozy place
maybe i'm a fashionable homeless
well i don't know i've never seen it
before i've seen a lot of like um
in japan i've seen a lot of people
homeless in stations
but i've never seen them being beaten up
they really try hard
harder than in other countries i would
say to stay away from
way more difficult in japan to be
homeless
than in other countries
hey you really don't see many of them
oh and
i actually watched like a documentary or
something like that about about this
topic like being homeless in japan or
something like that
and i think it was generally about why
they're why you never see beggars in
japan
because that's you see homeless people
yeah but you never see them begging you
never see them anywhere on the street
sitting there asking for money like in
any other country they don't do that in
japan
you watch that too
i i get it because of like you know
um
partially japanese mentality and all
that
um but
yeah i i've never seen i don't see it
ever
so
i guess
yeah
um
it's really tough for them
um yeah about shame partially i guess
yeah
[Music]
i wonder if it's the same in korea and
china
um
foreign
[Music]
there are a lot really
freeze pop squeeze pops
you really
got me there guys does that mean thanks
to you guys
i always say it
instead of beat him up
response response response
freeze pass
you [\h__\h]
okay okay well now i'm mad
[Music]
now i'm mad
in order to play baseball i need
the baseball bat and your balls
oh
i'll give you this banana next
uh
let's
bash his thumb
that's his name
show him how it feels to get your own
bum bashed
wow
scary
[\h__\h]
i think that was more than just a bomb
named
was that in a newspaper or
soca
hmm i'm tired
am i so tired
i binge watched tv last night that's
probably why
show
in the future like set in actually not
that far in the future uh 20 20 33 or
something like that uh
about uh uploading like being able to
upload your consciousness after you're
dead
or like in the moment that you die and
then um yeah it follows this guy who's
uploaded his consciousness and then
uh
yeah there's a little bit of a mystery
involved
it's funny though um
it's pretty funny so far
yeah an amazon show
i saw like an advertisement of it before
but i didn't i wasn't interested yet but
then then i saw the trailer it was
actually
looking interesting
um
it was pretty pretty interesting
the
the main
lady
actually there's two main ladies
in the game in the shell and they're
both really hot
there's two
ladies in that shell
one is like a blonde cutie
this is really pretty but there was this
awkward moment in the first episode
where they had um
intercourse
in their really really modern car that
drives itself and
after the intercourse it was so like
i've never seen a show before that tries
to hide the woman's
boobies
so awkwardly like normally they would
like pull up their like sheets
their blanket or or
for some reason be wearing a bra or
whatever
um but in this case
the guy was like constantly in every
angle
uh holding his arm in a way that you
would not see her
special parts
[Laughter]
but it was so awkward because it went on
for minutes and it just was like not
natural it didn't look natural at all i
thought it would be more natural if you
would just hold up the blanket so i
don't understand the choice in
censorship there
uh yeah and then for a moment for a
moment
when she moved i saw that she was
wearing like some kind of
skin colored band-aids or something on
top of her
lip knobs yeah
i saw it
yeah
[Laughter]
she probably really doesn't want to show
her nymph nubs which is okay but i
thought it would
have been better censorship to just use
a blanket anyway you'll probably notice
that if you watch the first episode it's
in the first episode
pretty much in the beginning of the show
of the episode
i'm sure it will bother you too
and then let me know how much it
bothered you for me it bothered me 10
out of 10.
it stood out so much it was so unnatural
okay
anyway
tati banana i think is waiting for
me taco
he's like oh no wake up wake up i wanna
go for a walk but then he's gonna be
like you're already in the park go for a
walk yourself
oh they have like a kotatsu
[Music]
i've never seen
um
a place like this before to be honest
like like not like such a
huge
area
with like tents and all that for
homeless people what are you guys
playing i can play something here cards
come play what
where is the explanation
i thought i didn't like notice it really
exchanging so it exchanged twice okay
ah there we go rules okay
how to play this game is played with a
kabuka or hanafuda deck
but only the cards from january to
october are used each month has a
numeric value equal to the month number
january is one october is ten aha
players are each dealt with two or three
cards which they then total
but for totals over 10
ah
only the last digit
is used
one's place
only the last stage is one's place what
the player closest to nine wins okay
only the last digit
ah
okay
okay i think i get it
there are four players including a
banker the banker plays against the
other players who places who plays the
bets
i think i get it
okay
four cards are dealt wait what
four cards are dealt face up on to the
table each player selects one card from
the four
on the table as the one to bet on
next each player receives an additional
card from the deck
the non-bank
non-banker players may stand with two
cards or a third card
to go into the showdown with a total of
three cards
players who choose a third card draw it
from the deck
okay
but if i already have two cards and i
have a number that's like nine or super
close to nine then i might just want to
not go for the third card
the banker draws once the three players
are standing after drawing two cards the
banker may choose to draw a third
the banker may choose which players to
challenge with two cards in which to
challenge with three
huh
a four one and nine one
pay double your bet
i know three of a kind triples it
a 10 10 one pace 20 times you bet what
okay whatever just start the game
okay
what the [\h__\h] is going on
which one are my cards
i have eight and four
which is a
12 so the two
matters okay then i want another card
[Applause]
[Music]
[\h__\h]
do i have enough points
right now i have to bet
what i don't know what to bet on
should i
bet on what's higher or what's lower
bet on the one
okay
why
doesn't matter how much
it's ah dawson though
wait what
what
what why does it say six
ah that's
that's the value of the card that the
banker just put on the one
showdown
but i only have a five
score is seven seven i have a i have a
five
why do i have a seven
either one and a six and i thought it
was the top left one is what i have
five is oh that's the banker
oh
okay
showdown
uh he's got a higher one
so that not keep
ah
i won against the banker at least
okay okay
result zero points why do i uh
no
i have 64 points now but on the right
side it says result zero point i'll play
again
so now
uh someone already bet on the three
before me so i can choose a four four or
seven
i guess i would go for a four
probably
yeah
i got a free
showdown
[Music]
okay
we're getting back our money
oh there's a nine ah but i get an extra
card
um
i will do
the ten or the two
[Music]
yeah 10 would be zero
so if i get a high card
this time i would be pretty lucky
yeah this is like the blackjack that
addiction that we had like a dragon
to feel safe if
my dear seafoam boy and everyone else
was saying too
if if i get [\h__\h] over now you owe me
something
showdown baby
wait what's happening
what
which one is mine
i didn't choose i didn't get to choose
one or did i choose it without noticing
i'm the dealer
why am i the dealer i have a seven
i would
show down
anyway i guess why am i
why am i the banker
show down
hey there's a warrior rocky welcome
oh i get that i'm also a warrior it
might be important maria but i'm a
full-time warrior
showdown
oh oh i can select my challenge
i'll definitely win against this one
wait but if i challenge this one i'll
get another card too no
because i can only challenge a free card
person if i have four cards so i could
challenge this one but will he does he
still have the option to add another one
uh
they have a secret card
oh oh
but they're not gonna add another one
right so i think i'll go with this one
cause
[Applause]
same amount eh what i have to challenge
this one too
oh [\h__\h]
why
oh
victory why why do i have to challenge
all of them
i want to get some
oh my god
[Music]
okay
um why do these people get picked first
what the [\h__\h] uh oh [\h__\h] eight and seven
oh my god
i'll go with eight
dawson
draw card
i understand everything perfectly now
yes it's over there yeah show me down do
it
use
i had a harder time this is easier
somehow
oh
two for free
that doesn't matter
i have
that's what i want right
showdown
oh there's another diner
i haven't lost a single time
that's maybe in the first round um eight
four seven five
[Music]
if i choose a low number i might get it
with one card if i choose a high number
i can still get a third card
i'll go with
five
okay
i'm so fine i'm still okay
[Music]
let's go
let's get to the files
oh wait i'm dealing am i dealing again
am i the banker
i'm the banker i think i have six
i know drawing a card
will put me even lower probably
six is bad
i'll show them
i might lose this round
rocks
okay but i mean i can still win against
the other ones
[Music]
yeah okay
that's okay
that's just a little setback
i know i know this would happen
i actually knew it kusama genius like
that
let's go with two
[Music]
use
mm-hmm
[Music]
seven
all of them are pretty high numbers
except
10 isn't because that's a zero
maybe
i'll go with an a
again
i got a 10 after that so i'm still at an
eight
no issa
today is really the day of mostly side
quests and winning games apparently
that's okay
that's okay we were going pretty fast
with the story anyway
okay i'm almost at a thousand
i can't spend more than a hundred though
oh no i'm the banker again uh
seven i had seven before and it didn't
bring me far
um
but drawing a card
with seven is yeah risky as hell
chances are too low so i'll show down
okay
now this one this one might win against
me
over a thousand i'm out of here huh
where do i exchange my body huh
what
57 million what what but
i'm at 24 million what it's that total
profit 57 million
what does that mean
i only got 24 in my bank
what
57 000.
you only won like 80k
i don't know i got a good amount of
money i think
sorry hopeless guys
i ruined all of you i guess oh there's
another game here coincoin
okay another time maybe but i think
koikoi is sounds already sounds more
more
intricate
there's a lot of games here what are you
side quests
what
we use wooden tags to bet here you can
exchange your cash for tags at any of
the games any tags you're left with
after getting you get exchanged back
into real money as soon as you get up
and leave another hotel
and he just explains everything okay
cool cool
[Music]
am i ready
i think i am
let's go
i'm not racist
i saved before i went to bed so
yeah it's gonna be okay i mean i didn't
save after that gambling session but
whatever
foreign
there's going to be a long ride with the
car that's like 10 hours or so
okay i guess not
[Music]
why why do we have this filter on as if
we're in the past
why what is the filter
though
foreign
can i just say
it really moves me emotionally that oda
and kirio are right now
such bffs so closely connected that
they're able to communicate
through telepathy
that is like so tt and wholesome
they just look into each other's eyes
and have this really detailed intricate
communication
you gotta love it
it's beautiful
yeah
i want one day
i want to be able
to communicate like this with someone
it would be just
the purest love
that anyone has ever seen
yeah it's more than just love it's
being soulmates
um
imagine them just sitting there in the
car
staring menacingly
foreign
and then turns out the other person was
thinking something completely different
damn someone's gonna clean the lenses of
the camera man
oh [\h__\h]
feels like we're in dungeon
i mean like an rpg dungeon oh my god
they're walking upstairs
it's beautiful
oh [\h__\h]
is there a boss battle ahead of us
knock knock knock
nice chandelier
noise
[Music]
i
on this
[Music]
is
um
they want to make me
[Music]
foreign
my
thank you
[Music]
foreign
oh [\h__\h]
the atmosphere
hello
it's money i guess
horse head
not what real why would it be a
horsehead that's so random that it
sounds like you're actually saying the
truth
would it fit into that though
it's mommy not a horsehead that's a lot
of money
[Music]
foreign
um
[Music]
thank you i guess
all right
it's pretty cool
pretty impressive
um
bye
[Music]
why
why are they all looking at me like that
um
[Music]
can i just like
use you as my bat
baseball bat please
okay i'm always doing it alone kobo is
here
hello kobuchan
again i told you guys she has kusogaki
tendencies after all
koba
koba don't call your mommy chicken
that's kobo bad kobo
just mommy or juice senpai or just
kiwawa or something like that or empress
phoenix
no
kobo has to learn
as much as i love kobo
yes yes
yes yes yes yes
i will teach her
okay
let's show couple how cool i am
yummy
i'm i suck at beast mode though
oh dear is there even an item to pick up
here
i don't see oh dear like without an item
it's kind of tough okay they don't seem
to all be going at me at once
okay okay okay
okay okay one down
what's with them
why did that guy look so scared
yeah
okay going well so far but i i would
like to have some aoe damage so let's
try
wait i'm not beast mode i thought that
was beast mode
[Music]
oh wait there are some items
yes
[Music]
[Applause]
let's go
[Music]
as well
oh [\h__\h] what i need to buy time for them
to get out well what do you want to see
i'm trying my best here okay
what am i fighting
was that little
smack okay
[Music]
[\h__\h] this
again
how dare she does she not see i'm so
strong
look at how
how cool i am right now what's what's
thinking about that
[Music]
oh
yes
want some on this huh
you're gonna get your butt spanked if
you continue calling me chimpkin
you hear that
wait what what did he say what
where am i where are we going
[Music]
i'm going up okay
ah i know it's not okay
gotta find them what do you mean find
them all right
[Music]
i beat up about 20 guys what did you do
means in the meantime
[Music]
the door was literally right there why
did we not just walk up
out the door
[Music]
it's not
go go go go go stop talking
go go go go go
oh they're finally fighting with me i
was about to stay like
nobody ever fights with me so sad
what the [\h__\h] am i carrying
what's going on
that must be so funky
[Music]
that must be so [\h__\h] heavy
sorry
sorry i know you were doing something
there
oh my god oh whoa hello i'll take some
more of those then
[Music]
wow oh my god
does this even do good damage oh it
doesn't actually
it probably would do more damage if i
just fight them one on one
but that was fun
oh there's more oh he has a he has a
chair he brought a chair
oh let me get that
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
what are you still doing there
do my friends have hp i don't think they
do
yeah
he knows exactly
where to stop
which by the way i'm saying
sarcastically because i don't really
think you can like the way he
punches them honestly depending on
how that person's physical condition is
i'm pretty sure there's there's cases
where that might kill a person
or
wait is he dead
is she dead okay oh my god
are you dead too that's fast
right now
[Music]
we're done
wow
[Music]
i'm
ow what the [\h__\h]
brothers
hey
stop walking away from me
[Music]
oh yeah
wait not before i played yakuza i didn't
care but
why the hell is there no yakuza
character in the super smash brothers
games while there's several characters
of certain other
games
series holy [\h__\h] wow
i might block that one oh no i did it
let's go
holy [\h__\h] was that a heat though
or just a cool scene for in between
come here
oh [\h__\h]
okay time to heal
oh wait no ah
i forgot
[Music]
oh i haven't done that one in a while
yeah ichiban
would have been i think a great choice
for
a yakuza game i mean they put fire
emblem in there
[Music]
it's not like everybody in the world
knows fire emblem i feel like like from
from like how knowledge not how well
known the games are
um
yakuza is kind of on a similar level
[Music]
foreign
oh i have 30 million let's let's buy
something
[Music]
um
should we do something for beast mode
reduce the rate that the heat goes drops
um
you to perform a resist card when an
enemy attacks during a rush combo i
don't know
help us to help health is always a safe
choice
i have a feeling it's not that's not uh
gonna end here
what does kobo say this dumb
ah
nice
sneaky
kid
um
[Laughter]
i think
you and me
we're gonna have a fun activity after
the stream
mommy's gonna take you
to disneyland
but in reality it's the usual room
but it's just as fun trust me
trust me
[Music]
[Applause]
i wanted to try some loops that i don't
normally use but i don't even remember
any of them what about can i like charge
no
okay
i told you even if i activate those i
won't use them what am i doing
with you guys
when the matrix
[Music]
i don't see it popping up
oh there it was
[Music]
we're like acrobats
welcome to the circus
i want to do something with odom
i didn't activate that that was just the
last scene okay okay oh my but wait
there's more oh is there something i can
carry around oh yes
[Music]
okay come here guys
get up
[Music]
nice
can i do yes
i was hoping for that
oh
that's funny
that's one of my favorite games from
like the past three years
that was such a good game
[Music]
i got it takes two trophy
the audio is sounding weird one second
my capture card is doing funny things i
think there we go
that should have fixed it
have you ever played a yakuza game
before
if you're still here
[Music]
oh
okay
i'm just gonna i'll be right back
never
oh there's always the first time
kobuchan they're actually they're really
funny maybe you had a feeling like me
like before i ever played a yakuza game
i was like oh they look like they're
really like scary badass games but
they're actually really dirty and dorky
[Music]
especially like a dragon so far i must
really say the most recent one like a
dragon
was way more derpy
[Music]
i think the whole um
fighting system
gave it a lot more derpy
um
[Music]
aspects because
the classes were so derpy too
like what was it like like a
[Music]
yeah idle class dominatrix brake dancer
yeah i think that's why i remember it
that's a big reason why i remember it's
so much derpier yeah yeah yeah yeah
okay but i want to know koppuchan
if if you didn't never play yakuza games
before how about rpg games in general
because when i was watching you girl's
debut i i saw that none of you girls
play any of the games that i like except
for maybe like mario party and stuff
like that
uh i was wondering
do not do none of you play any rpgs like
none at all
i wanna know
that's kind of what i do all the time
maybe john left or she's tapping
you impressed huh
well not really
he doesn't look very impressed
he should be though
ah don't know many rpg games
[Music]
well if you if you like what you see now
this is not really
the like normally when i play
like usually
the rpgs i play are cuter
but i think you should give one a try
once doesn't have to be yakuza there's
so many great rpg games out there
sounds good kobo
but don't call me chicken
or i'll have to disown you
and i'll give you kalami mama
[Music]
she's really pushing it yeah she really
is a cheeky brat
oh
this reminds me of like a dragon
there's no why because of the water
scene
eat some of this river
the sunset
um
if you act like this calling me chimkin
all along you don't even have to ask
this question because you only have one
mama then anyway
if you want two mamas
then you better stop calling me chunkin
this feels like a collab at this point
we're having an actual conversation on
stream
more mama more horses
[Laughter]
yeah and if you want more horse then you
need more mama and if you want more mama
then you stop calling me chicken
yes
yeah all of the people in the chat are
also willing to fund horses
but
but you need to be a good girl yes
respect senpai
yeah yeah
but i'm looking forward to collab band
being lived at kobachan i hope we can
collab something i don't know what but i
hope we can collapse something kobuchan
also uh
when we were dming she said yeah that's
collabor ah there we go
she said
she said girl
good girl mama peace okay okay
yeah i don't know what yet it's true we
still have like a month time so until
the collab band is lifted we'll figure
out
something
something something something something
something oh i was i was i already had
some ideas uh
uh
one thing we could do
is
i give you a minecraft en server tour
or you could play something derpy like a
super bunny man or something like that
um
or
although i have done this one several
times we could do the bomb game but i
already did that as a a couple times so
yeah probably not um but i think the
minecraft is a good idea we haven't had
minecraft in a while and and and and
someone needs to introduce you to the
ian sir and i think it should be your
mommy
yeah there are some good options
can introduce you to the japan server
but i'll introduce you to the en server
yeah yeah
she'll be if anything she'll be your uh
japan mommy but that'll be your ian
mommy okay don't you dare get a
different ian mommy
okay i i wonder if the new id girls want
to play minecraft you never you never
played minecraft before
oh my god
i also had my first minecraft experience
after joining hololive
uh we're gonna we're gonna make you a
pro
we're gonna make you a pro yes yes
i'll uh let's let's build a house for
you on the en server too you have an
indonesian server but you also gotta
come to the en server yes yes yes yes
we'll go on trips together i'll get you
a horse in minecraft
i have a horse horse for you waiting in
minecraft and then we can
um we can
we can ride it down the minecraft beach
yeah look at the beautiful minecraft
sunset
it's like
yeah sounds beautiful it's a it's a
date a promise
okay okay okay
yeah
not circles not now circle's gonna get a
brother or a sister
okay
okay and i'm gonna give you some berries
um
because then you become berries kobo and
that's my favorite idol group
so i'll have to put all kinds of berries
on you
don't mind me that's just for my
personal
satisfaction
yeah that is cover
what you you don't know betty school
ball right right i'll teach you about
betty's cobalt they don't they don't
exist anymore but they were an idol
group that was like active for like 10
years and they have really cute songs
and funny songs
yeah i'll teach you about it i'll send
you some songs later okay
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah
i don't i don't think she knows i don't
think she knows i'll give you an idol
lesson yeah
okay
okay coco mama has to continue playing
the game now and focus on the game you
can stay but mama has to focus now okay
this feels like it's gonna be the end of
the chapter
[Music]
foreign
oh
the stories are starting to connect
uh
[Music]
me
monopoly man
wait they really should bring out a
yakuza
wait can we like how if there's so many
monopolies out there how easy is it
to
get a deal of monopoly and put out in
monopoly because how about we as
merchandise put out whole live monopoly
[Laughter]
holo poli
live monopoly
like a collab like with omocat but with
monopoly
have to deal with hasbro okay i'll kill
you i'll tell management unless genma if
you're watching this
write it down
i mean there are so many monopolies out
there
i feel like it's pretty easy to strike a
deal with them
at this point
um
you probably wouldn't buy it why not i
would buy it i would buy that yo that's
like such a that's merchandise that you
can actually use
you can play with your other whole life
friends if you have some otherwise just
play with your normal friends or your
family
and tell them about whole life
it would be such a great way to
introduce them into whole life
characters
that sounds like fun
they're awesome i have heard about some
groups of people who are who have like
friends who who are also into whole life
pretty techy
[Music]
foreign
yes
ah
maybe we should just do a kfp monopoly
fan made one
i would love to design that
maybe like a members only stream
designer
aboard
oh my god
you don't
the original board game
i guess so i mean we can change it a
little bit
um
didn't expect the owner of the empty lot
to turn up in sultan buried maybe a
while before i'm back in kamurocho i
should make sure i'm ready before
heading out i thought this is where the
chapter was going to end but apparently
not so
sukita building
okay while we're here i guess so
i forgot how to do that though
uh
very good
bye bye
take care thanks for coming
[Music]
ah what do you mean
are you kidding me
the game literally just told me to come
back here
and then
this tells me there's still problems in
the area what problems
[Music]
oh ah
i thought it was a general problem
within the story
[Music]
like i have to pass a certain
point in the story
[Music]
these guys
oh oh
strong i mean what choice do i have
is strong really strong
i don't have a choice
i didn't say so i hope i'm okay
laser king lackey
well okay
long stick
[Music]
wow
sounds like fun
[Music]
nice music though i like the ost for
this part
i think this is a new one
[Music]
oh he's dead
hey are you a breakdancer are you
breakdancing class perhaps
[Music]
are you dead
i totally didn't understand i
misunderstood it completely
i thought like it was a story probably
because that was at the same time when
we were being chased
so i thought okay
i can't come back until we're not being
chased anymore
hey yo
okay so anyway i actually don't remember
how to do this
let's see
oh god
[Music]
what's happening is it time to pay out
i don't
[Music]
i don't know what to do
not ready ready oh what it's not ready
yet anyway
can i not do anything right now
[Music]
such cool
okay let me save
what y'all
yeah i did i didn't notice her
but i ignored her on purpose
damn
[Music]
go out and buy properties
oh i didn't see any bible properties
while walking around outside how do i
are they not that obvious
is that our money vault
holy [\h__\h]
what a door
damn
you gotta walk up to them they're not
marked oh
yeah only in this district
they're not marked at all how's one
go
can i buy this place no
this place
i don't know
okay we'll talk to that school
what are you doing now
please do not call me that anymore i've
completely stepped away from that scene
good for you what are you doing here
have you started up a new business
well it's about that you know i can help
you if you're
aha my business
health would be great but what can you
do
i'm no ordinary high school student i
have connections and experience built up
from my buddhist center business i can
help you with distribution logistics and
whatever else your company might need
okay
here we go again picking up really
random people on the street to help us
with our own business
it's her evil plan
the way she looks down there
and smicks
this will let me get a little closer to
him
[Laughter]
dun
okay where are we going there's two
marks
okay
uh
i'm on my way
i still don't know what pocket tissue is
all for
i guess i'll never know
oh
well wow
on my way
oh there's a store a sidequest thingy
over there as well ah is that the s m
one
maybe it is
yeah it is
no time for that now
sorry
uh we're going into this uh
this place no this place
or the side
oh yeah little asia i'm coming for you
yo the security is really bad here
everything's open
uh
uh-huh yeah that looks familiar
interesting place really
cool
what do you mean i forgot to collect
money
it wasn't available
yep
but did we not check after resolving the
issue and it said
i have to wait longer because i
can't collect it yet
it takes five minutes
oh
wait wait wait where the hell was it
here
okay
i have a good feeling that this chapter
is ending like the moment
when we leave
uh
where are we the moment when we leave
the city
but don't worry guys we have a second
uh
yakuza stream this week
we'll still take a look at the next
chapter of majimato like the the
dialogue in the beginning at least
yeah cause i'm curious
and it takes no effort besides listening
which also
is uh it does take up some effort to be
focused and listen but but less than
running around and fighting like this
okay i'm back i'm back now give me the
money
i've waited for so long
hello
[Music]
time to pay out
that's not even that much
and what now start collection
[Music]
should i change something or
not much at first
invest
but you're
but you mean
[Music]
invest in the buildings that means i
have to go out and touch grass though
[Music]
i can't do anything here
i don't get this stupid minigame
[Music]
in the first menu huh
that was the first menu
[Music]
yes i'm very invested totally
oh this one says b
uh huh
[Music]
uh i don't know who to put as an advisor
oh holy [\h__\h] he takes 2.8 million
[Music]
is that important
the advisor
the best ones per cut yeah yeah yeah i
get that but what about the advisor
i invested already oh okay so
oh i don't know
[\h__\h] this [\h__\h] am i done can i invent
can i start collection
change security guard in r2
huh
[Music]
you mean r right
i don't like this i don't like the whole
interface
[Music]
oh yeah
she's probably fun
[Music]
school oh yeah she's a new girl and then
better security
[Music]
what is that like that motivational
speech
is that why you're good at being in
security because you got mugged one time
[Music]
okay
shut up
[Music]
i will not
i will not let chad talk to me like that
nope
it's not marked here like that right
how
much
but how do i know what i can buy
i really don't understand
where was the pachinko i heard pachinko
noises when i was running past something
this was the potential
18 million i can't even afford this
right now
there's something
cheaper
oh no this is not no no no
what about
do i literally have to look up to
everything and see if a prompt shows up
about this place no
this price
no
nothing here
gnocchi academy i want that one
um
commodore health plaza but i can't see
where exactly they are
okay
halfway level
design purple
the purple
i know where the purple is somewhere at
least it shows me here
that one's probably expensive
do i have to talk to you guys
hello girl
how do i invest
i have to talk to
this guy
[Music]
the side of the corner
of the building
uh-huh
will do
huh
what
that one needs friendship with her
oh okay
what the [\h__\h]
max
friendship mm-hmm okay another time uh
is here
thank god i can read japanese so
otherwise i would have never known
i can afford this one
okay this is mine now
okay
but i already started the collection so
i can't um do anything with that right
now anyway right until i collect the
money again
if i understand correctly
okay i'm gonna go back to the place
now
[Music]
baby
let's go
oh
[Music]
um
i'll leave my banana in tokyo then um
oh
75 million
the big reveal honestly game you kind of
ruined it at this point it wasn't
that much of a big reveal anymore
well maybe i just kind of wasn't so
surprised because i feel like the chat
spoiler at me somewhere once
um
baby was just dead i'm not sure if i
would have been surprised if i didn't
read it somewhere
wow look at the nice number
damn
did you guys see it coming
i mean in some there must have been some
kind of connection
between those two stories and there must
have been some reason why that girl was
being chased so yeah i guess he could
have made that connection yeah yeah
foreign
chapter 11 a murky riverbed
coal
yeah we got bombed
i can only hear you one
yes only one white suit
i just it's as if i played this game
before
oh
i always know what magic was gonna say
huh
[\h__\h] he took my woman
oh
oh [\h__\h]
baby
um
really
[Music]
um
her new nickname
when she calls me
you can't do that
no hey
me
[Music]
foreign
oh
mmm
foreign
[Music]
huh
foreign
no more
i hate him
but now we're only really helping him
again because first of all he's abusing
him and
we need we we want for our own interest
to help makoto
just don't want to kill her
okay but
more on that next time
uh what
lip balm nah nah nah more on that
another time
majima healed his wounds yeah he looks
cleaned up now thankfully i need a
saving
spot over there okay
don't worry i'll stay i'll save
next time is i think
on for
no
huh when am i streaming yakuza again
today's tuesday first day i think first
day
am i staring yakuza again on thursday
oh yeah and tomorrow is snack box review
from sweden
um i will read super chats i
i'm not so worried because
it is
european snacks and european snacks
aren't
usually aren't too crazy off of what i
eat
so
anyway
here we go
thank you everybody for watching today
you're welcome to stay if you want to
hear some chit chat and just listen to
me read some super chat those
your messages and all that if you have
an order to pick up
like a super chat
thank you
[Music]
yeah
let me open up
my music player
what are we gonna listen to
[Music]
we did some side stuff today i wanted to
do that like
previously anyway
but didn't get to do it previously so at
least we did it today
um got some side quests
done
[Music]
i think what did you guys say 17 18
chapters or so
so we're at chapter 11 now
that's pretty looking pretty good
gotta go now thank you for watching
thank you
probably do some more stuff with magic
my next time too well perhaps yeah yeah
17 ah wow
we're getting really close
and i do if i do two chapters again
each stream then it will be
three more streams
probably
[Music]
yeah that's actually pretty good so we
could finish it next week possibly if i
do another two yakuza streams next week
[Music]
last chapter is kind of big that's okay
the last stream i all planning some
extra time for the next one
sorry i don't speak any chinese i just
know
and faith
yet and what i need
and
i forgot pretty much everything else i
studied a little bit for a short while
but i forgot
pretty much everything else
[Music]
ah nihao okay i know that one too
no no don't say nice chinese that's like
saying oh nihongo jose disney
after me saying the most basic
chinese
[Music]
just three words and it's like oh you're
something something language is so good
[Music]
no
don't don't even compliment my chinese
worse than others and that says
something
we got chinese or joseph
[Music]
i think it was uh
ah
[Music]
is i think my name is kiara
and
uh there was another thing i remember
nihan gao singh
is i think you're happy
[Music]
and that when i say i'm happy i think i
say wolhan shin
yeah
that okay that's i think that's really
all i can remember right now
[Music]
i was are you happy i guess it was a
question was it a question
[Music]
no no don't praise me no no no no no
don't praise me
i don't deserve praising for something
like that
no no no no no no um
no no no no no no no wow
[Music]
last pronunciation really that was my
that was my concern when learning
chinese that like
you can sound like a [\h__\h] idiot if
you [\h__\h] up the pronunciation like oda
no but like
you can literally say a completely
different
completely different sentence from what
you're
trying to say like instead of saying
something like how are you it could mean
i will i will
i will kill your mother
instead
that's like how dramatically different
it could be
if you just slightly slightly
pronounce it
differently
so
and there's just these really really
really tiny
nuances
that are
that were really difficult for me to
grasp
yeah
[Music]
so
that really frightened me
[Music]
japanese and korean is not really like
that
are there others that work like that
[Music]
vietnamese and ty
oh really
[Music]
oh
yeah i think i'll stay away from
learning a language like that
if i were younger i might have been able
to pick that up but at this point
if i really learn a language it's gotta
be an
somewhat easy one
yeah i gave it a try for a while it was
fun it felt really rewarding to
um start learning the language on
duolingo because i already understood
like
a lot of the
the kanji
um like i could guess a lot of the
things like duolingo would show me one
kanji out of nowhere that i've never
seen before and would be like what does
this mean and i would be like it
probably means this because that it
looks very similar to the japanese
version of it
so
it felt pretty smart
during that
[Music]
like i think that the the kanji for
gaussian for happy was probably
similar
[Music]
yeah that that's the one time duolingo
made me feel smart
oh by the way i want to
um really pick up korean properly so
um my goal is to at least learn the
writing
within this month if i find a day where
i can focus on it and once i got the
writing down i want to do even if it's
[\h__\h] i want to do another korean
duolingo stream
um
or or once i got the writing down maybe
i could ask
maybe i could ask nabi mama
yeah
i just wanna
make i want i want to do the ground work
ninja turtles no completely forget about
those ninja turtles don't worry i
actually i already forgot everything
anyway
when it comes to the letters i forgot
everything already anyway
so i think i can
without worrying too much
start from scratch
the ninja turtles will not confuse me
anymore
um
now everyone lives on hiatus for school
[Music]
oh
i wonder how long
[Music]
i don't know if cronie really wants to
teach me again
and
yeah inna is
i don't really think she wants to do it
either
my chat stopped moving
[Music]
yeah bales has been practicing
i respect that
i don't think she's on the level of
teaching someone else but
yeah i respect that
[Music]
we also have behind her but but i
wouldn't say she's a teacher so
um
[Music]
for basics i'll just
i'll just figure it out myself with
duolingo
[Music]
i don't think she has to admit to it
when she reads super chats in korean
flawlessly so but yeah i know what you
mean
[Music]
i'll try to ask nabi mama anyway maybe
maybe she can take one day
for one stream
to
[Music]
collab with me maybe maybe there's no
harm in asking
[Music]
and maybe i should watch those korean
programs that i used to watch again uh
the
superman show with the babies
maybe i should watch that again since
some pretty much out of tv shows anyway
to us right now
those are so cute and they speak a lot
in baby language so
i i picked up so much back then when i
watched it the first time
maybe i should watch the baby show again
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
i learned some words like andel
yeah the return of superman
watchy soil
yeah
is that why you learned milk actually no
actually not that was not where i
learned it i've been crony taught me
crony
or dueling wait did i learn milk from
duolingo wait no i learned it from
duolingo
i'm not sure anymore
but it wasn't from the show
anyway
zetachan is not really an option either
because there's a one month collab then
and i want to do it soon
and i don't know how good her korean is
like she said some phrases really really
really
fluently
but those are just introductional
phrases
who knows like those are easy to
learn
to flex a little bit i don't know how
much you really
can speak
i don't think she has been able to show
off
that much yet
buddy teach me
[Music]
anyway uh we don't need to try to force
any
collabs but uh as i said i want to first
pick up the
writing on my own
and then
we'll go from there
now
now let me open up my super chat doors
i'm scrolling swellings rolling swirling
swirlings rollings rollings rolling
swellings rolling sir bonnie excuse me
okay chill chill chill chill
by the way yesterday i ate those
leftovers from my hirakatsu it was
better on the first day but now i'm like
really really really motivated to make
more like when i cook
um i don't cook that much with meat
but in this case it was a good chunk of
meat
so i think i'll do it more often it was
pretty easy also i put the leftover oil
in a bottle like you guys told me to do
yeah
i'll use it again soon
[Music]
is that a new emote too qualia that
looks new
screenshots look delicious
that was not my hirakatsu i took some
photos but they don't look presentable i
mean they look normal like there's
nothing special about them they just
look like like
pork meat fillet that has been
fried in some breadcrumbs
[Music]
but the the the gif the gift that was
attached to my tweet was not
mine
i said it i
wrote it there i wasn't trying to make
it look like it was mine
[Music]
i want um
maybe i can ask genma
to um
uh
to buy me one of those like when you
when you get hirakatsu
or tonkatsu shoku in
japan uh let me show you
it's usually
you may have seen this before
[Music]
uh wait
push
here usually it's served like this
um
actually
it could also be on a big plate
with the salad combined
yeah usually it's always
combined where i get it um but anyway
what i'm trying to point out is the the
little um
what do i call it the thing that the
the katsu is
on top of
the
um iron
steel
thingy
[Music]
i want that
if if you just put it on a
on a normal plate and then put the rice
there and all that i don't have all
these like little extra little pretty
japanese bowls i i need that i need to
buy that the rack yeah the wire rack
i need all of this and then i can
present it nicely otherwise for me it
was just like
just i i randomly
put
all of the meat pieces on the plate and
then i had a salad in the
in a not so pretty bowl and i had my
rice
in a normal bowl
and then yeah i didn't even have miso
soup
you can't order it from amazon sure but
it will be overpriced while in japan you
can get these like so cheap
of these you can get like in the 100 yen
shop
probably
you can probably even get more than one
for 100 yen
[Music]
yeah maybe maybe genma can buy from me
and send it to me
generalize the patient don't worry about
that
i'll pay for it don't worry don't worry
it's crazy to make me so yeah miso soup
is not the problem but i want miso soup
i want i want the bowl that miso soup is
served in as well
with the lid
put on top of it
poor jenna why are you saying poor jenna
that's just a tiny little orange i never
asked her to send her anything
the last time she brought me something
was during during donkel document
[Music]
of course i would like to appear in any
of those things but for me personally i
want to do my 3d debut properly first
before doing any kind of half-assed 3d
content and that's something i've been
thinking about today as well
like
i don't know
i don't know what will happen first
me getting a proper suit to use at home
or
going to
japan
so it's like really uncertain
and i don't know when i can do a proper
3d w at this point
and i don't i could already use my 3d
model
in for example
like energy does
without hand movement
i could just like move my head
but i'm like
[Music]
what's the point of doing that
if i if i
use it then i want to use it properly
and i wanted to i want there to be a 3d
debut before and i will not change my
mind on and i might be a little bit too
stubborn when it comes to that but
no it's not about buying one for me no
no no no
the they don't have any stock anymore
but um
let's just say the company is
working on
providing
a suit yes
um but it takes some some time
and i don't know how much time
there's like no estimate
so i cannot
i'm trying to make plans but i can
not make any plans because i don't know
what will happen
and that's driving me crazy it's driving
me crazy
um
the other option would go to
would be going to a
studio but
i would prefer to do it from home for
this
case
because it's just less stressful and i
have i would have no time restraints no
time issues
[Music]
yeah
and i don't want to be watched by people
like basically strangers from like the
staff who work at whatever studio i go
to
and it's awkward having people who are
not related to cover monitor what i'm
doing like even if they sign
a contract or whatever an nda or
whatever
i don't i don't feel that comfortable
about it
it's embarrassing
so if i had to choose and i would prefer
to do it from home
and i will if
if it so happens that the suit arrives
more or less
soon
or or if or if i'm gonna arrive soon
but i don't know when i will arrive i
don't know when the suit will arrive i
don't know when i'll get to japan
so right now i'm the only one without a
suit in myth
[Music]
um
yeah
because all the other girls have i mean
cali doesn't but callie can just do it
in japan
[Music]
so everyone has
their ways of doing 3d already
except for me
[Music]
from home sounds like guaranteed scrub i
thought so too at first but
um ame has already like
told us and showed us a lot and said
it's really literally so [\h__\h] easy
the suit is basically like
a
basically like
turning on your pc
it's really not much work to it
you put it on you get into the suit
you push a button or something like that
you connect it with like wi-fi or
whatever i don't know
i forgot what exactly it was but
it's literally like two steps or
something
[Music]
at first i was worried about that too
but um
[Music]
i missed
me and
convinced me that it's
really not that difficult i mean i would
prefer to have some help if possible but
but i'll just give ame a call if i need
help
yeah
um
i don't know what you guys think
but
i think it will be tougher for me to
really
stay stubborn if i see all the other
girls doing
3d content all the time
then i'll probably
not be able to be as patient anymore
i'll grow impatient probably
but for me i i
i was looking forward to 3d
the moment i was accepted to her alive
yeah i was looking forward to that big
3d debut
the big reveal
and then having it be really good
quality like you know dancing and
singing and all that
and having like a cool background
having some gimmicks there
having some people call in and all that
and
yeah i heard about you know saying that
and that
makes me
feel a bit more assured and calm
that i won't be maybe maybe i won't be
the only one
um
yeah i don't want to be left behind
[Music]
i just feel like if i do too much
like to each their own but if i do too
much like of like like half-assed
half-body
especially now because i don't have a
suit yet the only thing i can do is move
my head anyway so
it really doesn't even make sense for me
um
i can't move anyway so why why why use
it anyway
yeah i want it to be special and i don't
want the 3dw to
have less of an impact
[Music]
because i spoil it too much
my model gets mistaken for 3d
[Laughter]
i'm so used to it now the first time i
saw it i really was like holy [\h__\h] damn
this is so good this is like 3d oh look
at my mouth
now now i got really used to it
but i guess you're right
thank you guys i
i would be very happy if you guys could
wait
for me to figure things out it might
still take
two three maybe even four months
um
but at the very latest for my birthday
i will
force it to happen
if if i can't secure a studio
here for some whatever reason would then
which shouldn't be a thing then worst
case i'll fly over to
where ami lives
and doing that amis place
[Music]
whatever it doesn't matter i'll make it
happen
[Music]
i know
um
[Music]
we should have gotten 30 million years
ago i don't want to wait anymore either
but i also
it's tearing me apart i know
i don't want to wait anymore
especially because you already got a
sneak peek like we should immediately
continue on from that but no i mean
[Music]
i need to do that for dw
before doing a million other things with
pretty
[Music]
i want to keep the original traditional
order
you're tearing me apart lisa what meme
is that
[Laughter]
[Music]
yeah i'll get some more use out of the
low poly
low poly thingy
no the debut is not the concert no no no
the room huh
[Music]
even if i watched it i probably watched
it in german i don't know
i don't recall it
sounds like a horror movie
or
a psychological thriller
[Music]
please wait
and i'll keep you
updated if i can if i'm allowed to say
things some things i cannot say but
when i'm allowed to say something
i'll let you know
[Music]
it's a so bad it's good film aha
i see a kuso movie
instead of crystal game it's a custom
movie
also i got really excited the other day
watching some idol videos from the from
the past
and
[Music]
i sent some of them to nina jay i was
like i want us to cover this and perform
this one day and this one and this one
oh and i want to do this one
i sent her
a lot of songs and she was like oh that
looks so cool oh that was so cool too
let's do it
like there were some
there were some songs that i sent her
that you're supposed to do with two
people
and
they have like choreographies that also
only work with two people
and i want us to reenact that
[Music]
was she familiar with them she didn't
seem familiar with them
which i was surprised about because um
they were pretty famous
thank you okay i should start start
reading super chats
[Music]
and jacob 47 kashin pyro homo nadan
kashin kakun tang kishin mr kashmig's
function violet evil garden dankeshin
patsy duncan speaking of bananas
we have this habit of buying bananas
and then not eating them for two or
three days and then they already get
darker and darker and then i don't want
to eat them anymore
i always waste my bananas
[Music]
jason
and then i always regret so i buy less
and less bananas instead of buying like
five bananas i i get i buy like three or
two and i still do the same it's like in
my mind i have
like
some some kind of
good
i just need to
let them die
banana bread that sounds like a lot of
effort
banana smoothie i was thinking of doing
that at least i wanted to do that
yesterday but then i didn't do it why
did i not do it i don't know because i'm
[\h__\h] stupid
and now it's darker again
[Music]
maybe i'll make one after the stream
by the way i'm having
i think i'm having lasagna tonight
[Music]
banana bread yeah i'm sure it's yummy
but
[Music]
it's effort lots of effort i don't even
have the the thing
that you would bake it with the
the form the thingy
and no it's not monday
i know
it's a sin
well i'll i'll i decide now it's monday
[Music]
[Applause]
you don't have a bread pan
bread
pan
no
what's a bread pan
bread
no i don't think so no no
no
i should buy one
i don't really have much for baking
hmm
and oh the next one also mentions it ah
omoket restock did you guys see it i
tried to notify you guys
asap on twitter there's more coming soon
too because already a couple things
already sold out again
[Music]
you sign okay good
it didn't restart everything yeah i mean
there was a list there
so
they couldn't restock everything at the
same time
but it was still a big restock
and so i saw a lot of people telling me
that they got the kfb hoodie so that's
good
good to see and miniature pincher john
comes on me down for the pinky potential
molting season got back again omo cat
collab products have been restocked and
are available for purchase yeah i was
able to buy caspy hoodie that fit my
body in this chance i think spring will
be fresh and helpful
wow
i'm happy that you got something good
for you
i think omoket was definitely
faster than
whole usual whole life merchandise of
shipping
i don't i don't i don't know how fast it
will arrive in korea but it shouldn't
take
a whole year at least
so i hope it wraps before the end of
spring
but it's a really cool
hoodie so please enjoy it thank you so
much
got stands and keychains oh nice nice
nice i guess you prioritized clothing
last time
i was waiting two months when i woke up
that that's still okay that's so
tolerable especially because aren't you
in europe
[Music]
they were a bit faster in america
it's it's better than whole life
shipping usually so don't complain
stop complaining
[Music]
mine arriving tomorrow
oh yeah
i got the i got the thing from the post
office i didn't open it should we open
it on stream
i can't show you but one second
[Music]
it's not very
heavy and it's pretty flat so i think it
is the those cups
[Music]
okay opening it now
[Applause]
oh
let's see
let's see what's inside it's christmas
baby
it's christmas
[Music]
it's not bad
what oh is this
[Music]
um okay there were two things in there
one thing was deco nina's new album
which
um
i would call
deku nina actually ascends to
a whole life in order to have whole life
send it to every
whole life member who sang dec who
covered deco nina's songs before which
is really cool
a cute gesture
yeah because i covered some deconino
songs
um
i got the album looks nice
[Music]
and then the other thing is
i guess i'll show it on twitter it's a
magazine
called
uh with somebody senpai on the cover
it also comes with a clear file
in in
swimsuit clear file
oh
you guys know what i'm talking about i
had contact wait did i did i have an
interview in this one
ah there's some
there's some stuff about the whole life
super expo in in here
[Music]
leading up to the concert
uh-huh uh-huh
yeah there's some advertisement about
the concert
oh
and
oh yeah yeah wait this is uh
oh
then there is a page that entered
several pages that introduced every
whole like japan member
[Music]
is in here too
oh it's just the basic poses though the
default poses
and then it's like
taka nasi kiara
and my my info
oh they they wrote kfb and capital
letters on this one
and recommended streams from each of us
and there's council then there's id
[Music]
oh then there's some recommended songs
oh
there is ah yeah i remember that i
remember that there is a
there's an interview that i did for this
magazine
there's a page where me and nancy are
together like she's on the right side
like the right page and i'm on the left
page
i'll put out the photo on twitter
and it's all in japanese but um they
asked me to
introduce
my favorite
favorite song that i made or like my
not my favorite book the song that i
would recommend
and why
and
[Applause]
if there are any like
behind-the-scenes stories and all that
[Music]
and what i like about it it's pretty big
and i chose heart challenger actually
surprisingly maybe
[Music]
i'm not exactly sure why
i went with that i guess maybe because
it was underappreciated
and maybe because i thought that uh
it comes out sometime after
the one year anniversary or so
i'm not sure
but i also put a lot of work into the
into the whole production of that one so
yeah
i think i'm ah and iris me and iris are
the only ones from ian
holy [\h__\h]
this
like everyone takes up one page okay and
then there's lisu who takes up two pages
talking about her original song addis u
[Music]
because she had a million things to say
about it apparently
oh but they also they didn't only for
the ones who wrote filled it out in
english i filled it out in japanese but
the phones once you fill it out in
english they um put both english and
japanese
uh translation
on these pages so
this is
is a [\h__\h]
book
[Laughter]
holy [\h__\h]
why is it so long
holy [\h__\h] she gave a lot of
text to work with them
[Music]
oh
then there's anya who
like basically everyone else
kind of uh introduced songs of their own
but i guess anya has no solo song so
anya introduced um
shadow iza blue clapper
ghost yeah those three songs
[Music]
okay and then there's oh then there's
some pages about actually two pages
about
whole live idol project first live
bloom
and honolulu first whole live fantasy
first live fun fun island and vaca oh
there's something about vatamin's first
life
an aquasimples concert
for last second first and for my first
vest
a lot of
nice photos and
all that
wow it's quite a lot of pages like one
[Music]
it feels like one
one
ninth
of this
magazine is about us here's like a
the
half of the
more than half of the magazine
is a manga
[Music]
damn
well
or or several mangas i'm not sure
i'm not sure what this magazine is about
usually
but we took up
uh 90
of the non-manga content
and i got this
swimsuit clear file i'm so cute it looks
really pretty it's kind of like
see-through and yellow
oh
whole live summer
brought to you by ozara subaru
i wonder if i'm even getting the cups
then because it wasn't in here
yeah okay so that was a nice surprise
for sure
the magazine came in later alligator
[Music]
although maybe i should check with
managers on first i mean i'm not going
to put up screenshots just little photos
i think it should be fine
in general
uh
i received
quantic
magazine
and i put up some photos of
the pages
[Music]
she might be sleeping so
she might not answer me
jmt
it's the same magazine polka did the
stream about no that one that one that
polka did was the pamphlet for the
concert
this one is a separate
random
magazine
one of the million magazines that are
being sold in japan
it's a different one they just did a
special
feature of whole life in it
[Music]
i'll show you
if jmt gives me permission
oh but okay i'll show you one thing uh i
know i don't wanna
you guys know i don't wanna spoil my 3d
too much but
jmt gave me permission to
show
something specific on stream
um
i asked if i can upload it in on twitter
as pngs i'm still waiting on the okay go
uh
but for now
i am allowed to show you
[Music]
uh
the
the the ones that were in the magazine
in the pamphlet
the 3d shots
on stream at least
[Music]
oh she's cheating it's huge there you go
wow
[Music]
rocky
armpit
[Music]
and then there's another one
but
for this one
i actually want them to fix one part so
let me let me cut it
let me cut it
i'll cut one part off
okay okay this should be fine
[Music]
this one's so cute isn't it
this one's you kai
[Music]
oh my god i'm surrounded by friday
nothing
[Music]
i'm grabbing you with that happy face
i'm like i'll get you and put you into
the usual rooms
your head to strangle i
don't know no i won't strangle you
always really cute
kawaii
and this makes me feel
very sad that i can't use my 3d right
away
to show it off
the cutest one is in the middle oh come
on all of them are me
i like how small the hands are oh
i would say
they just look that like that they're
not that small
maybe they are
should i get that fixed
i feel in that one holy [\h__\h] my face
wait wait wait let me change let me
change one second
uh you guys hang out with fruity kiwa
for a second
let me change it to my main outfit
my default outfit
then we can compare
[Music]
i can't do the hand pose but
my teeth are way more visible my front
teeth
how do you do that in front if i need to
if i want to show my front teeth i have
to be like
i have to open my mouth that much
wow i want to be able to show my front
teeth like that
[Music]
am i looking into the camera
[Laughter]
no
yeah the mouth shape is different but i
i like it i like this more this one
and this one is like oh wait
oh
[Music]
oh oh oh that angle oh
oh i'm down here
wait where am i looking i don't i don't
see the camera when i look away
let me look
[Music]
pretty accurate
a bit more orange in the fridgey one oh
yeah i guess it's a little bit more
saturated a little bit more contrast
yeah
but the the eye is a wow
what else
the hat is yeah
that is fine
both hats
yeah
i was saying that maybe the outlines are
a bit too
too strong here and there
but that's just something small that we
can fix later maybe
eyes wow
yeah the fringes yeah yeah that's that's
what i also mentioned before i think to
you guys when i said something feels off
and i think it's that normally here in
life today my hair looks really soft but
in 3d it has a certain outline to it
if you look at the the bottom of the
fringe especially you can see it
strongly i think and and the the ribbon
the neck ribbon
but i'm not complaining i like them very
much
in this beautiful form
it makes me sad i can't use it more
but but those are really nice i'll uh
if i get permission i'll upload them
properly
on
twitter
as png's or something so you guys can
use it for whatever and then i might use
these two
in a thumbnail maybe i was thinking
i want to wait for a 3d debut but maybe
for thumbnails
maybe for thumbnails i'll use my 3d for
now because i can do cute poses
i think i might make an exception for
the performance but i first have to
figure out
how it works
first of all
um
it would be pretty useful sometimes
sometimes i feel like i wish i could
implement my hands in
in my
thumbnails but can't really do much in
life today
and it would give you guys at least
at least in uh in still for him some 3d
potential i think for me
free um
that's okay because that's in the still
form
and it's not like super hd either
[Music]
oh the ribbon that's true my ribbon on
the large hat is a bit bigger in life
today that's true
it's actually quite a bit bigger
oh like it's smaller and trickier that's
true i didn't notice that
[Music]
i have to write this down before i
forget it
okay
[Music]
you might move your shoulders higher and
freaky well what are you trying to say
[Music]
yeah i didn't they're so cute
they're so cute
ah should we leave them up here
i'll leave them here
you come in here and you see three not
one not two but freaky one
what
exciting
[Music]
the birch oh
true
thank you
[Music]
side effects of the usual room
what a deal what a
steel
oh you came back for me lunch break
welcome back
surprise it's me quinoa
[Music]
koba has two additional sugar
i am not only one mommy
i can be three mommies for you
we're surrounded yeah
chickens i have multiplied
[Music]
and the gamer created wrestle free
dancing
thank you
thank you for the red super chat wow
all freaky hours
worse or are thanking you
the gamer created
[Music]
thank
come on can i can you probably admit to
hook about but that you're selling
computer specs online
that was a funny bit
yeah
daryl raw dance
[Music]
if you
if there's anyone here who didn't get it
again then don't worry there will be
another restock and another i don't know
another and another
there's some guy with a mouse mustache
don kitchen salty soda thank you for the
pink super chat i want to watch the show
more but i have to go to work in the
morning
i'll make more money for super chat
thank you
fighting fighting
i have um
this week i think i have some early
streams member stream is early too
because i i noticed that a lot of my
members streams were
late in the evening for me um and kind
of in the middle of the night for sea so
this week we have an early
uh member stream
and on the weekend
i always try to put them on the weekend
so that even if it's a shitty time zone
it's a time slot then you maybe still
can catch it
[Music]
oh freddie cuba was so cute holy [\h__\h] um
see you tomorrow yes tomorrow uh stream
starts pretty late
but it's a shorter stream so
please try to watch the archive even if
you cannot watch it live okay
and maybe try to come to the members
only stream salty soda okay
okay
fighting
jackets monkey thank you in the game
agreed
thank you for the pink super chat
thank you
sorry thank you i'm late here's a pit
here's pay a fine for being tardy can
you forgive me
[Music]
lot of the koreans like my
my evil
usual room act and all that but
maybe you're looking forward to that too
but it's okay i'm not gonna be mad at
you
i'm not gonna
act mad now
it's okay don't worry about being late
or leaving early it's okay i understand
you guys can't come much i'm really
impressed that you guys tried to come so
much anyway to my streams even even in
the middle of the night and then i don't
even speak korean and i really want to
pay back to you guys i want to give back
to you guys
this probably makes no sense if i
translate it but
[Music]
wait maybe i've there's a good word in
japanese for giving back that would
probably translate better
wait
[Music]
why she
delicious
[Music]
does that make sense
you understood it right
[Music]
me
uh
[Music]
why does it sound so
japanese
[Music]
um
wait not this month no no no no no
next month
for me in my head it's already april
like it's a chuni
no no
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay
thank you for the pink sticker thank you
thank
in an interview they said
the the kilo doesn't show up at fighting
games because they don't want them to
hit room
i heard of that before
ah
damn i guess he really doesn't hit women
in the game
[Music]
at all
did we fight woman enemies in like a
dragon ever
trying to remember
[Music]
yes we did like that uh korean lady
was the
from the chinese
was it the chinese or the korean mafia
that had a lady that we did fight we did
fight ladies yeah yeah yeah even if it
was just that or did we fight her did we
find her no wait no did we find her i
don't know
or was she in our team i'm getting
confused i feel like we did
yeah we did fight her
[Music]
oh did we
we did
at least
one
at least one
we made an exception or maybe did we not
fight maybe no you're not kidding i know
no no no i know not kenya but uh ishiba
i know no i'm just comparing if ichiban
hits women
[Music]
i should just send someone else to fight
in her
[Music]
uh
instead
oh that could be true
oh
damn it
it went wow okay i guess
ichiban also doesn't
fight girls
oh
okay
that is i guess
a reason to not
put him in to smash brothers because of
lore
but
why would you turn out um turn down an
invitation like that
super smash brothers in retain that kind
of implies
maybe it was like talked about before
there was a
a chance but they didn't make it happen
yeah manjima could have been cool
he's a [\h__\h] gentleman
yeah
damn
uh black version
and thank you for the rent super chat
oh you're right navida mini i remember
that i remember that from like a dragon
that when we were fighting kill
he would not hit my female party members
that's why you guys told me to put one
of my female party members into the
party before fighting kidville
yeah
wait did we fight kill i think we did
yes yes we did of course we did
i don't remember anything man
[Music]
thank you
it says kobo in the usual room new
roommate let's go
i gave it i gave her one more chance i
just threatened her with a good time in
the usual room
um
for now she will not be joining you
sorry uh she also seems to for now
have stopped calling me chicken
yeah
i was like so proudly so surely so i was
so sure
the other day when i was talking about
her i said oh you know how all these
other girls they seem like kusagaki but
kobu no
she doesn't seem like a kusuki to me at
all she just seems like a happy cocky
like a genki cocky we're just talking
about it and then she comes here and
then she turns into a kusuoki
[Laughter]
man
why you do me dirty like that why
that doesn't mean anything
oh yeah we all fought kawaiigaki
we were
we're a bamboozled
absolutely bamboozled
she fooled us
no not by her looks no no no no no her
look said kuzugaki
[Laughter]
but
her personality and her debut stream
fooled me
and i thought i couldn't be fooled
[Music]
thank you mother-son mwah
eh
[Music]
shooting games she likes fps we could
play paladins
oh yeah
that's the one shooting game that i
don't mind playing at all
especially because i got the voice back
of the famous paladin's announcer amelia
watson
i can flex on her with that
[Music]
brandon thank you
and james mcphee
[Music]
potential taking care of business
always i don't remember what this was
was it about kokochan i guess it was
probably about kobuchan
still thank you james
friendly
let me try to
translate google
translate
oh my god yes duh a million what yes
i know unbelievable
uh
[Music]
you
thank you for the pinky your attention
supervillains congrats for your whole
face performance so we still got some of
those
i loved it so much so that i forced i
mean i persuaded my loving my my loving
siblings to watch the whole concert oh
they thought you were great as well and
even said you were one of the best
dancers
[Music]
one of them just kidding
thank you
ah
how young are they
i wonder if they
thought it was cringe i hope not
thank you though thank you i'm glad you
got to watch it
with some nice company
some supportive
nice company dan kishon
[Music]
holy what i see you just come welcome
welcome welcome
you see uh three kiwawas and you have to
choose which one is the real one
[Music]
it's me
i mean we're all real but i'm the only
one who's alive currently
these kiwahs are just wax figures uh
that i stole from madame tussauds wax
museum
that's why you can't find me there
only because i stole my own wax figures
[Music]
thank you
for the pinky as a native speaker of
chinese i have to say you're pretty good
dancer now stop lying tell me why the
[\h__\h] you why are you always lying why
the [\h__\h] you lying
[Laughter]
thank you thank you
very sweet of you
but it's a lie
oh you guys like the armpit kiwawa
[\h__\h] perfect
oh
[Music]
i'm not good at english so i use a
translator it's been a long time since i
joined the membership oh but i couldn't
participate in streaming because i was
busy but i watched it on kitty nokia oh
thank you for always doing fun
broadcasts
thank you too
then you think if you remember you
should come on sunday to my membership
stream it's at a good time for korea
please come
i'm waiting for you oppa
um
[Music]
can i come to a membership stream too of
course
of course you can
[Music]
membership message let's go
let's go
[Music]
what was that
was that a cat i heard a noise
i don't see a cat in my room
welcome to the membership
what is plan for membership oh currently
i feel like gaming i feel like
[Music]
this is sound
with my headphones it's hard to tell
yeah i was thinking of maybe fall guys
again sorry but full guys is so much fun
with you guys yo
and it's quick
[Music]
i hear really
tiny
hammering sounds but tiny like it's not
an actual hammer against the wall
[Music]
are they telling me to be quiet
it's not even 10 p.m
i hope not because i never had issues
here
actually you know
a while ago until a while ago the
apartment right next to me was empty
and just a little while ago
someone
moved in
[Music]
i hear it again
do you hear this i don't know if they're
telling me to be quiet
it's it's like really tiny i wouldn't
bang on someone's wall like that
if i want them to be quiet
i don't know what they're telling me
[Music]
now they're hearing it again
maybe maybe maybe maybe the mic picks it
up now wait wait dude
what if i what if i don't talk for three
minutes if they still do it then it
doesn't mean then it means it's not
because of me
right
we're testing something
um
how i can play music though
for you guys
[Music]
it was immersive
okay what happens if i now talk again
what did i now read the pictures again
never mind it's not because of me
they're just starting to drill
right now i hear like a really quiet
they have like a really quiet hammer and
a really quiet drill
i hear like really really quiet
like soft drilling
yeah okay okay it's not it
can't be me nah
it's like a
like they're drilling
in in like in at the dentist's office
did you hear it
it's really quiet today actually i woke
up and i was like i want to sleep some
more but why is it always that in
moments like this
that's like the moment where you want to
sleep a second time fall asleep for a
second time
that's when they start drilling
somewhere in the uh house
you guys always are that lucky are you
guys always that lucky
like me
people neighbors only drill when i want
to sleep
i know right
now
wait actually
wait the weird thing about this is that
they're drilling it
9 30 p.m
but okay that's why they're so quiet
they're really trying to be quiet just
do it tomorrow then
i heard a little punk funk funk again
let's do it tomorrow then oh my god
okay whatever then
it's distracting me but okay
um
foreign
[Music]
bang on their wall exactly
i should be the one banging on the wall
anyway
it doesn't really bother me
[Music]
uh
the shortest giant duncan thank you
you're going skiing in austria next week
from you're coming from england
[Music]
i hope there's still good snow because i
actually asked rmt
um if it's too late to go skiing again
sometime soon very soon
and she was like yeah probably
[Music]
because it's getting pretty warm here
am i
feeling
little tough i mean there could still be
snow but not the best snow
i hope for the best for you the higher
you go this the better the snow will be
uh probably i can tell you that
and and go early in the morning
uh rmt tells me that
the slopes are the best early in the
morning before everyone else uses them
go with the very first
uh
ski lift
until there's no hokey oh
no
[Music]
i saw that
yeah shadowverse added the resplendent
phoenix girl as a leader finally
wasn't like like during the shadowverse
tournament wasn't i saying like oh i
wish she was a leader
or something like like what
or did they tell me ah she will be one
day or she is in the chinese version or
something like that i don't know
or a japanese version
of shadow verse
it just sounds familiar to me
[Music]
why did i
i feel like we talked about it before
oh
we're anticipating it
don't quite crawl me neither
[Music]
one important thing to be done right yes
that's what i'm thinking thank you okay
i'm glad you agree missed miss dankeshen
yeah um
there are more dokomi tickets going on
sale on the 4th of april
[Music]
what's your favorite weekend day guys
huh
mine's
saturday
[Music]
love the chit chat today i trust you
feeling that a real debbie before doing
3d stuff is better
i really like that you want to stick to
whole live traditions
yes that's important to me this
comparison now by the way highlights how
beautiful your 2d model is already it's
so close to 3d oh
yeah yeah yeah
thank you
it is it is very very well made indeed
yeah the textures are like literally it
looks like they just
placed it
on top of it like
plastered it's just one on one the same
like the hair
they probably
i don't know how they do it but they
must just probably
put it on top of that
i don't believe they have had to drill
that
looks so good
[Music]
about as subtle as ichiba
i at this point
i have to be this
subtle
i i have to be
but i'm not saying anything
um
[Music]
thank you unity chat
pump duncan black mage 666 thank you
skye thank you for the red super chat
does that mean i can have a free times
kiss today oh
let's try
thank you for the red super jet
here goes nothing
[Music]
okay perfect perfect
wait one more time one more time i did i
was wrong in the beginning
[Music]
okay okay i'll cook
[Laughter]
many a kisses
my mouth didn't move this time
no no no
no
a bit late but amazing performance
at home office might i ask for ghost
love score by night wish the sun is kind
of never heard of that
i was actually thinking about singing
some old
uh
pop classics
like
i guess just wanna have fun and oh girls
just wanna have fun
uh just like in that area uh
i had some others noted down forgot
about them
i was
already busy learning those songs
probably
[Music]
we have some whitney houston and i don't
know there were some
songs that i got really
inspired the other day when i saw
a certain
uh show
um
yeah maybe i'll throw in some madonna
[Music]
yes
classics that everyone has heard before
please look forward to it
[Music]
moscow moscow nine nine nine nine nine
nine nine cute cute pop classics
[Music]
thank you for the pinky sorry tanjo i
switched my ocean to the left
wait which side left my side left or
your side left i'll i give you none of
them you can keep the middle one
you think thank you for the pinky i'm
not lying ten so thank you okay
but those phrases that i said those ones
i've practiced a bit if i tried to say
something new i probably really really
really butcher it
but i try to be very careful
when i speak that language because it
can be messed up so easily
um
[Music]
thank you
and with that i'm done reading super
chats so thank you everybody for
watching today i'll go now i'm hungry
and a bit tired and i want to cuddle my
kitty cats
um i'll see you tomorrow
probably reservation won't come up until
tomorrow yeah i'll sleep first before i
put up the stream and the thumbnail and
all that
um
[Music]
later k
oh that's so cool to sing
little k what's up k hey kane
i missed you okay
[Music]
sound like
thank you like you're really chill
about me
going to watch amano oh that's a good
idea what is she streaming thank you w
w korean
thank you for the pink super chat no
text what
what
really
[Music]
thank you i like your your profile
picture
no no more comes anita
she's streaming a detective game ah
interesting
oh by the way
i
uh back when mummy
was oh my another one thank you kamsa
[Music]
why are you so generous thank you and i
was saying back when mummy was about to
debut or when she debuted
boy rhizo3 too late
i'll read it one thing uh
she um
i wanted to do a holotomy
one-on-one collab with her
and
i i really wanted to play kiwi with her
but back then i couldn't play it yet due
to uh
reasons
but now we can play it so
uh we're gonna finally play it next week
yeah next week will be double hulatory
because it will be a one-on-one collab
with mumei
finally we'll play kiwi
it's a cute co-op game with two kiwi
boobs
yeah
and the other one will be the big
holotoy collab
[Music]
i'll get double mummy action that week
no no no no no nothing will get
cancelled this time
it was uh really difficult to
get a date going with these girls
but
yeah in the future i'll probably focus
more on smaller holotoy groups that are
easier to manage
to
get a hold of easier
[Music]
double mummy action yeah
yes
these birds are so elusive yeah they
just fly away
you you can't you can't like just run up
to them you need to slowly approach them
slowly so that they don't fly away
but i really just wanted this wonderful
hollow burps collab
um
because of reasons just because just
because she wanted it to be done
they wanted one big
collab where we're all together
and then
i know we can do like one one two two
two and one
it was two on one three people four
people collapsed and all that
so thank you rice for free for the pinky
on you i forgot it's payday today where
is it oh i guess
no the month is still two more days but
okay
maybe it's pay day for you here is this
month's salary congratulations
congratulations on hollywood gaining two
members in the past few days two
two
ah holo stars
well the homo stars one is not a verb it
just has a bird mascot i think you're
just saying it as a joke so you probably
know
uh the whole burp one is not a
verb
as far as i know just has a bird basket
and
the uh
yeah kyla is not a real penguin
she just gets called a penguin because
she
looks like one
[Music]
yeah
if the holostars one joins
ah
[\h__\h]
crap if the whole star one would join
then everybody with a burp thingy would
join
ah crap
crap so um wait what did you guys say
flex it right flex it
flex it did you guys see it flex it
i think you guys said flex it it doesn't
help
[Laughter]
you see my inner fine
[Music]
punch it okay hunting
i'm not laying egg
she's not getting a sister
thank you best idol my life what what is
happening
what
why why why why why why why
thank you thank you
[Music]
i will go now
yes
thank you everybody trevor g also thank
you for the super chat
okay
stretch
and in germany
[Music]
laying an egg
no
no no
[Music]
tomorrow swedish snacks and i really
hope this won't be disappointing again i
might have to cancel
this
series or my subscription
if
to that snack bugs thingy if this one is
a disappointment too
i'm scared oh my snack books reviews
will be famous for being a
disappointment and not being accurately
representative of each country's snacks
man i'm scared i'm scared
i don't want to get people's hopes up
because i'm so scared now this snack box
has only disappointed me until now
only literally only disappointed me even
the international one disappointed me
because it had shitty really shitty
pop-tarts it could they could have sent
me good pop-tarts but they sent me the
worst flavor ever
i'm sure sweden will not disappoint
i don't know
it's a fun game for this series scuff
snack box scam boxer
i hope so
i'll continue it until my um
subscription runs out at least
and then i might look for other places
or do uh original ones for a while
asking people for
australian and indonesian snack box and
so on
scan box review we should just rename it
oh no
[Music]
he doesn't want to leave
what duh
okay i'm going now
bye-bye
no way
yeah it would probably be a mix of
norway and finland snacks yeah
i can see that
bye bye
[Music]
bye
oh my god
[Music]
so
you