[Music]
reflection going under confused
Obsession I still wonder if I was made
for you if I could always
see oh please oh make me up
[Music]
you perfect for you pretending like it's
Jack me down so life and
it got I'm asking why you never see what
I want what I need oh do
you do
you follow through let you pursue but
now you so me on a m I tell you up into
shreds I don't even know what to do with
this man cross it be good my
me with told you do anything the left
and but I be the king and queen of
you yeah begging you to see I'm you you
are me it seems like everyone wants it
all around around running running around
on and on keeping me captive Escape my
way you say I'm way too fragile I'm just
your perfect Idol break me shake
me you never see what I want what I need
oh do
you do
you follow through like
you
now you sold me on a Mir I you up and
I don't even know what to do with this
man tell me the cross it be good play A
Part my
[Music]
Mir
and you make me fall in love
yeah
[Music]
my you so me out on i k you up into
shreds I don't even know what to do with
this man me the it be good play A Part
my
miror
I do dis on and on and on
Mir
[Music]