[Music]
so
kiki
hey
yeah
welcome
everybody once again
to tuning the finale but there's a rust
logo
science wait oh forgot
i forgot i [\h__\h] i forget tweeting
about this apparently a lot
oh
cat hair
time
[Music]
okay i got the cat hair nice
then we shall tweet
everybody
yes
stream starting
yeah everybody
watch to make tonight
finally all right
starting
comment
watch
me rage
as a cute fox
[Music]
yuri
every time
you really have to haven't heard that in
a million years but i think it sounded
like that
i have a smoothie
uh i have a cat called smoothie and a
smoothie called smoothie
[Music]
what did the song
go like
i never cat hair
oh no wonder i have cat hairs in my
mouth i'm drinking smoothie
oopsie must have been a mistake
i named my drink yeah i named this movie
it's so original
wait i wanna
i'm gonna listen to the hiroyu reopening
opening
which one was it there's several ones
this one
ah
[Music]
yay
this [\h__\h] is a banger
sorry i'm just
just enjoying
myself
i'm so cute
ah i should sing uh yuri songs in my
karaoke sometime but then that would
mean i need instrumentals that i'm
allowed to use and i don't think there
are any
ah
sad life um
i know you know guys there's so many
songs i would sing if there were
instrumentals that i could use but uh
ah
nine no it's not kind of fun there's
like
uh on camera there's at least some
korean songs some
but japanese songs
no
nothing really it's mostly english songs
but i'm i'm like oh felix ah
i haven't seen you in a while wow
thank you uh what was it what was i
going to say i'm grateful enough to have
cut off on for all the english songs at
least
they have pretty much almost everything
i need
except some
what were there was there was one artist
who or two artists two songs i wanted to
sing and i told you guys before that i
don't have the instrumentals so sad
[Music]
no
yeah hayley kiyoko for example hi hi
chunky wonky
is it your ritual now to say hi in the
beginning of my streams
[Music]
you say it in the beginning and smoothie
says it in the end
well i don't know what was the matter
with her yesterday she was
so needy oh well she's scratching the
scratchy pole
yes go scratch it tear it apart just
like in house of the dragon
well
you're way cuter than them though i'll
give you that
you don't you don't intimidate me quite
as much as they do
did you hear that guys
just cute
the moment i reach out for her i'll move
a little bit from my chair that could
mean that i'm about to stand up she runs
away
it's [\h__\h]
cheeky cheeky brat
meow
man
what's it today
is it uh
we will talk about the
first episode because i just watched it
but we'll talk about it once i'm in the
game
controller check
sure
bgm
check game on the screen check but kind
of not perfectly positioned um
[Music]
[Laughter]
he's so cute
by the way what are you coming here for
if you run away anyways she wants to
play catch
up
what are you here for now she's she's
hiding in the lower level of the cat
tree in in the in the box you know
as if i couldn't see her there
okay are the parts still there when i'm
in the game
i don't recall
let's see
yes okay then i could i might as well
cut them
all right
might as well cut them why not oh sure
okay is it now
actually sixteen to nine i'm like
nine
sixteen to nine
so confused with this window size okay
now it's good no no it's decent
oh sure
okay
welcome back everybody we we are going
to finish this today
it will be a challenge but i'll i will
finish it
although i wouldn't mind the screen to
be a bit bigger on my side why is it so
small
how is it that no it's [\h__\h] tiny on
my screen that's no i don't believe it
it's that's smaller but it basically
just changed it into the same size but
16 to nine instead
can we well can we have it bigger what
is that what's the what's the 16 to 9
but bigger now
what's 16 to 9 the bigger this one
no that's definitely not it
this one
now is that 16 to 9
oh my god
oh my god what is it
[Music]
she's so stupid man what is her problem
ah do i need to like
chase her once so that she will shut up
will you bear with me for one second
she's gonna run away now yep
[Music]
i think so yeah pretty sure okay here's
here's my offering to the
gods here's this cattle
[Music]
no you do are you gonna leave me alone
now huh
are you gonna let mommy stream now huh
[Music]
cute right i know so cute if only you
could see
ah
okay
please leave me alone now
you go
and you leave the room okay don't come
back i love you
please come back
she is very squishable yeah
okay
hopefully she's now satisfied
uh
okay
this is a good size i can actually see
what's going on in the game wow
it was a mistake to buy a 4k monitor i
feel like because the bigger the
resolution right the the the more like
the more the higher the chance that obs
can't handle it right
like my pc or so i guess
but i have to make it big enough for me
to see something
yeah
okay so we ended here where um
there's i think
some crazy cult ritual going on let me
move myself
a little bit
i can force my money to be 1080 oh
interesting
okay
i'm scared uh do we remember how to
fight yes yes yes yes probably roll
and then square and triangle are those
thingies
okay well
am i supposed to just run right in there
they come from this door
yeah i think so
there's other doors so you know what i'm
not gonna run straight into that that's
like
oh
it's just one of them
he carries one sword but no shield
looks like me come here
nice
okay warm up cool sword though eh
this looks kind of sick
uh
what are they doing
don't
they also like walk super slowly like i
said that they're like zombies and they
have no poise
at least it feels like they have no
voice
do i even have to
do something about this
their laser doesn't do [\h__\h]
are they [\h__\h] weak i thought they
would be a little bit stronger or have
like you know mirrored abilities to me
i do like their sword
oh i see that okay
oh
and instantly i'm scared of them
instantly
ah [\h__\h]
shite
oh man do i have
the mask
but i don't need it here right i'm a
ghost so
i guess i'll i'll keep what i have
oopsie
here comes the real challenge
[Music]
yeah
hey what's with him
ah
is this another casework
where i can't go below
like 0.5 hp
yeah that dude felt a bit stronger right
that one is faster
was there something there
no no no no
that one was kind of minibus what
you're joking right that was how was
that a mini buzz
they're learning as they fight
are they really no way they can't be
that smart
uh move
move your corpse
um i'm like dying
oh oh
oh no i thought this was the main room
again but no no
i see those sparks i'm not gonna run
into them
stream spikes
okay uh yeah this one had normal eyes
the other one the stronger one had like
like glowy eyes eyes
a carrot or a pepper whatever you want
it to be your choice
stream bikes
did you guys see the new schedule you
guys were all really happy with it
apparently you're welcome
i'm glad i could make a schedule of your
liking
a lot of different games
that we just recently started
tuning
cult of the lamb
rust and we're gonna start age of
empires
because ooh not you guys no
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
that's not the right weapon
wait what did they just
did this
just
[Music]
okay i can't die
wait where do i
revive okay okay
ah
wait there were two rooms here i went to
the rats in the first time right did i
yeah i can just run past them they don't
give a [\h__\h]
oh i will do that
i will do that
uh
yeah i can heal but like
[Laughter]
i know
okay what was i saying oh yeah um
so for the
for age of empires i remember that game
from my childhood
i think i played it a little bit
hi you again
somebody of my family definitely played
it more than me
um but yeah i know like was like
basically about you build like
yeah you build
a
village a city and
an army and then fight against
the others
what i did not know is that you can play
together with other people online i
wasn't aware of that
until like recently
um
hey youtube
is it for everybody
well i don't think it's for everybody
okay for me fine here do you what
okay just a little hiccup okay i was
saying i didn't know that it was
uh possible to play it online
uh does my shield help
or do they still drain
um
they [\h__\h] scare me i hate these
anyways ah yeah my shield helps
oh [\h__\h]
i hate you guys so much
what was that [\h__\h] okay i'm going to die
again
[Music]
that's what i'm saying yeah no she's
mailing at the wall again
[Music]
i parried oh that's what that was i
didn't even do it on purpose
[Laughter]
[Music]
she's suffering with me how do i deal
with those birds the best
they annoy me so much
yeah maybe there's ghosts
oh screech scratch
maybe there are ghosts
[Music]
bombs
i could also
ice um
yes but it only has free charges
[Music]
bye-bye
at least the rooms are so small that you
can immediately just run into the next
room you're not going to be followed
endlessly noise
using the lure
oh
no that feels just like so cowardly you
know
these [\h__\h] birds
[Music]
oh they do follow me
but why is he running around like
he's so confused looking for his mommy
wasn't that weird just now
he ran in like a circle like what
is he drunk confused
is he sleepwalking
do some more
okay i'm just stalling have you noticed
that i'm stalling
these boots
oh she's she's just sitting in the back
now watching me
good cat
uh oh thank you for the pinky i'll be
reading super jets today sorry for the
little delay
oh now she's not sitting there anymore
ah what
what
why are you so cute
[Music]
how is it already hot again
it was just chill in my apartment
because i cooled it down
[Music]
okay i will i will i will
i will i will i will
[Music]
i rolled right into the phone i could
like roll through it
[Music]
work on him
like even if i hear myself though they
drain it like it's not like i can heal
much
oh
what the [\h__\h] corner this [\h__\h] out of
them
why is this like a boss fight huh
you come here
they dodge so well too don't they
corner
[Applause]
this might just be even more annoying
than the uh invisible enemies
look him up
uh take somewhere to catch him yeah i
mean they can fly they have the high
ground so it only makes sense but
i told her
oh yo that was hard to see
oh
wow
another one
damn
we're getting incredibly
overpowered you would think but i'm
still failing
hard at the game oh now we're above the
ceremony okay
it's interesting
i wonder if normally they would the game
expects you to go straight into that
middle
or if they
expect you to go into the side rooms
first
there's another little
wedding going on here
why are you sleeping
okay
they're like
oh these are the stronger ones
oh thank god
holy [\h__\h]
they rolled and oh my god
oh my god
[Music]
uh-huh
why did i
i thought i was pushing the attack
button i swear
no
oh no
sorry
oh sorry
still sometimes
confusing with the ps5 control
didn't open was there a shortcut there
was it right right after i died or what
got it left and start to go there back
there
left
in the in the very beginning
oh man too late now
[Music]
anyway
right before the stream i watched uh the
first episode of house of the dragon
that's what my tweet was about
sorry if i worried anybody but
[Laughter]
um yeah
context
first of all i say i like it i guess uh
but for my taste holy [\h__\h] there's a bit
too much
brutality violence and blood going on
but that's what people like about
um a
game of friends right so
have to deal with it i guess
[Music]
at least i got the first hit
so
don't let them hit you
no okay i was too cocky
[Music]
no
literally so obnoxious
[Music]
[\h__\h]
on
[Music]
yo one is bigger no
was he just flying higher
[Music]
[\h__\h] birds
[\h__\h]
birds
that's not fair
give me my [\h__\h] hp back
is this what you would create a shortcut
i wonder
like above
i'm a bird
oh yeah shut up i
[Music]
forgot oh wait what
ah there oh i wish i had one more slot
[Music]
i mean in theory i could
get rid of my sword and just use the
magic items only then i would have free
free weapons
to work with
yes which
right wait is that actually a strategy
because there are mp potions
[Music]
is that a thing people do
like not use the sword at all
wait how do you switch to mp potions
this one
how did you notice me
what
i don't know what to do without a sword
and now i drink a pee potion and all
yeah
and without my sword i feel like i'm no
then i should maybe do this or
uh
this maybe
but no at least for the normal enemies i
don't
uh
i don't need
how about this
the normal foxes
i don't really need magic obviously just
a waste
okay back to house of dragons
so
i mean
even if you consider the fact that you
know huh
blood and
s-e-x is so entertaining
i feel like it was
i feel like they just wanted to
do
put as much of it as possible into the
first episode
to get people into it
but i don't know
is that just me what do you guys think
did you watch it
some something
like there was that there was that uh
what do you call that uh
lanson
thingy fight
that was brutal
and then the thing that damon targaryen
did with the city watch was brutal
and then
the one
scene with the baby was brutal
jousting oh yeah jousting
it was also brutal and it was all like
so close together like in the second
part of the
like the the last third of the episode
was more to my liking
it pushed too much that's what i
can see yeah
okay how would how do we do this now
[Music]
waste all my potions on that
well first of all
this
i missed i was a wrong weapon that
wasn't even what i wanted to use but
okay there we go
and then i'm already on the magic
already
ah [\h__\h] wrong one again okay i need to
get used to like how i arranged them
so
stupid uh
okay i should have used that for aoe
though i guess
and now i have the problem that
oh man
wait give me a second
[Music]
ah
it no i don't think this is the way to
go grappling sword yeah
yeah
and maybe this if i have some magic
at hand
[Music]
okay
three good hits in
it just takes so much time if i do it so
so carefully
okay
they normally can't even reach me uh
when they do that if i'm far enough then
just take a step forward and then i hit
okay
now
this might be an
unpopular opinion
about um
house of the dragons actors
but
i i don't
uh i have no problem with the acting
abilities
but
ah how did i
miss
i actually don't like the the
faces in for this
like to fit this particular character
for damon and the the girl the princess
girl
uh
like i feel like the the whole platinum
blonde
and
super powerful dragon roll doesn't quite
fit them
yeah matt smith that's that's his name
he's like really famous right
i just
i just don't like his face in that role
i'm not saying he's ugly or anything
maybe maybe it's the wigs and
their makeup
finally oh my god no damage though no
damage
takes someone's time with no damage
yeah he's like from doctor who right
that's what made him popular
um
it just feels weird to have him in that
role
for now
and then and then the girl
i feel like they just tried really hard
to find an actor an actress
that
resembles
uh
what was daenerys's actor's name i
forgot again
uh
you know who i mean
[Music]
straight for shortcut okay
amelia yeah because they did again the
thing with
the dark eyebrows
and a little bit of a darker skin
um
and you know obviously the platinum hair
but i feel like they tried to find
someone who resembles her to recreate
that
phenomenon
maybe i don't know i could be completely
wrong and all that and this is
probably just talking [\h__\h] but
is anyone
yeah does anyone agree with me
this is now the the lower level room
that i yeah okay
[Music]
shortcut
if you can remain just calm while
playing i think you got this yeah the
way i just fought the crows is the way
to go
maybe the only way to go for me
ah the potions oh yeah yeah [\h__\h] red hmm
oh there's
oh
she'll only be there for a while man you
kind of spoiled me about that
man
i mean
thanks to what i experienced in game of
thrones
the actors who are there in the very
beginning who play such big roles and
you think you'll you'll have them around
for a while um in game of thrones they
weren't around for a while
um so i know that but
why don't you tell me that bunk bonk
bonk bunk
yeah i should i should switch potions
again
you don't know
what
you just assumed since the book is based
yeah if you read the book then you
probably would know
or you would think
i get that
[Music]
you guys who read the books know more
about it than me
about what's
probably possibly going to happen
what
why can't he focus on them they're it's
like they're not
considered to be there before they open
their eyes or see me like before they
wake up
i can't focus on them
[Music]
well then wake up [\h__\h]
okay okay
i'm gonna open the [\h__\h] window man
it's too hot and i i don't understand i
have the window open all night it's cold
outside
but no
[Music]
hello neighbors welcome to my stream
i'll try to not stream uh scream scream
too much
[Music]
are you [\h__\h] kidding me
i'm outta here
[Music]
better for my voice that is true
oh hi jungkook's juicer
enjoying the cold air
why did that
what why why did it why did it go
backwards
why
i looked the other way didn't i
incredible
oh god the air is so good
[Music]
air's so good
what
did you see that why did i do it again
i'm not happy with that
i won't accept that nondecay
i'm not even focused on anything
it worked the first time
pedro please what
what
that's strange
yes i was facing them directly and i
just let go
even if i was focused and i would have
been focused on them because there's
nothing else in the room but no i wasn't
even trying
it's time i'm using my dynamite
eh
okay
no
see that's how you waste the [\h__\h]
dynamite
[Music]
i
i'm i'm so [\h__\h] mad already then you
they're probably gonna throw more of
those
at me but two at onces
where am i going oh yeah what once is
mean
oh man
come here come here
did it get him
[Music]
don't lose your cool yep yep yep yep
yeah yep yep yep yep
that was a perfect shot
i didn't even have to use my body
explosion oh my god thank god
i don't want to ever go past these boys
again so
please don't let me die
not
i'm not intending on death
soon
huh
what's going on here
is this just like a
mission impossible kind of situation
just don't get hit by a laser it's funny
oh so difficult
it's not difficult but
why would you do this
what
no i'm not gonna waste dynamite on that
[\h__\h]
oh no
what's going on here
mommy
not again
[Music]
oh man
no enemies in this room but
a terrifying
[Music]
thing to look at
what can i see on them
this is symbolism i don't know what
would it symbolize
maybe we'll learn
eventually
ah
so
interesting
let's pray everybody amen
what's gonna happen
now that they're still down there
not reacting
oh
what
[Music]
those are not the ones that come alive
i think i'm pretty sure
okay now we go down there and kill them
those are not the strong ones right
what does that mean but aren't there
they like
those bodies that we just saw they're
normally inside of those monuments right
that's what we learned
why is it gone now that we
[Music]
shut
it off around it
why why is it gone now
at all
[Music]
okay um
besides that i think house of dragon was
good
and looking forward to more it's just
[\h__\h] triggering that i have to wait a
full week
[Music]
and i'm glad i didn't do a watch along
because
some very um
sensitive scenes in there again
i don't know how we would have watched
that together
um
but
my mom actually wrote to me she says
that she has judged too early she
enjoyed the first episode sasuke
they're so slow
[Music]
there must be a catch here
they they can't be setting all these
weaklings at me
there's something really big coming
oh that one is fast oh
why is that one so fast that was not the
strong one was it oh my god oh my god
was it
okay okay
okay although i could have used the damn
it
could i have used the statue before
killing those oh well i'm i'm not
doing that bad we're fine
skulls for the skull god yeah
it's eyes were not glory yeah yeah some
some of those weaklings can run some of
them can't they're just not as motivated
i guess
[Music]
gonna go this way there's a room there
a room or a
chest come on no
really
bamboozled
okay then we're going down or up
maybe it's based on their distance from
you
or maybe maybe
i was the same distance to all of them
no
sure
where are we going to
oh a new outer okay
spooky spooky spooky
it's getting interesting
i will think it was interesting since
the first moment i started playing it
ah a shop
oh
a shop here
should i buy the dynamite how much money
did i have not much i probably can't buy
anything oh all those are cheap how many
three four hundred
not bad
the coins are a thousand right
i don't know is there anything else here
worth buying what do you think
or 26 you have a good amount i could buy
more
not sure if i want to save up for
anything
[Music]
it's not worth buying right
maybe one more
baris you don't really use one
[Laughter]
could you ask this guy for a discount
like look at him actually he looks kind
of nice
the way he moves his hands
kind of cute though
holy [\h__\h] that's actually it's actually
really cold let me close the door i'll
check if there's a cat outside one
second
no cat okay
that bit's cute
actually though it's not a normal
skeleton it's a it's a fox skeleton
isn't it let me look at the ears i
didn't know they have uh
bones in their ears
never felt
so hard when i touched uh a cat's uh
ears before
me nihonet
kitsunella
interesting
wait i currently can't buy upgrades
right
i mean i don't think i have any
materials for it but could i buy them as
a ghost
sorry it's just me stalling again
i'm scared
oh wonderful oh boss fight okay
makes sense um
i don't know what we're going for
i don't know what's happening boss fight
already i feel like this was nothing
much
of a like you know
pre-dungeon
um
hello
interesting we get a close look at the
oh do i have to light the candles
okay so there's these three symbols that
we've been collecting
oh no what
some music started
okay
we're fighting things ah okay okay okay
what
what what what
what that's a little bit too many
excuse me
what
what do i have to do all of them
[Music]
i'll take my body now thank you wait but
there's like some puff here
no
if only i could jump huh
maybe that'll give me the ability to
jump if i kill all of them
what could this be
do i get a portion out of this because
it seems like we get what what we asked
for
yes
oh
am i supposed to like use them while i'm
fighting these
peeps
oh god [\h__\h] this [\h__\h]
how am i supposed to kill these
all right they all just started blasting
they use them when i'm alone but yeah
yeah yeah
i'm gonna leave them there
you get good
what's the
if i if i change can i yeah can i change
this to mana if i have a different
amulet
and then i just start blasting back
i don't know
wait i can't
i can turn on another one if i don't uh
pick these up huh
okay that's a waste
wait can i do it now
no
i have to pick them all up okay i can't
just leave them there for when i need
them
uh-huh okay well so we'll definitely be
doing this again
now we can experiment
[Music]
so we just start blasting
is there a trick
[Laughter]
uh yeah okay i can't i can't just don't
die and pick up um these things well um
yeah um
[Music]
i'll do those first i'll i'll always do
those first because i think there's a
lot of um room for failure there
if you um
if you miss
but let's go
i think i i have a tactic
i think i have a tactic
i'm not ready
once the cameraman
okay okay
okay
okay that was good that was good that
was good took one one hit i don't know
felt like one hit
looked like more
[Music]
just start blasting
you basically give them back
what they throw at you
[Music]
let's see what else is
what would that be
is that just my my my my clones
those
those oh i didn't like those either
that one
is that i don't remember this these ones
are fine these ones are fine
um
shouldn't even be needing any of these
weapons
it depends on how many they're standing
out though
[Laughter]
let's see
don't eat what i couldn't
a what
oh but it's like a
like a black one oh oh oh they keep on
coming okay uh [\h__\h]
didn't expect boredom okay then we have
to kill them quickly
before more and more start coming
oh wait this one's bigger this one's
bigger oh
this one's smaller again
[\h__\h] what it has a shield
okay
okay oh they keep on coming and they
don't stop coming and they
it's like it's like
asking me if i did my homework if i
remember how to fight this
i don't
but there's no more coming
oh no he's just chilling there because
he didn't see me oh
[Applause]
okay
kind of wasted but okay we do get a uh
a refill whenever we want it just once
though
[Music]
okay beautiful beautiful
okay okay that one's cleared
two and three more to go although no
four more i guess because this this is
something
this is the big boss probably
i guess i'll go with this one
oh god
this is this
will be so
triggering
when you die like in the second to last
one or so and you have to repeat
everything think it's time for heal
no it's not
i don't wanna waste these i feel like
i'm gonna fail at least one more time
though i wonder if the alerts are
helpful here in any way but
what do i want to use
oh not that i
i need i would need mana to use any of
this anyway oh [\h__\h]
uh then in that case
just just if
this dire situation calls for it i'll
throw some dynamite
but besides that i'm gonna go for a good
old fist fight or sword fight
i predicted you to spawn there
everything
oh these are weak oh these are actually
really weak okay this one's stronger
oh
yeah
oh [\h__\h]
okay okay now now it's getting stressful
[Music]
why
take care of the weaklings first
so that that they don't interrupt
okay
just go away body is in the way man
the weak ones doesn't even they don't
even go for me they don't even want to
fight me
[Music]
you just run around having fun like it's
another day on the playground
okay
very good
easy
[Music]
[Laughter]
can you guys get closer together again
they don't seem like they're on the same
level though
[Music]
are they
just eat this i'd only hit one of them
okay come on you can get one hidden
i know you can't keep
i was supposed to hit him from the side
i was on this side
my god okay
okay now it might be time for a heel
[Music]
um
for real though if i change into the mp
thingy will they give me some mp2
because i need i need some mp
need
let me check
i don't know
well i if i pick it up now
no
yeah
what the hell
i need to eat the blueberries
sean thank god i have so many
okay
let's hope that this was not wasted
the speedy card might be better
than the sneaker one oh
one was this one
good idea
am i faster
i don't know what
some of them i don't remember the
meaning but if you guys say this is the
best one then i'll go with this one
let me out
okay
are these the ghosts
maybe
because that would be [\h__\h] because you
can't see them like on water or are they
just you know those copies of me
what's
that
[Music]
the candle once
oh
okay
um wait
if they are the ones that teleport
then
maybe like this
um
yeah they're not too bad
come on wish me luck
okay
oh yeah okay okay those [\h__\h]
nah all good
just get out of there
right now
okay okay
okay i'll get one more
okay if you stop them in the middle of
teleporting then
you can still bring them back okay okay
no [\h__\h] up now kiwawa i did that with
no damage i think
clean
very clean
okay okay i'm so tense i need a massage
i'll drink my
drink my smoothie
last one yeah but what is the middle one
that's
if that's a big boss fight and i lose at
that one and then i have to do all of
this over again and i'm gonna be really
[\h__\h] mad
i could give one
use dynamite for these are those the
ones at the graveyard that [\h__\h] me up
so often
they they have a huge reach with their
uh weapons
uh i don't remember
what my best strategy was fighting them
did i use the grapple
hook and don't remember
the dread beat
my strategy was serrano and in the end
maybe but i guess does that mean that i
had no strategy at all that worked
just the common ones
okay then you could even we could even
shoot them
[Music]
i don't want to make a mistake you know
i don't want to [\h__\h] this up
strategy was being sneaky yeah
save my mp oh
for what
i was too tired to fight them good yeah
okay i had a
handicap
okay we're just gonna blow them up i
guess
try to save mp
but just in case
just in case i'm in a die situation now
i might consider using that um
good
hurt them together blow them up i will
try i hope not too many come
okay you can do this kiwa
i have all my potions i have all my
health what am i scared of
redoing this
i'm stalling
my hands my hands also don't feel like
like they know what they're doing you
know
[Music]
just get into it
just dive into it
easy
that was worth it okay
[Music]
oh that's a lot man
that's
should have blown them out faster
oh god
okay okay holy
ah [\h__\h] big but don't be scared
hit me
okay okay
poise weak
it's easy to break his guard
[Music]
i'm sorry guys
i'm sorry
i'm so sorry
i'm so sad
i'm so sorry and you're so sad
[Music]
oh
where are
they okay
okay okay
basically just like last time i think uh
last time i also just had one hit and i
still have my body to use as an
explosion
uh
then we go with these ones
again
i should have maybe changed my weapon
but no i'm just going for a normal
sword for this
where's the next one
we're gonna speed one this guy's scared
let's go
believe in you gamer girl
believe
ah no
oh that one's stronger i forgot i forgot
oh
it's okay it's okay i get a big heel
afterwards that um
is way too much anyway
stretchy jeep
mama
whatever
is
[Music]
but they have shields too
didn't i
it's okay we're trying to save them
okay yeah
no need to be so such a coward kiwa
don't need to be so scared
uh
how did that fight these just normal
no normal ah [\h__\h] did anybody write it
down what was my what was my system
bombs
do they use bombs
they just oh these are
those are not the mages
for the mages and no problem for the
mages sort against the weak ones bomb
for the big ones
okay okay again and let's prepare
let's prepare the bump
don't want to use anything besides that
if possible
that's fine didn't i do this without
damage i don't know
i'll be fine
the small ones are [\h__\h] easy
and then suddenly a big one comes
that [\h__\h] everything up so we gotta be
fast
that's the big one
[Music]
get out of here
oh man
gosh i'm i'm so tense like i'm holding
on to my breath sometimes
[Music]
okay
[Applause]
you know the good thing is if we run out
of dynamite we have a shop there where
we can buy more thank god for the shop
now i understand why the shop is there
okay
is it time to
you know we could we could risk it go
for the mages and then he'll
or he'll now
evil either way we would hope for no
damage run on the mages
um
drink one potion and then
yeah i mean i still have two potions i
feel like you're gonna be fine yeah
yeah if if i focus super stay
water
quick quick breathing moment okay
oh there
my arms feel so weak my hands and my
arms
oh man
putting too much pressure on myself
ah
uh oh
yes
my name senpai
wrote to me today for something so
surprisingly
unrelated to anything ever
just asked for like
advice on something
so
out of nowhere
[Laughter]
probably because i speak english which i
found very really um funny
and i i felt like [\h__\h] i don't even have
a good answer for you
but i'm gonna
try to answer even because you asked me
out of all people hmm
not gonna say what it was because i
don't know if she like wants
it it's it's nothing nothing like
embarrassing or anything super secret
but yeah
just not gonna say it unless she says it
in her stream maybe i don't know
[Music]
i i think i was able to
at least mentally help her
okay
mages
it goes up
i wonder if the spawning point is always
the same
oh [\h__\h]
i'll [\h__\h]
oh
my
not the best start
oh [\h__\h] i focused on the wrong person
i don't even need to roll out of
not these good as before but
it works
i went to him to hit him
i'm gonna run to this guy
ah
i had a ribbon last time somehow
okay
i'm gonna [\h__\h] you up
still no damage
okay one left
how are you gonna do this all alone no
friends left to bully a little ghost fox
all right i think it's time for a little
reward
gimme gimme me
give me the good stuff
ah
oyster aussie
okay so what was my problem with these
what was the issue
i don't remember
that i was just too scared to get in a
hit it wasn't so bad it wasn't bad at
all
but what were my weapons some dynamite
and
and i tried to go only for the dynamite
huh but i used the gun maybe sometimes
and it didn't help much
hmm
yeah they do big damage but yeah they
have no defense really
that is true
did they have a shield
you guys remember
no
okay
it's okay wow it's okay
maybe a bit wasteful but oh well
i don't care
okay
but what comes now what comes now
a big big big enemy
[Music]
can i get a small spoiler
i need to mentally prepare
the monolith enemy
oh
if it's it's not gonna be just one huh
just one is fine
first bus
that's not the first eh
first boss
was not a monolith yeah i don't know now
you confuse me
that was uh
the first of the very first one
the one where
so just one though
maybe
a second one will spawn in a bit but if
you're faster you can kill the first one
okay
i already used so much dynamite i need
this to go well
oh man you stick on two shots we'll kill
it
oh
really
but can it reflect it can it block it
do i need to shoot it at a certain
timing
i want to redo all of this switch to
magic potions gun spam but then if i
need to heal myself it's like i'm too
too
scrat scrambled scrabbled scrambled to
change back to the right thing you know
[Music]
it has no shield
okay
yeah yeah i'm also thinking it would be
nice to have the berries in the slot but
oh well i wish you could just use it
like directly from this menu without
having to first
put it into one of the shortcuts and
then having to put it back put something
else in the shorts but how can you do
that during a battle when the menu
doesn't even pause anything
berries instead of bombs
okay
i mean both are
um
items that don't come back when i die so
it hurts me but
okay i can do this
just go all in
spawn in the middle
did it change
do something
nothing's coming are you gonna just is
this this is a timer oh
okay i'll go
[Applause]
please don't tell me there's no
something else coming this is enough
this is enough
that was the right strategy
thank you for telling me it's two shots
oh my god what could this be does it
give me my life back or maybe um jumping
uh no
or i think i don't know
ah
i got an achievement you feel a tingling
oh wait that's not the crown that did
something i i read about it in the
manual but i don't remember
oh yeah look
my
rolling is insanely faster
oh my god does this count as a jump can
i oh yes that that will be how i get
over there
finally
but is it only like if it's on the same
level
i wonder
i mean that those are stairs so that
doesn't count
i have an interesting
crown
but
i'm gonna tell you one thing here put on
the tin foil hat
what i'm wearing right now
looks like all that energy that
comes from
uh
you know
they're
that farm or whatever
where my mommies die my ancestors die
so
i'm just using
yeah the evil energy
but
i'm using it for a good cause hopefully
i'm in the
place i hate the most again i think
i
should be
here yep
here i am
what do you want me to do here
i don't want to fight any ghosts
ah were there some there was
some
the altar was only reachable by jump
right the one that triggered me so hard
where was that
was am i imagining something was that
somewhere else maybe that that was
somewhere else i guess
quarry
okay um
i would like to save once at an altar
please
okay but we did it guys
oh
is this gonna have
meaning now
i am trying to pray there you go
can i collect my
these things
karana
wait now i can reach it yeah
oh
the last upgrade items
ah but i can't go to the other one on
the right right i have to go to each
hero grave
right
yeah [\h__\h]
now that i don't like because some of
them were in
places and i don't even remember
oh that's how i get everything back to
normal
oh
where am i oh
i found the chest
[Music]
see now it's hot again remember when i
closed the door i said it's cold now
it's already hot again
okay
it's incredible
i want to tear down all the walls
of this apartment
no it's not it's not summer it's not
cold it's not hot outside
it's literally freaking cold
where do we go
if i die now will i have to do
everything again that's what i'm scared
of
i'm gonna go
the
shortest route down to this altar
go up the ladder this one
already went there
i talked about this i said that this
will this event we will learn to jump
it's [\h__\h] noisy outside
where the [\h__\h] do you get down
this is cool and all but eh
[Music]
one
ah
getting there oh
did i ever bring that rope down no i
didn't
how could i have gotten there oh just
hey yo
this is so cool now man
the game just gradually
with the grappling hook and all that oh
what is that
gives it gives you more and more
it's thundering
options to
see more of the world but it
i can get that page yeah and maybe the
other one in the in the
like what was it in the whale fountain
whatever
oh
again the same battle fought uncountable
times yeah i tried fighting that [\h__\h]
before but maybe now
with the crown
air to the air
there's one part of english that we can
read here air to the air
wait is this
it's just these two pages huh
it's a cool page though
it's a cool page
[Music]
okay
um i wonder
what's the best way to
oh i can go down
wait a second though
about here
no okay what's the best way to get to
all these
places now that i need to go to
to regain my
abilities
great feeling of progression yeah that
is true game is sad and beautiful yeah
oh
ah there's aren't those just the ones
that like tell you the stories like oh
play pablo
don't understand but yeah
i agree
i agree but i don't understand
those are not enemies right
now i really want to see like
i want to explore okay for now we're
just exploring we'll find everything by
accident
oh hi
hunk
cool
good talk
yeah yeah
oh i can't go up
ah
explore the main area for now there's a
lot of new things that have opened up
now okay okay okay
i guess i'll do that yeah
a coin a new coin
i have to find the well again
[Music]
beautiful
what is that
all right how do i get up
should we teleport maybe there was a
teleporter
oh wait ochoto i almost missed you my
friend
give me those cheese cubes
oh
oh wait that must be a new area
what
grandma
where am i
i was able to jump there so it must be a
new area
west or is the west garden
it looks a little bit like that
maybe i came from a different entry wait
let me see
oh
oh yeah it's the garden
even those tiny
tiny platforms
where the [\h__\h] was the hero's grave
oh is garden map is it in
was there hero's grave in the west
garden
i think the
ah
i knew i should have like marked down
all the all the hero's graves
i just looked at it
what
okay here let me save
why did you guys see that and i didn't
let me go there
ah
why did i never pray this away
oh yeah
why did i never do this one
how did i get up here nah amazing
impatient when something doesn't work
i couldn't reach it before oh i guess so
same elevation that's that's not
necessarily always true though
i gotta go for the other side
it's not always true but it seems like a
general rule
but sometimes there's exceptions
yeah
so i have to test it out
just
where'd you guys see the hero's grave
is it just me or does it use less um
stamina than rolling
there was a little lag in the game
though
[Music]
sorry close to the room again it's again
too cold
cause you're hot and you're cold you're
yes and you know
and then you're out you're up and you're
down you're yes and you know
[Music]
[Laughter]
ah okay and we'll let me go back is
it makes no sense okay i'm trying to
figure out the ruling here
[Laughter]
the fan yeah i could probably just turn
on the fan but i'm trying to bring in
actual cold air
from outside
you guys said
oh sorry oopsie you guys said you saw
oh why why is it cold
can i just
what
is it gold just because i got it back
with the town's club oh you're signed
with a telescope ah
where's the game oh it's just on my
screen sometimes just on my screen
something is off while in obs it's fine
interesting wonder how that works
let me go
where do i go
now i have to see the world with
different eyes you know how you have to
learn how to see everything in portals
now
i have to see everything in
teleportation not quite like portal
teleportation but you know
i have to see everything with a crown
with the eyes of a ruler
ah god damn it
i'm lost
i'm stuck
wait a minute shouldn't i have
like
okay maybe i'm mixing things up now but
um
okay i thought this might turn into a
portal like yeah like the golden one no
then i mix it up
i mix it up
like slight change in elevations
i'll wait here
let's check out that area what
that hole in there where did that lead
to
is that new
and my lamp doesn't work again that's
also length it just works whenever it
wants
what is this place
when i teleport it gives it a little bit
of light
i can't make out what it is
i got the ice power here oh
[Laughter]
oh that's why nothing's there anymore
it's okay
[Music]
oh my god dodging will be a million
times easier now
i can just
dodge through them so fast
holy [\h__\h]
i'm gonna look again
ah it's right there
but i can't go that far
[Music]
oh no we'll have to just
oh
experiment
i was here before i went that tough
already
page will tell me the page
the page is there page of gate oh
there was a page there
this is where the gator was
stitch
page
hold l
oh yeah but i can't reach that
i
have to reach it for a diff from a
different direction i think
yeah okay
what
oh
huh
no we've been here before right
uh-huh
sorry guys kind of tedious moment let me
let me get a tangent for you out of my
bag out of my pocket
and
tangent notes there we go
oh yeah
[Music]
okay so i have a tinfoil hat fury
wanna hear it
bye theory
is that did you guys see the the new
whole life summer music video where yago
was dancing in uh yukata
supposedly
my theory is that that's not the real
yago that's an imposter
first of all his face looked
too young
just looked too different
his expression seemed
not quite like the real juggle
and i don't think the real juggle would
ever dance
you guys are too easy to fools
wow is it worth going there
yeah i don't think that was the real
jackal
very
they i don't know they they put someone
else in this spot so they could uh
fulfill his idol dreams
and they're chomping at me
he trains every day yeah but he didn't
look like the real yago to me his face
just looked
ah
go away this is [\h__\h] annoying me
am i like getting any closer
i found a new path at least
i'm not hating no
not hating
whoever after this juggle did a
wonderful job
it's very idol
how do you know i'm the real keyboard
ask me a question and only the real key
wobble could answer
i'm [\h__\h] here again
couldn't you go down here
i remember something
wasn't there like a path down here
won't let me go down
where is the bathroom game stream real
quick yes see now i know what you're
talking about shouldn't that be enough
proof
[Music]
two plus two is four
follow the crocodiles
ah
i'm not a big fan of confrontation
explain what the pretty quick
the word itself uh stands for the
english word um print club
it's a japanese pronunciation of it and
it's not a club though it's just a photo
booth japanese
in this case japanese photo booth
and you can take pictures in there but
it's like not normal pictures they make
you look really really cute by
um putting like a lot of how much for
the [\h__\h] do i get down here putting a
lot of filters on you oh wait here
hi
dead
same i'm also
dead putting a lot of filters on you and
uh change your eye size change your face
size they make your face smaller
is it enough can i stop
hunting
okay i think i'm getting there i'm
getting there i'm right there
i think
yeah they don't really i mean they
sometimes work on foreigners but they
just look um weird
it's just
yeah
the features are made to enhance
like asian facial features so when
they're used on
a different kind of face
then it looks kind of off a lot of the
time
here's your rowing machine
well i never had one
oh i think that question makes no sense
is that a dead end there man
what about here
no
what the [\h__\h] man
this getting to places should be easier
now
not more difficult
okay let's go this way
oh this is a new path too huh
it's good to explore
it's fine oh wait that's an upgrade item
ah nice
we'll be able to upgrade whatever that
was for
hp
soon tm
anywhere i can go from here
[Music]
okay
hiding out for college oh have fun good
luck
it's just
it's like those doggos that jump into
nothing
i think i already said that before when
i first bought them but now it's even
more accurate because like
they bite into something they think
that's there but it's not their
bamboozle
oh
am i there yet what it
it's so cute oh well uh
i have one kind and i think i'm missing
one more or two more
eight
okay one more right because it's free
free free
oh
[\h__\h] one more which we can buy at a shop
i don't know if the game expects you to
do that
or
if that's just optional if you're too
lazy to look for them
but i guess the more you get
the more wishes you get
hi oh you're fishing
wait how come i'm not able to oh a page
to fish
oh that's that's the money thingy right
let me
use that right away come on
almost got scammed
by the water
you know
those look like fish on the the signs on
the bottom looks like fish
fish and like
oh it looks like fish on the water and
on top there's houses
fishing houses
i agree i understand you completely
well
what is this page
survival tips keep an eye on your bars
you'll give me some bible tips now
extra bumps for some reason you must
like using them but yeah i was wondering
about that why why is it plus one
why is it plus one why this is not just
yeah
i don't understand i didn't understand
that at all
use special techniques
what
rolling and sword
you get extra bombs by using bombs
ah
as you use them you get a regeneration
thing about
if you use bombs you get the ones that
recharge on healing what
every 10 10 years you can get one free
permission
what
okay
i think you missed this page before oh
was i able to reach it because it does
seem kind of late to get this one
hey teddy hide in also
title time hold a hmm
x wait extra
i can refill the stamina
and get extra damage out of it page 16
more info
and what is the
why what is the bottom right telling me
is is that just entries like to like
hold um
some
caves but
boss blocks the way to the bell tower
will come
wait that's the ah that's the other
that's the uh
that's the page of the worst
garden that i never had with all the
info on it
i definitely should have gotten this
earlier
oh man
what the hell how come i
missed it i i found so many things you
know
for some reason i had trouble finding
this one huh
yeah that looks like a place i could
have probably
used before
[Laughter]
oh
okay
anyway
not like i needed it
that info on there was
nothing i needed in particular
okay heroes grave should be there
somewhere
right
[Music]
above this is one level above
ah
where am i going
oh oh oh oh oh am i reaching it now
maybe
yes maybe yes
i have arrived finally sorry
it took me a million years
but we have to explore anyway to get all
the chests
[Laughter]
maybe the game will lead me for all of
this automatically very nice
wait that one looks like i could reach
it the other one
that would be a nice bonus okay we got
uh which one was that
please be hp please be hp please be hp
all right with my defense
hey let me go there
huh
okay
gonna say i love to scarf thank you
it's cute isn't it
that's not bad yeah i guess so
hmm
[Music]
wait so they actually
did it take my defense too
i guess then the enemies must have been
adjusted to be
like
weak enough to not make my lack of
defense too noticeable though
wait am i missing something
should i explore more
like what about here
no
no okay
um
i don't know if i should explore more i
feel like
maybe we're done
hopefully i mean let's look at the map
that we just
got hmm
there's a path there that leads even
further to the left
or
is it just pointing to the text there
that means nothing
have i been there if yes
well well well we are gonna gold
anyway
[Music]
the secret
maybe just text secret secret ah
it's not much of a secret if they point
to it here
but have i been there now i want to go
there but it's like on the other side of
the [\h__\h] map
already kimi no no no you
i won't know how to solve it are you
calling me stupid
[Laughter]
yeah
i should try to translate how why would
i even start
you're telling me to learn another
writing system right now right here
the question is it's just a writing
system though right not a language so
hmm i just learned korean give me a
break i still need to master the korean
[Music]
i'm missing a page i'm surely missing
some
page still yeah
wait the
the crocodile
jump it's called chopping young like the
champignon
[Music]
cute
oops
okay we're just gonna go i want my
powers back
it's cute yeah
nice guys in the snow
where do we go next huh oh hey we can
look at this now
couldn't look at this before i guess
uh
you guys see a hero statue because i
really don't see one in this case
oops
what if we go for here
what
what oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] was it always this
corrupted
here
oh i can go through it
all right it's just getting more and
more spread everywhere
oh my god i love these shortcuts
oh
what is this some health potion
thingy
uh let me see do i have some notes on
that one i don't think so
oh
where is the ah here
lucky cup lucky cup
lucky
enemies sometimes drop hearts card oh
cool
that's cute
i don't know how that's cute but it's
cute
oh it's so nice to be able to teleport
for everything i wanna go get that
[\h__\h] page i don't know
how far we are from it but hi
and exploration is actually pretty
peaceful now because um
we can
uh go for everything with
seems like no enemies mostly except for
the
chomping yums i hear that's what i was
all talking about are you dead or just
chilling
okay you're just chilling
that probably means ha ha ha ha right
finally
this page they dangled it in front of my
nose for so long now
if this is just a [\h__\h] troll page and
nothing important gonna be mad
yeah
okay i
this know this i saw already the golden
one question mark
i wonder what that means
get all those things and then
huh it's kind of the other way around
don't know
we go from ghost to getting all the
things and then
with this this is yeah it is the other
way around because in this picture the
hero's grave looks like
just like you know
normal place as opposed to for us it
looks like like the ghost world all the
time
um
so
it's the other way around for
us some door i think i know which one
yeah yeah oh several yeah those doors
are still closed this one is
yeah
this one this one is still closed for
sure
i remember we just uh stood in front of
it
and then there's a combination
down right up left up right
she's just thinking
do you also just sometimes sit down look
at the scenery on your balcony or
whatever and just think about
directions
or just think about
arrows
so you take
the holy cross
is this the combination to open the
doors
i guess
look at the door
is it
well well this picture i can't make it
out much but is it
combinations
of a pattern i need to follow not a
whole doll
hi holy cross oh wait yeah oh it's right
here one of the doors
what do you mean there's a pattern
try it out
down right up left upright
down right up
oh [\h__\h]
down right up left up right down right
up left up right
oh
paint
let's go
oh
hidden secrets holy cross
we saw that sign
we saw that that sign that sign that
sign the one on the under the arrow on
the west garden map
i saw it 49 the golden path over world
what
and then this here
scribble down right
up left
upright
down right up left upright
and
a
take your rightful place clearing the
game
ah
telling me to play the game no
my rightful plays hmm
[Music]
down
right up left
up
right
okay
but here's nothing else right just the
page
unless
no
a b
where is it b
b
a b
what
the door has a pattern
oh yeah i see a pattern
yeah well whatever for now
oh you mean a page b for now it's
whatever
don't care for now
i want to know where the hero's grave is
the next one
[Music]
ah we can
teleport to somewhere if we knew
if we had a specific
one in mind next but
i don't have a specific one in mind
there was one in the overworld though
right
um
heal my corruption please thank you
oh wait we can uh let me do an upgrade
no
ah because we're lacking the material
for here
oh
okay this one we can do once we get this
specific hero grave and for this one we
just need the material
i don't know where to go
i need to get my body back yeah yeah
yeah
go in the house
okay donkey
[Music]
uh i just ran past it
where was it
was it here
yeah yeah yeah
what's in the house
now
oh wait that was always there and i
don't think i ever found that
yeah have i been here before yeah yeah
yeah
that's a secret door
oh yeah this room is also like still
like a mystery to me
[Music]
now
i think you found it
ah you mean
that path i found it before
oh
perhaps
it felt so new
okay
um
let's
see
uh hero's grave was marked
like what
what did it look like again
let me see on the
west garden
human's grave
is it is it that skull
this one the candle
was it the candle right okay
that means here do we see a candle
i don't see your one
here
must have been somewhere inside
i'm missing everything this time around
hey
yeah
[Music]
hunting for candles now
should we go into the east forest yeah i
was thinking so too
um
where where am i now here okay
okay i'll try to go
um
yeah the game is so open now it's just
like go wherever you want first i guess
um
so it's like a bit overwhelming now but
once there
go back the door secret door
page i mean
this door
honey do you want me to go here
that's why you told me to go to the
house
up down right up down i don't know
tell me again please
um
[Music]
up right no down right up left up right
down right
down right up left upright
down right up left up right no
[\h__\h]
down right up left up right down right
up left upright
don't want
is it a different one
in this case
wait okay
down
right
no i don't know
i'm trying to compare it to the door now
but like ah
other the right door
down right up left okay
so i start at the big
big spot okay
up right down left down right uh-huh
[Music]
in the end
uh
what the [\h__\h]
what
these are probably really helpful for
something
but what
um
[Music]
left
up what is this sound
the bottom right thing is that in the
east forest
ice plus
a fire wand
plus grappling hook ah one of them what
no together plus the grappling hook
what
there's some weird sounds in here
wait what
do you hear that
did you guys hear that
there's something here
it was really really quiet for you guys
probably but yeah there was some weird
sound
[Music]
i'm here again
no no no no i don't know
wait that was two two out of three doors
right two or three
if you don't count the big one
no
i guess there's more
there's free here but i guess there's
more maybe
i don't know
one in the west garden but i don't want
to go there again because we just came
out of it
okay
now
[Music]
if that one picture was in the east
garden then we indeed have something to
do there
uh a reason to go there
but i kind of first want to focus on my
body i don't know what i should focus on
first
oh can i get that
somehow
yeah no there's another secret door in
the west garden right
well i'm gonna go to the east garden
that flower
why is it pink
ah
i can't go
[Music]
i can't
at this point of time
ah via teleportation oh
okay
[Music]
well for now i'm just gonna continue
exploring i guess
[Music]
where should we go
is there a
hero's grave in here
is there a reason for me to come here
i wonder
i forgot
have written down everything
you should have made memos
no
i can go to the quarry from here
and there's oh there's a there's
probably a hero grave there right
the quarry
uh well judging by this map there's
no hero grave
but i would be able to reach this altar
finally
so
there must be a reason why they would
want you to come back oh [\h__\h] the quarry
i hate the quarry
in the monastery okay
yeah that would make sense but could i
not just like teleport yeah see there it
is there it is
that's the no that's the swamp
and the swamp is where the cathedral is
i want to teleport here
just give me a teleportation thingy
ah
soda
see i remember this place
eh i did that one already
oh this place is so yeah
oh wait everything's
yup
oh my god
i can't go anywhere
everything's flooded in
whatever the [\h__\h] that is
but there's a chest a lonely chest down
there that needs my help
okay sorry guys this is something i
didn't know
who could have anticipated that
i can't go down
yeah i thought i couldn't go to the rope
[Music]
how
how would you go to the rope
go down
follow the stairs what
yeah but i thought it was just you know
water there ah but i guess i can go over
to the other side okay
oh there's a little bit of exploration
that can be done
is this late again
don't recall
what oh
the monastery
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] uh [\h__\h]
okay so we still need that um
[Music]
i'm gonna replace that
let's see
this
a dead end though
no
the other way maybe yeah
okay
let's go down with the rope
um
guys guys guys guys
remember i still wanted to tell you
about my
my
uh
the part
the parting
the parting of korea
yeah yeah yeah so i woke up early after
only getting like really oh oopsie
short amount of sleep
little amount of sleep
i got a quick breakfast
in the
executive lounge
and wait i want to look up first here
got a pretty quick breakfast and then i
uh oh there you go
and then oh yeah yeah yeah but before
that on the night before oh my god i
really tried my best packing
after i came home like around midnight
or so because like we
ate ramen on the river until midnight
right and then we drove back
into my hotel
it was pretty late
and um
yeah
so i got home i didn't have
much time to pack if i wanted to sleep
but in this case i had to sacrifice my
sleep
was it a tight fit well i already knew
by the amount of merchandise that i
received and the amount of shopping that
i did
that it was gonna be a bit difficult
oh thank god there's at least no enemies
i knew it was gonna be a little bit
difficult
to
oh
am i going this right way
to fit everything inside
um uh
yeah
i tried my best really
huh
prepare for battle oh no really
oh
where'd you come from
oh you're [\h__\h]
strong it's okay i'm strong too
i'm fast just like you
oh my god
oh [\h__\h] my dodging is too good but wait
wait
no this is easy it's easy i just have to
literally dodge everything
i can maximum take one hit it seems okay
well i was i was saying and no that's
fine it's fine it's fine it's fine fine
fine but it didn't look that strong holy
[\h__\h]
why so strong though this doesn't look
like where you would out of nowhere
suddenly have a boss fight
kind of weird
a a weaker enemy would be more fitting
oh my body's there
yeah why
i turn around and then it's there
and now it's not there where did it come
from do i have to
go up first look at this [\h__\h]
uh-huh uh-huh
and then go down
wait but then i could just
not go here
or do i have to fight this enemy i might
i could just choose to not go here
it's just suddenly there
i have to
okay
oh nice dodging okay
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
wow
gotta be patient
shotgun spam with my yeah cause healing
is not even worth it man
healing not even worth it
we're gonna cheese it we're gonna try to
cheese it
what's that one again
let's try that strategy
cheese chunk
okay uh where was i um
or can i even talk now i don't know
do i have the ability to talk
i'll leave that body there for a second
ahaha cool cool okay
guess i'll have to go back
maybe i could even ice it yeah i would
probably dodge it huh
see dodge every single shot
i'm gonna try it
oh [\h__\h] that didn't work
oh [\h__\h]
a little bit too late a little bit too
late
but okay it works it works it looks it
does not do much damage but if we spam
it
we'll get there
it's not like we have anything to lose
oh do we need all that mana afterwards i
wonder
[Music]
okay
so i was packing all that stuff and i
knew it was gonna be a buy
uh but i somehow made it fit
perfectly
it somehow all fit in even though that
was a [\h__\h] on a merchandise man
but what i noticed is that it was
quite heavy and i know i have noodle
arms and all that but in this case i
really knew
this was
incredibly
heavy no i didn't actually i left like
two t-shirts and
one pair of shoes that was actually
broken anyway
i did leave that
[Laughter]
i just keep on coming
oh [\h__\h] oh oh [\h__\h] i chose the wrong
thing oh damn it
that's okay
yeah i left some shoes
[Laughter]
makes me feel ticklish
what do i get back this time i wonder
[Laughter]
okay
what do we have
what is that again
i feel the power
hmm
it was not my hp not my uh mp
it was my potions ah they heal more
again
ah
wait can i
no but there's a page there
okay
[Music]
so after a [\h__\h] eternity of packing
really nicely really effectively
i even like i took out the i had like
three cups uh like teacups mugs
from
the aniplus cafe
and those take a lot of space right so
what i did is i took them out of the the
cardboard boxes
and i
um put like socks and stuff whatever
i had to put into the suitcase anyway i
tried to fill the cups with that
yeah yeah yeah
so i tried to strategically smart
packing
yeah yeah
spawn yeah and even you know how did i
tell you i bought like a [\h__\h] ton of
masks at that store called mask lab i
even went to the store a second time to
get even more
they they come in like some cardboard
boxes so i got them i took the masks out
of there they're all individually
packaged in plastic but by taking them
out of the cardboard at least
a little bit of space is saved
because it's kind of junky
yeah so i got rid of that
i feel like the game
is
giving me automatic
um shortcuts
by forcing me to go one certain way
there's no like exploring here
actually
maybe on purpose to help me out not
waste too much time
by having the energy in the way
everywhere
it's nice
yeah railroading
oh very linear
it's good not in the overworld though
okay
and then i
[Music]
finally went to sleep and i i woke up i
got the quick breakfast
and then
i already did my checkout in the evening
before to waste to not waste time to
spend time
to save time that's the word to save
time and i i ordered a taxi to go to the
airport on the evening before two
um i was like super prepared yeah
um
so i had the taxi come early in the
morning
with more than enough time
to reach the airport like two hours a
little bit more than two hours early
and then i arrived and it was everything
just went so smoothly i may have not
gotten much sleep but besides that
everything went so smooth the parking
went smooth
the checkout went smooth
the taxi
everything there was no no traffic jam
ah everything was super smooth
and then
i
uh
arrived at the airport and i returned
my pocket wi-fi
really smoothly
again i was surprised because i could
literally just like
i gave it to them and that's it
didn't have to like
pay anything extra or i don't know sign
any documents or so just have to give it
to them that's it
super easy
i don't know where i'm going next
i can't go here
maybe over there
and that was smooth and then the rest of
the money that was in my transportation
card because i charged too much on it ah
this is new because i couldn't read her
before
the rest of the money i could actually
uh easily take out by going to the
convenience store where i i also bought
the card in the first place where nabi
mama bought it
and um
wait he's gonna charge like a million
bucks for this uh
and uh yeah i could take out the rest of
the money and i could still keep the
card but yeah if you have it in korea
and you
charge too much on your transportation
card and then you live in the country
and you don't don't know what to do
you can get it back
um
my dad
so i did that and then i went to the uh
money exchange place and exchanged the
rest of my one
hmm
so i did all of that very smoothly
can i just take it you're getting it for
free
mario
wait what is this why is all
traced
do i need my 3d glasses for this
well
door in the mountains
yeah i saw that one
heroes grave
holy crust mm-hmm what
holy crust what is that supposed to be
your scribbles are [\h__\h] fox
bed is that my house
oh
out of 22.
fairies
can i get fairies in this game i can
uh tell them
and then we have this
door in the mountains
has the last upgrade items or what
what
or it's telling me where to get my
things back
and then go to the door in the mountains
maybe
we got the
free
already i think
um
and something about the controller
yeah
okay
so where do we wanna go next
this one is where the spiders are
should we try going there because that
has my hp
bye bye friends
bye bye
i can take off my mask too
[Music]
i want to be fast
yeah
east forest east forest
yeah i keep on trying to go there but uh
this is not the right path i need to
find a different path
a teleportation would be good
would be good
where was
the
have i been through that door down there
before
have i opened that one already
where am i
no
okay remember that i'm gonna try to get
find the way down
[Music]
okay and then finally after eating
uh
a sugar glazed donut from krispy kreme
uh as a like a extended breakfast
oh
i should obviously be able to get over
there
come on
wait
i've never done this
oh
okay
um
that was yummy
yummy doughnut
then i finally went to check in my my
suitcase
and
[Music]
was i was pretty worried about it
because i knew it felt extremely heavy
so
turns out
uh it was
approximately
nine kilogram
over which is quite a lot man i would i
did not expect you know
for them to
accept that because
maybe one or two kilograms
yeah i would expect them to be nice and
say
oh go ahead it's fine
so when i saw
the weight on there i was like okay
um how much does it cost
can i pay with card
yeah
and then
he said he asks me the counter cry
he asks me oh um
[Music]
was it your first time
here and i said yeah yeah i'm just
returning home
and he said oh did you like it are you
gonna come again and i said
yeah probably i think i think so maybe
next year
and then he says
okay you don't have to pay for it it's
okay
he's being nice to me because i enjoyed
the maybe in the hopes of me coming back
to the country again
oh am i getting three new cards
a
a flaming broken sword
what is it a flaming sword
but why is it broken
oh okay just one card and some berries
nice
okay
binding contact no not really but i feel
like his
um judging by how that conversation went
i feel like his um
intention was
if i give the right answers
he's gonna let it pass if i give the
answer like oh this is my tenth time or
no i didn't like it he was gonna say no
you have to pay
[Laughter]
no i don't think no there's no [\h__\h]
way that he's from kfp
ah where do i go next
[Music]
but oh my god like nine kilo over
and he just lets it go
ah
i was so thankful for that
i didn't expect that that that's so
so gracious
isn't it
i can go there now
wait a second
okay
[Music]
it's not not usually a big deal if a bag
is heavy mostly they need to make sure
it's safe for baggage
yeah but you know they could have easily
you know made some money if this was
like a
worker in a bad mood or in a shitty
airport that doesn't like people
or shitty airline they could have
totally said yeah you have to pay even
with one kilo over like i remember when
we returned from italy
um
because it was a shitty airline
uh my friend had like
uh like what maybe one or two
kilograms over
and had to take out like
uh some stuff
even though it's really not that much
why not just say whatever it's not like
it's gonna break someone's back
right
yeah so annoying okay which one is the
east forest this one maybe i don't know
[Music]
ah that was a completely different place
there here a statue here
[Music]
the feet holy crush
are you
you're the owner of this place
is it the librarian i'm a cute you're
getting it i'm not getting it what are
you getting
me
that's interesting coming back to this
place now
oh
i want to go there though i want to
check out what there is
there's nothing there
[Music]
should i keep on going down
okay
i'm gonna keep on going down
anyway i was super excited to get a pass
on my luggage and i will never forget
that very nice man
is that sad you're gonna come to life
i can move it
uh i'm gonna assume that i have to fight
this thing anyway oh my god
foreign
there's another one though
uh [\h__\h] my my pots are currently
monopods
i mean
[Music]
no i'm not sweating
okay okay okay that was a good first try
we'll be fine we'll be fine we'll be
fine
we'll be fine [\h__\h] but now i'm here
i mean
where's the closest teleportation thingy
oh man
i should have uh
i should have said hello to the statue
there i thought it was insignificant
in that moment
there you go okay it's not so bad
found
yeah and that in general
because of that dude being there the
dude chilling there the librarian i knew
something was off
now i understand everywhere we go we
have to fight
one of these strong enemies
in order to get to the uh the heroes
altar
the grave i mean
i heal thank you okay
forgot again
there we go
i mean we could try to take him down
with the
um with the gun again
we could but i feel like this one's uh
easier for me to handle than the other
one although there are two so it could
take endlessly should
[Music]
should i shoot him down as well with the
gun
it has a shield oh yeah
we could try them maybe i'll try once
because otherwise it takes so much time
is that sword though
what just happened
why am i suddenly
it depletes my
maybe it makes my sword super strong
but it takes all my
my health
wait don't let me heal myself what the
[\h__\h]
one hp and your sword does fire damage
oh
cool
no no no no no no no
i can just unequip another oh
my father would stay like that
okay
i managed to clear chill just over by a
few grams and they still want me to
reduce
i end up with all my power banks being
thrown away
oh what the [\h__\h] man
just a few grams
you know some of these people
and those airports they just
they just want to make somebody suffer
because i don't know
they don't like their job or something
which i understand like it can be a very
stressful job surely i can imagine
[Music]
how are we gonna do this again
okay okay now i know
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
i come here
ah
nice
[Music]
like even when he gets hit like that it
doesn't take him any time to like
recover and take a hit like
on me take a swing on me
oh you would think that he needs a
moment to like wow
yeah he doesn't stagger that's the word
i thought i had him too
good fight good fight
is
i need to really do it from a safe
distance
ah that's not too dangerous but okay it
worked
there we go there we go there's one more
right
no i still have enough monopods to take
another one just like the same way
uh-huh i see you you think i can't see
you you're very obviously alive sir
[Music]
okay
oh [\h__\h] uh okay no i thought he was
gonna block that one with his shield but
nobody could
i'm already out of mana
now i have to do the rest with my own
power
i can't do it i know we've tried it
before and i went i got pretty far ah
that was so fast dude
[Music]
hi um maybe um next time i use some
berries as well
[Music]
four months two shots but nothing also
two shots oh see i know something was
weird about that
okay
i knew it
oh that one stays gone
[Music]
oh well then it's easy well then
i thought that one was gonna come back
[Music]
ah
so that one does count as a boss monster
then
okay
um
[Music]
it's okay though
i got some some cheeky [\h__\h]
some cheeky hits in
okay
oh man this this
teleportation skill makes everything
just too easy
[Applause]
[Music]
[\h__\h] go away oh wait this was up there
up here
fun fun fun fun fun
it's at least not as [\h__\h]
annoying as that boss fight we had last
time
so this is uh oh is this mana what was
the
for attack
monorail attack
mana
magic
magic back in the game they
i should have gone for hp first because
like i
i just i came here with no expectations
but yeah there's a hero grave everywhere
everywhere
all right let's go back
and go to the next one stumble upon the
next one by accident again
last two are in the forest true
the east forest
okay let's teleport there then
only two
left only two are left
oh yeah i guess so
uh hp and attack oh
no callie fancier
oh man see today the game is fun again
and there were some painful moments
already in the beginning with the
the crows
the ravens and the
the clones of me
but besides that
it's been fun
um
back in my groove yeah oh i'm getting
used to it again wait let me heal
let me heal
wait can i upgrade something
i can upgrade mp
oh
yeah baby
[Music]
um
shotgun's plenty i'm i'm relying a
little bit too much on it maybe
but in my first fight against those
knights you can only see that i i could
do it with the sword only if i wanted to
i could
is this the one
to the forest
oh [\h__\h]
uh okay i'm a little bit too early here
i guess this is like i'm supposed to
like come here
what if i kill her now though is it
possible
oh [\h__\h]
what's that
that does a lot of damage huh let's give
it a try why not it could be fun
could be a flex if i do it
i'm just gonna shortcut everything
oh okay that hit me
[Music]
[Laughter]
monkey times
oh now i want to try again this is fun
is this the final fight
it's easy man
it's [\h__\h] easy
i'm gonna win this now what happens if i
win it now will i end the game early
what happens
yes
that is the oh okay yours attacks that
no i can already do it now
oh
okay maybe the other phases are more
difficult
okay okay i want to try one more time
though and if i get close to killing it
then i'll just let it kill me
[Music]
oh
kibaba version of gremlin gremlin loves
was that oh yeah
it's a fast battle
a fast battle oh oh you got me there
i'm actually
letting you
i'm letting you win
out of mercy
oh
ah
too far
[Music]
i'm letting her go
ah killed me too easily but this is
definitely possible especially if we get
our hp back
hp and
attack yeah yeah yeah
once we have that back it's easy clap
easy clap
yeah i could use the fire one too
because i'm only using the gun
i don't know
she doesn't have a shield so
yeah i could just go
where is the east forest
ah that's not it that's the west right
oh but we could check out that secret
while we're here
oh
can i get it now because before you guys
said i could i wouldn't be able to get
it
wait no am i somewhere else
i know i'm here at the bottom
here
i can't get it now okay
um
ah gotta go around here
clearing the game or seeking an end
use the power of the holy cross and
traverse the golden path share your
wisdom be
ah take your rightful place share your
wisdom
is it about the two different endings
uh it's like if i if i get every page i
get the true ending
if i just go right to the uh and last
bus then i get the normal ending that's
what it's telling me well how many pages
am i missing
right so this is 53
1 15
okay three pages missing in between here
not missing not missing four three
two one
forty
forty nine
forty eight forty seven
six five
four three
two one oh okay
zero i've been doing pretty well
29 8 7
6 5
4 3
18 i've never been so
unintentionally what's the word
good at finding all the secrets at a
game before 17 16
14 13 oh 12 11 10 nine
eight seven six
three ah okay five and four are missing
and um
at the very end there's three pages
missing
but who knows maybe i wouldn't have them
now anyway because it's something i get
like now
unintentionally completionist yeah
well okay we're actually not that far
off of getting
the true ending the extra ending
get the a ending first is better oh can
i like
do does it have to be separately
five pages missing only without even
trying
mine's
what do you mean with not i can't get it
normally
now
wait how
am i missing a pop here
i
can't just not
use this
teleportation thingy here
why is it so useless why is it so
useless
the teleporter only leads to the page
what the hell
hey was that the only teleporter in
the east garden
where is this lead again
ah
well shall we go to the east garden from
here no the west garden i mean
well now i want that stupid secret
jump past the middle
right
i can't
we don't need the secret oh okay
i can i can
well okay let's go east forest
whatever doesn't matter
[Laughter]
[Music]
now this makes sense
now it makes sense
[Music]
shall we go to the ruin the tall how
about that one
we don't have the
here was grey from there yeah it's the
way
doesn't [\h__\h] matter where we go first
what's your eh
hole
the atoll is currently not reachable
[\h__\h]
i see
was there no he was grave there
then
what about
eastern vault
here
oh i have it
yeah
no there was no hero's grave there
daniel
okay saving
oh
what the [\h__\h] is going on here
oh it's gone
siege engine yeah it's [\h__\h] gone i
took it
i took it sorry i have to why are you
guys so weird about it don't be so weird
about it
things have to be done
i took that right
oh yeah this was the first boss fight
[Music]
don't be so
don't be such a drama queen
guys
i did it for a good reason
i mean even
this little fox when in the moment it
took those things
the fox didn't know what it was doing
for what purpose but
the fox had a feeling that there was
gonna be a good purpose a good reason
for all of that so
stop crying
it all has a bigger meaning
it won't hold up in court
uh so where is this anywhere that we're
gonna find here huh
i pull the windows
those uh candles isn't this a
teleportation thingy
this is a golden platform shouldn't i be
able to teleport here
ah is it here
is it
looking scary here ah
oh there's the altar um
is it here
i'm a little bit scared to teleport over
there
i can't okay
what does that box thing and maybe it's
not here
when i go back
suddenly
was it glowing this bride before
was it
where is the
surprise enemy hat
i'm expecting something here
oh god
hi
here was grave is that lin
thank you i forgot
thank you
[Music]
oh god oh
oh no these days take my they drain my
energy again
okay okay oh no there's more of them we
are right
okay thank god
that's the way to deal with these
[\h__\h]
but there will be more right
but wait there's more
ah
[\h__\h] they got me
oh [\h__\h]
i [\h__\h] help
gosh i hate them
it's difficult to keep on switching uh
[Music]
ah it's already over yeah
so keep on switching i don't want to use
the gun already no
i wanted to wait until they're at least
a little bit smaller that was my goal
yeah and switching
the focus
continuously
to whoever's closer is a little bit
annoying
run past them
but they're gonna follow me
running in this game
it's not really the solution in my
opinion they dropped mp yeah
okay i'll just i'll just shoot them
i'll just shoot them okay i'll kill ya
oh no i only got
it doesn't even have to be the big gun
don't have to take out my bead guns
i don't know which one is more effective
more wasteful but you know the
the risk of the big gun is that you're
gonna miss
uh-huh
yeah
oh [\h__\h] i'm out of mother
okay
okay okay
okay i got it
sorry i really have to focus in this
game
oh that's it
that's all i have to do for this
one i expected more
can i go there
secret wait before i take my thingy i'm
looking for a secret
maybe i shouldn't
oh was this
cute
can i take the broom
i wanna clean these things up
oh
i kind of need to go to an idol meeting
hmm
nothing came out of it what is the
there must be something
no no no no there's something here
there's something here
there's something here that must be
something here
[Laughter]
that was completely blocked wow
special chest that's a really special
chest
what
no item i've ever received before made
such a special sound too
where is that
oh
how do i use that
what it's not here
what was that can i
fly
a golden room no it's a broom not a bell
the trophy room it's a trophy
so there's more of these what the [\h__\h]
but that's not part of
a hundred percenting the game right
that was one of the last secrets i found
wait but if there's so many trophies and
i actually missed out on a lot until now
no
i was always so
so
for real with everything i always
looked so
closely not related to content okay but
that wasn't a lucky
cute find
these are tough to find but this one
wasn't that tough though because i found
it
because i found it it means it wasn't
that tough i got my feedback
last is
yeah
i can even do an upgrade last is attack
this fight was really easy though i
expected a
like more difficult fight what the [\h__\h]
hmm
[Music]
[Laughter]
we could even if you say we could even
clear the game now by just killing that
lady
we're so close at the end huh well it
has already been three hours so i guess
so
makes sense
one more one more one more
okay but then i'll go to an idol meeting
now you guys you're
okay with it please don't go please
don't leave
i don't
i don't meeting
[Music]
i cuddled my cats a little bit and i
also got a muffin
[Music]
a chocolate muffin
all right i need to turn on the lights
okay
[Music]
i'm i got some snacks
because i knew i was gonna be hungry
you couldn't drop them laughing
[Music]
hmm
okay
let's go
um
go next
right
question mark hp upgrades
wow
[Music]
oh so much hp
you see how i got the lady like one
chunk down with basically no hp
and no attack
oh i'll be so [\h__\h] powerful when i'm
done here
holy [\h__\h] she won't be much trouble i
was really scared to do the last bus but
if that's the last bus
oh
never mind
[Music]
um
which one is
the east garden
isn't this one
no that's the library
that's
where we came from
we went to the eastern vault just now
town ruins is just the overworld
the quarry we
went to this one
west garden we went to this one
there's
uh no statue in the room at all
and this is where the boss is
huh
look at the next page
this one
is this how i have to go for one of
those doors to get to
nah you don't mean this page right you
mean this this one
the bottom bottom right
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
yeah
that is like looks like it's not even
part of it
okay
all right what is this
yeah okay
well here we are
ready to get our last
uh stats back
to become as strong as we are supposed
to be because we deserve it
uh just checking out if there's some
secrets some new things for me to
oh that's all ready all ready to hear
was great
oh you are you're the enemy i'm supposed
to fight here are you the one protecting
it
but i want to go find secrets first
new secrets with my new ability
is there nothing here
i'm going to find something
[Music]
she could have done
secret
oh hi lady she's
she doing yoga
it looks like she was doing some
yoga moves up there
meditating
nice yeah this place looks
mostly the same
where's this again
oh huh oh i guess maybe there's not much
here to find
someone
maybe i you know can find another trophy
or a page
still missing some pages
guard house 2
this was still the beginning in the
beginning of the game so maybe i also
missed some
secret
pops or chests here i don't know
no okay see even back then i was good at
finding stuff
lower forest
okay
i never came back here before with the
grappling hook did i
right here i can actually not teleport i
do need my grappling hook for this one
uh oh yeah the chest i didn't get the
chest yet
nice
another one
oh money
uh this one ah see the first one you get
with the grappling hook and then you you
get here you see another chest and
you're like what the [\h__\h] i can't reach
this one either i have to come back here
again you're [\h__\h] kidding me
wait the flower was
oh
another hp upgrade
yo
damn i thought we were done oh whoa whoa
whoa whoa whoa what what
yeah let's go
[Music]
wait that chest down there let me get
that one how how how how how
how how
i spy with my little eye up half to the
chest the last coin to get to nine at
least
[Music]
is there something here
okay another grappling hook huh
where does that go
up here oh
this thing there's a trophy that's a
trophy that's a trophy that's a trophy
that's a trophy but there was a page
that said something about this that i
have to uh combine some weapons for some
reason
uh
was this about the trophies
no
this is the one i saw this
which page was that
i love this book i want this printed out
did i sell it print it out
that would kind of be a spoiler to
yourself to the game obviously
it's not quite like a
like a real guidebook for like a
different game
because in real guidebooks i would say
there's not
this much i mean you would you would
think this doesn't help me much i think
it didn't help me much for some for at
least the first half of the game
now it's starting to actually help me
oh translated that would be cool
the original hello that game manual oh
wait i can't find the where was that
what was that page
wait that enemy is the one that's up
there but have we ever seen that anime
anywhere else before have we fought that
ever was it was that maybe the first
enemy we thought because i can't
remember it's too long ago then but
i feel like i've never fought that one
before
was it on the memos oh
oh
yeah okay
oh they are the level one enemies okay
so what are they trying to tell me with
this
just get up with the grabbing hook but
why why
why do i need the i sent the
fire weapon
is that thing so strong up there
wait does it mean that here there's also
a trophy
are those memos for the trophies
[Music]
don't know
ice and fire to kill it
really
do i
just attack from here
oh
it doesn't
seem to need that
both copy dish wait but
how do i how do i get up then how do i
get up then
[\h__\h] ah
i should have i should have frozen it
then i can hold on to it
or what
need to reset i think i can reset yeah
cause like um it saves every time i i go
to a statue right
well wait then
otherwise
oh can i reset just but will the enemy
be back if i just
leave the area once
or do i really have to reset the
the game
will this enemy never come back
oh just oh just a normal reset ah okay
wait there we go
okay i thought it was like really
serious like a really really bad fuck-up
oh
never saw this before okay was i was i
able to come here before
was i
this must have been possible
okay let me um
yeah
hey walking off the screen
normally the enemies are still gone
no
yeah it's still gone
just walking off the screen doesn't help
so i'll have to
sorry guys we're close to the end don't
worry don't worry
um
i have to find all the secrets all the
trophies now too
now i think all the trophies is
impossible but
just because we already saw it there
and it was in the manual
as a hint
now i want to do it
yeah
yeah it's my final run i'm gonna enjoy
it
[Music]
yeah yeah
i'm gonna miss tunic
these like
games that feel like they're made for
you
they don't
they don't just come that easily
wait
if i hmm
how can i ice it from down here
or do i have to press it at once
oh that's a thing
i don't know
oh wait i have no no we're everywhere
what we learned a new attack basically
it stuns the enemy
but
where's the difference in just using the
ice thing because that stuns it too but
in a different kind of way and more aoe
regal weasel is the achievement i got
for that
no now i'm using it
separately
eh i'm i'm not sure
i'm not sure also i'm not sure if i'll
ever use it again but
huh
was an interesting revelation just now
only against enemies maybe
maybe
the timing
um
and we probably don't need it anymore
but maybe it's one of those things that
if you know it
could be useful in the boss fight
because we were gonna use the the fire
wand anyway
but if we actually
can stun her with that but does it use
more magic okay wait let me see i use
firewand only it takes that amount
i use
both but
wait wait i need an enemy to use that on
can you guys check the mp
uh and keep an eye on how much it uses
there's no enemies here to practice on
i shouldn't [\h__\h] i did it wrong
you guys crack me up oh there you go how
much did i use how much is that i don't
know how much that does okay i have to
continue doing it because i don't have
my
i don't have my
my weapon out so what did that do
is it
that uses a lot i feel like using both
at the same time uses less than just
using the ice alone
you're right right right right right
yeah so it's a cheap stun that also does
damage
[Music]
its cow
now we're gaming guys now we are gaming
interesting no enemies besides
from there there's two
she's
gonna explore
wow
i
have the power of
exhaustion
i'm out of
yeah but i'm there
i'm fine i'm fine
these ones gave me so many heart attacks
in that one map remember the good old
days
remember guys the good old days of the
last stream two days ago
two
days ago
baby oh bombs oh thank you
too i haven't seen those type of bombs
in a long time i know my hero grave is
probably over there but i'm going to
check here first
east forest
oh it's ah
wait are those considered um boss
monsters now because they projected the
hero grave so if i heal myself here will
they be back
because normally those are not boss
monsters but they had a different role
this time
i'll hear back
ah
but he can't aim at me from up here
loser
oh
wait since when was there one there
didn't see that one last time
i have the high ground now
you can't deal with close combat can you
ignore this guy
evil jaw
evil
what
what about that is evil they're evil
they've been boozled me so many times
man
yo there were quite some differences and
difficulties uh with these graves
interesting
like the the last two that we did were a
lot easier
than the other ones
oh wow there's chocolate cream in the
muffin
wow
now how do i get
oh
you see
what my ear is poking there my my right
ear from you guys left ear
for the whole time i thought that was um
a page
and i was hoping to get to the middle at
some point to get it
it's just a reflect like a light
reflection
same
i thought it was a page
okay
so now wait we got all the upgrades so
now we just killed the last bus
no
but then the game will end
but girl foxes just wanna have fun on
oh foxy just wanna help
[Music]
okay we'll get the normal ending first
and then we'll get the pages that i'm
missing you guys will have to help me
though probably to tell me where they
are if you can
um
so our choice of weapon is the gun and
yeah i'm gonna go for the wand and the
mag the fire wand and the gun for now
i don't think i'm gonna use a new
combination
i think
i wonder if you can combine other
weapons too
one page is super hard to get
oh hp upgrade ah
okay i'll go to um the one
what
go to the one that we just came from
i can use other healing besides potions
that is true but like putting it into
the slot and then putting the weapon
back into the slot
for me is something i can just not
handle
[Laughter]
i don't need it
i have so many potions yo
and now i have another hp upgrade
oh but it is true that i guess i don't
need my items anymore so i could use
them but i don't i don't think i'll need
them
yo
my hp is like a tower
like a skyscraper
i will tweet it out that i'm gonna do
the last boss now
i'll tweet that
uh where's my browser
oh
how come i closed it
a new window
how did i close it when did i close it
let's let's let everyone know
i'm doing
the final boss
doing the final bus
now
and then the trail ending
climb box
oops reverse cups look
[Music]
um
i am trying to figure out what true
ending is in japanese
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
two
[Music]
yes
now
people gonna start maybe coming into the
stream in five minutes and they'll be
like
where's the last bus and i'll be like i
just killed it that only took me five
minutes sorry guys
no no
i mean it could
we'll see
now the question is though
do you like nah definitely need healing
right
i can't just
use mana pots again with the last bus
that would be ridiculous
um
what was this again
is it one free death
that would be nice
what should i do
i can i can but
is that
should i
is that how i did it the first time i
was up against her
if you can dodge everything yes
i can dodge a few times and i mean my hp
gives me a buffer of you know about the
things i can dodge
strong ah that was that strong
explosions
what was this one again the shield one
i don't even need this one to be honest
with my teleportation i don't even need
to run fast i can i can go for a
different one for that too the shield is
very longer parry oh
i'm not gonna use that
what was this one
you know
i wanna go for a useful combination
faster stamina regeneration
oh that's useful because uh i mean
i mean a teleportation honestly really
doesn't use that much stamina but it's
at least more useful than other things
and then this how about this combination
i've kept on this one and this one the
whole game
it's like i'm quizzing you on tunic
stamina region very useful
i think so too okay
well i feel like we can do this with so
many different combinations and
strategies but we'll try this one first
today
um
second one is blocking cross let's
stamina but then you'd have to block
[Laughter]
[Music]
wait at this one
or this one
wait do i have a meaningless one in here
because then i'll i'll change to speed
after all
or something else i don't know what
should i do what was this one i wanna
put a fingertip on a blog you're free to
fight another no no no no
it's hard to wait
i'm thinking right now
but one of the shoelaces
is the one
broken sword good no it's not unless i
really don't get any damage but
it brings me down to one hp i don't have
that much confidence
lose that defense oh
increase damage less defense
that would be interesting maybe but
okay let's try first like this oh god oh
god oh god okay i'm going in i'm going
in guys
[Music]
oh okay i will only do that when i'm
like behind here
[Music]
okay
that hit me
oh
[Music]
oh stamina
okay
oh [\h__\h] okay sorry i'm super focused
right now
[Music]
easy easy easy
oh i'm surprised that she didn't dodge
that
oh [\h__\h] i looked at the chat for one
second
oh sorry okay but it's a really good
first try though
[Music]
did i hit her with any of those i'm not
sure what happened there
[Music]
wow
she's so confused by me because i'm so
fast i'm so fast
she's so confused
why is this fox so fast
i also did the same attack twice
[Music]
to know
the our opponent you know
i'm still getting to know her
okay cool cool halfway through on the
first try
um
[Music]
i'm still learning her but
oh oh wait revive here okay
[Music]
nice first try um
i consumed a few too many parts the
thing is i have so much hp now and my my
pots are still i have seven hp but
the potions are still only on four
i wonder where those other potion
healing items are
oof
would be good to have that but okay
[Music]
go next it's definitely not impossible
i've had harder times with other enemies
nice
touch
oh
whoa
[Music]
i got one hit there
oh pretty nice ah so little damage and
already one-fourth down
okay
oh [\h__\h]
oh what is that oh yeah oh [\h__\h]
okay
shouldn't have done that now
[Music]
okay got too cocky again
but i've still weighed way more potions
and we're already at 50 again
let me hear
[Music]
i could have gotten ahead there
[Laughter]
i'm crumbling
[Music]
ah
nice
i like this fight
smooth but i'm out of mana and i don't
have the intention of switching to
monopods now
but it's pretty easy even without magic
as long as i can move this fast yo
[Music]
oh oh [\h__\h] i ran out of oh
okay okay that got me that got me good
oh
oh never run out of
stamina uh
[\h__\h]
she got me she got me out of my ribbon
okay okay okay okay
oh
she got me
but
it's totally fine i'm still very
motivated this is just this was just a
second attempt
it was better than the last time
as long as we don't have to try so often
that i get worse instead of getting
better
[Laughter]
reminding me of uh
two days ago
mm-hmm
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] i should really just go all in
when i
have the chance for that
oh
she missed me
[Music]
i thought i could afford that
okay now i'm just like playing around a
little bit too much
sorry i'm sorry
sorry
sorry mommy sorry in case you're on my
mommy because that chance is pretty high
or one of my one of my mommy's
[Music]
oops that was way too far
i'm getting worse but okay sometimes we
need these uh fat fries to kill me can
we kill my camera just can't killing
just kidding i want to try again
thank you make it short
need a need a restart a refresh
no
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh man
that one will never be
not funny to me
bananas
would you mind coming here for a second
yeah thank you
oh [\h__\h]
that one shouldn't get me
oh [\h__\h] that one neither
[Music]
oh
oh my i'm getting busy
i'm getting dizzy [\h__\h]
this point of view makes me really dizzy
right now oh my god
my gosh sticks off
[Music]
oh that one's scarier
i like twice but not when you do attacks
twice
not too far a little bit too far
[Music]
out of magic already ah kind of wasted
it there huh
[Music]
did i get hit sometimes i can't see oh
now i got it
[Music]
wow
oh god i'm so speedy
second name kiwawa gonzales
[Music]
shockwave okay
good good good good good good
hush
ah okay it was pretty good it was pretty
good but okay this
is oh mama mia
i
am
checking
oh it's lagging the game is lagging for
me
ah
now it's back to normal
one hp or five in the dream
ah
one is being a
dream couldn't i couldn't zoom away my
my stamina was
at its end but okay
good
i got pretty focused i was pretty
immersed emerged
in kanji nichikazo connects
ain't no start
and it starts let's go
fun fun fun
now i don't need to learn anything i
think i'm doing pretty well
if anything
this was just what the fourth try or so
third fourth time
there's still things sides to her that
i need to
like i don't know yet but it's okay that
i don't know yet because we just got to
know each other
it's like our fourth date man
come here
[Music]
got a good amount of hits there
this this is what you were talking about
huh i did it
this one i learned too
i can read that one perfectly and yes
you guys i saw that one coming but i
think don't think i dodged it
i'm going
quite the aggressive way
[Music]
ah too far
beautiful actually quite a few mistakes
too but
i'm playing more aggressive right now
[Music]
that's a big chance to go to the front
and attack her when she does that
uh oh yeah okay
oh [\h__\h] that one down is a bit hard to
see there
[Music]
oh
nice holy [\h__\h] i think this is the one
[Music]
oh it's lagging game is lagging
[\h__\h] it's losing fps on my side but it
might only be like on my side again
music is so chill actually
[Music]
oh
[\h__\h]
i
[Music]
oh
good run it was fun
it's good when when a boss fight is
challenging but it's still like so
enjoyable makes me laugh
um
this game i want to marry this game
you need to go buy a ring
that fits
this
enormous
finger of the game
staying enormous because it's so good
wait i just want to explode my body
that's not quite what i want to do
[Music]
oh what oh my god okay okay okay
ah too aggressive kiwawa
[Laughter]
i thought it was the other attack that
makes the big circle
[Music]
i like it when she moves away like that
like ah you're so close friend
but i want to cuddle this little fox has
no mommy
oh i'm on the stamina
this doesn't feel like the right
one
oh [\h__\h] last one got me
[Music]
was that dodge like two last minutes
should i
go earlier
oh [\h__\h]
making a lot of mistakes sorry
okay that was that necessary because i
was so [\h__\h] close anyway
i
don't ruin my my beautiful
runs
[Music]
i could still make it
oh i should have drank drunken dead in a
little bit more of a safer place
yeah i'm gonna die i'm gonna die i'm
sorry guys i know i'm so close yeah
i know i'm so close but i never got so
close before
wow sorry sorry sorry i could have done
it
if i think if that last time i drank the
the potion was in a safe distance
and she wouldn't have interjected it
then i would have
done it yeah
cool hey i don't want this fight to end
though i don't want this game to end no
i have
separation anxiety guys with games that
i like
and tv shows that i like
oh [\h__\h]
i did that by accident cause like
teleportation and exploding that is the
same
key
can you stop using the same attack
[Music]
oh that was the triple attack
nice combo
[Music]
getting a few too many hits oh from here
so what are you guys gonna eat for
dinner today huh
huh
how was your day
how's the weather
that again
[Music]
beautiful that was a beautiful dodge if
i've ever seen one
[Music]
i'm getting really good at this
the timing was bad sorry
ah that one i'm really bad at dodging
that one
because it looks so similar to the
circle
i'm gonna run out of stamina
come back yeah come back
i should oh that was
twice
okay we have to stop this insanity now
lady
she did that it's like four times
okay i'm winning
two parts
[Music]
okay don't don't [\h__\h] it up
no she's spamming like everything
[Music]
i underestimated everything
guys hello hello i'm in the second face
hello this is back is back hello hello
oh my god
are we back hello hey hi i'm in the
second phase hello
i didn't expect second place
[Music]
yeah i'm not gonna make it but okay i'm
doing pretty well for the first time of
the second phase she has some new
attacks but she spams this one three
times
oh god
obvious worst possible timing ever
okay we got halfway through the second
phase
oh my god
what
[Music]
you didn't see it when i got the last
hit and
but finally
a boss with a second face that's the
first time i think in this game
oh
it's not it's not that easy after all
so
i have to do my
best oh sh
[Music]
it's not gonna get easier
although i'm getting better
i like dancing man
ah [\h__\h] too far oh oh that made it not
actually was guilty
close enough
you guys see how aggressive i am
dodge that one and that one
oh [\h__\h]
halfway through
[Music]
no don't ruin my perfect run
no no no no no it was so beautiful
[Music]
[Applause]
suddenly she can't be like
what
no no no no no no
that was so good
it was her fault
it was her fault she can't chicken
chickens
handshake event going on right now
line up guys shake your hands
your own hands but not like that don't
touch them just shake them
sick sick sick
yeah that was gonna be such a good run
right you know it
you're going to stand
i'm always sick without touching
i'm talking about just shaking your
hands
two two very different things can be
said with one
one word huh
[Music]
away
ah okay okay okay okay
four times
that was my fault and my bad ah again
okay it seems like i have uh forgotten
the ability to dodge that one
ah and she knows it yeah okay kill me
kill me please this is our terrible run
terrible run
no okay don't give up
but i need you know to leave as much
room as possible for healing in the
second run and the second phase
[Music]
so
i honestly
i need the first phase to be
pretty good
oh
and this is not
it's not a good run
ah no not good at all
really really sucky
really bad really yeah okay i deserved
that one
running too much nah i have to be really
dynamic in this fight
um
bad rental practice yeah
freezing
freezing her huh
yeah i don't use the magic wand as often
as i
could use it it's not even that hard to
get her she sometimes dodges it but
sometimes
it's actually pretty easy to get her i
could change to phrasing her
maybe we can drive
[Music]
oh
interesting
[Music]
would you mind coming here
oh [\h__\h]
even after being frozen she still got
that hit in
did you see how her sword was still
descending
oh it didn't hit me
uh now it's kind of bad to do that
a pretty good ice weapon
it doesn't last for that long though
[Music]
oh [\h__\h] was out of stamina
let me hit you
oh [\h__\h] oh it's a dead end you know it's
a circle but i wasn't a dead end
[Music]
i need to heal i need to heal
okay bad run too
[Music]
i wish my [\h__\h] tiny ass dagger was
longer
[Music]
oh
ow
okay we're almost
almost there yeah
now i know that's not the end
oh that's [\h__\h] scary
i'm gonna play
campbell
[Music]
so much for being careful
hi donkey wonky
[Music]
okay okay okay
can i quickly switch to
changing to berries
i don't think i have time for that
[Music]
oh my god
ah
so
reckless ah
[Music]
no i don't i really don't need you now i
love you but i don't need to know
you know bp i know
it's really difficult
yeah you flopping down on the floor
asking for belly runs is not a good
timing but i love you yeah
[Music]
your baby
yeah you're trying to give me some hope
huh
okay okay i'll take that hope
okay
junkers get on my lap let's go a little
little break how about we let the cat
play a little bit
i are recharging huh she's so soft
[Music]
that second phase
you know the first moment when she
revives the second phase i used that
moment to get a good hits a good couple
good amount of hits in
because that's very precious but i could
also use that time to switch one item
to berries for healing purposes
so maybe i should do that but you know
in those kind of moments i'm like too
too nervous this um
uh
like
i don't know
how to do it in such a
short and stressful time
practice it now
i don't know
ah right now i have to cuddle my cat
the gun yeah i mean at that point i'm
like out of mana anyway and not gonna
use it anyway so
um
i would change it to hp berries
if
anything okay chunky wonky is gone
got enough of those cuddles apparently
so i would do this and then go back it
shouldn't be too difficult because
especially i don't even need to change
back to anything afterwards
it shouldn't be that difficult
or
why start off with that because i didn't
even use the gun in the last run i think
but now
we're gonna use the gun
strange at the end of the first phase
before she transforms
ah no that's dangerous too
second phase seems like she pulls out
the attacks even faster but first face
is also no joke so it's not like i
really have the time to do it in that
phase either
if i could run around while being in the
menu
but i can't
if i could run while being in the menu
then i
might be able to do it but i can't
hmm
all right stabbed with the berries let's
see how the switch goes
oh oh sorry
that was
wreck less
gosh
how is her hitbox so tiny
it's like she's a ghost
and me too but no i'm not a ghost
anymore
ah holy oh that's dangerous
ah reckless
[Music]
goddammit
ah i thought too late
yeah it's pretty bad
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] this run
[Music]
[Applause]
it's okay it's okay i'm still
i'm still um
i'm still happy
happy happy happy mother get it
[Music]
i can do it you think so
probably at some point
[Music]
go next
put some pep in your step
i was not already pep in my step huh
[Music]
okay good good good good good
oh that was the freak dance hitter
brief
breathe keep up
oh interesting
[Music]
this is really like elden ring level
dark souls level you really have to
learn
this opponent's move and dying a few
times is perfectly normal
[Music]
yo [\h__\h]
ah [\h__\h]
[Music]
what is so pretty decent run
ah not anymore
[Music]
in the first couple of runs i had
better
timings
for the magic items
[Music]
like some some things
at some points i get better and at some
parts i get worse
[Music]
almost there
okay now i have to
switch
oh my god i don't think i can do it
[Music]
i can't get out of bed
okay
okay i have some buffer
[Music]
that problems getting out of the menu
for some reason
but
[Music]
i uh have gone closer not further away
wait all the berries i'm gonna be eating
i won't have the next time
i forgot
oh yeah her sword has the training power
now
oh my god
okay this is not the run i guess
[Music]
oh
i can't
wait i still have one pot
it's even bigger now
no i won't make it
can't beat
it the game is so difficult
hush
let me hit you nice lady please
let me hit you
[Music]
i'm gonna die
i don't know how am i gonna do this now
i have no
no berries left
[Music]
um
bye berries
i don't even have that much money though
no i'm not gonna waste my dynamite too
like she also moves
[Music]
what does this give you again when
oh man
when you get a wish
wait what you need one more but it was
free free free
where's my wish
slots oh [\h__\h] slots there's not really
like any cards that
will help me with this fight
[\h__\h] that
my hand hurts now too
well i could change
accessibility but that's like
that's so weak
if i can get like the remaining
stamina and
um
potion
no items but i would have to look up the
locations
i'm using a controller what do you think
i'm using
decoys ah
is that why you guys said to keep the
decoys but even then i only have four
and if the run goes bad and i wasted the
decoys on that
the stamina isn't even the problem yo
it's not that much of a problem it
happens maybe once
per run then i
run out of stamina sometimes i die from
it sometimes i don't it's not such a big
problem like you make a
make it out to be
the problem is that at the end of the
fight i just
don't have enough hp potions or whatever
left
i'm struggling to survive
it is not the problem no
now i can't get my items back
you want me to try this combo
[Music]
not even like that that in order to hit
those two
at the same time
i kind of have to move my hand around
the controller upwards you know what i
mean
to reach them both
successfully
if i try to do it with a normal grip
there's a high possibility it will fail
because my thumb is a little bit small
it's a bit tricky to press there i could
i could position it so that it's like um
like this but then i have to get used to
the fact that my sword is suddenly now
here on square
and you know how it goes when in the
middle of a boss fight after you're so
used to controls you suddenly change the
controls
um try out some different strategies be
more aggressive or blocking pairing some
attacks maybe could help
dodging once to avoid most attacks
multiple refinery positions
i'm just just trying to stay like fast
and
unreachable to her
[Music]
oh man
but i wasted my berries and that makes
me sad
[Music]
didn't they say i get like more damage
but these are all you know
once i waste them they're not gonna come
back so
when i experiment with them and it goes
wrong then they're gone
[Music]
keep
one
keeping closer in the first phase
makes the humans chad said seeing very
sweet
this final fight when are you going to
use them
but do you not understand my logic like
i used them
and they helped but i die anyway because
it's tough then i can't use them the
next time when i need them
[Music]
and then okay i understand reading her
without
using them is also a waste i know
but still but
i mean i guess
but then again in any case those are
items that i i have to go into my menu
and then put them on my
on like some setting first
and
the only moment i can do this during
this whole fight is it when the second
phase starts
switch equipment back a pop of pepper
you mean this
i still i forgot again what that one
does
ice being useful to switch
but
i'm gonna like be like how to get out of
the map i don't know why i failed last
time i put something there and then i
just go it's that easy i don't know why
i mess it up when i'm in the battle i
just get too nervous and
then uh
and freezing her and in the beginning of
the second phase when she's down anyway
when she's waiting
will just end up giving me i think the
same amount of time
i think
i stein on mine and sword don't use
dynamite when she's standing still
but you mean
at any given point of time or in a
specific timing
just enter baron what is the use of two
types of magic
then i shall go with the eyes
this one
just to make sure
eventually we can also try a strategy
where i go with the mana berries and
hope to just spam magic at the end
but for now how about i use this one
this one makes me stronger right and
heals my stamina i guess but like i
don't understand the healing stamina
part because
it heals itself up pretty fast anyway
generally
like in general
not it doesn't make as much sense as an
hp potion
[Music]
i should just fight her with a stick
pepper is the one for ah
does it recharge
how does it reach out to stamina then if
it's not making you stronger either then
how does it recharge does it just
recharge once
or
overtime
then i guess this one is better
a timed buff
does your stamina stay full
for a certain amount of time
even if you zoom around
honestly i don't think that's that much
helpful
cause how do i know
when to use it to prevent the running
out of stamina i would have to know
when i'm about to spam it so hard that
i'm running out of it
but i don't think i can predict that so
it's for defense
really
i guess we don't we'll never find out
what that really is for but
i'll try the the peppers
the chili pepper whatever that is
uh strategy i guess
[Music]
i have a tendency to accidentally
push the wrong button i don't want to
push
you know if i was playing this on my own
privately i might go for accessibility
settings and make it easier but i'm
streaming it so it's like
the most
embarrassing thing to do as a streamer
on stream live
but before i start crying that will be
my last resort
but i'll maybe even hide the screen so
you guys can see my shame
yeah it would help because apparently
there's a setting that makes your um hp
and your stamina
or mp not go down
wait there was something
no stamina restrictions no fail mode i
guess you go down to one hp and then
oopsie
we could at least turn off the stump and
no restrictions if you guys keep on
saying that the stamina is you know the
reason i die
we couldn't need to dance
it's less of a help than the hp
[Music]
i've been so good for this whole game
okay and i'm still good i'm still good
at it i did a good job with this bombs
but
okay i'm gonna try a few more times then
you guys are torturing me
oh
man
would be quitting
no it would
the hp made me know
you guys are so mean just want me to cry
and i would still be a gamer okay
[Music]
i know i spammed it i know i know
i was scared you know
free it's very precious
[Music]
getting some good
hits so far
oh [\h__\h] i don't know why i went there if
i said go closer
i did it
oh god
oh [\h__\h]
god i'm really good right now
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay should i use that should i use the
thing
[Music]
i'm doki doking so hard right now
oh god
oh [\h__\h] up
ah
now
[Music]
i was i was
no
ugh
[Music]
it's just a game
i don't i don't know if i can read super
chats today this will take a while
so
oh
i don't think i can ever get such a good
run again
[Music]
my heart is beating
but it should be
should be beating
yeah bye
the suffering is real
hmm
remember the video what video
a video
and i used the
i used the
item but i'm not sure how much more
damage i did and i didn't even get that
many hits in any way
maybe
do this i don't know
did you guys see how much more damage i
did
didn't seem to help right i don't know
[Music]
maybe in the last phase
let her attack the decoy but i only have
four
[Music]
i would only use it if it's a good run i
guess
um
how long does it even
let me see i don't know how long it
um
tunic
what is that carrot or
chili item chili pepper
item
and the hero will glow and
did you see me glowing
i didn't see myself glowing
when you eat a hot pepper the hero will
glow with red energy for a little bit
during this time you deal extra melee
attack damage but how long
i didn't see myself glowing either i ate
it like three times
or two
a single user on a booster attack
briefly can be purchased
but briefly how long is briefly i need
exact timing
counter
i don't think i was glowing
that's a lie
what
uh
pepper a singer you know it can be no
it's the same info
chili was a lie
those you
can you find our class hourglass i don't
know of such an item does it make does
it make the game go slow motion that
would be such a sick item
[Music]
it does
what
i
i i i will you know since it's something
that's not a consumable
but i can like use it as many times as i
want i will try
this method after all
i'm not gonna do this and we'll try it
and we might have to
practice a bit
or even switch i can't push those two at
the same time with a normal grip
[Music]
but i think maybe i can i can try to get
used to
this i can try
i can try i can try but then i run out
of i'll run out of
magic
i'll try to do the first phase
as much as possible without using this
yeah and then use it in the second phase
because if it stuns
then it's very important to stun her in
the second phase more important than
even in the first phase
but it's a new tactic so we'll have to
kind of get used to it again
[Music]
but i thought while i was looking for
the pepper the chili item i saw that
there was a advice
to use this combo
seemingly being the best way to beat the
boss
besides decoy items maybe
and if they say that
and i guess i should try it
okay you'll come here first
[Music]
for attacking
ah [\h__\h] okay
i have to get used to that
okay we're [\h__\h] up this run anyway
let me test this oh
okay
let me test it
now now i press it separately
now again
is it because of
the lack of
mana
i did it again
um
so kill me please thank you
[Music]
yeah no i'm just testing it out i i if i
get the hang of it
and i want to use it in the second phase
but right now
see just right in the beginning the
first few hits i i used the
fire wand
accidentally instead of
the sword button
because i put it somewhere else
[Music]
test
wrong but okay i'll take it
now this is again
just a test run but i can't
[Music]
i can't push it at the same time it only
worked the first time
[Music]
nikki knight
at this time it worked
i did it wrong again
it worked okay okay okay okay
just like maybe it's just like
uh instead of pushing it really strongly
no
now i'm out of mana
hmm
i can get used to the sword being on
square but
it fails so often to press them at once
switch to mana potions while you're
testing
ah i guess so yeah okay okay
um
no i practice on her
no
[Music]
wrong
i think was it wrong i think so
wrong again
right this time was right i don't know
i'm pushing them at the same time but
it's very finicky
and now i only push the magic wand
okay okay okay okay
okay okay i think i'm getting a feeling
for it
yeah okay
i'm getting it
it's actually is that freeze longer than
the normal
phrase ah it missed
oh
that's a possibility too
that was wrong
that was wrong too okay
i mean if i get it wrong and i'm luckily
close enough to her to actually
get the ice at least to hit then no
problem
a little bit of a waste but no problem
okay can we thank you
why don't you switch to one night so you
won't be punished as hard
what do you mean how am i being punished
because most of the time it's uh it ends
up being ice you mean
harry strat more effective yeah
okay
let me do one run
where i tried parrying which i have used
never effectively and consciously in
this game before
i shall try
okay okay it didn't work
didn't work
at least there's a there's an item for
it at least
[Music]
didn't too late
didn't like
let me get this
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh no
okay
i can't do the parry strut
and leave
um
i don't think
that would take me a day
to learn the timing
we're gonna
practice a little bit more sorry guys
[Music]
did she do it three times again that
[\h__\h]
[Music]
wrong wrong
wrong
hmm
oh wait one time i got it oh was that
the normal freeze
can you see like a difference
oh if you could do this in my real run
being so [\h__\h] weak
that would be great thank you
are you [\h__\h] kidding me [\h__\h]
is this for real
i'm not glitching or blogging or
anything
okay now she gotta attack in
eh
what
wait i'm i have mp potions i can't do
this right now
[Laughter]
okay i'm gonna switch real quick uh wait
that's i don't have to
[\h__\h] i can't
i can't switch with the middle of the
fight
like that
what
ah
i would have always people just left man
i i do that again
but was she stuck she didn't really look
stuck
but it's not like
it's air
it's not like she has um
what's the word
that's not her normal
it didn't feel normal
stun luck you can do that
you stagger to infinity but is that
legit or
i want to repeat that
[Laughter]
am i aiming for that now
um
[Laughter]
every exploit is legend
i
wasn't even trying to win
oh my god it's the it's the runs where
you don't even try
right
[Music]
can i get you to the wall please
or should i just be really aggressive
see i'm not sure if it was the wall
or
if i can do that anywhere
[Music]
ah she's at the wall that person keeps
okay see come let's do it come on let's
let's do it it doesn't work it doesn't
always work
oh [\h__\h] okay
although i did get her
quite far down oh [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] i can't go away
ah okay
[Music]
i did get a little bit more hope and
motivation back
from that
friends where i lost my berries
until now
hey
ah is that when she turns around mm-hmm
[Music]
hmm
are swings first
uh
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
oh
oh i don't know what's happening but i
think we're doing it again we're doing
it
we're doing something similar to it
okay it's over it's over the moment is
over
[\h__\h] what's going on what what are you
doing
[Music]
ah
that's one i use too much again yes
what interesting i feel like i can make
that happen sometimes
[Music]
i wonder if you can even do that in the
second phase
i feel like
it's very hard but
i find that very funny
okay we were trying to stay closer to
her
okay
ah [\h__\h]
that was by accident because i
dodged into it
ah okay can we do it again
can we do it again
[Music]
i want to do it again
again please i mean i mean while i
practice this ah it worked
[Music]
oh my god
may i do it may i do it melanie
holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
always need consent
to exploit
the wall hack
how about now
no
ugh
[Music]
oh
i would like to have more um
healing plots when i reach the second
phase
[Music]
if possible
oh
it's always the runs that you think it's
not them
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
may i drink my potion
i can't
[\h__\h]
i was wrong but okay
[Music]
just let me do it right once
i know no magic left
[Music]
huh
having more pledges
you're improving it's just early you
wouldn't even get into second phase yeah
i mean it's true
that do be true
but at some point i i can't improve
anymore because it will take hours and
hours and then it's just like
ah
wait if i
even wanted to do let's say because i'm
doubting i can do it at this point but
if i wanted to do the true ending do i
have to also fight the boss again
because i guess then i would just turn
on hp um baby mode because i'm not gonna
do this fight the second time
no oh okay
true landing is different
i don't have to fight here in the
training
we should just go for the true i think
at this point
okay
hold on
my hands hurt
see this is the problem now i've played
this so often that my hands hurt and
it's just gonna get so [\h__\h] tense and
weak
[Music]
um shake hands shake hands guys shake
shake heads
um let's talk a little bit about
something else how about that let's talk
about something else is there something
you guys wanted to talk about
with me something you wanted my comment
on
hmm
shaking intensifies yeah yeah
birthday raffle
i don't know i think the emails are out
for you guys to apply
for it but
i don't know
uh
how long they're gonna do it
they like
thankfully because i i can't do this
kind of [\h__\h] uh
management is taking care of that
so i don't know any
details of what's going on
popcorn oh did you guys see i don't i
guess i didn't retweet it did i i
retweeted the art but ah korean bros put
up like some kind of um specially
commissioned art
and
to be
shown at like stations in seoul
i wish i could have seen it in person
i guess it started today or yesterday
ah
until the station
the number two line i was using that
number two line so often i could have
seen it
i don't know which station it was though
isn't that several stations any korean
bros here who can tell me more about it
is it on several stations and how many
how many seconds is it shown and how
many times a day
i want some stats give me those stats
korean bros i should probably ask pong
pong seems to be the one who knows
because it seems like pong organized it
is pong here
pong street says what it is oh
circle land is a circle i've been using
mostly actually for my whole trip except
for when i come came from the airport
uh to the hotel besides that for going
anywhere else i only used the number two
subway line
you can go literally everywhere with the
number two subway line it's so useful
what the [\h__\h]
it's so good
i'm not here right now let me check you
guys say his tweet says it then
yeah it's a good silver line
ah there you go
oh oh oh there's some info here
ah 22nd until the 28th there's like a
explanation oh
oh it's so big
oh
some big screens
huh i can't read the explanation is
korean
does it say i mean how with how long i
mean for
how long in that moment it will switch
to something else right it will not
always be this until the 28th
right
samsung subway exit
oh so cool i look so cute on that ad
or is it
if it's just that one
screen maybe it is always me
hey i'll show you guys
in case
so right now
it's like in a place like this
it's pretty big but i think it look no
no there's two there's two locations
there's one that's like above some
stairs
it's the same art but it's in a
different location see it's like you go
i guess this is a place where you go
down to the tracks
that looks pretty huge
the kai
um
so cool
ah
cool
they got help
from someone who's done it before for
nabi mama
and i wonder there's a qr code on there
i wonder if people actually gonna people
who don't know me
actually gonna try to
read the qr code and
and check me out i wonder
i wonder because normally you would just
walk past it right even if you see a
cute girl
normally you wouldn't walk
like you would just ignore it probably
but maybe if you've seen her live before
and you're like oh bird what
takanashikuwa i know that girl
eh
why wha what's going on oh she'll be at
popcon oh cool let's go
i should support her
too cute to ignore
[Music]
thank you so much for doing that
um
yeah and like i don't know how many
transitions just one
is there two
two in one station
or
it's two stations and one each i'm not
sure
in seoul
subway stations
very awesome
um
[Applause]
if you saw the nun and you'd start
nerding out all the normies looking
yeah it would be nice to have stuff like
that more often in other parts of the
world too
some representation
well
need more representation
two in one station oh
my certain dominance is it
what station which one by the way
which one
wait no i missed
the
the name of the station
samsung station wait there's a station
called samsung
is that where the popcorn is
samsung station i don't remember samsung
station
the exit near pokemon ah that makes a
lot of sense
it's it's called like
the maker of my phone what a coincidence
what a coincidence how is that possible
okay
what was the current strategy trying to
get her to bug out in the wall
i don't know if it's a bug but
um
just trying to attack her as often as
possible
okay
oh she got me there
oh she got me again okay
seems like i need to get back into the
groove
[Music]
let me just practice let me practice
then
i can't it doesn't work so good for me i
wish i could combine it into one weapon
like in link's awakening what was it the
links awakening
was it
why am i thinking of a different game
where you can combine two weapons you
get into one
where's the lane's awakening
i thought so find those buttons to a
free button in your controller
but
i can't put both of them on one button
how would i do that
that would that would be amazing but how
would i do that
i don't think that's possible
try just fire rod
or some chip damage when you need to
back up from attacks yeah
yeah
using them separately
but i guess that's
wouldn't that be such a waste they say
it's so powerful and i can see that i
can see it would be powerful if it would
actually work well
can i watch someone else's boss fight
maybe that helps me if i watch someone
else fight it
tunic
um
last boss
let me watch
no commentary
i'll just gotta end it at the ending so
that i don't see that how to easily oh
how to easily defeat the aaron tunic
is there commentary to that i don't want
the people to hear it hey guys uh okay
sorry guys
let me quickly watch it this one's short
this one's 2 minutes 21.
is this person german her accent sounds
so german
uh-huh
yeah yeah
oh wait that's interesting she uses or
does she not i guess you changed it
what in every [\h__\h] screenshot she
shows the the cards she's using are
different which ones are you using girl
seven i have more than seven i think of
eight
so this person would
use the
dash away sideways um
why she uses it so often even in the
first
phase
uh-huh
oh it looks
looks pretty
easy
oh
ah
if you she says and it looks like it
really does if you keep that same flow
the whole time
like in the second phase
of
just going sideways dashing sideways
shooting that thing at her attacking her
three times dashing away and so on then
she only continues doing the same attack
that where she dashes and leaves that
trail that purple trail behind her
it continues on and on she won't use any
other attacks apparently which is nice
and all but
i don't know if i can really make that
work
that seems like i would need another
hour of practice
and even to get to the second phase man
yeah it baits an attack um
[Music]
hmm
you know even in that video
she has like um
10 no you know really low 10-5 hp left
on like in the last
um in the last fourth it's really
dangerous because she goes for the whole
fight with only mp parts
and she spams that stun continuously
okay that's one way of doing it
there's one video that says the ultimate
cheese technique 18 seconds
interesting easy way to kill the final
boss quickly
hmm
okay he uses the magic wand
not the stun
then uses berries the blueberries to
heal up
and just really spams it in the second
face
spams the normal
magic one the fire wand and the scene
actually hits a lot
but the video starts when she's already
like
only 40 percent left
she still
evades a lot but if you just spam spam
spam spam spam
you get a lot of hits
this person also has way less hp than me
and has
hp potions
and just heals themselves with berries
with the heals the the mp with the
blueberries but still has mp uh hp
potions
sounds doable yeah that sounds
more
manageable
but again here we have the the risk that
let's say i do that and i use a lot of
my mp um
berries
and then right before the end i fail
she kills me after all
and then i have no more berries left to
do it again
yeah
berries i think are purchasable maybe in
some
shop that we found but i also don't have
much money in the moment
we could try it
but if i lose once
i mean this person does it with at that
point when when the air has 30 left they
still have 18 berries i don't know with
how many berries they started out
but i also have a little bit more mp to
begin with compared to that person i
have 13 only though what are those
isn't this an mp potion too or what was
that
are there separate mp potions
oh ice bumps
oh
i never used those before
do they make do they do the same damage
and same length of ice
as uh the ice
dagger
and do they go off right away or
use them all so you get the free refills
oh those get free refills too
i do have a good amount of bombs yeah
i could i could spare some dynamite i
guess maybe
but
is that really the strength what would
the strategy be with dynamite besides
using dynamite
because then i i could then uh try to
combine
the cheese strap with spamming the magic
fire wand
with the dynamite but then nah then i
have no way of hearing the mp unless i
go for mp potions completely
but i don't trust maybe after
ah
i would want to try to switch to
um
mp potions in the second phase
maybe
but um
let me try something
let me try let me let me try something
this will be a test run
and
this one
what was that
why did i have that one on ah
bigger when did i put that one on what
the [\h__\h]
i'm trying something ah
not with the dynamite yet
[Music]
yeah i just want to spam the wand for
now
see what happens
uh
oh wait uh audio muted [\h__\h] i'm so sorry
ah [\h__\h] i can't turn it on now
if this is the random sorry the run is
without
without you
give me my stamina back
can do a lot of damage spamming this
but i think even then in the first phase
i would try to focus on using normal
swords
maybe
too safe
oh i got pretty far by doing that oh
sorry yeah that was a silent run
okay um
now there should be sound again
[Music]
first face just sword second face magic
yeah and then since i didn't use
the ice dagger now i mean i could try to
implement it or use something else
or yeah yeah could even like you know go
for the berries
and then use hp potions
if i feel like i really desperately need
hp i feel like i will i feel like i will
need it uh
but they're gonna be wasted i swear to
god this will be such a waste
um
no wait that's not the right one what am
i gonna do
which one should i do
can i get you know what i was so
confusing to me i'm gonna look up tunic
um
what do you call these
card cards
explained
we're at the end of the game i just want
to make it understandable
ability cards
uh ability cards gun okay
uh the ring that i always use is razor's
attack when low on health oh oh
wait
i don't have that one
the other ring is racist defense when
low on health oh i thought it raises it
all the time
uh
inverted ash hp becomes
mp potions anklet slight increase in
movement speed perfume do we have that
one is that the
increased stamina recovery
which one is that oh well where does
your attack while lowering defense
tincture
wait what's this guy it doesn't even
show the
the card don't know what it looks like
now we don't need that one reduces the
cost of stamina while blocking
nah don't need that enemies occasionally
drop hearts no don't need that range of
enemy detection nope damages and stunts
protects against hp drain
i wonder
if we have this mask on
if in the second phase
uh when she hits me with her sword or i
i step into her
miasma
would it protect me from
that right it would right why am i not
wearing it it doesn't help me in this
case okay folk useless
um i guess i would be
making the second face like almost
meaningless because that's a lot of like
what her second phase is
uh
retrieving health is dropped to one inch
people your sword now lights enemies on
fire
i kind of want to at least try it out
once
to see how that actually we're never
used to that
let's see how that actually turns out
and what else we have
on it
don't even
these are all really not that useful
oh perfume is that is that
um
leaf
perfume
increases stamina recovery
okay well
um
wait oh
what oh i was like why did i not get
healed oh yeah right
uh so i want to set her on fire
what was this one again
it doesn't show the right one
red picture
what's this one called
better blocking
that's shield you don't block this one
really
that's the one
the one with the straps
bracelet
okay um
what else could we use then
stamina recovery
yeah
okay and then
since i'm just testing now
um
what if i set her on ice first and then
on fire with my sword
interesting
but you know one hit and i'm done for
oh [\h__\h]
let me try it
cuz i want to see it once
it's probably like extremely powerful
but only pro gamers can use that because
you have to do a full no damage right
wait can i heal myself up
no
so sad that means though that i could
switch to mp potions
did i get my body last time [\h__\h]
is she on fire i don't see her on fire
what
isn't she supposed to be set on fire
does it just not work on her
i'm not even doing more damage or
anything
[Music]
what
that is not worth going down to one hp
hey
that would be so lame if it just doesn't
work on her it already makes it so
difficult that you have one h like no hp
so honestly what the [\h__\h] okay
so that doesn't
work we need to settle on the strategy
now
i don't know
what is this one
dagger strap is it that one magic
dagger's casting time is reduced maybe
and p spam worked
you think so
so
shall we try to
and p spam
was the berries
or first try to at least get used to it
with
inverted potions at least to get used to
it and if we feel like we really need hp
then we can still
try to
fix it
and then and then
i'll combine it with ice sometimes maybe
okay
i don't know
in the second phase
i'm now changing it's really i would
like to refrain from changing like that
ganbari mas
oh [\h__\h]
wasted
[Music]
oh beautiful beautiful beautiful
i think
sometimes breaks really
help
how many times
[Music]
ah
i'm not using it right now i guess
because i wanted to use it in the second
phase but uh
i guess that makes no sense
what would make sense is
um
starting with
huh
um
i don't know anymore i don't know what's
the right thing to do there's so many
ways of doing it but
none of it is easy everything needs you
to get used to it first
i feel like you know in this menu the
time continues normally
but when you go into this menu
she went into slow motion
but i was like
trying to find the right card in that
moment
replacing the red card with the right
card which is just
too much
i don't even know what other card i
would want
you're all [\h__\h]
so
sword first face safe magic for second
use health potions and fire one that
could be the better strategy
i will do it
like this now and i'm probably gonna
lose all my [\h__\h] berries
but okay i will fight with the sword
first
use my hp potions
but obviously try to use as little as
possible
second phase hopefully with still some
hp potions we attack and spam the magic
wand
and he will back up with the berries
that it's is the ideal situation but of
course it's not gonna work like that
of course it ain't gonna work like that
i'm not ready i'm not mentally ready
either
so
ah
whoa i did a lot of damage man for one
attack
so
oh man okay that's
kind of bad
oh that's pretty bad
ah
[Music]
it's okay just kill me at least i didn't
waste any berries kill me like you're
moving me
yeah the potion upgrades would be cool
can we like
maybe
if you guys knew any location
that i didn't check yet for um
this
[\h__\h] powder i wouldn't have enough
money ever though 1200
i feel like
if you look at the cost of it
just to get up to level five while
getting up to level six of this one only
costs 300 means that
the ones that you don't have at this
point
they're supposed to be
either
end late game or
or how to get
looking at the cost for that man
only stat upgrade left is a single hp
upgrade
no no
no it says next
i still have something left
time stop item
tunic
how to find the hourglass should i go
find look look for it
you guys think it's worth it
let me check um
i want to see somebody using it
last bus time stop
or like
hourglass
tunic find the boss cheese strap is this
guy using the
high dps stun strategy i used orange
pedal ring tincture and louder echo to
get another stun in
meow
movie
his camera blocks his
top right i can't see what items and
potions he's using
nah
this run is not so good
but it seems like he purposefully got it
got the
enemy into a special spot yeah
what
oh
he keeps his dead body
until the very end
he did the second phase in like five
hits
watch this guys i'm gonna send you the
video
because he stuns her
somehow in the second phase and it takes
five [\h__\h] hits how
what
i used orange pearl ring tincture and
louder echo to get another stun then
i mean yeah okay okay he yeah he stunned
her by using his dead body in the second
phase
hmm
no he didn't use perry
holy [\h__\h]
he even doesn't even have hp left at the
end in the second phase and he doesn't
heal once he just takes like five
seconds to kill her
literally
what wait the thing that stuns her is
is it the body or did he do something
else i think it's the body because
that's why he got the louder echo
oh
yeah yeah that's what stuns her
but even before that he's able to break
her
what
why is his damage so high
what level is his attack
he probably has the damage abilities
you mean
abilities you mean the cards
yeah he says he has a
orange peril ring is the orange
paralleling this thing ah that makes you
stronger when you have low hp and he has
one hp so obviously it makes you much
stronger i guess
oh
that's
i don't have that card
holy [\h__\h]
he gets her to transform at the wall so
he can instantly attack i mean you can
attack instantly anyway no matter where
she is i did that the whole time too
but i never was able to stun her like
that i got like three four hits in
pretty good but i was far from getting
that much damage does it raise your
attack that much
damage looked like triplets to me
oh he wanted to be weak yeah but i mean
a little bit more than one hp would have
been nice
yeah
i don't know how
if i could recreate that i would first
have to even go to look for that stupid
card
the other ones i think i have
but
what the [\h__\h]
okay
glass cannon belt what does that mean
okay manu and schneider you need to
you need to turn down your tsun tsun a
little bit okay
i was suffering for over an hour and i
was
losing focus and all that anyway
it's good to get you know my hands to
relax for a moment and my brain too
okay
and it's good to see
other people's
step strategies and all that too because
i'm like i'm confused i don't know what
to do at this point i'm trying to get
some other
ways of doing it
yeah so turn it simpson down because i
can't take it seeing comments like that
it just
really makes my mood worse okay thank
you
first time you've done it the reason why
i normally don't do that is because i
feel a little bit like it's like
cheating to not find out all these
things on your own
like looking up these these boss fights
maybe yeah is still fine if you've tried
it a few times yourselves but yourself
but i can't even speak english anymore
well i've seen several strats but i
don't see any
i don't see any hourglass
stretch
[Music]
did i watch this one
yeah that i watched that one
i don't see anyone using the hourglass
oh wait
no
but there's an hourglass location
[Music]
it's
in that um
under a ground area with all the of the
rats
no wait where is this
yeah no i think it's there
is it
no
it's different
looks like it but it's not
what
how did i never
i
i swear to god
how did i never find that
that's so easy to find
looking under the bridge it looks so
obvious that there's a secret there
oh see
what
getting the ring is faster the ring the
attack ring
ah
about that strategy
it's cool but
how about we get both
it but it's already half past 12 pm
i've been playing for six hours
monitor i just need to do something
um
okay um no you know what we're gonna
keep this to get used to it
shall we
6 30 am huh
thank you that one thank you
i like you too
i must go to bed good night
finally part three no no [\h__\h] way i'm
right here i'm right here in front of
the bus
[Music]
but don't worry i'm not suffering like
that one time when
we played skyward sword
it's not like i have a deadline either
today
um so
under the bridge which one is um
[Music]
attack up defense down
oh
that's okay he has like
two cards that uh
make his
attack higher
damn
if i can really do that much damage
that would be insane
then the first phase shouldn't be too
difficult either right
i wish i could see like if he's no
obviously because he's using those three
cards he's using the normal potions
okay um i want to go to i guess the town
ruins
or
yeah
or me asking or is like such a german
thing to do because we like to say the
word or
in german a lot to question things
it's like we use right audio gun
okay oh wait a second have we gone to
the overworld
since we're turning back into a normal
fox
cause we're not a ghost anymore
but we still see the ghosts
and there's no enemies huh the best time
to explore is now
what
uh where
uh
is the bridge it's somewhere down oh
is it here
that place right there
let's get down
[Music]
oh to get down right there yeah
how did i never walk in there before
what
in the video
there were um shooting machines here but
they're not here now cause all the
enemies are gone
so i can just laugh
actually normally here
and here
and over there too
there's um the shoot shoot shooty shoot
pew pew machines
normally oh look at that that's a
there's the sign
oh my god
wait so how do you use this they're
running out of space here
there's certainly been a second row they
don't expect you to get this many items
can i just please throw away the [\h__\h]
stick i'm not using the stick ever again
although i would like to see a stick
strat
i want to see how this works
um let me go outside unfortunately
there's no enemies to test it on
let me see how much magic it uses to
oh i'm i would be cool if i was uh fast
though
oh and you can turn it on as long as you
want so you would turn it on while
you're standing in front of her
turn on and then start blasting high
high
[Music]
but it's not like
you can see the moves coming that's true
but it drains mana and then
you're just slow too it's not like you
get like any more hits in
does it really help yeah
helpful for dodging i guess
um easy animation cancel
but cancelling her animations
so far has not really been a thing
okay where is um though
the other thing um
where is that the other card what was it
called again
what was it called
iphone core
i forgot
a orange peril ring location dark tomb
oh no
is there a video on where it is orange
pearl rain tunic location
tunic speed running tutorial orange
peril ring
wait is 8 minutes 40
the amount of time it took you to finish
the game or what in this video i'm going
to demonstrate oh sorry you hear that
okay now
wait what difficult they know there's no
enemies
so there's not so many problems as he
has
are the spikes gone too
you know the ones that come from the
ground
i would say they're not
um
not um considered enemies so
probably still there
uh he has no lamp because he's doing a
speed run but we still have the lamp so
it shouldn't be hard to find
the ring
can you just do it with the lights on
please
oh
fire so loud echo orange brown ring
there you go
watching a different tutorial now and
how to find the orange pearl ring
don't do them yeah you go to the dark
tomb
uh you walk in
go straight
straight straight straight straight
straight straight
spikes
straight straight straight straight
straight straight straight
oh
no not there what are you doing
eh
why is he hitting
those
things what oh that's why it was
what
i'll show you the video
yeah how
why did i not get that one
why did i
not get that one before
hmm okay
let's go get it so we have more options
[Music]
those are switches
uh-huh cause he just like goes
he lashes out at them but i guess
enough it does nothing because you
already got the card at that point
uh wait how do i
i would like to go
up please
oh
[\h__\h]
ah this is
i feel like i'm wasting my time
i don't know maybe i should just
go with my first few like normal strats
again i don't know
i don't know no audio oh oh [\h__\h] i still
had it
sorry
i am
am
i still kind of want to see how much
damage it does
i kind of want to see that on myself
[Music]
now i put it in my head and now i don't
know how how to get it out
so i think we have to do it
thank you guys
oh when i'm running past um
uh
somewhere where one of those remaining
maps are let me know
any any ones that are missing so we can
get it while we're doing it you know
while we're here
oh can't enter the tomb at least not
from here but hey here's a page
okay here's a page
[Music]
civilization holy cross the power to
defend if we had that one before
a terrible power rises
oh
one of them was like the bad one who
like had other ideas
cathedral the world is thrown into ruin
oh
okay
a prison and a bacon a beacon
the air air to the air
holy crust
i understand
waiting away free successor me
the golden path yeah yeah i understand
i understand
right so we would have to
uh
get
wait wait what was that while we're here
what was that with the
with this building
there was something about it
oopsie sorry
there was something about this building
in my
notes
well i can sleep with the old house i
can sleep there okay i'll check it out
um
[Music]
what am i looking for
the last page this one
what does this mean
left up down right
[Music]
i'm going crazy
yeah yeah i see the flags so like the
the fabric on the thingy and the wheels
have different
cuts
but do you want me is this like a rhythm
game where when the
this one is right under me i press that
button or
right up
but um
is it like a rebel game
when the cut the ah
is it only the lower cut
the lower
fabric not the upper one can i ignore
the upper one
it might just be the
the lower one
or the cold
it's more like a pattern
a pattern for what
for inside here
oh hi
[Music]
seek to go one path yeah that's what i'm
doing
i wasn't here again i feel good
some dungeon i had another shop maybe i
can buy something
you have something useful for me i have
no money though
oh
nope
not really
bye-bye
i need to know about the holy cross
uh
okay i'll i will
am i missing out on something cool when
i don't do this
because i'm about to finish the game
maybe some sometime today
how was my first fight with her
my first fight was good my second fight
was good too there were many good fights
but i have yet to kill her successfully
it's just a treasure just something for
true ending
so a map
because i do want to do the true ending
eventually
maybe on my private time i guess i don't
know
maybe i should just do it off screen you
then i'll tell you about it
okay i'm gonna go back to fight the
[\h__\h] now
i'm gonna go back
i mean i could probably teleport into
the
uh dart tomb right
but
i don't know
you guys said i'm wasting my time
at least i got a little break
and we could try out at least the
hourglass see if it helps at all
i wouldn't mind at least testing it on
her
oh i need to heal though uh
what was my two goal
go to location is there like an altar
close by here too
which one was this one oh yeah it is
okay you know what this is
closer
maybe
healing
why i'm worried so much about time
because i've been playing for six and a
half hours
i sleep at the old house oh [\h__\h] what
does that do do i um okay don't tell me
i guess but is it important to do it
before the last bus
no
okay
wait
i didn't think about my items but
let's go
[Music]
maybe at least with the hourglass the
whole stunning
strat
could be easier
oh wait
oh what
i'm confused
i'm so confused
she's like oh
where'd you go
oh
darting is
out
uh i'll i'll throw that item out
it's cool to have but
maybe at least in the second phase you
could because she gets really fast in
the second phase
hmm
getting hit in slo-mo looks cool
my quote
um
so
no uh
what are we going for now
this
why not
it's one of the cheese strats
although they used magic potions but
as long as i have berries no no they did
use they did these berries i guess they
did did they
oh no
hello
[Music]
good stuff
bar
oh i dodged but i dodged into it
why can't we do it can we go this way
yes yes baby oh [\h__\h] she's
ah she
she
escaped from my grasp
okay
oh oh pretend
[Music]
see a break is really good man
i was supposed to take a break
yo i even got a hit in between her combo
[Music]
in between guys
cheese strats when you're just a pro
gamer
[Music]
huh
[\h__\h]
no
[Music]
[\h__\h] i'm [\h__\h] up so bad
even though this could be the run
[Music]
oh you have no idea how hard my how hard
my beat is fasting
[Music]
oh
you could hear my heartbeat
if my
oh my oh my power left my body but that
was such a beautiful run i'm happy with
that and
i just i just was holding my breath and
but doki doki was so strong but
what is happening
okay let's enjoy this ending oh [\h__\h]
the break was good it was not a waste of
time i'm telling you now because that
was good oh this is a bad ending right
that's why the true ending is a true
ending
and the music sounds really bad
oh i'm just another one
of those foxes they're using
ah
i failed
i won the fight but i failed because
they put me in there just like all the
other foxes right so all the others that
were
all of the others are maybe heroes too
they all attempted to end this
millions and millions of them
[Music]
but no one was able to do it
and it's just
an endless cycle
but the ironic thing is the thing that
you're fighting there at the end
yeah
then what's the fight for if you win it
and winning it just means you're losing
is the fight maybe just my imagination
oh
or i'm gonna be the next one
that the next hero is gonna be fighting
the next aired the air
i would be the next heir
[Music]
oh that's it
i take her place
so you think you like ending the cycle
but you're not you're not doing it at
all you you had the wrong
the wrong object the wrong goal in mind
the wrong objective that's the word
you thought that that was the way of
ending it
but the real way of adding it is
collecting all the pages to one book
oh what yeah because that will tell you
what the real objective is
and now i'm so [\h__\h] hooked i need to
find the pages right now
oh
i'm so happy i'm done with this fight
because now we're gonna get the rest of
the [\h__\h] pages it will take longer
than an hour right right right
oh oh oh wait so i guess i mean i i
don't like the other theory that i just
started coming up with that you become
just one of those millions of boxes that
um that are turned into energy and those
those um
those
um
monoliths
i like that idea too but i guess we're
just becoming the next air i'm shaking
i'm shaking guys
[Music]
exactly how i felt after being the air
wait oh
wait i know okay
now i need to look up you keep on
running when i tap out it stops oh no it
continues but it just freezes
oh oh it's more game over
wait i mean it implies the game is over
but it also is telling you game over
missing three pages return to seek
another path that's beautiful i only
have three pages left yo we can totally
do it i'm like i'm like i'm like oh no
wow i'm i'm on a frill oh my god
which pages am i missing let me check um
we were missing like
can i calm down can i calm the [\h__\h] down
or
what and copy save and carry most items
i want to do both can i do both
what
how do i do
do i get the option of new game plus
later too
let's press retract okay okay okay let's
go let's do this
um
okay uh let me check my book
three pages they say
52 nothing comes after 52 i assume um 51
50.
okay
and one of the first pages i guess
there's more after that
there's a back cover
is that what i'm missing three four
five six
seven eight nine ten wasn't there
something missed in the beginning or did
i get that one already 13 14 was that
the the west garden
that i was missing 15 16 17 18
19 20
21 22 23 yeah i guess it was i already
got the one that one
right
twenty 41
forty okay
okay so it's 48 49 in the cover
why am i like this why am i like this
right now it was blue i'm so happy i'm
[\h__\h] finally did and all i took was a
[\h__\h] break and a little bit of this
one spamming all the other stupid
strategies [\h__\h] him [\h__\h] all these other
stupid strategies don't need anything
any any no just need gamer skill like me
just need to be skilled like me
okay wait uh 48.49
i will look the
uh location up because
we're done okay and i collected all of
these other pages
50 [\h__\h] pages
without any help
yeah so
[Music]
[Laughter]
it's unique page
48.49 hey it gives me that as a
suggestion as if a lot of people
struggle to fly those two pages
there's literally videos that give you a
page for that only show you where page
48 and 49 are
oh
22 seconds
the golden door
oh yeah
ah that door wait where was that door
where was that door there's a
combination you have to press when you
stand in front of the door
sorry i'm so hyper right now holy [\h__\h]
calm down calm down calm down
the golden path is google
mountain top yeah
um but not that mountain top it's that
mountaintop right yeah
so
go there by just going up okay
um let's teleport to this place
i watch your video
so thank you
yeah i deserve to be hype and thank you
do not
oh i said something lewd okay i'm not
gonna uh which one was the
god damn it all these [\h__\h] pages
which one
uh
that one
hi
ending because this was just a
bad [\h__\h] ending
but it really motivates you to find the
true ending
and i i mean i probably wouldn't be so
motivated if i still had like what 20
pages to find but how can you possibly
miss that many pages anyway
yo
impossible i found a lot of like chests
that are hard to find but i think the
pages are
mostly relatively easy to see to catch
i would say
um okay so oh
oh maybe we can go
um
down this way and then left over that
bridge that is supposedly there and then
ah
no maybe not
maybe i need to go
i don't know some paths you know are not
even accessible
it's kind of hard to tell but oh you can
go here
um
that was
oh that was a path oh wait
it might be right there
oh yeah yeah
not so
difficult can i go for that no really
where does
it
was that it no holy [\h__\h]
yeah okay so that path doesn't work
ah the grappling hook oh oh oh oh oh oh
oh oh oh
oh oh
uh
why are we grappling on too oh
oh that works and honestly this should
work too but okay i guess they probably
oversaw that one brief chicken but now i
i i can breathe now
i i have regained my breath i think i've
calmed down
[Music]
okay
um
so is it up left down right down left
upright
oh
cool
eh
yes i wonder what's in here
oh
secret secret gathering place
nunny
what can i
gather final treasure
and then there's a list of places that
exist but only some of them are in our
language
a location of the fairies oh okay so we
have to go there
next video oh next next part
oh wait wait one page is two pages oh i
thought we have to find one more we just
have to find a this is like a advanced
calendar
and and a christmas calendar is winter
at the advent calendar advent calendar
advanced calendar
it looks like an advanced calendar the
golden path
are these two connected
this one you might want some great paper
er
hey i have um i have the anna aniplus
collaboration
uh
um
memo the memo pad
from nino my inanes right in front of me
and it has somewhat of a grid
do i need to actually use actual pen and
paper now because i do have some good
paper here that would be perfect for
this situation and i might show you
the scribble that comes out of it but
i'm not sure why i'm scribbling
okay i have a pen i have a memo pad
oh
pen memo pad
i am hyper
okay pen licks
i was i was wondering if i get to ever
use this
because i normally don't use pen and
paper
i always make notes on my phone
screen work shouting works too
pen and paper is an astounding joy okay
get the back cover first okay okay
back cover uh which which page number is
that
or should i just write in tunic
um
last page
instruct
[Music]
but but wait no no no that would mean
that i
like automatically get the ending i have
to no i can't i have to wait
but
so this is just optional doing this
this here is just optional
if i get the last page i'm just done
oh two more
oh hi
not optional not this is required okay
so
we first have to get to the secret
gathering place
now i wonder
is this
the code to get to the secret gathering
place
where do you where do i even start what
are these numbers what do the numbers
mean mason
what do they mean
are those the pages
so it's like go first to page 12.
wait a second
what's on page 12
eh
[Music]
is it telling me to go to page 14 17 and
13 no
maybe it is telling me to go to page 14
what's on page 14
no
i'm wrong right
why is there something hidden here
[Laughter]
maybe i have to look at this sideways to
read it no
yeah yeah that thing
well what am i why am i supposed to
scribble down now
what is that
let me look at the next one
should i write those down should i write
these numbers down
uh
should i write this whole thing down so
i don't have to keep on
like um
going back to this page
the shape
yeah
yeah okay
or i just screenshot no but it's nice i
can show you my handwriting
39 miku
um
9 40
oh my god this is the real gamer life
now i'm really gaming
i'm writing something down
to have an overview
of what i'm doing
and
11 2
52 only real gamers write things down
guys
see at least i'm still trying to um
figure out the riddle on my own while i
could just look it up on google or
youtube but i'm trying okay
ah maybe this
okay but then
so there's a square
wait what
it just tells you to start from 12 right
ah is it telling me
[Music]
i'm so confused
uh
so why is that square there why is that
square there
and where do i continue do i go left to
the lego alright
uh
one two three four five one two three
four five six
copy the lines but like where would i
put them
what where what i don't
well
i don't want you guys i kind of want to
figure it out myself but i'm lost um
oh wait do do the do the blue lines have
a meaning too
oh
so am i let's say the golden square is
the numbers i put down
ah
then but how many
how many
how many do i go up three
three up free to the left
maybe three up three to the left okay
yeah
and then
two down
three to the right
okay
maybe
and what now
ah ah is that the path so i go to page
nine i don't know
doesn't make any sense
is there such a square here
h9
i don't see it
i don't see anything
[Laughter]
page 9 page 55
wait 55 i don't even have i think
i don't have 55 what about this by the
way
does this help me
what is this
what is this path on the potion huh
what is
what is all of this
does this help
does this help me
this is not related to the golden path
okay
um
[Music]
that arrow
is this is this is this the golden path
uh this is this
because
it does
look a little bit like what i drew
on
my
on my
my pen
no
wait what is this number 190
is this related to the golden path
oh that's 100 oh what the [\h__\h] bad
handwriting this fox has
what else am i missing here
what am i missing
i'm trying not to look at
things in the chat that look too much
like an answer in case you guys are
spoilering it but the same time i'm
hoping to accidentally see it
get all the pages read page 48 first
i can't [\h__\h] rate this
well okay there's in all the places
yeah but
but how are they connected with the
numbers
and the pattern i just
maybe i have to look at the big map and
and um
[Music]
if i
what
do i do i go to these places in that
order
ah wait
i know i know i know okay is it that i
go to those places in that order and i
did
the
dings
the steam garden
uh
the forks in that order
no
and that would be
that would be a nice riddle
because they were everywhere and i
always thought like maybe they have a
meaning like you at some point you have
to um
[Music]
hit them
in a certain order [\h__\h]
can i get one more hint please but not
too unto too obvious
that's another secret really though
those are the locations of the secrets
what
go back to page 12. go to page 16. okay
12 and 16.
what's on 16.
i mean i see these errors maybe these
errors mean something
okay let's look at 12 first
no one else
laughs
oh
16 why is it on 16. i see there's a path
here the golden path
ah
but where
why is it
is it on any of the of the other pages
down
left down
right up right down right up right
so if i is that the golden path if i
walk that way or the
what does this mean
is this this is related to golden path
right
49 page 49
copy each page
in the little squares
but
copy each page in the little squares
copy
what copied page in what squares
[Laughter]
wait
[Music]
uh
oh
i mean
that's
oh
[Music]
okay wait wait okay okay i'll cook it
let me um
let me make squares around my
memo
on the doodle
the squares
oh why do i do it like this just
like this okay
i'll show you i'll show you should i
show you and show you a show you're sure
that looks like [\h__\h] okay
but then one two three four five six one
two three four i have
i have one row less though i guess it
doesn't matter because it stays inside
the i don't know
so
oh
oh if i look at it like that i guess
although although like um
see where where
my sword shows here that's longer on my
side is this armor cold oh [\h__\h]
[Laughter]
okay then what about
so stupid why am i so stupid
this page
what am i copying into
but this is what i wrote down so i don't
have to look back to that page anymore
this is what i wrote down on my memo pad
i wrote the golden
squares i wrote them down
on my
on my memo pad
so
okay we have this if i
but where do i start like if i if i if i
try to draw this path for my on my memo
how do i know where i start
26 every time in seconds it is on it
runs between 5am to 1am about 120 times
whoa
wow thank you
damn good morning
inside the square with that number
ah
oh my god
how can i draw so much in that one time
i wrote my squares are [\h__\h] tiny
fifty ah wait all fifteen
what is fifteen oh there okay so
uh
down
ah
down left
yeah
in 15
i draw this whole path is what you're
saying
all the way to the bottom maybe i don't
know
and then
and
up and and then
right what the [\h__\h] am i drawing here
and then
uh
this is on 16 so on 16
i draw it kind of like
a little bit below the top right of that
square
and
then down somewhere there
and we don't see where it goes to the
right but i'm assuming it's there
and then up and then right
okay
now where do i continue i didn't see any
other paths
some paths
are gold in here
does this mean something
[Laughter]
like that and
and that papi is golden
and i guess this door is golden but
that's not that much golden stuff to
work with the sand is gold
some piece
do i have to go to the golden pieces
that are on the ground here
oh page 12.
maybe i have to go to the golden pieces
on the ground
start on page 212. uh
but i don't see
this one i already drew
but i'm i'm supposed to draw it on 12
and not on the whole
oh
i kind of drew
this on the whole
um
everything
okay so i'm only drawing it on 12.
okay
okay then it actually connects up 16.
and then it goes down and then
uh up and then right
okay
[Music]
so i connect to 16 but then
how about okay then we go to page 39 for
example
or continue from 16 okay i'm gonna go to
34. here
ah there's a golden path here
there is a golden path here
okay
so
it's up
and
don't tell me i have to walk
this whole golden [\h__\h] path
that'll be a long walk man
i'm down
do i go until the edge or not i guess
not
okay i wrote that down so let's go to
46.
ah
is it this little tiny thing when i was
scrolling for the pages i was like
no way that this is also a path
but i guess it is
and that's a weird path
uh
up
right
to the left and up and then there
so far i'm not quite seeing anything
all right now i go to page 28.
oh
[Music]
here
aha the only golden path that i see on
28 is this one
okay
i see okay i'm puzzling yeah
now go to 22.
ah that's why it looks so weird like i
need 3d glasses
wait what
where's the path though
ah
is it just like um
right down where is it
huh
[Music]
is that it ryan down
it does connect um
15 and 28 properly
oh it does
not quite look closely
there is a blue path here too but okay
yeah
look closely
i mean yeah they're kind of like
differently placed a little bit but
is it just really really slight tiny
right down left and right down right
down
that one goes left
that one
i mean a little bit but
zigzag
how much zigzag it's not really a line
either it's just squares
yellow background line
we're looking at the same thing right
are you seeing something i'm not seeing
only the yellow outline
oh ah
do you mean
right
right down
down
left
right down
that's so weird what the [\h__\h]
i don't know how to draw this on which
page are we 22
how am i supposed to draw this
so
right
how tiny is this supposed to be though
does it matter
that it has to be super exact left
down
right down okay it does connect
i can't see what i'm drawing i've made
it way too small
okay
uh
okay yeah 15 i already did i guess
so we go to 27.
okay it's a cross the holy cross
i'll just make a cross
okay
um
i can either go to 18 or 21.
let's go to 21.
that's what that means yeah yeah i knew
this had something to do with it
uh so this is 21 so it's
but it's not connected with
wait did i write 21 twice so what was
that supposed to mean
i feel like i wrote 21 twice what the
[\h__\h]
no that's 27 i guess my 27 looks like a
21.
let me check really quick
are you guys bored yet yeah it's 27.
i should just do it in a screenshot and
there's draw on top of that whatever i
committed to doing it by hand on paper
okay
uh
down
left
down right and
is it going down a little bit is this
one not connected to anything
is this really the one
i don't see anything else here okay for
now that's what it is but i don't see it
i guess it goes to the very right is it
supposed to go to the very right to the
edge
probably probably okay
and then yeah it's like a quartz
moderator
er what's good
in english
18.
is 18 just straight
where is it
am i looking at this banner or am i
looking at this thing here
oh no right here here here here it is
here
very subtle
a crossword puzzle yeah okay this is
okay to the right and
there's a cross here too though kind of
and that doesn't connect with my 21
though
it doesn't connect
also so far like whatever i'm drawing i
don't think that once i'm done i'm gonna
be seeing anything do you want to see uh
do you want to see what it looks like
right now
you will see i'm just gonna show it to
you
okay
it's terrible
it doesn't help me i think
[Music]
oh yeah oh that's already
so it's about
this size and reality
[Laughter]
uh
but okay at least like i mean i don't
know because first i drew some wrong
line on there in the beginning you can
you see that like in the top 2 4 50 to
42 which goes for those numbers
and then the bottom two
and now it's confusing me but um
should i redo it
it's almost midnight guys
i have to live with this i hope this
will be working i hope this works
i'll put it here
[Laughter]
uh
[Music]
i mix up 48 with 18 what
oh no really
and 12 pages 48.18
what
oh
i see it
but um
6 52 50 42
31 33 40 18 what
what
well
looks fine to me
okay i'm gonna redo it
i'm gonna redo it in in the description
snipping tool let's go
[Music]
at least you saw my hand writing up
until this point okay because in
snipping tool you can draw on top of it
so i'm just gonna use that but i have to
[\h__\h] redo it
at least some parts maybe i can
go by what i already did
uh let me put this over to my cintiq
drawing tablet
yeah who needs sleep at least i'm not
streaming tomorrow
tomorrow
uh
how do you zoom out and sniffing till
it's too big
oh you can't zoom
what the [\h__\h]
okay [\h__\h] you ah
[Music]
control scroll
oh
no
doesn't work in here
what was that okay like this
your show and then your show
could i not even write in
wasn't there
i know gouda does this she sometimes
draws like in obs but i don't know how
she does it
hmm oh she does it
yeah i wouldn't know so fast
i don't know i don't know okay and then
it was like
this and then this and then this
and then this and then this and this
and then this and then
this and this and i should copy
someone's homework at this point what
the [\h__\h] why am i doing this
and then this and then this is
and these continues peacefully
and this is does this need to be very
exact tell me this one thing does it
need to be super exact
[Music]
yes
no okay good okay okay thank god
oh
i can't see this one very well oh no i
think i'm good
left and up and right
now that one's kind of wrong
can i undo
no i can't
ah i can't okay
and this it is
[Music]
and then left over to 15 i'm at 15 now
down
[Music]
left
and then up on the edge and then
right
i still know what i'm doing with all
this afterwards i hope it will come to
me clearly
but
um
wait but you guys said i messed
something up
okay you know i will redo it from this
point until 15 it was hopefully fine
so
let's look at uh let's look at 27.
it's just a cross okay
27 is here and it's just across
right
i hope
and then 48
48 48 48
48 was wrong
should be 18
what
well now i'm working with the screenshot
what do you
mean top left is 48 right
which is here
and then the golden path for 48 is just
this
i did 18 instead okay
okay okay yeah i don't remember drawing
this one in that's right
okay now it makes more sense because now
it connects okay
why did i do 18 cause it looked like a
one to me okay
uh
okay maybe not all the way to the edge
i'm not sure
uh-huh
okay that's roughly fine hopefully
uh
paige
it's so cute how they put all of this
they sneaked it in there
sneaky developer
ah i kind of did that one
not so well
i'm redoing 48 by memory i hope it was
correct okay and then like this
up a little
no down a little
down a little right a little
up a bunch
right a little down a bunch
all the way to the bottom
i hope that
this one is fine
okay
next is
21.
i still have a lot of numbers to do
holy [\h__\h] okay at 21.
didn't i
oh yeah i already tried doing 21.
now um it does
doesn't connect with the cross but right
but it connects with 11 at least
[Music]
okay
i'm gaming
this is
the
this is literally me right now
and now
we go to
uh
four
page number four
uh
here
huh
i don't see anything golden
look closer
i mean that is that looks green to me
and it's just a couple straight ah
okay
okay scribbling scribbling
all right
up
right down right mm-hmm
um
50.
you say it goes all the way up to two
oh you mean there's two path it doesn't
it's not like um connected
it you would say there's two back two
paths going up to two
i guess so
i thought it was just like you know
okay i'll draw it like that um
so it does two paths to two and one to
fifty
right
top is cut off okay we have two l's oh
and page
two by the way here's a golden path two
huh kind of but maybe not
page two
oh i have no page one this is page two
oh okay then the two they make sense
yeah yeah okay
although
i'm even more confused now that this
this looks like crazy it looks crazy
okay um 50 it is
oh god
i'm dying
i'm dying guys
uh-huh
that is
hard to tell but okay i'll try to
recreate that
all right and all the way up to six
right and then
uh
two paths leading to 42 right
okay
i hope so
um
let's go to six then
oh my god this takes ages
six
i need to take a fruit candy at this
point holy [\h__\h]
oh sorry guys
i know you don't want to hear it
um
this will be worth it hopefully
my personal satisfaction
up
but how far this looks like it's staying
pretty low
um
i i really hope it doesn't need to be
like super
accurate
um
lift it up
ah there
i was looking at these things but okay
there's um oops
it's here
and this path
um
oh wait is it it's it's just this square
is it
not the long line
that leads out of it
or is it
it's kind of weird because my line
starts very low coming from six
okay i'll redraw it
maybe here that's still kind of low
the longer yarn too
oh
okay i'll go pretty long until the edge
now make a make a square
and then i go left and then but that one
is not so long when i go down it's not
so long should i be in the middle
the notch is important okay
you know if my memo doesn't work out i'm
gonna look at someone else's homework
but at least i tried okay i can say i at
least tried okay
yeah i know i'm streaming longer than
usual sorry
is that supposed to be a path
you're [\h__\h] kidding me no
and what else could it be
is it the golden blurry color in the
back
or is it that but all other plants don't
look like this
but how can i tell what
what the path is in the background now
there must be something else
it
is it connected is it a little bit down
a bunch to the left a little bit down a
bunch to the right and a little bit down
and that one is a stretch you know
i just
ah all the way to the left so it
connects with 50 huh and then
outside of 50 you go back to 42
go quite a bit into the middle and then
down maybe
oh they're not connected oh
but what about the two paths leading out
of 50
no i mean they're connected to 50 right
it does connect okay good good good okay
okay let's see
now to 33
[Laughter]
nothing really
everybody who's
here
waiting for me to finish this is a
genius i love you guys is this the
golden path here
just like the
the still like the cut out
of
you know
you know what i mean
i don't see anything else
i must be dead
okay
down
right
all the way to the left and add like a
little bit of a
uh line
to cut through it okay
thirty-one
uh please tell me it's that and not this
whole thing
must be that
uh okay
i see it
that's not so pretty let me redo that
[Music]
that's all
right okay have a good eye for those
really and now i see everything and i
don't know what i'm looking for
uh 40
40.
are the coffee stains to golden path how
they're circles
what
now this there must be something else
it's not the coffee stains right
how would i draw that
circles
two men okay
there must be something else i see it
wait oopsie i see it i say that is this
here
no
this is such a like
this riddle makes me feel really like
the developer
put so much love in into this game
and so much heart and soul
like even for the developer
this must have been
pain and fun to create
are you
i did 18 somewhere else right that's why
it's familiar to me okay
it's this one
yeah it's a well-made puzzle and i've
never noticed beforehand i thought some
things were weird maybe like the coffee
stains but the coffee stains don't mean
anything after all
or they mean that
the developer was very tired while doing
while creating this game all alone
that's why i freaking loved it i love it
too not really like for this puzzle but
for generally for being a great game
and that hasn't changed until the very
end i mean last episode was a little bit
painful but
i still love it it won't change anything
ah golden path is this
uh-huh okay
uh uh 44. uh-huh
yeah i guess that that's true
oh that was kind of hmm
okay oh that's how it works there's um
another like um
a line going through
weirdly right
yeah across
it goes off
using all my brain cells today
49 is just this line up here huh
um
but very up high at the top
ah now 12
and 44 will be connected by this
on my side it's not quite on the same
height but let me fix this
[Music]
okay
and then oh we're almost done we meet at
55 55 is the middle
uh that's where the the 55 pages that we
don't have right we don't have 55. okay
nine
is it that
did what no that makes no sense it
wouldn't meet anywhere
there must be
something else
this is tricky
uh
huh
maybe
but it has to be something that comes
from the bottom
comes from the bottom upwards
oh
[Music]
what
i mean this is kind of sass too but
[Music]
look at the photo
what
um
[Music]
my
supposed
to no i'm i have to draw something
that's golden right
hint it's not in the page
oh
ah do i have to go to my safe data
you'll have to go out of this menu when
this gameplay like go out of the game
into the menu
wait does it want me to delete
wants me to do data removal and delete
my play
don't do okay
hey if people play do this do this alone
and try it
dude dude
okay so i go to my safe data and load
the first one
maybe
i will i will do that
uh
how do i get out of the game there
what should i
do i have to say first like i didn't do
anything right that i need to save
yeah
i think i think
i'm gonna go to the title screen now
i only have one file they had free
what does that mean
and i can't what okay
[Music]
no i just went back because i thought i
did something wrong
oh
eight eight eight eight eight eight
i got everything maxed now
i got a [\h__\h] ton of money and at 999 so
yeah that seems legit
maximum power but it says i have
pages
let's see what this means
but i still don't know what to draw into
9 and 55 am i just gonna freestyle that
oh god can i [\h__\h] this up let's go um do
i have to fight things i hope not
hey i'm scared do you have to fight
things i have all weapons
okay we're going
up
wait the path is already there
oops [\h__\h] that was by accident
am i is it okay to go off of the path
as
as long as i
go back onto it
uh
wait this is not correct
don't shouldn't i be going down
this is not correct
oh i'm drawing this right now
am i drawing this onto nine
what the
up but how big am i supposed to make it
i don't know in what scale i'm doing it
but okay
uh up left and then
uh up right i think
why am i white now i was black before
up left
up
music is weird
but it's not necessarily negative music
okay and then
right
across
i don't know how far to go but i guess
i'm just gonna make it in the middle
and then does it go outside of the
screen
it doesn't go outside of the screen it
goes
it goes up
[Music]
okay
yeah i should make a separate note just
with this but
how much longer is this
it's so
complex uh it's ending okay okay okay
now well it looks kind of weird but okay
oh and that's 55
is it just straight
straight straight straight left
up
but isn't this nine again
it repeats yeah it repeats what am i
supposed to
do
why does it repeat
why does it rip ah
does it have something to do with these
things
ah just go back to the other side oh
okay okay
that's a weird save file
[Music]
okay
and now go back to my normal save file
oh man can we not copy all of this
what are the
if they gave me all of that just to
follow the path what do the numbers mean
then mason
why did they give me that much money
does it have a meaning
why did i give me exactly this amount of
money five zero nine free for does that
have a meaning
[Laughter]
um oh
why am i here
do i have to follow the path now
this way
do i go for the darkness
wait wouldn't that be [\h__\h] weird
[Laughter]
wouldn't i die
no okay
uh
am i going to the mountaintop now
that one
uh big door in the mountain in the snow
that's just where i left the game okay
okay
okay okay that's like the only place
pretty much that still has no
like
proper explanation for why it exists
that big-ass door i still need pages
oh yeah but
where is it
the bed
bed
one and fifty okay well we'll sleep once
in the bed apparently does that give me
a peach
huh
are we going for we already did the
regulating we're going for the training
now what do you think we're working on
this whole time
um
you finished the manual puzzle
yeah
oh
well i mean
the only number i'm missing is supposed
to be five i thought we didn't have page
we don't have page 55.
have you filled all the squares no
i don't i don't have 55 but besides that
i think i uh
[Music]
oh i filled every square
besides 55.
well um
well i go
i'll go
i'll go sleep at my house
i guess
is that my house yeah
only page 4080 will get paid for okay
wait a second
let me try sleeping oh was that possible
before because i never checked that
option
wait give me that give me give me that
wait that was here all the time wasn't
it all these things were here all the
time
i want that oh wait there's a page here
this place right there it fell down what
no
no well that's just a bed with a weird
shadow
i'm going crazy
what did i do
what did me helping do what me sleeping
help
[Laughter]
the enemies are back oh [\h__\h] no
[Music]
why'd you tell me
to sleep
this makes everything more [\h__\h]
now i kinda wanna reload myself
this won't help me
but there's no corrupt oh
oh
i can sleep oh it switches i can do it
again
wait a second
is that
on the curtain
um
but is that for page 55
wait what's on page 548
you guys said to check 48.
i don't know what that tells me
[Laughter]
i don't know what that's telling me
get up half there and find out
55 is just a straight line i figured
this much yeah
um
but where am i supposed to draw
this
why am i supposed to draw this
i'm just going to draw it down on my on
my inner knees
thingy
up
add a nudge
right down
and a nudge
right
up
and a notch right down add two nudges
okay
ah
eh
doing that on the d-pad doesn't work i
don't know how to do the nudges i guess
how would you do the nudges do you press
both um
i'm testing it
i don't know what timing
notch means double input oh what how am
i supposed to know that
so up up
right down down right
up up
right
down
down down
i pushed it nothing happened
maybe i need to go outside first because
i already pressed some buttons
and it didn't work
faster
up up right down down right up up right
down down
[Music]
is it trophy
uh-huh no this one's golden
i'm free it's a berry
oh
you're welcome where are you going
where are you going i got an achievement
that said i'm free
where is the land of the pools
[Music]
or the land of the promos
how do i get to the secret gathering
place i still don't really get it
or is is the golden path leading me to
the secret gathering place
use that pattern
try out the 48
in
ah inside or anywhere
up left up right down right
oh my god it works
oh i followed them ah are they showing
me where to go
um
let me write this down
up
left
[Music]
yeah i'm following them okay okay
up left
up
right down right okay
up left up
shut [\h__\h]
there you go where are you going
and they're going different ways
okay you know what do i need do i need
it to be uncorrupted for this
because the enemies annoy me
i don't want to do it with them
um
i don't need it
okay good
okay okay
nighttime
it was like kind of that way
if i go here
[Music]
yeah that place is us
what
i can't go over there
what do you mean what do you mean
fairies what does that mean i'll do it
again
you should stay here
baby i pray
oh bomb okay
i was just gonna pray
uh
thank god i have a lot of dynamite still
because i didn't use it all up at the
bosses oh [\h__\h] oh it worked
[Music]
oh yes
the music
why is the music
what
it stopped
now it's turning again
pray to the cube
no there's a riddle too huh
god damn it
it got faster there
[Music]
yeah i'm guessing like the faster the
hotter like hot and cold
oh
no it stops why does it stop
why does it stop
it got like really fast
okay wait for it to stop
i'll write it down
write it down
i think
is it
right
but how often
like several times
up or is it just right up and then
right again
several times
when does it end when it stops again
is it going right or is it turning i
don't know
thank you
right right right right up up up right
right right up up up right right up up
right up
oh [\h__\h] i wasn't in the game was i
no i am
yeah is this wrong what you wrote mr
agent
right right right up up up up right
right right rub up up right right up up
right up i guess i missed one no
it doesn't work
right for up
i feel like i'm doing exactly that
how does a normal person self i mean
[Music]
wait where did that hint go
let's just write out loud
right right right right
up up up up right right right up up up
right right up up right up
oh i did that
[\h__\h] weird cute man
afraid another one cool
can you lead me to your
home
what now do i follow them again
would i go somewhere else
wait for me oh oh it's right there
um
oh well i'll ask again
just in case
nope they stay here
do i put a bump here
wait they go kind of far let me throw it
like this
no
maybe below like here
it doesn't look like something you could
well blow up
but the tiles
yo
i guess they
yeah
is it oh wait
no
um
even if they are in order
what am i supposed to do with that order
am i supposed to like um
pray in front of it or
use the combination in front of it
that's a nine that's probably if that's
anything then that's a nine
that's
that's a
what what is that
uh
i don't know what that is
i can't see numbers in that or is it is
it the number of tiles it's not supposed
to look like a number okay well then
it's
oh one two three four five no don't
focus on that one two three four
five six seven eight nine
[Music]
those are both five
huh
am i stupid
uh
what
it's a two and a three and a five
oh yeah you mean um
so
this one would be a one two three four
five six seven
a one a four
for example
and then this one it's hard to see but
either one two three four five
or six if there's one hidden but how
would you know
oh
yeah one two three four maybe it's
why would they hide it
would suck
you guys say it's a six
um
down left left foot one two three why
what
down
why would that
what why
count up from one
what
one
two three
four and then ah five six
seven
uh-huh
uh okay okay again now
down
left
uh down
up right down okay i just have to do it
faster i guess
down left left down
up
okay
another one
it went down to the sky
um
here
you stupid fairies man
such a pain in the ass
i'm coming down
if i have to
do i have to
i should probably
blowing it up with a bomb voice easier
can we do that again
what is this
[Music]
and then you're near there
oh i can go there oh but not really
just walk in
huh well
and now that's just this place again
we already went there before
oh wait the pattern
right up left up right up breath left up
up right down left down right down left
downward
ah
oh hey i can see myself with the crown
thanks to the crown
although i can see myself in general
cool
um
okay
oh
so this game has fairies too
oh wait am i supposed to
write this down
why is this one hard
i don't see any options of paths
i have to write this down
i know
okay
so it starts from here i assume
maybe you guys can write it down you go
can you guys write it down for me left
left
up
right right
i hope
up
are you writing this down
only one left
is everything just one
how would i know how would i know how
the [\h__\h] would i know turning a kernel
corner doesn't count okay
okay left we start again
up
right
down
up
right
there with a notch
left oh yeah there's a notch here notch
so left left
left left
is it left left left left or is it left
left
i guess it's left left left left right
yeah
up
and
uh right and then up
okay and here now i need the code right
you guys probably just copy pasted it
from google right now everybody who's
spamming it now
or did you did you or are you waiting to
enter it until now
okay use it
left up right up right down right up
right up left left left up right up
i use the one from kyle carrot
specifically i wonder if the other ones
are different
what don't tell me there's another fairy
in here that won't lead me nowhere
i want to be teleported to your guys's
home immediately
i'll [\h__\h] you
i have to go down again
that little sucker
oh i have to do six more of these
[\h__\h] are you [\h__\h] kidding me
i'm not gonna cook at 2 a.m okay i was
gonna cook today if i end at a good time
which i was hoping for
but i didn't even read super chats and
it's
20 minutes past midnight
good that i have another frozen pizza in
my uh
fridge
hallelujah
and we're gonna suffer together until
the end right we it will create a
special bond it's nice
where are you going
here okay cool
uh-huh do the flowers have a meaning
i guess the flowers have a meaning or
just a pink flower
well i pray here
can i just make it easy by praying
oh man
the flowers
um
where i started maybe at the pink one i
don't know
what how am i
the pink one is obviously the start
what one do i do i guess it's input
again but like
i do
what do what what do i what do i what i
do
um
what
what aside from the right flow i don't
trace one connects in a straight line
ah
so up
all right ah
hi hi hi hi hi okay okay um
can i do it just by looking at it
up right down right down left right left
down right up yay
okay i'm getting a lot of help from you
guys but i'm still also trying to use my
brain you know i'm trying
does any of this lead me to the cover
page or am i just doing this for extra
something extra
this is required okay
um
[Music]
this way
wait
oh here cool
[Music]
oh
i mean there's flowers there
oh i was just supposed to go here
wait have i ever been here before it's a
shelf
oh it's not a shop oh that's where i got
something before
the path here
is the input i have to do
they're reusing this location
oh my god this was so obnoxious
okay okay if i need you to write this
down again
um
up
left
down
left up
i hope
right
do i have to count like some nudges too
i hope not down
right
[Music]
up right down
left
up
did you do it guys
but was i too fast
[Music]
you sound like turkeys aren't you guys
chickens
okay
wait can i do it again restart reset
up left down left up right down right up
right down left up left up hey
okay so these [\h__\h] riddles i swear to
god
let me go there
can i zoom
you're welcome
i hate you
how many more four more oh my god
it doesn't work
i know it works
at least it's helping me by
going in an order that makes it
relatively accessible
are going here
[Music]
down
no
ah
how do i get down
go down here
and walk around there okay okay i'm here
i'm here
ah does it want me to go through here
you could find a lot of the hidden
chests
oh this groom we saw it before and they
were like what does this mean
i see a pattern on the wall
but it's moving
what the [\h__\h]
oh
what
[Laughter]
um
uh
uh-huh
where where am i supposed to start
google this one
on the circle
what circle
i only see edges
where's the circle
is that out there here
down
down right up right down oh [\h__\h] i don't
know where it continues
uh
[Music]
what
come back circle here down right
ah
oh come on
no [\h__\h] way
uh but it comes off there
[Music]
[Laughter]
can we just get this one from the wiki
yeah
down right up
right wait i see it i think i see it
oh
maybe you see it
is that one connected yeah i think i see
it
does it end there
okay then wait i can do it write it down
when it comes back
listen to me
oh we can use the hourglass ah no need
right up
right
down
left
oh maybe that was up
up right down
right
left
wrong then maybe that one where i said
right maybe that one was up okay again
down right
up right
right
down
oh maybe it's right
up
left
wait
this is kind of three-dimensional while
it's 2d i'm not sure how to interpret
this
it doesn't start with down
i said up left
left
up
or left
but how do you look at this
how do you
how do you even look at this
it started right
maybe because i'm looking at the one
that's close to the water here there you
see that the one i guess but they appear
in two locations they appear in two
locations
yeah just give me the answer
let's just google it how do you know uh
which one this is
okay miffin is this the one that you
googled me finn and thank you soon okay
that kashan you guys are fast
right up left up right down right up
right down left down right
how the [\h__\h] do you figure this one out
okay
i don't even give a [\h__\h] anymore
three more or what
two more
trial and error
okay
where are we going this time up
wait
wait for me
yeah pattern doesn't really match what
i'm saying i thought so too
um
do we just go inside here no you're
going up wait
let me go up here
[\h__\h] you
uh
there's a different path ah
[Music]
what
and the sword yeah i had since the
beginning i just normally during the
stream during my streams i don't take it
out because
it's like
uh
i mean it doesn't really make sense it
takes a place and it usually doesn't fit
the mood
where the fairies
[Music]
ah
here
the fairies are the flowers have a
meaning again
oops
no let's read this ah
oh i see
i mean we don't know which one is which
but assuming the first where do we where
do we even start reading in the system
though and which direction do we read
because i see maybe four different signs
and it could be up down right left you
know but um
where do i start from the top left and
go to the right or do i start from the
top left and go to the bottom you know
manual
is it on this last manual page
what is it
would it be here
[Music]
should i just type in this
that's the one i already did
and i didn't even need to help for it
you know my fruit is dying oh my god
oh god
eight out how the [\h__\h] has been eight
hours
i haven't done such a long stream in the
while huh
good that i scheduled a break for
tomorrow
[Music]
what am i supposed to do here
you guys are you fairies i'm sure it's
here right
uh
oh they seem pretty certain it's here
well this has to mean something
is it
hmm
how do i know which one is which
manual do you have something to tell me
please tell me
[Music]
the seeking spell is written here is
that how i found out about it how did i
find out about it
that's what i've been putting in
okay
oh
[Music]
compass at that one down here
wait
wait i'm like
i'm feeling sick at this point because
lack of food oh i still have a little
bit of the muffin
the complex let me look at that yeah i
see it i see i see i see something there
so for example
that means up
that means
wait i don't know [\h__\h] this [\h__\h]
oh
um
[Music]
i don't know
no i'm not taking a break mm-hmm
screenshotted do i not need my
um
do i not need the other thing anymore
wait is the final input what i wrote
down on my golden
advent calendar
that's ridiculous that's a lot of things
to input
that's a lot of directions to blend oh
my god
[Music]
that was [\h__\h] insane now i'm losing
my mind
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
what would the cross mean
though i wasn't a nudge that was a crush
i'm not good
[Music]
wait
it is a nudge okay
all right
why was i
hmm i'm okay i'm fine
maybe hopefully um i'll just write this
down
i'll try
new note
so
do i understand this correctly
um
that on the top is
up
let me
let me write it down
um
until where is that the sign though
and where does it end
okay i think it's just that
that's up
and then left is
and
right is really [\h__\h] complicated
going up
left
down
right is really complicated
i had a lot of different emotions during
this stream
in this stream you can see takanashiki
wawa fifty shades of chihuahua
hooray
fifty shades of kiwawa oh okay i wrote
this down
where are we going back to
ah
this
[Music]
uh okay but then i'm still
i still don't know is there a hint that
tells me in what direction i'm supposed
to read this
am i supposed to read downwards
or to the or sideways
left to right like a book okay was there
a hint that would have told me that or
okay well i'll read from top to bottom
left to right then
i'm glad
okay um
so it's
correct me if i'm wrong
um
and and write this down
it's
uh
left
right
wait that doesn't look like anything i
drew
what does it
is that
what is that is that down
maybe i forgot to write something is
that is the third one down
no the second one is right
yeah third one is down right okay
so left right down
up
uh left no
up sorry not left so
left
right down
up
down
right
uh
oh god
left
uh
it doesn't even look like what i drew
you know
um
up
right
down
uh
left
wait
where did i stop or i looked away for a
second and which row was i think in the
last row
oh
you guys are probably gonna give me a
copy-pasted answer from google from
google anyway right
um
down
right
and the last one is left
i hope so
this is actually what i just did
why am i what am i saying all of this
for then
okay
okay did i do it correctly
i hope so
i couldn't blame you i would probably do
that too
or would i all know
i would think that the phone people are
writing down what i'm saying and the
desktop people
are just googling it
left right up oh [\h__\h] i was i did it
wrong sorry sorry sorry
left right down up up down right left up
right down left down right left
[\h__\h]
now was it wrong because i put it in
wrong or because what you wrote down
what i said was wrong
hmm left right down up up down right
left up right down left up down right
left it works
and i just put it in wrong
i might have just put it in wrong
another golden chance
to snow care if he loves you i love you
guys too thank you for staying for so
long
where are we going next let's go it's so
much fun let's go
ah this way
already
probably probably in here they probably
went in here
oh did they
do you have a ferry to sell
ah he has nothing to sell
i'm gonna check if this is
correct
oh it wasn't correct
it wasn't never mind
wrong place
wrong time
anyway
i can't go there wait but i see okay
you're stopping there
okay ah flowers again
okay well then if it's the same as
previously i know i can do it
up left down left
oh [\h__\h] one more time
it's a bit more complicated than the
other one
wait what
if i go up and left and then down left
here
and then
down and then right
then what
i guess i just go down
but then then i ignore this little
flower that makes no sense but then okay
let's say i do that i go here i go here
i go here and i go here it doesn't work
this one doesn't work
zoom out
i can't zoom out more than this
up
left down left
here
maybe i just have to go this way
[Music]
i'm fine i'm fine uh when you go down
you go to the right one
oh
i go to this one ah okay
done
ah and then down
down
okay
uh
up left down left
down left down left up right down right
right down right yeah i did it
first try
even though it's a bit complicated this
one and you have to do it fast
so think fast and look fast
are we done
i think we've done this what's the last
one
guys
[Music]
the fairies will stop [\h__\h] with me
just [\h__\h]
tell me their secret
so that i can go
to sleep
where
here exactly here right
huh
all right but back here maybe
there's some flowers here
the flowers are supposed to tell me that
i have to go through here wait
oh oh my god
what what
just watch him okay wait
and then i input that oh i'll fly i
thought this would be bigger like a
dungeon okay
i'll look at it up
right
but where does he start
down
left you kill us by accident oh you can
shoot it from here maybe huh wait now he
went diagonal
i guess he starts
uh
here
okay down
some music started
down
right um am i wait am i supposed to
count
the
the checker thingy [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] i don't know when he goes through
two checkered fingers is it down down
i don't have to collect ferrous anymore
yeah yeah i just have to do the uh input
again right
only if he stops
okay okay okay
okay the place to restart
or is that restart or i'll kill you i'll
shoot you when i'm done with this
eh you only need ten
yeah but how do i i thought it would
lead me to
i don't know i'm just trying to do what
the fairies are telling me to do
this is the eleventh one i don't need
this one
but i thought they would eventually just
lead me to the final um
destination
i have nine i need 10.
okay let's just do it ah shaq burger i
will trust you
i believe this
down down right up right down left down
right up right down down
thank you i love you
you're amazing
let's just assume this is my tenth one
but how are they gonna tell me where to
go though like
and do the fairies give me extra lives
but like now i don't need it anymore
no one needs this now
[Music]
extra lives now could have used them
earlier what the [\h__\h]
okay
48 you save look at page 48 you think my
brain oh
it checks off the ones that we already
got
which is now
all the ones
almost all the ones that
are not written in english
okay but where is this where's the
secret gathering place
this doesn't tell me where it is
hey what are you telling me that would
have what would uh would this have told
me that the manual wouldn't have told me
where it is
i want to check for myself
and how do you know 10 is enough
[Music]
good question
a little picture of it
waterfall picture somewhere
my throat is dying now
i'm gonna talk like this now
hello everybody
this is
this is it
i'm in a good mood you know
in a really good mood
i can't talk anymore
it's a loaf
no [\h__\h] hour
where's this picture i need to see it
otherwise i can't go
because it's as if i didn't know
don't say it
don't [\h__\h]
i'm not whispering
i'm just talking
with low effort
okay
where
where i die
i can't breathe anymore
oh what the hell man
that's interesting here by the way
is that a hint to a secret
you see that everyone
did we ever go there
did i ever go there
did i miss it
please tell me i didn't miss it
i got it cool
that was the burn cool
cool
awesome
red
i don't see a [\h__\h] waterfall
no i don't see what
i don't say what
what the [\h__\h]
or maybe maybe
this
yeah i don't know have i ever been in
this would it have been possible for me
to watch it before like would it would
it
wasn't empty at that time maybe
maybe i even was there before
and it was just empty because there were
no fairies because i didn't send them
there i've been there before
ah
well maybe it's that waterfall no we
just came from there right
yeah yeah
oh yeah
not that one okay i'll check out another
one um there's another one there's
another one close by
relatively i think if i'm if my
orientation doesn't fool me
maybe oh maybe i'm wrong uh
oh golden door hello
oh yeah
if i go there
can i go inside
no maybe from the lower level
oh mama mia
mama me
yes beloved i can tell
i was thinking it might just be below
[Music]
i hope this is the right way
you know how i used to have really bad
orientation issues on this overworld now
it feels a little bit more like my hood
this is where i grew up
what
how come i can't go there with my
that's the same height
yeah okay
oh this looks
[\h__\h]
oh
[Music]
now this room also has meaning and
i guess that
uh map only shows up when you have ten
which will tell you if you after each
time of getting the ferry you uh come by
here you will see that after this ham
fairy ferry
the map is here so you can stop getting
them but why would you get 20 then
is there like an extra reward
taking it
oh dear lord
[Music]
oh my god
for additional support and secrets
what
good
oh what what
i don't know
i don't know what this means
oh i don't know what does any of this
mean
[Music]
i'm sure there's like a message from the
developer written on there that i can't
[\h__\h] read
what now
is this how to read the language
and this is
um
on those pages there's some extra stuff
you just needed to paint everything on
it is for funsies
oh i i don't need this i can just go to
the golden big door and input my
um
my whole [\h__\h] paragraph of directions
another not the golden door i guess the
mountain door
my personal
do you guys know the
the scrubs episode where they put a
toilet on the roof and that one doctor
who uh who has i don't know what you
call that um illness
he's like that's that's my personal
everest
what is this a secret that i didn't find
before
oh no maybe not i think i found it
and my personal everest now
which is all too fitting
is um
that mountain door
but i mean it's fitting because it's on
the top of a mountain it just makes a
lot of sense
that that would be my everest
yeah they get like super inspired up
there
i liked that episode was funny
oh man scraps is so good just recently i
i rewatched everything
just recently although not everything i
think i
actually stopped sometime in a later
episode later season
i mean i'm still kind of re-watching it
just rewatching a lot of things at the
same time right now we're watching the
office and scrubs and
still watching taskmaster
also now
i told you guys yesterday i think that
not just because i watch the show
doesn't mean that i think it's an
amazing incredible show i just watch it
because i have nothing else sometimes
but i'm also
watching
fresh of the boat
i used to watch the
first season at some point a long time
ago
and i didn't quite like it
but then i saw recently that it had a
couple more
uh where am i going this way
it had a couple more seasons now so i'm
like okay i guess i can binge watch this
and i think
i mean there's a lot of bad acting in it
but
um
i think
it's it has its cute moments and
yeah
i i hate jessica's acting you know the
mom is this where where is the mountain
again
had jessica jessica's acting and eddie
the the main the oldest boy his acting
is [\h__\h] too but it does get a bit better
over the years because you can really
see him grow he gets really [\h__\h] huge
too like in terms of height
[Music]
wait
the mountain over there over there over
there okay
thank you estan yeah yeah yeah you're
welcome sorry oh
i didn't expect this all to take so much
time so i'll have to
uh
really think about what to do with the
super chats um
i hope it's not too much
yet
where's the mountain
here here here
fresh off the boat yeah
a lot of [\h__\h] acting i do think
surprisingly that the youngest child
has
is one of the best actors in the whole
cast
and one of the best child actors that
i've ever seen the youngest child and
the second youngest child they're both
pretty good
but it's kind of weird that there's such
a big
wait are these directions too
i'm hoping
not are they
they could be
okay so i just stand in front of here
and i i put in the whole [\h__\h] code
are you [\h__\h] kidding me
then i will
um
i will
should i should i say it first can you
guys write it down or do i just
[Music]
i put it on but what if i do a mistake i
have to start over
oh is it 100 inputs okay
you guys can probably not even write all
of that
um
down in the comments yeah okay let me
okay it's i write it down in in
in arrows uh up
you guys could probably just [\h__\h]
tell me though i should just google it i
should just go but then
but then
no
no i'm writing it down on my own up
left tell me though if it's wrong you
guys google something google it and then
when you hear me saying something wrong
spam that it's wrong okay so that i at
least know i did something wrong
so look at it while i'm i'm saying it
out loud
okay
okay listen up i'll say it slowly
up
lift
down
left
up
because it's gonna take a while
down
did i do something wrong so far
no hopefully not
uh
left
up
right
right no
uh left sorry right left so
that was just
confirming oh [\h__\h]
it's probably fine up
right
down
up
left
up it's gonna take way too [\h__\h] long
[\h__\h] strike having
no i'm fine right
up
left
down
uh
if this is wrong i'm just gonna use
something on google
but we try it ourselves first
uh up
right
up
then there's a cross that's a nudge
right
so up again
this is the [\h__\h] torture man
left
up
couldn't it have been a shorter cold huh
right
down why did it have to be so long right
down
right
i'm not even halfway through
down
[Music]
left
down
right
uh
up
right right
down
if i get this first try that will be
amazing did i say right left upside down
because i'm going right and then i'm
going up
and right
and down
[Music]
and right
and up
and
no
down sorry
down
oh doing good cool
right
up
right right
down
left
yeah
did i do something wrong
huh
input wait [\h__\h]
wait where am i
left down okay uh
right just i'm just gonna believe in
myself
down did i lose you guys
right
down
left
left double left here there's a
i notch have much space anymore am i on
my eat up head
down
right
uh
down
right
no left sorry i'm confusing directions
that's how bad this is
uh
uh what left yeah left okay and then
down there was one left and then down
and then there's right
up
right
down [\h__\h] hell
almost there
right
mm-hmm
i don't have space anymore
up i work [\h__\h] tiny and still don't
have space
right
right nudge
down down nudge again
left
up
right
left
down left
up
left
right
right now what is that supposed to be
i guess yeah okay
right right
and up
no left and up okay
that should be it
i don't know how i'm gonna put this in
correctly but let's try
[Music]
could take a few tries
i hope it was correct
let's give it a go
do you want to see my they want to see
it first
let me take a picture
[Music]
at this point i don't even care how much
longer it takes but it should be done
in the moment
[Music]
brain doesn't work anymore
this is what i'm working with
[Laughter]
all right
let's do this
the crumbs no there's no crumbs you guys
are always asking for grams shut up
okay i don't know what you're talking
about
focus
up left down left
down up right up right up left up right
down
[\h__\h] i think i made a mistake
down right up
no i'm not saying everything out loud i
was like trying to focus it quietly
the the thing is i kind of get lost in
um which row i am a little bit um i hope
i i'm on the right row but okay let's do
it again
[Music]
can't blink oh my god
[\h__\h] which row
[\h__\h]
i feel like i skipped a row
oh god
what the [\h__\h]
i have to be fast
it
no i feel like i i repeated the wrong
[\h__\h] i was like in the second to last
row but i've repeated the row
yo the roads are really hard to
uh
[\h__\h]
okay almost there one more just a real
boss fight
concentration
okay i'm starting up
uh
oh god
[Laughter]
[Music]
i guess i
that wasn't in the set in the last
second to last row
um
there's one
on the very left the first one that i
guess i crossed out
because i made a mistake but i read it
as up
so i guess i had one extra that wasn't
supposed to be there
okay i'm actually gonna
no no i want you guys to see what
happens right away when something
happens
that's um i think i cross it out i'm not
supposed to put that in that's nothing
the last you're missing an up before
left up
not before
really
really really did you check you checked
my homework you corrected my homework
really okay so it's the last three r
well the last four are
right up lift up
right up left up
was that in
okay
okay here we go again
another try
i think i
if i didn't have that extra one i
probably had it
okay i'm starting
[\h__\h] i made a mistake some of them are
hard to read too now i don't don't know
anymore what i was intending to write
uh
what is what is the
what's that one uh in the
one two three four
five
in the fifth row
the third one
from the left is that a down
i mean how would you know right but i
think it's a down yeah it's probably
down
fifth row third one from the left
that's a dumb one
but i made one mistake i was pretty far
though
was i was way further than that okay
one more
oh man
starting in three two one go
[Music]
ah why did it not work
why didn't that work
why did that work
did i put something in wrong or did i
write down something done wrong or did i
read something wrong
did you do the extra up
yeah i did
[Music]
google tag well they can't import it put
it in for me i have to put it in myself
but
maybe if i look at a different memo
um
tuning
last
input
maybe
maybe there's some
maybe if if i look at it
differently
okay
okay um um
wait can i make like a google translator
read this out loud for me because if
they read it
uh
google
translate like a put to voice you know
three
two
one let's
go i'll add like a countdown
[Music]
but i have to tap into the game and
that's what the that's
[Music]
it's a bit too fast too can you like
make it slower
high oh yeah she goes slow when you do
it a second time
hi
[Music]
nice maybe this is too slow for the game
though
[Music]
[\h__\h] i made a mistake
is this i wanna is this too slow for the
game though
why is it fast enough
uh
speed does not matter
yeah of course it does otherwise it
wouldn't recognize like where you make
the mistake too
it's a line five ah it doesn't matter
i'm using like uh something from a guide
now
okay okay um
uh we're starting hi it's why i'm slow
start
hi
[Music]
one okay it's really [\h__\h] long they
she made like one weird break
i don't know why maybe it's because
i don't know why
okay okay
okay one more time it's
[Music]
links
oh
[Music]
oh there it is there's the ending
i wonder if you um
if you
if you um
move in between if it's um
yeah
a problem but is this kind of too slow
like sometimes she makes weird breaks
read it yourself it's better
okay
i'll try
okay okay okay go
up left down left
[\h__\h] i made a mistake
[Laughter]
up left down
left up left down lift up right up right
up left up right
down right up lift
up lift up right up left down lift up
right up up lift up right down right
down
right up right down left down right up
right right down
right up right down right
up right right down left down left
down right
down right down left left
down right down left
down right up right
down right up right right down down
left up right
up left down left up left up left up
right right up left up
ah
what what what why not what what did i
say something wrong
what
know that you must stand in front of the
mountain though but not too close oh my
[\h__\h] god
what do you mean not too close
also you must input the path code rather
quickly if you make long pause of the
clock
okay
i was too close i was standing right in
front of it apparently that's the
problem are you kidding me
oh my god
up left down left up left down left up
right up right up left up right down
right up left up left up right up left
down
left up right up up left up right down
right down right up right down lift down
right up right right down right up
right down right up right right
down left down left down right
down right
down left left down right down left down
right up right down right up right right
down down lift up right up left down
lift up left up left up right right up
lift up
[Music]
this is
[Applause]
so you can see this clean scares clearly
let's clean screen scream scream clearly
oh that was tough man
i probably got it right the time before
but i was too close what the [\h__\h]
the last paint
[Music]
what could it possibly be
that fixes this cycle
at some point did you hear i was getting
like melodical singing
[Music]
yes
thank you for playing achievement
unlocked instruction booklet
wait
are we not breaking the cycle
you're playing you've come a long way
haven't you you've probably found a lot
of secrets maybe you stumbled across the
hidden trophy room perhaps even freed
every ferry no
we hope you've had fun but there's at
least one more thing for you to do if
this is your final page you should pay a
visit to a certain sub
this could have not been my final page
to certain someone and share your wisdom
to
should i go back to that
place where killed the boss
keep this letter you never know when it
will be useful do not dispose of or eat
this document
uh-huh
really
i
we have all the pages
so but will she listen to me will she
not just fight me again
all right
let's go
through the air and break the [\h__\h]
cycle
we're not part of your [\h__\h] system
anymore
no no no no i will not be like you
i will not
walk in your footsteps
i will
not
i will take your system and i'll throw
it on the [\h__\h] ground
oh my god
let's go
oh wait
was wouldn't there have been a shorter
way typical to a golden path if i go up
to the golden teleportation thingy
similar sorry
somebody's celery
i think that one is kind of closer
say first
yeah yeah yeah
down as fast
at least i mean i'm going this way down
oh yeah what i guess oh i thought this
led somewhere else faster oh
okay
eh didn't i
get to some
thing
by going here before
no teleportation here
oh
oh it was just a hero's grave
sorry i
remembered something wrong
hello
uh really
ah
okay really
wasn't i able to go to the cathedral of
the library from here
i guess not
really really
really
[Music]
okay
it's a good workout to keep on running
up and down this stupid-ass mountain
normally i would never want to play this
long i would have ended it long ago but
uh
you know this is
unique last episode and
well especially after the first ending
i had to see the real ending
i had to
now
where am i going again oh yeah it's a
teleportation thingy where's uh how do i
get to it the fastest
oh
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
soon i'm going to start an opera after
yodeling after
oh this is always like this
i guess so
uh
i hope i i hope there's no way to dying
now because like if i die now
i'll be respawned like really far away
i don't have to fight her right you guys
said i don't have to fight her anymore
i'll just talk to can we just talk
oh
you're not gonna attack me now huh
you're just chilling here are you sure
about that
sorry oh
oh oh oh i started i started to fight oh
oh i oh
i was like you know i thought my hits
will just miss
well either way even if i go return to
my loading or if she kills me i'll
return to the same spot right
i'll be loading in in the same spot now
[Laughter]
this will just give me ending a
should i
i saved my healing at a statue once but
i don't want to mess it up do i
[Music]
what i did i healed at the statue once
that's saving
what do you mean you didn't save
is it safer to just die
okay
we kill her again
just kidding okay kill me
all right scared
yeah i did save
[Music]
you're too weak
hug it out
[Music]
this better go well now
okay so here we are yeah i saved this is
what i meant with us saved
now we have to go down the [\h__\h]
mountain again
or up up and then down
let's be more civilized this time yeah
yeah yeah
oh
yeah
i'm sorry
i'm sorry i choose no violence i swear
let's do it peacefully
let's talk it out
we both want it surely
i mean
you look like you have no weapon so i
thought you know if i
tickle you a little bit
you you it would just go for your ghost
after all
man
at least now i know that way
i know that way
i'm i'm like so used to this placement
where am i yeah yeah yeah no i know
where i'm going i know where i'm going
i'm gonna save here now in case i do the
same thing again
which i won't
i won't i i
won't not
i wonder if after this ending you get a
new game a new new game plus
where you suddenly understand what
everybody is saying
that would be cool
can we have that
so many eye openers would be there and
probably everybody like telling me very
obviously what to do
hi oh there's my body i'm just not not
gonna pick it up
because if the explosion kills you then
yeah bye
[Music]
she takes the sword but
she doesn't attack me with it
she
comes to her mind
ah oh she was about to attack me but she
looks at the booklet that i made
the manual she's like well what is this
huh
wait do you mean we've been repeating
this for so long ah
well no
we keep on repeating the same mistakes
thank you for reminding me
oh oh the realization makes me
into i don't know
a statue
no it lets me go
oh
looks like my mommy
mommy
it's my real
[Music]
mommy oh
she's starting to remind me
and we end the cycle
can we see more more of the good
aftermath
[Music]
and happy music
oh it's just chilling everywhere
together
oh
what happened to like all the like
corruption and all that like the
miasma
is it just gone
the monsters too
just by breaking the cycle once oh
jamming out jamming out
i need a bit more explanation
oh i'm making a snow angel
how did you get there
[Music]
and
wait i need i need more i need more
information
when
no can i contact the developer ask for
more background
i need more
oops i need mom
hey was more than one person who made
this
what was that info about it it was made
by one person
i mean it still looks like a fairly
small theme
oh there's people that crowdfunded it or
oh no it's just so few people in the
front
[Music]
that's something wrong oh well it's
amazing
nonetheless
eh but what happened to
[Music]
what happened what happened
i need more information
doesn't explain everything
it doesn't explain everything
the translated manuals online cool
good to know
last oh it's nine and a half hours the
last stream that was that long yeah
that's i don't know
oops
[Music]
it's so cute
this one's such a good game but i have
no voice left i don't know how to talk
i'll give you my opinion you guys know
how much i love the game
oh
you guys know it
there was definitely like a difficulty
spike
um that made it definitely closer to
what people were saying about it
being a dark souls and zelda combination
you're welcome
[Music]
but it was a challenge and it was a fun
challenge
and there was so much
love
and affection and passion put into the
creation of this game that i could feel
the end is not game over this time
[Music]
new game
do i start out with all my items
in this case oh i do
oh sick that would be so
easy holy [\h__\h]
whoa whoa
except
ah there you go now there's a mana bar
super chats um are you seriously asking
for that
it's um
almost 2 p.m
do i have to save my new game plus and
the statue
i'll just save it
like one more time
i'm probably not gonna ever play it
again but you know
no i don't have to i'm to do it though
here you go 2 am what did i say p.m
oh yes because p.m to me always feels
like you know night evening night time
it feels wrong to say a.m okay yeah
okay
holy [\h__\h] every single one of you guys
who stayed until the end
deserve a medal
mm-hmm a golden medal
oh yeah
now oh thank you for the super chats
guys thank you
i will read them
next time now we have cult of the lamb
next time so i'm just gonna make that
one into hopefully a bit shorter one or
maybe i'll even start one hour early
[Music]
on
um
and yeah tomorrow is off and remembers
only i was thinking either playing a
game or watch a movie
because we haven't watched the movie in
a while and i might just want to chillax
and then uh friday
ireland beats crafting i it's like um
pixel arts i was thinking of making
um evil like chihuahua and chickens or
also whole live members depending on how
many i can make
into
like just their faces their heads as
pixel art i'm gonna try
um
yeah you guys know iron beads you like
iron the beans and turns you can like
make it into a charm it turns into a
charm or whatever you want it to be
and no one did that before but i had
that idea already a long time ago
i ordered a new side table for
handcam streams so i don't have to use
my cat tree anymore
and i ordered a tiny baby iron and i
ordered iron beads they should arrive in
time so
it should be fine in time
yeah it's gonna be cute
maybe i'll try to recreate some sprites
if you sent me them
especially like maybe takuma
if takuma has them like previously like
dakuma made something for for that
monument the ikotoba monument i think
uh
they kind of like
sent me like a
like a
like uh you know a thing where you know
like which which blocks to put where
if i can look at it like that it would
probably be even easier to recreate it
as iron beads
but not necessary
yeah i'll see what i'll make
just
not exactly sure what i'm making but you
know
you know so anyway yeah blueprint yeah
kind of like that
yeah yeah yeah that's what i mean
basically what you would use to build
something in minecraft and like a pixel
art
anyway i'm gonna go now um amazing game
loved it so much
[Music]
took up my whole [\h__\h] day but
worth it
yeah
pretty exhausted now whatever we're so
good
yeah nine and a half hours thank you
guys for staying for so long
people who stayed the whole time you're
crazy because you probably also have
[\h__\h] to do
thank you
thank you for spending your day with me
huh
i procrastinated because of you thank
you
[Music]
i know we say
oh good night um good enough and in
german we say our financing
i'm i'm i'm gonna
i'm gonna leave it there
[Music]
what
what is
that i'm imagining comments
thank you guys
thank you for streaming at a normal time
for you're serious you're welcome i mean
now it's already late but i didn't think
it was gonna be so late
thank you tunic for being an awesome
game i'll miss you
but i also recommend you to other people
because you were a great game i love you
tunic i'm talking to you like a person
because i'm gonna marry you
i'm gonna make little tunic indie game
babies out of you
so that we have more games like you a
good game good game gg
monkey
[Music]
okay gonna cuddle with my quitocatos now
bye-bye see you on wednesday
love love love
[Music]
you