do
[Music]
come on
do
[Music]
ah where's the game where's the game
what's the block game
it's
[Music]
they stole the game
it go
where'd it go
[Music]
come back
where'd it go
[Music]
[Applause]
hello
i uh
i've been attacked i've been attacked by
a witch
her name is
smooverella
and with her cute
[Music]
she demanded
the cutlery knows and i had to give it
to her because she's so soft and such a
baby
oh yeah
i had a little nap a short nap
a quick nap a short snap in my terms
very much so
yes
um and my subscription was so
anyway
no
why do i need to say why do i need to
learn to say no to cats i don't want to
it's not like i want to
[Laughter]
no thank you no no i i don't
agree no no no no no no thank you a good
idea for other people maybe but not for
me no
this this witch she really really
deserves the cuddles because she's so
cute
and um
but the cuddle
spell makes me feel very drowsy you know
yeah we'll get we'll get there welcome
everybody to today's stream
[Music]
and
today
i originally i mean i only wrote maybe
on my schedule so i don't even feel i
don't even feel guilty about it
uh but i i was supposed to do something
else today but
oh
[Music]
um
but some things happened uh aka my
participation in
oh the cat by the way is in minecraft
right now the cat that you're hearing
my participation in the mario kart
tournament
um
in uh yes uh in the night time for me uh
it was around the time where i normally
already have fallen asleep
uh
so it was a very bad time for me
[Laughter]
uh yes i have participated and i wanted
to take oh man i'll tell you guys all
about it eventually later when we are on
our way to somewhere
um but yeah i wanted to change my plans
to something
shorter uh but then i realized hey
minecraft we haven't played it in a
while
i kind of want to play minecraft please
uh but we're not gonna play too long
okay
which ones are better
which ones did i like better
let's
take him okay
shadows
no but like really
no really
wow
light
oh it's sassy what it is it's been so
long
oh my god what the is that
who made that
what is that a pikachu what is that what
is that who made that
daddy
who made that adorable senpai it's cute
it's like a battery is that a bad wait
it is a battery
oh where's that thing that council said
that there were some girls from council
said they were building something and
asked me to
ask me if i had some uh
what was it well
some material
they wanted to build something
where is it where did they build it
probably not here huh
[Music]
um
oh man oh meow simple house no rubik's
empire house
oh
gingerbread gingerbread house yeah yeah
where did they build that because they
they uh apparently borrowed some
borrowed i mean when am i when am i ever
getting that back
let's be realistic uh but i took they
took some what was it called again uh
spencer vlog oh my god they took some
um
stuff besides the oh this is awesome
okay i want to check it out that's my
wingies
my hot wings
[Music]
i have my hot wings
oh look at my christmas hat yo that's
probably from optifine is it
no
how do i know
i need to first of all
maybe put some stuff away
you're dropping not me
[Laughter]
my chimpkins dropped an egg
uh
oh yeah uh here take this and uh
never wreck basalt never wreck for
muhammad
ah
well
here you go here
uh
oh he says
[Music]
my inventory is still very chaotic oh
wait no bgm by the way because
last time we played minecraft i was uh
finishing my
road to
the mesa biome yes yes
[Music]
hey hey hey i need to repair my
booty boots or i just take some other
ones instead yeah
[Music]
i miss this museum
foreign
[Music]
wait when you're if you're here so
easily to grab so close then i might
just want to capture you right now
wait
i need to have leashes
i have one lead here you
and the other one will follow anyway
right
while we're
while we're at it
we might just want to do that
[Music]
still there nice suit
okay
[Music]
i'm here to rescue you and you you
follow you're nice guys okay come on
come on
this way please
ruby scary
where do you want to go where you want
to stay guys
we could give one of you as a birthday
present to amen
does she have a bunch of alpacas
we're here with you we do or we
now bring you to the other ones first
oh
i'm moving so weirdly with my elytra
you following me yeah good cute
cute
okay so uh minecraft has our server has
updated to the
i think
most recent version
uh
hello
will you stay there too
because i don't want to put you in right
now i'm kind of too lazy to do that
yeah there's a new version of minecraft
the block game
blockbuster
and 1.18.1
[Music]
gingerbread house taco
and
uh i guess we already had like part of
the update already
but now we have the full one maybe
supposedly yeah we definitely have the
full one now
so uh i wanted to explore a little bit
this is a gingerbread house that's so
cute
oh cute
what is this
what is that
this is cute though is this the
gingerbread house
oh wait that looks like chocolate nice
it looks like chocolate good job
oh and that's that's the
yes quartz of course they borrowed
quartz from me
uh to make the stairs because there's
nothing else in that color that you can
make into stairs
that's that's so cute oh this looks also
like chocolate makes me want to eat
chocolate cookies right now from leibniz
oh man
whoa
they made the inside look like we have
snowmen and the fireplace yo
[Music]
pretty i like it
oh that's really nice with the carpet
oh the
lights
oh
the snowmen are living there that is so
adorable
oh sugarcane is that what you call it
right sugarcane
hawaii
the outside snowman died oh there were
outside snowman here
and that's my fart
like that's probably my quartz can i
take it back
not sure how much they took oh look at
those beautiful blocks
not sure how much they took well we
don't need quartz today so
whatever for today
i don't care
uh
what i don't want to do
is like one of the new things okay so
for the people who don't know look how
beautiful it is
oh let's get a fortune let's get a
fortune at my shrine um
so so uh for the new update uh
into the into the sky
uh 64 blocks have been added
for the bottom as well they added 64
blocks for the bottom as well and with
that they um they they replaced all of
the
uh what's it called again the the blocks
at the end where you couldn't uh uh
uh
mine through anymore they replaced all
of that with deep slate so now you can
go underneath
a bedrock yeah and then you can go
underneath now and then there will be
even more things 64. and that also
changes
um
that that completely changes
how
uh
uh the the diamonds and stuff are
distributed
among us no among the
the levels underground
and there's new caves the caves look
very different and one of the caves that
i want to find today
is the lush caves because they look so
pretty
[Music]
oh cute
okay so uh usually
at the start of every year you go to a
shrine i should probably take this uh
myself
[Music]
clap club pull up those are not looking
good huh
okay
or the people who
put their fortunes in there here let's
put these back in here and they'll now
keep wow one gets her
kiwa one gets her fortune
let's go
go
[Music]
big look in 2022
i agree with that that's the best thing
you can get at my shrine here omikuji
omikuji but
but everybody um
with that said
uh i will be doing a proper
shrine visitation stream outside of
minecraft on sunday
after the outfit reveal one day after
the new outfit very video um because
tomorrow is our outfit reveal for a new
outfit oh my god already yes i know yes
yes
and
yeah tomorrow
uh after the real and then sunday i want
to do a themed uh
uh
stream
where i go to shrine and i um
i get omikouzi my fortune and also for
other en members and i will explain to
them uh what it means because they're in
japanese from a certain
uh application from her life called
holole or her eye
i will be the mikko for the day
yes
[Music]
so okay now
uh
what we need to do guys is find
i thought i heard there's an easy
correct me if i'm wrong i heard there's
an easy way to find the lush caves you
look on the
oval world you look for an azalea tree
and if you dig down from the azalea tree
you will eventually reach
a lush cave is that true
i have done my homework it is true okay
well um
[Music]
we might want to bring oh we have a silk
touch pickaxe but we might also want to
bring a non-silk touch pickaxe
oh army boobs
i'm a happy birthday
did you guys watch your birthday stream
it's you
know
she as always
was
was the amer that
we all know
she was wonderful uh
we are gonna take with us
i don't know uh a pickaxe an extra
pickaxe
[Music]
where's my never right pickaxe i don't
see it isn't it mine
is it down here
amelia swalson
yeah she oh there it is she um
[Music]
she was dancing
in full body 3d but this time it was not
wolfy
it was like a buff version of it which
looked really really
um
charming
we're not gonna endlessly go
mining i just wanna find the cave and
then
chill for a bit
no i i i didn't think i like both girls
i
i i
but but but i'm
cute you know no matter what she looks
like i'm a cute can't help it what
should i bring guys
i don't know what should i bring
[Music]
i think i should probably bring uh an
ender chest and maybe uh
maybe one of those
get the charm nah i'm not gonna die who
do you think i am i mean it's been a
while but
hey
where did it go
where was it here yeah
[Music]
after holding my hand though right
nah
shears ah
to cut the there's some stuff that i
might want a cup of shears
okay nice nicer
uh a bed yeah okay
maybe maybe a water bucket
uh
we'll take a bucket
[Music]
might want some more food
i don't really have good food what the
hell
i'm golden carrots
[Music]
okay
can't be
need less torches ah yeah right okay
then i'll not take anymore
and i already am taking right now hi
[Music]
look at it swimming cute
you shouldn't they're they're washing
their hands they're washing their hands
oh and now now like
there will be less enemies i know about
that there will be less enemies now
i fixed this thing here supposedly
i hear enemies but they're not here
they're just underneath i guess
i mean why isn't that moving
why are you not moving
you're so far away like how am i
supposed to fix that
oh
[Music]
man hello
i don't like those zombie sounds
so loud
what is santa
you're sick
[Music]
these are the korean bros yeah yeah the
new members thank you for joining oh oh
guys we reached 1.3 million
[Laughter]
1.3 million subscribers
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
um
thank you korean bros for joining
everybody else as well but i think
recently like uh
it was mostly korean bruce
yeah thank you so much thank you for the
love and the support everybody thank you
you guys are just sweet i wanted to do a
celebration but now i i it happened so
quickly and uh
i
it just happened and
now i have
every day planned out with other things
already you know
i want to go sleep i want to go sleep
but i want to play minecraft come on
forever
okay uh right now wait no i'm ready
oh every time i do preparations in
minecraft i get so distracted and then
i'm always like did i have to bring
everything and then
turns out i didn't is there like a like
uh ender chest in
[Music]
i saw one somewhere where did i put that
energy on
yeah this is the one i wanted
and you know what else would be nice to
show up
where do i put this to eye nowhere
i know where gosh okay
what else with the stale
let's get rid of that yeah new update
exploration is what we're doing today
only a little bit though might want to
do it a bit more next week
uh
oh my god so noisy are you
oh
this is not building materials who puts
like all kinds of random stuff in here
[Music]
okay one more song
food
[Music]
fund
i want food i want food do i have some
food in here
i really don't know where where all my
stuff is
where i have what because it's been so
long
food
no
[Music]
sent me a screenshot a few days or weeks
ago
just with like a screenshot of my bee i
guess she was here again and she was
like so cute
yeah that bean got stuck there and it
will be there forever it will be there
be eternally
yeah i'm gonna take
i could take golden carrots
is that a waste no let's just take bread
okay time to go now i'm ready now i'm
ready or do you guys have any idea that
if i need something else that i forgot i
have a bed
i have bed i have weapon i have
everything
wait pickaxe pickaxe silk touch yes
sucks such thick clutch for the in the
chest
and for others shears i do have
shocker oh i forgot the shoulder i
forgot the shocker
i emptied the shulker but here it is
[Music]
okay
fill your bucket with water okay
ena as a kfp
i don't trust her chimpkin
i don't quite trust it
okay
[Music]
you shouldn't be too far away are they
only in a specific biome
not sure where to look for it so i'll
just randomly fly over
i think there were
where i saw it was a mountain but this
is always some mountains
newer chunks no but but but but isn't it
so that
it was all underneath the bedrock so the
caves are everywhere
isn't it everywhere though
i was told that
uh since it was like 64 blocks and added
underneath and on top
that i can find those caves everywhere
caves are everywhere right yes and no
you don't don't spit me
ah the tree only will show up where i
haven't been yet oof okay then
then we might want to go a little bit
further
through some new trunks
chunky chunks chunky chunks
[Music]
where do i have
gun powder
and how do i make gun powder again
where to get gun pot where'd you get
fireworks
[Music]
did you guys see fireworks extra in one
a base crypto farm
ah
but no one no one camped there i suppose
i did
no one was camping there probably
recently
uh where was it again somewhere over
there yes yes
does it even work now
hello
i come to take the offerings free
yeah
hmm
[Music]
it's not gonna get me very far
[Laughter]
tiny
uh we could go to
[Music]
some uh whatever
whatever um i'll find some if i work
somewhere
i think maybe i have some extra
[Music]
maybe down here
ppp
yeah i just wonder if there's really
that much of ppp's really worth going
there huh
oh no
why
why god why have you forsaken me
[Music]
why
i see something you say gunpowder
[Music]
can i make gun powder out of tnt
i can probably right
go baby i don't wanna go beep beep me
today
[Music]
last chance
fireworks
or gunpowder
[Music]
power from inna crony
is there such a thing as borrowing from
cronie
i have yet to find her a bunker anyway i
don't even know we would probably spend
like 40 minutes fighting her bunker
um
[Music]
there was two gunpowder that's nothing
it's nothing to gun powder and a chest
up there i don't know that's it
[Music]
yeah
my sweetie she would
never say no to me
[Music]
[Applause]
i'll take you some i'll bring you some
cool stuff from the lush caves what do
you think about that
cool stuff from the lunch caves hell
yeah oh
baby i'll take the smaller one okay
let's see how much i get out of that
bring you some souvenirs
last cave less cape let's give let's
give let's keep let's get let's keep
woop
[Music]
mmm
yes that's so much okay we're ready to
go
finally
we need to fix elijah oh
but we'll be mining stuff
won't we get uh
[Music]
we got esp from mining stuff
what if we go to phoenix and trade some
iron that repairs my my elijah right on
it it does right does it what i think it
does right if i if i take off everything
else that's mendable
yes okay that's better that's a better
idea
touched to the genius in the chat
[Music]
and then i have some more iron somewhere
oh god
or i could also upgrade this
[Music]
what else was i trading recently for
watermelons and oh maybe i could trade
some of these blocks
not sure which ones they take i forgot
[Music]
why
just take more tits
more tits
more tattoo
[Music]
iron foam
what is that
[Music]
what the
oh my god a shrimp
[Music]
what though
oh
[Music]
she went all out again didn't she
i know i know i can't jump over fences i
hate it
[Music]
oh my god
whoa what is all of that
how freaking long did that take her
oh right click the bend oh
how long did that take her
[Music]
oh my
three streams she's so
so fast i hate feeling stuff how does
she do this
wow
[Music]
yeah
is it finished no
[Music]
oh my god didn't she build something
like that like
what
didn't she built that on the japan
server i didn't realize she was billing
it on the en server
huh
[Music]
okay well uh wow
oh well that totally distracted me
i was i was going for ah i was going for
the iron i was going for the iron
rod cover
[Music]
but i don't want to waste all my
fireworks
uh i really wonder how far we should go
or how far we need to go i was thinking
of maybe going that direction i just
kind of have the feeling that
we went a lot into all the other
directions but not that much over there
i could be wrong but that's just
me personally
wait where the azalea trees before the
uh
before the update already so if not then
i can be if if not then i can be sure
that
there will be a cave underneath right
they were not there before
okay well then all we need to do is find
another entry they shouldn't be so
difficult to find because they have like
little flowers
uh little pink flowers
all over them hello
i have been gone for a while
[Music]
oh
where is the guy who wants zombie meat
i think it looks different than these
guys oh you made a baby what the hell
would you make a baby
why did you make a baby
where is the dude
where is he
eric the cleric ah
hello
[Music]
wait why am i
wait so did i do something
[Applause]
one eight one
uh
it's the only thing that i have mending
so
uh wait uh
did it did it meant
hold it in your off hand
okay
[Music]
hmm
oh yes it did the trick
task
[Music]
yeah thank you
that's all i needed really
oh maybe i can mend my
[Music]
my panic axe
may i oh it's more expensive why would
you do that to me
well why won't i run why
he knows i have
you too well okay i'll give you i'll
give you a bunch because i want to mend
my pickaxe
[Music]
why are you all going up to six
why are you betraying me like that why
they got lonely without me that is
understandable
yeah i i did abandon you i played
pokemon okay
forgive me oh wait someone did you just
uh reload
come on oh come on oh come on
oh mama mia
a tragedy this is
i'll give you
i'll give it to you anyway do i still
have tatsu
no more tatsu
you have some sand bye
bye this should be enough
we'll be fine we'll be fine
okay
we'll put the emerald somewhere here
there's probably some iron here too
okay i'm putting them here and putting
this here and doing this here
and okay which way do we go guys which
way choose
choose your own adventure
i want to go
uh
wait which which direction was that
where i wanted to go
north east right up
after the mesa
okay then we can take the train
we can take the kiwa train
[Music]
hello did you lose your animals
and yeah it's kind of although that core
block looks nice i'll give you that
okay
uh man that's really far away man oh
where did i come from again uh uh
uh where's my home
follow
[Music]
uh
uh okay okay okay okay we go for the
nether we go for the never i've seen
some of the new caves that they even
look like to never some of those new
caves
it's crazy i need some gold
i need the gold and
we are going to put my hot wings in here
is there some gold here
[Music]
golden armor
didn't expect that we're going to the
for the never
[Music]
where did i put it here
okay
[Music]
okay finally after
after 48
minutes
it only took me 48 minutes
unbelievable
how does it take me so much time every
time hello
don't kill me oh god it's so dark again
in the end
and never and never
in the nether
we shouldn't really use the shaders
that's just minecraft okay
respawn anchors what does that mean
hello
[Music]
you're not going to kill me right now oh
they have a vending machine
no no no no no that's mine no no i
should put a door there
don't tell me there's millions of you
there now
no
[Music]
okay if you guys missed it i made a
a speed
track
to
[Music]
the mesa biome look at it look at it
just look at it beautiful
it didn't even take me that long
my piano got scooty masta
is in
last time on kiwa minecraft
wrote two missus
look
yeah we're beats
here
dude
[Music]
once you
once you're a little bit off the track
then you just can't go straight anymore
oh my god oh my god oh my
okay we have a problem here we have a
problem here
ah
go straight
don't go straight
this is
[Laughter]
you wait which way is it what
it looks away now i don't know which way
it is i think it's this way
okay okay okay okay
[Music]
and here we are
we have arrived
[Music]
guys
oh this this place is very dangerous uh
always very dangerous here
no guests right no gust
no guests
remember the times when i died here
scary times okay
so we'll go past the mess up
this is an endless
obsidian farm
[Laughter]
which way was it this one
[Music]
which one was it
i was gonna build a path from here
i think
was it this way
[Music]
no
well oh
what did it say
first
no what did it say no
first stop second step last step first
uh
kyle island was was carl island the
first one
i think so
second
something with amer right uh
i'm a copper or what's the other way
around it was the other way around now
[Music]
oh i'm a copper okay
i'm a copper and then third
or last was
hair messed up
and then sponsored or so by a cafe
right
you fly oh
i can't be no
just a buy kfp
[Music]
uh ready to go
please say it's the right way yes
where's my here it is
yay
[Music]
and this place is now way less infested
with enemies
also thanks to the update
good morning
we shall
take nothing
oh there's another one here
okay so we'll fly straight from here
uh or we could also go in a different
direction
we'll go straight right should we go
straight or should we go left we could
also go left
west
uh
west west okay west why west
extend ah if i go straight yeah that
could be an extension to the rail true
true and easy an easy extension
okay let's let's go straight uh
okay from here
careful guys
careful
how far do we need to go for new chunks
how far do we need to go
we are now
there look it's so nice it looks like
honey and mustard and
and ketchup
yes
that's how far
probably just pass the missile oh
okay that's good
look out for
nice trees with pretty flowers
oh it's an ocean
well great uh whoa oh coral reef
sheep
go straight qraga go straight
oh
poory
uh
stupid biome that i don't like
although it does have nice wood
going straight
straight
[Music]
move it's right here
no
well we have the coordinates we're fine
we're fine
flowers
oh i feel like we're up so high already
oh no tree
a bit of it
okay
nina
this is new yeah it looks new
[Music]
hello
is it really rare
i hope not
[Music]
oh god what's with all the lava pools
what the hell
is it always on top of a mountain guys
oh god no no
[Music]
no there's one hey you someone
no way
oh
did anyone else see one or are you
trolling me
you better not be trolling me
are they just like singular or are they
do they come in groups
remove shield to see better
[Music]
you saw it it's singular you saw one
did i go past it again on this way
careful now
was it was it
you found a medal put below your right
body it is
how can i not see it
it must have flowers on is it down here
no
dig down
let's check each single tree
[Music]
i thought i see this in there
look at the trees i'm looking at the
trees but i don't see any flowers
where are the flowers
i should fly again
[Music]
i don't see
are you guys are you guys sure
it was
certain
this was the hole that i flew over
are here baby
no
no no no no no no
[Music]
uh
wait what the hell i can't wha
it won't it won't do the firework
it's lagging oh please don't kill me
okay let's walk a little bit
how come
[Music]
that's not one of those you guys mean
that train
doesn't have any flowers
i'm trying to be careful also all of
these don't have any flowers and they
said left
[Music]
what do you think not there it's no on
your right big hole big hole area this
is a big hole area right
or one further over there
[Music]
i wish there was a horsey here
oyster ting
[Music]
careful
not i don't think i'm blind
chet are you drunk good question
good question
are you that's trolling me
it's your makeup man
maybe here there's one is that a lush
cave because there's water down there
hey sheep
by the water
i mean just
there is is there always an azalea tree
above a lush
cave or is that just something that
comes extra of it sometimes
that doesn't look like a lush cave to me
unless you have to dive underneath
sometimes not always but commonly
[Music]
we'll just look further
we'll find it eventually
maybe go a little bit off path no no no
no
hello
i don't think you guys really
saw something
i don't believe in it
sorry guys
[Music]
oh snow that's not good right oh but the
village nice too
hello village
i have been distracted once again
hello
oh coffee you guys are
you need to go out of the door one by
one
[Music]
oh he got frozen
it's supposed to be frozen
thank you for the chuckle cup
congratulations
thank you thank you oh thank you
[Music]
i shall take this offering thank you
what is this big house oh
a cartographer oh i can empty map should
i make a map should i make a map i don't
quite understand how a map thingy works
does it work like that no
you really like that no i don't know how
it works
still still a nice wood a nice one
there's no
bad wood
right click on the map
what what
[Music]
i need to look at it first now
right click with the map on your hand
what
hold map and then right yeah okay i
didn't right click not on the table just
ah
oh maybe i shouldn't have done it here
okay now can i make it bigger
oh no that just makes it uh
it gives me a copy how do i make it
bigger use table to make it bigger
make it bigger on your teeth
wasted a map
oh good that i have some extra paper oh
it's become huge is this the maximum
that it's adding to it
oh no
huh
unknown map why is it now unknown
oh
oh oh
and we can even
do i always need to look at it first
oh
they're so confusing
[Music]
yeah b
how big can it get oh we can mark that
as a layer tree we can mark it on the
map if we find something close by
it's calculated
[Music]
oh
i keep on changing positions here
[Music]
how big no more okay that was maximum
well you know what we'll keep the other
map we can open it up somewhere else
then
can i make it bigger before
beforehand
no i can't
okay
oh oh sleepy time sleepy time sleeper
time
do you have a bed no
put my bed done
good night oh yes i mean
take the table and the paper uh
okay
although i mean is it really worth
marking it on the map because like
aren't they like everywhere anyway
probably not so hard to find right
oh well
oh well we'll do it anyway thank you
thank you for that very helpful
oh is that
is that ice uh
what is that ice biome oh a creeper
[Music]
oh but there's a cat that go
he won't come so close anyway okay okay
wait i forgot from which direction we
came
we need to go
uh south right says south white
south
as a layer tree
it won't be here right what is that
what is that
it won't be in the cold biome right
oh my god it's so cold here
okay good idea good idea
already went too far well but it's so
pretty here
oh oh yeah yeah another village
yeah that's another village
oh
hello
how peaceful
oh man i
oh i already used up so many fireworks
santa's village yeah maybe we watched
the
clouds together and the members only
stream and it was a really really nice
movie klaus house was a good movie
[Music]
there must be at least one tree on this
big ass map right
[Music]
this looks like an airplane landing
thingy
wait what is what is this
well this is blyomi
what is this
azalea root replacement
it's just an island it kind of looks sus
okay
stoney cher i never saw it before is
that new too
thank you
thank you for the red super chat
oh jungle jungle jungle tango
[Music]
what is that
is it cocoa beans is it cocoa beans is
it cocoa beans i've never seen them
before they're cocoa beans cocoa beans
[Music]
sorry i got excited
okay
[Music]
could there be an azalea tree in the
jungle
or is that impossible
the impossible call me bit me
i'm on a i'm on a streak guys i'm on a
dmc ice rink
oh this looks beautiful the e m c a
[Music]
all these trees look so nice
maybe there's a tree here i feel like
there must be a tree here
i feel like i have this feeling that
there will be a tree here
no maybe i'm wrong
[Music]
with all these trees i can't see the
forest anymore
i said in german
a bee
[Music]
my fireworks
have you guys seen one
check some deep caves yeah that cave
looked cool but like i'm on a mission
you know
are you young i shall not be distracted
well here is the mesa wait what the
what the
a mesa village
what no that's a that's not a mesa
village that's just uh let's say oh
wait i don't think i've ever seen that
before
[Music]
yo
they look cool the clothes they wear
look so cool
hello
hello you're cool
phoenix jen
oh
[Music]
i like your doors
i mean they're kind of like uh
what is that
[Music]
they're kind of like prison doors but
okay
nice nonetheless
[Music]
that is an interesting
village
but it's too close to my mess up perhaps
okay
continuing to fill out
my map
that looks
curious
[Music]
what is this what is this what is this
what is this
oh what's this
[Music]
tricia i saw that i saw that from far
away
[Music]
why is it not in the water why is it
above the water
[Music]
wouldn't it be fun to
wait air air wouldn't it be fun to
suddenly be attacked by a drowned with a
trident wouldn't that be so much fun
[Music]
i wonder where that goes to i want
ruins pretty cool i must say
oh
just a freak okay i just took a peek
it doesn't really go anywhere
it made spooky noises though
i missed this i missed exploring in
minecraft
[Music]
look how
i'm gonna get that chest
i'm gonna kill you
[Music]
ooh copper
where's the other one hello
hi
hi maybe that's the treasure that's on
the on the uh on the map
oh then
[Music]
get it
ah
what a shitty treasure
[Music]
useless
okay i'm out of here
useless destiny useless
okay
three three
three go go
[Music]
mesa
look for a tree that's that is on its
own by itself what about here this is
nice oh it's getting night
i brought my bed though i brought i did
bring my
tree on its own by itself
is it singing all
by myself
i don't wanna be
all by
myself
i'll find you
i'll find you three chun
i will find you
and then you will not be all by yourself
anymore
oh you know what i was at the lush caves
where um there's like a ton of moss
that you can mine
isn't that like until now moss was only
obtainable by traders or or by uh by
treasure
so this is like huge isn't it
what was moss useful for again though i
forgot about that
look at this cave which cave
which cave which gives you one meal cut
that looks cool
oh
so it was just special because it was so
unobtainable okay
i get it i'm running out of fireworks oh
no
at least the message train is not that
far away
i should fill out the map a bit more
[Music]
uh which way to fill out the map this
one
no
i think i'm too far
[Music]
three three three three three three
three three three three
three three three
go back
oh this is where i just came from
and wait which way is down on the map
[Music]
south
south i'm going south now
[Music]
well i mean of course okay okay i
understand okay well that that makes a
lot of sense
okay here we are
wow
[Music]
you look into some cave entrances
they're massive easy to see if it was
easy to see if a lush cave is there
really what about the one that i just
flew past by could there be one there
[Music]
is it here
careful
i'm so scared
i'm scary where are we
well we can uh
put a bed somewhere here
do you see a lush cave chase do you see
a less cave which i don't see a lush
game
[Music]
i felt like i was just falling it didn't
quite feel like gliding i didn't feel so
safe
deeper
i want to be sure before i like go
endlessly into one of these caves and
then die and then lose all my things i
would prefer to die in a certain lush
cave
what is that
grow leeching
lighting
interesting
i want to be certain
i was gliding didn't feel like i was
gliding
gave me a heart attack i felt like i was
in a roller coaster you know when the
roller coasters go down
like swoosh
gives you a heart attack
it's an arctic fox eh
i thought they
don't appear naturally
[Music]
its mouth cute come on
you're so cute
i'm not here to tame it though
this way
[Music]
tree
three
onion rings
come on somewhere
somewhere there must be an azalea tree
iggy iggy azalea
a bubble fox
uh
you guys see one
[Music]
do they even spawn in this kind of biome
are you french hens
yes okay
more common to appear in the jungle
we've been through a jungle
[Music]
i suppose
not very common in a forest
like uh snow forest
[Music]
change textures to make azalea leaves
stand out more is that
possible
[Music]
how would one do that
i wouldn't say that's cheating
i want 20 40p so i can't help
yes i need to catch the
azalea tree in 4k
where are my 4k bros i don't even stream
in 4k
[Music]
you guys have a tree
i mean if it's covered by snow it won't
be the snow biome right
most most in jungles in savannah but
don't know if that matters
little there is too
known to this day about the mysterious
azalea trees
come on usually i'm so lucky in
minecraft
what about today
[Music]
no way why is it not here
whoa cool horse
dark horse
is that what they called
sakamata
when they saw her racing she was in
group a right i was i actually i wanted
to sleep um
until my turn but then i couldn't really
sleep so i did end up watching the whole
tournament from beginning to end even
though the victory cup the winners cup
even that i watched
and um
i'm gonna run out of fireworks on my
gun
if i run out then i'm just gonna
just gonna look through caves but okay
um
[Music]
yeah i watched it all and and kuru in in
her group she was
so good i thought oh my god
holy but then when she was mixed
with the other ones in the winner's cup
she
she was uh
compared to all the other insane
insane drivers that we have
she was just uh decent then
but holy
i did not expect that
yeah and good as well i was so surprised
to see i mean i knew from her own
streams that she was good and all that
but i did not expect her to be able to
you know
um
like
oh god
uh
i want to look inside here
hi speeda
i did not expect her to
to um
have to say
uh yes she was fourth overall that's
that's insane
keep up yes i did not expect it to keep
up that much that was really impressive
really impressive
[Music]
now
these special trees
[Music]
jungle log
do i have jungle logs
[Music]
i don't think i have jungle logs at home
i wanna take some
[Music]
i'm gonna take a little bit
i can uh with uh
wait how do you plant a tree again i
have to wait until it drops something
right
until it drops like a like a seed
and let me sleep
saplings
you need saplings
drop me something drop me something
[Music]
did i have to destroy the whole
uh tree for that
i have to destroy the leaves right
uh
[Music]
whole train the whole tree
is up so high
whatever what is that is it a melon
melon
[Music]
how do you tame a parrot
i don't have a parrot yet a lot of other
people have a parrot but i don't
how do you tame a carrot
maybe the parrot can show me the tree
with seeds how many do i need will it
will it follow me
hello
parrot
hello where did it go where did it go
it's so pretty
there it is
hello you're so pretty
oh no there's a little
cave here hello oh oh it's so pretty
hello hello bird hello bird oh come on
oh cute okay i'm cute
can you take this how much you want
oh my god wait let's follow me now
oh my god it follows me will it um
will it teleport when i go too far
you gotta
i bring you more food
oh my god so cute
oh you're so cute you're so cute
oh you're so cute you don't even eat
anymore you just uh i can make you sit
like that how do i how do you make it go
to your shoulder
oh
cute oh cute
walk by him
okay walk into it
[Music]
so even if we don't find a lush cave i'm
happy because now i have a parrot yay
yay
ah so cute
okay okay oh you're coming with me right
now
are you with me
wait
shut the light
oh
[Music]
oh man
anyway let's talk a bit more about the
about the tournament i guess
yes so i have partaken in this
tournament
mario kart tournament i i remember like
last year
uh
when it was happening was such a huge
event but they only had the japanese
members and i think the first gen of id
back then
[Music]
and
i was like oh this just looks so
exciting everybody is so hyped up about
it
oh it would be nice if like yeah one day
maybe i can participate too
and here we are i did but it was very
painful
i tried to sleep as long as possible
before the tournament but i just
couldn't i just couldn't when you wanna
sleep more than that's when you can yeah
i was too excited and i think i was too
nervous effort no no no
no i'm not
probably very close to me you gotta say
air fireworks because i'm running out of
fireworks for god's sake
um
oh isn't this where we first where you
guys said that you you see one
yeah this is it
where is it where do you see one
where do you see one
[Music]
meow
where is my parrot on it
what
huh
why is my parrot not here
[Music]
and what the hell man check your
shoulder it's not here
uh
it's not here why did it not just go on
my shoulder okay whatever i don't care
[Laughter]
[Music]
anyway
uh yes once again back to the topic
[Music]
um
yeah yeah i couldn't sleep was too
excited i even was dreaming of mark hart
before tournament end and when i was
sleeping after the tournament i also
dreamt of mario
kart oh man someone saved me i will
never get mario kart out of my head
anymore
never ever never i can never escape from
it
i did practice so much before the
tournament two i was like watching the
tournament and i was watching um his
birthday stream and everything and on
the side i was
uh practicing
um i was practicing with the time thingy
with the ghost there
and
i was practicing online with you guys
and then i was practicing online with
random people
oh god um
treasure
hopkins ah
golden home ending
it's crap this is just crap
i'll take the
although the golden block is in a weird
awkward position
and take that sand
pro minecraft player
at your service guys
that's your service
okay and now
[Music]
i can't find that
you know what the map i'll just go
further on south or somewhere else where
i came from
on this map i came from like north right
because i went all the way south
please go back home yeah i need
fireworks
[Music]
lucion i'm not gonna go back home i
wanna find a stupid cave
[Music]
i will find a tree
the problem is there's too much snow
around here as well
should have kept the fortune stick
maybe
[Music]
ah
so anyway
i think i think i was um
i had two problems during the tournament
problem okay no wait i had three
problems
problem number one which wasn't that bad
at the point of
the the group d tournament it was not so
bad yet it was worse during the zackle
club but my my first problem was
um
that i was definitely lacking sleep
because i couldn't nap as much as i
wanted to
and uh
yeah uh by the time of the jackal height
i was really not feeling well i did not
want to be part of the tackle high
i had to stay up so much longer and uh
yeah it
i felt really
weird i was trying to keep electro ah oh
i was trying to keep myself
awake with a monster energy drink but
yeah
if only you were an azalea tree
okay i'm going back for now
i told you guys
find the cave look for moss you can bone
mill the moss for another layer tree
uh-huh
wow
i will go back once retreat for once
[Music]
more god damn it
i have failed miserably
i failed miserably so the other problem
was besides me being tired
um
that
group d
was also not
not uh
how to say a force to be
reckoned with
was not
that weak there were some strong players
in there and
we also were lacking
one
member
shion senpai who
couldn't participate
so that automatically means there's
higher chances
of me
uh
getting into the tackle high right and
and having even more stronger
opponents although i'm not sure how
strong she on senpai would have been
oh this looks so nice at night
get it
wow
where is
my
audit
where
is where's the mess of biome
oh here
that's a sheep
wow big sheep did i check that one out
okay now we just need to find our base
guys
uh
what why is it just a little trunk
maybe
you think there could be something there
yeah
oh the village the village
[Music]
uh
sorry brain empty go west
go west i'm going west
but there's no missile i don't know
where the hell is the missile why is it
just so tiny
what
[Music]
shouldn't it be this
way yeah yeah who said west
what's that west
whoa
whoa whoa what's with this tiny mess of
my oh man
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
[Music]
out
uh
hi chimpkins protect me cappy
there's a light source over there would
it mean that the enemies would not come
there yeah
is there an enemy here
no
for the meantime boat yep uh i guess so
good morning
let's make a boat
i guess
let's make
a boat
but i want to look
i want to look for a train
i don't want to go back
uh wait shouldn't is there gun powder in
the in the in the mines in the mesa
[Music]
where's that did they have gun powder
i want to explore wow
you know what i'll go by foot yeah how
do you
maybe i can tame a donkey but i can't
sit on it without a saddle can i
go inside the caves okay
i was scared you know
[Music]
okay
well what is our best bet to go
like
what's our best bit
well i don't see a cave right here right
now so i'm gonna look a little bit
but this is too close to the
isn't that a different one though like
[Music]
we should go we should go south
no
that's a different one right yeah what
the hell
why
so close to the other one how
is that lucky or is it just because it's
still so close it's still somewhat
considered the same one somewhat
not that
it's like towers like what the hell
go homemade fireworks
i don't wanna and i'm lacking gunpowder
anyway oh man
oh man
hello wow
wow looks so different than my other
mesa biome here
maybe i'll find at least my my base
or
that looks like
it could turn into a cave
or dad
i'm sorry guys i have disappointed you
all
hamburger land yay
far away from my face
[Music]
wow
no we don't do that chihuahua we don't
do that
but don't look on the water for a cave
i know it's tempting
[Music]
oh
uh
what
what you have you have two stacks
[Music]
to fly in circles genuinely amazing well
and yet i have to find circles
i fly so many times in circles and i
still can't find
circles
that is the real mission that we're held
for
that is the real reason why we're all
here
find
circles hello
nice carrot bed
i know i've been here before
i don't know
oh wait you have a different cartoon
graphic table you have a compass
and another empty map
i'll take i take
i take i take i take i take
i give
and i keep and i keep and i keep
how nice of me i'm giving you copper
repair before it break it will break
as far as i know it's not possible to
break it
and it will be fine
[Music]
make another map
yes i could do that eventually
[Music]
how kind of you to offer your help to me
oh here is the cave we can check this
one out
um should we check this one out do you
think there's a chance it could be in
here
yeah i do have a i don't have i do have
screenshots i'm just too lazy to look at
it
sure yes maybe
no clue okay well then
oh no don't don't do this one
[Music]
i put some stuff in here
uh
i will put also this
here and then i'm gonna put my elytra
in here
the rest of the fireworks maybe should i
oh should i bring them with me
should i bring the compass what was the
compass for again
yeah hot wings are
safe and sound don't worry about it
77 durability don't worry don't worry
don't worry don't you worry
you should be worried about me going in
here
that's what you should really be worried
about
[Music]
open
open the map
wow
wish i could see it on here if it has
what i'm looking for
okay
leave a spare weapon in the chest should
i
a spare weapon i don't have a spare
weapon
i'm bringing all of this
i know it's dangerous
but
maybe
what should i
need bed oh yeah
really wait let me let me uh let me take
this one
or take a different one
[Music]
bed
please leave the fireworks i was
thinking like
over two ways we could fly back up you
know
[Music]
but okay
share two sheep no no no no why why when
there's beds here huh and even in the
perfect color
yeah
okay hi kitty cat
where was i where did i put my stuff i
hit
[Music]
here it is
our adventure awaits us kfp
uh
okay
you said leave the filex uh also let's
leave this here and
let's leave
[Music]
what happens when you touch a phoenix
oh god okay
a phoenix a phoenix is not scared of
such a thing i will not be scared that
easily uh here take take these foods
oh maybe
okay
i'm scared guys
i am scared
oh it's been so long
uh how to how to explore
leave the ax oh do you not think we need
the axe
okay
so we need to look for moss block do we
need to mine down or
[Music]
oh god i don't know what to look for
oh dear oh dear oh dear oh dear oh
i don't want to die
i don't want to die i don't want to die
what if i fall down
torches i have torches we don't need
that many torches
ah
i don't like to be like
moved by the water against my will i
will go
by myself i will decide where to go
oh dear
oh wait
keyboard no keyboard son no no
how do i know how do i know
how do i know
oh there
see i could have fallen into the lava
right next to it
if i were it to be clumsy again
what am i what am i looking for
ah
what's your step yes yes
what am i looking for
what does this so there's uh there's
that thing that's the glowberry's drip
stone there's drip stone yeah
this is just a ravine ravine
this is not what i'm looking for
[Music]
should i look into a different cave
this looks like a drip stone cave
i'm a hummer
okay we're going somewhere else
[Music]
definitely not lush
ah
okay
no problem we'll go somewhere else
uh
we should just uh
we'll find another one
how where where are they
[Music]
uh
not that rare
okay
wait this is
it's okay
there are undo lines there lush games
are fairly common
[Music]
okay where do we go now
i felt so safe fairly safe here because
of all the because of the village but
okay
uh let's go this way
someone did say that they think they're
more common in jungles and
these by all means i guess but who knows
if that is true at least i don't expect
them
i mean even in the winter biome since
they're underneath they would probably
spawn huh
even in the snowy ones
i just fell into lava with free never
rides congratulations
you win frustration
isn't that nice it's an emotion that you
will never forget
[Music]
wait where did i stop
where did i stop talking about the
tournament where did i stop i said
i said yeah uh so the the the problem
with lack of sleep the problem with our
team
uh yeah i think i already said all right
for all the reasons the problem with our
team being smaller and the problem with
our team
being uh pretty strong too like we had a
lot of
a lot of our group we had a lot of
strong
opponents as well
[Music]
so
yeah i feel like my chances were
uh
pretty
low to begin with and then
i was also really really really i didn't
stream it so you guys didn't see but i
would say i was pretty unlucky
in uh
in my races i would say that
i will claim that i was fairly unlucky
unlucky and not in my best form i i did
not perform that well either i must
admit
[Music]
yes
and
i will tell you uh one
embarrassing thing
after the last race you know i was
already like super exhausted tired
shaking nervous
uh
i think partially because of the
the
um
energy drinks they probably partially
made me feel
uh
kind of crazy
um
more emotional than usual but the moment
i saw my last ranking
i started crying and i was so angry
i was so mad but i think the reason was
mostly because i did not want to stay up
any longer
oh my god oh dear
oh dear what happened here
ah
i didn't want to stay up any longer
and i just also felt like i failed kind
of was kind of embarrassing but
um good that i didn't stream
good that i did not stream because you
would have uh found me in a very
vulnerable vulnerable state um
i can't find the cave oh what about this
one
i don't think that's the one
i don't think so
what about here
that looks like it could be something
no
oh
[Music]
let's look into here
i'm feeling fine now well afterwards
after that
failure and after half an hour of
break in the program that i uh
spent
waiting and and trying to calm myself
down
uh
i i uh
wait
yeah then i was part of the zako high
and it's aqua high i mean even for the
zucklehead
i i was first but
honestly i could have done much better
if i wasn't
absolutely at that point i was ah
i was feeling sick and hungry and tired
and shaky and blah
i was not feeling good
yeah so
i could have done even better
if i wasn't in a better condition
but thankfully i did get third overall
in the tournament at least in the in the
in the tackle hud but honestly
i could have done better i could have
done better i know it i know it
is
if i find something i should bring the
sucker box that's why i put the chest
out here and then put everything in the
chocolate box into the gesture
[Music]
not the torches okay
yeah yeah me or senpai only wasn't at
zako high because of her disconnection
so honestly um me and bales
should have been first and second
miyu senpai wasn't even supposed to be
there right
[Music]
now
honda
my bow
i didn't bring my bow
okay
okay it goes all
i'm scared i'm scared
what a bucket
what do we see what do we see
what do we see
what is that huh
how deep do i need to go to see what i'm
looking for
there's no enemies though so far i'm
happy about that no lava
[Music]
uh
could be very deep yeah is it it's below
it's below
a
deep slate right
okay should i dig deeper
[Music]
dig from here
is it well you
you normally have to dig anyway right
like there's no way around that you
would it would always be covered by
um
by one layer of
if i understand correctly
coordinates
not always oh man what if i find nothing
what if i find nothing
oh man i thought it would be easy to
find what i'm looking for
[Music]
maybe if i had oops maybe if i had more
uh
maybe if i had more 5x it would have
been easier
we could have just flown around a bit
more
anyway
yeah after the taco high
i i guess i felt at least a little bit
better about my placement i kind of
redeemed myself
so yes supposedly this is newly
generated yes yes
comment
commentator
and uh
where are we
okay so under 0
or
does it go now to minus 64.
[Music]
is that how it's written now
no
oh
would you look at that that is deep
slate that is deep slide everybody that
was fast so under that maybe
oh i heard something
what is that sound
where's the sound
minus 64 is the new bottom oh
yeah um
i i i would say that if the tournament
was at a better time for me i would have
enjoyed it way more hello you can't
reach me can you what do i see here
red stone what what is that
it looks like a cave
no i don't know
it doesn't look like a lush cave though
could there still be a lush cave
somewhere around here wait that looks
like the thing that i read about that
looks like the never
[Music]
looks like kind of the never
looks promising
[Music]
oh man
yeah it's just a big cave system keep
exploring okay pour water down
oh yeah i'm scared
don't be scared
you're a warrior
maybe i can already shoot some from here
uh i don't see anyone anymore
oh god i'm scared what if i die what the
i want to buy the waterfall
this is is this something really
dangerous down there
oh god
hello i'm coming
i'm coming
hello
don't mind me i'm just making everything
brighter and then we can have a fight
okay uh shield
[Music]
let's have a fight
come here
have you given up on me
ah i don't see you
oh did you feel that oh die
die bastard
i'm not gonna let you go
never gonna give you up never gonna let
you down
uh-huh that's right
what is this oh what's this
yeah
okay
wow wow what is all of that it's so dark
can i turn it up
[Music]
before it's goko uh shuttle wait shuttle
awaits can i turn it up
it's already maximum bright
karina
torches
oh i'm scared
[Music]
i don't see anything
i don't know what i'm looking for i
don't think this is where the lush cave
is
although i mean the big this big cave
system could be connected to a large
cave right
or no
[Music]
come up here come up to my level
um does my bone not have mending oh dear
too dim for a large cave it's not an f
but could it not be connected yes it
could be connected right
oh
[Music]
oh i forgot that they spawned over world
i forgot
um
[Music]
cool cave still i mean even if it's not
what we're looking for
cool caves i must say
i like the deep slate everywhere
[Music]
just running
aimlessly
that's it that's it that's it
i'm taking my torches back then
[Music]
falling gravel what i don't know where
is that a thing
more worried about the enemies but okay
oh wait what is that again
[Music]
ah tough
the the azalea root replaceable
underneath really confuses me what does
that mean what does that mean
[Music]
did i look down here
what was tough again
it's tough again
oh there's blue stuff too okay i mean i
guess let's get the gold we need to go
home with something right
[Music]
let's take that let's take the blue
stuff
i gave all my lappies like zooming to uh
piccola i think did i or to gouda i gave
it to someone
um
okay
uh
all right let me take my torch here
i want my torch back
okay
[Music]
uh
uh should i look down here
[Music]
speeda oh hello
i see you
oh
[Music]
i'm going down
for a torch
wait now i want to look what's there
some kind of spawner
oh no no no no no hell no hell no
put torches in it place torch around to
to break it
why would i break it i'm not gonna stay
here
i'm not gonna
have a party with those people
no no no
[Music]
no
okay um
[Music]
so this is not the way
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
your chest loot down there at the
spawner
um
[Music]
mia hi smoovie
it's mobirella
is it useful varela
are you here to cast a spell on me again
uh
[Music]
oh is that the other place where i went
to hmm
this makes things light up huh
[Music]
ah is that connected oh oh yeah
oh what is what is these is this uh
oh god i'm getting lost diamond
diamond hawking
[Music]
i have a feeling we'll find nothing
diamond mmm
[Music]
oh man i'm getting lost
how deep how far should i go
it's huge guys
those yo hirosuki
how about that
huh oh god
did i go down no there's so many enemies
down there
ah
we must go deeper no no
i like that you can just find random
diamonds so oh dear oh hello
oh hello
oh no
okay
bye-bye
if that's how you want to go and leave
this world that's fine with me
ah
i should retreat at this point doesn't
look like there's lush cave in your hair
[Music]
you think so
where did i come from though
can i come from over there maybe
[Music]
does anything like that look flush to
you
does that look lush to you guys no
okay
i will take back
my torches
and follow them
i do like lush
uh products by the way i like lush bath
bombs man
me liking some lush bath bombs
um
[Music]
time to go back
and but i accomplished nothing it's been
two hours and said it was gonna be a
short stream but i i i thought that i
would at least find what i want in a
short stream no no i'm not giving up yet
i will i'll find i will find what i'm
looking for
yes
[Music]
where is what i'm looking for
at least i'm finding my way back
yes yes it is here
taking this
okay
i really like this new outfit kiara well
thank you it is very recent but i will
bring you guys another new outfit very
soon should we look over there at least
a hello uh hello
should we at least take a look on the
other side that looks
cool i just goes upwards
[Music]
are you scared
you scare me
quite
[Music]
i will serve all of you all customers
must be served
yes yes
wait is that
diamond
[Music]
i'm coming for you
i'm coming for
you i do need more diamonds i i don't
really have the
a collection of diamonds that's what
piccolo senpai was also complaining
about
when uh i welcomed her to the ian's
river
yeah yeah
[Music]
fight me
fps game let's go
not much of a shooter right now
[Music]
right now there's i like how the oars
are like literally everywhere now
you can find them
in so many places however uh
i heard that
diamonds was it dinosaur was it other
ones that uh you won't find them so
often if they're exposed to
uh like so much air
is there a spawner or something over
there what is it with you
oh
[Music]
no
oh there's a you see those
there's a lot of them that's probably
not worth fighting them all
yeah i'm out of here
tiny monsters up
[Music]
i'm so bad at this
okay
taking back my water
no water for you guys
okay that was not very successful um
that's okay
sometimes
sometimes i i mean this this is why i
didn't write it in the title because who
knows if i would have even found
the lush case
at least we saw some stuff from the
update okay we saw some of it
and we got some oris
at least
[Music]
hello
i come in peace
i i leave in peace as well
isn't isn't that how you would want a
visitor to be
[Music]
okay no peace
no peace after all
[Music]
oh it's raining
i hear rain
[Music]
there's a good chance to find a lost
cave in the coral reefs
underneath the water
you mean underneath
oh my
so much rain oh no my stuff is getting
wet
no
no no
[Applause]
um
yeah i was looking for the azalea tree
for a long time oh there we go
it stopped
[Music]
what do we do should we go
should we go all the way back trying to
get more fireworks and then fly more but
that could take a while too
that will take a while as well
[Music]
um
find lush caves under the headquarters
see that's what i'm thinking too
there is a chance that they're
underneath where we already explored
anyway but the reason why we went so far
out i guess is because
is because
azalea trees uh would only spawn in new
chunks
[Music]
are you okay horse
you need some help
let's keep that
hmm
where did gunpowder come from
well you know what
yeah
put that all in here
yeah cause it's all new anyway they're
we can definitely find a lunch cave
somewhere but it's just hard to find
them
if there is no azalea tree anywhere
um
that's why i went so far
oh wait now now it's gonna die now it's
getting dark
[Music]
horse protect me please
if you dig down in the old chunks you'll
find that there is still bedrock at zero
no there's there should be no bedrock
there should only be deep slate
bless
me
uh bone meal the bushes you get from
moss on the land tree itself is hard to
find while flying
[Music]
yeah it removes the bedrock i know that
i know that they don't know they don't
know that
oh
part two of that cave
[Music]
oh hello
ah
[Music]
what makes me so curious
bad kiana go back
damn it
damn it what was that was that did
someone shoot me
[Music]
go back go back
go back to safety
thank you guys for the kison height
i wish you also all of you much much
kizontite
which means health in german
food check oh yeah good idea
it would be so nice if i would just
stumble upon an azalea tree by accident
now wouldn't it be chat
wouldn't that be
so nice chad hmm
of course that's not gonna happen
no
because azalea trees are so beautiful
i'm not
i'm not worthy of finding them
no
oh
oh dear
that was dangerous
[Music]
aren't they isolated are they really
are they dead isolated
then if yes it would make it actually
fairly easy to find them but i have yet
to find one
[Music]
yeah yeah we say health when someone
sneezes yeah it's kind of weird but it
is it is what it is
okay i'm just jumping around randomly
hoping to find something but i can't
i can't
i'll fly it back
yes to
my missile headquarters hopefully six
fireworks is enough
okay
let me look at my coordinates
looking at my coordinates
if it's in a plane it will be isolated
obviously because there is no train ah
not in a forest
ah okay the forest it can be we shall
not isolate it too
much
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
it's just easy to spot okay interesting
what was the folder again for minecraft
screenshots app data right app data
[Music]
screenshots
no that's that's not it this this is it
yeah
okay somewhere around 330
and 11 000
[Music]
okay that's pretty far
oh i don't have mine
we'll try to fly as far as we can and
don't worry about it
[Music]
we can't fly that far anyway with four
or six fireworks
it's not as we not like we can get that
far
okay but we just need to find the right
direction this direction right
now
[Music]
no not quite
right that's east that's north but
that's not it
a little bit a little bit wet
[Music]
north west northwest
we have your boat no
[Music]
free 300 x is 331
something like that
and then that is 11 000.
[Music]
use horse i don't have a i don't
this is the direction this is it this is
it 100 correct
bonked my head who am i where am i
where am i
tree could it spawn no i can't spawn in
the middle of my own because i already
explored that
slowly
wait i went too far i want to fight
i went far
[Music]
this
is
not
not quite
what
i
i should oh my god
what was that
[Music]
i will swim
i will go for a swim
oh a village
okay uh i need to get the x up again
which is that way
and i need
the 12 000 to go
down again but for now we go this way
don't mind me
oh don't mind me
just panicking a little bit
oh he's always panicking
it was just a bloop it was just a bloop
my father was getting attacked okay
uh
anyway uh that's done
uh let's let's have a talk let's have a
chit chat
uh
yeah
um
what was i gonna talk about oh
well for example i have some topics
things that i wanted to talk about with
you guys
i didn't get to talk about it where am i
going where am i going where am i going
300 it needs to be like 300.
uh
but you know i'm not good at
multitasking
ah yeah there was something i wanted to
say about that maybe maybe on it but was
it okay
uh i do remember something else that i
wanted to say
remember
wait i wrote it down
ah i did see that and i put us a clip
today
yeah she scares me that kusogaki she
scares me
i should not be intimidated by her but
she intimidates me
i must assert senpai dominance
oh no whatever i want to talk about my
massage and stuff too but now let's talk
first about the other thing uh oh oh
yeah about me could only thing
uh
i wanted to say
um
one thing i wanted to mention you know
how we did these like
these phrases
uh for the telephone game
[Music]
um i did not start any of the sentences
on stream right
i
like we had this order and and we had
four four rounds of five rounds and
if it had been one more round i could
have started the sentence maybe but uh
there wasn't but that then i guess you
guys maybe assumed that none of these
sentences are originally mine right
well actually
uh one of those sentences was mine
so when i heard it in a butchered
version
uh
i was like on it wait that's that sounds
when i said oh that sounds familiar
that's uh when they said my sentence to
myself so i think they kind of messed up
there
i don't think i was supposed to
um
hear my sentence laid on of course i'm
gonna recognize it however even though i
recognize it kind of i i did not use
that to to my advantage
um i did just like
repeat literally what i heard in the way
i heard it as if i
didn't know what it actually
was supposed to be i yeah i read the air
in that moment i was like i'm not gonna
ruin this now
but but the actual uh sentence let me
tell you
where did i write it down
um
[Music]
where did i write that was it here
yeah
my i we were asked for some sentences
now the the pizza one was obviously
suggested by goura
but the ones i suggested like free i
didn't know like what kind of
sentences i should um
uh
yeah uh
uh give them but what i came up with i
feel like they kind of used my first
sentence as well but changed it up a
little because i said fishing fresh fish
from the ocean on friday which is like a
tongue twister and they used a similar
one i think they changed up my fishing
fresh fish from the ocean on friday
they added like freddy to that
that was kind of me
but that's it yeah ah
i'm gonna set that one in like a
different version so people thought that
ame came up with it but no that was not
that was not from her i don't know who
assigned the sentences i don't know
and then the other one i said was just
mother makes the best morning omelette
because i was like maybe they don't want
something like a tongue twister maybe
they want something more normal i don't
know and then the other one was my
favorite winter sport is ice skating
what's yours
isn't that
did they use that i think
they used that one i think
yeah the other one was freddy fries
fresh fresh on the friend of for free
on friday
yeah this one they used but yeah cronie
started that one i guess so i came up
with two sentences kind of
but
i did not get to start any sentences i
think it was assigned wrongly and then i
kind of knew these sentences already and
the thing is like i also
uh i think i also knew
what guru
uh oh yeah i already
i already um i heard the sentence that
gooder suggested
uh before as well i heard that one too
before although i kind of forgot it so
like partially i didn't know i did not
remember the complete sentence so that's
at least something yeah anyway we need
to sleep in the game
um
yeah there's enemies
[Music]
okay
okay we're good
we good
okay uh what was the direction
what is it already oh wait walk okay i
went
this way this way this way
this way
this way this way this way both have to
go down
and when did this
[Laughter]
well excuse me i can't
multitask at least this way you have
you're able to spend more time with me
guess we gotta go a little bit over the
ocean
don't you want to spend more time with
me
have you watched the clips why would i
watch clips when i was literally in it
all you mean for the times when i was
not in the same voice chat channel
ah no i did not really uh
did not really watch
much of that
but uh
yeah it was it was fun i'm glad they
called me oh but then i noticed one
thing
uh there was this other
this other program that they did
with bales iris orina
and
[Music]
one more person
uh
anya right yeah
i think those four or was it one more
yeah uh
and i looked at the i looked at the
lineup
and then i looked at the lineup in my
group
and i realized something
the hundred yen
lineup
is
the girls the foreign whole life girls
that japanese viewers consider to be
good at japanese
and then i will ask myself am i not
considered to be good at japanese
anymore
[Music]
should i not have been in that group
i know that because i've been barely
speaking japanese then because i've left
japan
that my japanese skills have really
deteriorated or however you say it i've
gotten worse at japanese okay that's a
fact
but
now i'm not even getting invited to the
cool japanese speaking foreign group
anymore
if
or or they still consider me as such but
they did not invite me there because
they needed at least one person to speak
uh
to be able to translate
uh the mess that they're making in in
the telephone game
i'm not sure what to make of it
where do we go
where are we going where are we going
dolphin i can't look that fast
i think it should be somewhere there no
what it no we went too far again
one two four is it
this way
maybe
[Music]
probably like probably the ladder you
think it's that
[Music]
[Laughter]
very concerned about that
because like i see it i see the way that
japanese people talk about me now like i
see how when i see it in twitter ego
search they're like oh iris
and
they're like iris and anya so good at
japanese kiara yeah she hurt too i guess
it's like
but in the past in the past before id
second gen and before
uh uh iris
everybody in in the japanese community
and they were like oh my god
she's the best at japanese
and now we've come to a point where
it's not me anymore who they think of
when they think about
girls who are good at japanese were not
japanese man
man
oh man
but i can assure you if i were to go
back to japan or do or just
talk more in japanese in general i would
be
back to my usual peta peta self again
to my usual super good japanese
professional
proficient professional
skills yes
yeah um
one thing that i don't know though is
where the hell i am
i think i kind of saved the wrong
coordinates
uh
[Music]
i mean they are extremely good it's just
it's just kind of like looking at how
other people are considered
the pros now it's like what happened
what happened man what happened
what happened
it's so sad
it's just so sad okay i'm looking at my
screenshots maybe i'll find more
accurate uh coordinates
ah found them three hundred six and
thousand eight hundred
three hundred six
okay we'll get there let's first do 306
somewhere here
and then thousand
you need to go down this way okay
okay
hi hi
now
[Music]
bunny just died
sorry bunny r.i.p
[Music]
i think it's also
i don't know dave because i've been
barely speaking japanese in my streams
anymore
um but they do i think bales and iris
speak
like a million times more japanese in
their streams than i do nowadays
and that's probably why
uh
that's probably how the japanese people
now like
all they hear is them speaking japanese
they don't hear it from me anymore
so
maybe they forgot maybe they forgot i
can speak japanese too
although yeah what about whole talk
i think they forgot about it
i think they forgot about the existence
of horn talk
japanese time zones perhaps that as well
that they stream more during
their time zone but i think it's also
that you know bales and iris have been
like kind of appealing to that audience
in their streams
[Music]
um
like as far as i know they speak quite a
bit of japanese and then
yeah you know word goes around
the word goes around
and uh anya of course i know anya speaks
like
so much japanese in her streams and she
has a lot of japanese viewers
and she speaks very very pretty japanese
anya's japanese is very nice to listen
to
i i must i must agree
if if i live in japan my japanese goes
back to
super good again
really
trust me
oy moyada
the am i
how am i not able to go back
i mean i need to go over there
i need a coin
is that what that is
yeah
finally
[Music]
i think i think iris and me um
are
on
the same level but just uh
there are some things that i'm better at
and then there's things that she's
better at
yep
like for example vocabulary or or
grammar or um
uh
what's it called uh like
not dialects but like net slang or
whatever
[Music]
i don't have better english what
anyway there is no need for
everybody to this is exactly the problem
this is exactly what i don't like
there's no need for everybody to come to
be comparing each other's
uh
skills in everything
and saying this person is bad i know
this person is better now this person is
better it does not matter
everybody has their strong suits and
their strengths and all that but i just
i just i just felt a little bit sad that
i just wasn't
considered uh to be part of the nihongo
speaking gang anymore
um
yeah that's all i wanted to say
but also in a humorous way i wasn't
i hope you guys are getting that okay
this is not uh
this is not
bracket
serious talk bracket or serious uh
bracket kiana cries about
not being cool anymore
i'm just saying okay
it's funny how i was not in the 100 yen
group but i was as a
translator perhaps i was in the other
group
well we're here what do we do
what do we do
don't shock done
serious
serious kia that is not cool anymore
maybe they split the groups by time
zones
that does not really make sense either
because
um
hello european time zone mixed together
with japanese
and and uh american time zones
i see what you're getting at because
they're all in like a japanese time zone
but my group was like all all thrown
together too
[Music]
should we go back
yeah
my little time zone i'm all alone here
in europe
so lonely
[Music]
i guess i guess mine down at your home
you think i'll be lucky and find
something
[Music]
don't think i'll be lucky oh wait oh no
oh no oh no wait
[Music]
dolphin health help me dolphin
help me help me please help me help me
yes thank you oh thank you
[Music]
this portal wait is there four
portals now
was that three
someone fix that for me please
no i did not end up fixing the portals
as you can see
[Music]
i miss japan
i do miss going to japan
[Music]
nihon
koiskonado
um
sorry my brain is like blah no is that
what i wanted to do that's all i wanted
to do but maybe i bring uh
put that here
okay it goes off
for the portal
do you ever plan on moving back no but i
i do wonder
sometimes i think about
oh it's so noisy
sometimes i think about whether like if
i should
move to a different country
in europe or
i mean i kind of
always thought uh moving to the uk was
an option but you know now it's um
they didn't exactly make it easier i
think
um
yeah
now
if if they were still
you know
if they didn't
go
then i might have very much considered
moving to the
uk at some point oh my god
go straight
again
stop
go straight go straight go straight go
straight
okay
why because uh at least i know the
language
i just
i just i just would like to be in a
country where i understand the language
you know
um
[Music]
maybe switzerland would be cool but haha
same problem
all the countries that i'm
interested in
what the i thought i was falling
down
maybe this window was not the best idea
oh i thought i was going to die right
here i thought i was going to die
shinokato
i'm gonna put some glass or something
there eventually
oh my god
germany
i i don't like germany but to me it's
just like too similar to where i'm from
i would want
to live somewhere oops i left that open
um
that's different you know
that scared me too
scared the out of me
a change of pace yeah change of pace and
change of people
and sceneries
but i don't know that's for the far far
far far
off of our future at the moment i'm
comfortable here i literally just moved
in 2021
several times and
i
i i'm definitely not ready to go through
all that moving stress again no no i
want to move within europe because it's
just easier to move within europe
yeah
[Music]
that that's no that's i'm not going i'm
not going to move to brazil
not going to move to russia no i'm not
going to move to canada no
no shut up
it's way too far
no you're ridiculous
[Music]
the netherlands would be nice probably i
know the people are very nice and it's a
very pretty place but i don't know i
don't know as i said it's for the far
far future
who knows maybe england will come back
how's it going england are you feeling i
am feeling coming back maybe
reconciliation or something like that
belgium oh yeah i love me some belgian
waffles every morning or yeah yeah
belgium belgium
belgium is belgium pretty
what are we gonna do now camping we came
back monotake done
[Music]
i'm not impressed with what i have
what's the time it's almost 1am my sleep
schedule is
i
i wouldn't exactly have a problem with
staying up longer but
well the worms collab is at 1am
i have to be awake for that anyway
[Music]
no way yeah norway is nice oops wrong
chest no way is nice i like that thought
[Music]
repair wings ah
yeah yeah yeah repair wings uh where did
i repair them like ah by selling iron
okie dokie
[Music]
good idea
gun powder would be nice is there no
trader that sells gunpowder
i don't even need that much purple boy
yeah my own outfit reveal is 10 p.m my
time are you guys ready it's in less
than 24 oh my god it's less than 24
hours
[Music]
oh my god
guys what's happening i'm the first one
i'm the first one top beta
buta
oh my god
hold your horses everybody hold them
hold them
new outfit
now i know what you guys will think
about it
always so curious about your guys's
opinion stupid cat
[Music]
oh go down down down down down
i'm holding them you have horses you
have horses to hold
all they be sleeping
you're sleeping so
early welcome to the club of mess-ups i
mean my sleep schedule was messed up
since forever
like going to sleep at 5 00 am was
normal for me
but
now it's even worse now it's
even worse shut the way
i need my did i
is there a in the chest here
did i put an ender chest into phoenix
though
i know i have one with me but is there
one placed down already
put the leg to the leg
i feel like i would have put one down
[Music]
um
[Applause]
[Music]
damn it
okay i'm placing mine
we could
mend this one too right this one has
been in yeah yeah
okay buddy
eight
are you kidding me do you want
to be beheaded
oh my god
that is ridiculous
i have to hold one right one
[Music]
uh-huh
uh-huh that's not much
what the is the matter with is that
how you thank me
somehow you repair me
send them to the chopping block off of
their heads
no no no you guys are so rude
i did not deserve this kind of treatment
okay this one is mended
buddy buddy buddy
it's unbelievable thank you
daddy will come later really how much
nine
nine nine nine
wait he's back to normal why are you
back to normal now
thank you
at least someone with uh back to their
census
[Music]
ah shut up oh my god you guys are so
noisy
this is so amazing you're wondering why
i didn't come see you for a while huh
just kidding just kidding i love you all
phoenixton is my baby
phoenixton is my baby i don't have
anymore
[Music]
i have anything else to trade here
yeah whoa
white wall black wool oh where's the
wall guy must be over here
[Music]
organize the chest hell no
bring cronie to me
i don't but did i have the wool people
here where did i put the wool people
[Music]
people know
they weren't the blasphemous oh
i said why did i put them there
is that 18 to 13 or is that 10 to 13.
[Music]
i think it's 18 to 13.
but it's great
it's great though
[Music]
there must be more
oh
[Music]
no my electron electronics done don't
need any more for my elijah electra
what
did i have some grey wall then
yeah
okay
hello buddy
brown
sorry guys this is the kind of boring
part
we'll
let me fix the short stream huh
i'm it would have been short if we wanna
if we would have found uh what we were
looking for
but i was robbed of that experience
[Music]
i am very not amused
what is that
ugly child doing here
huh
children not allowed in phoenix 10
sorry um your leader is currently in a
little bit of a mood forgive me
[Music]
this is only temporary
who is a sassy lost child
[Applause]
okay
uh
i wanna
go get gun powder
[Music]
gum powder
skate makes me feel dizzy today
[Music]
does it look like halloween over there
base farm bay's farm is not producing
anything we were already there
it's not producing anything
i know
previously picked on his property
[Music]
i will go to ppp
the chunk is unloaded
[Music]
wait is pb working now
you mean on the japanese server
hell no
[Laughter]
i told you guys my stance on that
i told you
[Music]
we are here to take long train rides
please don't go to the pbb base
[Music]
how to get out and then stop it
okay we will try it
afk
i don't
i don't want to do that on stream that's
the most boring thing i can do on stream
i don't know if i even want to like i
kind of want to continue exploring
let's already pass with that it feels so
wrong it's like 1am here
[Music]
i wanna i don't wanna
i don't want pvp to be like
alone forever
you know
[Music]
super chat reading
super chat reading while i am king
i'm not in the mood
let me let's let's go there
and see how fast it produces if you guys
say it's that fast show me how fast it
is
wait but i could take more gunpowder
from inna but
i mean
i don't think i
even if i go
afk now and and uh collect that
gunpowder i guess we're probably not
gonna
go
far anymore today huh
[Music]
i don't want to go next week though
i don't want to find the lush cave next
week and i will have a full inventory
full of fireworks i tell you that
thank you for the membership come sign
me down thank you
[Music]
where am i uh
did is onsen look like that that's not
the onsen that that over there is the
answer what is this
what is this
stop do not enter do not enter stop whip
who made that
when the hell did she build that did she
build that
uh
we have the plan of finishing it for
halloween
good always starts building things and i
feel like she rarely finishes them
[Laughter]
for next year
yeah i guess so next year there's always
another halloween spoopy halloween
all right
uh
should be something it should be
somewhere here
[Music]
what was it more over there
there's a tree farm
ah that one what's that one
no
is that not the trident or anything
no that's is that it
[Music]
here i am hello
it's not been very long
so what do you got for me
i did bring a bed
fortunately
let's
look zero
okay
please
[Music]
why do people keep on asking about the
fanfictions
i don't read fanfictions
i'm impatient
make it go boom
where is the boom stuff
bales
where's the boom stuff
fails fails bails bails bails bails
fails
bails fails bails bails fails fails
fails bails
fanfictions where are the fantasies i've
heard of them
i've heard of something like that
hmm
i never tried to shoot someone with uh
with the zoom function oh nice um
give me that exp yummy yum yum yum yum
thank you
oh
nice arrow
[Music]
doesn't make a difference if i'm at the
top you mean at the very top uh i mean
there i thought you just mean above
though
above
okay
[Music]
well that's a fire far away
that is very up high
oh good that i have another bed
but what their enemies wouldn't even
spawn here it doesn't matter right if i
sleep or not
i think it does not make it go faster
but how long do i wait up here
[Music]
10 minutes
they spawn better during the day
30 minutes 10 minutes
[Music]
and free look at mob cloud where's the
mob counter here
[Music]
but okay um
maybe we'll just uh
i will just end it here
is it
there's a tiny lash cave and you're
telling me the coordinates oh no
oh don't ah
what should i do chat should i go there
[Music]
if 300 500
300 500
i saw it it's ingrained in my brain now
that's very close
i want to look at it
i want to look at but but don't do that
again don't tell me when i'm not asking
please
[Music]
300 500
cool bales that is so scary
that is so scary
okay
oh afk off-screen
she always says and never does but i
will i will i will i will
do i have the bed
yeah
died several times here oh my god eh
where there
crony died well the thing is
you might think when you fall down you
might think you have to like aim and
move around but you should just fall
down straight and then it's safe
did she move around
wait and hear it working
i just heard something working i think
now go go tamita
oh but there's nothing in here
okay okay okay you know what before we
end i'm just gonna check out that
quickly
[Laughter]
then let me let me uh go back once uh
and uh organize one more time because my
inventory is full
and yeah
[Music]
i just want to see it i'm not satisfied
and fanfiction
where
where is that anyway is that in crony's
bunker
[Music]
one fireworks
yeah after searching so far we can just
we could just say that's what i found by
searching
in the bunker well that's i'm not gonna
get there go away cow what is it what is
it what's the matter of you
is that the right direction yes
slowly descend into madness
but
okay
[Music]
inventory
happy birthday
okay happy birthday
weird uh message uh i don't understand
but happy birthday
[Music]
how many times did you say that this
would be the last time what do you mean
last time i said nothing of that sort
[Music]
no no no
i said nothing
[Music]
i don't know what you mean
i do not know
[Music]
just throw it all in here
just why did i bring all that wool with
me
why did i bring all of them
happy birthday
happy birthday to you oh yeah i wanted
to talk a little bit about almonds
birthday i forgot
to talk about it did you did you did you
watch her stream i called in
and and and i i wished her happy
birthday and i sent her flowers and the
flowers arrived in time before the
stream
yeah yeah i sent her a huge big bouquet
of yellow
flowers like yellow roses and yellow
daisies and all that
i called in a lot yes
several times
yeah i saw no one else was calling in so
i was like okay i guess
what the hell no
she did send me a picture but i'm not
sure if she would be okay with me
showing it so i'm not showing it um but
it's just a flower bouquet
[Music]
i mean normally with like
real live friends
[Music]
i wouldn't
i would not really like give someone
flowers as a birthday present
uh
but like i just wanted to send ame
something physical you know
and
i there is not
much there's not many options
to send like physical stuff like
to order a career to send something to
that place in a different country
unless i had more time and then bought
something like an actual object or
something and then sent it personally
with the mail but who knows when the
hell that arrives
um
yeah i just wanted to you know
she'll give her something physical and i
think for that for that purpose it was
nice
and special to give her
flowers yeah
and i i love personally i love receiving
flowers i don't receive flowers very
often actually like never but uh
so i'm it's
not
[Music]
what am i doing
yeah she seemed happy about it so i am
happy
[Music]
i just i just wanted
something that she can touch you know
oh wait i still have the minecart
put up the fan mail okay if we can
change that yeah no we're not
we're not allowed to receive presents
only letters but yeah that's also a
thing why are not opening
is it broken am i lagging
uh
i'm lagging i think
[Music]
i can't go into the boat
i'm in the boat and the minecart is
there okay
[Music]
yes
we are back
what was i saying what was that
what was i saying
what did i say a letter yeah yeah yeah i
was reading letters
i finally received letters but they were
from like valentine's day and before
valentine's day
definitely mostly before my birthday i
can't
game is dead
[Music]
maybe it's a sign that i should stop
yeah so if you guys want to send me fan
letter
ever if you consider that then maybe you
might want to send it now if you wanted
to send me something for my birthday or
so
yeah server is not doing so hot
it's a sign isn't it
[Laughter]
so yeah if you want to send something
you should send it now even if you send
it now it probably won't make it in time
for my birthday
okay
[Music]
well this is how i quickly get to a lush
cave no
uh what the what
what
ah
well okay thank you oh my god
it's daytime
this is so trippy
server is killed where it was you when
server was killed
i was in the void when servo was killed
they say servo was good i was no
i said no
well
i take that as a sign
we we will not go to that lush cave we
will find our own lush cave
soon
on our own when we have more fireworks
okay what a nightmare yeah i will go to
bale's thingy
uh and
afk there
but we will end the stream here
and
yeah
i'll see you tomorrow in my outfit
reveal
thank you for the membership message
[Music]
yeah it's a 30 minute relay so you can
watch all our outfit reveals in a short
amount of time and then we'll have a fun
fun fun worms collab on my channel okay
[Music]
it will be on my channel only yeah and
that will then be the end of this crazy
week once again where am i i have it
where am i
i think it's this way
what
[Music]
right because it's it's a saturday now
already in my time zone
[Music]
sunday um
uh
next week also crazy every week crazy
crazy
every week is crazy my shoe
is look i see no
ah one more thing that i did want to say
after watching amez
3d live concert
i i i did think that
um
you know how i talked about definitely
100 wanting to do
um
a 3d
stream a proper one for my birthday
even if i don't get to japan by then
i think with ami's help
one way or another somehow we'll make it
happen
somehow somehow
somehow
i'll i'll get amit to help me
so that even even if i can't go to japan
on my birthday i can
stream
what i
was dreaming of
do like a little bit of a concert
no not buff kiara
i want cute idol kiana
i don't want to get buffed no
i don't want to
i chose this lifestyle of noodle arms
and i'm proud of it
kiana buffa nashi exactly because
they're nashi means no in japanese
no buff
no no swole no i'm not gonna get small
no
you know
think of it it would look weird if buff
ame would carry buff kiara in her arms
princess carrie it would look so much
cuter if buff ame would carry noodle
arms kiara
in her both arms like a princess
yes
[Laughter]
[Music]
it can't it can't be two of us there
can't be two of us
also that was a fake element from a
different dimension i think
i don't know did she go back at the end
did she go back thank you for the red
super chat thank you
[Music]
huh
what do you mean buff another part you
mean my boobies they don't need to be
buffed
she went back to her timeline
um that's that's kind of sad i hope
she'll visit us again
i really did not expect her to come out
with that buff i'm a model like where
the hell did that one come from
[Music]
oh man
yeah she twerked for me i asked her to
twerk and she did
it was
that was that was gorgeous it wasn't
working was so cute
[Music]
um
was there anything i wanted to say
uh
this box is very trackable yes yes
[Music]
i hope i had a wonderful birthday
um
let's have more talk
talking time next week okay
we'll we will do
minecraft and i'm i am thinking of
starting zelda zelda lynx awakening next
week so that's another
stream where we might get uh some time
to um talk also monday monday
uh members only stream in my evening
time
where we will be
testing out
the
whole
snack box
thingy yeah
because i have that snack box lying
around here
and we'll we'll eat it on stream while
chit chatting in a member's own stream
and that's what's happening on monday
finally snack box
no it's not it's not japanese it's like
one japanese snack but it's a mix of
several countries it was supposed to be
a specific country's snack box but then
in december when i received it for the
first time finally it was a mix of all
kinds of things so here we are and i'm
like i can't make a stream out of this
and now we're doing a test run and
members only
um
next whole talk soon ah
uh
[Music]
next whole talk is not next week
i think it will be happening
maybe if all goes well on sunday the
23rd yes not on saturday
but on sunday
could be
oh it's not really that there is that
much prep work it's just you know
schedule scheduling
scheduling so that
the guest has time
guest is a busy guest
very busy guest so much to do
that loop i don't think we're gonna be
playing devil but we'll see we'll see
we'll see i'm still working on the
schedule a little bit
there's a lot of fun streams next week
though don't worry about it
okay i'll go uh i'll go now uh thank you
for the fun uh gorilla minecraft stream
back to my minecraft that was i was i'm
glad to be back to minecraft it's fun
but we'll have to
explore some more next week
thank you guys for watching thank you
innocent bystander for the red super
chat i'll be reading super chats um
on sunday after my after my shrine
stream
okay everybody and once again thank
everybody for
1.3 million
subscriptions thank you for the support
if you're not subscribed yet then how
about you push that a button and hit
that notification bell yes yes yes yes i
think that would be a good idea
to not
miss
any special streams especially the one
for tomorrow i dare you to miss that one
i need to make a thumbnail
[Music]
time yes
thank you everybody and in german we say
[Music]
vida zayn
love you
[Music]
do
oh oh you still hear me
[Music]
thank you
there is no union meeting i saw that
comment
[Music]
no
oh no she wants to cuddle me
she's casting a spell on me again
[Music]
oh no the witch is back
she's dragging me into my bed
it's cuddle time
[Music]
netflix and cat
netflix and cats
[Music]
i can't give in i don't uh no i can't i
can't not give in i i want to cuddle
with that witch
[Music]
[Applause]
papa