[Music]
[Applause]
Microphone
[Music]
Well, since he wasn't there, let's do it. I
feel like we can do it if one or more people gather together.
Babu, let's do our best today as a baby! It's
really,
really good
24 is okay, okay, okay
[Music]
Okay, okay, okay, okokok Let's do our best. Let's do our best
today, let's be a baby.  I'm going to
do this with the baby, so I'm going to
wait a little bit and check this out
[Music] I'm going to
adjust the stupid and useless screen, I'm going to adjust the screen, I'm going to adjust the
road surface just a little bit here, and I'm going to
adjust the screen, um, and I'm going to
do this like this.  OkOk, it feels good.It
feels good.Let's move from standby for a moment,
Sue.Okay, I'll do my best today, Bab-chan.Let's
go.What is
this?It's
too demonic.
Alright, alright, so let's wait for a moment.
Alright, so today I
'm going to take it easy with Babu-chan. The
princess is adorable, so please do your best to comment and be a parent.
[Music] Is
the volume okay? Turn it up a little more.
Okay, that's about it.
I think I'm going to get a little buzzy about this.
Well, I hope it doesn't appear on the top left of the screen.
[Music]
What? Are we
going to win?
Yeah, about 30 minutes ago,
finally,
Umo
[Music]
Ban Pan
Hello Hello OKOK
Ha, Shirakami-
chan, Marine Lunacine area Anna-chan,
Ina-chan, Hako-tan, Hako-
tan
.
Thank you for the tea, Babu. Thank you for the tea, Babu.
Exciting.  Let's do our
best and have a good time, Babu. I'm going to drive the winning Babu, Acho-chan. I think I'll give it a try if I send a lot of idiots to drive, so I'll do my best. Thank you, Babu. Thank you, Babu. Thank you, Babu. Thank you, Babu.  I
feel like I'm going to go crazy today,
but Shirakami is really weak, so I'll
at least go to the middle and watch the high flames in the morning.
I want to have a leisurely high-level sightseeing
Babu Neeun I'll
take a look at the bad hair and choose.
Do it for my mom too. No, there are other moms who
have the qualities of a mom other than Shirakami,
so let's just keep it that way.
Marine Mama, Louie Mama,
Chiara
Granabaa.  Neri mama Luna
maigama Ruire mama
Subaru mama We're
all here
Hakobama Kagoshima mama We're all running together with mamas and mamas
Today we're Shirakami Today we're with Shirakami mamas  Let's
run together, mama
[Laughter]
[Music]
Everyone mama
On the official broadcastMarty
Official broadcast mama
Ee-chan mama is mama
Ae-chan mama and
mama mama I'm full of people I'm happy
Company please  Hurry
up, 150 individual race normal item
CPU, all machines have 6 races, yes, I'm
starting to associate it.
And then I can't help but stay still.
Mom, mom, official moms, look at mom,
mom, moms, look at me,
bubu babu, oh
mom.
Wait, wait, that's
dangerous. Louie mom is here too. Let's go to the baby park together. I'm
not scared, finally, mom. Louie mom. So that's
it.  I'm Babs, who's going to be a raccoon,
everyone, please fill me in as much as you can. Let's talk about it in the comments too.
Okay, Ogyaa!
B-mom is the
only mom I have.
[Music]
[Applause]  It hurts,
it hurts, it hurts, it doesn't hurt, so it's a big mess, Babs, I'm a big
mixer
[Music] There's
also a big mix of moms.Nothing.Good,
wait, who was that Bob?You just
hit someone, Babs.Wait,
who are you now?  No, who did I hit? I
thought it was the Babu who hit it or what it is now, but it turned
out to be a different Babu. Who is it? Who is it now? Who is it?  I think I'll
go to Mute City. My dad is here. Maybe Be-chan got randomly.
Yeah, okay, I guess I
hit the exit. I hit Nene
Mama. It's
Peach Circuit Bab.
Page Circuit Bab.
[Music]
Papan.
Okay. I
'll call the number one accepting mom.
-
[Music]
Make sure you take the coins too. If you
put on your butt, it'll fall on your butt too. If you
don't have your butt, you'll be dead. If you don't have your butt, your butt will be targeted.
Coin Bug
You should do it
Ishoyosho
OK Babu
Subaru Mama I'm
sorry Good show
[Music]
Nothing in my butt I want items in my butt
There are also more than 10 coins
[Music]
Coin  Babu got his back.
Shirakami's items are fine.
Stop. There
are no items.
[Music] Babu is
having trouble using Chanjaba London. Babu
avoids bananas and it hurts.  It's
a bit of a pain bomb. It's a dangerous bug
at the end. It's a really dangerous Babu in France. It's a
Babu who
doesn't want to be dropped here. It's a Babu who doesn't want to be dropped here.
[Music] It
hurts
[Music]
Mei-chan Babu
Wow, that
was terrible,
huh?  I don't know what to do, so let's
mute it and move on.
[Music]
Gui
No, but I'm
not a small fry, I
'm not a small fry, I
'm not a small fry, so I guess it's okay.
That's the last one. It's a
scene where I didn't get the double item.
[Music]
Ah,
Mute City Babu,
here I am.
Or, after that, Mama
[Music]
Mama, Mama.
[Music] I'm
a little
late. [Music]  [
Music] I don't
have any items.
[Music]
[Music] You're a
good kid.
OK Babu -
Okay.
[Music]
But the pub is reeling.
Cushion.
[Music]
Let's go.
As long as it's okay until Snow Mama falls,
Babu will go.
[Music]
Okay, okay. It's
still good Babu. Oh
no.
[Music]
No.
Man, it's hard to run out of items here.
[Music]
Surgery was shown on the air.
Surgery in packaging.  I'm glad you showed me
[Music]
Yeah, that's
good Babu
Yay, Babu
is going to Big Blue,
Big Babu
Big Babonic Babu,
bop pap
[Music]  That's
not good, Babu. Big Babu. Babu is doing a big balm. [Music] Oh, it's Big Babu. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Yesterday, it's like yesterday's Marin-chan. Maybe the white team is doing that. It's not like that.
Big Babu, everyone, have a good time
Big Babu
Boo
[Music]
[Applause]
And you can
get the item Stop
Babu Babu is so sad Yes, it
looks like it hurts
Lie
[Applause]
[Music]
Mario in reverse again
Reverse number babi, you tata ta tata
tama
[Music]
[Laughter]
Autumn There are
n't many mountains, but ah
[Music] I
can see the back of a small fry  Come on,
no, I don't like the small fry
[music] I do
n't like the small fry.
Well, no, what should I do? It's all about the white hair. If I
win, that
means I also win Rainbow Road.  You're
starting to see some dangerous small fry.
No, I don't want to go, small fry. I
don't want to come. Shirakami's back hair ends in the middle, ends in the middle, deep [Music] Dolphin has come. Dolphin has come. Marine has come. Marie-chan is really good here.  Crouching
is really weak here, right?
In other words, it's bad. We'll
put in a framework.
Hmm, look, it's an accident.
[Music] Are there
people around you who are using duck tactics?  Lua
Luigi is the only one, so I
can't catch it, I
can't catch it, I ca
n't catch it
[Music] And there are people who can't catch it [Music] Oh,
what did I get hit with? There are a lot of
accidents
[Music]
I did it, Babu, here and here
Okay, well, well, here
[Music]
[Applause]
Did you get it?
Baboo, it
's a big mess.
[Music]
How about that squid in the car?
Something
amazing came. Good
[Music]
Oh, but Marie-chan was really fast. That's
amazing. Okay. I'm
not a small fry. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Nice Baboo.
Then, Rainbow.
Rainbow Road.
Okay.  Alright,
alright, it looks like a bubble. Let's see
what happens.
[Music]
I have a feeling it will happen. It's
Bowser.
[Music]  Bowser
Castle and that too.
[Music]
It's going to get rough again. It might be dangerous. If we
're at the bottom, we'll be in trouble.
Wait a minute, no. I do
n't want to restart. I do
n't want to do it next time.
[Music]
There's no mom item.  Babu,
dear mom, I
don't have any items, Babu, I
don't have any items [Music] I can't even get coins, Babu is like this
[Music]
In this world, it's a poison babon
Wow
[Music] It's
so bad
[Music] It's scary [Music] It's scary
if it actually falls when it was about to fall. [
Music]
[Applause] The
girl's camera is so scary, it's
so bad. The chocolates are getting more and more
[Music]
Oh no!  It's not enough
No, it's too scary
[Applause]
[Music] There was an encora, look! [Music] It's
too scary, but two of them are too big
What is this?
Computer
Oh no, it's like this
[Music]
Hey, why are you blowing up against the white mold?
Safe,
good, good. Ah,
thank you, thank you.
Good, mom.
Okay, so we'll disband this group.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you.
Okay. Let's
move on to waiting for a while.
Okay.  Wow, that was fun!
Did it fall out of the glass?
[Music]
Wow, that was fun! It
was a really good item.  You'll be
hitting the opponent from behind, and you'll be
hitting them all the time.At the very
end, you'll realize that the butt is important.That's what I understand.It's
great.It's
fun.After this,
there's a strong hit, so everyone, please
enjoy it.  Please,
I'm probably thinking of recruiting underground lords on Twitter, so I
was a little nervous and thought about what to do, but I
thought I'd go deeper.
No, I don't know what to do.I'm a
little worried about whether or not I should do it.I'm a bit worried about whether I should do it or not.I'm a little worried about what to do.
I
think it's okay to say that I'm anxious about Fridays, but
wait, let's do it. Is it
okay to be anxious and worry about what's going to be broadcast on Fridays?  Which
one is better? I
'll do it unstablely. I'd prefer the unstable hose. It
's Friday, so I'll do it unstablely. OK
. The
accident rate was really bad. It
was an accident that caused many accidents. That
baby did her best.  So,
today is an unstable challenge, so I
wonder what time it will end. Well, I
feel like I'm living quite smoothly and on schedule.
Well,
it ends at
6 o'clock, so I guess I'll start
after 6 o'clock, maybe around 8 o'clock, but I'll be
doing it a little unsteadily from 6 o'clock
to 12 o'clock, I guess 24 hours.  I think I'll try to
maintain a slightly unstable system until that point,
so I appreciate your support.
[Music] I'll
use the broadcast, so
please continue to follow and enjoy New Year's Kappo.
[Music] Do
everything you want to do,
play.
[Music]
But
hold my hand and
smile forever