[Music]
[Applause]
we're
here us Mary marry Among Us Among
Us Mary among us marry Among
Us why not what's not to love about
those
guys welcome everybody to the uh
Christmas or Holo Ian holiday Among Us
stream we have gathered here today with
so many lovely cute girls and we're
going to have fun choking and stabbing
each other right yeah sounds fun vi
vi let's go awesome well we're going to
um do it without proximity chat by by
the way guys uh because you know we have
some first timers here I think it's
Advent girls's first time Among Us sing
here right first timers
that's yeah we'll find out how they act
when when they're imposter we can't tell
yet like for others maybe we already
know a tell but for these new we don't
know what is their tell maybe that's
maybe you could tell us would you be so
kind in your introduction to tell me
what your tell
is please n you got to find that out
that information is classified going to
need a little cash money up front first
I'll try well okay then let's start with
introductions and start with the only
one who's a real astronaut here
Amy h Hello Amilia Watson number one
astronaut
detective I like Among Us so I'm excited
to play Let's oh
y can out because maybe there's some new
viewers at this point who don't
understand why is am able to wear her
own clothes in the game and why am I
wearing P's clothes and wearing man's
clothes am do you want to explain uh yes
we have uh we had a collab with Among Us
where you could get a few uh Hol live
outfits and items in the Among Us shop
but I don't think it's available anymore
it was kind of a little time
time too bad if you miss out me and are
P right
now I thought this was a keyboard slam
you guys are actually you guys are in a
room okay oh yeah oh wow okay I thought
you just slammed the keyboard K exactly
what it looks
like I know that's what it looks like C
looking like a slam Oh no you're giving
them hints you're giving come and jam
and slam welcome to the slam jam please
join thank you ma'am there we go amti
who is CM spam I
is all right well I guess that's Mor
somehow oh you have spam color
too you had a Spam color that was
amazing nice oh well while we're at at
Callie's uh you know bullying her for
her name Callie please introduce
yourself so we know that's really you
okay if you say me a s it's me Mory Kai
beh hold live english's hardworking
Shinigami uh I'm in a place with very
terrible internet so I can't stream my
POV but I'm very excited to be here with
all of these lovely ladies as a sheriff
completing my tasks and making sure that
we win the day let's go yes you wouldn't
kill
anybody my job
Cal you're
so but yeah I'm so happy you're joining
even though you can't like stream
properly thank you so much they trained
me well I wanted to show off my new
skills that the dead
beats members fairly recently oh we got
to watch out she's good at the game oh
only thanks to the dead beat you just
ask us how you kill people in this game
true I did just do that okay I guess I
didn't help at all that you played it
recently it was
unhelpful well okay moving on to funa
where is she where is she I can't find
her oh
you can't vote me as the Imposter if I'm
hiding
right
there English promise hello yeah I'm
here does it feel does it feel like
normal now like it still feels weird to
me to hear that introduction
promise yeah I so fresh still it is it
is still pretty fresh but I like it
fresh off I think it's boat freshh off
the boat I feel like everyone the boat
boats yeah what's with this current
Trend in the H life English of watching
school days what's going
on last year finally yeah it was pretty
good about the
Tre there's a staircase did you know
there's a staircase a I know now thanksa
I have no idea what these girl are
talking about good I'm so confused I
don't even know it's too cursed it's
nice that everybody is having fun school
days and all that fun a jolly season it
is great piece of Cinema yeah all right
Iris our number one Christmas lover
hello yes you're number one Christmas
lover here hiis it's Iris from H live
English promise your
yeah yeah um uh I love this game but I I
I really suck at being imposter but yeah
so so yosu yeah but I'll do my best do
you are you really bad at it I don't
remember I I was horrible at imposter
last time I played
this cross her finger she gets imposter
maybe you just need a better mate to
work with cuz you're dumb d m oh
[\h__\h]
little bit of a poopy
head's what you're talking about the
lobby will fall apart it's no problem
but let's take our
time okay yeah by the way have you guys
speaking of Iris have you guys all seen
the yesterday and today's episodes of
the Holo Ian Advent calendar cuz Iris
was very involved in them I was very
involved in them yes it's amazing and
they were both in
3D
space y so Iris why did you do it uh oh
it's cuz you know we needed some light
to bring up the Christmas spirit you
know mhm mhm and what better light than
actual fire right yeah oh that makes
sense and you know it was my whole plan
so that I I could become the Christmas
tree in order to become the Christmas
tree you needed to burn the actual
Christmas true true you took it place
that's kind of messed up
IR it is the master plan it's pretty
late yes very L it was
fire indeed fire fire light the fire
fire fire light the fire light
fire okay uh everybody's uh joining in
again in the lobby I think I'm coming I
got my I freed Comm spam he doesn't
exist
anymore
she's real spam I'm
sad code if I have streamer mode
on yes yes yes it's hidden for me it
does yeah hidden people self
introduction please hi uh bom you I'm
close you sparkling Gem of Hall English
Advent and today I'm a space Rock but
that doesn't mean you're allowed to
Stellar Stellar me out of the ship so I
am not S I am
nice wow
okay that was Prett good you can be nice
sace no no that doesn't work doesn't
work
here man I have to prove yourself prove
the truth you can't fool us people
you're
sus already you're already sus already
why
you I think I think it's her
yeah pretty good
guess okay let's move on
too
police I I H I
know together
we okay
Coco sometimes I become a dragon
sometimes you know but as long as you
know I'm not Chihuahua I'm not FAA
I'm there we go and together we make the
best crew mate you know good dogs good
crew mate not an kind of unfair it's
kind of unfair yeah imposter
it's two of you guys are
ready vote them out right away every
time choice well let's not do that but
indeed as a crew mate they might be very
helpful because it's two brains for one
I guess I
guess who's controlling look controll
I'm the legs you're the brains FL I'm
also the the pointer
finger nice
looking that'll be nice to see one one
day they will play separately but today
is not
today isn't this game on mobile and
maybe somebody could play on mobile I
was I don't know works unfortunately I'm
TR connect really doesn't work on this
side
one well okay and then no
please imposter hi darling remember
being
herea is Raven CR cute I'm an imposter
today because I'm pretending to be M and
yeah I guess so
yeah be yourself oh my gosh fake it till
you make it fake it till you make
it we're we're a nice couple in N aren't
we ironic I should be running away from
you I don't want your child
narissa even if honeyworks made a song
about our child I don't want
it okay and
then
please this is
oron from H life English Pro what H life
English
promise um please don't arrest me I'm
going to be a very good egg for today uh
cuz even if I want to be an impostor I
never get it I almost never get it so
you can trust me I believe her I TR I
trust yes I trust her I trust everyone
what are the chances that she's get I
look so kind pretty high a scientist
none of us will get imposter probably
yeah probably yeah yeah that's how it
works yeah sure how many how many
imposters are we doing I set it to
two sh a deputy I don't know
fre I think three would be too many
yeah
okay and I I have in case you're
interested uh two long tasks and five
short tasks uh as well as two common
tasks I don't remember what common tasks
were that's
suspicious why you don't remember
yeah oh yeah cuz imposters don't do
tasks well it's been too long rolls or
something right like you can do stuff
now or
something like rolls rolls oh yeah
wasn't there something besides crew mate
now like um uh
like imposter like the Spy or something
like yeah yeah if you look at the bottom
left you can see there scientist
Guardian I think it'd be fun yeah okay I
don't know how does that work though I
don't
remember the beginning so wait yeah
there's four rols there I don't know you
girls can probably see them in the
settings uh on the on the computer here
there's a scientist who can access a
portable vitals panel so they can check
at any point of time if there's somebody
dead so they always see the status of
the crew and then there's an engineer
who can use the vents even though
they're not an impostor but then you
might be sused and you have to be like
I'm not the Imposter I just vent because
I can oh that's pretty
cool and then the guardian angel uh is
to go of the very first one of us that
dies oh is that how it works the first
person that dies oh yeah something like
that the garden the Ang is the ghost of
the first Dead crew mate they can
temporarily shield and protect other
living crew mates oh yeah so I guess if
you're the first one that dies you
become the guardian angel and then you
can protect somebody else so that they
don't die yeah if you do it properly and
well timed you'll be able to prevent
imposters from killing their victims
sounds amazing me throwing so that I can
become the
garden
a already
are and then there's a shape shifter who
can who can change the appearance and
disguise themselves as other crew mates
why would you do that though that just
confuses everyone makes an impost easier
to move or they're not even imp harder
to find too because then you know the
Imposter can say I'm the engineer and oh
no I'm the shape you know please I
promise I'm not a murderer it doesn't
say that it's only impostor but why
would why wouldn't why would a crew mate
do this I don't know why would that one
off but I like the other ones yeah
should I should I keep them or should I
I think you should keep them it'd be fun
oh it is okay yeah it just doesn't say
so so wait does only one impostor is
only one imposter The Shape Shifter is
that how it works oh can set how many
there will be I can say
two I can say we want two or I can say
we I want one or zero I can set it in
the
settings but if I do one then only one
of the uh imposters will be Shape
Shifter but only 50% chance the one will
be oh yeah I can I can make it higher
too that we have one for
sure really default it's good right it's
probably the
default okay okay default then let's
keep the rolls then let's go we're going
straight to the
Fung before
we before before we go um can we have
the visual tasks off because if we have
it on it might be too easy visual tasks
off oh
yeah yes very good okay and before we
start I'm Tak I organized this thing the
logo and the thumbnails are commissioned
by me so
problem don't kill me because I I pay
for this okay don't kill
me right
we byebye byebye
byebye God damn it I told you I was
going to be
innocent see I'm always innocent like
what the heck do I do water
can
okay I'm not really
sure it's either the game loves me who
is coming
up am I supposed to oh
okay oh that's not
cool
that's not
cool no no that is
weird now I'm
going there we
go I hate
this
done
clean you know F Moko actually seems
kind of
suspicious no
no I'll miss you by
you guys the only real astronaut you
know what that means we don't have a
chance of getting back to our own
[Music]
Planet unbelievable so who saw Watson I
didn't see her at all I I didn't see her
at all oh no I didn't see her while she
was alive who who reported just now me I
did tell us about it did tell us about
it where was the body so I was going
around
Communications um trying to figure out
the mushrooms and went not and I went
down uh the the little zipline and then
in the storage room Amy was
dead Storage storage
room we saw around the bus room yeah you
saw
me wait so F was also in the storage
area no no we were at the mushrooms and
we were having problems with that and
crony Senpai was around and then crony
Senai went down but for Senpai was there
too yeah
um Moco was chasing me
around conf I don't know what's going on
I have mushroom problems yes I had like
a meat problem I don't know like I
suddenly turned into like a a lighter
pink and there was like a chunk of meat
chasing me what was
that puff and then they CH into people
or something like that what does that do
is that just an effect to freak you out
or does it do something uh I think it I
think the the the mushroom like if you
touch it or something um it hides the
the people so you can just like kill
them and run away and they wouldn't be
able to tell who kill my skin or
something like
that oh did I why do you know that
H yeah my skin got swapped as well yeah
me too that's SK oh that's new and then
I had a little worm next to me for a
moment and then poof it was gone and the
light was back
on but know what what goes on in this m
i I don't know I feel like I trusted
crony Senpai and now I feel like I don't
trust crony Senpai talking a
lot I will say I passed by and I was
actually running away from crony cuz it
felt like she was chasing me I didn't
even see
you where are
you you you followed me
the
really
who
there oh damn
lby okaybye
okay I don't know the fact that she had
like her own like um
name okay
okay silly silly
Iris that was weird I didn't even see
you oh wait whoops not supposed to use
this
I guess it's f m then cuz like that was
very
uh a random way that was just random
voting maybe it's full MOA and
Nissa cuz like I genuinely did not see
it that's what I mean like if you touch
the mushroom um has that weird thing
going on
wait wait I found Nissa like five
seconds ago though is in
the part of the map with the lab in the
hallway I don't that's
unexpected wait that I really didn't see
her though I saw narissa around like
next to the greenhouse when I was I was
moving to the laboratory she's above the
green
house I saw her walking around I didn't
see anyone near her see anyone else yeah
I only
saw last time oh did she I see we didn't
see anyone except Senai and I think
she's good wait I forget who voted me
out ran away instantly cuz I trust
anyone who voted for crony in the last
what was were trying to get her out
because they no I Ved her because
dead
a tell us before huh H yeah I know three
people going to start yeah to kill her
who did
it I don't think they'll admit
it
true is the third could have been an
imposter though honestly like I don't
know yeah did you guys turn off
the oh it doesn't say oh it doesn't I
would have put behind her if she
self-recorded because look at her look
at her Iris you lying out your butt
supicious I don't know I don't know I
don't know you wouldn't be this
suspicious unless you were the impostor
in your Shir I'm not I swear to God I'm
not I I I I set out right that I saw
like narissa pass by just 5 seconds ago
before her death if it was actually me I
wouldn't say that my goodness I didn't
see you though uh no I was I passed by
her last night I'm currently at the
meeting room I went the opposite
direction that's why I think stuck that
b and Iris seni are suspicious I think
so too why you doing not I was walking
around I was in the L the L wait where's
my the lab and then was on 10 seconds
I'm vo
B I was I don't have enough
inoc it's not me I swear it's not me I
failed to protect you guys a that's
cute my God
is we get
him
oh there are so many external imposters
damn five I thought we won yeah
Tombstone wow excuse me you didn't even
notice I was dead
guys passed me and biu killed me
immediately good team report good team
you two that was pretty funny nice one
Tombstone let's go yay was surprised
well you know what we learned from that
because call was pretty quiet sus out
the quiet quiet
ones fooled me cie he fooled me
too strategy I was just confused cuz
like my voting was super rushed I was
like wait wait why am I suspicious all
of a
sudden literally just Spiderman
everybody pointing at each other no one
it was peer pressure peer you don't have
have to vote if you don't know true we
don't have to vote I just felt like I
needed to vote I mean that's Iris I
thought it needed to be like majority
vote to even get anyone off I thought to
I didn't think was enough to kill me the
setting a little bit of
a
yeah strong at this H we're good pretty
good doing our tasks aren't you the on
thought you guys were
I guess we say no matter what you can't
be
helped well that was a good first round
let's let's try to be you know we an
extended voting time oh
sure uh it's currently 90 seconds should
we do 120 or at least a little yeah at
least 120 12
Max that should be good CH says
apparently we can vote or skip the vote
if you're not confident like who it is
you don't have to yeah pretty confident
pretty
confident talking certainty there pretty
confident voting out all yeah I was
pretty
confid the the confidence isable then
you maybe cannot trust your
confidence yeah true
enough all right then let's start
another round
yay even though this is really fun here
thank you crony for finding
this see you on the other side bye bye
see you guys bye I told
you I told you I'll never be
impostor not in this lifetime no
sir watering
can
could be the name you think
so wrong wrong
way that's kind of
suspicious that's
weird I don't know why foka Always seems
so suspicious they're just like minding
their own business what the heck did I
just
do that looks
burnt okay they're just going around
together that's nice
beautiful I feel like someone should
have died by
now okay it's just
there
okay oh
whoops wait how do I get in
here wait
what
wait I can't get in here oh wait no just
just go around don't
worry what the heck is
this oh no someone
died wait I shouldn't be doing
this it's kind of catch
[Music]
you I got to
stop no not again come on yeah come
[Music]
on what all right I'll break it down for
you oh please what I did all my tasks
you guys could see me I think some of
you saw me watering things in the the
mushroom place I moved some storage
around roasted some marshmallows went up
to do my tasks in the communication room
what do I find Watson dead middle of the
floor I didn't see anyone leave though
anyone near Communications recently
where's communication top right top like
a what is it up the zipline wire zipline
zipline I'm far from it for a little bit
but we didn't see much I just Zine yeah
I was just in the jungle
area yeah I know there was there was
like oh oh okay these white white things
are okay yeah the line you can go up and
down but yeah I wasn't there yet um in
the bottom right um there was a lot of
shape shifting I don't know who is who
yeah there was a lot what happened with
that the mush is that the mushroom stuff
working on everyone everybody everybody
got a skin shift right yeah it's so we
don't know who is who and then we can't
prove like oh that person was there or
whatever they all look different like
not each other right so it's not shape
shifting yeah no it's just the mushroom
power
yeah yes oh by the way I just want to
say I haven't used it yet but I am the
engineer mushroom it does it oh I I can
vent but I'm not the The Imposter just
saying I didn't use it yet though I
wonder recently was anyone around upper
engine Lookout or mining pit because the
impostor may have tried to escape by
going down the ladders I will check it
out I was walking that way but I didn't
see anyone okay I've been down over in
the left area for the whole time doing
my tasks so I haven't even gone over
there yet I haven't been up there yet I
have Tas and
communication I was going to go up I'm
currently passing it was passing by the
greenhouse I was going to go up but and
then yeah I went up the first time no I
didn't hard to tell still hard to
tell yeah but people was kind of quiet
just saying actually bi boo passed by me
and didn't kill me so maybe you two are
imp again me this is the first time I'm
doing Tas I can tell you I've been doing
water with narissa and then I did the
marshmallow thing and I game I sh
asteroids and I haven't been up there
yet so I I do have up
there okay we'll see we'll see evidence
inconclusive but keep your eyes open
yeah and maybe don't don't go alone
don't go around alone guys go with a
buddy hopefully it's not the
bud we don't need a
buddy
[Music]
fine well going back to whatever was I
was doing which was going to the
greenhouse uh it's this
way what the heck how do I go oh I
know this looks like
a whatever it is
what oh it's
gardening
damn it I really got to stop
this uh fix the
[Music]
antenna all right
okay that's not
good
[Music]
what who just
died I knew she was
innocent suspicious though she was I
passed her going down the ladders from
communication to the L
part maybe went up the commun where'd
you find her so I was going up the
ladder to the communication and I didn't
really see her body but um I saw the the
vent which is the plant kind of opening
up and then closing so they vented
to yeah they vented to wherever it is
from Communications
oh oh does anyone know where where the
vents from Communications conect go
anywhere right I think all the vents can
only usually I don't know in Old Maps
usually vents only connect to other
events see I should have checked and
then I could have told you but too bad
no
idea I I can kind of say I think crony
is not self-reporting at least because
like I feel like I was I was running
around with her a little bit alone yeah
I saw you yeah yeah and she didn't and
then I saw Cali running around around I
think we were alone for a little bit but
she may have been on cool down as well
but she yeah she was coming down from
that she was she was coming down from
that area yeah I told you I crossed
paths with her oh okay but yeah and Cory
said someone vented
[Music]
H where were you a good question where
at the beach the beach we're just kind
of going around but we don't really
understand I don't know what's going on
the map here if you hit tab it'll show
you where you are oh tab yeah hit tab
the map will pop up there's also the map
icon on the top the map
icon yeah the top right a there's a
setting I see a map but I don't
understand it it has a lot of marks on
it yeah a lot of marks that is that is
it exclamation
marks a lot of marks on it does it have
some x's on it no no I'm
curious question not the marks I mean I
don't see so many marks on my map yeah
what does an impostor see maybe does a
previous impostor want to tell us what
they saw like Kelly yeah Kelly I saw
some xes with circles on time and i'
click them
sabotage a lot of marks on the
screen marks
I'm do you have anything to say to
defend yourself we just doing our
tasks the map we have
everybody I guess we can t along happen
to
the
Goodbye
byee by bye-bye
I hope we don't regret that see you
later oh wait whoops okay
um wait where am I let's go together or
not shoot the
comals
beautiful some nice nice chopping skills
very nice and like a real Chef
now so fauna has been kind of
quiet maybe I'll point it out
later h
why is no one doing
it it's real real
suspicious
okay it's been fixed
okay I just have trust issues
okay
who who's dead cie
wait I just saw her like yeah I saw her
too yeah just saw her too I feel like I
saw her body right underneath the the
ladder the the left ladder um you can
check the map you can check the map and
see exactly where the Greenhouse Green
House close to the greenhous yeah wasn't
she just with me at around like yeah I
saw everyone at communications and I was
getting some stuff done there and the
and also the lookout and then I went
down and I saw her I guess she moved
fast and then
died is there anyone around there I'm in
the lookout right now I'm in the mining
pit I was a around I think when everyone
was around um we all went to
Communications home everyone like uh
everyone
except uh who was it like R Rissa and
FAA uh I think they were around like
Communications and like Lookout and then
everyone else went to the other coms
um I am sorry FAA but it seemed you were
being just um you know a little very
cautious I don't know if you were
careful about being stacked killed but
you moved away from the the radio like
where everyone was trying to fix it
and well you needed to go do the other
thing right to fix it I was the first
one there in the radio and I tried to
put in the code but I think you have to
put in a second
code yeah also I had two tasks that I
did in Communications oh
okay did them cuz I was I was on Lookout
I was putting the code in I think I was
the first who arrived and then nothing
was happening so I I thought I would go
to the other one and I saw Cali was like
doing the code at that point as well so
she was like she already arrived and
then I left her alone there and I was
about to go up to the other
communication thingy but then uh it was
already fixed so then I went back and I
saw I think I saw crony again or so I
didn't see fauna and I didn't see Iris
at all I saw you Kiara all of you guys I
don't know I I saw all of you guys the
communications I was I was with alone
for a while and she didn't kill
me I saw Nissa go down go down I didn't
I was going to the green going down
where are you right now um I ended up in
the lookout because I got lost and I was
very
confused aren't we
all yeah little suspicious of crony cuz
she didn't vote for fu
Mo we have no time running off of
supicious enough to vote [\h__\h]
yeah I I don't know either I'm going to
skip you're going to skip
but skipping
no good luck crew
mates I guess I'm
just a suspicious this
person well what about me as suspicious
I
wonder what are you doing what are you
doing here that's so weird you are
weirding me
out okay thank
you oh okay she's
alive um this and this
this mcus is fine I think she's actually
doing her stuff
so what the heck is
this look ridiculous can I
pet I can't
pet oh you can go to the mines how I
don't even know you can do
that honestly I shouldn't be standing so
near the
BS mushroom
mixup interesting I guess that that's a
new
sabotage it's too
quiet it's too
quiet okay everyone's still
alive
uh hello hello hello help me I think no
is trying to kill me ah you are so I
can't believe you I was not I checked
everyone's vitals and I decided to go
back to the meeting canell and I saw her
and I got a little scared so I ran back
but then she chilled so I thought it was
cool but then she hit the emergency
meeting button much to my surprise no
the thing is there's a little bit of a a
back story I was running around and the
only people back story yeah my Tas what
do you mean
backstory I was running around I was I
was you know I I I was running around
crony alone she didn't kill me I was
running around FAA alone she didn't kill
me and both of those I kind of fought
were sus and then I found you and you
kind of followed me and now I think if
it's not cron if it's not fa I follow
you what do you mean I ran into you and
then I ran back to the meeting area
you are so fake
K I was also around crony and she did
not kill me either yeah she even though
could have and as I was doing tasks I
could have killed crony too and I didn't
which I would have if I had the
opportunity to if I was well tell me
everybody tell me Iris uh and tell me
fauna what are the remaining tasks that
you have I'm done with tasks I'm also
done with tasks yeah I saw yeah B sorry
if you felt like I was chasing you I I I
was kind of scared I was kind of scared
you were like stick to me like little
time yeah I have I have a task to do at
the dock okay and I have one at the
cafeteria then do it and then we win um
task win let's go guys yeah also I think
people who are done with the tasks can
um follow just wait in the meeting area
or follow yeah I mean we have to do the
tasks we can't just wait in the meeting
no no no like people who are done with
the tasks can follow people around so
that they wouldn't get killed I think I
do think nissa's a little bit Marissa
you and me Let's Stay Together if I'm
dead soon thenay with you no we're
staying together whether you want it or
not we're staying together now uh I'll
actually tag along with you guys if
that's okay just to see if one of you
die is there wait then maybe you two are
the imposters no I'm done with my tasks
as the thing so I don't they want to
kill me it is kind of scary oh my God I
didn't kill you when you were
around yeah what the yeah oh you two
didn't kill each other because you're
both oh my God come with me and why you
depending it on the blue women yeah
let's just all stay together and we'll
see what the blue women do oh my God
this is
discrimination no I'm all done follow
Iris we should pressure her yeah let's
follow Iris okay yeah yeah you can
totally follow me yeah okay nice hey who
it for me me little [\h__\h] wait am I
getting okay okay good you better you
little [\h__\h] love you please don't kill
me
okay all right well let's
see let's
follow all right
hovering on the report she's taking a
little too long kind of
weird y task win who was
it excuse me I was it was desk what who
was the
impost who were the impos wonder who it
was it
was doing so good put us on
[Laughter]
the I'm sorry I was suspicious of you
fa I'm sorry I was suspicious of
[Music]
you f and Iris why didn't you kill me we
were for long I wanted to keep someone
on my
side and because crony was susing fun in
the beginning I was like maybe I should
keep her on my side and kill crony
instead and like I I saw that Iris was
uh going into the same room as uh
narissa was so I was kind of waiting
outside the room to see if she killed I
think she s I was trying to kill I was
trying to kill you actually um when you
were inside the lab I was I was
following you and I was going to kill
you but then I noticed you were moving
weirdly and you were like running away
and then Marissa came comes in right
away like oh never mind I can't kill
you went back I think I was playing a
little bit too cautiously but um so
difficult there's only there's only me
that's I I was I was worried it was
still pretty good
yeah that was still impressive yeah I
can't I can't believe you suspected
me I
Wasing
Wasing all well it ends well hopefully
when we're together alone in the males
nothing don't drown me in the ocean
please
yeah oh sorry I was stuck let me just
I'm here sorry Jo us
um I don't want to like you know make
any hard rules because you know you just
kill whoever is conveniently there but
please do not kill Amy right away next
[Music]
round no no no we need our we need our
space on out to do her job kill me first
I love being the ghost I want to see
some detective work yeah no
pressure okay we complete I changed one
thing I changed that the votes uh you
can't see who voted for who yeah that's
good trying to vote
someone oh boy let's go all right good
luck see you later
bye [\h__\h] yeah I'm so sorry for
swearing
um as you know let's say I'm like
looking through here blah blah blah blah
blah and
then have to go through
here there's a lot of stuff going on
here yep doing
this and then let's sabotage things
okie dokie and then I do this and then
this and then close cuz why
not
then like that I should really kill like
one person at the very
least
yippe
yippe I can't find
anyone hello oh for a moment I thought
you were dead again hello
oh no
no well all right hope is dead detective
I just saw her alive like less than 30
seconds ago where must have just
happened I just found it in the meeting
room but I was up in the drop ship if
you looked the map and then I went down
and I found her body there and bio was
up there and fauna was up there and bibu
looked like she came from down below so
I'm a little sus from Australia because
I knew no one would kill you so I
thought it' be safe for that's down
under
sorry was following the both of us
though so I'm kind of
s I was just making sure no funny
business was going on who was around the
area like less than 30 seconds before
she was found dead like I it felt like
like 10 seconds before so I'm I'm like
What's Happening that was a really fast
yeah I only passed by in that area it
was like bi Boo and fauna and that's it
I say in that area specifically I saw
see anyone like coming from that
direction I saw that bishu was around
the storage room and then I was using
the
zipline and like bishu wasn't taking the
zipline up with me
yet oh Well people would you like to
defend
yourself I was following Amy because I
no one was going to kill Amy so I
thought Amy was a safe but a saw you
didn't she not following her but coming
from a different direction no I was
following a this entire
time running away from you I didn't see
you I was following you the entire do
you want to kill her why are you
following
her this is voice conclusive I've done
one task so far it was asteroids I
haven't done the rest because asid I was
following yeah the asteroids didn't you
do asteroids in the last one to what
what is the asteroids one
like EXC maybe she has her favor I went
straight to
Communications mus are we going to skip
I are we going to
skip I feel like
she's by the way Iris I don't know if
you know but you mut oh it's because
she's dead oh never mind
yes she's muted for real this time she
is dead I just wanted to make sure she
joins the conversation you
know may tells
us
I or one
[Music]
of byebye
people I mean we wouldn't be able to
tell us I didn't even vote for her I
voted I just skipped oh
I didn't vote for you people it wasn't
me oh thank you I just
like
bye
bye okay I'm going to go over here and
be like yep I'm having a party right
here yep that's a
thing that's a thing that I'm doing
okay and then I use
this and then they're all over here so
I'm going to do
this it's VA I watched her kill FL oh
[\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
I knew it huh she's dead she's
dead the switch the mus maybe a shap
shifter maybe that's a shape shifter no
that makes it so much worse I went I
know it's not bio because I went down
because I saw bi boo pass us we were
both waiting to get into the kitchen
because last round Fu Moko and I were
frying fish together right so as I was
waiting I went to get cuz I was like
Advent together
strong it was right in front of the
kitchen it was right in front of the
kitchen is where is where the death just
happened and I saw someone running up to
the Splash Zone so where was everybody
and don't
lie wait you found which which of the
two bodies did you find I don't I don't
know where I don't know where
it then I have something to add I was
just up at the very top of the
communications and there was crony and
there was fauna first there was fauna
and me and everything was cool then
crony joined I left and now fa is dead
okay can you confirm
this um after I was uh doing the ladder
task I went down to the zip line again
after that was done so I didn't really
see you saw up there yeah I saw Kiara
and fauna up there and then after I was
done with the ladder I went down the
zipline and I couldn't see anything else
aside from that maybe someone vent I'm
not really sure cuz it's kind of a short
time
you I mean I
know I know I wouldn't do my alibi
really quick and I saw bi Boo and we
were alone and she didn't come after me
or anything but I was in the Splash Zone
in the beginning I collected shells and
then I left okay where were you though
at the time of the
murder I went up to stor Happ I reported
it immediately yeah I I know I went to
Splash Zone and I collected the shells
and then I saw bioo and she didn't hurt
me and then I went back to storage okay
and then crony FAA and kiata were over
in Communications yeah so Watson where
were you I was at the
laboratory laboratory I I am s of a
because Iris was around me fa and Amy
yeah I am too and now so now I'm Su it
trying to vote someone off no cuz the
last the last murder the everyone who
was present we know that it wasn't fa
now and obviously iris is dead so it's
only you or bio but I know where bi was
the time of the murder that the first
round I reported the body and both biu
and faer were with me and none of them
said that they bi even said that she was
following me the whole time but she
didn't see me kill anyone
huh for crony trust me trust
me yeah I trust you I
trust who are we voting for
I'm selfreported
[Laughter]
no what are boats yes oh my God impostor
gone
bye-bye says no I don't know Kiara is
really suspicious right sorry okay see
you
later whoops
okay ooh oh that's a thing
cool cool
cool oh wait I want to haunt let's
see uh I should have killed more my
bad all right let's
see m uh let's block that off so that
it'll be okay oh wait where'd she
go
wait why is
Kiara an
impostor wa I thought it was cie that
was the
impostor oh shape shift oh
okay oh wait no I should stop using that
I should have went for the reactor what
was I thinking ah
silly then after that's done I should
probably go
for
the
okay let's do the reactor
then oh no I got stabil
ized nobody
chatted I want to separate
these let's
see
look oh no reisa I I wanted to check if
anyone and re's dead a yeah I didn't I
was wondering
too I I think Kiara is safe yeah cuz we
just did the emergency thing together
yeah and then I'mma joined right when we
finished it I ran away both of you guys
are I thought both of you guys imposter
and you were going to kill me
no I why do you think it's I really
because the first death was Iris and me
FAA and Iris were the ones that were
closest to each other
and yeah well that's and now I'm scared
I know it's not Kiara because Kiara
didn't kill me or anything
so okay I still have three tasks left by
the way but wait so why did why did you
just call him eating
because I was wondering if anyone
because we're about to finish our tasks
and you don't want us to finish our
tasks I was too quiet and I was scared
if anyone was going to die and I thought
like might as well chat and Kelly what
were you doing I went down to mushrooms
mhm and what's the last task you did the
Sorting the mushrooms into the jars and
the crystals okay K has been quiet yeah
I mean ask me any questions you want but
if you talk too much you get so just ask
me any questions and I'll tell
you what's the last task you
did um I don't remember was in
the I can't ask chat too because I can't
even look at chat um I know this sounds
suspicious but yeah I don't
remember I'm going to vote for a I think
yeah you're the Imposter you're just you
called the meeting because we're so
close to finishing our tasks that you're
scared no [\h__\h] the trash
scar aren't we all I mean I saw cie and
she didn't kill me and I was running
away from you guys cuz I thought you
guys were going to kill me so H that's
my defense yeah okay we going to leave a
vote okay oh you guys if you guys vote
for me you're wrong just so you know uh
oh I'm gonna vote for
Celly
or call you most sus cuz I saw you I saw
Kar and B together and you guys didn't
die so unless you're both the impos
no we're not uhhuh that's exactly what
an impostor would
say well you think everyone if there was
two imposters alive we would lose by now
so there's only oh okay true so one of
the previous was well crony I guess was
the one that got knocked out right so
wouldn't that be yeah yeah huh I don't
know
he know I say we just Skip and continue
doing our tasks unless you guys are if I
was the impostor i' try to vote one you
guys out right now and then I'd probably
win so I'm going to skip you guys are
wrong regret your
decision right oh Callie
gaming are we winning please what all
right how many more oh sorry
sorry yeah no you
can't
just kill just kill just kill there's
only three left just
kill just kill it's not this it's not
this it's not this it's not
this let's
freaking oh Kell
G wacky it wasn't me my god well played
well
that was
wild so actually I turned into that's
her she was oh turned into fun I see see
we thought Kelly was quiet too
but [\h__\h] I'm so sorry I'm how do I ever
redeem myself to you it's too late it's
too
late believe me
I I'm not a real amig
goling
I tried to protect her and now I'm the
one that killed
her s yeah I can't I'm sorry I can't
believe I got imposter
twice ly good at lying I've been
watching professional Japanese Among Us
players recently oh wow yeah everybody's
just Poker Face the whole time had
practice
War you guys you didn't listen to
me damn it and I still didn't get
impostor a single time
man maybe next time you'll get it you'll
be super good a little more time let's
go next
round next I the way the ghosts uh were
going in their own channel did you have
fun yes yes oh recommend it it was fun I
don't know why recommend it crony was
probably too guilty to
join oh wait there's a dead voice chat I
didn't even
know voice CH I was like why isn't she
joining I was like probably because she
feels guilty oh no I don't feel guilty
at
all Abol feel any shamey just randomly
get voted off too cuz I don't remember
like everybody yeah I got voted up I was
like oh no
for that
what new yeah cuz I told you yeah yeah I
told you to believe me see oh it was
actually good what I did thank she was
right you were so right easy way to tell
easy way to tell if if kie is imposter
she's quiet if she's imposter
all so I don't know bye you are the Imp
wait okay now I'm getting scared cuz
I've never like gotten this much stuff
before
like now I'm scared you
know
like H yeah
there
we it's so fun
how do I get in here oh yeah okay I got
in
here yeah and the reactor cuz why
not and then like
this no
nice man what are these people
doing okay uh let's see I want to use
this and go
down oh man I hope there's someone who's
just
randomly like in
there ooh I hope I can do a stack kill
over
[Applause]
there oh wait it's already
okay
I didn't even see I didn't even see I
didn't even really see I didn't f wa I
didn't even really
see just there wait two people what what
happened was that wait who did I see no
no no no it wasn't me I where were you
where were you when you pressed
it who pressed it wait where was I I
pressed it uh I was oh my God I was so
in my tangent oh my God I went up to the
top right to the communications and I
was just Tangen thing and doing a task
and suddenly I see a dead body but on
the same spot I think I saw at least one
more person maybe another maybe two
people I think so K
Iris and then I just came into the room
and I saw Callie
outside we I just the ladder all of a
sudden Communications well we went the
line with the same time and then I was
trying to go in the way to the mushroom
door but I got rid of the mushrooms but
uh maybe killed by
accident maybe it's just Amis him by
being silly uhhuh wait
what wait I'm me you were there right
when I reported right no I I just walked
into the room like after cie she was
already in there like alive and you guys
were all doing the power thing or
whatever and I was also starting to do
the power thing putting in the code but
then you guys finished it and then
somebody reported Callie's body so I
didn't even see it wait so you're saying
besides me there was Cali and you
inside the
[Music]
communications was on the other side of
the mushroom wall so I don't think they
could kill her on the other side of the
mushroom wall but I don't know yeah I
just went up the ladder was how it went
and then all of a sudden report there
might there was one other person in
there but it was hard to see cuz
everybody was bunched up I think it I
saw purple yeah purple was was was
Call's dead body no no the purple is
beo that purple we do have something to
report
yeah we
heard okay you are the and the
M we were thinking maybe this am
being that's good thing that we we do
that I heard that I thought she was
saying someone else and now trying can
we have someone who has a talk talk
please me me me yes so um I was at
communications I saw a bunch of people
there and I was trying to like uh do my
task and like I was still on the task
when it happened so I didn't really see
anything oh so you were also in
Communications until this report okay
wait you were there even now when when I
reported you were still
there um yeah yeah oh so you were one of
the other people I where I wasn't sure
who am I seeing Oh
[\h__\h] well I remember this I will
remember
this but
oh a
[Music]
joke okay well seems to be a hot place
there so I'm going to go and work on
this and then it's kind of popular over
there so I'm going to block that off
maybe I'll go to the
kitchen most people don't really go
there
actually what wait wait what they just
killed everyone they just destroyed
yeah there was like a crowd of people at
communication wait did did
you did you guys kill four people
go
yeah wow see The Quiet Ones it's always
the quiet ones I knew cronia never
hasn't said anything but I was talkative
last round that's I
you
both
innocent I thought it was too sounded
but was susing for was susing Amit right
because of her statement but it
wasn't
purpose
webe she just being silly High the two
imposters would of course vote for fuo
oh I
see you I'm sorry oh my God this is what
happened okay next we we got to go that
was fast you guys want to do a different
ma don't give it to the blue people next
time
people ah yeah okay I'm really good with
like you know all this imposs
stuff I'm happy
[Music]
now yeah I guess that's a
task and then get this out of the way
sorry I got really excited that I was
imposter I swore I don't know what
happened to me that time but
I'm sure someone's going to fix it I
don't want to get stack kills
so let's
see I'm going to
[Music]
die oh uh this one no this one
no
this oh that one's so
fun
what just
happened I ran up because of the
communications thing was down and she
was right there in Communications in
front of the the
thingy I was at the other I was at the
other I was with but I didn't see her
body I was down by the dock I was in the
labs oh me um oh yeah I just met crony
in the yeah
yeah Iris and I are doing the other task
the power thing kill each other we're
safe AR maybe some
T what
Nissa where were you I was down by the
dock I I figured that you probably all
were going there and I wanted to keep
doing my tasks so I just went down and I
was doing a sand castle and then I was
checking since yeah don't the
I passed I passed the Tex yeah they
disappear but if you pass them you can
still do them oh okay yeah I was
checking manually okay no or if you just
still like remember where they were
before it went down
yeah well Mo
reactor
reactor whatas what were you doing at
the reactor we're doing our task we're
just trying
to
to use the map I don't like the map I
like finding the little yellow mark on
the the screen it's more fun now you
know now you know what mark it
ising the
yellow what I actually haven't done that
yet the yellow there marshmallow is so
cute it's little Among
Us uh the marshmallow oh the
marshmallows
[Applause]
yeah so inconclusive but what task were
you doing
yeah the marshmallows are nowhere near
the
Rea that was that was before yeah but
what were you doing today huh we doing a
bunch of in the
reactor what were you doing in the
reactor yeah what were you doing in the
re kind of
su I vote for now I'll give you guys the
benefit of the D thank you please don't
kill us
again
oh jeez what is that
[Music]
scree oh they're so
cute uh I don't want to do
it I I I don't want to do it I don't
want to do it I don't want to do
it okay
okay
uh nice
okay wonder what she's doing
chilling
nice that's my
motto don't trust I'm going to drink
set so strange strange
strange strange how they're all going
together wait where where am I supposed
to go wait wait wait wait I can't find
my task here where is my stuff oh
[Laughter]
here there we
go
where's the mining oh gosh darn
it pow
pow really
Amy it wasar it
was killed don't believe there do you
see I saw people kill am I am medic I am
medic I can see people's vitals yeah and
I can see you kill am is that how it
works I am I can see people's miles I
have three battery charges
everying how many people are alive this
is the first time I hadic I saw Ki no
people no no this is hard for me because
just I had just seen bibu and but I did
not see kiata I was going down and she
didn't follow me so she might have
realized she was alone with a but uh
bioo also when she killed me
self-reported and then immediately this
is literally the first time I've gone to
scientist and I have this is the first
time I played it so how would I know
that I have three charges of scientist
yeah she did say it was kind of her
first time in a while uh the body is up
the
station I
saw was it you probably just looked up
some guide about
those actually time I have whatever
scientists whatever I can check people
well I was I was so often alone with
others and I didn't kill them so why
would I you know can somebody vouch for
me cuz I think I was Al alone together
with a lot of
people come
on for a while but I was not alone with
Kiara yeah I was Kara for like a Split
Second I was with s times alone and I
saw crony several times I think alone
and I saw narissa like maybe one or two
times
alone yeah it felt like um either Kiara
or fa was going to kill me cuz like they
were just kind of walking around so I
stuck around one of them to make sure I
didn't get killed um it would kind of
check out if Kiara was the impostor
though I believe
wow okay I'm
sorry goodbye forever thanks forever H
what was it I I love you or I'm thank
you die thank you
forever
well somebody's not
voting I just accepted that you guys are
voting me me out but I guess you'll
you'll you're running on the
clock it's so sad I I was always with
you
guys it's so sad I you goodbye goodbye I
will go up like a phoenix and I will
rise like a
phoenix yum Fried
Chicken
okay let's go going to go going to
go
mine
mine why is she following me around
getting suspicious getting kind of
paranoid you don't want to make me
paranoid why cuz I'm
paranoid you don't want to mess with me
when I'm
paranoid oh
strange
okay how difficult is
that oh so both has to be
active Okay that's the case that
okay
weird Okay
strange strange how you put it there
specifically
hello
hello I I cuz I I I believe it's F what
really like when we were going to when
comms were down we were going up I see I
see like um many of us were going up I
think it was like I think I saw fa beu
um I also saw I was also with crony and
Nissa alone none of us killed each other
um and we were all going up to comms but
then I see F coming down from comms
ignoring the fact that comms is do the
bottom one first right we just try to do
the tasks and you know at the Top If you
were at the top you would do the top one
right but we're just counting on we're
focusing on our task yeah you can't see
the tasks on the map when comms are down
you yeah you can't see yeah you can but
if you walk around you can find them
that's that's what we did last time
too % ear that's why I
decided talking at once and I can't get
anything that's how we play
a time what's what's a task you did
what's the task you did the
green green house doing what
why' you you you come came back down
from comms even though comms is
sabotaged all the way back down to the
greenhouse the green housee is
pretty green greenhous is
pretty you got
[Laughter]
a who are the cutest puppies who are
[Music]
wow Liars look at the Little Liars
oh cute Little
Liars just about bowing it cute cute
Little Liars the sequel to Pretty Little
Liars don't be like I make a grave
mistake
[Music]
byebye
goodbye bye come on
for yeah don't don't um delay your death
it's yeah it's inevitable it's time to
go excuse
me that's like a death metal byebye
puppies
[Music]
yay
funny so
good that was really good susing out
Iris that was impressive yeah that was
good from the reactor too even the last
round when when we almost voted them out
cuz they didn't know what they were
doing at the
reactor that made me 80% sure and then I
saw them going down from com oh yeah
yeah definitely what Tes where crew mate
will do the
exact me
yes I'm so sorry it's okay I trying to
survive I think I think out of this
whole group of people me and fle are
like the worst Liars so it wasn't a good
combination I was my your B
my we were so bad to
was
yeah M makes me
laugh I make M laugh too you you see see
I I had the good the good life you know
I did the marshmallows and then she goes
oh we did that last
[Laughter]
time oh my god well at least I finally
got imposter do we don't want to do one
more round yeah oh can we try hide and
seek for the last game change the yeah
hide and seek hide and seek hide andek
uh hide andek sounds fun it's like
hideand-seek like how you'd really think
hideand-seek would
be for hideand-seek wasn't there an
actual setting for hide and seek yeah
there there is there is uh you might
have to make a new room though maybe um
if you can't change it in the settings
um on the computer yeah then you might
have to make a new room is it yeah no I
don't think you can change it here M
okay
then I'll make a new one
okay okay it's kind of like it's pretty
much like playing tag yeah cute yeah um
any preferred
map let's do the oh yeah yeah let's
do
nice I'll send you the link in the group
uh the the in the group mhm okay this
chaotic but really fun thank you I've
never done it before oh it's fine and
it's a short game too
so let's go
perfect man scary this one this is like
the only time I actually want to be
imposter yeah it's pretty fine I never
want to be impost ever again for this
say we don't have to mute for this oh no
I don't think no
reason
okay just try not to give away your
location on accident I guess we can mute
if we're
done uh yeah like move to the yeah we
don't have to
really yeah in this game
hey wait we can we can hide in V oh is
there only
one oh is this like
zombies why
you oh we're really slow do tasks and
the timer goes down quicker so slow we
have three minutes to hide
left three minutes to hi she's in the
med
Bay engine she's
coming what wait
what oh man is she green she's green
she's green what
color oh
wow everybody's clumping together
everyone's
dying where is she right now can make
down quick my
[Music]
God is that
call wait how does this
work
oh no name tags oh no you can hear the
music come close to you when she's close
by that's
scary crony where's
crony don't say it
yeah oh
no oh that's fun that's so quick you
that was so short another one another
one can we can we pi increase the speed
for both the impostor and the the the
the crew
mates can we increase the speed for both
crew mates and I want to also I I uh I
think I have to make a new Lobby because
I don't think I can change the amount of
uh Seekers oh there's only one Seeker
one oh yeah it's fine to leave it on one
we just need to speed up so we're all
running really
fast okay maximum oh too fast
too this is how it should oh jeez oh
boy
go yumy let's
go let's
go I think so oh I hope so I'm going to
be Unleashed for my you might even be
faster honestly no yeah I did okay oh
God where do I go do we have to do task
do your
taskas I don't see them I see tasks I
really want to finish that
task it's all
good why do I have
no I'm SC hear I hear the base we got to
win we got to win this I can't find you
guys what the heck everyone oh it's so
fast the task task task task task
task not her going on the vacation with
her oh Jee I'm not even near you
terrifying
a horror game all of a sudden on
this terrifying screams
[Music]
here going
louder this is so much more chaotic yeah
it's so Chao
get in trouble maybe I should you hear
the guitar you're
like she
[Music]
coming hold it
together oh God my eyes are
[Music]
spinning H you're going to be even
faster in the final round I'm alive okay
should I do tasks yeah n don't don't do
tasks don't do Tas just just keep
hiding I need around
chicken she get one more minut come Kar
don't stand still because it's going to
show your location later on it shows do
you guys know where I am location yeah
there's a there's a red dot uh that
indicates where the crew
is have I shouldn't have moved I
shouldn't have bodies I see dead bodies
I see dead
[Laughter]
[Music]
people [\h__\h] does she see me from the map
too or only when she gets closer oh God
God oh nice zoom in
let's
go that was so clutch
clutch that was impressive IR that was
really good I don't know how I just
didn't really see her on the screen that
often so thank God everybody was
so that was close though teleporting
across the
map yeah the ghost couldn't even keep
track
is who is it this time let's go who is
it oh
y let's go today I think have fun r
r does doing tasks do anything like
short time early task wi if we do if we
finish them all yeah then we could get
lucky
finish to hide it's hide and seek you
got to
hide wait why can't I oh
no oh wait where where okay got to go
got to go got to go that's wrong I'm
sorry sorry oh wait it don't
work she was oh no
what damn
it I do wonder if doing tasks is even
worth
ITV she ran fast she ran
fast it's so fast it's so
fast it's so
fast can
we might be a little
unfair
oh okay I felt that was the wrong
direction
okay let's do our
Tas I'm so scared to move around I saw
something do
[Music]
[Applause]
task only three
left where is everyone a danger meter ah
one more one more
minute such a good hiding spot
though
Goode 30
seconds that was a really good hiding
spot yeah that was
[Music]
aing all
the whoopsie uhoh you guys are slippery
yeah slippery everybody so
fast over oh
no a it's so fast I
[Music]
can't you got to
survive oh
[Music]
[Applause]
man
what you do you're
Phoenix oh
no oh
no w
[Applause]
wow many seconds was left one literally
one wow that a good match though that
was that was
[Music]
clutch that was the clutchest ever
what can't escape time at the end of the
day but was really slippery yeah really
slippery
oh my God that was exciting yeah that
was so
thrilling I mean exting I'm I'm pretty
exhausted from that but we can do
another one if you want I'm down for one
more oh
actually actually actually you know wait
wait oh no before Oh I want to I want to
speed so fast yeah it's fast oh good
okay never mind good good
good you wanted how do you how do you
the whole time um there's a kill button
so don't you worry okay oh my God no way
I don't want to be it no the monster is
Unleashed she has awakened I'm coming
for you nobody's using my hiding spot
right a good idea don't use my Hiding
you might go use it I don't even know
where it is you're
hiding
shoot not a rampage there were two
people there I only saw one
person
over does the music get louder for me
too I feel like it does I know it gets
louder when you're near someone really
even for
imposter you [\h__\h] get out of there get
out of there you little
[\h__\h] going on
scary
[Music]
no I Ain doing this screw
this
[\h__\h] where are
they that was my hiding
spot where are they where are they oh no
that's okay that's the stack okay okay
okay I still got time I still got
time I saw someone where is
she that hiding
spot i s
again
oh my God that was no no I haven't found
anyone in like ages you passed by
somebody
[Music]
oh someone's here no oh
[\h__\h] where are
you hello I'm all
alone no hints no hint
oh what was that there was some button
popping up there the use button yeah
it's kind of hard to press it in
time I even see you that's lame what the
heck didn't see you well I saw you
that's all that matters oh dang it
nice
quick oh
no oh one more one
more
[Music]
run no no no
no still one more
minute they're literally right run run
run run run
you can throw it through a loop just one
[Applause]
[Music]
onecircle p p p p p p p
wow do
[Music]
doie that was cl again pretty clutch I
would say get into the
Mama Mama Mia that was wow that wasun
yeah that was fun that was merry I'm too
excited to say anything so let's start
with the with the goodbyes from anybody
but me um am please do yeah this is
really fun I'm glad we could get
together and have like a little
Christmas Among Us celebration
yeah
the perfect holiday SE holiday game
right
yeah just red with joy and some blood
when I think of Christmas I think of
Among
Us and ornament it is pretty festive the
colors are festive this makes me want to
play this makes me want to play on
Project winter yeah oh my goodness cus
yes I
know
wow thank you I'm sorry you died so
[Music]
often need detected but that's okay
still fun call what about you you had
some good good kills today it was nice
getting to dust off the old Scythe for
once and get back in the game for a
little bit that was nice yeah Killing In
Style yeah I had a great time with
everybody here everybody here is fun to
talk to fun to argue with in a fun way
in a fun way yeah in a fun way I guess
that's about it we should argue more
often yeah let's do
it no no I can't maybe not yeah no we
just stay T but within among us we can
argue as much as we want right and then
outside of Among Us you know we're
different people among us changes us but
only within among what happens in Among
Us stays Among Us yes it stays Among
Us
[Laughter]
all right and Fa please please tell me
about your experience today science
Rules science science Bill what science
do science go science Rules and
statement thanks great
I interesting I don't quite understand
but I agree oh I don't think Kiara knows
about Bill it's all right don't worry
about
it don't worry about
it we'll tell you later we'll tell you
later oh it's a m okay
I Mrs Mrs Santa Claus Mrs Christ yes
yeah know this was fun I'm glad I was
able to lie better this time yeah yeah
you some good
lying for
IR never suspected everyone everyone
great I love how bad F was at ly yeah oh
yeah their first time I love the scre
the screeches are so nice the same as me
when I played for the first time don't
worry was always like that it's great I
love it thank you very much that was
they were so lucky cuz like in that one
round they were about to be voted off
and I thought I was going to be alone
but then somehow somehow they survived
we couldn't save
you no it's okay we couldn't save each
other even if we wanted to yeah well
thank you Iris and then
people what about you was happy to be
able to kill people I wish I was able to
kill more people but I
will of people I was able to kill this
time that's the spirit thank you for
your service that's the that's the
Christmas spirit let's
go ho ho ho it was some good reaping it
was
solid good job again I'm so sorry P it's
okay a
trail what stays in Among Us days among
exactly
exactly a lot of things to do we really
good at lying right yeah that was
it yes yeah and uh we have fun we we
yelled a bit screamed a bit and we did a
lot of
lying yeah but most importantly we have
fun so
true yeah when I saw I was imposter with
F I knew I knew that you weren't going
to be good at
lying
we have to do
our s yeah it's all good it's
funny I had so much fun thank you so
much for putting it together Ki welcome
yeah thank
you I'm sad I had to be the impostor I
don't like it brings me no joy
yeah muring me I know what you mean no
oh but you were so good though you were
good at it
with blue women blue women are
scary blue women I always say it it's
the blue people the the avatars I always
say
it yes thank you you're welcome I'm glad
you had a good time let let's continue
this in the males yeah
peacefully the other Blue Woman
Quon yeah it was a lot of fun I'm kind
of surprised that I actually got
impostor twice uh because I never get
imposter yeah I never get these
roles yeah and thank you for organizing
this it was a lot of
[Music]
fun I guess you know there was all sorts
of drama but like we said earlier what
happened Among Us stays Among Us wow
wowow
wow wow beautiful well said Thank You
Quon well yeah that's pretty much it um
but Christmas is not over yet I think
there's still members that have like
special streams upcoming so check them
out everybody and I just want to make
one quick announcement about the whole
Ian Advent calendar some people may
already know but the last day the 25th
day will be delayed a little bit so uh a
few days uh the it's out of my hands out
of my power now but please check back on
it next week we'll all tweet about it
when it is finally up uh so stay tuned
stay excited and thank you for spending
Christmas with us viewers I say to you
viewers thank you for spending it with
us and thank you to the girls for
spending it also with us thank you for
getting together at this time
thank
[Music]
you ho ho
ho had a lot of fun that was really
great and I hope everybody has a nice
nice holiday season eat some
cookies y Yum Yum Yum Yum okay I have
some protein milk in my fridge oo that's
very Christmasy
Sant Santa come to to drink your milk oh
protect your
milk all right I don't think that's
going to make Iris like Santa anymore my
my Santa brings all the oh no Santa is
iris is literally a tree now
okay to drink the protein milk we can't
let him get any stronger than for Santa
no don't give him the power no the
cookies oh I
[Music]
oh
word makes it worse that doesn't really
s something I want to tell my children
go over yeah okay with that I think some
people
are
[Music]
so thank you everyone it was kind of
chaotic um I had a lot of fun f it was
kind of
unexpected that I got impostor twice in
a row which is nice cuz I never ever
ever
do
yeah all right but hope you guys have a
good day and yeah I might be around
mayhaps
tomorrow
as a gorilla Stream So yeah thank you
thank
you but if I don't see you
tomorrow uh happy holidays Merry crimus
and
[Music]
me