[Music]
so
hello hello
thank you everyone for
coming in
and celebrating my
my birthday
thank you thank you
uh oh i forgot to oh my that's
thank you for oh oh my
give me give me one second
forgot to
oh my
[Music]
thank you
hubba
do you guys like the cake that i
that i made right here
i made it in one go
that's pretty good
i know
looks pretty oh oh my
oh my
[Music]
yeah
um
[Music]
thank you
thanks
okay
um
but i'm really happy
that everyone's here
and
oh
oh goodness
um
no thank you
hub
thank you
[Music]
okay
um where do i even begin oh yeah
uh when i was
making the the video
[Music]
yeah when i uh
i i pulled an all-nighter so i haven't
really uh slept
i did get i think three hours of sleep
in
i kept i kept checking over and over to
make sure there weren't
as many mistakes
yeah
and i hope you guys
liked it
yeah
uh
what oh oh yeah
and
thank you thank you everyone once again
i i saw the crow mayday toe tags and
it was really amazing and i would like
to go through uh
the feed together with you guys
uh
the the bgm is too loud okay give me one
second
okay how's that
oh boy
thank you
[Music]
uh well
i'll be doing collins uh and about
[Music]
i mean i'll be doing collins at around
20.
so
um
but before we start
seeing who joins us
let's see uh
oh boy thank you everyone let's see
let's let me show you
let me show you what i have
watch this
uh
[Music]
bam
and then
bam i know it's hidden so i got you
you are still there
so see this
look at this
okay wait
uh okay now look at this
[Music]
and
you ever wanted to have perfection
herself
well
behold
by
wada arukumama
herself thank you as
always uh
i recall her watching my ring fit stream
and i'm sorry that you had to see that
and
it's very nice
i love
it and i like the i like the cronies uh
plushies in the back it's a very nice
touch
and um
let's see
uh this next one
over here
bam
it's by cats
uh katzen the one who worked with me for
uh the daydream music video
i reached out to her again for
a beautiful ribbon
and
i actually kind of want this for myself
since my wrists
my wrists are in pain
okay well i'm not ambidextrous but
yeah my my hand my wrist has been aching
so i would love to
rest on myself my perfect self for that
does it actually help
who knows
[Music]
and
uh
this one
the one the one i really like is uh
the cronies plushie
and you can switch the hats
uh
so in a way it's kind of customizable
and you can switch the ribbons you can
do a switcheroo
it's so cute i really want it
and look at the bag
has a little
little gear thingy it's very cute
[Music]
oh mummy hello
right it's so detailed
yeah
and i really want it
i want to see i want to see how it feels
and
yeah the hourglass on the on the foot
and the little uh oral orocrony on the
year it's really cute
[Music]
and
let's see
uh
are there more
oh yeah
and then
i also
have the system voice in japanese and
english
because why not
and
you also get a postcard with
my actual signature
but yeah
yeah that's
i'm so bad at chilling myself but yeah
it's
it's cool it's in
it's in a gold foil pretty cool
wow
and uh
yeah my my handwriting um
it's not as fancy as the one that you
guys thought it was for the daydream
music video but
you know
but
uh it's it's gonna
uh
start
releasing the launch is going to start
at
12 pm
uh japan time
so
less than an hour from now it's going to
be
released
i think i think that's everything
yeah
look at that look at that beautiful face
oh hello
oh man
look at that i'm down bad
kind of like looking at my amazing
portrait of myself
right
perfection i know it's amazing
what a mama thank you
i do look perfect thank you thank you
and
i think i think that's everything yeah
yeah
okay
how do i remove this now
[Music]
my brain
okay good
and then bam
got it
yeah but
oh
i was
i was taking
uh all day pretty much all night
all night all day i was taking last
night and
took a three hour nap and then i
continued working on it with the
with the editing for the video and the
mixing
uh so
yeah if i seem kind of out of it more so
than usual that's probably why
[Music]
yeah i i hope you you guys
liked it
and
what else what else was i gonna say oh
oh i uh i saw
some really cool um twitter posts for
the chroma de toe tag
so
i don't want to spoil it but i've seen
some
and when i saw it i thought to myself oh
my goodness
thank you
it's so amazing
we got you some gifts i i saw it it was
so cool
[Music]
the the cameo i i saw some i didn't see
all of it because i didn't want to spoil
myself too much but
it was so cool
thank you
and
uh
oh the art tag is trending oh
and
uh i just wanted to say
thank you
[Music]
i feel like
i feel like six months has
flown by so quickly
and
man
yeah time flies when you're with
perfection herself that's right
mm-hmm
[Music]
and
we we have some
fun crazy times here
we gaslight
gatekeep girl boss each other but at the
end of the day
i'd like to think that we have a lot of
fun here and i hope to do that
for many more
do you fly crony
oh yeah
speaking of i i gotta bring out my clock
i gotta bust it out give me a second
whoop
calls for a special celebration
obviously
[Music]
yeah
my clock
lo and behold i am hitting it oh aku
tonjok chat that's right
with my clock
[Music]
it's beautiful
it's working that's right
i got it working
[Music]
yes it's for the best and special
occasion
and
oh wait i gotta i gotta make sure i set
things up correctly
[Music]
oh yes
just double checking things
[Music]
okay
so nervous
there's just
so many things to prepare
um but i'm so glad that i was able to
get things out of the way now and
just enjoy it with you guys
that that is a big clock i know i
you guys haven't seen it in a few months
but now you guys realize huh
um
and uh thank you for everyone who has
been sending so many supers i i can't
even read them
uh
[Music]
oh uh and also
what should i say
what should i say um
i wanted to say
oh man my mind is so blank right now i'm
just
so
so surprised
[Music]
man
zola there's a lot of people here
so
thank you for that
i'm not nervous what makes you think i'm
nervous
come on
oh yeah kang pai
[Music]
ah
now this actually calls for celebration
so calm pie
[Music]
i am now infinite plus one year
one years old
i i don't really know how that works but
don't worry about it
technically it's not even infinite plus
one it's just infinite because you can't
plus 1 infinite
infinite is infinite
in human years maybe i'm 61 years old
but i age well if that's the case
[Music]
more infinite why
one isn't infinite what
you know what
that's fine
let's see let's see
and we are going to get our first
call-in
very soon
and let's see
[Music]
let's see who joins us
okay
[Music]
just double checking
make sure everything's fine
[Music]
oh
hello
that
did i surprise you
oh
i didn't i didn't see you when you came
in but
damn
happy birthday crony
thank you
how are you
i'm i'm good i
my mind is drawing a blank right now
just really nervous
i've noticed i've noticed
[Laughter]
no need to be nervous everyone's here
because they love you
thank you it's really good to have you
and thank you so much for taking the
time to
be here
taking time to say happy birthday to
time
right
yeah
oh
uh
i
have
one question for you
[Music]
so
if we could collab again
oh
what would you like to play or do
[Music]
i i i want to do an off collab reviews
oh enough i i want to do that yeah
yes do you want to go to europe
have you ever thought about it
i have actually um maybe sometime next
year or so i feel like
things are going to be
less
bad
by next year so i i do want to visit
oh which which is there like a country
that you're interested in in europe
i wanna
i wanna just go around to places but
maybe
like
italy
oh
have you never been to italy no i've
never been to europe
oh my god it's about time europe is
really good for like um like traveling
through a bunch of countries in like a
short amount of time
um i i would
i wouldn't mind showing you around you
know i
went daily uh a couple times so i i know
some italian words as well actually
what do they all mean
those are mostly um
terms that you would use uh
in
hotels
or in tourism i suppose
which was actually pr i would say it's
pretty useful because if we're going on
a vacation you would want to be able to
communicate well with the hotel yeah
yeah that's true
wait um
actually did you do you realize do you
do you know the european map do you
realize your austria where i am is like
right next to italy neighboring country
oh
i am bad with geography i just
understandable
i wouldn't really know a map of north
america
i mean i know canada is like above
america but
i can't really say
anything about the map of america
i
have
no idea how maps work um
how maps work well there is a top
direction up there there's north and
then right is uh uh east and then bottom
is south and then
left this
west
yeah i just
i know that one okay i better know that
one
but by the way i have something small
it's really nothing nothing nothing
nothing i want to draw you properly
sometimes because you're beautiful
oh my gosh
thank you so they're so cute no
no no no no
can i can i show it
yes but um yes i guess so
thank you i love it
no
i love you too
oh and we gotta do a diablo two come to
i heard that you were interested in um
skin called lost art
so
yes but like we oh
i don't think we can play it yet i mean
that's true but you know
you know
if we can then let's play it once we can
hang out i'm super excited for what
let's push push some more okay okay okay
yeah my friend my friends have been
addicted to it so and i heard so many
good things about it i wouldn't want to
play it
yeah
um
let's let's do it i've been playing it
too but thank you so much privately you
already started yeah
oh
i wanted to keep that first experience
for like a stream moment oh yeah yeah
that works too
i have one question crony uh-huh
why
did you show the merchandise right in
the beginning oh i saw some people doing
that so uh
huh
i've never seen anyone do that before i
was like is this is this an accident did
she do that on purpose ah
it must be an accident
oh i know what else does that you keep
normally crowning let me tell you how
birthday stream works but it's okay you
can switch things up but normally you
start by talking a bit that you do call
in class this is like the classic
birthday stream and then at the end
uh you show the merchandise because you
want to make people you know wait
oh
you want to make them get excited
but but you know what i like the
original way you're doing it and that
dakimakura is looking really hot
thank you
what the bumba so great you're gonna be
a trendsetter everyone's gonna show
their merch off in the beginning now
i mean it's more time to sell it i guess
no not really it's still only one month
guys get her merchandise it's only
available for one month since you didn't
mention that cronie i think you didn't
mention it i did
i'm new
one month until the yeah after the
birthday so guys don't forget
thank you so much kiara
you're welcome happy birthday thank you
let yourself be celebrated eat some
awesome big cake and
and get a lot of presents and love from
everybody okay yeah thank you and have a
good night
love you
yay
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's drawing so cute
what the heck
look at this
man
oh
hello
[Music]
thank you
uh
i was listening i i didn't know you
already showed the merch i was like oh
that big of god accident oh christ
it's not that bad it's
none of it i just
i wanted to see it i missed it
oh
thank you
oh yeah um
i did want to
collab with you um yes
yeah but
oh man it's always my scuff you know my
pc breaking down and i just never get
the time
oh
both of our pcs are messed up maybe it
has some it's time fluctuations or
something a bit
maybe actually that would make a lot of
sense um did you know that
i actually
uh
got my pc
because of you
oh
you know
i i have the same thing that you
had i thought it looked really nice so i
wanted to get it
i mean
that's not what caused the problems is
it
no no no no no i mean uh
i mean it was it was good
now it's good
it's my mind's messed up too but it
looks nice doesn't it yeah it does look
nice it's it's so pretty
yeah
but
no it's not
like i mean i
i looked at it and i thought to myself
oh wow that's really pretty and
it looks pretty good like just overall
so i decided to get it and then
i'm gonna make a public announcement i'm
gonna reset that tweet and i'm gonna be
like guys don't get
[Laughter]
this but
at the end of the day it works out it
works out just fine
yeah i sent it off it
took a long time but i i got it i got it
working and it's a great computer
thanks to you
nice to meet you yeah
okay that sounds sarcastic but i mean it
because i i do like this pc
yeah it does look nice it is pretty uh
do you have a question for me before i
go
um
so
that watch you have oh yeah
where'd you get it from
uh
i gotta go
[Music]
she left
goddammit
god damn it
curse you time traveler
pain this is what i get for managing
timelines huh
this
is fine
but
man
she's so cool she's nice
i really like her
she
she saw me bumping into glass before and
i was
that was an experience
[Music]
ah man that was
that never happened
i made sure that never happened
never happened
oh man hello
that was like asmr in my ears hello
calling you from bed
oh you're calling from the winter i
don't know how i sound but okay
oh
hello
thank you
oh you're
your voice sounds so great how's the bed
man
i am i'm trying out this thing you enjoy
called sleep
and i
i quite enjoy it
nice i'm so proud of you a lot of people
should do that more often sleeping
it's a blessing
i couldn't do it today because
my birthday
but i um i haven't looked at your baking
uh
your baking video yet but i will i will
laughter
yeah i can't wait to hug myself
and i don't have to hug the mirror
anymore it's just hugging myself it's
great oh yeah i think i think the
documentary is a little softer than a
mirror
yeah definitely a little a little more
accurate
a little a little more accurate what
does that mean huh
it means you're soft
i i am thank you very much i'm glad you
understand
and sana is
[Music]
cronie big
soft and sauna is big
and right in front of us is cake
oh how would you rate this cake
i will
rate it um
maybe nine out of ten softness of grainy
granny
wait
why is it not 10 out of 10 where's the
one
because you're the 10 out of 10. you're
perfection right
this cake can't be more softer than you
oh that's okay wait we're talking about
cake softness i was talking about if the
cake is good or bad
damn
feed me
yeah of course um i will feed you from
the bed
[Music]
[Laughter]
it'll be great
yeah
it's like oh
[Music]
i remember when we first met um chad and
everybody thought you were the cool one
but you never fooled me
i i still am pretty cool thank you very
much
no no you you never told me you're
you're soft and you're asleep and um
[Music]
oh my god why are you saying that
it's normal to check up on people
[Music]
yeah just just take care of yourself yes
she's so precious and um please
please take care of her and make sure
she's the most happiest clock ever
because she deserves it
and sana just as well because sana is
cute and sana is big if you don't think
she's cute she will destroy earth so
watch out
yeah i think that's it i might be a bit
late
for the next person
okay
thank you sana
have a good sleep you need it
thank you
[Music]
bye
i love that girl
she's so sweet
[Music]
so big too
kind of scary
[Music]
oh wait
but
that i mean
yeah it's normal to check up on people
so
whatever so
[Music]
this is kind of no big deal
i wonder what she's
doing from then
trying to sleep oh did you wake up for
me that would be really sweet
oh wait who's this
hello
help
must have been the win
oh hey
oh it's fun
and i was supposed to have internet but
i don't have internet and i'm on my
phone but i appear to be
running out of data oh
oh goodness
oh thank you for taking the time
um
[Music]
i was trying to watch your stream but i
had to watch it in like 160p
because my phone is dying
oh wait well happy birthday happy
happy birthday
yeah but happy birthday happy birth i
mean thank you
i i hope your movie is going away
show you because oh you're dating
but i want to show it to you whenever i
have internet okay
wait we're like sorry wait
how how much data do you have right now
i don't
oh god
it's
it's struggling
well it thank you for taking the time
it's so good to hear your voice
yes please take my remaining data crony
it's all for you oh this kind of sounds
like your last words and it's really
ominous
it might be
no no i'm sure i'm sure the internet
will come back at some point
one day oh i want to tell you fauna you
are a gamer
but
yeah
no matter thank you yeah no matter how
you try to deny it at times i've seen
you you were a true gamer
um
is this a compliment yeah it is a
compliment
why
we play games being good at games is a
compliment
okay okay okay thank you thank you yeah
you know you're a gamer too
i mean i
i didn't get top high score in the
racing game so
yeah you're pretty good at a different
game
what game
i don't recall that well it's your it's
your specialty i'm not on liberty to
reveal it that's your choice
[Music]
wait what cleaning cleaning
clean yes
wait what were you thinking
no there was the one game that you were
like oh this one i know this one and
then you played it and you beat it you
got a high score
oh
cleaning
[Music]
yes
i think
yeah
you know
i gotta say fauna we
we make a good team
you think so
should we team up again
we should team up again let's team up
again or go up against each other
whichever
maybe both maybe both yes
sounds good but thank you so much for
stopping by fauna thank you i wanted to
tell you your video was so cute and
funny oh thank you
video
i loved it a treat
have a good one and good luck with
moving
thank you happy birthday
[Applause]
[Music]
fun well
man i'm surprised that fauna didn't fade
away in the middle that
the beginning sounded so glitchy in the
beginning i thought it would just not
happen
oh oh hey
hey
inna
ina
you know what it is today
it's pie day
also my birthday
oh yes of course oh yeah right
yeah
i mean it was way too obvious that it
was my birthday so you know
uh
[Music]
wish you a happy birthday
oh you're
you're thinking about it
think about do you think it'll be worth
it i don't know i mean what do you think
i don't know can't just watch you happy
pie day
happy pie day it's good
hi is good friday everyone yeah good i
have cake
no oh
i think you missed the memo pony oh
shoot
the pie
can you bake me a pie
anytime
are you actually good with baking
yeah i can bake i can bake
[Music]
have you ever baked on stream i did kind
of
what did you consider it baking i did
like a no cooking
cheesecake ones
cheesecake
and some macaroons but they turned out a
little
on the wonkier side but i'll bake for
you any time
ah
thank you
next time we can all collab again we'll
do a baking stream
ooh i'm gonna butcher it
a butchering stream i mean
i don't think we can have cameras for
that
oh god
happy birthday happy birthday i hope
you're having a good day
love your merch
thank you he uh has a lot of ribbons
oh i have a question yes question answer
um what was your first and current
impression of me
[Music]
um well when i first saw you and heard
you i thought man i thought you were
gonna be like the
the chill
you know
damn it everyone keeps saying
i mean you just give off that aura and
then now that uh
i've
gotten to know you you
have a have a side of you that's a
little uh what people say pun
but
there's like a big gap you know that uh
that just emanates from your
uh
perfection i should say
yes
but i'm still cool right
[Music]
as cool as cool
oh
as
as cool as
refrigerated cool yeah
man we'll i'll get you next time
oh you're welcome to try cronie you're
welcome
our pun battle will be glorious it will
be legendary it will be
uh
i'm gonna reach out to you for
a collab i saw your
message
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
i just want to play out with you
sometime
yeah
i'm interested
yeah let's do it okay
yeah by the way my um current
um question of you is that you're you're
you're very kind and caring like at
first i thought you'd be
they'll be on the cold side but you care
a lot for uh everyone around you and
you're not afraid to ask
ask the shop for extra
oh my god
[Laughter]
when no one could step up to the point
a big
big
big role that no one can step up to
except for you a hero we needed in our
time
well you know what i'll do it again for
you any time
okay thank you thank you
okay anyways happy birthday eat
something good maybe maybe not only cake
with some pie and
and
cake
and yummy stuff takoyaki
[Music]
you thank you great order yeah i'm
waiting like uh would you like it as a
take out
yes please okay
we'll get it delivered to you as soon as
possible hey thank you for using taco
eats have a wonderful day
thank you too
bye
[Music]
i haven't eaten anything today so
i hope the delivery comes fast
i'm pretty hungry
ah
where's my uber
i'm here oh
oh hello are you my uber
hello
hey
happy birthday
oh are you okay
i'm fine i'm just a little dead that's
why happy birthday why
[Music]
oh okay i was like what is thick
hey happy birthday how are you doing you
doing good thanks man i'm
i'm still kind of out of it but i'm kind
of warming up to it how did you even
handle your birthday your birthday was
amazing
no i don't know you're doing good don't
even lie
no you don't even start you're doing
great
i saw your freaking
baking baking vodka sugar perfection
oh good oh thank you
oh
thank you oh
um
remember bae remember
how we were going to play
yes power wash
yes
we're going to do that we have so many
things to do
yeah we have a cuter last night we have
so many things
we have so many things to do
i mean look what
are you playing power wash this way i
feel like i saw your schedule you're
playing power watch this video yeah yeah
you playing power wash i'm also playing
i'm not i'll call you if you want
oh
we can
remember the first time we told and you
you showed me power yeah yeah
we were we were talking we were talking
on the call and i was streaming power
wash and you were saying oh man that's
pretty good
man just do that easy
yeah
i'm down oh i'm so down i'm so down
let's do it
yeah i saw i saw your merch oh my god
that plushy is so cute i swear i'm gonna
my bed by like next year is gonna be
full of just plushies and i'm so excited
yo but plushies are so nice it's kind of
therapeutic to have so many soft things
around you
really like your mug by the way
it's huge
i know thank you yeah you can drink so
much coffee in
stay hydrated stay hydrated stay
hydrated
stay hydrated
anyway we need to catch up more i've
been we've been saying we need to catch
up for the last like two months
yeah i mean we kind of did yesterday so
kind of yeah you're right you're right
you're right
yeah all right all right
it was cute
i love it
you cute stop it no you're cute
no you're cute no you're so cute no you
suck it's not no
stop it
oh no
catch you around
okay
yeah all right
is that like is that my cue to leave all
right yeah i mean no wait is there
something else you want to say i don't
know
would you like ask questions or no
question i can just go it's up to you
where's the girl you make the rules oh
oh i mean i
i was saying oh we we should play power
but i do have one question okay oh yes
um is there anything you'd like to ask
or tell me
um
i like you
i do
[Music]
see you
soon
[Music]
what a cute little grill
little red little cute
little red
so cute
man her
hair
oh oh hey
oh hi
oh hey
it's you
it's it's me yeah oh
it's you it you
you happy birthday oh
thank
i have a gift for you want to see it oh
oh hit it
okay okay my ipad died sorry i must
paint hold on um
oh my goodness
can it top uh
cabbage patch cronie
oh my god
as soon as i said it man
as soon as i said it that is amazing
[Music]
i i got it i gotta show this immediately
i wanted to expand on it a bit
just a bit
it's my mouse
yo that is some flawless skills though
thank you
i i spent like 40 minutes on
40 minutes
believe it or not
yo
it's it's
it's everything that i could have ever
wanted thank you oh you're welcome
i hope one day i can get you like a real
one
oh
oh yes
oh i want one too i want a body pillow
that's so good
oh yeah i mean
if you ever get something similar of the
sword i
i wouldn't mind
what would that be would we be like
sisters no
why
like like twins
oh yeah
twinsies twinning
um
[Music]
i
just wanted to tell you
um
you know
[Music]
we should
whenever we can get the opportunity um
[Music]
you know
maybe
i'll
come over
oh
oh sure
oh you actually should i got a new place
and an awesome uh
sleepover oh
oh man sleepover let's go
upgrade it to a queen bed perfect for
you
oh wow we get to
share pens yeah i'll sleep with your
feet or something
why can't we just share the bed normally
um because
because animal will be there too and
we'll take take the other side it's okay
it'll be like a big family it's fine
oh i still look forward to it
yeah it was really fun hanging out with
you guys so i want to do that again
let's do it
when it when a time it makes sense when
there is time there's always time yeah
i'll always make time for you oh gosh
i'll be there
you come here
thank you movie
i just gotta say thank you
[Laughter]
i mean we can both say thank you why not
thank you cronie thank you for being
born thank you thank you for being born
gosh i'm so happy it's your birthday as
a reminder you're born
[Laughter]
my time limit
goodbye good goodbye
see mermaid hershey she's gone oh man
that girl
she's
she's so silly
i don't even know
oh i think this is oh god what
hello
oh wait
i had the wrong table but i'm so sorry
hello crony
happy birthday
thank you what was that sound just now
it sounds like oh no that sounded like
fart
like i had the the gosh didn't go xlr
with all the the routers mixed up oh
geez anyway how you doing oh wait hold
the detail
oh yes thank you
how long did that take you to think of
um
came up with the yesterday
oh sick have you slept at all
no oh i i took a three hour nap so
that's pretty
pog
[Music]
well
nice oh wait what oh okay wait wait
that's fine too
i saw your birthday merch
oh thank you how do you like it
i'm going to get um the money is it two
plushies
yeah oh no one
no one plus you all okay because i
wasn't there i'm gonna get one of each
i'm gonna make them kiss but if it's
only if it's only one then i guess i
have to get two and then proceed to make
them kiss or you're just telling me
huh
you're gonna have a mirror well maybe it
maybe if you were on the other side but
i don't know oh maybe if it's like one
of those secret mirrors that they have
in the department stores where they can
actually watch you
have you seen them in department stores
i didn't know that
test it with your finger and make sure
that it's not it's a it's not a two-way
mirror
yo
that's kind of messed up
that's very messed up yeah yeah why are
you telling me this on my birthday
why do i keep trying to say that like i
keep trying to say happy birthday on my
own birthday i don't know why
but thank you
of course of course of course of course
we should
we should hang out
sometimes
come kick my butt and smash again
sometime i miss that
oh okay i didn't know you were into that
kind of thing but sure i love it i love
it and i keep going like
i'm gonna play now man hey you wanna
come get my button
i
i'd be happy to um also i've been trying
to um
i never
uh get the time but i want to
start training in
dvd
um
yeah want to use that that which we call
it
was a wraith
ah bing bong bing bong is good yeah ray
sneaky sneaky sneaky boy also i found
the sound effect i meant to play earlier
it's here
[Music]
if you can hear that i don't know if you
could hear that even but yeah wraith is
great rape is fun what was that just
i'm sorry am i going like way too fast
for you i just had a rumble um so
it's okay
oh i hear it thank you well confetti i
thought it was a knife
oh wait i thought it was a what i
oh god okay not yourself i will never
ever play something
very good because they clearly aren't um
anyway
oh yeah it was good
dvd
dvd prop night any time let me yeah
let's go
show me
show me that disrespect
yeah play the funny fart sound always
love prop 9 so great
oh it looks like it's my time to uh oh
your
time has come
yes my time has come
anyway happy birthday
bonnie i hope you get a nap i hope you
did take a nice fat nap for your
birthday thank you i sure will it's
gonna be great you too
thank you
yes
[Music]
what a silly grill
yummy
sashimi what i mean
red bull gives you wings
that's always fun
[Music]
you know red bull actually tastes like
apple cider kind of
i've only had it maybe twice i don't
know
hmm
[Music]
[Laughter]
why why don't you like it embrace it
it's okay to be the way that you are
i don't sound like that
i can't i can't sound like even if i
wanted to i wish i could i wish i could
uh let me try it mm-hmm
cronichi no i can't
each
oh hey
this is my sleepy voice this is why yeah
oh did you just wake up or something
yeah i just
oh
i went to sleep really late last night
i woke up and i i looked i looked up
crony merch on twitter first thing in
the morning
and then i see jackie marker and i'm
like oh
oh
imagine
waking up with the cody ducky makara
right next to me i feel like
oh yeah
of course
it'll be beautiful
waking up to myself it's like a dream
come true usually i would have a mirror
next to me so
you don't need that anymore yeah i don't
need that
exactly
[Music]
like um
i was originally like trying to find
your merch from you know the your um
the youtube youtube description right
for some reason it doesn't work yet
maybe it's because it just came out it
just says your before not found so then
that's why i searched it up on twitter
yeah i feel you there buddy
it really
uh
but you know i thought you were pretty
good with shooting games but
you know way out
ah yeah
that was yeah
yeah
um
we got we got a way out of a lot of
things
yeah but your your shooting game
i mean
if it was good
you would have won right
what no
wait i did i did technically technically
i did win
uh-huh
the e mashing part that part yeah um you
know well
uh i didn't notice we had to match the e
as fast as you did
it's not like i'm coping or anything
you know
hope coke soda
[Music]
that must taste nasty
wait why
wait don't you have hope soda
i do have hope soda but i would assume
hope cope soda would
it's pretty bad
you got coke in there you know
what it is
soda
oh there's coke in it we don't have cope
and hope no we don't no i don't but
isn't coping hoping
no it
isn't
not not real no
what's the difference
that's my question to you what's the
difference between cope and hope one is
very positive and one is very negative
man can i talk about your ducky again
really okay
you
know you know how like um usually
duckies there's like the slightly more
mellow side and then there's the you
know the
side right like yeah you know it's
double-sided i always say you're a ducky
the both sides are pretty ooh
did you did you want to be
on either side you can't you can't be
like i remember bae once told me that um
daki's the reason why one side would be
mellow is because you know like in the
afternoon you would like when people are
in the house and you don't want to show
them you you want to be you know mellow
and not try to sound like your ooh-la-la
or anything you flip it over to the
mellow side and then that nut you switch
it to the oola last site is what she
told me
so cronie my question to you is which
side do you consider to be the bellows
[Music]
oh
the the
the front side not the side side one
[Music]
yeah
really the front side that's that's your
that's your mellow side yeah isn't that
pretty mellow the one that's not that's
not you on the side right it's like the
you yeah the one on the front
like lying on my back
oh
really i
i thought it was
thanks man this makes me think
man you know we should really go get
that electro from minecraft one minute
oh yeah we should
yeah
and we can fly yeah
all righty i will now take my leave
happy birthday cronie thank you bye ris
it's iris
i don't say it i don't introduce myself
i love teasing her
that's great
[Music]
what a what a what a lad
what a gal
well i'm gonna drink some water
[Music]
oh
hello
[Music]
there you go now everyone can hear hi
cronie
happy birthday to you
thank you thank you for coming
birthday to cronie hi how are you happy
birthday
yeah thank you
um
oh wait what was it gonna say
oh yeah you gonna say something yeah of
course what's up
um
how yeah i i actually have a question
for you how do you play
jump king so calmly
like it sounds like a rage inducing game
yeah
i mean
yeah it is kind of a rage game
um honestly um
i mean only only if you're moomey
and like bad at it but you know
um if you're me then yeah you're
probably fine
oh yeah
yeah several several times oh i mean it
i don't know it's like uh
it's hard to explain you can i mean the
deadbeats have already heard me scream a
couple times
um you still get screams i never rage
quit i can only rage continue crony
which is the way to go
but uh
yeah rage continue that's that's always
the way i recommend it um but yeah
actually junking it is a rage inducing
game um i think at the end of the day i
just remind myself it's just a game
uh just why i don't really rage quit a
lot of games i feel like i feel like i
tell myself it's just a game time to
time to do something else
yeah though i i i feel you i just don't
want to get mad which is why
um i want to check out jump king since
you really like it but at the same time
i'm scared because i know what happened
with uh getting over it with bennett
party that was
oh yeah that was probably the only game
that i don't want to say rage quit but i
kind of looked at it was like i don't
like this game anymore which is
technically
actually you're right i didn't outwardly
like get mad and say it i'm not
gonna play this game anymore but like it
was like a silent race quit like all
right this but you know what
i'm gonna make it up i'm gonna get back
in there and uh and i'm gonna beat it
someday and i'm gonna prove foddy wrong
because he's laughing at me from
high up in the tower shouting down at me
up
[Music]
um and and before you go i wanted to say
um
oh man i really i really hate how my pc
has broken down for the entire month but
now that that's done after your album so
like albums done let's uh let's play
i got the thumbnail ready and everything
a month in advance
yeah
excited very much looking forward to it
me too excited to collab with you for
show
yeah
i hope we have a great birthday and i'm
really looking forward to doing
something again together sometime
and i hope your album goes well
thank you yeah
i'm still grinding but we'll get there
eventually
slow and steady wins the race
yeah exactly here's my birthday wrap for
you i came up with it five seconds ago
crony crony cheese and macaroni caroni
is the best and that's not baloney peace
damn
whoa there's a lot a lot of food in
there a lot of things rhyme with cronie
thank you he's not a phony
i wanna i wanna she's my homie
i wanna rap like you someday
oh man thanks yeah i know those rhymes
were real slick
only uh only the
the top of the top the best of the best
could come up with that
anyway uh the others are waiting for you
i'll go talk to you later
bye karoni happy birthday i can't wait
to get your ducky makara and put it next
to mine bye
bye
[Music]
yeah her documentary was really nice too
i remember that
[Music]
oh man my lips are so chapped what why
why is it like this
[Music]
can't i open this chapstick
oh anya
oh hello are you over connie
hi
happy birthday
thank you
i was like oh no
i i had to do that
i'm sorry you you always do that just
starting from super mario
i love you
i love you too
yeah but when you do that i don't know i
feel a certain
certain feeling
and i don't know
a certain feeling maybe maybe it's love
you never know
yeah you know what
love love
love
love there's so many form to the filling
yeah many layers love love is like an
onion it has layers
[Music]
delicious
it's
it's grain i i mean i haven't really
gotten the chance to eat it but i had
something all right
oh
that's nice
yeah
uh a question when you were yes hosting
your birthday
yes did you sleep
uh
i think i took power naps and death
hey
okay oh my god
okay that's a normal thing okay
how long did she sleep
like three hours four hours
oh three hours that's not bad
that's that's not bad how short are your
power naps
i don't know
[Music]
damn you are built different
oh thank you i'll take that as a
compliment
yeah yeah
always
and
[Music]
i i
anya's birthday was few days ago so be
sure to check out her merch
yeah oh my god oh my god your
merchandise like i i heard you shook
your merchandise at the beginning
but
i didn't get to see it so i i had to
look it up on twitter just now
um
[Music]
was i
was i not supposed to
oh man
it's okay i didn't know i thought i was
supposed to show it during oh no
there's no problem with that like i'm
pretty sure there's no like particular
issue with that just that you don't
really see it often you know
i'm
first time for everything oh
no it's okay there's always first time
for this kind of stuff
yeah at least
i'm first
yeah people will remember me yeah
oh my god
like i'm i'm i'm gonna admit i'm not i'm
not a ducky makura type of person but i
will get your ducky makara
[Music]
i know yeah
yeah let's let's go let's make it happen
oh my god it will happen don't
in worry future indeed
yeah yeah yeah
thank you so much cronie for having me
thank you
and thank you two for coming to my tatsu
a few days ago oh of course no of course
have a good birthday then
yeah bye bye
bye bye over corny
[Music]
oh god
why did you say that
[Music]
oh no
pain
so much pain
huh
[Music]
oh
hello
hi
thank you for coming thursday oh my god
wait yeah oh my god thank you so much i
guess this is the first time we talk
isn't it
um
wait i don't have your png give me one
second
again
thank you thank you
thank you for inviting me i didn't
expect for you to find me
i mean i i want to get to know everyone
but
uh it's just
it's just man
i i did i did see that you are i always
want to talk to you later
yeah um
oh oh you you do hairstyles for other
girls too right wow uh connie um
you want to go bald if you want to go oh
oh okay wait
wait no wait
wait is that how it works wait i saw
cooler hairstyles
yeah i mean i have to make you bald
first right oh
oh right you have to make me fall first
and
then put back the hair let's try the
second time
um
i mean if i'm gonna have hair later on
then
i'm gonna have hair later on right yeah
right
please tell me i have hair later on
that's not going to be the finished
product right
hello hello
hello
[Music]
you're gonna make me bald huh
yeah
what
what what is that long silence i'm
scared
hi hi guys sorry
oh okay
what what happened
[Music]
you know and did the usual it's always
storms right here lately
oh pain
thank you so much for taking the time to
yeah even if there's a storm
you know it's okay you thank god you
didn't hear the fun
huh wait i can't hear you
uh hello
goofy
hey
[Music]
hello
um
[Music]
no i can't hear you though
oh
oh you can hear me oh okay hey
you're like i can't hear you but you
can't hear me it's weird so sorry god
storm's coming
that sounds so ominous stay safe
sorry guys yeah the storm is really bad
this day so sorry it's all good stay
safe and thank you so much for coming to
my birthday
tom thank you for inviting me too and
yeah i'm
looking forward for your
bald crowning
thank you i'm
looking forward
to it i will have hair right i i
will wait
okay great thank you thank you
okay thank you for your time thank you
happy birthday
[Applause]
[Music]
she's not gonna make me bald right
oh god
oh goodness
wait
oh man
oh
oh wait hello
to answer your question cronie she will
make you bald
oh
is that
does she do that does she usually do
that
it's a weekly thing you'll get used to
it
oh
has she ever made you boom
three times
anyways
thank you ollie
thank you i did this woke up i didn't
get i didn't have the time to actually
ready anything
i'm so sorry what no just the fact that
you're here means so much to me thank
you
it's the only thing i can give my time
to you
it's so nice how are you doing how's
your birthday
it's going great um
i
feel like
i feel like it's a little
unorganized but i swear i organized it
but
i don't know maybe it'll get better uh
[Music]
um we should play
uh board games again in the future
right
we can have like another chest we can go
head-to-head or i can teach you shogi
are you interested in shogi ooh
yeah yeah i want to invite you next time
with love yes i'll be waiting for it
yeah i don't know how to play shogi but
i think that's like another form of
chess so
it is it's just been a little bit slower
ah
and i i know that
you really like apex
so
cronie wait is that a marriage proposal
who are you
i
i'll be your wife anytime
is that how it works
we are now
husband and wife or wife and wife
oh god
i i see you
summoning um
you're
you're lucky
lucky lucky
wait
my my brain is so empty right now
olly
the lucky olly
oh man my bra olivia yes thank you
yeah
olivia olivia is always there when you
summon things for legendaries or
something i don't know how that works
but they're like loot crates
i i don't know how that works either
people have been sending me screenshots
of them getting goods with olivia but
never happened again to me people
my luck
[Music]
yeah but i've never played apex before
so if you could maybe teach me
since you seem to be the expert i would
appreciate
oh don't worry i'll i'll be sure to take
it nice and easy on your first
thank you i greatly appreciate
please be gentle it's my first time
i'll be looking forward to it anytime
anytime at all if it's apex
yeah so um i'll be sure to give you your
present later but
uh i'll make it right now but but i
wanna make you present so please uh be
sure to look forward to it have a
wonderful birthday cronie oh thank you
you too
wait what i kind of i mean how hap i
just said happy birthday to god damn it
uh good good day you do you have a nice
day to you too
i mean have a nice day
you too
bye
why am i like this
man
why do i keep saying these things gosh
darn it
ah
whatever it's a it's a it's a work in
progress it's gonna get better
[Music]
happy birthday to me
okay
um
but yeah i gotta
gotta do something
[Music]
while we wait for the next person
i am the next person oh oh hello wait
who is this
who this
oh
i am the moon the moon
the moon moon hello
hello
oh you sound tired
oh i just look
oh
i'm sorry thank you so much for coming
that's fine thank you so much for
inviting me connie
i
i have a gift for you before i forgot
oh really
well you didn't have to
oh that's so cute
thank you
oh
i'm not really good making a kind of
like an anime
style so i use a cartoony style
it's really cute i really like it let me
let me put it up
wait where did that other art go gosh
darn it
this is chaotic
um
but i remember
meeting you in
the minecraft server
when
when we were merging
and you ended up in the en server and
you're asking how do i go back
how do i return to the jp server it's so
hard to find a place i just like i i go
to every place that i know
i talk
uh you know like a spiral
uh-huh where there is a big big building
spiral i think that is when you fall
down um i will go to the gp
but
i just
uh thanks god i'm i'm with my elites i'm
not dying
yeah but
um i
heard that you were pretty good with
redstones
so you know um
um i'm i'm good with with you know
duplicate the redstone that i found
um
but yeah i still i still need to figure
out uh the redstone that you want
you know the the
hidden letter
because that is the on the previous
version uh i need to fix that before we
do it together
okay thank you yeah i i don't know how
to do redstone so i'm i'm in caveman era
so if you could teach me that would be
really cool
[Music]
so you want to upgrade your bunker
ronnie
yes
i
i want to
have a hidden door
is that possible
that is possible let's do it
um
let's do a letter
together yeah
i'm so excited
i'm so excited too
it's been ages since i've played
minecraft so i wanna
i wanna play that
it's been a while actually i haven't
visited a holo en server
so it will be nice if we do it together
yeah we're going to go there
i want to visit the id server too
oh sure you can
i will i will tell the
thousand letter
oh yes yes
thank you thank you i really look
forward to that
yes
me too me too all right um i don't know
am i am i taking a lot of time
oh no no you're good i mean i'm good i'm
good
happy birthday again karani i hope you
have a wonderful
day
and yeah so
bye bye bye bye
[Music]
oh man
she's so
she's so nice
[Music]
[Applause]
you don't see
anything uh-huh you didn't see anything
hey
[Music]
oh my what
okay and then
who else was it
see what you didn't see anything that's
right
[Music]
i think i have everything ready now
i think
i think i'm pretty sure
i was drinking water
[Music]
yeah you guys didn't see anything yeah
that's what i thought
[Music]
so
uh we get to have
a bit of break
oh man my neck
[Music]
oh
oh man my neck cracked like four times
[Music]
you guys did you guys hear
did you guys hear that
cronie stop i know i should probably
stop it's probably not good for me but
it's just it feels so good
[Music]
ah
oh man
um
then
man play these talented people they
didn't even have to do anything for me
like just the fact that they're here
means a lot
[Music]
and and how do you draw like that
water
[Music]
oh yeah i forgot to tell you guys the
merch is
available now
i'm just kidding it's not
it's available at um was it
12.
oh
i see
uh
wait let me
[Music]
okay
it's available in 25 minutes i know i
know that
just we do a little trolling here
uh
[Music]
or
maybe
i'm
saying it out loud
oh boy
i can do this
[Music]
hello
ah
kuronichiwa
happy birthday
oh wow
[Music]
yes
[Laughter]
um
is
[Music]
yeah i like the
combination of you and me
combinations
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
oh
[Music]
me
thank you
i love
uh
[Laughter]
she's gone
um
oh she's so nice
[Laughter]
thank you
just
not not very good with any hong kong but
polka
poke is just
very understanding
yeah polka is something else something
great that's right
look at this
[Music]
is
nobody knew that you were coming of
course i didn't accidentally um
have you out during streams uh
yes
oh yes they were like oh so what's going
to happen
who's after this
i i don't know why i did that i thought
i was being sneaky sneak but i i guess
not
that is darn it
oh man i'm a totally unexpected guest
everybody have surprised now
yeah i'm surprised
happy
birthday crony
i don't know why i chose that png it
looks um
kind of yeah sending nice to you like
that i mean
it looks like you're eyeing the cake
which i don't blame you it's a pretty
amazing cake oh true yes very very
amazing and tasty what cake is that
uh
strawberry
masquerade cake
okay
sounds good sorry good i hope you're
having a blast with your
birthday i just woke up by the way oh
wait i i can't tell your your voice
sounds so
perfect
and i i think it's just you know i think
it's just because i sound the same every
time but speaking of perfect you are
perfect today on your birthday and also
every time of the day oh thank you or
the yes
thank you thank you oh i wanted to thank
you that i remember a lot of things from
our learning stream
i know akusayan khani and akuchin
takroni and tidu
and
and then
what what aku tonjokchat
oh my gosh yes
perfect perfect perfect perfect yes the
word perfect
let's go
yay
but today we are not hallow because we
know how perfect cronie is on our
special day all right
yeah
now we are doctor
ayo
yeah
i mean i don't blame you
uh sleep is amazing i want to do that
every single day
i know sleep is good
sleep is underrated we need to sleep
more i mean sleep is underrated and
overrated at the same time
i guess so i don't know for people who
have too much sleep which i envy by the
way that's um i want some of that sleep
yes
what's the longest that you've ever
slept
i don't actually know like the longest
time i haven't slept i know but like
i've slept probably like around like 12
hours plus plus plus plus it doesn't
really get much longer than that
oh what about you
mine was
13 or 14 hours
wow
were you were you staying up
uh
i went to sleep at 6 00 am that time and
when i when i woke up i looked at the
clock it was 6 30 and i thought to
myself wow
like i feel really well rested for a 30
minute nap and
i checked my phone it was
it was night time
yeah well rested indeed but that's okay
rest is important right you know
having those brittle bones at such an
old age you know you need the rest right
right
my bones are pretty good still going
pretty strong
all right yeah that's fair that's fair
that's fair all right all right all
right all right
maybe you do
i mean i'm young and free and good uh
yeah sleep is nice young healthy bones
you can't i can send you an x-ray if you
want
you actually have
an x-ray
really yeah yeah
wait your doctor sends you that
no i took i took i took one recently oh
i can send a copy to you you know wow
proof you know just for you know if you
want it if you want it oh i get to see
your
deepest i get to see my bones
your bones all the way
[Music]
oh oh my that's so scandalous
idle bones
anyway where are we talking about bones
on your birthday um i hope you have a um
great birthday
do you have a question for me do you
have a question for me or not
[Music]
i mean there is a question that i would
like you but that has to be in private
um so let me ask you another question
um
okay
uh
what was
[Music]
your first and current impression of me
i thought
wow
that's a big clock i said
[Music]
yeah and also you have a nice face and a
nice voice but that still applies now
i mean you have a great face and a great
voice
thank you
thank you but yeah i was thinking wow so
nice your voice like music to my ears
but that's still yeah that's still true
that was my first impression
what about now
now
now it's still the same except
hmm
i didn't think you were
[Music]
this
narcissist
oh damn okay
you're doing this on my birthday i mean
it's not a lie but
damn it's not alive but no i think like
no no no no no honestly
if you if no if i were that perfect i
would be the same you know i would be
the same you know so it's justified
you'll you'll one day learn the beauty
oh yes oh yes sensei
tony sensei i will teach you of course
thank you okay now go to sleep
all right
i will go to sleep you can join me
anytime you want have a good birthday
cronie bye bye thank you
[Music]
yay
goddamn this girl has to expose me on
stream i don't know how to feel about
that
and
that is everyone
um
so
wait let me just
uh bam
[Music]
and then
do this
man i duh i did not know that i was not
supposed to
oh
but hey really really cute art
man i really like these
how do i
how do i put this back
oh shoot what did i just do
[Music]
uh what did i just do
okay
what a mess i'm like phasing in and out
of existence i'm sorry my bad
uh let's
okay
i think i'm doing it
[Music]
oh yes
nice
no
how do i
oh
oh man
okay no i got this i'm gonna move it
i'm gonna move it you like to move it we
like to move it
okay put this here
and then
mummy's amazing picture
wait which one is it
wait which one is it seriously
[Music]
how do i get moomey's picture
we like to move it
move it
okay not this not this
there are so many
things going on i don't know which one
it is
which one is it
oh it's this one okay i got it i got it
guys
okay
oh
[Music]
wait i can't see it if it's like that
no
what do i do okay i'll just put it here
it's cute
okay
maybe i should take off my clock
so that i
can see
better or or you know what actually a
better idea
let me uh
[Music]
yeah
that's right
[Music]
small clock
yeah
okay
and then
and then i just
wanna talk about
things let's talk about things
um
so
guys
i feel like
first impression wise i kind of
understand what you guys are talking
about and that i was
uh the cool
the cool warden of time and everything
which i still have by the way
but
what is
your current impression of me
now
[Music]
i mean the first impression of chat i'll
let you know later
[Music]
perfection of course
adorkable
what
[Music]
ha
easily embarrassed ha
well you know what guys
[Music]
i
i would say that
my first impression of chad
was that
um
to be honest we didn't really know
we didn't really know about each other
that much
so
we kind of had to
figure out
um
i mean yeah you guys were you guys were
down bad i mean you guys are
always down back
you guys you guys are
i guess the the difference is that we
know how to
we know how to banter we we know
we know how to have fun
and
yeah um
should i
let's say it yeah
you guys
have changed
for the better and worse in that
while
we are bantering and learning how to
take a joke at the same time i look at
post chat and
i think to myself
where this all stemmed from
[Music]
and
and the other times where i say that i
want to crush you guys and then
you guys would respond gladly and
i guess i guess this is what happened
you started it warden oh yeah and then
you guys started gaslighting me yeah
that's a thing too
[Music]
um
so that that changed
but
it's for the better and worse there are
both good and bad
and that's that's fine
because in a way we're
mutually gaslighting each other and
you gaslighted us that's not how it
works honestly
[Music]
and
i'm kind of worried that one day
[Music]
if the the cronies gathered together
um that would be
that would be quite a sight
would they be reenacting
post chat
um
if that's the case i don't want to see i
don't want to take responsibility for
anything i uh i don't know you guys
i don't know who you are
i will never know
[Music]
i i don't know
you want to see kiffing no it's really
fine i
i'd rather die
yeah
um
you guys all know that i lurk in
the chat sometimes and
post chat especially
it becomes quite uh quite a sight
[Music]
and i don't think it was like this in
the past
what happened
i lurk everywhere that's right
[Music]
oh
you know what guys
[Music]
do you guys have any questions
because you know
i'm i'm always up for questions and
answers
what's it called ama i don't know what
ama stands for but
uh that's what they usually call it for
these
[Music]
hmm
my favorite food
spaghett
oh ama means ask me anything oh okay i
thought it was standing for awards or
something like that
are we your bros
you ain't my bro
crony
[Music]
and
what else
wow that's a lot of questions
who do you like to be your wife cronie
of course that's a question next one
what is the meaning of life
i don't think i can cover that on the
stream that will
happen over the span of
next few streams
[Music]
and let's see
when am i coming back
what does that even mean
am i not here
[Music]
oh
see
[Music]
what are these questions oh what class
do i play in lost ark i play the
sorceress i wanted to play the archer
but
uh that was gender locked so i couldn't
do that
made a pretty cute character
i'm currently uh
level 39 i haven't been playing often
lately but
my favorite movie
a joker
that was pretty good an
um
what else
oh
yes hello guys the the merch is out now
and whoever
was curious to see how the merch looked
you can look in the description below
check it out
yeah
oh and also favorite movies i like
christopher nolan movies i think they're
pretty good um they're pretty
they they make you think
brain expand kind of thing
[Music]
and
what class would you prefer with eldon
ring um i have no idea uh
what elden rang is about aside from the
fact that it's a souls game and i've
never played any souls game
[Music]
and
thank you great billy mays
uh
yeah
the the batman trilogy is great i love
that
what's the voice pack exactly well
i mean
i can't spoil that
[Music]
i heard that there's going to be a lot
of backseating for eldon rang but you
know what
can't be that bad
[Music]
you can show the merch on screen
hey oh yeah
oh so hey guys uh while that
thing i showed earlier never happened
but if you guys are so curious
uh
look at this
oh hello
mumei oh no
wait mummy
[Music]
mummy picture
goes here
[Music]
yeah
okay so
let's do this again
wada mama
amazing simply beautiful
and then
watch this
bam fade
and look at that
it's a body pillow cover the front and
the back
and both are very oo la la
um
like iris said
and look at that
it's beautiful it's amazing mmm simply
tasteful
perfect
[Music]
and
this
by cats
the the artist who
um who i worked with for daydream really
talented by the way amazing
very nice
if you would like the ribbon go for it
[Music]
and
a cronies plushie
look at that you can switch the
accessories back and forth so if you
want to be
a butler sure if you want to be a maid i
got you
everything
it'll be cute
and then
system voice
in japanese and english
i try to
cover
[Music]
what i can off the top of my hand
and
yeah
that's what i did
and then
and then you get a postcard with my
signature
button gold
oh my god what a deal
what what a deal
do you use an accent for your japanese
no i do not
it it is
regular nihongo maybe
i mean there's probably a slight accent
i i don't know but what a deal
what a steal
what
what a dealio
okay i'm a i'm a natural
chiller
oh god
i quit
and look
wait did i already show you this
but look
i look amazing
i look so beautiful
oh yeah
what a thrill
what a deal
what a fetch
only
only crony
and it's on sale march 14th and you know
what it's march 14th somewhere and where
is it
japan time and guess what it's out right
now oh my goodness crony did you just
say that yep i know that's what i just
said it's crazy i know
oh man
what am i gonna do with this knowledge
that's right you'll simply live with the
knowledge
thing
this has been crony
goodbye
okay i'm not actually leaving but you
know
[Music]
i can't believe my ears well you better
believe it buddy
ugh
crony am i daydreaming no you are not
it is actually legit 110
true
you are
the thing
i have no idea
ah
she was gonna say
i should have eaten something
my brain
my zatsudan skills
where'd they all go
[Music]
[Laughter]
wait i'm gonna i'm gonna drink some more
water
[Music]
uh is crony reading a script or
something well this is a pretty bad
script if i'm reading it off a script
and i gotta fire the scriptwriter if
that's the case
and if i wrote it i should fire myself
goodbye everyone this is my graduation
[Laughter]
i'm kidding
[Music]
ah
but
um
you know my signature
tried really hard to make it
[Music]
look cute
and relevant
and
you know how the big o has a cross hair
looking symbol
that's uh to show that
it's a clock like a really simplified
clock
and you know how
um
why am i trying to describe it when i
can just put this up right okay not this
one put this up right here
okay watch this
uh
[Music]
yeah see this over here
oh
god
yeah see this over this the signature
see so that
oh you know that cross hair thing that's
a really simplified clock and the eye at
the end it has an infinity symbol so
isn't that cool i put some thought into
it
uh
i
hope it's
decent
and you know what even if you don't
think it's decent too bad it's already
done
it's i'm such a bad i'm such a bad
salesman i mean i'm a great sales lady
let's go
[Music]
and
yeah
okay
um
i was thinking as to what kind of merch
should be available
and
[Music]
um
in hindsight i feel like
it would have been nice to have a pocket
watch
i think that'd be really cute
but you know what
those are always ideas for
later on
[Music]
and
uh what else oh but the crony plushie
i'm really happy about that one uh
i didn't think it'd be possible but
you know
lo and behold it is possible and
i love
i love it it's really cute and i want it
i think i get one shipped
if not i'll buy it
[Music]
and
yeah i'm gonna i'm gonna put a crony
plushie right in front of the mirror and
roll please
like oh
oh crony
oh the cronies
oh you you look so good today oh hey you
too
oh
kiss
yeah no i
i won't i won't do that
oh but
also
i have some leftover cake
uh it's strawberry mascarpone cake
[Music]
but i gotta check if
if it's spoiled or not cause i bought it
back in
uh
back when
[Music]
uh
a little less than two weeks ago
but it's i mean
it's cake
it's sweet sweet things don't go bad too
quickly it's probably fine
don't eat it i'll worry about it when
there's some
funny looking things on the cake
it's fine
i don't i don't
think i've
gotten food poisoning before
it's probably fine
bread does not last long but maybe the
fridge is really good
[Music]
it's fine
i'm infinite years old guys i know what
i'm doing
[Music]
and i mean
nobody
okay
let's not say that but
[Music]
nobody that i know has
suffered greatly from food poisoning and
you know what i'll take it
and besides i really wanted that cake
so i'll have it it's my birthday i can
do whatever i want
i'll eat everything
in my sight i haven't eaten anything
and
i haven't slept
i'm unstoppable i can do anything that i
put my mind into
[Music]
nobody can stop me
i am not saying right now
i'm going to i'm i'm
on a path of destruction
fussy cake is bad well i mean i'll i
won't eat it if it's
[Music]
fuzzy
like
i can eat around the fuzzy area
[Music]
i'm gonna miss cronie oh my god don't be
so dramatic
hmm
[Music]
was it always the screen oh come on
it's a fine
[Music]
oh thank you to osvaldo leo
la hello i'm not too good with words but
i only wish you a happy birthday and
hope
you the best thank you for everything
and i love the merch thank you
oh oh wow
and what else what else what should i
say
what should i say oh man there were so
many things that i wanted to say but now
that now that i'm here now that
now that this happened
i don't know
my mind is drawing a blank
um
crony can you do a flip i can't do that
my my mortal form is very restricted
[Music]
maybe if i become a clock i can do a
somersault
take a deep breath
you're right
ah
deep breath
okay i'm gonna
drink
i'm gonna drink another water
[Music]
oh
um there was this one thing about the
daydream music video that i never
mentioned
so
you know how in daydream there's a clock
ticking sound i asked for that
and then i asked for the monologue to be
included and i wrote the monologue
it's very edgy i know but
i mean i want it to be relevant to my
lore
so there's that
[Music]
uh
oh the line is dripperish
no it's not it can't be
and
uh
what does the system voice pack have
well you know
what system voice packs have
like systems
[Music]
i sound drunk
well
i mean
hmm
do you want me to be drunk right now i
mean i can
[Music]
what is a system voice pack
well you see
the system voice pack
but that is a spoiler
i don't know
i don't know i've already i've already
spoiled of my merch at the beginning of
the stream which i didn't know was
a spoiler
now i don't trust myself
i'm like
[Music]
the tom holland of
[Laughter]
but it wasn't such a big oopsie so it's
fine
okay
um
quick tell us what hollow en3 gen is
gonna be about
oh
that's gonna be about technology
and how technology is
both a blessing and a curse
and
those
those higher ups the gods the gods i was
mentioned uh at the beginning of the
lord yeah those those people are going
to
rule the world with technology but
different aspects of technology
[Music]
uh
and then there's the
the technology guide
and then the techno guide
and then
the
[Music]
just a computer tech support guy
yeah
it's uh pretty crazy
and
yeah that'll be quite a sight to see i'm
personally looking forward to it
yeah like smartphones and other gods
yeah
yeah techno gun are you guys excited
you guys think i'm serious
don't ever take me seriously
technology is always something to look
forward to oh yeah
and also
not that's a curse
[Music]
what is what is something that
i haven't talked about before
[Music]
did i ever talk about the time i
had to touch grass with the lack of pc
since both of my pc decided to
miraculously break down at the same time
which was unexpected honestly
[Music]
oh i did tell you
i mean i was touching grass but
do you know exactly
what i was doing
um
so
i
give me give me one second i'm trying to
i'm gonna look up my
my laptop so
i forgot that i even had a laptop so i
was just uh
kind of lying down with my phone
and
just looking at
how much fun other people were having
and it was kind of like that one
spongebob me where squidward is inside
his home and he sees patrick and
spongebob having a blast outside it was
kind of like that
and
[Music]
and then i was thinking
i i was
i was thinking about nothing pretty much
actually yeah my mind my mind pretty
empty and then
and then i came to a realization that i
had a backup pc
and thank goodness i didn't throw it out
so i went through all this struggle to
set it up
and
i turn it on
the screen won't turn on so i thought to
myself what the heck is happening
and i tried it over and over
and then the pc itself won't even light
up
and then it broke too
it was amazing
why are you reliving this nightmare
because you know nostalgia trip we look
back
and then
[Music]
and then i go back to lying down
and
uh
i'm just
i'm just in despair
and
laughing at my despair because that's
what i
do and
and then and then i realized that i have
my laptop
so i pick up my laptop i turn it on i
can't play any games but that's okay
uh
and then i was recording stuff on my
laptop
it worked out
and then i didn't like the takes that i
gave so i had to do it all over again
and then the crony space happened yeah
that's right
you mentioned that in the spaces god
damn it
why am i so consistent
why
at least you know that i don't change up
my story it's always the same thing
uh
when's the next one
after i move you know what just give it
time maybe
maybe next month
or may
moving is such a pain
[Music]
remember cortana
you're dead to me
oh
oh i have another problem
i have another problem recently and that
uh
there are several apps
several softwares on my taskbar and
whenever i try to remove it
by unpinning it
it's gone
and i restart it
it's back
and i don't know why
i'm always having problems i know and
it's so cool
it's almost amazing at this point
okay
but enough rambling
enough rambling
let's
let's go check out the crow mayday toe
tanks
[Music]
i want to see
how do i
how do i do this
gonna
type
mayday toe
[Music]
oh no i don't like this point uh
yes
yay
no
[Music]
now let's read it no wait yay
mm-hmm
chromatetoe
i wanna see
i wanna see where the
crowmaydaytoe are
wanna see him
dancing
[Music]
oh
right
i have just been informed by the manager
that i can pin the merch link
in the chat
haha
uh joke
joke is on you i can do this
[Music]
is this how i do it
this is how we do it
[Music]
wait it gets cut off
uh
that's
okay right
[Laughter]
no it's okay i i got this
no no no i i got this don't worry don't
worry manage your son i got it
look
ah shoot
[Music]
no no i know i know manager son i know
how to
pin
i'm just trying oh
gosh darn it
uh you know what that looks good enough
you know what
let's have one link
let's let's just have one link the the
official site
yeah that looks
good enough
manager son believes in me
thank you
it's it's gonna work it's gonna work out
okay
get this
i lost my comment
where where to go okay
did i do it
[Music]
i did it
good enough
[Music]
yay
i got
i got the seal of approval from the
manager's son
oh yeah okay
now with that out of the way
let's look at the chromate dato
[Music]
okay
oh wow
these are all so cute
new yorkers waking up tomorrow to the
greatest thing they've ever seen oh yeah
but the times square
i really want to see that
[Music]
hmm
wonder if people are going to
oh god there's a long baby cronie
[Music]
oh wow you're so quick you made a meme
already about the spongebob thing that's
amazing
thank you
[Music]
why isn't it today because uh
uh
it's going to happen in pacific time and
european time
yay
memesters are fast
indeed
[Music]
oh yeah
oh you guys have cake
that's so cool
nice you guys are celebrating it with me
made blueberry chocolate whipped cream
pie from scratch that sounds delicious
oh
um
when when we usually browse through the
[Music]
the the the
the hashtags
do do the other girls show it
i don't know how it works please help me
chad
hmm
[Music]
huh
sometimes
oh they show specific ones okay
[Music]
oh i like this one
uh let's see
okay i'm gonna save the ones that i like
[Music]
oh someone's making a fan game why
that's so cool
okay
look look guys
it's amazing
[Music]
this
look at that
ah yes me my mirror and my ten thousand
birthday merch dakimakra
uh
that's uh
is not far from the truth that will
actually happen so
uh tihi
[Music]
oh wow
nihongo
[Music]
i can't read
okay i tried to look up translate.google
and
the first search result that i
looked up was trust me and we will
escape from this city what was i even
looking up
ah
crony
[Music]
there's also a japanese version thank
you for the system voice in japanese
yeah
i hope you like it
[Music]
oh wow so many people prepared a lot and
you guys really didn't have to thank you
so much for that
man
[Music]
oh
even a poem
ah
made a cocktail to celebrate orocrony's
birthday
ooh
name of cocktail warden of time
oh
so cool
you guys want to see a clocktail hey
that's pretty good
okay let's see
[Music]
look
at this
bam
look at that
that's so cool i wonder how it tastes
like maybe blue raspberry
looks awesome
[Music]
but like if you mix up your drink it's
gets really hard on you
[Music]
i drink it right me too
goddammit
i have some cursed things too
[Music]
there's one from polka
kurome
[Music]
to
ah polka
oh wow miso also draws that's so nice
thank you
hmm
hey i see i see uh
stuffed with rainy and polka
[Music]
i can't wait to look through all these
i didn't have time to look uh look at it
today uh that much
until i finished it maybe 30 minutes
before the stream
because i was still working on the video
but
i'm really really glad
[Music]
oh wow speak of the devil thank you fong
oh man
these are so sweet
did you see the cameos
i don't know where they are i'm trying
to look for it
hmm
let's see
[Music]
scroll down i'm scrolling down as much
as possible
[Music]
posted it early okay
um
[Music]
i see a cake that was like you aged well
nice
wow these are so amazing
i always look at
um artists and
they're so talented
[Music]
and really tasty looking um
baked goods
really like that
oh my god
[Music]
i don't know if i can show this since
it's pokemon but my two favorite pokemon
latias and latios
oh my gosh
thank you
that's so cute
oh man you drew the pokemon so well
thank you thank you guys savage
yeah that's so cute
[Music]
3d oh
crony copter cake oh oh man
well you guys prepared so much
[Music]
wow
this is going to take forever for me to
look through
wow
i would like everything if i could
oh you guys died
wait no you guys are still alive you
liar
[Music]
ah
huh
[Music]
i found it
um
wait
i i found it i found it i'm gonna i'm
gonna ask
um
[Music]
man
i want it i want to watch it
[Music]
i'm asking i'm asking
it should be fine
[Music]
okay
let me
play
this
i think
[Music]
oh so cool
oh okay so i'll
read
um
happy birthday crony there's some
messages from johanna
the
uh
little sister little sister i lay
chester
i i never
knew how to pronounce it
um the laychester alliance and the
dresden empire wishing you a happy
birthday
who could these messages be from
[Music]
um
okay let's see
[Music]
oh
says that i can
yeah i can yes okay
sweet sweet
[Music]
sorry for taking my time
i just
[Music]
want to make sure that i don't
mess this up
[Music]
okay
there we go
building more hype
[Music]
okay let me uh turn off the
the music for this one
and just watch
[Music]
and
bam
then
this
and this
okay
cronie you've got a delightful national
holiday coming up that midnight is more
than ready to celebrate with you called
your birthday i know how i would
celebrate it i'd play a little fire
emblem and i suggest you copy me on that
one just sprinkle in a little
celebratory cake and you've got a
perfect recipe for a memorable adventure
hopefully you're able to give a hell
yeah fist pump to the sky for making it
another rotation around the sun i'm sure
you've got grand plans for the year and
how to make next year even more amazing
and if your plan is to just continue to
play a fire emblem from this birthday to
the next
just make sure to hydrate deal
it's joe ziji here the voice of claude
fire emblem three houses here you're a
fan that's awesome midnight wanted me to
congratulate you and give you a happy
birthday wishes for your birthday coming
up in march i hope you have an awesome
birthday surrounded by cool people that
you love and that love you um have fun
on your youtube channel it's super cool
i think youtubers are awesome you guys
do super unique work uh on
all these platforms it's really really
really cool i couldn't do what you do so
congratulations happy birthday fear the
deer
oh man happy birthday cronie this is
tyler and i play edelgard and fire
emblem three houses and midnight let me
know that it is your birthday so happy
birthday i hope that it is a wonderful
day and it's the start of a brand new
wonderful year
um
i know that you're a b tuber and that
one of your favorite video games is fire
emblem which is awesome so i hope you
enjoy all the roots but especially the
edelgard one because
it's awesome
and i hope that you have a great
birthday so happy birthday from me tara
also from edelgard and definitely from
midnight all right happy birthday all
the best
[Music]
ah
thank you
uh
oh amaze only singing
i can't let oh wait
oh that was close i almost
almost had to private my stream
okay
but oh van
thank you
oh that's so cool
yeah thank you so much midnight for
reaching out to
those people
and
yeah
wow i can't believe
[Laughter]
thank you
amazing so cute
oh wait i forgot to
turn turn the the the bgm back on
i'll make kamio
they say cameo
what the heck is wrong with me you know
what it's my birthday i can say whatever
i want
thank you so much
[Music]
i'm just gonna
you know look through
it's cannon
cannon
it's kamio from now on
oh times square is live
oh
wait how do i see that
i'm getting an ad
[Music]
it's live in 10 minutes oh i gotta stick
around for that then
[Music]
let's see if i can share it if not
um i'll be watching it
[Music]
enjoying your birthday yeah
oh man you guys don't have to
i'm just
i'm really happy thank
[Music]
you ah
man
this is
it's amazing
[Music]
thank you thank you guys
never
never really had a
birthday where everyone's celebrating it
for me like this
[Music]
i mean don't don't get me wrong i would
celebrate it with a small number of
people
but it's it's been a while since
uh
since i've celebrated it with
people i guess
at most i get cake and
treat myself
it's about it
and
you guys are so giving
[Music]
so thank you for that
now you get expired k yay
i'm gonna eat it after
i'll let you know if i'm sick
[Music]
oh so this is gonna happen
in
six minutes
i hope an ad doesn't pop up
because how would i explain
[Music]
and thank you everyone for the warm
wishes
and
just being here
for
giving me so many things
[Music]
how could we watch the times square um
if you look up times square live cam uh
there are
different things that show up
[Music]
i think there are no ads okay
and it seems like
[Music]
wait what the heck how do i
welcome to
oh god i went to a different place
[Music]
oh wait how do i go back
i i don't know how to navigate through
this
yeah which view
south
[Music]
the
nasdaq billboard
nasdaq
[Music]
this this place is
huge
[Music]
how's it
how's it even gonna happen
[Music]
it's a cylinder screen thing
i think i've been uh
been to times square once
oh
is it
the cylinder one
is it the one uh with
american eagle
at the very front
wait why is there a countdown
am i looking at the right thing
i'm looking at the right thing
yeah yeah the the tall building is it
that one
i'm looking at the one with the wavy
thingy
i can see mickey mouse
really i'm seeing psychedelic thing
that's the one we looking at
[Music]
man how did you even
arrange this that's amazing
[Music]
so it has a nasdaq logo at the bottom i
see a number at the top
let me let me let me look
i think that says
2 0 2 one
something like that
[Music]
i think that's two
i got the one okay nice
nice nice
[Music]
it's fine it's fine i'll probably
i'll probably find it
uh i'm at the times square south
[Music]
one minute
oh one minute one minute okay
yeah it's blue now it's blue
[Music]
yeah the blue waves
now it's orange
[Music]
the tall thing at the middle of it
how do you guys even see viewership i
don't even see that
[Music]
oh oh i found it i found it i found it
it's the one with 1.5
000 people 1.9 000 people
yeah it's the one with weird square
things around the cylinder right
[Music]
and there's like a weird ad
right
[Music]
it has a qr code am i seeing the right
thing
okay i'm looking at the many squares one
okay okay okay
[Music]
i don't see it
but happy no why am i saying that
yay happy birthday to me
says something like
it's ready new york
happy
birthday to me
thank you this is everyone's birthday
[Music]
hmm
wait what the heck why am i getting an
ad
thank you
i can't
i can't see it
maybe it was the wrong time
but
do you let me know
when it shows up
[Music]
unless it already showed up
thank you thank you
[Music]
so that's why you were talking about
blood clots
i wasn't looking at that part
yes these are very interesting ads
is that 300
[Music]
thank you thank you everyone
can someone
can someone clip it when they
find it later on throughout the day
because i wanna i wanna see
[Music]
is it because of daylight savings
we do a little crony
[Music]
do
okay now i see the blood clot and
hmm
daylight savings
gosh darn it
decentralizing soul
[Music]
so
does that mean
that it'll be ready
an hour later
is that it
[Music]
when am i gonna fix daylight savings
well you see
i feel like i will
mention this again but
you see
i am only a manager of time
i cannot interfere
i only report anomalies and i need to
wait for approval before i can take
action
it says civilization duty
yeah i just i just work in the office
and sometimes uh they give me the okay
to
use my tick tock
and then it's fun
who's your boss
time boss
[Music]
still an hour to go
wait it's on
oh oh oh oh it's on
[Music]
look it's on
it's on it's on it's happening
[Music]
yo
uh
[Music]
oh no it's gone
i want to show it on stream
[Music]
wow
that was awesome
yo that ad was so much better
than
all the ads included here
someone did you clip it did you clip it
please clip that one
oh man
[Music]
it's back to
it's back to souls
[Music]
again the next seven minutes it'll show
up yo let's do this let's do this
[Music]
then a new okay
oh yep
my
[Music]
my app is ready
so this is going to be showing up um
like all day
is that it
add watch along yeah
oh you can rewind the stream oh
oh okay
[Music]
did it when did it happen
oh oh there it is
[Music]
let's see
look at that look at that
i don't want to miss a thing
[Music]
get out get out app
i don't care if my app is ready
[Music]
okay
wait wait i gotta i gotta show the
specific time
[Music]
yes there we go there we go
yeah i gotta i gotta crop out the rest
uh
because this is the most important part
so we gotta we gotta look at this
oh my god
okay
watch this
[Music]
yo who animated that boros it's so
good ah
man
[Music]
these are so cool
so many art too
[Music]
man thank you so much guys
look at that just look at that
[Music]
for so much art
yo look at that transition get out of
the way i don't care about your ad
everyone's gonna see how great you guys
are
thank you
surrounded by so many
talented
and
amazing people i
wow
infinitely better than every ad on times
square that's right
[Music]
oh it's playing again
where
oh it's playing again okay well we gotta
watch it
[Music]
let's go
in real time
[Music]
and that outro is so good
where does that qr code lead to
[Music]
yo that's so cool
okay nope
nope i don't want to see other ads
we've seen enough blood clots and
apps being ready
it leads to the fan site
i want to say that where what's what's
it called
would it come up if i type fansite
orocrony
[Music]
huh
it's the discord
oh well let me just pull up my discord
now i'm just kidding
[Music]
crony no why
why no
wait
wait why
oh oh don't don't look
okay i don't want to spoil the fun
wait what's what's in it all right
should i not ask
[Music]
it's not allowed what do you mean that's
not allowed
can i
don't worry about the sight wait how bad
is this site am i supposed to be afraid
[Music]
it's not safe for crony
well that gets me kind of determined
crony fan site
[Music]
what is it called
huh
[Music]
why are you guys scattering
no one's saying anything okay
well you know what i do have a spare uh
spare phone so let me see if the
uh
the scan works
give me one second
uh
okay
all right
where's it where's the phone
huh
[Music]
okay
delete the evidence but
what is it
yeah you guys are such trolls
[Music]
uh let's see
move back to improve focus
is it too flat
it doesn't
doesn't detect it
[Music]
what are we talking about
come on what's the secret site about
crony
nasdaq
qr
hmm
[Music]
is there a is there a front view
of the nasdaq board
[Music]
uh
see
[Music]
yeah that's right i can use google
okay that's the same thing
[Music]
oh it's playing again
oh i missed it gosh darn it
i'm determined
[Music]
hmm
i'm gonna
i'm gonna try to scan it
huh
[Music]
i'm gonna
it's a fan discord server
[Music]
i see
crony is trying to get in this discord
server
[Music]
uh
laughs
[Music]
[Laughter]
ah
so this is what this is
[Music]
oh
let's see
let's see what this place is about
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
i see it i see
i see
very interesting
[Music]
well thank you guys for arranging this
it's
[Music]
[Laughter]
this is an interesting place
[Music]
i see so that's what you guys were up to
okay
interesting
um the bomb levels are negative 11
points now it's getting
[Music]
uh
it's fine
i'll leave
i'll i'll keep your privacy
but thank you everyone for
arranging it
[Music]
really appreciate it and this is this
has been a very interesting experience
like the cameos especially that was
really awesome
but
the qr code leads me to some very
interesting places
[Music]
hmm
it's okay i'll leave i'll leave
[Music]
wow
okay this
oh this this is a very new experience
okay
so that's why preach hat wanted me to
you know
leave pre-chat alone
i see it
there is an imposter among us
[Music]
oh it's playing again
i'll never get over this
[Music]
and all the arts are so nice
just looking at it my bad
[Music]
man
happy birthday to
[Music]
me and pretty much everyone i feel like
this isn't just my own birthday it's
everyone's birthday
[Music]
so
thank you
i keep saying thank you but
it's really because i'm
thankful
this is a birthday for the people
it's our birthday
yeah it's everyone's birthday
and since it's my birthday
i can do whatever i want
[Music]
and it's our birthday
and
i'm so glad to be celebrating
everyone's birthday
with my birthday
yeah
happy birthday to everyone
be sure to blow out the candles
um
are you guys ready to blow out the
candles
hey
five
four
wait no
happy birthday to you
happy birthday
dear
everyone
happy birthday to you
whoa
blow out the candles whoa
okay
three two one
[Music]
yeah
whoa
the flames have burned brightly but now
they have died
and so
shall our new journey start
[Music]
the cake will launch in three two no
i had a lot of fun
thank you guys
and
this is honestly
unforgettable
[Music]
hmm
happy birthday
[Music]
and you know what guys since it's
everyone's birthday be sure to treat
yourself
and i'm gonna treat myself to a nice
nice
nice cake
[Music]
are you a happy warden
hmm
[Music]
hey
um
birthday wishes
well i mean if i tell you what my
[Music]
it's not gonna come true so
i'm gonna have to keep it a secret
but i guess one of them would be
i hope
everyone can be happy
and
the kindness
that you've given me
[Music]
i hope um
that can be
given back in one way or another
and i hope
kindness will always be around you
hmm
[Music]
well
with that
i'm i'm gonna go treat myself to a nice
cake
so
you guys do the same
[Music]
and
yeah
uh crow korea sue me
and
i'll see you guys tomorrow
yeah eat the moldy cake
and
yeah
thank you
i really mean that thank you
[Music]
i feel like a wink isn't enough so
thank you
how
he
[Music]
you