[music]
JA
N
[music]
H
a
[music]
N
JA
[music]
DET
H
[music]
T
Let's go, on our shining path, an unstoppable grave
I want you
Fly as far as you like
You can do it, so believe it and run!
into the light
Get used to it
Days of nothing
look up
I wonder why my heart is empty
And the empty feeling is written in my mind
Ignore yourself like that
It's true, it's not supposed to be this way
I'm more excited
The things I say, my heart is filled by me
Come on, let's all go and shine with excitement
I want to send a smile just to you, forever
Fly
Big
Believe in it and run
It's a miracle
[music]
Hey everyone, thank you for waiting for the Hololive part.
4th motion meeting 2020
Yeah
Ibajibabababaji begins, begins, begins
From the beginning to the beginning, this year too.
The leader of the White group, Wolf and the Red group, will serve as the executive members.
I'm Samiko, the group leader, and this is the year.
Operated by Nesbaru as a complete executive.
Thank you for your participation in the proceedings.
Please, please
I'm the group leader's pickpocket. Thank you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, so this year
What do you think about being on the MC side?
How do you feel about it? I'm worried.
Yes, it seems that the worry has become a bed.
Is Kigumi okay? Has the distribution started?
Mom will be watching to see if there is any problem.
Everyone here looks like a complete mom.
I'm worried about my mom. I wonder if everyone is okay.
I've been in touch with you, which is kind of unusual.
I'm sure it's a great book with a great view.
I thought it would work out fine.
cage
I have prepared a lot this year as well.
Please pray for my success, I'm sure it will be a success.
Well, it's already at this point.
Yes, yes, and look at that opening.
I think you received it. Yes.
God Miyo came this year too.
I heard that God came down this year.
Hane anime opening style lyrics
Thank you for letting me compose it
Thank you very much, it was last year.
A song written and composed by Umata Ano.
I thought it would be like reusing the , but Masa
Yes, yes, I think you will do it again this year.
I thought Taorizu was really amazing.
Thank you for your praise.
Thank you very much
Thank you very much.
Today's hashtag is here, Hash
Tag Hololive Sports Day 2023 Kochihane
Mamiko also makes mistakes every time, Holo.
It's a live sports day, so everyone can't go wrong.
Please feel free to tweet like this.
Please please please
Well, let's start with today's program.
I'll take a look
Click here for today's program
Yes, it becomes a program like the one you see.
Miko will explain each competition.
Please, first of all, as usual.
The opening ceremony will be held at a certain
I don't know if there are any messages or not.
Yes, I feel like that.
And yes, the second event is Holomen half here.
All competitions have been newly implemented.
Wow, that's the first thing that's amazing.
Moko's holomen hunting is borrowed
It's a bit like competition, yes.
Yes, yes, try to get compliments that match the theme.
That being said, during practice, there were no questions asked at all.
I don't think it happened, but this is my first time.
It's quite spacious so I don't know what to expect.
No, it's quite pointy.Yes, it's pointy.
The third event is Hollow, aim for the top.
Up here is someone using the Trident
It's fine to aim higher than
It's a sport where there are a lot of people who are extremely passionate about it.
I've been practicing a lot.
Yes, yesterday too Yes, it's really amazing Yes
And then the whole competition will come. These are the two of us.
All of us will form a group and fight each other.
Yeah, we're going to fight, yeah, we're going to fight, it's simple.
I think that the tying exercise has become a fun sport.
Yes, yes, yes, that's good.
Well, we'll be participating as players, so let's go.
I won't give up, I'll do my best.
Let's do our best, yes and sesame 5
The event is called "Gogomagome" and the event is called "Hihikoshi".
In the role of Ehi and the role of a knight, it is a race.
Until we can work together and aim for the goal.
As for whether Mohime is Maraku, that's not the case at all.
Leadership has become more important than ever
Yes, this competitive princess is having a really hard time.
Yes, yes, yes, it became a cooperative game.
After that, the 6 events are spring, summer, fall, and winter.
Spring, Summer, Autumn, Winter, Yes, that's right
Hey, it's dangerous, so I'm going to go now, spring, summer, and autumn, and I'm not going to leave it alone.
I was a little nervous when I heard that.
It's okay. What kind of sport is this?
Therefore, it has become an obstacle relay.
So let's all do half a lap each time.
It was the final competition, where players had to connect the
After that, the ceremony will be closed.
Yes, yes, that doesn't mean we won this year too.
We'll have to fight for that goal, but okay then.
Next, I would like to introduce the members.
Here it is, please aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Hololive JP Hololive English
Hololive Indonesia and Hololive
A total of 39 members participated from their devices
Thank you for doing that.
Yes, teams will be chosen by lottery in advance.
It will be randomly distributed.
It looks like this, but yes
What do you think? Everyone, red team, white team, yellow team, yes.
The attention line is really full now.
Is it warm? Is it warm?
There's a lot left over, after all.
I see, there are quite a few things like Father.
Show your leadership and help everyone
He put it together for me, etc.
After all, the new members are really
All the new members of the red, white and yellow team
He worked really hard at practicing.
Everyone, seniors and juniors practice together.
I'm sure you did, so please come by.
Thank you very much for your support.
Please, what do you think of the group? What do you think?
We have all the craftsmen, and the craftsmen are also competing in various competitions.
It's like Tsui of those who have mastered it.
Oh, that's true, isn't it?
Both the voice and the cat had an amateurish time.
I'll see if there's a follow-up as well.
I'm pretty good at any sport.
There's an image that it's coming out.
I seriously don't seem to know how to follow up.
That's because everyone is so good at it.
I'm looking forward to it too.Okay, finally Mio-chan.
What do you think of the white team? Yes, the white team is pretty good.
We have a strong sense of unity and everyone else
It seems like there are a lot of older sisters, that's for sure.
Yes, that's right. Members around me.
Even though I'm busy, I'm holding on to it like this.
Azu-san and Kanea-san should proceed.
I was doing something like that, and Makia translated it.
There's a lot of strength that comes with giving things like that.
I think it might be Chim.Yes.
Yes, by the way, it's today.
Raden is not feeling well and will be taking a day off.
I'm sorry that it happened.
Demachotoaama Holomen Hunting
As for that, I'm sure someone will come out as a pinch hitter.
I think it will be in the form of a gift.
This means that there is one person missing from the line.
What a sudden replacement.
And I'm going to have Nekomata Okayu join us.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, thank you.
He's a pinch hitter. Thank you.
Calls within each team 2
It is divided into sections: Red group AB White group
There are two locations in the form of ABB of ABB Kigumi.
Since it is divided, please feel free to share it individually.
Please hide it and enjoy the conversation.
I would appreciate it if you could. Yes, please, please.
Yes, and participate in each competition.
I would like to introduce the members.Yes.
Here are the members participating in the first three competitions.
Okay, here it is.
Okay, what do you think? Everyone, Holomen.
To be honest, the topic of hunting is different.
At this point, there's no way to practice.
I can't help it, I'm a little sleepy after all
It's like knowledge.
hey
So what will happen in the book?
I feel like that's something I don't even understand.
I don't know, but the group has been working out a strategy.
Is that the case regarding this?
It's a bit of fun teamwork too.
By the way, follow-up is for each cat.
The whole team is practicing hard to win.
That's right, so what's really going to happen?
It feels like the first half I don't know, yes.
I already want to support everyone.
Let's go with the feeling that yes, then the second half
Here are the members participating in the two competitions.
It has become
Yes, yes, yes, Yumesei Race and Shiksht
Yeah, yes, the dream voice race is fine.
It seems like it's an image of someone making a plan and doing it.
But as the Red Team,
When the princess says yes, yes, the princess is quite true.
I can do it like a sense of command.
I feel like I want to protect and protect now.
Yes yes yes yes I've seen that
After all, I have a lot of experience.
I think it's great to have a great sense of insight.
I thought so, but what about you two?
I see, what's going on with the white team? I see.
Kana-tan has a pretty good summary.
There is something like power to all of you.
Maybe be kind, maybe I'll do something about it.
It feels like I can fly my fingers pretty well.
Looks pretty good for the type.
It looks like I'm going, and the group is no group.
Hanemou Iris, also known as Princess Hanemou, is Princess Hanemou.
That's right, I'm already a cheerful princess.
It's been a long time since I've given accurate instructions.
I just talked to Mari-chan.
Looks like you got a good time. I contacted you.
I want to sleep a bit. Good luck, mom.
I'm looking at books, and my mom is looking at new kids.
Well, I'm participating, and finally.
Yes, yes, these cats are also sleeping.
It was spinning around. It was spinning.
I was practicing.Yes, this is also a little bit like this.
It's likely to be a game where you don't know if your team will win.
The pressure of the actual performance is also the last one.
That's why I'm so nervous
I think you will, but please do your best.
Please do your best.Yes, yes.
Well then, let's move on to the opening ceremony.
I think so.
All players will be admitted in a timely manner.
Aaaaaaaaaa
Hello, I'm here. Hello.
Do you know where I am?
You know what? I don't understand this. It's scary.
Here we are, we're just positioning the camera.
I don't know but everyone is amazing
I'm looking forward to it. I'm out in the hallway.
I'm jumping out of here. Let's have some interaction.
It's amazing inside the school. It's really inside the school.
Well then, this is it.
I think I'll call you then.
Red team members please enter.
I wonder if Masukore-chan will be able to come?
[Laughter]
keep it up
water
This year is great, this year is great
It's a cat
[music]
It's desu
Yoda
Hey there!
It's not white, it's dark
Oh, that's nice, beautiful, beautiful, wonderful
Right, this is Mel, Mel, Mel.
This year too, he is a genius.
Some people are missing from the yellow group.
But I'm still a little hesitant.
Together with Aja Shiori, who came with me.
Hey, let's stay here with mom.
Let's come here together.
Are you making an announcement? I said yes.
Next, everyone from the white group, please enter.
I hope it's the white group.The orchestra is okay, after all.
I'm calm
It's the cat. It's here. Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, that's great, that's amazing, that's beautiful, that's difficult.
So what was the red team like earlier?
Well, it's true that there are a lot of kicks.
yes
This is the white group of power.
Hey, it's because of that yellow group in the end.
Can I have it? Next, let's talk about the group.
Everyone please come in. Good luck Shiri-chan
Good luck, it's okay, I'm hiding.
I feel for you too, so here it is.
There is no sillette mixed in here.
Maybe
[applause]
Here we are, fighting each other, really fighting each other
More and more
Fall
I'm not saying this, just a little bit.
It looks like they have a signboard for the group.
Where did you get that from, mom?
This is the signboard that was installed by the wearer.
But somehow Shiori-chan is the only one in pink.
I have a signboard
yellow to
freedom
We have too many
hey
Yes, yes, but everyone is lined up and I love you
So first of all, Hololive Grand Sports Day self.
Ms. Miko, a member of the team, would like to give a greeting at the convention.
I'll do it, everyone.
Hello meow
Hello everyone gathered again this year!
Thank you very much for your help.
Even though you are busy, seniors and juniors really help each other.
Until today, even in practice, please keep working hard.
I think so, but today is the actual event.
Let's all do our best and win!
I hope you can pick them.
First of all, let's have fun and win
That's what I'm aiming for, everyone.
Please enjoy today. Thank you very much.
Please, please
[music]
Thank you very much.
Next, President of Cover Co., Ltd.
I have received a message from Mr. Yago.
It has arrived. As always, see you there.
Check out this amazing
Thank you to all Hololive members for your hard work.
I am Motoaki Tanigo, the representative of Cover Co., Ltd. and the voice of Torishima.
Today is the sports day that everyone has been waiting for in town.
When I was in elementary school, I thought of group gymnastics.
I remember practicing hard.
Flo Live has been practicing until the event.
Dear members, and today's
Miko and Mio have been preparing for this event.
Subaru, thank you very much for your hard work.
Let's cooperate with each other at today's sports day
Encourage each other and fight bravely until the end
Let's do it. And usually Hololive
To everyone who supports the production
Thank you so much for practicing until today.
To all the Hololive members who have
Please pay attention to our efforts and support us.
Dear Hololive members,
Please be careful not to get injured.
With that said, I would like to give my opening remarks.
Aim for itadakimasu
It's great to win, we should aim for the championship.
It was great to aim for the win.
It's about Principal Nema, so everyone.
Mone is Iwatto and Zeta and a little bit.
I was listening while looking far away.
Please look at it, it's actually on the flower bed.
Shion-tan Shion-tan
Sakaakaakaaka, listen to Naga-sensei's story for a moment.
Please, I was just listening to you.
Talk, don't listen, don't listen, listen, team
Yes, I told you to do your best.
keep it up
It's rough, but it's getting more and more amazing every year.
I feel like I'm getting better at it.
It's something like ne de de de de de de de de de de de de de de ne.
Thank you.
Lastly, I would like to have a player take the lead.Yes.
Red team, Tokoyami and San, white team, Asanun, and wood group.
Mr. Hacos Bells, what is this?
mosquito
Please come to the table, please.
Masukara
Please excuse me for a moment, the wooden group is a little
I wonder if the problem is the courtesy fee? HakosuHakosu
Come on come on hakosu hakosu hakosu hakosu
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah that was good
That's good, that's good, that's good.
Is it okay? Can I go? Is it okay?
No, it's okay. Yes, it's okay. Hey.
I would be happy if the player teacher could do it for me.
Is that okay? Yes, that's it.
Please
Mr. Masu
I
as a Hololive member
The teacher is hijacking sportsmanship.
I'll use it to fight cute 2023
November 4th Red Team Representative Tokuyama Toa White Team Representative
Azuki Yellow Representative Haspels Yay
Yay Depa Depa Awesome Awesome
That's wonderful thank you very much
Then all three of you can come in.
thank you
Who threw the bread from here to here?
Yes, from here, thank you.
That concludes the opening ceremony.
This is the end. Well then, everyone.
Move to the Holomen hunting venue.
please move
I'm going over here. Everyone, let's go.
Excuse me
Masu-ani-san, oi-ani-san, let's go, ani-san.
Sanani
I want to have Ani-chan-chan-chan
Oh home hunting go go go
Go go go
Go go go, yes, so the first one
The competition is holomen hunting Haimiko
Please introduce me to Holomen.
Hunting has become like a competition for borrowed goods.
Three hunters were selected from each team.
It became a competition to catch the fleeing home.
The red team, the white team, and the yellow team are in order.
Each team takes on the challenge and completes this twice.
The second week of the opposite role is played by a different person.
Three people will compete.The rules of the competition are
The theme will be announced to everyone, so the hunters will
I took the praise that matched the theme to the prison.
You don't have to show it like that.
The subject doesn't have to look so good.
There are 3 questions in total, and each question can send as many people as you want to the prison.
You can bring whatever you want.
Give the most praise for the correct answer that matches the topic.
The group that came will win, and the score is 1.
15 points 2nd place 10 points 3rd place 5
It is a point
Looks like I'll have to get some tests done.
hey
Yes, I want to win in this competition, in this competition.
Is there a point for this?
I guess you could really call it knowledge.
That question is, for example, how many centimeters or smaller is the home?
Yeah, there are some things like that.
It's coming, isn't it? Yes, yes, what about that?
It's like, ``I wonder if it was?'' but it's fine.
It's difficult, isn't it?
Are you going to catch it with a guessing trick?
Or like, let's go to this person.
Teamwork is also important.
I think so. Yes, that's right.
Yes, this time it's about rice hunting.
When I say practice, I'm not seeing the subject for the first time.
That's right, because it has to be done.
It didn't really feel like practice.
So now I'm rather holo
Do you have knowledge of the live members?
I think that's the point
Well, that's the correct topic.
We manage that group to make sure they are treated equally.
The team worked hard together and did their best.
By the way, that duck statue
It's still there, take that.
Is that okay? Hey, everyone, viewers.
Dear Mr., this is a bit of unfortunate news.
It's not a pity or anything, but as expected
I don't think you'll stay until the actual performance, do you?
This is according to Subaru's request.
First of all, before we start, what are your wishes?
I don't have any, so I don't know when to take this.
This is the work you can do
But whatever I said, it's gone.
I want this
in
I said yes, so I took off my nipples.
It's okay if it doesn't show up on the screen.
But yesterday, there was a white thing up here.
Yes, there was one, but this one was removed.
After all, the problem is difficult, but it's like this.
It would be a bit difficult if
We have made adjustments so that you cannot climb on it.
It says that things have changed, so I'll do my best and run around.
Please do your best.Yes, please do your best.
Well then, I want to join the Red Team.
I wonder if it's okay? Yes, it's the first game.
hunter fly bestia zeta and
Mr. Selsfarne and Inamis before Ne
It's hard to hear, but there are 2 games.
The hunter of eyes is going on his own path.
The sound of the sky is clear and the rose is clear
Hello everyone from the red team can you hear me?
Can you hear me?
I can hear you all enthusiastic.
I would like to ask who you are?
Is there anyone who can tell me? First of all, let's talk about that.
One game, yeah yeah
Zeta Yes, I practiced hard. I did my best.
I worked really hard, I tried my best
You worked really hard, Minecraft.
I feel like I still don't understand it a little bit.
So please practice a lot. Thank you for your hard work.
Really
Thank you very much
Thank you, I'll do my best, do my best, do my best
By the way, that guy has some kind of plan.
Operation Masuka
Yeah, hunting plan.
hunting plan
[music]
Ade slot game is about to start
Let's go with passion, let's go with passion
Let's Passion Passionate So
Passion Passion Plan Passion
I said let's go with the plan.
Yes please do your best yes yes
Well then, let's talk about that blue color.
How is it for your first time at the Sports Hall?
And how do you feel about the first event? Yes.
That's right. I would tie that person up like this.
I haven't had any experience like this yet, so I'll leave it at that.
I'll do my best.
Do your best, do your best, tie everyone up
What does everyone have?
What does this have? This is a pom-pom.
I'm going to do it, pon pon pon pon, okay?
Hey, you're cute. Please do your best. No, you're cool.
So it's cool, cool, cool
That's cool, thank you for your support
Please do your best, everyone.
Mihai I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best
Please be patient, thank you very much
Now, please stand by.
I'm really looking forward to it, I'm really looking forward to it.
It may be a theme that we have thought of.
Well, that's the reaction, isn't it?
I'm looking forward to it. I'm really looking forward to it.
All the hunters of the red group, please come.
Tachia okay entry okay
Thank you.
Dung
Yes, it would be amazing if I could catch this.
I don't even know if that's the case, actually.
I think the difficulty level of the problems will increase considerably.
No, that's right, I guess it's a coincidence.
Will you catch it soon?
It's a bit up to you, maybe
It seems that there is a possibility that there are many deviations.
Hey, sorry, Zeta is still asleep
Hey, I might not have been able to enter it just now.
It's true that I didn't do it, but now I'm done.
It's okay, it's okay
Are you okay? Yes, I'm fine.
Can we start?
Do your best, are you okay?
So the first challenge is yes.
Please wait a little longer
Right, okay. Well, I'm the first one.
I also sleep a little bit like that.
I think there is, but yes, Minami Achinami.
Hey here, viewers watching right now.
Is it a request or a mindset?
It's just a feeling, but I'm sure something will happen.
Mone, please support me with your warm comments.
I hope you all enjoy it.
Looks like a viewer, maybe a guardian.
I wish you could watch over me with all your heart.
As for the 10 items, I feel grateful and grateful.
That's right, there are so many people.
Partly because they gathered together.
After all, I can't help but get angry about something.
Yes, there is a possibility that this could happen.
Well, if nothing happens, that's it.
That's wonderful though.
There's a real possibility that something will happen.
I hope you can see the area softly.
Masune yes yes please
Masu
So what do you think? I wonder if we can go soon?
Can I go?
[music]
Well, in a place like this, after all.
It's great to be able to see individual rules.
Yeah, that's right. It's definitely like this.
Many members are chatting
It doesn't happen very often, so I'm sure it's something
It's a bit nice, isn't it?
That fish in the water is quite fun just to look at.
It looks like it's coming out. Stop it. God is here.
I'm scared of God sometimes and the fish in the tank
I'm sure there's a better way to say it, but it's swimming.
After all, seniors are juniors.
Or rather, she recently made her debut.
The same goes for EL members and JP.
It's the same with Rigro-chan, but everyone.
Thank you for participating. Let's have a little interaction this time.
I think he brought it a lot as an opportunity.
That's what I'm thinking, so please enjoy.
I hope I can get it, so this is my first time participating.
The most important thing is for the members to enjoy it as well.
Yeah, I was nervous because I wanted her to have good feelings.
I guess there were a lot of people who seemed to be doing it.
I hope we can open up more about this in the future.
I hope we can connect here.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Is it time to go?
I wonder what the situation is like now.
I see. I'll just have to make some adjustments now.
So I guess the game is being adjusted.
Looks like it's in now, listener.
Please wait a moment. Please wait.
Yes, thank you. By the way, last year
Who won last year?
hair
It's hard to say, ``I hear you,'' but I keep hearing it.
The white team is winning, we will stop this this year.
It seems like a possibility, with Nemikoteme.
I'll do my best. I really want to win this year.
So why is the white team always winning?
I don't really understand it either.Every time I say it quite a bit.
It's true that it was such a close battle, but it was the last one.
The point difference is really small, yeah yeah yeah
Something like that happens every year.
Yes, yes, every year, every year.
It seems like the red team is really strong, according to every review.
It looks like it's going to be splashed, maybe it's someone other than the white team.
Yes, but I heard that you have received something.
I'm not going to take it this time.
Not this time, this time I'll be eating Himegumi.
No, it's red, so it's red, and by the way, which sport is it?
Is there something you are most confident about?
Yeah, no, but I feel like I'm confident in my voice.
But I guess that's the deciding voice.
This team has also improved quite a bit.
I have an image of it, but honestly I don't like it.
Hunting I can really see the competition I'm about to do.
I don't think so, ha ha ha what will happen?
I don't know, but it's actually pretty big here.
Maybe, but yes, by the way.
Well, let's go first.
There are some themes that we have thought about.
Yes, I thought about it as a whole.
It's kind of like what we think
It's like thinking all the time.
We have created a new theme for you, so please enjoy it.
I would appreciate it if you could give me a yes.
The first challenge that has kept everyone waiting for a long time.
It's the red team.Let's go.Okay.
Okay
The start is something like that, too.
But please do your best, Aremi-san.
Please wait a moment and do your best too.
Good
Ok, the first topic is Hololive.
english
So here it is, the time is 6060 seconds.
Holo will be displayed within 60 seconds.
How long should I take live English?
I'll do my best to see if this happens
It's nice, but
The iris is coming tomorrow
The right side is pretty good, no, it's pretty good
[music]
Hey, good, secured number 4
I'm running away, I'm running away, I'm running away
I'm running away. I'm finally out.
I'm listening to Operation Spider Ubu.
cloud
[music]
That's right, 4 seconds 3 seconds 2 seconds seconds left
I'm here
[music]
I'm scared, what do you think? I'm looking for a
Masu
Not just wobbly
is
[music]
do not have
Because I'm Masumo Chibi
Neose
I'm looking for
I'm sleeping Anya is made by Spider
Made by Spider It's here. It's here. Look for it.
It's in Mineyellow Pyramid.
The yellow pyramid clouds are surprisingly strong.
There are quite a lot of images that seem to be there.
Yes, JP is more
I'm in a state where I want to take it with me.
I want to give it to someone. Who is in this?
Kiara is surprised that there is someone who wants to give it to her.
Terua is sticking out
It's really Sui-chan
Please just catch me, if there's any left
A bit of cod
I'm sad, but if possible, I'd like you to catch me.
It's just an impression, right? It's an impression.
I'm confident
Everyone has a great appeal
Masu
Nea I'm failing
Nede de
It's my soul, dear
I'm a little bald, but it's hard to find anymore
I don't think so, but the topic will change.
inside
There
[music]
No way, it's so big!
I don't think the appeal will start in chat.
In the end, it's definitely me. It's me.
How was it? It was quite interesting.
Hey, it's a bit interesting after all.
This seems like it, and quite a few people are saying it.
It's really fun to see what's going on
Mio-chan seems like she wants to give it to her, but yeah.
List all the relevant people together
I'm sure there are many of them.
Even though you don't seem like there are many of you, you have quite a personality.
I'm looking at that part. That's right, no.
There were a lot of people, but it was quite difficult.
Yes, it was difficult, but the number of people secured was 7.
It looks like this.
It's amazing, it's amazing, it's amazing, it's amazing.
Well, I would like to interview you.
How was everyone at Masuyu?
[music]
I'm laughing so hard about it. It's fun.
I wanted it, it was good, it was good.
Good, what was difficult?
Even if you say yes, yes, you are tall.
Be careful. It's difficult.
It's hard to do that, right?
That's amazing, we secured 7 people and Zeta was the first
I was so impressed with Tanais.
Play amazing amazing
It was a really nice play
I've already caught 4 nice pauna.
Karane Pauna 4 Pipo is amazing Pipo, it's strong
Yes, it's strong
Thank you to all the hunters of the first game
thank you
Please keep up the good work, Senkyu.
Jibugujibu is all about money.
That's true. Next is Maa's JP.
As a member, hey, it's the white group.
Oh yeah, I made a mistake with everyone in the white team.
This is the White Team. So to everyone in the White Team,
I would like to interview you.
Yes, the first game flies
[applause]
[music]
There are three overseas members, Kae and A.
Yes, I would like to hear your enthusiasm.
But the second hunter
Introducing Mr. Hunter in the match.
I will introduce Captain Noel and
It's nice to meet you. That's good.
That's why all the Shiranosasan players can hear it.
Can you hear me? Can you hear me?
First of all, how about some kind of strategy?
Is there such a thing?
from
have the right people
The everyone for now
Are you serious about catching me? No, no, that's off topic.
It's good not to use it.
Yes, I see, we are the ones in the second match
I'll use my power to catch Mone and Kono mo.
If everyone hits the demon, someone will hit a few.
I want to do that but I have too much money.
That's the white team, that's the power.
Quite surprisingly, we survived with white power.
I'm coming over, and I just saw the topic earlier.
How does it feel? I thought I was going to go.
What is monoya?
Kotomi Mio Tepa makes me want to protect her.
Who is the cutest member?
But yeah, yeah, who is that me?
It was included, Mio-senpai, no, that's it.
Please how was it?
Don't make me use na
I wonder if that's it. I wonder if the rest is good morning. This is so.
You might be interested in it.
I'm waiting
That's what I think
Twitch, do your best, do your best
Neehai
Thank you very much yes
Thank you, who is doing the subvoice?
But yes, thank you very much.
So, everyone, please stand by.
Masu
Okay, so the white team is on standby.
It'll be a while until it starts.
I would like to do things like that.
Who is that?
Was that what you wanted to protect, for example, Ame?
That's right
Oh, what else?
Um, that's right, there are too many targets, so remember.
There were so many things that didn't exist.
It's so [ __ ] messed up
I don't think so.
I didn't include anything like Shiro.
I feel like I've put it in there or something.
There are too many subjects and my memory is buggy.
Well, well, well, well, we'll see later.
What I mean is that I want to make it public.
I think that
There are more unique questions.
Looks like yes, I'm looking forward to it.
Please, yes, this is the white team.
But you know, Raden is taking a little break.
That being said, those ABCs are amazing.
Raden, who is appealing, is on vacation.
It looks like it has a katan in it instead.
Yes, that's good, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, but it's fine. The white team is the first.
It was like a story about your sister.
Maybe I should open the lid and listen to the story.
It's a bit like power is power.
Just having Kanata gives me a little bit of power.
All the responsibility lies with you.
You seem to be able to do it. You have a strong grip.
But I'm sure she'll catch it once.
I feel like there's no such thing.
Yes, she does have a bit of an older sister vibe.
I definitely want to win like this after all.
and a passionate feeling towards fear.
I think you could see that.
I'm pretty sure it was the same game Fauna from earlier.
Yes, out of the 7 people who caught 4 people, this is amazing.
Yeah, it's pretty amazing. It's a dark horse. I'm looking forward to it.
So these first seven people are one thing.
It may become a standard number.
That's right. Is there more than 7 people?
What will happen again? How about the next game?
Hey, what do you think? I think we've got the number of people already.
But is it okay to start?
What do you think? What do you think? What do you think?
Not yet?
It's amazing that the chocolate line is running around forever.
but
I'm sure Chase is practicing on the field.
Yes, but
Polka is the first to hit me again.
I'm a little worried, but is your mom okay?
I wonder if it's okay.
Just saying you're here is everything.
It's 100 points, so I'm sure everyone is happy now.
I wonder if that's what it is. I spent this time thinking up a strategy.
Tarito
Looks like they're fighting each other somehow.
I wonder if some of us are
I think it was appealed or something.
I guess it's not like that.
Isn't that an appeal?
It seems like it was in there.
Looks like I'm ready.Ao, I'm ready.
Well then, please do your best.
Well, let's say it's the white team's challenge.
Let's go. Then I'll press this button.
Well, please, I'll go.
Good luck with your start, let's go, let's go, let's go!
Go
Some people are out for a while
But this is the white team, the white team
So, first of all, let's talk about the topic.
Debut from 2021 to 2022
This is a little difficult Noe Hollow Live
The frog that the member caught caught
I'm catching some early, early, early floats.
I caught the slope, I know the color rules.
mosquito
It's a mosquito
Yo kapakulik
not pa
Tao, rain fails, Nechan and Nea are suitable.
That's what I'm talking about now
Nete means a little while ago.
Yeah, it's like after the lab.
Is it in front of Kai Pora or in front of me?
It's the year
It looks like it's right, but I think it will fit in.
I want to get a hologram, but please touch the sign properly
Can you touch it?
This is Masune. By the way, the rope is
Even if it stretches out, if you touch the signboard, you can enter.
Although it is a specification, it is probably not understood.
Maybe it's not done yet. This is bad.
is
Other
bad hairstyle
[music]
That's it
It was difficult for the Shortcut members.
It feels like guessing the member with the hair of
I don't think it's going to happen that much.
Everyone is inside this yellow play equipment.
I'll find you frozen
or maybe this
However, I haven't touched the board yet.
That's terrible. This doesn't understand the rules.
It's terrible
Signboard The rain is thawing The rain is thawing
That means you can include it.
Mel-chan is also not Mel.
The title has changed, but the title has changed to Holo.
Miko says this is the final title.
Capturing Holo Kids Kids
Good luck kids!
I have it in
As a kid, I think Iris is different.
Well, Iris is also a big sister.
There are different festivals and festivals.
Surprisingly, she's my older sister.
Who the heck is a kid? Probably me.
I'm aware that I'm running away.
Good luck, there are a lot of them.
There are so many, so who's the best?
I just finished watching it and it was painful.
No, it was quite a struggle.
There are so many kids who wonder who they are.
Well, there are certainly a lot of red teams.
Now that I think about it, there seems to be a lot of yellow.
Is that so? By the way, who is it?
I guess Shion is definitely a good choice.
Maybe so, so yes, yes.
It's okay to say that the game is over.
I was struggling with this.
Maybe I didn't touch that sign.
By the way, the touch of the signboard looks like that.
Yes, the clicks are slightly different between the right and left sides.
Ah yes, maybe that was a little difficult.
That said, the next step is
Is it a wooden group?
Okay, now, what kind of battle will the Kigumi show?
I don't know if I'll get it, but the wooden group is going to get it.
I did a lot of holo hunting too.
Yes, we all took the initiative
I was planning a lot of strategies, so that's what happened.
I was hoping it would go well.
But yes, that strategy is actually power.
That's right, let's catch them all, everyone.
It's power. Is that a strategy?
No, but maybe it will work out.
I'm rooting for you so much, then.
Well then, let's go to the interview. To all the white people.
Okay, everyone in the white team, give it a try.
How was it?
Or hello halo halo halo
was difficult
Difficult, big yes, difficult
If you touch that difficult signboard, it will be a signboard.
touchtao
Opolo Kids Understood Hololive Kids
Hololive Difficult Difficult Meme-Holokids
Hameholo Kids Jesus Swiss
Slochio
Kematsuri is erotic brat festival is no horokino
Kids No Kids Issumatsu is mediocre.
That's what I thought, but I guess so
It must have been a little difficult, right?
The title is still that nice fight.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much
Thank you very much and please do your best
As a continuation, the White Team has to catch two people.
has been completed
Oh, this one was a little overtaken by the red team.
Okay, what do you think about yellow?
We'll see what happens, yeah, do your best, yellow, yeah
I'm watching mom. There are more than two Kiras here.
If you get it, you'll be in 2nd place in the first game.
I don't even feel it, but I wonder what's going to happen
I don't know, it could be 221
Yes, it's like, yes, yes.
Well then, we'll start as soon as you're ready.
But I think he's quite nervous.
Crony: Yes, Kuro, do your best.
I'm going to the interview with the yellow team.
Please wait a moment, yellow group.
Please wait a moment until the interview is complete.
Yes, please wait a moment Yes, yes, great.
I wonder where everyone got this sign from?
Did you come? I brought some bread with you, right? I'm in the classroom.
I've put it there, yes, but next time...
It's a challenge for the yellow team.Okay here, the wood team.
I would like to interview everyone in
I think the hunter in the first game was Watari Kadomaki.
Potty polka Anya Melfissae
And the hunter in the second game is Toki no Sora Natsuiro
It's a festival Hasbells, so do your best.
Please do your best, I can hear you.
I can hear it
Everyone will do their best, please do your best
Please do your best. How are you doing?
Do you think it will go well today?
Do your best and pass the passion
passion
Medical
[music]
Passion Sui are you okay?
Shinmen
A bit of mental and physical passion
Everyone talks about how much they love each other
Sugi-san, Sa-san, Hai-san, something
Umm, do you have any particular aspirations?
I have a mental problem
[laughter]
Newatari
San-san, can I have a moment please?
We are strong for the moms who understand
Good luck!
I'll do my best and I'll win
I will win for my stubborn mom. Will my mom cry?
I'm lonely
How is it lonely? This tone is a bit of a joke.
I want it, thrusting into me.
want
Good luck, I'm not sure if the lotus is alive or not.
Lotus is alive Yes, it is alive Lotus
That voice, that voice, is already pushing you into life.
Good, it's tough, please do your best.
Can I get some enthusiasm from you? Yes.
Yes, mental and physical for mom
There are people playing Passion.
Hey, do your best
How about Ne-chan and Ne-chan? I have some knowledge.
I think it's necessary, but I'm confident.
I don't know about Kakei, but it's mental.
It's okay if you have physical passion
It's a word of information. Let's get along. I'll do my best. Let's get along.
Good luck, Mac-chan and Sora-chan.
Good luck. Good luck. That's it.
Thank you very much everyone
If you're on standby, please, I'm playing.
It's so, so powerful! It's so powerful!
It seems that just being able to read is not enough.
Neme was helping me.
It's rare and seriously rare. Let's get along well and do our best.
I would like to have it
I guess Nesakigumi is pretty okay.
Okay, well then, Emikochi as well.
Is the start button ready? Yes.
Please wait a moment. Thank you.
Yes, the fugitive is now reset.
I became a fugitive.
Would you like to enter again, Mom?
I'm sorry, it's okay, calm down.
One entry, one more entry
Entry
Please, baby, mommy, I have to say this too.
I thought I was able to do it.
I'd like to get started then.
Okay, let's take on the challenge. Good starting point.
Okay, what's the problem going to be?
What's going to come out? Okay, first of all.
The first theme is that the level will be this year, 2023.
This is also clear
I think my memory is quite clear and clear.
I got caught. Good luck with this.
This thing is gone right away
That's nice. Two people right away.
But yeah, I'm catching it.
That's great, that's great, just touch the board
It's okay, everyone, Omo
I'm so happy. Mel-san is me for some reason.
I agree with you, Hatsumen.
I say that I am also a newcomer.
This is not the initial stage, but the feelings of a newcomer.
I haven't forgotten, everyone, because I forget.
Now the topic has changed.Okay, the topic has changed.
Look for people who are taller than 160cm.
That's how it feels. It's surprisingly good.
That enid member is a really high-ranking member
There were so many that Kaela was caught too.
I got caught. Yellow is in pretty good shape.
Okay, there are 8 wonderful yellow people.
Yo, this is dancing in first place.
Please say hello, there's still time.
Do your best, can you still find it?
Wow, Noel has been arrested, Noel.
teeth
Better
After all, the members of Nee are tall.
Right now, right now
Haha, I have a small image, though.
I agree, Chan did her best too.
Everyone's legs look sexy
Throw
Dasaae has changed.
Neat lie
Right?
Lol fails also fails
Worried about swelling
sincerely
[music]
hand
I guess this is rare
hamo
[applause]
different
who
Please stop it
Stop it.
Yo
Just kidding, kidding
N
Sorry for leaving it behind.
Hey, no, no, everyone, just leave it alone.
I can't get Subaru's thread to be assembled.
and here
I guess there weren't that many, right?
No, that's true.
I think there were about 3 people on the team, yes.
I see, that's right.
But you know, it's number 1, so it's worth a lot of points.
I didn't get it, it's amazing that I won 1st place.
It's amazing! All the yellow people are so good!
If you have any complaints, please contact Subaru Ozora personally.
chat
We have been accepting complaints up until now.
Please chat privately, okay then.
Would you like to interview me please?
Yes, that's it, everyone in the wood group, try it.
How was it?
I feel sorry for this.
But no, this is Subaru after all.
It depends on the person who thinks it's neat and clean.
It really depends on who you are.
I was in it at first
I thought he was a hidden success character.
I did, but it happened so I didn't know what happened after that.
After talking about various things in chat, I thought it might be different after all.
I took it off thinking
There was an exchange
I don't want to do it, but it's interesting, everyone.
That's amazing. There were 12 people. It was amazing.
wonderful
I'm praising you. It's your mother's pride. It's yellow.
team
But it's not bubbabu a bit
I'm doing my best. Go ahead, mom.
I'll go then, do your best.
Mr. Aim
[music]
I said thank you and said yes to that first game.
Thank you to all the hunters
Please do your best even after Tako. Good luck.
Please do your best.
Well then, it looks like we got the score for the first game.
So I would like to announce those first.
Here is the point
So what's the number of the yellow group?
It was 15 points, so the red team got 10.
Points: White team has 5 points
It has become
I see, there is a possibility that he will sleep in the second game.
Yes, there is, so I hope the white team does its best.
That's right, that's right, what do you think?
I just started so I don't know anything about it
Yes, I don't know, without counting the temperature.
Let's go
Okay, well then, let's move on to the second half.
There will be new themes in the second half.
Yes, I have prepared everything properly.
Iha-dono is watching, isn't he?
The appeal is amazing.It's amazing.
Are you saying you won't protect me?
That's right. I'll protect you. Please protect me.
I wonder if we'll get it again. Red team, uh, white team.
I thought I'd do it in the order of yellow group.
This is the second match for the red team.
Hey, let's become Aku, Kanetan, and Aki-chan.
cage
I'm a JP member, what do you think?
Members: Igross Team Plus 1st generation members
Well, in terms of knowledge, Aki-chan is
After all, we are the first generation, so we certainly
I'm a first-generation student who has been watching over me, so it's likely.
Even though I'm wondering what's going on,
All those newcomers too.
I hope you do your best as a newcomer.
Everyone, especially Nee Aki-chan, is the main character.
There was a meeting where I was practicing with Tene Aoku and Kanete.
Yes, but it has a very unique atmosphere.
So I'm looking forward to that as well.
What kind of atmosphere do you have as a hunter?
I want you to do your best. Do your best.
will start as soon as everyone is ready.
I want to go, but it's still a little bit longer.
Is it going to take? Yes, I think I'm entering it now.
That's right, then this.
The entry becomes the start you want to end.
Your stomach is being beaten by an amazing Toa.
Stop closing the door so suddenly
It's okay, I thought it was neat and clean.
I was judged to be not pure.
Isn't that what it's all about?
Even after the splash, the slope protected me.
If you hit Toa and then hit him too, protect him.
No matter what, the slope is neat and clean.
I probably didn't include Kotosaka neatly and neatly.
I haven't put this in. I haven't put this in.
Okay, so let's move on to the red team.
I'm thinking of going to the second game.Yes, that's it.
I'm going to go
It's the second half of the start.
The title will be new. Left click left.
Left click on clitoris to peel off
I'm practicing 2019
Reviews from 2019 to 2020
The more exquisite it is, the more exquisite it is.
It's difficult, no, it's difficult, 2019 3rd generation
Not a 3rd year student
I think 3rd generation or 3rd generation 2019
Yes, probably in 2019.
It wasn't as good as it was.
Souzu-chan has about 34 aircraft from
After all, Kara-chan debuted early.
A little earlier than it should have been 201
After that, Zene-chan is also from 2020 onwards.
That's pretty good
It's difficult to get money from one side
I'll catch you, so catch me
I don't think it's close.
hand
I did it by hand and it went in.
It looks like it's going to be boring, and the topic has changed to solo.
3 or more songs
Difficult It's a little difficult, but I feel like it's difficult.
But people who debuted early have more than three stations.
It's more likely that it's the song.
my song and
On top of that white hill
Messed up
There's Su-chan
I definitely have it.
There are so many
Better
Chanchoco-sensei also joined, but you're not there.
There's no reason
Not you
It's not you, Ozora police arrested you.
I'm a person who has received a tax payment, so I'm here.
sky observation
This is quite difficult.
It's all up to me so far
There are quite a few.
I've done it twice and three times, so I've done it twice.
A lot of things
There's definitely a different person
No, that's not it. Yes, Watari is that every time
Running away or doing something like that, it's barely bad.
Did I do something wrong? I did something wrong.
It seems like you've been arrested. Are you kidding me?
We started talking about whether or not I had done something wrong.
Masaare
If you have time, please catch me.
No way
That's all a lie
So there are 5 people in the red team.The question was quite difficult.
It's difficult to conclude, I'm a newbie after all.
I guess there are some members.
I have a senior who has done that kind of thing before.
in
I feel like it was awkward for me to say it.
Well, I guess it depends on the topic.
After all, it's difficult, but I'm good at this.
Somehow Wame has been targeted more than once.
Apparently he was running around, but it was just barely bad.
No, it's cotton. Yes, I'll interview you with that.
I'm thinking of going, everyone in the red team, give it a try.
How was it?Yes
I wanted a tsukkomi
Oitsuko Sensenpai is a bit beautiful and blurry
There aren't enough human resources, right?
We are able to manage on our own.
I was waiting to see if I could do it, but really
What was difficult about you?
So, the first question is the question itself.
I made sure to take notes
I knew it, but I couldn't find someone.
The simple fact that there is no
I'm serious, I'm serious, I've already found you.
Since there isn't, I'll just put the person in front of me.
Let's keep doing things that seem different after all
It seems like it's a plan to throw everyone in. They also understand the problem.
Oh, the Ozora police didn't take any notes.
Well, it's just that this person is different.
You capture it while saying it, it's amazing
It's a bit frustrating, but I feel like that's okay.
But there are more, so there are still two teams.
I don't know, but I still don't know.
I think there may still be a second place.
Yes, that's right. It's just the beginning.
So please do your best even when the cat is the most annoying.
Please, I did my best, thank you everyone.
I'll try my best, I'll try my best, yes
Thank you to everyone at the match.
Thank you very much, keep up the good work
Please, I'll do my best with the jokes. Good luck.
Good luck in the competition! Let's continue the competition!
This will be the second match for the white team, so I said yes.
White team's second match, Noel's leader Chiara
It's Kanata's three people. Yes, these three people are quite good.
You seem to have a lot of knowledge, but here's a lot.
That's amazing, that's how much knowledge you have.
As for that, it looks like it's going to be pretty solid.
I guess it's just a little bit of expectation.
After all, it really depends on the problem.
Well, what year did you debut?
I probably remember the year I debuted.
I'd like to compare it to that.
It might be possible to do that.
I'm sure those two from earlier.
We are really the latest debut.
So yes, it was a little hard to understand.
I guess it was difficult after all.
But it is true that Chiara is said to be unrivaled.
Yes, yes, yes, that's the feeling.
Even if it's just for a moment, both Noel and the other side are pretty amazing.
I think that the members are quite
I'm pretty knowledgeable about whether the information is accurate or not.
I have an image and am also doing a program.
Hey, the white team ended up being inside.
Is that okay? Yes, one last thing please. That's it.
Haa, wait a minute, now
We're on standby right now as a group.
Yes, I can go, it's okay.
Yes, yes, then let's go to the white team.
It's a challenge. Please wait a moment. Who?
I'm already in the middle of the game.
Okay, this is a bit disappointing. Let's try again.
Please enter.Yes, yes already.
1 degree
Yes, please wait a little longer. It's okay.
Is it okay? One more entry please
I'll do it, I'll do it, I'll do it, I'll do it for the actual show.
I get pretty worked up sometimes.
Yes, that's right
Hey, okay, okay, polka is something, mom.
I said sorry, it was a little funny.
Yes, thank you very much.
Well then, it will be the second challenge for the White team.Yes.
Good
I'll do my best, I'll do my best, from here.
I see, that's the first problem.
What's coming next? Your height makes me excited.
150cm to 1 is a little difficult, but this is it
There must be quite a lot of them.
There are a lot of Hololive members, right?
Hey, JP members did a lot of work.
There are a lot of people around 155cm, so I don't use strings.
Must have
It's the heart.
The game is nice, but it's different.
Apparently
Isn't it suspicious who he's hiding from?
I realized that
[music]
The book is finished
It's amazing, it fit perfectly.
Hey, I'm catching expensive fish. I don't have time.
This is an easy-to-understand sled
It's easy
My ears are full of pain.
I guess it's surprisingly difficult to find it.
to catch
That's right
It was a hole
Wayo is not an ear, the back is also different
Masu
It's red-eared. It has horns, but it also has ears.
That's right, actually.
Hamotahake
The next day came
Tari
It's hard to hear because the signboard is in the way.
mosquito
I'm not good at catching
Nay last
[music]
[laughter]
I'm catching you so much I'm catching you so much
Yeah, it's different
too
This is pretty big, full of adventures.
I can't even go to the festival or enter.
There's still time, 20 seconds left.
Is Bo still there?
mosquito
I don't know who you are, I'm not stupid.
Is it a blur?
Na-chan is dumb
No, it's blurry. It's blurry. Blurred is over.
Amazing 13 people, this is amazing.
This is a great result.
Yes, the past complement is 13 people.
So, yes, that bokeh is pretty good.
Yes, that's right.
There was a lot of scenery, surprisingly.Yes, that's it.
Okay, are you going to the interview? Yes, yes.
Please, everyone with gray hair, try it.
How was it? How was it?
It was fun, it was fun, it was fun, it was fun
The jokes were so fun
Now I'm saying you're stupid, you're stupid
I caught it. It was mostly blurry, so I'm glad.
I'm glad I did, it's mostly blurry
I wanted to say thank you very much.
It feels pretty good.
No, I wanted to do my best. It was fun.
Thanks to Polo Talk, Polo
I guess it's thanks to the talk lol
I'm doing a talk show, so that's true.
You're amazing, Chiara, you know so much.
I'm very knowledgeable so I'm doing my best.
Thank you everyone for being so nice every time.
Thank you very much, keep up the good work
Please, yes, I'll do my best.
Thank you very much. Now then, the Kigumi.
It will be the second match of the Kigumi team.
The match is Toki no Sora Natsuiro Matsuri Hasubezu
Three people will become hunters.
These three are also quite the early group, so I'm sure.
Nineda has quite a bit of knowledge, especially when it comes to Hacos.
I guess there is, after all.
I'm sure there's gore too.
I can give you more details, Sora-chan too, of course.
Well, with zero regulations, it's so, so, so, so so so so so so such.
Sora-chan tends to be quite at her own pace.
Well, I guess it's really different.
How well do you know the members?
It depends. What will happen now?
But hey, enjoy it, please do it.
I want it
The original title for the shrine maiden from the second game is still out.
Is this the one that will come out in the end?
It feels so easy, kids.
But I wonder what will happen.
I wonder if there will be any problems, even if there is a difference in points.
I'm a little curious. I'm sure this is true.
I'm looking forward to the final announcement too.
Here it is, come here, Yellow Team
I want you to do your best and widen the point difference. Do your best.
If the yellow team is in first place, it will be worth a lot of points.
Red
Both the team and the white team are in a bit of a bad situation.
Please keep it down as much as possible.
No, I mean, to suppress it.
Looks like we have a standby. See you then, Kigumi.
It's a good start!
Holme hunting begins here
This is the last match. Good luck, but the team looks strong.
I wonder what will happen?
Dare was in 2017 or early 2018.
What will happen with this? There are quite a lot of these.
Yes, probably so.
[music]
I don't think I'll survive my whole life.
Just so-chan is running confused and waiting for me.
It's coming
Ta-chan has arrived
Ta
The festival is early
bobo yes
Chan
[music]
Karamasu
Yo
Much better messed up
I'm looking forward to it
Think about it
This is blond hair. This is also beautiful blond hair.
early blonde
It's early and there are plenty of people, so Horraim is like that.
Yes, I love blondes
So what will happen? Is there anyone else?
I lost my stubbornness
Amazing lol
Oops this is gone messed up
It's really fast, only 16 seconds left.
Next to the departing umbrella
of
Now on to the next topic.The last one is Gamo Seshi.
It's different because it's cool.
The difference between being cool is that Toba-sama was arrested.
I wonder if Masuyo Satoba-sama is sexy or not?
He's so sexy, isn't he?
It's sexy blue for the second time, isn't it?
It's different, it's different, it's different, I stopped it.
yeah
That
It's okay if it's not sexy, right?
Now
Hey, take a little bath
I just did it.
[laughter]
[music]
I'm in the middle of the day.
We said yes, so there were 12 people in total.
It turned out to be amazing!
Great hey here
Let's have an interview with the Yes group.
How did you all try it?
Who is the key person who wasn't Seki?
By the way, I was thinking of putting Saka in.
I think he probably didn't take that bath.
I don't know if it's because of it, but that's what it was.
I wonder if it's true that the bath judgment is so good.
I guess it's because I haven't taken a bath enough to sleep.
The judgment is quite strict.
There are quite a few people in cages who have already been captured.
There were quite a lot of sexy groups, right?
Yeah, I don't like it, but it was pretty amazing.
It was a smooth festival for all 12 people.
It was amazing, I really caught it
The book that was Tane
I put it in. What do you think of this amazing Neso-chan?
At first I didn't catch it at all.
When I couldn't get caught and looked closely, I didn't have that rope.
After all, I'm not that good.
I blurred it out
I'm running around inside a little bit.
Yeah, whatever, that second blonde one.
I thought it was a good idea to play it properly.
After all, it was the 17th and 18th class.
It's easy to understand because it's around the same time as me.
It's easy to understand, isn't it?
Yeah, that's right, so I'll make it a bit of a theme.
It was cheap. I was lucky.
You were lucky, then continue.
Please do your best. Good luck with this too.
Okay, I'll do my best, so that's the second part.
Thank you to everyone at the match
Please do your best with Tamona, do your best
Thank you very much
It's a little bit from the beginning.
It was a very intense match.
Yes, that doesn't mean it's true.
Looks like the score for the second game has been released, so here it is.
We would like to announce the scores here
Okay, now what's going to happen in the second game?
First place goes to the white team with 15 points and the yellow team
If you put 5 points into a 10 point group
It looks like this.Here it is.
It's a form of matching 1 earlier.
The format of playing one game and two games at a time
The count is now complete.
So now it's time to tally
Looks like it's over so let's go home hunting
The total points for the two games are as follows:
Yes please, please
Oh no, but I still don't understand this.
I don't know. I said yes to this, so it's the yellow group.
The white team has 25 points and the red team has 20 points.
is 15 points, so the yellow group
It has become a form of leading ah yellow
Even Nene seemed to have been practicing a lot.
It seems like it was quite strong.I guess it will continue in the future as well.
I'm looking forward to it, but this cat's sports day is the first.
I don't understand, it's really true
Be careful because you don't know what's going to happen until the end.
Tighten up, yellow slime, do your best too
I want you to run all the way to my thighs.Yes.
So, let's aim for the end of the next competition.
Move to follow-up venue
Yes please please please please
[music]
It's okay if you say yes.
Atiku was really fun
I think all the listeners are watching too.
I wonder if it was fun.
I think it must be difficult, but the people watching are already
Is this person really no good? Who is this person?
It's like, yes, yes, it's a little bit.
It was fun and I definitely want to see the hall live.
I don't know anyone, but I haven't seen it yet.
There are also people like this, and this person is like this.
It was easy to understand because it felt like
Kanato and this person are about this height.
Well, what year did you make your debut?
I think it was easy to understand.Yes
Yes, that seems like it
Yes, but it's quite a bit. After all, it's the beginning of a cat.
I could not see it during the training stage.
It was a lot of fun because it was a
That was interesting, right?
Now, the second competition is up.
Aim for follow-up from Miko
Please introduce the competition.
Aim for the top, floor up.
Yes, everyone really worked hard at practice.
I wonder if this really feels like an individual competition.
However, it is a follow-up after all.
I think the participating members have a strong sense of responsibility.
So I practiced until the wee hours of the morning.
Or wake up in the morning and practice.
I hope you did a great job practicing.
That's why I'm really nervous
Yes, but the pressure of the actual performance.
I think there are a lot of techniques.
There are quite a lot of members.This seems like a good idea.
Well, this is Nemikogake.
The awesome holo-up added by san is so cute
I was watching it thinking it was cute and amazing.
I added something in the back
I wonder what that pink thing is?
It's like soft serve ice cream.
I really understood soft serve ice cream when I made it.
That's what the person who made it said.
You said poop, but yeah.
It's not poop, it's poop, it's different.
It's definitely ice cream, oh ice cream.
That's right, there's a face on it, that kind of face.
I did
It looks red, so I said yes.
A total of 3 people, one from each team
Start at the same time and use the trident
Yes, there is a time limit while climbing the scaffolding.
Compete for ranking based on the highest score achieved within 5 minutes.
Yes, there is a weak jump on the trident.
There are two types of jumps: and strong jumps.
There is a small cooldown time when using it.
Yes, this competition will consist of two games.
A total of 6 people entered, 2 from each team.
Yes, yes, and this is a special gift.
However, the highest reaching code is 10m ahead.
1 point maximum, I'm already at the top.
You can earn up to 20 points
Okay, that's great. Well then, the contestants who are participating.
Let's do an interview with everyone, not just a greeting.
I want to.Ah, are you okay?It's okay.
Yes, yes, yes, Ms. Koseki from the Red Team.
Yes, and Sakaguro-san, yes, and
From the white team, Roboko-senpai is also a high school student.
Yes, from the Kigumi, there are stars, Mercury, and
Anya Melfisa will be taking part in the Haichan Gae
That means everyone has the same voice.
It looks like you're inside Cheever.
Yes, everyone, can you hear me?
Can you hear me? Yes, are you nervous?
do
This technique is the one that makes me the most nervous to imitate.
I'm sure you're just nervous.
Let me ask each of you a little bit about your enthusiasm.
I think that's why I say yes because of beauty.
Eri
No, I was actually looking at Momiko already.
Yeah, yeah, I did it too. It's early, it's early, isn't it?
It's so fast no no no
I guess that's true.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, it's fast.
Become a nerd
Speed Aor from
[music]
Please carry the speed team on your back and
What about Robochi? Yeah, no, it's already Bijuu.
Sui-chan is fast, so I'll try my best with Makeji.
That's what I want to do, yes, aim for the goal
I'll do my best. I'll do my best. Look, I got caught up in something.
Teru
Pressure-chan is really weak in real life.
from
[applause]
It seems like you didn't follow last night's practice.
Remember, you can do it, do your best
That's right, you're doing your best, Mom.
I'm looking at you, mom. It's the last thing I wanted to do.
But who is this? Really, even your mother.
I added it a bit thinner based on the leader's wishes.
I guess Sui-chan is good.
I want to believe that I can do it. I'll do my best in practice.
This person was great. I'll do my best, Mom.
Yakiniku Rune Mom Thank you for this time Mom
Nice to meet you Yakiniku, please do your best
The next one
Now, can I ask you the name of this next time?
Well, next time I'll make this 1000.
Is it possible to do an interview?
Shall we do a third interview?
Are you okay please?
It's okay if you say those words one by one. Yes, yes.
Yes, Mi-chan will do her best, so I'll leave it to Saka.
You're my senior, right?
Do your best, do your best, do your best, okay?
Next, the reliable white is Chiara, yes.
I'm serious about the actual show. I didn't watch it, but yes.
oh dear
Well, I guess the length is a win.
Moyo
How's the sun smelling? It's already 3 o'clock.
I was practicing until
I'll do my best, but I still rely on Mizu-senpai.
Masu
fruit
Who can say anything about the follow-up?
It's more of a battle with myself than anything around me.
Hey, let's turn away from the pressure.
You might be nervous, so I hope you do your best.
Please do your best, please do your best, yes
I'll do my best, I'll do my best, I'll do my best
Well then, please get ready. Yes, yes.
Please, I said yes, so this time Holo.
It's rap, but to the viewers
Let me briefly explain this at the very end.
At the place where I found myself when the time was up
This will give you points, yes.
Yes, it's not the highest point, but the last one.
The score changes depending on the location.
Yes, I fell down on the way.
Does that mean it will be there?
I see, I'm just halfway through.
There is a bed, so go from there.
Because it is possible to respawn.
Look up while touching the bed as much as possible.
I think it's best to say
I guess that's what it feels like.
I'm ready to standby. Let's start.
Kaneoh, it's finally starting. Yes, yes, then,
I'll go to one game, good luck game
Start, start, do your best
I'm telling you to do your best. I'm scared.
The scary part has just begun
How high can you go in 300 seconds?
It's hard, it's okay, it's dangerous, it's dangerous
It's not that fast, so it's a battle with yourself.
It's a battle with myself, so there's no time left.
I guess that's pretty much the case.
In the slow, slow, slow game
There's no such thing as Yuria climbing slowly.
But everyone is doing well now.
Is Yosa-chan okay? Sae, 0 regulation robot
And Sui-chan, the robot fell here.
It's amazing! It's amazing!
Better
I'm going to check it out, it's amazing, it's already halfway through
I feel like the middle part was too fast, though.
After all, this means aiming for the goal.
I want you to aim for the top without worrying about it.
It's bad, Suichan, and Suichan is bad.
At first, it seemed like it was a warmhearted thing to do.
The same thing happened yesterday too, so I'm nervous.
Don't panic, I'm seriously panicking.
It's okay, Susui-chan was sweet at the beginning.
It's from here because it's not.
I'm a woman who climbs to the top.
It seems like the quickest and shortest route.
No, that's right, the shortest route is View.
You're pretty good, okay, calm down.
I feel more calm now, when it comes to the actual performance.
It seems difficult to perform at 70% of my ability.
There is also
Mustard
You're so good at using scary and okay.
I've been climbing a lot, too.
Yes, it's being done, the visuals will be coming soon.
Amazing beauty approaching the goal
It's really fast, but Senpai 4 is amazing.
Reached the goal in an amazing 170 seconds
I've reached the goal
It's early
My pace is amazing 165 seconds
Let me know, the water is being chased. Do your best, water.
You still have 155 seconds, fly, fly!
It looks like water, it looks like it's flying, water is good.
Rocco-senpai is also pretty bi-paced, but hey.
I'm standing my pet firmly aiming at the goal.
I'm definitely moving towards the top here.
There's no rush in your voice.
I'm very close to reaching the goal.
I'm at my own pace. That's okay. That's the last part.
It's quite difficult
Hey, it hurts. Hey, everyone, we've reached the goal.
Beauty is watching to see if you can do it, so it's okay.
Well, it's the last time for Robochi. It's okay.
Sarobo-chan's last okay
Yes, I left it and reached the goal.
Taka, it's okay.
Sasui-chan, we still have 100 seconds left.
It's okay, Sui-chan, I fell here once.
Even if I fall, I still have time to go.
This is where I want to score.
You can still respawn. You can go slowly.
When I got back, I was hanging out with my friends.
Well, the follow-up bond is starting to grow.
Everyone practices Boroap late at night.
I did it, so I'll leave it to everyone to say goodbye.
Well, it's been a minute and I'm finally ready to go.
Don't be in a hurry, just keep steady.
Don't panic, don't panic, don't panic, that's difficult.
That's right, let's do it now, let's do the rest of the colorful things
We've reached it. It's the last minute. Welcome home.
Oh, what's going to happen? I'm back.
I'm back. I'm here.
The goal is almost here. My hands are shaking so much.
amazing
Let's go soon, let's go
fly
Everyone made it to the goal from the first try.
Congratulations! Congratulations!
Congratulations
Masu
I'm just saying
You know, I'm always at the top or I'm at the top.
Why did you bring it up so suddenly? I cut it out.
The visuals I cut out were crooked.
Unmistakable beauty stands at the top, as expected.
It's okay if you don't like Calico, everyone.
I've reached the goal, yes.
Okay, here are the scores from the first game.
Yes, yes, this is all together.
20 points great This is a bit of a second half group
The pressure is really bad.This is true.
I was really impressed when I just looked at it.
Yes, that's right. After all, the actual performance is after all.
Sui-chan doesn't leave that 150 seconds at all.
I wanted to score a goal, so yeah, yeah.
I'm a little nervous about the actual performance.
No matter how hard it is, I will definitely reach the goal.
So we all got 20 points.
Congratulations on winning it Gujiguji
If you say yes, then here it is.
I would also like to ask the members of Chotone.
But I was quite nervous and the next member
The name is A Kuroekihara. Yes.
Don't get nervous even after watching two games. Watch this.
No matter how nervous I am, it's already dangerous.
Oh no, Sui-chan, my hands can't stop shaking.
That's what I said.
The wind won't stop, it's reflected in my image
It's a little visible, I'm sure I'm alone.
It's quite difficult to challenge yourself, isn't it?
It's become a battle with my own mental state.
That's right, but in the end it's okay
I calmed down and climbed up.
I guess it'll be okay once you calm down.
Yes, yes, then next.
Hasakore will be played as soon as entries are completed.
Is it starting? Yes, please enter.
Let's get it! Yes, the entry is on standby.
Did you do it? I'll take a look now.Yes.
Yes, it's done. See you then.
Let's start, okay? Please, please.
Well then, let's start the second game. Good luck.
It's starting, it's starting, do your best, shut up, shut up
Don't do it, talk as loud as you can, talk loudly
Some people say it's better to talk.
I see. I can't. Now we've started.
Saka is aiming right now, but Saka is fine too.
I'm the type of person who is good at games, so I'm good at it.
I said I haven't studied at all, so I gave it a solid 100.
He's the type of guy who scores points.
I'm feeling a little sleepy, this time at all.
Although Chiara was quite nervous
I was practicing really hard so
I hope you do your best.
Mr. A, too, until midnight last night.
I was doing it, I was doing it, what's going on here?
Rag lag rag rag rag lag came, came, came.
Sorry, there's some kind of lag happening.
Looks like it's a rug monster.
Hey, what's going to happen? Ani and Saka
is now standing in the same place and Chiara is leading the way.
It seems like Chiara is doing a lot right now.
I'm calm. Calm down and keep going.
climbing climbing
Yosaanya is the checkpoint
It's probably better to change the Piala.
I'm definitely the type of person who shows up right now.
I'm pretty mentally stable.
That's right, I want to protect this place.
Yes, Anya who fell right in front of me
Shima and I get along just as well.
Well, Chiara is a mess.
I'm kind of in the zone
I'm sure he's not talking at all.
I'm in the zone, it doesn't matter.
It's great now
Here's the checkpoint for how fast it is
messed up the last checkpoint
early
Now, can we reach the goal like this?
Kia, try your best, try your best, I guess.
Yesterday I was playing haha, so I'm sure it's Hiasaka.
I am trying to find the shortest course.
Seriously, it's really good, even on the slopes.
I have an image that I can do anything.
You have a good image, right? Saka also has a bed.
I wonder if this is Nido.
I'm holding on, I'm holding on, I'm holding on tight
Chiara is already colored, so this is the last one.
Kia and Chiara have reached the final stage.
I'll score a goal later
It's okay, it's okay, Anya-san, please follow me too.
I'm sure you can get there all at once.
That's amazing, it's going to be a Kigoru goal.
This is my first time. I think I can go too.
rare
I wonder if I can go, which is rare and good, 128 seconds left.
I was able to reach the goal.
Let's score the goal, there are only 110 seconds left.
I'm here, yes, I'm chasing after you.
It's quite fast going up the hill. It's fast.
When to use jump
Oh, that's great, there's only 100 seconds left.
Well, there's still time.
It's about a minute and a half, so the slope is a trial.
I'm doing a great job!
I'm not going to stop there, really.
Believe it or not, I caught up with you.
I asked the listeners about this.
I'm doing this while discussing with him.
I'm doing this. Something like that happens.
I'm looking forward to seeing you, A-san.
I don't know what will happen tomorrow
Can I dodge this and reach the goal?
Good luck! This is the place where I reached the end of my time.
Well, the last place I was there is no good.
It's hard to get out of here, it's an error slowly
There's only one minute left, 45 seconds left.
Don't rush, do your best on stubborn slope, this is a slope.
It's a battle, but let's do our best.
I don't want to go to Dongle.
It's okay, there's only 30 seconds left, okay.
30 seconds left, 30 seconds left, both of you.
There's still time to reach the goal.
Those of us watching were also quite nervous.
It's 15 seconds since I started getting a little nervous. Same.
I'm with you now, how long do you have 10 seconds left?
I can't go to higher places, but I'm farther away
Oh no, can we make the last 5 seconds jump?
Is it dangerous?
This is also a nice fight.
Yes, I'm pretty sure I'll say yes.
It was a close battle, yes.
Although it's not a yes, Chiara has achieved the goal.
200m and Anya
It's a 114m hill, it's a little high.
And the slope is 176m.
It was quite a battle of money.
Oh, it's amazing, but everyone is hollow.
It's pretty good since I was practicing close up.
It was a high level battle.
So, yes, really, this is it.
The score for the second game will be a little different.
Kanayaihaihai includes the second game.
The scores are as follows:
Yes, this is not included. Game 2
that only
Let's go together, so let's move on to the next one.
That means there is a one point difference.
Yes, the yellow group has 18 points and the red group has 17 points.
Yes, the white team has 2010 points.
Yes, thank you very much.
Shall we go for the interview then?
Okay, first of all, how did you like the two members of the red team?
No, seriously, I'm glad Biji-chan was quick.
Biji-chan is there
It's too cold, the slope has fallen quite a bit on the way.
Tane Trian's error was quite good.
I was like, oh, I can't go there.
I'm going to go there or something.
No, I was watching it, I was a little nervous.
It's a challenge that makes you feel like you're actually doing it.
I guess I wasn't nervous enough.
I'm glad Tasune took it Nee-chan
He said he wasn't nervous at all.
Mon
Mimi was able to afford it, but Janmi was amazing and the fastest.
In other words, I dropped it very quickly.
So I dropped it, and now it's hot.
So now on to the two members of the white group.
I would like to interview you.Yes
Yes, how was it? No, I had fun clearing the game.
I'm glad that the two of you are so happy.
You did a great job. Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you, that seriously has already evolved me.
I feel
I was in that zo who did it.
I was in Niimi, I found a new fusho.
I feel great that it has become so.
I've recovered. I'll be able to reach the goal in the morning.
It became like that
I thought it was kind of amazing to be someone like this.
I think it's amazing how quickly you're improving.
Tatayo But General I didn't notice it so this book
I didn't realize it, I thought it was a long press.
Well, it's a victory for the team.
Thank you very much.
Good, good, Roboko Senpai, Kigumi's O
How was the two of you? Sorry.
Can I get a word from you, Kase-senpai?
I see that there will be no tomorrow, Aui-chan.
Now then, Aji-san, can I have a word with you?
How was it? Yes, that goal was in my eyes.
It was before, right? With Rags.
Looks like there was a fight too. It's a mess.
It's a shame, but that's true. I'll do my best, though.
I tried my best, but I tried my best.
It's frustrating because the sports day is still going on.
Please do your best, you are nice.
Thank you very much.
Thank you thank you mom
Thank you, yes, this is my mom looking at you.
Okay mom, that's okay, so here we go.
The second competition will be a comprehensive specific interim announcement.
Click here for comprehensive benefits after finishing
The first place is
Yes, yes, I'm 40 and it's quite like that.
It's a narrow gap, so run away and have a chance to turn things around.
Yes, run away, there are still two other groups remaining.
Let's do our best, Red team, do our best too.
Yes, then move on to the next competition venue on the Kiba Line.
let's do it
Mashoba is a competition in which everyone participates.
That's right. Yes, that's right. Yes, that's okay.
That's why we are also watching Nema Flapa.
I was nervous, and so were the listeners.
I don't think so, but I
I wanted to support everyone who was working hard.
Really, really, regardless of the team.
All the members didn't tell me to fall down or fall down.
It seems like everyone wants to do their best.
Follow-up is the same regardless of team.
All follow-up members work hard together
I'm glad I did that.I'm glad I did.
Yes, I was a little impressed.
It may or may not be good, but it's still a tense competition.
That's right, it's true that it's the second event.
It was quite difficult, that's why
To the members who participated and made this happen.
Well, everyone is applauding. This is everyone.
This exercise was amazing!
This time there were quite a lot of team events and individual events.
I'm sure there aren't that many.
I think you did a great job.
I think so, yes, quite one person at a time.
He is working hard to compete in the competition.
I don't think so.Yes, yes, then yes.
Now, the third competition is Kise.
I would like to introduce it to you.
The Yohai Line has been a three-way battle with the participation of members.
Yes, there are two people in a group with the highest level of performance.
Can only fly and jump and
Those in the knight role can attack and hold a shield.
Yes, yes, you can attack the enemy knight role three times.
You can even defeat Yes in the final
Ranking is determined by the number of targets defeated.
Yes, the time limit is 1 minute and you can respawn as many times as you like.
It's possible. Yes, I was able to ride.
Are you okay? I have three matches against Naoki.
The score is 15 points for 1st place and 10 points for 2nd place.
3rd place with 5 points. We are the generals.
Yes, yes, our general has to go home.
Are you unable to do it at home? I'll do it later.
This is the place where I defeated the general.
As an additional bonus in addition to the cat
Each time you kill an enemy you get 1 point.
Hoho, on top of that first match.
It will not be added to the number of points in the gauge.
However, this total score at the end
Yeah, yeah, add it as a bonus point.
Well, even if you were in 3rd place, you would be given the general 5 times.
Looks like you'll get 10 points if you defeat it.
Since it is a bonus, we
Let's do our best. Yes, yes, yes.
As I said earlier, Miko participated in this competition.
Three of us will be participating, so here we go.
I will pass the baton to people who have Karanema.
Hey, who is the MC?
Well then, to all the contestants
Let's start with the interview.
Everyone pick up the baton before passing it on.
Do I have to read it too? Yes.
Well, I'm sure this is it.
Hey everyone, as I said earlier, it's one.
Raden-chan was absent due to poor health.
No, that's right, this time it's a pinch hitter.
Maokayu, the cat who is crying as a guest, is a guest.
Thank you for being a pinch hitter
Thank you thank you Oka
Thank you very much Kayu.
I'm in Kayu's white group, I'm here.
What do you think? Can I call you?
Is there a person? Please wait a moment.
Wait a moment
Please give me some rice porridge.
Well, even this year's Minecraft is pretty good.
Would you say he was a member who stood out? Yes.
I do a lot of different things in Sabah.
That's why I made you say so much.
I'm glad I was able to participate even a little this time.
You know, I really thought about that during the practice period.
It seemed like my schedule didn't match up.
But
It's okay this time. It's okay. I'm contacting you now.
I understand. Yes, I asked you to come in.
So he rushed over.
Yes, thank you. Let's try it. Yes.
First of all, let's hear from Akagami
Let's hear it, everyone in the red team.
Listen
Yes, there's Aki-chan this Kiba line.
I'll be returning, but how are you feeling?
That's okay, the red team is losing a bit right now.
But I still think we can make a big turnaround.
I want to destroy everyone for some reason
I think he's a man who will destroy you.
Hey, that's right, the number one that we're proud of.
By all means, beat up that leader too.
Let's go. Sorry, sorry.
I'm sorry, maybe other staff members
's voice is back, our voice is back
The voice of the management is included.
I got a little bit of it, but it's good
Yes, are you okay? Please.
That's right, please, it seems like it is.
Please, I wonder if the blue porridge is coming?
It was good for the white team.The white team
If you do an interview, there will probably be some porridge.
It's a good situation, everyone in the Yes group.
Looks like you're okay
or win okay yes maybe you can hear it
do not have
Good, thank you, Mikocchiko
I guess he's going to ride on top of Mel later, Mimi.
Tomiko hasn't done it even once yet.
Right?
That's a lie because I haven't done it yet.
That Miko runs away while jumping.
That's fine. Don't have a strategy meeting now.
Please jump, I'll become an enemy that won't run away.
Please take a closer look. Good luck next time, Red.
Let's do our best
hey
Yes, everyone from the white group, can you listen?
Can you hear me, white group?
Sanyoisho Camera Sanmiko's screen is
Could you please upload it?
It's painful
Thank you very much
Thank you very much for today, Moneko Mayu.
Thank you very much.
There is
[music]
Be scared, because one person has turned into a suspicious person.
I wonder if it will happen
That's right, I say yes, please everyone
I want to lead Nerikatan to victory.
It's fun
That's too cool
Please do your best. Let's do our best.
Everyone in the white group will do it.
Okay, let's go to the yellow group.Okay, lastly, the wood group.
I would like to ask the members of the Kigumi
I heard it
I heard it, yeah
halo mental spiritual pansion
A word of praise
Please protect Subaru-chan
Seku will do his best
Let's
[applause]
Thank you so much!
[music]
There's something really special about the fact that it's so good.
excitement
I noticed the unique excitement of the group.
Yes, I'm having fun. Yes, yes.
So from here on, we'll move on to the present.
Since I'm going to appear, I'm going to give Shinji A a proper look.
Please say yes in the form of kissing me.
I would like to wish A-chan Nodoka
Thank you very much, please
Please
Yes, I received this.Fang battle starts from here.
To my Hololive staff friend
Good morning Hololive newbie
We will send it to you with our staff member Harusaki Nodo.
Thank you for your cooperation.
It's a little bit, I just heard that voice of mine at work.
My work voice has been picked up.
Have you accumulated all the bad news?
No, no, no, no, yes.
So far, the current benefits are 52 points for red group and 60 points for white group.
It seems that there are 63 pieces of woodblocks.
It's a close race, but let's take a look.
How was it Kae-chan?
What can I say about follow-up?
It's a great match and easy to watch.
Even though we are enemies, it seems like each other has some good qualities inside.
That's the good thing about it.
I can see that there is a lack of communication.
I went away thinking it was a lot of fun.
You know, there's not that much of a difference.
Surprisingly, 23 is really fast.
Chris was quick, but what do you think?
I wonder if Nodoka-chan or me too.
I don't have much experience with mcra.
But you guys really don't know about the Trident anymore.
I wonder why I'm using it so quickly
Thank you for showing me that I can climb high.
I'm really excited, it's the first time.
Is it Flow Hunter? The hunter competition is
The person I thought was so neat and clean turned out to be different.
The chat section looks like a joke.
Even if you don't say things like that, peace and order will be maintained.
Although I was feeling bad
Please don't make it so unsafe?
In my opinion, it was interpretation 1, but what do you think?
Hey everyone, everyone from Hololive.
It's clear now, ah, what's going on?
I answered 100 points, but that's not true.
However, personally, I think Aremi-san is
Iris is the person I thought was dumb.
I was surprised that it wasn't. I see.
I wonder if Airi is stupid.
Yeah, yeah, I think he's a big idiot.
That's right, that person has their own interpretation
Yes, there are various interpretations.
However, I thought it was interesting. Yes, everyone.
I'm on standby. Please don't worry.
Are you on standby? I see.
What do you think? What do you think?
What do you think? Please wait a little longer.
Please, everyone, see you after this.
I will be participating, but what do you mean by everyone participating?
It's not the first time or it's not the first time ever
What was it like doing Lil at the sports day? It was your first time.
Was it that? Was everyone there?
I fell asleep and already 3 teams are sleeping
I'm going to play the Tohaiba line, but I'm practicing.
The distribution was delayed, but I feel like it will be over in a moment.
So yeah, it's only a short time, so everyone.
Who is the cat?
Do I hit it a lot? Yes, I hit it or something like that.
Calliope's cat killing is high
I'm glad you had a great time.
Yes, I would like to see it.Yes, please.
That's right, and the general manager is going to be sponsored.
I'll do my best because I'll get some points.
I hear that the organizer will be defeated.
It is a competition in which all the generals also participate.
Well then, what do you think? Kill Point
Added when you defeat the boss.
You can earn points by
Is that true?
I wonder if that will be reflected?
I see
Let's all go together and tell the general.
After all, that kind of development might happen.
Maybe I don't have a new one from back then.
I see, it's just a pinch hitter
Thank you very much, thank you very much
I received the message, but there was one suspicious person.
It was included, but it's a holo side, so holo
I'm a live meba. But today
Money, I guess you came here to get all sorts of money.
I guess that's what it looks like.
I'm making a little bit of money, but
Yes, just stay in your suit.
However, I think I'll post Kanata-san.
Thank you very much for your participation.
Kayu-san is also a sloppy president.
Well, I'm pretty sure he's the president, so let's do this Minecraft.
After all, the play time is long.
He's also strong as a pinch hitter.
I wonder if that's what happened earlier.
I thought you taught me how to operate it.
I'm glad I figured it out quickly.
I heard it was good and it showed up
I hope you do your best, yes.
I'm looking forward to it, everyone.
Are you ready?
I wonder if it will take a little longer
I see, when it comes to competitions for everyone,
Preparation may be a little difficult.
There are quite a number of channels.
It's okay to move, but I'd like to move.
Especially as a graduate teacher.
I thought I could take it slow, but it took quite a while.
At that high pace, here and here
It's like, please, just a little bit.
At first, I was buff and spoke a little into the microphone.
I'm sorry for doing that.
Thanks for letting me know, I'll fix it.
What's more, preparations are still underway.
I've reset it for a while now.
I'm resting up, everyone, just a little bit more
Please wait for a while.
Please wait. Everyone is on the screen now.
Ride me, ride me with those fangs, get ready
I'm here, but I can't hear the conversation.
I don't have any, but what do you think?
What do you think of the fans watching the practice stream?
I'm definitely paying attention to this place because it looks strong.
Do you have any comments?
I would appreciate it if you could let me know.
Even though I said please, there are quite a few comments.
Many people are watching 74,000 people today
After all, the big sports day is said to be attracting a lot of attention.
That's why I'm doing a huge reset.
It's amazing what they're doing this time.
The stage is also really packed with attention to detail.
Not to mention everyone, that's why we're building domes and such.
There were ships and things like that.
This is amazing This is amazing The feeling of this wave
The sub is well reproduced.
It has a very amazing finish.
It's definitely like this, and it's a highlight
Maybe edit it, it seems like it's up again this time.
So please look forward to it!
It's done. Well then, yes.
Let's go right away.Let's go right away.
Thank you very much.Okay then, Fang battle.
Start of the first game
[music]
I wonder if it will clear up. I wonder if it will start. I'm so excited.
We're all up until the start
It is being counted
[music]
Well, it has begun, everyone.
Isn't it too early to start? Let's see what happens.
I didn't have anything to eat while I was there, so I quickly emptied it.
Maybe it's just the result of practice, but I got used to it.
There are many great warriors out there.
Well then, let's move on to Miko and Mel.
I heard that you can listen to the conversation between the pair.
Let's listen to each pair.
Let's hear what kind of conversation they're having.
Kanao came to Mel's place.
You seem surprisingly calm. Help me, help me.
I heard a bit of a screeching voice.
It's a bit of a mixed bag after all.
I feel like it's even more of a cry.
I think Aiha-san is calm as well.
I was defeated, so let's call out to each other properly.
I'm really concentrating.
Now, the conversation between Gura-san and Kuroni-san pair.
I'll listen to it, and then I'll take a look.
[music]
Mashoo
Oh, I can hear you, just calm down.
It's Masune
It sounds like "Nekore da" so much
I think he's talking about dying or something.
Well, Kisanee is here after all.
As expected, it's a great place to go
I think Ra's voice is a little cute.
I can hear it
Masasaa
And as for the games
21 up there
[music]
1 minute passed in the blink of an eye.
However, the person who had 0 kills was also polite.
There was a cat, but I managed to get a kill.
I was taking it all the time.
After this, it's up to you as soon as you're ready.
I would like to participate in an interview
But what about Jinbi?
And just a while ago
Miko's pair who listened to our conversation
I heard that I will be able to interview you, so let's talk.
I would like to ask Miko-san mail
Can you hear me? I can hear you.
Thank you for your hard work.
What did you think after trying it? A few words from both of you.
I would appreciate it if you could give it to me.
It was a mess, so I turned it around.
I was able to kill quite a lot.I definitely killed it.
It's so nice
It's amazing 4 kills is amazing
I got a lot of kills, nice
Thank you. See you next game.
I really wish I couldn't hear Komiko's voice.
It looks like it's a little swollen.
It was a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit
Please feel free to have a conversation during the match.
I pray for you, but I can't hear your voice telling me it's okay.
Ah, I hear a voice now
It's amazing to hear that voice
The battle that comes out is huge, so listen carefully and adjust accordingly.
I want to do my best to hear your voices.
Please try your best to really hear it
Yes, thank you, yes.
Just once, please, to that staff member
I would like to request a reset
Please reset
There was also a little bit of sound, though.
I think it would be nice to be able to make some adjustments.
I can really hear Masu's voice.
I wonder if there was a slightly different microphone installed.
By the way, when I was in that waiting room...
Hey, I can really hear Subaru-san's voice.
I'm sure I heard your voice.
I heard a lot of noise
There it was, as expected, everyone.
Okay, come on. Next time, it'll be the second match.
However
Points earned are still not available yet.
I guess it doesn't feel like it yet, it's true right now.
Do you get points?
It seems like something like that, I guess it'll come out a little.
Oh, I'll be there.I'll be there.Okay then, the first one.
Here is the score of the match. Please go ahead.
Now, read it out loud.Red team: 16 points; White team: 7 points.
The Wood Team has 11 points, so the Red Team is strong.
I've made a comeback. I'm looking forward to it.
I don't think there's any way to turn it around yet.
Is it still possible to make a comeback?
Yes, yes, Bell-san and Nea no Miko-san
I think the team also contributed.
I think it contributed to the number of people
I think yes, the White team is at the moment.
In terms of overall points, I feel like I'm in second place.
But yeah, I'm in second place, but I have to
I guess you could say that even if I was left out, the White team would be disappointed.
I heard there are a lot of older sisters, so that's definitely true.
Are you being kind? It's definitely a close battle.
How much can you do after the cat inside?
However, I may be a little hesitant.
Thank you for your unbelievable kindness.
I might get confused a bit
Take a moment to take that breath before you let go.
This is what happens when you are there
You may feel kinder
The more I sleep, the more I feel so good
This is a team that is just messing around.
I am steadily earning points.
I hope you will continue to do your best.
That's what I think.I see some woodwork.
Every time, someone was fighting with each other.
I have an image of that.
It doesn't look like it's being eaten, it seems.
When I tried to do that, the statue of me sliding my wrists was saying that.
Please feel free to contact us.
Yeah, there were a lot of things, but yes, it was an attack.
Don't miss out on power fashion, even after the second half of the second round.
I hope you do your best.
I hope you get through this, yes Subaru.
It seems like your number is 2.
So don't pull it, then yes.
It looks like the second round is ready.
A little more and a little more
Just a little more, a little more
So I could have run away now.
I was told that I would not let him escape yet.
Yes, they just kept gathering more and more.
I am preparing an electric meal.
Please give me a signal to fly
Is that okay? I won't go then.
2 games
start
54321 Good luck
Good luck! It's starting now.
The yellow hazel has started to become a little defensive.
I feel like I'm on the defensive.
Oh, it's really cheap, so I'm going to hit it with a few numbers.
I see, I came here thinking of a strategy.
Hey, then Mio-san and Ame-san pair
It seems like you can hear the conversation, so let's go.
General
Hey, it's quite aggressive, so let's attack, that energetic voice.
I heard it, and now it's finally here
Yes, my dear brother, my dear brother
Yes, yes, yes, it's okay.
I'm glad you got the kill. That's great.
I feel like I'm good at avoiding sleep.
Team Calliope and Fuwamoko pair
It seems that you can listen to the conversation, so please listen to it.
[music]
I'm talking to you. I'm in charge.
I'm not calm
You know, that amazing F from Mario Kart and stuff.
I can almost imagine Aard coming out.
I see, it's definitely amazing.
I'm calming down. Oh wow.
tea
I was so excited
a
It's over, there it is.
to
Yes, it's 1 minute early, so I'm early.
It's over in a flash
It's gone
There will be another interview after this.
I look forward to hearing from you, everyone.
How was it? I don't want to play the second game.
After all, the team has come up with an amazing strategy.
I felt like I had thought about it.
However, in Ade, here is Mio Ookami's
Apparently we can interview the pair.
I would like to hear your story.
Yes, can you hear me? Both of you
Yes, I can hear you while shopping.Can you hear me?
Can you hear me? This is an interview.
Thank you for coming to the interview.
Please let me know how you thought the match went.
Please, yes, thank you for your hard work.Thank you for your hard work.
I can hear voices from inside my house.
There is no such thing, so I see.
Please, I'm sorry, just now.
I got 0 kills on the first try.
But I finally got 1 kill and it's nice
Thank you very much for the first time.
You can definitely put in points to make sure you don't die.
I don't want to, so it's important to stay.
I don't want to drop it, please try a little harder
I would like to go, thank you very much.
Thank you, I will buy the exercise
It was cute, zaa, it was cute, 3
Please do your best in the game. Please do your best. Excuse me.
Thank you for your help
Masu
I said yes, so Ume-san will see you again soon.
Please reset.Yes, once.
The field will be reset.Okay now.
This will be the 3rd race, but it's the 3rd race.
I'm going to enter, but yeah, yeah, I'll get points.
Yes, because you can see the scores only for the second game.
Will the points be scored in the first two games?Yes
This is only the second game Yes, the second game
Please give me the score. Yes, the red team is strong.
After all, the red team has made a comeback against the white team.
Egumi's strategy line was clever.
I felt it, but surprisingly, that pain
I feel like I'm going to hit whatever comes my way.
It felt like that, so on the contrary, I wasn't aggressive enough.
Is it really that meaningful in terms of number of kills?
So, in the sense that you can definitely earn points?
If that's the case, I'll at least get beaten up like this.
We are doing it together now.
But I wonder if my power is being tested like this.
place
It says "bokoboko".
Bokobo-chan and I are stirring things up here too.
Yes, the third match continues.
The last Mokuba Line, yes, up to 3 games.
I went there and stopped for a while.
So I see, I see, yes, in 3 games.
I'll dye it red at the end, Tor-san
We communicate with each other verbally.
They're competing in the match, but the red team...
Earn points by playing games properly.
So we have to fight each other and the words are as expected.
This is because I'm very persuasive.
I guess it's okay, I just pretended it was okay at first.
It's amazing what you do, but you're doing great.
But it's totally possible to turn around.
I hope you'll do your best in the third match.
It seems like I want it. Is it number 1 overall?
Point Before this cat's nekise
Yeah, I want to make sure I don't get overtaken.
I'll do my best if money works hard too.Glass
This is also the first time for all of you to participate in the race.
That's true, but isn't it quite familiar?
I really want to do practice broadcasts and things like that with everyone.
I'm so sorry that I was being attacked so much.
No, just your lives.
I tried to write something and erased it a little.
That's why M is included.
I'm sure it's okay.
I guess so, but the color is a little different.
I wonder if I want to go with a clean feeling.
I think everyone's words are wrong.
We're fighting each other, but it's porridge.
Mr. is a bit of an enemy. He is supposed to be a friend.
But I'm going to tell you that I made a mistake.
I'll go out of my way to tell you through the general chat.
I am doing something typical of Yu-san.
What about the food? Everyone one after another.
I have entered. Yes, please wait.
sky channel
Let's defeat it! The pressure is amazing. In just one word, it's amazing.
After all, when you start to feel something, you suddenly feel it.
When it closes, the pressure will increase.
I felt the growth from the sky.Growth.
After all, I feel it and would like to hear from Mr.
It's a good thing, a good thing, Hololai Brush.
So, after all, yes, yes, my
It seems like everyone other than your team is your enemy.
I guess it looks like they're getting along so well that they're trying to defeat each other
I'm here now, here's an entry.
Well, I lived here one after another, but yes.
Hello, what's up? It's nice. Under the cherry blossom tree.
My craft is definitely riding fangs under
It's true that you can do anything.
Looks like you're ready. Well then.
It's not coming. It's the start of the third game. Ah, it's the end.
That's right
[music]
321 Everyone, please do your best. Good luck.
Please, what strategy will you use next?
Yes, in the end it doesn't matter what strategy you use.
I was also attacked by Neunkichi in pieces.
First of all, Subaru and Wasan
It's the two of you listening to the pair's conversation.
It's amazing how fast it develops and how dangerous it is.
It's amazing how many times have you lost me?
in
Don't do it again and again
[music]
Well, it's bad, but my heart
I feel like things are progressing pretty quickly.It's fast.
Nemo pair Chico and Noel pair
listen
Why? I'm sure it's okay tomorrow.
I'm going to the big sister Subaru-san.
Even though I tried to call out to them, I was targeted from behind.
Masua-chan, look behind you too.
I finally figured out where I was being targeted and moved behind.
This is the book that comes from Machiko Luna's bond here
The splash will be reset once.
Yes, yesterday's friends are today's enemies.
Well, it's almost over. Yes, that's it.
Thank you very much Zeta-san, you have 3 kills.
Airoha-san and Azuki-san are also colored and wood.
It's amazing that you got 3 kills.
Neiha-san, yes yes yes, as expected of a samurai
Yes, there is a place there.
Shall I go to the interview? Okay then, right away.
Let's go to the interview here.
Wooden pair of Ozora Subaru and Sanwa
I heard that I can do an interview, so let's talk.
I would like to visit you both.
Can you hear me, Tsumarusanwa?
I can hear it, I can hear it, thank you for coming.
Thank you for your hard work. I can hear you.
Only in my brain
I'm talking to you, so I'd like you to translate it for me.
Yes, I heard you.
Okay, so after today's game, I'd like to say a few words.
I asked if it would be okay if I received it from both of you.
I guess I was winning in that feeling.
But I definitely had a passion for it.
Ah, I think the quality is over.
It's true, but it's also a taste, so I'll go with Asiaji.
I must say I was in the best of spirits.
I wonder if Genki-san really conveyed this.
I heard that Genki-san was number one, and he was the number one to shout.
It's not like I'm too energetic. There's nothing wrong with that.
not caught
Are your ears down?
I definitely want to do my best.
Yes, Amone, the fortune-telling still continues.
So I hope you will do your best.
Thank you very much
Thank you very much. I said yes.
So the three games were over in a flash.
It's over, it's over, what's up?
Maybe it's just that it's over before I can look back
It seems like it's all over now.Every minute goes by quickly.
I certainly thought so, but
It started quickly, everyone, time is of the essence.
I know it's short, so I'll just say it like this.
Let's go on the offensive, we both move without hesitation.
The match progressed quickly.
I think it's the same, but it's still 1.
Game 2 game 3 game and how to attack everyone
That's why the yellow team especially changed things.
I was using it and putting it back again after all.
In the end, I went on the offensive.
But what happened to the score?
Yes, the red team was strong, it was strong.
Well, how was the third game?
I guess I just went.
Don't worry, I'm looking forward to the results.
We are currently compiling the data.
We will notify you once you have earned points.
I would like to inform you that I would like to
The organizers of Masumata are playing a game where Neena appears.
So that's true, everyone.
I think it got really heated.
I think it was fun here.
That player has become a player.
The score is only for the 3rd game, yes.
So here it is
This is Jean-Jean, the third game is Red Team 12
This means that the white team scored 19 points and the yellow team scored 7 points.
The white team made a comeback and it was amazing.
Well, Ha-san and A-san got 3 kills.
Thank you very much.
I can't read it so much, it's yellow.
Maybe it's a bit harsh?
I'm afraid that the general is that general.
Everyone is back, so let's move on again.
In return to the three of us, we are also printing teachers
I would like to return to
Everyone, please look forward to it!
Please enjoy and thank you
Thank you for waiting.
I'm in the middle of the day, so I'm home now.
Good thing the sound quality is back now.
Just said yes, so E-chan Nodoka
Thank you for the progress
Thank you very much
Better
Well, it was a little scary, 41ki
What's wrong with that? There's a white bug right now.
I thought it was something like that, but overseas people
I'm just saying you worked really hard.
No, there are already too many kill leaders.
It was a little bit of a final rise.
I was able to guide you
But the pair that Chim thinks he made are already around
It was so confusing that I couldn't understand anything.
is
But no, it's a little bit, well, well, well.
Well then the last 3 games yeah yeah yeah
Let's take a look at the rankings and listen a little.
I think I'll go. Yes, the Red Team, the Red Team.
After all, I asked Master if it was the last time.
Let's try it out, ask Jaato-sama's team.
I would like to pair Toa-sama and Kinte.
Is it yes?
Yes, I don't care how it went, that's right.
I think the red team was already strong on average.
I think it's strong
That's right, Toa made up a strategy just in case.
Everyone's like, ``Let's do this.''
Follow me then
Even if there is no voice chat
Communication or cooperation
I think it must have been removed.
I really want to protect Miku.
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
When Miku slips on her hand, she says "I'm tired"
It's like I'm swinging it around a little bit.
I think it was very well balanced.
I'm thinking about it. It's a bit disappointing in the end.
But it cost 280,000 yen, so nice.
Nice nice nice everyone is amazing
I really tried my best.
Thank you for the book, Senkyu will do his best in the second half.
Let's do our best
Well, let's go to Jasan's white team, who did their best.
The white team is right, after all, Ko-porridge-san.
I want to go see a little pair of Mr. and Kanata.
I'm fine, shall I go?
Yes, it's a little bit, but I changed the top and bottom part of the way.
That's right, I changed it, right?
I wonder if it was a strategy.
What is it, Kayu-chan, can you hear me on the island?
muscle tone
It's amazing, move on, the last 41 km
I joked about it
Please stop it, Negida, it's my strength.
Yo, I turned bright red when Miko-senpai returned.
It's just too strong
Too white. What do you think? The number of kills is amazing.
Who was it? Who cut it first?
Cha-chan and Kiara were amazing too, everyone.
I'm sorry about that at the very end.
I defeated Subaru-senpai twice and Miko-senpai once.
I don't like it, stop it, I was being chased so much
Kaela and others came a lot too.Kaela
That's amazing
It was a great help
Okay, so the white team was great.
But at the end, a little cat mata porridge.
Thank you very much
Please give me your impressions.Yes, here.
Thank you very much, along with everyone.
I was happy to be able to play with you.Continue cheering for the white team.
Thank you very much
stubborn
Thank you, thank you, it will disappear in an instant
It disappeared for a moment. Well then, it disappeared.
Next, I went to an interview with the Kigumi pair.
The wooden pair I would like to use is Hacos.
Why did I choose this pair in the first place?
Well, simply how were these two?
I wonder if my mother is worried about that.
That's amazing, Hacos is also actively working overseas.
While interacting with the members like this, this fang line
I was practicing, so I was wondering how the results were.
I just wanted to ask if it happened.
I would like to interview you
Can you hear me please? Can you hear me?
I can hear it. How was it?
Let's play our roles as kid leaders.
I think I did a great job.
What did you do?
Noe's last game was the 7th
People are amazing, amazing kills, how about Hacos?
Did you see it from Hakos' point of view, it was cut quite a bit at first?
Taiya was pretty strong. He was really strong.
First of all, are you okay?
It's okay, it's okay, it's the Banchou, the Banchou.
Didn't he demonstrate the power of
Kube Masen Kube Match Thank you
The second half of the sports festival will be held in the future.
Good luck in the second half as well. Good luck.
Please do your best, thank you
Thank you to everyone who followed me.
Thank you very much
Yes, that's the end of the benefits.
I'd like to take a look at it, but no.
Click here for the total score of the 3 games for the Ga Line group
Do your best!
circle
or
[applause]
Wow, that's awesome, so the red team got 46.
The white team scored 38 points and the yellow team scored 23 points.
That's amazing! It was only around that level until just now.
I guess it turned around
I turned it around
Since it was Neyoshi, the second half of the game continued after Nemako.
What will happen next?
Do you want to go? Yes, but then let's move on to the next competition.
Let's all move to the race venue.
Let's move please
It's amazing, it's amazing, it's amazing
Yeah, I don't like it a bit, but the red team is a little bit
Miko was a little moved when she turned around.
No, I'm definitely happy, and I think I'll wear white again.
It came out because of this, so it's still in the second half.
It's all from here, it's still from here.
It's a whisper and an obstacle race after all.
Shishitrace is quite a bit
It's a game where you don't know who will win or lose.
Yeah, yeah, it's quite a bit, isn't it?
I think so.
Well, really no, this time.
I will also notify the listeners.
But there is a creative course.
Isn't it? Yes, it's stage 2.
Yes, that place's theme pot practice theme
Yes, the second question is the one that has been published for the first time.
The topic is Holomen.
It's a practice topic along with hunting.
There's a topic that I've never seen before.
That means it might come, too.
I hope you look forward to it.
That's right, so here's the fourth one.
The competition will be a short race. Yes, yes.
Then please introduce Mikokarase.Yes.
The Ehigoe race consists of 4 people per team.
It's a competition. One person plays the role of a princess, and the other three play the role of knights.
Various gimmicks while protecting Narihime
It is a race to clear.
Yes, there are 5 stages in total and the first
stage
This is the stage where the lights cross over the heads of the three people.
It seems like shouting out loud is very important.
Yes, the second stage is architecture and a message game.
The stage of crawling is the third stage.
A stage where you work together to cook food. Yes, yes, yes.
And the fourth stage is the block cipher
Wastage Yes, yes, there is a fifth stage.
It's the last stage of the mob. Yes, it's strange.
I was able to send them safely to the goal.
The score will be 1st place, 3 points, and 2nd place.
20 points 3rd place 10 points
It means oh yes
So I won this competition.
I was just telling you about this event.
Are there any points to win?
Thank you Yes, I will win this competition
The key point is exactly the princess's commanding ability.
Isn't it the power of direction?
After all, without these instructions, the knights
can't do anything and it seems like
Yes, that's the kind of game it is.
The princess keeps saying things like ``cats''.
It's important to participate because yes, yes, yes, yes.
I would like to interview everyone
I think so
Yes I can hear it
Yes, yes, let's hear it from the red team first.
Let's go, Red Team Noe
The role of Gato Sane is played by Shin-tan and
It's blue and fluffy.
There are four of us here, and those two are the ones who are fluffy.
There's only one person
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
So how about your enthusiasm?
teeth
I'll do my best, I'll do my best
We all practiced until late at night.
I'm sleepy. I'll try my best. I usually go to bed at 9 o'clock.
But I practiced until 1 o'clock and went back at 9 o'clock.
It's true that I practice too much
Seriously, nothing happened at 9 or 10 o'clock.
I sleep on days when I don't have to, which is amazing.
So you woke up really early?
Yes, definitely try your best
Hey, let's do our best. It's okay. We'll do our best. We'll do our best.
Please, it's okay
Do your best, try your best, then I want to join the white team.
Masuhaiha
Yes, white group, can you hear me? Can you hear me?
Masu
So I'd like to start by introducing the players.
I think it's going to rain when it rains.
It looks like it's a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit
I was able to become a person, Hideshi, yes, the cavalry role is Azuki.
chan yes yes and yellow yes yes
And Nanamu-chan, hahahaha
There are 4 people.
What do you think? I don't have much enthusiasm.
Those knights of mine protect me.
I'll give it to you
I think it's okay. It's okay.
Okay, this time I want to protect those three princesses.
I think there are three princesses.
I would like to protect the three princesses. Thank you.
Please, princess, yes, no, no, no, this much.
So cute and such a cute Yume-senpai.
Is it okay? It doesn't look blue.
Kai is amazing and chaotic.
do not have
Do your best, do your best, fight fight
Okay then, let's ask the Kigumi one last time.
I would like to go to the group where the role is played by Iris.
The knights begin the Summer Festival
It's a Lyrica festival, right?
So what do you think, Netsuhime, how are you doing today?
The princess has been established, yes, the princess, this cat, that knight.
We want everyone to enjoy great cooperative play with
I'll show you how wonderful it looks
It's Su
[music]
at the fastest speed
It's number 1, I want you to take it.
Princess yes the true princess is me
princess
Yes, please do your best.
Thank you very much
Good luck to all of you for your entries.
I hope so. Yes, yes. Now, this is finally here.
Well, it will start as soon as the entry is finished.
It looks like it's going to be a long time. Yes, everyone is here.
Yes, yes, it seems to be okay.
Yeah, this is making Subaru a little nervous too.
What do you mean, Subaru is a princess?
I'm not a princess even though I don't have one, but I'm not a princess
Although I'm not the princess you call Nakaichi.
As expected, everyone is working really hard.
I've been practicing, so here are the results:
I think it's good, I really do
By the way, that number of matches was just the first round of the cat.
That's right, that's what it is.
It looks like it's going to happen again. I'm nervous.
I'm sorry but please enjoy it.
I want to get it.Yes, which team will be in first place?
And then the cat's race, the princess's
It seems like people are paying attention to my appearance as well.
Hey, the knight has also become a proper knight.
Even the smallest details have been reproduced.
That's right.The cooking is actually ours.
I showed you a little bit yesterday.
That's right, Mami Oya's signature hamburger.
Miko Kahai's elite pancakes
Subaru's fried chicken is something only Subaru has.
I was a bit surprised by the simple fried chicken.
Subaru is served simply with fried chicken.
No, no, no, no, this is wrong.
It's like Subaru, no.
I'm sorry, so I can't get ready.
With that in mind, I would like to start
I think so. Let's start the decisive race.
It's about to begin, my heart is pounding, it's about to begin.
I wonder if we can work together well.
Yeah 1 start started started started
It's begun. First of all, let's go to the scaffolding over there, princess.
Let's carry you, so crispy
Hurry up, it's important to say it out loud.
Yes, I think it's a very difficult stage.
However, we all went here quickly during practice.
Yes, the latter was in the lead.
Yes, the difference between gold and white is fine, it's fine.
Calm down. I'm calm. Very small.
My finger is shining, I guess.
It's okay, it's okay, be careful.
White is ahead with a slight lead.
Yes, stage 2 is here, and the kisses made it.
Please tell me what you are.This is that 2.
The first theme becomes Holomen's name.
Let's make a new name Holomen.
The difficulty level of this topic has not increased significantly.
Is it going up?
It's pretty easy to understand, for example, rap.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, Ako
Looks like you cleared the first question like a child.
Hey, you're early. Come on, red team. What the hell is this?
Red team, what are you making?
I don't think this is true.
Spa red team looks like Ozora Su So fast white
The team was also successful. Good luck, yellow.
Yes, Mr. Stage, I'm watching the Red Team.
Good luck but eat what you want
I thought I'd give you a present.
However, yellow is having a bit of a hard time.
It seems to be
hey
Who the hell is this?
I answered correctly.I answered correctly.
There's nothing left to do, hurry up!
You're eating too, aren't you? You're eating too, aren't you? Red, red
It's so fast, this cooking costume is crazy
The red color was very bright.The red color was very early.
Early red, early Saeaa is leading with the princess.
Let's answer the question.
Red is too early to answer. It's too early. White is also now.
Let's break through! Yellow, do your best, do your best, we'll hit the end.
It was the last stage mob subjugation until I gave up.
What kind of problems are being raised?
Although it is interesting, white and yellow and red
Hurry up, yellow! Do your best! Yellow is here! Red is here!
Red is in the lead by a long shot
It's early, the battle has already started. Yes, white too.
It's in a bottle. Hurry up. Yellow. Good luck.
The yellow color has fallen off quickly.
They're chasing me, it's looking good, Mob.
The hunt has begun. It's already begun.
Airo is messed up and red group is the last stage
The white team is now in the second stage.
It's important, isn't it?
Do your best, the princess is putting out her dick from behind.
I have
Come on, it's quick, quick, quick
Is this the red color that will be cleared soon?
Cleared the stage 3
White, come on, yellow, do your best, do your best, you're strong, stubborn
stubborn
mysterious
Kekekekekekekeke
Red is really nice, nice, right now
I'm chasing you, thanks to White
Yellow, do your best, which one?
What will happen? At the same time, almost at the same time
Defeated
That goal was quick
It's a shame, but everyone's time is so fast.
That's a great inspection
There are new problems that I haven't been able to practice yet.
Amazing and quite high level battle
Yes, this was at a pretty high level.
It was like 5 minutes, but it's like 7 minutes.
Only think about that
Apparently it was a Subaru after all.
Yes, it was a Subaru, but it's quite large.
The name Subaru sounds pretty good to me.
It might have been easy, but no.
It was made in yellow, so at first glance
I see.
What kind of questions did all the children have in the past?
I'm a little concerned, but I can't really see it.
So we're definitely amazing.
Please check it from each perspective.
Yes or no, everyone's time was fast.
It was so fast, it was so fast. 1st place red.
But it's 3 minutes and 26 seconds, and there's a difference of tens of seconds.
It was pretty cool, right? White was 3 minutes and 48 seconds.
Well, my house is 3 minutes and 51 seconds, so 3 seconds.
It was the difference, but it was yellow at the end.
I rolled it up and it was amazing.
That was amazing. That made my heart flutter.
I was so excited. I was so excited.
Yes, it was a good fight.
Now, I would like to move on to the interview.
We will interview each team here.
Can you hear me? Yes.
I can hear you, congratulations on the red hair.
Congratulations!
Well then, how was Shion from Knight?
try it
No, I seriously practiced and practiced a lot.
It seems like 4 people gave it to me, so that's correct.
I'm really happy that I came out with that result. It's great.
It was really fast, it was crazy
It was early, wasn't it?
Umo
The topic is Subaru as expected.
Yes, it's yellow at first.
I think this is because I was making something.
I was wondering what everyone was making.
Replying to @sarah_mcdonalds
I hope you can watch it.Yes
Congratulations on saying yes.
Congratulations! Congratulations! Congratulations!
Congratulations, let's do our best on the last ride too.
So
would like to go white
Okay, then I'd like to hear about the White Team.
I think so, but yes, yes, how was it?
I don't care how sloppy it is, but it's the end.
Mume-chan is about to defeat that guy.
I got caught in the cage or something.
Hey, there's something between Wave and Wave.
It looks like a cage, but it's actually stuck.
That's right, it's Mira, but I defeated all of them.
me being here
I'm glad I came second in Sugo, wow, wow.
Well, I've thought about it.
I did my best, despite some accidents.
I overcame it well.By the way, the topic is
Who was there? Who was there? Ah, Luna.
It was Lunar, no, here too, Canaluna.
The bond between them was pinkish.
I was at a loss, but it's already in kana.
I believed in Luna's bond.
It was so heavy that I got very sleepy.
Thank you very much
Thank you very much Guchogu
Thank you very much, then continue
I would like to hear from the Kigumi.
Yes, I tried it and what did you think?
Wow, that's really frustrating, right? Practice.
Tamon's catch-up at the end was really amazing.
Yes, I was catching up, I was catching up
It was amazing that I made a mistake in guessing the question.
It's okay even if it's really bad
It's okay, mom, I saw you working hard.
That's right, I did my best at the sports meet.
We'll all do our best until the end.
Of course it has a meaning.
Aiming even higher, everyone until the end
Let's run to the end, Mom, you're beautiful.
good luck
By the way, what was the topic?
Even Laplace was Laplace after all.
"Daun, show me something" and the last one was porridge.
It's certainly difficult, isn't it?
How did you make it? Mom, Akami later.
Especially the yellow team's Okasou desu.
We'll all run until then, do your best, do your best
Good luck! It was a nice fight.
Nice fight, please do your best.
There is
Yes, okay, yes, that's it.
Let's see the score of the race Yes
Yes, the red team was in first place, so it was 30
Points: 20 for the white team, 10 for the yellow team
The point is yes, Red team, Red team, a little bit.
That's amazing. In 2023.
Maybe the red team is coming? No, it's not yet.
I don't understand, it's still like that, it's still like that
I don't understand, I still don't understand this.
From now on, the next competition will be the autumn/winter race.
Let's move to the venue. Dangerous Spring, Summer, and Autumn
I'm going to say more, just a little bit, I understand.
I won't say that, but that's an amazing ladder.
remove
That's okay, that's the end.
Do you have any hope of making a comeback by playing in this competition?
Hey, what's going on? I have this.
I'm already calling for a ticket.
Yellow is definitely there, right? It's a complete reversal.
If you don't have that kind of eyes
No matter what the outcome is, we'll all end up together.
I'm sure I'll do my best until then.
Mom looks like she's going to cry, please do your best.
It's great, everyone is doing their best, really class.
The mother starts crying at the council officer. No, it's true.
Everyone, everyone, everyone, do your best.
Even though it's true, there are quite a lot of yellow colors, one by one.
After all, I figured this out and did it this way.
I think it's twice as frustrating, though.
I also ran the final relay under the direction of Sora.
Well, Lyrica and I are really nervous right now.
I think so, but please do your best.Yes, that's fine.
I want you to do your best.I want you to do your best.
Next up is Shito Shuto.
Same as above, 1st place gets 30 points, 2nd place gets 20 points
30 points, 1st and 3rd place are 10 points, so it's one chance.
Yes, there is.
I wonder if there's a certain amount of red, and red is at the bottom.
If white and white or yellow are on top, it's one.
I have a chance, now that I've come this far 1
I have to do everything I can to aim for that place, but I'm sure there will be obstacles.
Lillet is the last one because this is the best.
It will be a competition, so yes, spring and summer.
Introduced by Miko, who will be the last of today's winter rele.
Please, yes, yes, spring and summer two in a row.
It is an obstacle competition with a motif.
Eight members from each team will be selected to participate in two tournaments.
Run through the seasons alone and pass the baton to the next person
After completing 4 laps of one course
This will be the goal.Yes, yes, in this competition.
There are points to win, Kamiko.
Yes, this is the first one.
I'm pretty sure it's punk.
Time is so connected that it's punk
This is what you eat when you get bread
I think it would be nice if it were available, but yes.
Yes, there are certainly some types who run without eating.
Of course it is, but it is so.
Well, there are, so which one should I choose?
That's the strategy. Yes, yes, the rest is
Isn't it Tsuta after all? No, this is the second half.
As expected, the ivy is the key to the costume.
After all, I'm going to use the full amount of vines.
It's early after all, right? If it falls early, it'll come again
at the end
Yeah, I wonder how this is going to turn out.
Yes, as I said earlier,
The score is 30 points for 1st place and 20 points for 2nd place.
The third place in points is 10 points.
The contestants said, ``No, I don't know.''
I would like to interview everyone from
I think so.Okay, let's start with the red team.
Let's listen, but first, members.
Introduction from 1st layer to Fumaoe 2nd layer to 1st layer
Eye 2 Ente number first
Let's go in order, Eja Afumo-kun.
And Kueunkaune and Fauna
Yeah memerucari mercari
[music]
Yes, yes, Shion-tan runs at the end.
If you say yes, then go to the interview.
Can you hear me? Can you hear me?
Masu
What do you think? Well, let me ask you something.
I'm thinking of going, but it's so fluffy.
It's the first one, but what do you think?
I'm a little worried, but at Hime High School earlier.
I got a little carried away after buying that.
[laughter]
I want to run hard, so cute
Yes, let's keep going like this, let's keep going like this
Let's do our best
I stubbornly said yes, so it was the last competition.
So let's all do our best, do our best
Good luck. Next up is the white team. Okay.
I would like to interview the white team.
But first, it's the contestants' turn.Yes, yes.
1st layer
Nerisa Yes, next is Choco Sensei Choco Sensei layer
There's no Mume, and the fourth floor is Commander Noel.
Yes, the fifth layer, ah, yes, the sixth layer
Kaela Une 7th layer is Azusan Une and the last one
That's the basics of knowing something like this.
I mean, Minecraft is getting better and better.
I feel like people who are used to it are coming in.
I just feel like I want to catch up.
You look amazing! Interview
Let's go, okay?
[music]
White team, can you hear me?
Okay, how about it?
So who should I choose?
Or something like that would be fine.
Well then
When you realize what an anchor is, become an anchor.
But I guess it's because the wind is moving so fast.
I've earned your trust, so I'll do my best.
I would like to, that's wonderful
Oh well, let's go to the white team, by all means, win first place.
I want you to do your best, please do your best
Please be patient
Thank you very much. See you then.
Lastly, I would like to ask the Kigumi.
The wooden structure from the first floor onwards is Iris.
This is Hajime-chan from Narumasu.
Can you hear me?
Yes, yes
Who is Kaa Genki Gura or Ima Gura?
[music]
Genki Ririka is really nervous
I don't want to hang out, but remember, director Sora.
Those days when we ran, I think it's okay now
It's hardwired into my memory, so it's my brain.
I'll do my best, then please do your best.
This is my last competition, so I'll give it my all and do my best.
Let's go
Yes, MVP, Granny, Kuroni, everyone.
Do your best, Neshiri-chan, do your best too.
Thank you very much everyone
Please do your best.
It's finally the last competition, everyone!
No matter what the outcome is, I'll stay here.
I want you to give it your all and run to the end.
Yeah, it didn't feel very short at all.
It's so early, I felt it, Mio after all.
The 10 minute experience you mentioned may be true.
I can't believe it, it's true, it's true, it's true
I don't want to say that I have one, I'm serious.
I thought it was too much.
Seriously, it only took about 10 minutes, so fast.
Everyone just said yes.
I wonder if he entered.
Yes, it's the first time, so I'm sorry.
Let's go to the end, all of you listeners.
Everyone, please support me a lot at the end.
Please, please, see you in spring and summer.
It's a start, do your best, let's do it automatically.
The first person and the second person will be automatically tested.
It's amazing, it's amazing, it's groundbreaking.
This caused me to wonder what number it was.
That's right, Iris.
Do your best, let's catch the lil' pigeon
Let's go for it, number one! Let's go for it! Red is in the end!
I'm in the house, but it's a bit
Maybe I fell behind, but I did my best.
Okay, first bread
white
And everyone's close, hold on to your bread
Yes, I am eating.
I'm leading the way. It's fast. Good.
Good job, Ri
It's fast, it's fast, it's very fast
I'm trembling to do my best
It's so sparkly Chico
Delicious chico, delicious chico line, amazingly delicious
The chocolate is delicious, delicious, has it fallen?
It's a little hard to see here, but this is Steelo.
Let's liven it up and do our best
That's it
The color is more vibrant. Oops, I can fix it.
Nao is working hard, Nao is working hard, that's it.
Win now yellow is leading yellow white red
It's my turn, but everyone doesn't do it.
This is good
Red is likely to catch up with white here.
What will happen to the white everyone tunnel?
Now, Director Sora, we're doing it carefully and carefully.
The director is Saa Sora, as expected of the director.
Here we go, white and red at the same time.Red becomes 2.
I'm just barely used to it
Adepan is running without eating bread.
Eating fish
Do your best, Director! Do your best! Do your best!
Osaco
white white
I still don't knowI still don't know
This is really the last one, this is a really close battle.
It's a very close race.Looking at the team's good performance.
The water just fell.
Come on everyone, it's delicious.
Rika is good, Rika is good, do your best
Good luck Rika, Rika has achieved some success.
It's almost the same time, it's almost the same time, do your best, do your best
Do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best
Do your best, try your best, do your best, do your best, do your best
The support was so enthusiastic that everyone kept their eyes on the screen.
Let's chase hard, let's do our best, it's like this
If you enter, come out.
Tamel
Mr. Saso behind
[music]
I didn't have the ball for a while when I came back.
Come and eat some bread and give me some bread.
It's okay, I don't know yet
I can't
le
[music]
The Red Team is ahead, but in first place.
It's Kaela. Kaela is running here.
It's early red, it's early, Toa is early, Toa is early.
The hair is long. What a great run.
Kae also makes a quick mistake.Kaela is also quick.Kaela
It's early, Kanomi Polka was able to get the bread.
Is that so?
I can understand even if I drink Polka-ka.
Okay, now next, Totanaice.
It's okay, it's number 2 Daz-chan, number 2 Daz-chan.
Now the baton has been passed to the last anchor.
I'll do my best, try my best, try my best, now is the time
Now here, red and white are amazing at almost the same time
Hey, it's a good battle. We'll see how it goes until the end.
I don't understand, I'm calm.
Okay, calm down, is this an anchor?
I got an anchor in Aka, now I'm a white anchor.
Pointing to the front of
[music]
Do your best, do your best
[applause]
Do your best, salt is delicious, as expected of salt
Just a little more to the Umaisan goal
I'm running
Congratulations! Let's start here
Good luck, white is now 2, from the beginning to the end
Do your best, do your best, do your best
Do your best, do your best until the end
The water is finally here
Mr. Zhang, do your best and run till the end.
[music]
[applause]
Eggplant, no, just a little more
Mom is impressed.Mom is impressed.
Mom's gonna cry a little Mom's gonna cry too
That's right Mom, Mom, I think I'm going to cry.
But everyone had a really good run.
I slept
I really liked that ranking.
Yeah it was amazing I had no idea
1st place Red group 2nd place White group 3rd place
It became the yellow group.
Yes, it's a bit too hot.
It's already at the level of live commentary.
There wasn't
[applause]
It was just an arrowhead, after all, I had a fever.
I'm sure this relay will work.
Yes, I have to say, then I'll be number one in Citrile.
I would like to interview the team of
Masu
Can you all hear me? Congratulations!
Congratulations, it means you were hungry and fast.
Everyone from the red team was quick.
Congratulations!
[applause]
Unfortunately, I was left out in the middle of the game.
Maybe I'll turn into a rhinoceros on the way.
It took a long time, but I managed to get 1st place.
I did it
That's wonderful. Congratulations.
How was Shion-tan? I don't know what happened at the end.
No, I was really nervous, so I was a little nervous.
I don't remember much, but a lot
It was a great move, everyone was working really hard.
No, seriously, I'm glad I came in 1st place.
Thank you everyone, everyone is really nice
That's really nice, that's really nice, that's really nice
Thank you for your hard work everyone who played nice
Thank you for your hard work.
Please look forward to it.
Next up, let's go to the White Team.
I'm going to the team Shirogumi interview Hey Shirohaku
You did your best. You did your best.
good
Okay, let's talk a little bit about how I was acting.
From the beginning to the end
It'll be okay until the end, so hold on to everything.
I'm here. It's okay. It's okay. Key.
It's okay, I don't know what the result will be.
There were times when it was removed and removed.
It was great to be able to finish in 2nd place.
That's great. That was a nice fight.
It was a nice fight Gucci
It was a nice fight.
Congratulations to the group for a great run
Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work.
I'm tired, let's go to the next yellow group, wait.
please
Negumi members
You've done a great job, mom.
I was impressed
Just a little reading, run until the end
It looks really shiny when you cut it.
Thank you very much. See you soon.
What was it like at the beginning of the interview?
The anchor was nervous, right?
Damn, but it ended as soon as it started
Then it ended the moment it started
It looks like the team that has locked in gold will end.
That's what I'm saying
That's why I had so much fun running.
Well then, in the end, I'll call it the best run.
Best of all, I'm glad
Everyone, you did your best. You did your best.
Thank you
Thank you for your patience, I say yes.
With this, all competitions are over.
I wonder what the final result will be.
I'm looking forward to it. I'm looking forward to it. That's why I said yes.
After this, we will hold the closing ceremony, so everyone please take a look.
Please meet before the meeting.Yes, at the beginning.
Yes, this is the very first one.
I need to get better at the game.
If not, I will interrupt.
Yes, yes, why?
Please, it's over.
It took a while. Once it started, it went by in a blink of an eye.
It went by so quickly.
Even though the time passed so quickly, there were so many voices.
I think my throat felt a little rough after I took it out.
Well, that's the last one.
The score was amazing, everyone was beautiful, the Kigumi was okay.
Is the wooden group okay? Is it okay if the group is the only group?
It's Takocchi, so it's kind of free, Kigumi.
After all, the feeling is the best
I'm passionate about it, so where am I now?
Maybe I won't understand
I see, they definitely fight each other.
There's something really wrong with the team.
No, that's true, isn't it?
I'm calm and alert.I'm calm and alert.
Look at the polka
Yo, I don't look at polkas, lined up like polkas
Everyone's volka, Tatsuno's volka
I have a lot of polkapa and bread that cheers me up.
Is it okay? Is black okay? It's over here. Yes.
It's a little too much and they fight a lot.
But it's okay if you proceed with that.
Okay, yes, that's the closing ceremony.
It's starting, but how was Yami-san?
Well, this year is fine.What will happen?
To be honest, I had no idea.
But yeah
Everyone is working together so well.
It's amazing how hard you work, it's a close battle every year.
I thought it was amazing and worth seeing.
I guess it's true, to each his own.
There was a drama
I think it's a drama, including practice.
But yes, I thought it was really good.
For those who are trying their best but can't get it all together,
Wait a minute, I can't let mom in that group.
That's why Mio-chan was talking about English just now.
I'm coming to ask you to get along well with your group.
They lined up nicely, right?
Yes, yes, so how about the ceremony?
I guess it's okay, let's connect Schat.
Yes, but that's a bit of a problem right now.
I feel like please wait for a while.
I see, it looks like I can go, it's okay.
Yes, that's fine. Now, everyone, let's hear our voice.
Has it arrived? Has it arrived? Has it arrived?
It has arrived. I said yes and closed the ceremony.
Before this, for the competition, I'll say a voice.
There was a lot of chat movement.
But everyone, Nee-chan and that one.
A-chan and Nodo who supported me
I was thinking of saying something to you.
Good morning, good morning
Thank you very much Heaven's voice
Thank you for your hard work. This is the voice of heaven. Thank you.
Thank you very much again this year
Thank you everyone for this year too.
It's full of hard work and individuality.
The three organizers did their best and we
I can see it and it is very moving.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Thank you very much for your help.
Thank you very much, everyone.
Thank you both so much for your cooperation.
Thank you very much, all three of you participated.
I think it was fun to do it, so please give it a try.
Please do your best until the end, haha
Thank you very much
So, everyone,
We are about to hold a precept ceremony.First of all, let's start with the ceremony.
Chairman of the Sports Day Executive Committee
I would like a greeting from Nosamiko.Yes.
Yes, everyone had fun at this sports day.
is
mosquito
I'm glad it was fun, really, everyone.
It was good
Thank you everyone, really every year
Thankfully I'm really busy now.
Well, Flo Live is getting busy.
But even so, there were so many people gathered together.
Hey, let's all cooperate and each and every one of us can really do it together.
I see them being revived, calling out to each other and helping each other.
Miko and the others have already seen everything, so it's true.
Nima, I'm really full of emotion.
This is what I think every time. Thank you very much for your continued support.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
There is
Thank you very much for this opportunity.
Thank you very much, I'm a newbie.
That, that, that after all, en and ID
I hope to have more interaction with the members of
Let's all blow and Hololive more and more
I think it would be great if we could liven it up.
Thank you very much for your continued support.
Yes wonderful yes please please
Next, Mio-chan, please.Yes.
Thank you everyone for participating again this year.
You did your best. You did your best. You did your best.
Good job Ei
Everyone said that they were super great.
That's the finish line for this year, thank you
Thank you very much.
Next Subaru
Yes, Subaru too, I've been in touch with you for a while.
There's a lot of different things about the team.
I wanted to let them see themselves, though.
Every team is already working hard.
Well, I think the results will come out this time.
Let's do it! There's one thing we all worked hard on.
It's so big, I'm sure it will become a treasure.
I think that's why I hope to make use of this bond in the future.
I hope you enjoy watching it.
It was a lot of fun thank you very much
Thank you very much.
Tamashi Nice Speech Yes Nice Speech
No
Senkyu Senkyu Senkyu Haito
Finally, let's announce the general benefits.
I would like to come to the party. Announcement of bonuses.
is about 1 and then 100
3 in the order of 10 at the end
I would like to make an announcement all at once.
Now, let's take a look at the sports day executive committee chairman's list.
Please, please, yes then.
First, I will announce the number 1.
Please give me a beat then.
Wow, the red team is 8, the white team is 8, oh, the yellow team is 6.
Hey, what, what, it's a little scary
This announcement ceremony is scary, I don't know yet.
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know, okay, let's continue
I'll announce about 100 of them first.
Yes, yes, here is the number of 100.
Is that so?
please
Oh no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
It's terrible, I still don't understand, all of these are here
Yes, it's about 100 in all.
If it's dangerous, I'll go last, everyone.
Okay, so finally, I'll make about 10 announcements.
of
Please 111
So, the red team won with 158 points.
It's Akagami.
[music]
[applause]
Congratulations
amazing
Hike it, don't let it pass, don't do it.
I know it's frustrating, but
It's already reflected here, it's already reflected here
It's dangerous, it's dangerous, let's get along, let's get along
Let's get along, friendly please
Please be friendly.
with 138 points
White team placed 3rd and became Wood team with 106 points.
You all did a great job, everyone did a great job.
Yes, yes, it was amazing.
When will the award for "That was amazing" be given?
That's right, there's an awards ceremony this time, everyone.
It's okay to go to Sano, the yellow group has a rainbow medal.
This is Geo. Okay, okay then, yellow group.
The representatives of the players and teachers, Haskana Hasbe.
Chanbe-chan, please come here.
Please come
Well then, let's get 3rd place and medal.
Whatever it is
Aremikosanmisana
[music]
I'm going to make it to everyone as well.
Everyone is with me
[music]
[applause]
I have the neck ready for you now.
congratulations congratulations congratulations
So excited
It seems like everyone is following me.
Next up is Geo, who won a silver medal for the white team.
chan yellow group zuchan is coming
Please don't follow me, even if I'm standing.
I'm looking forward to it, but I'm nervous.
Congratulations to the white team, this is chan gold medal ji.
Thank you very much
oh
I'm eating so much. I'm eating so much. It's amazing.
[applause]
Congratulations! Congratulations!
Congratulations Osato and yes
And then there's Geo, the red team gold medalist who came in first place.
Yo
So
[applause]
Red team wins
Thank you and congratulations
oh
Congratulations
[applause]
Stop it, stop it, stop it
Say
Get along well
[applause]
hand
Let's get along well and see each other right in front of us.
wish
[applause]
It disappeared in a blink of an eye.
I wish there were so many diamonds
So that's all for now.
Let the live athletic meet 2023 be harmful
Thank you very much.
Ta
That's not to say it's not good, but it's a little bit bad.
Why do you want to take a commemorative photo?
Well, what should I do over there?
Let's put it on that table in the middle, okay?
Please, it's on the table.
Maybe, maybe, maybe
I'm sure you're done, but I'll take a photo.
No matter how we line up on the right, we'll line up. We'll line up.
Please line up and we'll get in too.
I'm putting poop in there too, I'm not putting it in, I'm putting it in.
Teruka is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa.
look
Teruai ii ii ii
Everyone is here, everyone is here.
It's still a little too late
Katakatakata here
Please wait a moment. Wait a moment.
Please give me a whole piece of Soliri.
Wait there for a moment and come in.
It's true that everyone is lying.
I have a great book that comes with a great book.
I'm happy, Area-chan and Konota fell once.
I don't have a medal, but I lost it.
Noe seriously yes it's true you medal
Gone
Ta
There's no such thing, no more
I won't get mad if I do it once, I'm gone
It's okay, it's sad.
sad sadness
Sugido
That's it, yes, that's it.
I can't give it to you, I can't give it to you, wait a minute.
Please put it on, it's warm and warm
finished product
Oh, that's good, everyone.
That little place in front of me
Should I watch it? Koro-san, maybe I should watch it.
I'm flying like a sanro sakoro
Sanne is flying, Koro-san, but it's a village
Look at the real village, look over there.
It's true, it's the cameraman in front.
The cameraman is here.
here and there
There's something
Hey everyone, are you okay? Can you see it? Let's take a photo.
Masu
[music]
I'm close to Yoto-sama.
I'm kind of hugging you.Okay then, let's go.
Yo hey cheese hey cheese cheese
Yay, hey, who's the one who threw it just now?
Who threw it now Who threw it this year?
Did someone throw it again? Stop it, everyone.
I'm throwing so much, I'm throwing so much
Don't litter, take your garbage home
I hope you can see it.
Thank you very much. Look at that cat.
Thank you to all the listeners as well.
The management that cooperated a lot with
All the staff are always very kind.
Thank you very much
Thank you very much.
Holorime Grand Sports Festival
It will end after 2023 Yes, that's it
Let's meet again, everyone holo
I'm going to the live show hahaha I'm going to the live show
Live
[applause]
Yeah yeah yeah
Yeah yeah yeah let's get along
I'll come over soon, I'll be friends with you.
[music]
hand
What do you think? I'm looking for a graphic.
It's not just about graphics. It's not about graphics.
I want to encourage you to do your best.I want to give you all that I have.
Chiara is surprised that there are people there.
Teru
[music]
For some reason Mel-san said it was me.
Well, Mr. Lu is the one doing it, but it has changed.
Tatsuga
If you fail, your failure will be confirmed.
hand
Masu
Failure is different
That's wrong, please stop it.
Stop it!
[applause]
[music]
Yes, I think the last theme is a bit blurry.
but soon
My senior
There's a lot of cha, it's good, it's good, it's so good
I'm catching you, I'm really catching you, no?
Is it sexy to be different?
mosquito
It's sexy, it's sexy
It's the second time I've done it. I wonder if this is okay?
No, no, I haven't taken a bath yet.
Lio Lili is here, how blue and sexy
I think that
Is it too much? It's okay, but here.
After all, it means aiming for the goal.
I want you to aim for the top without rushing.Practice
That's amazing, I reached the goal in 170 seconds.
It arrived on
It's so fast, look, it's only 100 seconds left
It's okay, it's okay here once.
Fallen down
Go soon
Go
We scored 12 goals after a great first game.
Congratulations Moe I think I can go
rare
That's great, but I don't want to stop it short.
That's really true, Anji-san.
Believe it or not, I've caught up.
So let's go higher and let go more slowly
It's dangerous, 5 seconds last jump
I wonder if I can go. It might be dangerous. I can go.
Is it dangerous?
It's amazing, it's the fastest, it's crazy
It's early
Why did I drop it? Why did I drop it?
I dropped it, I'm serious now
[music]
is
yes
Pipi
Ah, it's decided, everyone.
Isn't it a little early to start? Let's wait and see.
I don't have anything to do while I'm at it, but it's too late.
I was knocked down by the feeling, so I spoke properly.
Please call me
Yes, but I'm not calm.
Calliope, I can't help but play Mario Kart.
There are a lot of images where F comes out.
surely
certain
[music]
Ah, it's almost over here
Well, it was a bit scary, 41 kills.
It was so fast, I thought it was a nonstop game or something.
I thought, ``Please do your best!''
Freshly made
of
[music]
What is the red team making?
Could it be that Subaru red?
The team is Subaru
[music]
It's too early to eat this dish.
The red color of the costume was very bright.
early red
[music]
Hurry up, do your best, do your best
stubborn mystery
Nice, go, go, go, go, do your best.
keep it up
Do your best, red, do your best at the very end, do your best
Good luck, which one?
What will happen? At almost the same time
I defeated it
That goal was quick
[applause]
It's a shame, but the time is so fast
Everyone
That's amazing, Iris
Let's do our best and connect the pigeons
I'm running, I'm eating food
Here we go
in
Do your best, do your best, do your best
sasakoko
Come out
Tal
behind the tail
[music]
Mr. Hey, it's a good battle. How will it turn out until the end?
I don't know, calm down.
Yes, calm down, this is the anchor.
I lost my anchor. Roja also made a mistake.
running with
As expected, this is where I started.
Do your best, it's finally time to do your best.The beginning is swimming.
I'm watching it and I cut it to 8 until the end.
[applause]
[music]
After all, Akagami won with 158 points.
is
[music]
JA
T
[music]
a