e e
la
[Music]
k
k I stole ena's CSS
again every time every time I'm
abroad have you noticed I always steal
her
CS not always but most of the time don't
tell her I don't think she knows I don't
think she knows that I always used it
ever since she first gave it to
me the reason is because um well how
long is this how long ago was this wait
I can tell you how long ago this
this
uh
October or is this
January no January January
2023 so 1 and a half years ago we had a
stream what stream was it some sponsored
stream probably cuz we always do like
taco Tony does so many sponsored streams
have you noticed like we we we continue
to get like asked to do stuff together
for sponsored stuff there may or may not
be another one coming up where it's
specifically me and Ena again and I'm
like it
why though why I mean I don't mind but
why uh yeah it was probably vyy connect
one and a half years ago and uh I think
I was abroad again and I was like you
know I was like setting up and was kind
of like uh stressed out and I just
needed a a a CSS for the YouTube chat
really quickly and she just gave me hers
cuz she was at home I think so she could
give it to me fast
wow that sounds don't take it out of
context no um or maybe she wasn't at
home she was just more better set up I
don't know because this was uh January
2023 that was before our debut 3D debuts
but leading up to it I
think I'm drinking tea right now I had
uh a very sweet breakfast that will
maybe make me throw up in a minute um no
I'm probably fine although I did feel
like kind of sick for a moment before I
had the breakfast weirdly sick but
probably fine um I got tea I I bought a
big bottle of
water and I have some snacks if I need
them in the fridge I want to I don't
know if I should like just Tang it right
now right here or if I should do it
within the I want to I want to start out
with one at
least
um um man I think I look up too much
for now okay so first of all I changed
to Orange just because I had the
opportunity to do
so my my stuff my hat and so on is
orange now yay I'm am I peeking
hard Peak wo it's Peak well I don't
think I I don't sound like I'm peeking
to myself ah no I don't think
so lot of noise okay well there might be
noise I hear a little bit
too not optimiz there's no because the
AC is on on maximum because otherwise
I'm going to
die doesn't sound like you are you do
sound different what what do you mean
doesn't sound like I am what H not
peeking okay there's a white noise
you're going you're not going to hear it
once I put on the game
probably the noise is I don't know how
to cancel it with this they they gave me
this huge uh mixer that is really fancy
and then and I've used it several times
in the studio now uh but I never know
how to use it I always have to ask the
staff for the same thing over and over
and over again um and I I did find it
kind of nice so I looked up the price
but it was really expensive previously
when I checked it
out um yeah if if you're curious I'm
using a Yamaha
ag8 they they put a freaking Yamaha ag8
into my room so okay just so you know
I'm not in the studio now and so I am in
Japan again this time for a longer time
that's why I uh instead of a hotel this
time I'm in like a you know apartment
kind of place um just like just like
back in the day with the 3D debuts me
what you have an
extra why would have an extra
ag8 wait what do you mean you're going
to bring it to Japan and like give it to
me or
what
[Music]
H interesting I mean I I just never know
how to use it but I could get to like
get to know it I don't know if I need it
I'll think about it if you're serious
about it I consider it because you know
I I hate the road bter that I have I
hate it with have a
passion I'm like really considering
going back to the go XLR I'm just too
lazy to set it
up yeah
um huh we should meet up
mayto in any case we should meet up U
but yeah where was I uh oh yeah so I'm
here for a little bit longer than usual
so it's like kind of like like back in
the day with the 3D debuts where I have
an apartment I have uh you know like a
kitchen and everything um and this time
is even nicer than last time they they
they booked it for me because I have
like several
things uh like you know company projects
so they pay for it I pay for like a week
or so of it because like in between some
projects there's some extra time where
um I guess that goes over their limit of
uh what they would um take care
of uh and normally I would just like I
would be expected to go home I guess and
then come back but I said no this like
too stressful I'm not going to go home
for one week or so so let's just let's
just extend and put my um I guess
actually it's because
uh I'm doing one one of one of the
things is my own project so I I got to
you know take care of that financially
by myself my
freie uh birthday SL aniversary stream
that's going to be you know my own
project so I have to pay for it makes
sense um anyway uh so many things are
aligned so I'm here for a longer time so
I have a proper setup but so last time
uh for the 3D
debuts they gave us some setup but I
think it was not like this I think um
not
as good and well prepared as this I
think um um but last time in November
when I came to
Japan uh I I I I came from my own
project right that was like
3D uh uh recording and I I back then I
booked an Airbnb
cuz I wanted like an apartment style
place instead of a hotel so I could
stream uh so I had I had something like
this um and then I then I asked for some
equipment like I don't know what did I
ask for uh headphones mixer microphone
microphone stand stuff like that um and
they brought me exactly what I asked
for uh and I brought my own laptop you
know
um because I think that's how it worked
last time too in our 3D debuts and so
they brought me that stuff are you guys
still listening are you listening they
brought me that for November and
yeah and I didn't end up using it
because they brought it to me kind of
late after the days where I would have
been available to stream uh okay okay
you're listening good um so I didn't end
up using it also because the mic that
they gave me on uh in the trip I think I
it was pretty bad too um but just we
kind of missed the days where I would
have been available and then I got too
busy yeah um but anyway so they brought
me remember they brought me only what I
asked for uh in November yeah and since
then I've been to Japan several times
but I always was streaming in the studio
when I was in Japan because it was
always like shorter uh periods of time I
think um now this time I asked again I I
was bringing my gaming laptop I was
bringing on my own a second monitor I
brought a second monitor a portable
monitor I brought my fat ass big fat
chunky gaming laptop I brought a mouse I
brought
uh uh game capture card and my switch um
I think that's roughly about it uh now I
asked for like all kinds of other stuff
I asked for
uh a mixer a microphone a microphone
stand
headphones and that's that's roughly it
then I get in here and apparently they
booked the place like uh starting from a
few days before I arrived I didn't
expect that they would have have it
already prepared I was like um you know
assistant manager Chan picked me up and
and I was like so when do you think
they're going to bring me my equipment
huh because last time it was like really
late a few days later after my arrival
so I didn't expect them it to be right
there and and she was like no I think I
think it's already there and I'm like E
I don't believe it and and she's like no
let me check here they say um it has
been all set up and I'm like really I
have to see it with my own eyes
otherwise I will not believe it then I
came here and I walked in and first of
all
they booked a good place comfortable
place yeah yeah just a million dead
flies uh at the window but that's okay I
I vacuumed them
up they freaking what did I bring my
fatest 50% of the weight for the
suitcase is is made up by my fat ass
gaming laptop I swear it's so [\h__\h]
heavy it's so [\h__\h] heavy and the the
the the cable the loading cable is like
also the same weight as the laptop
pretty much
but if there's a freaking gaming PC here
I think it's a I don't know it might be
a normal PC I don't know but there's a
fat ass PC like on the ground a proper
Tower PC thingy and two monitors two
proper monitors they put two proper
monitors and I'm
like last time last time I think during
um during 3D WS of
myth um they also prepared a lot of
stuff right but I think we used just the
table a small table that was made
available from the the apartment that we
were living in so relatively small table
hard to squeeze all the things on there
that we needed uh but they actually put
an extra like a fat heavy steel gaming
PC here like they they must have like
unbuilt it and rebuilt it they must have
unbuilt it brought it here and built it
in here it's huge I have so much more
space like there's an extra desk from
the apartment but this is this is what
they brought and it's like a fat
ass gaming desk pretty much and a fat
ass gaming chair and and uh the fat ass
Yamaha ag8 that is pretty fat and
impressive uh a fat ass gaming keyboard
that lights up RGB and an RGB Mouse and
and a fat ass Elgato mic stand hello and
a a a nice Shore m that I requested
thank
God and and fat ass monitors fat ass PC
they even brought me game capture card
they brought me like everything the I
was most surprised about the the table
and the fact that there's a PC there and
I didn't have to bring my gaming laptop
I didn't request all of this they just
brought it here like
what so I was like so disc
combobulated and Bamboozled and so
perplexed and I needed a while to
register what was happening I laid down
on the bed I was like like assistant
manager was still there and I was like
what the [\h__\h] what I can't believe they
brought so much stuff what what
what what why is this here why is there
so much stuff here I so
discombobulated legit uh crazy crazy
crazy like I
I'm I'm I'm amazed okay because I don't
think they brought this much stuff
during our 3D debuts so I'm just
thinking to myself wow wow they are
making things you know better as I said
before I think in a different um
relation in a different context uh
things are improving and uh probably I'm
I'm guessing this is how this is how
Advent has been living
these past months with a nice setup but
yeah thank you stuff son I did not
expect there to be so much stuff they
even they even like cabled everything I
didn't have to do anything pretty much
except um figure out that the the USB
hub a fat ass USB hub that they put
there has buttons for each single USB
hub on there that I have to turn on in
order to the for the USB thingies to
work I didn't realize that um until a
little bit later uh but that's also
pretty fat
ass uh yeah like everything's there like
what I'm I'm I'm I'm
amazed an active power to use is that
what you call
that it's like toggle it's really it's
really thick it it's cable the cable is
confusing me why does a USB hub need to
be why why does the USB hub have one
power cable and a USB cable huh that
must be a fat ass I'm sorry I keep on
saying that everything's
F that must be a fat ass USB hub thingy
it has a power cable it has its own
power cable it's too strong to be only
lit up by the PC
power wowy tooy yeah it doesn't take
power from the
PC yeah no it really I really had to
process all of this and and yeah um they
prepared it nicely and now um I I think
I can stream comfortably for the coming
months I thought I had to get here and
and put my fat ass gaming laptop on the
tiny uh uh desk the single desk that is
in here um for lunch and dinner eating
purpose I thought I had to put it up
there put squeeze my portable second
monitor on there and everything else uh
the mixer the microphone etc for I had
to put everything else on there by
myself and hook it all up and it would
be really annoying but no everything's
already set up so I was like
motivated I was so
motivated who's G is responsible it's
the only appropriate word I can think of
right now to to describe the
immense um shock I have received through
this uh extra service
yeah this amazing but like I I I don't
know maybe it's because they had access
to it like several days before uh I saw
like a lot of I say the the BL is really
nice and and modern and comfortable and
all that but I saw like a [\h__\h] ton of
tiny ass mini mini mini mini mini
flies uh especially on the Windows sill
uh and here and there also in the shower
and all that so I was like what the [\h__\h]
and then I sent pictures of that um to
jenma and I asked her when when is the
last time this place was clean this this
everything's nice and all that but the
Flies are really weird yeah it's drain
flies she asked and uh was basically
told that they probably came from the
sewage and I should have the water
running for um like 15 minutes or so um
but they
Canan Ian staff can come by to clean
just like when last time when I had
issues like turning on the light or so
like apparently they just sent Ian staff
to clean um if we needed it and I said
no no no no no no no don't worry about
it I can clean it myself I was just
wondering like what's going on here why
are there so many dead flies at least
they're not alive at least they're not
alive um so I just vacuumed it all up
and now everything's fine
I don't I'm not going to waste their
time coming here of course not like
that's not their job their job isn't
cleaning uh like our
accommodations no it's not even interns
it's like managers last time last time
that was a manager who came to check my
my light and then switched it on and it
worked
immediately that's traumatizing I don't
even want to remember that
uh no I didn't ask for them to I said
nope okay that's fine um I'll do it
myself I just if anything I would have
maybe asked the the complex like
complex's cleaning staff but it's fine I
can do it myself I just wanted to know
why what happened maybe it hasn't been
cleaned for a month I don't
know so yeah uh wonderful setup I can
stream here uh for a long long time I
think um we'll have fun and we'll start
off with which which bring our which
bring
our
MTO is telling me about the the mixer um
why she has an extra one
I
can't what is this what is this
layout what is this keyboard layout I
can't type with
this oh okay okay okay okay oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay okay okay
[Applause]
okay sorry I had a little little shock
uh
um she's there W who who who who okay so
I guess let's play I I I I downloaded
the game and everything installed the
game I I set up steam and everything
beforehand uh I hope this works I I
already plugged in the
controller so I think this should
work let's
see grab a controller and kick back I
have one connected what are you talking
about
does it always say that even if you have
it
connected
oh it
works my comfort game is
back my comfort game is back
[Music]
it's not so loud over there right it's
not so loud for me
[Music]
either I'm in a good mood yeah I I I'm
surprised I was able to sleep at night
because I
um oh ah uh cuz I
slept uh like I came to Japan in the
morning and I didn't sleep too much in
the
airplane but I also watched four Vikings
Valhalla season 3 episodes that's nice
that was really good that's so good new
Season's so good new Season's so good
trust
me um but didn't sleep much there and
didn't sleep much in the night before I
took off uh at home uh so I was pretty
tired uh when I arrived in Japan and it
was the heat immediately struck me like
lightning
um but then uh you know the travel to
the uh apartment and like setting a few
things up and then I I went out to do
something uh just uh some getting some
stuff done immediately and that made me
feel wow I lo I lost all my energy and I
was like dying I I I swear I was like
so wow so dead so I hurried after I was
done I hurried back um
to did I eat yeah I ate a little thing
and then I slept and I slept so long I
took like a 6-h hour nap and I woke up I
I woke up at like I don't know like 8
something and I I woke up lightly and I
looked at the time I was like oh I
should probably wake up Clos his eyes
again sleeps for another 10 minutes
wakes up again and I'm like oh oh oh I
only fell asleep again for 10 more
minutes my my body is telling me to not
fall asleep again huh okay I should
totally wake up but eyes fall fall again
I fall asleep again I wake up again it's
only another 10 minutes pass so I'm like
oh oh my body is so amazing I thought I
thought I would sleep for another hour
if I closed my eyes again then I did
that again and again and again uh but
then I finally wake
up uh like maybe at
9 9:30 or so
yeah and I was like well now I'm
probably [\h__\h] now I can't sleep at
night but I was able to sleep at night
so I'm am well
rested and so so happy about the new
house of the Dragon episode that was so
good but I have an existential crisis
because next episode is the last one and
that means we have to wait like 2 years
for the next season which is insane
[Music]
I might die I don't know like 2 years is
like an
eternity man life's not fair why does it
take so long they're like they have they
they should be faster they have so much
money can't they do it faster can't they
do it
faster we met cool dragons yeah so many
new not really new dragons but can I say
one thing um I don't even know if this
is going to happen so it's not a spoiler
but I think I mean can we all uh agree
that uh what's her name Rea is probably
going to get sheep stealer right I mean
she's actively looking for it I would
say cuz she's like [\h__\h] that I want a
dragon I want the dragon and there's
sheep stealer obviously like somewhere
roaming around where she is at now she's
looking for it so I don't really know I
didn't read the book so I I don't really
know how
how Wild those wild dragons are um if if
they're like you know really usable and
rable and and if you can really command
them I wonder probably you can right is
this not a SP no no because I don't I'm
just saying I think she's going to go
get it I don't know yet because it
hasn't happened
yet I mean the the fact is a that it's
like eating sheep that just sounds like
a natural dragon thing to do I wouldn't
say that's like a problem
right I hope she gets it that would be
really cool if she shows up with this
wild dragon that nobody expects that she
could even get it and then yeah she's
going to be useful and
respected yeah it's probably just part
of a dragon's diet like I mean it's no
problem with eating some sheep right
it's a [\h__\h] Dragon what else is going
to eat
plants waffles I don't know no just got
to eat some sheep it's
understandable I might watch House of
the Dragon later down the road you
should it's really good this this season
is really good so far I'm just pissed
that it will take another two years for
the next one M there's a cannibal Dragon
ah yeah right who eats other cannibal
other dragon
yeah yeah I know it keeps on getting
mentioned there's like three wild
dragons that keep on getting mentioned
in the AL shift reviews Recaps of the
episodes so I'm very aware of them they
get like mentioned a million times by Al
shift uh there's threee uh the other one
was uh what was the other one
again yeah I know there's a lot of shows
who are you know in hibernation but I I
don't I can't
wait I
can't none of this has been said in the
show what do you mean what what what do
you mean it's obvious that she's going
for it they already no they already
mentioned the Sheep stealer
uh they meent they mentioned they
already mentioned that there's a dragon
like there and she's like what the [\h__\h]
and and and and it's obviously eating
sheep they already talked about it we
don't know the name well well maybe you
should be watching all [\h__\h] reviews or
read the books then it's not a spoiler
no no no no no the the the fact that
dragons exist in a show called House of
the Dragon is not a
spoiler get the hell out of here get the
hell out of
here W there's houses in the house of
the Dragon what there's houses Mama Mia
the shook
the shook that you gave me with that
fact houses and
Dragons what people too well people
would really be a spoiler because that
that's not in the name that's not in the
title of the show what how would we know
that there's people we only know there's
houses and
[Laughter]
dragons dragons in my dragon show what
what
oh by the way in the airplane I watched
uh I did I did I I was like I was going
for the movies because my both my uh I I
I watched all the episodes that I
downloaded from Vikings Valhalla and I
was like wow I I still have so many
hours on this [\h__\h] plane so I
watched um was it uh Fantastic Beasts
third
movie I thought I already watched that I
was like so unsure I I watched the
trailers of each movie and I was
like I definitely watched the second one
but even though I watched it the trailer
footage uh looks unfamiliar to me but I
definitely watched it so I watched the
third one and yeah there's a third one
you guys are surprised about it too it
was it was good I liked it it was a good
entertainment on the
airplane is bad bad m
M I guess I can see maybe I have to say
though for watching on the airplane it
was really good like I was uh happy to
watch
something uh
decent on the airplane I don't like it m
I liked it I enjoyed it okay yeah me too
honestly I
mean I think I was kind of annoyed uh uh
by uh the fact that that okay some of
the story some of the plot is
maybe me and why the [\h__\h] does he
survive in the
end just building up for another movie I
guess I don't know but it was still very
good for watching something on the
airplane um spoiler well I didn't say
who I didn't say who many people
survived
yeah people survive when they
live let's play I attenting too much
already we're so back we're so back
we're still back let's do training cuz I
have one point
um what should we do I don't know which
one maybe this
one let's run
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay let's go let's go let's go let's go
run run run run run run run
run
no I still counted as a success though I
think she didn't trip
completely a
[\h__\h]
nah okay no
extra oh bubble get success bonus 20%
that's that's fine
wow oh physical training stage free
let's go how come our physical training
is bigger than mental training actually
we're focusing on Magic okay overload
strike too momentarily overloads the
body's abilities in order to deliver a
fierce blow a powerful shock wave is
generated at the point of impact skills
will consume high amounts of HP increase
okay
uh yeah we don't use that that much
quadruple swing oh
oh cool we have we had the swing then we
had the double swing then we had the
triple swing and now we have quadruple
spr spring Swing Swing how far can we go
H okay we're pretty F in the story um
today might be the second to last uh
episode of this game I really really
like could you could try swords for a
bit H I do have a good sword to use if I
wanted to do that but I just feel like I
generally haven't skilled into it but
apparently I have been like lowkey
Skilling into
[Music]
it same bro
same can you move your yeah I guess I'm
not in the in a good position maybe my
staff is also too big well yeah I was
usually here let's go here
okay we slept and now uh we have to go
to death squads lir to receive red
Beard's
package okay what was what was that
about again what
[Music]
package I am in a good mood wow I'm in a
good
mood let's
[Music]
go I'm glowing you
too the scarf so you can ah scarf yeah
cuz one scarf around my neck will fix
the immense overwhelming
cold that would await me
there intruders
okay an intruder has appeared at the
death score layer I should get the
details from
Lena
okay who could it be random people or
someone
important what's going on
hello oh
[Music]
for the
wow thanks for the Super Chat
wait wait wait what if if the if the
guard who saw the Intruder got knocked
out how do we know that there's one if
there's only
one and we don't know the identity
because the guard was knocked out how do
we know that there was one in the first
place
HHH cuz he woke up then then he would
tell them what their identity is it see
like by that phrasing it seems like he's
still knocked
out
okay you wishless of this go go buy it
go pay it what go play
it makeing rid of this pillow my chair
leave it to
me searching for the Intruder there's
only one Intruder I'm guessing it's a
Royal Palace Warrior but why didn't he
fle flee when he was spotted let's find
the
Intruder where is
he somewhere in here
[Music]
right this place is not that big it
can't be so hard to find ah
is it that uh
executor wait it's happening right there
how can they not look around the corner
and be like ah yeah the Intruder is an
Executor she's standing right
there why are they like it's such a
mystery
huh
W yeah they would literally hear the
fighting that's going on between them
having time to think about the
opponent's next
move and talk to yourself about your
plan how to counter it mm
mhm he's such a
protagonist hello welcome to the stream
K you're
late animy B
round uh only a quarter of a second pass
mhm probably that's what it seems
[Music]
like oh she lost her ah n n what's so
surprising about that what does her face
look like why is it so
what okay I mean I didn't recognize her
but
how did they wait how did they recognize
her in this form when nobody [\h__\h]
recognizes me just by growing up when
I'm still wearing basically the same
clothes I did not recognize liia just
now that was actually not recognizable
to
me are you kidding
me the absolute uh what's the double
standards
of this
[Laughter]
game liia wait but I thought only
witches can turn into
executors I don't think she's a
witch game audio low oh right I can
raise it like this for now and then I
can raise it more when I'm out of this
menu
H pieber is a master of
thegu cran I was so
fooled the exposer to dark
magic yeah but but Vin did not become
a executor just by that I thought you
have to be transformed into one by the
pope
weird and only witches become executor
still as far as I
know he was the Prototype yeah but the
Prototype of an
Executor whatever whatever
[Music]
20,000
20,000 that's nothing and we even have
no he's not fighting he's just standing
there bro what happened you were just
finding a moment ago what happened to
your
[Music]
motivation M Mia everybody just gives up
immediately it's a
shame Yum Yum
Yum the ab defense is already but she
seems pretty weak I don't know if it's
even if if we even need to turn it on
want to try the quadruple
swing yeah why
not oh without a sword
2,300
wow but now we have a
[Music]
easy I'm not even thinking I'm just
doing
things so easy cross yeah yeah yeah not
bad oh
critical I thank you for this beautiful
helmet Yum Yum
Yum by the way my flight was pretty unev
ful but I tried really hard to get an
upgrade I really wanted to buy another
upgrade cuz the flight right I didn't
pay for the flight so and it was premium
economy so I really wanted an upgrade
because I I'm pain in my body and I
can't sleep
upright but it was fall and they just
wouldn't let me buy anything man okay
you don't get my money then oh God
oh maybe on my way
back y
that was a critical and suddenly was
less oh because maybe that's that was
all the HP she had left actually liia
come on
live on
liia how long was the flight long very
long uh 12
[Music]
hours chicken I like that I like I like
the executor's
[Music]
[Laughter]
designs a hug will
do just hug her it fixes
everything our item earring you mean the
dark magic earring I don't think so it's
too late for that to
help I think you have to put that on
[Music]
before byebye
Olia yeah fashion fashion F
fashion
[Music]
fashion Justice somehow like
automatically naturally joined us and is
on our side now he ran desperately
toward the Pope's Castle Olivia has had
it it disappeared
inside
[Music]
oh he's acting like a protagonist bro
I'm the
protagonist he wants to steal my my
whole purpose
[Music]
he's he's hijacking
everything hijack
jce
[Music]
where's
[\h__\h]
foreign fore
[Music]
fore oh thanks for the
pinky his name
is you're so sweet to your friend
damn getting getting your friend a Super
Chat
greeting
Mikey Happy Birthday
Mikey Sun M
congratulations happy birthday to you
happy birthday to you happy
birthday thank you for the support enjoy
your birthday and celebrate
[Music]
yourself oh she's she acts like that but
she likes it she likes being captured by
her
[Music]
Crush oh
let's go can we fight it can we fight it
I want to fight it let me fight it
please give it 200k
[Music]
HP but there's only like one
left
true all right there's two
lives one's behind him oh
Don't Let Go
Justice oh you can let Let Her Go
actually we have a bird that picks us up
if we need
to this is so
romantic oh he's [\h__\h] now he's so
[\h__\h]
wow oh oh oh oh ow oh oh oh nice nice
nice nice
nice there we are we're back
again you must be so discombobulated
[Music]
now she's so cute
[Applause]
iene p and Justice escaped safely with
the help of the death
squad
yippi we're thinking with portals now
she's playing Portal while we're playing
wi spring r
[Music]
and play which
we can fix
[Music]
her nah she's
fine she got plot
[Music]
armor no oh now he
like that's the point where he's like ah
[\h__\h] the Pope
[Music]
oh yeah it's it's new really new nice
fancy plock
[Music]
armor told you so
spee foreign
[Music]
the void in his heart he's such an emo
boy
[Music]
both Pope and Pie star with
P really makes you
think pie maybe was a metaphor for the
pulp all along and Pie is poisoning us
all just like the pulp and Pie is evil
[Music]
the real Pope is a pie we ate along the
way he's actually a baker he's making
the pie and he's scattering that's why
all the guards have the
pie oh why just stop oh wait why is it
not charging it's not
charging ah no wait why
not my my phone
charger it's connected
though it's turned on
[Music]
it was it was just Loosely connected I
think is is it
now okay and now it's charging hope it
can catch
[Music]
up what did I wake up to a waa stream
good morning sunshine I used I used
surpris but I had the stream reservation
up for a while you should have known you
should have known you should have been
the
[Music]
where yeah why were you absent again
where do you go all the
time yeah we're pretty amazing
let's
go yeah by the way just because I'm
streaming at at this time now it doesn't
mean that all the streams will be at the
time
actually I think the rest of the streams
for this
week will be evening jst
[Music]
like s or 800 P.M
let's go what about my scarf
though what about my
scarf seven seven
[Music]
orm this a good PST time well if only if
this is a short stream but it's
not cuz started at 10 p.m. PST
right it's going to go on past midnight
and EST is already past midnight so I
know it's a shitty time for you guys
[Music]
so h a 900 p.m. PD
hey it seems like he's part of us
now more opportunities for those two
to have some moments
together what did you just
say for his own purposes okay
[Music]
oh so he's just leaking all the info to
us that's that's your way of helping
us Justice for
[Music]
okay okay J
BL
stop stop making him like boost his e go
even
more yeah to
MC she thinks she's so
[Music]
cool let's go righta bring him back to
Earth
where is she going phasing
through dur
tur the tur
Temple let's go scorf es scar said to
have been used by an ice switch in the
past it tricks the magic of arys to
protect the wear from the extreme cold
of the snow
F
dinosaurs
yes oh he what the [\h__\h] is she doing I
didn't notice she
was she's tracking him or
what
cute cute
oh damn
useful she just does whatever she wants
with
[Music]
him I don't know
how did you guys watch
morning show was I
featured I think I was featured yeah
yeah yeah I was on the
news I was on the news
yipp I'm famous I'm famous now
like I always oh yeah I saw that too M
Channel I was also featured oh my God so
embarrassing like coo show okay because
I I I'm already used to being featured
for scandalous things
on uh on on coyo show But Me Senpai I
don't think did she feature Me Maybe
slightly but yeah m
M um H cing I'm so
embarrassed your boo was a nice
distraction from all the arc stuff yeah
yeah yeah little bit of a different
flavor thrown in there we like it we
like
it hot
[Laughter]
to I did bring my whole uh xense setup
my motion capture setup by the way cuz I
didn't want to wait until like all the
way in September when I'm home to record
things I thought there were there might
be some things that I want to record so
I hope it works I have I think
everything that I
need yeah I hope I can make it work
because uh it always needs like the
license there's like a a USB stick that
carries the license basically and
another sticky thing I don't know what
that does there's like two things that
make it actually work so I think I got
it
all brought the gloves too and the the
base for the gloves basically to react
to it on the PC yeah yeah yeah what do
you mean the suitcase it's already here
I don't think it would get lost it's
fine cuz normally that only really
happens for like connection
flights I think or with really shitty
Airlines
yeah maybe we can do that 3D K this
month then
um I don't know if I would do that here
I don't know but I wanted to do some
shorts yeah physical license key
basically so what happens if you lose
that I guess they can send you a new
one yay 46 mons thank
you wow
yeah yeah yeah yeah in Fury I could also
land it to anybody who's here wants to
try it out but they they don't they
don't ask me so I don't do it
but I I'm going to hopefully record some
shorts uh when I got some
[Music]
time did you wash it no I need to wash
the shirt yeah cuz it's still sweaty
from the last time I wore it which
wasn't long time ago so I didn't have
time to wash it yet yet and I forgot
about it I need to wash it
no they did lose my suitcase because of
connecting flight yeah yeah yeah it's
usually just with connecting flights but
even then even I had I I uh I have a lot
of uh flights with connection
connections too um but I don't know last
time my uh luggage was lost
was M I think only when I traveled with
my family with my mom many many years
ago as a young young teenager SL child
uh because we used cheap ass shitty
Airlines and
connections and I think it was more
common back then even yeah long time
ago you became the
conservation conversation started when I
was boofing and had several randos at
least asking if I saw you Freddy H
recently and we bonded over it you
bonded over my ass over my fat
ass let's
go hope everything goes well while
you're in Japan uh it's actually
surprising that I'm in a good mood
because when I was on the airplane I was
kind of
like dreading everything and I was like
I don't want to [\h__\h] travel anymore I
hate this this is exhausting I just want
to be home with my cats
you know I wasn't was
not I was not having it I was getting
like I was looking out the window I was
like oh my ha I love this so much I
don't want to anymore cuz I've been I've
been out and about so much like
okay uh I when when did this start like
in June I think first I went
to Germany then I flew back to Austria
then I flew to uh Japan then I flew back
to Austria then I flew to Italy then I
flew back to Austria then I flew uh here
to Japan again and in between I always
only had a few days at a time back at
home sometimes 2 days sometimes 3 days
sometimes 4 days but basically I never
really had much time to recharge and and
just go uh about and have a normal
schedule these past weeks and I I I I
saw this schedule ahead of time before
it all started and I was like already
dreading
it at least one of those was a vacation
yeah but it wasn't really
relaxing uh but yeah sure that was a
little bit of a a a good one I guess but
yeah now now this trip and then you know
uh Ian concert and all that uh is also
coming up this trip is very uh a a lot
of stuff and then after this trip I'm
going back to Austria but then I'm
flying somewhere for a short amount of
time
with uh as I think I told you before
with an Ian member
um because things lined up that
way uh I think I'm back home maybe for a
few days and then I'm flying away for
for you know short time but uh then by I
think the middle of September I should
be finally really
back yeah so all of this is
really getting to me but right now I
feel really good I'm fine I settled down
I think it's it helps that everything
was already set up and comfortable so
now I feel I feel fine I just I think I
need to stay inside because the heat
outside is [\h__\h] and it's it's not
good for my physical health so I'm just
going to try to stay inside as much as I
can then I'll be fine and not think
about my
cats some days in between can give some
rest yeah hopefully um
yeah I'll I'll rest in between the
streams and all the the work I have to
do I'll be fine let's
chill H can temperature outside is too
hot yeah it's really really really bad
like the moment I step
outside it's so weird because like the
AC you know inside and then you step
outside and it hits you even harder like
it's like the air is hugging you and
choking
you I mean I this is not new to me I've
lived in Japan before and I spent many
Summers
here it's not new to me but it just
sucks it doesn't get
better yeah the humidity is really bad
that's what makes it feel like the the
air is hugging you that's what makes the
air feel so
heavy you know I hate it I hate it
[Music]
in Japan
arcs so far so far the sweat has been in
control somewhat I just I just can't
function
outside
M yeah it subjects me to different
weathers that's true too mhm
H how's the weather in New York I
wonder is it is it
humid I can't imagine it being
humid tell
me very
no
no let me look it
up
so uh Tokyo weather right
now rain I don't see any
rain
uh okay I don't know it I guess uh
because of the rain I don't know 30
[Music]
37 with humidity
61% some oh tomorrow
68% it's surprising less humid when it
rains is that a thing wouldn't it be
more
humid anyway and then New
York
okay
wa what
humidity
75 63
68 and today
or during this night right now
what the temperatures are a little bit
lower generally like four to 5 deg three
3 to 5 degrees lower and more shitty
weather and rain and thunderstorms as I
can tell a lot of a lot of rain and
thunderstorms in New York this
week but what's with this humidity in
New York what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
[Laughter]
H cuz it's Coastal
a
wow near a body of water what is near
near Kobo
[Music]
okay focus
guys we gave him a magic sword why did
we do
[Music]
that can she teach me how to do that I
want my sword to be on
Flames no sound board no I am the
soundboard
[Music]
did you guys hear the sounds in the
spelling be like the there was some
cheering and
some and
some that that was
me that was me adding some uh sound
effects you're welcome I was helping
them out they didn't know I don't think
they knew where it came from
well maybe I will
wait why does her voice sound so high
again did she revert back to child
mode or is it just me and it was much
higher as a
child she sounds higher than I don't
know she sounds like her child self
again a voice for cry
Crush
ah I can put Justice in my own ew no
ew cuz she's in a good mood ah
okay I finally have a way to get into
the snowfield time to equip the ice
switch scarf hey is that oh wait is that
a special item slot thingy finally or
oopsie it is that's what goes there wait
I have four slots and we're at the end
of the game and I I finally got one item
did I miss anything like somehow that I
could have gotten
before
H she looks much more mature in the art
yeah
true uh
snowfield can I teleport from
here m
where are
we can I I guess we can go
here you can get free at most on first
run
oh so this is normal that I didn't find
the others
[Music]
yet yeah they made a lot of pberry art a
lot of art for
the um for all the dialogues and also
with all the different
outfits that she
has so big respect for
[Music]
that kill some
BS let's
[Music]
go I watched this new video from uh
what's his name again the British
guy who does silly things
um he did a
uh a hot dog eating challenge with G
wild grizzly not Grizzly uh uh wild B
bear bear yeah Max
F it's weird watching my stream this
time
right yeah his new video is with a big
ass bear and he looks so
cute he looks so cute the bear is so
fluffy and big and he he he had he was
so he had such good manners he ate the
hot dogs next to those people and then
after he was done eating his
stack after he was done eating a stack
of hot dogs he he didn't go over to the
humans and eat their hot dogs or the
humans no he just left in so such good
manners maybe maybe British no he's not
British I think the bear is from America
he a good
bear good bear just ate the the hot dogs
and then he left no he didn't eat the
humans no he
didn't otherwise the video wouldn't
exist
probably such a good bear apparently
it's a rescued bear and um he's sweet he
has this whole land to him he's he's
been taken care of and he was in a few
movies apparently it's a famous bear
good bear the bear would upload the
video
bear trying to start his own YouTube
career he could he
could
yeah be
propaganda because I talk about my
crossover no no no no no I'm not raising
my voice I'm I'm making it sound like
baby because cute animal this is my
talking to animals voice
so
what cute bear Friend
[Music]
Bear yeah look at me I got my
scarf nny what do you want
strawberries in a [\h__\h] ice field
where I can't
survive how would strawberry survive I
just realized I actually realized this
yesterday um I told you there's some
more strawberries growing in my in my
garden
[Laughter]
right they were still green when I left
them but I they looked like they were
going to be red and edible while I'm
gone I'm so sad I'm not even going to be
able to eat them
myself also I only ate like half of the
Cucumber or like a third of
it uh cuz it was really big and I
deleted the Tweet because I really had
no weird intentions the thing is I was
cooking um some noodles for my tuna
sauce and I I made a salad of the
cucumber and so I had noodles there and
a cucumber and I wanted to show off the
Cucumber before I eat it and so I wanted
to compare it to something and one of
the closest things that would be a good
comparison that I had close to me was
the noodle so I put it there but then
afterwards you guys were a lot of people
were like giving a lot of like weird um
comments and and I was like no that's
not what I was trying to imply with this
at all but now that you guys are saying
it I mean I see it too but that's that's
not what I wanted and so many people
were saying saying it and I mean okay a
few ones is okay but like everybody was
saying it and then I was like no you you
ruined my
cucumber yeah even keie but I don't
think she was saying anything weird
though if I remember
correctly
man the Tweet was up for a while though
not my fault that you missed
it and a
gy it was a griffy c cber do it's
true but I realized what I did and I
deleted because I don't I don't want to
be I'm telling you guys I'm really
actually so prude you know you should
know it by now only like people think
I'm like this and that right but my my
my real viewers my real
kpers they know I'm I'm I'm not like
that
and even if every once in a while I'll
throw out a joke like that maybe but I I
don't that's not really like who I
am it's just me trying to be funny
sometimes but you know I'm not
really I stopped saying Cave of people
now you're Cave of peelers oh speaking
of peeling I really should have peeled
the
Cucumber I've never had a cucumber like
that before like I made it into a salad
so like I I I I I sliced it up and all
that but
after when I was eating it I realized
the the peel is
really thick and like very noticeable
unlike with normal
cucumbers and it looked so different
from the inside
too and the the seeds were so thick like
it almost seemed like like watermelon
seeds incredible
what a garden grown cucumber can
do and it was really light colored and
smooth
inside M it looks so different from a
normal
cucumber yeah you get that with big
cucumbers the the peel yeah yeah yeah
yeah very very noticeable thick peel but
it was interesting also when it when it
when it grows when it's a baby cucumber
it has like so many um pointy bingies
like a like a like a
Sanic uh on top of it so when you touch
it it it really hurts but then it goes
away when it's finished
growing close to real cucumber not
industrial product yeah yeah yeah make a
nice satii yeah oh could have done that
but I really tried to eat as much as I
could before I left so that I got
something out of
it yeah but I couldn't eat at all it's a
huge
cucumber yeah little
horns at least we know you have some
good so for growing more it's it's
interesting though because I I haven't
been um what's the
word uh adding like the the grow
thingies at all I really should but I
keep on forgetting about
it haven't added it a single time yeah
fertilizer I really should be adding
fertilizer to everything but I haven't
added in a single time
[Music]
oopsie has
it is she implying he he's slacking off
and he shouldn't get promoted eh what do
you know about him pberry
is he
sus I don't remember our last
conversation but I don't know he's sus
isn't
he I don't
know oh but she she agrees well I am
pberry same thought at the same time
the characters with who don't have light
in their eyes they're always like
there's something up with them they're
so
less
obviously it's one of the ways they show
that the character is so less or
controlled or
something with this this kind of arch
style
yeah what my forehead
[Music]
I don't have a forehead it doesn't
exist no we should give him his own scar
we should wrap him up like a
mommy beute
let's go find some
dinosaurs okay new enemies let's go wait
they have little little little snowman
on top of their
heads
cute
6,400 element ice oh you would like my
[Music]
fire
um this one's Fire have I haven't been
using it at all because it's I think
it's
weak and this one's what you can
actually summon him as a b oh my God
that
okay he's her pet
now
wow let's just summon this one explosive
is basically fire I don't know if the
game sees it like that but
[Music]
wow
5,200 per per Yeti ow ow ow ow ow ow
ow this game really is St on
ska actually true she's a witch she gave
him a
sword she's into
him H yeah you're
[Music]
right
damn turn bonus we w we
W I guess I'll eat some pie
probably yeah
[Music]
Louis was very rude yeah true she's not
really
[Music]
rude and she's not
asnd not tnd at all
really but you know there's some
connection there that I can see
yay little snowman I don't know if
they're controlling them I wouldn't
assume so automatically we will never
know
[Music]
probably oh they slow my agility when
they hit me
[Music]
oh he gets two
hits what he has [\h__\h] AOE attack
let's go he's
good he's
good there's somewhere like Shion and
Alin also true she puts the fire on his
sword
true glittering
ice
nice true but I I mean besides that I
think think they're very different
because of their
personalities but yeah the the system is
similar
[Music]
indeed let's try this one it's not fire
but at least it hits
[Applause]
both wait he had zero summon cost oh I
didn't realize
oh well I guess cuz he's a human and not
like a typical pet but uh actually where
is the difference oh look at that that's
a a dark magic infused Yeti down there
but we're going to go elsewhere first
cuz didn't activate the teleportation
[Music]
thingy and I want to fight more
more yeah what
jti what I'm saying
Yeti yei how do you say
[Music]
it good
morning if you just woke
up so wait then I can have a lot of
stuff out here
actually I even have still two points
left left I can put a a fourth one out
here one of the cheaper ones this one's
cheap
yo that's
[Music]
op I was saying it right
good
[Music]
a holy
moly and so full
party let's go let's go let's go let's
[Music]
go um wait actually maybe I need the dry
pies to craft something I forgot if that
was necessary
[Music]
we still have some
lto might as well use
it wow let's go
[Music]
I might
say that Amma is my Oshi yes that's all
I'll say to
that is my oi
[Music]
I love
her ow ow ow ow ow ow ow ow ow
[Music]
ow wait somebody said are you guys
joking somebody said I didn't expect
that and another one I didn't see that
coming you that's said J
[Music]
oo look at
that oh that was a waste oh oh oh not
quite AE let's
go
Swing Swing Swing Swing my bab
j
y j y you don't get it unless you're
into K-pop and all that you w't
understand this
meme J1
P
always always oh her house wait where do
I go that first then if
this this is her house and down there I
saw a dark magic
dude it's because like okay so I don't
know it's going to be a long that's a
temple isn't it it's going to be a long
explanation
man he's the okay yes Adam song is uh
really good like it like
it
eh
um I don't even I don't know if I even
want
to he's got some Shenanigans yeah like
okay he's a producer he's a c producer
he owns his company one of the most
successful K-pop labels in Korea and he
he himself still makes music he's kind
of comparable with Tusan from
Japan
um and I don't know where to how to
uh so he's like he's relatively old now
but he still does some music and he will
like the idols that he hires often he
will make them perform with him in his
concerts as like kind of like side
dancers and
singers and
um he also like does like this these
Idol survival shows and all that he's in
his 50s yeah I will say he's still uh
good at stuff like he's obviously still
a good singer and good dancer but people
like to joke
about
him because like he over
sings and I don't know it's like you
know Dad energy like when he performs
with these younger other idols and and I
don't know you got to you got to get
into it uh to understand and into every
song he produces he puts in the JY jyp
um but also uh yeah I know it's funny
it's funny you got to get into it and
watch those clips and all that to
understand would you like to help the
stranded human Expedition team oh
sure they're dressed like they're about
to
uh
join what was it Aqua gate
[Music]
they look like Ocean Gate they sound
like they're about to go aboard the
Ocean
Gate oh my God Ocean Gate
[Music]
reference who would have expected
that wait this one probably doesn't have
ice weakness does he I don't know I'll
summon
whatever 47,000 ooh spicy spicy I like
it oh ins ah yeah it doesn't have
two don't care
whatever okay now I expected something
hard
hitting a you guys saw the load of the
Rings
musical some of you guys guys was that
the first uh like the opening day or or
was it just has it been on for a
[Music]
while I saw like it looks like it's
basically like the same style of set but
just bigger like the venue looks bigger
I was way more cramped when I watched it
in
England I haven't been to a musical in
years got to hang out with some really
cool kfp nice you're welcome I'm sure it
was great yeah they seem to I read some
reviews from you guys they seem to have
kept the the spirit of it and and not
the same actors uh but pretty much like
very similar the only thing I've noticed
from what you guys wrote about it like
there are some of them play uh
instruments but not all of them huh in
the England version everybody was
playing instruments all the time
everybody had some fancy instrument to
play doesn't seem doesn't seem like it
was like that much but they also made
some improvements apparently to the
England version like making the the
sword glow and
stuff they yeah I improved on it that's
good that's nice sounds fun if any
anybody else in America is interested in
watching The Lord of the Rings Musical
that I've been talking about previously
uh it's now in America which in which
city which city is that why are they
doing that and people say yeah so many
people went to it by now for
me even in
[Music]
England
Chicago wait there's a l of drinks
musical yeah yeah yeah it's really good
I I watched it last year last year's
summer went to England for it it was
kind of like uh on the countryside in a
small theater but really lovely really
nice
M and um now because it was so
successful they brought it to America in
Chicago best advertisement ever got was
you I bet I would think so
yeah I would assume
[Music]
so don't hit the people in the back
there good good good
[Music]
yeah it was hard to get to in the
UK was like it's in the middle of
nowhere had to take a long ass
train from London and then a bus and
then walk through nothingness if you had
a car it would be no
issue let's do the quadruple swing
H
4,600 bro maybe it's time for me to put
out the sword instead of the
staff
[Music]
sheesh
nice almost 50k mob killed with
[Music]
ease you're welcome they look
funny let's get out of here
bye-bye you're I was about to say like
reward doco H if you want a reward ask
Red Beard for it you know Red Beard
we're his personal Expedition team we're
on our way home from harvesting
glittering I but how are you not frozen
oh they're dressed up way more than we
are I should ask I should actually same
of you a dress like that oh well you
have the ice wi scarf we used to you so
you'll be fine but we've been harvesting
glittering eyes for years without it
maybe it's because you're dressed so
thickly our Expedition cloes are
especially designed to water of magical
chills down this it doesn't allow us to
move as freely as you do anyway we'll be
seeing you until the bus you helped us
thank you bye I like their
goggles they look like those kind of
glasses that are so thick that it makes
your eyes really
big cute
okay now we did that that's a little
side thing I do Wonder actually since we
can teleport here I think I'll go
straight to Red
Beard I want my reward and then we'll go
back otherwise we'll forget about it
probably reward oh they're back there
they they were fast they can teleport
too or
what
I I know
well you're looking very a re word come
on don't be so ungrateful I never asked
you to save them you didn't oh [\h__\h]
you oh give it this useless trinket oh
it's probably going to be
useful what key to the cave oh looks
fancy I thought it was a weapon sealed
by luden's pet an ice key the key to the
cave where lud's pet is imprisoned that
animal may be of use to you even though
I said it's a useless key you'll find
the cave somewhere in the snowfield
ah is that the the door that I found and
not the uh Temple then if you were going
to thank me anyway why bother with all
that
earlier is that anything about a thanks
blah blah blah what I'm sure there's
plenty of high quality glittering ice in
there especially if it's a cave capable
of sealing wa who what what does the
glittering ice even do I didn't look at
the stuff
yet you know what I'm going to do now
you know what I'm going to do yeah I'm
going to go with a [\h__\h] sword
[Music]
H 90% for
40 yeah let's go with this one I think
that's one one of her best
swords oh my God she did it oh no she
didn't oh yes I did what do you want
Again by the
way Lightning Dragon horn oh yeah we
don't know that where that one is yet
that emoji is cute
emote during combat I don't think I can
switch
no
um for
Glory wait there's something
there
ah the music here is
nice let's test out the sword shall we
yeah now we're both sworting
together for
justice oh wait I would want to do
probably physical attack I mean I don't
have to right
[Music]
but actually that kind of sucks I could
have done AOE and much more
damage
instead um maybe it's not so good
actually I'm already
[Music]
disappointed it's only good for single
Target Maybe
[Music]
no but you say i i i i al I also think I
put so much in Magic but then our
physical is higher level than our magic
stuff mental stuff really makes you
think really makes you
think see at least this is this is a
good turn
[Music]
oh critical that that was good I kill
one I get a a
double that that was good
oh okay we didn't notice that last time
we passed
here a hole in the ceiling at the end of
that cave that leads to dark Temple
okay oh wait we didn't go here did
we just saw it from afar this
one wait do you guys oh you don't see
it behind chat here you see that little
bird up there is that another weird
version of our black
Joe with bunny ears and bat uh wings and
I don't know a a snowy face
oh it look it looks like the body shape
is the
same no you're going to poison
her no more pie Berry you're going to be
poison Berry
but I wonder how she
lives are we going to go in and be like
girl you live like that
Oh What A
buildup let's go that's a cute ass house
though are all witch's houses so cute oh
hello wait what thought that was her oh
she's there oh that's her
bird it is a
bed but is definitely meant to look
similar to Black Joel look at him he
looks funny
a she's so cute I don't think we've seen
that pouting face
before stop
girl man what's wrong with
her I can fix her okay single Target
6,000 only
girl
what
what I mean I won't even need all of
[Music]
this fixing
time who what's that
shield
cool won't help you much though
I got you
[Music]
cornered 40% I kind of want to see what
it
does 40% of
HP oh that's not so good but okay we
killed
her where were you when cute witch was
killed I was in front of her
house my pet dragon doesn't have the 20%
from feeding it oh did I not did I not
feed it oh I'm going to check it
out well it's cuz I got a
scarf join join us join the death squad
come on
girl
no why why do they hurt you and why is
that bat so cute and fluffy and friend
shame
love the
door so round just like our friendship
shaped
pets yeah let's force ourselves and
intrude her
home let's annoy the [\h__\h] out of her
when she wants privacy privacy what's
that I'm going to eat the Privacy up you
don't deserve privacy
Robin has gathered some fresh
strawberries for Luna Luna is but Robin
she just mentioned that Robin has
betrayed her girl maybe don't give her
the
strawberries wait are we [\h__\h] stupid
if we give that to
herock knock knock knock knock knock I'm
Gandalf she's she's a little bit bbing
right
[Music]
now maybe he maybe they're they're fine
and it's his apology and there was a
misunderstanding cuz if she would eat
them then
whatever happened between them is
probably not as bad as that she would
think he might poison her seem's like I
have a thing for pie and she has a thing
for strawberries witches seem to always
have one thing that gets
them no is she crying is she crying
[\h__\h]
[Music]
stuck don't make fun of
her yeah no but she lives in the
freaking snowfield where there's
literally no food of course she's got to
be happy about strawberries don't don't
Jou her
her eyes are moist I'd be more concerned
about those weird strapes on her face
what is that can we wipe that
away I'm I'm just making a joke about
anime
effects didn't come across so well
[Music]
they're both
kute are we not being oh okay girl you
live like
this wait she has a white bat up
there oh no it's still the same is it it
looks wider than
before wow in the most positive sense
girl you live like
[Music]
this I like it huge book man what the
hell is bigger than
[Music]
her same
age could she have a
sister ah
oh
oh oh okay we're not the same
[Music]
age yeah yeah yeah that is true I can
confirm cuteness I am a cute con
[Music]
that word by the way I knew already
before the the spelling be did not teach
me that
[Music]
you want to join me and help me cuz
you're worried or so H cuz you like me
now
H yeah that's what I'm going to do don't
you want to join me you also hate the
pope don't
[Music]
you death squad sounds interesting right
you seem like the kind of person who
likes death
[Music]
doesn't never sound good to you
H yeah true have to do something have to
try you'll either die trying or survive
trying or or die not trying what's the
best option here
[Music]
huh wa ice magic let's go well thank you
that's for someone who has been pushing
me away so much suddenly a huge
gift what fore
[Music]
101 wait so you telling me to use ice
magic against an ice giant why would I
not just use Fire
[Music]
magic yeah
so you are saying to use Fire
magic uh uh but first I need to learn
how ice magic works but I'm not going to
end up using it against the ice M okay
[Music]
classic
yeah
yeah predictable
script angrily sips
[Music]
tea maybe we should we should put it in
a kfp ferace and bring it to her
maybe that's what you should do
girl the path to the dark Temple is
guarded by an ice giant it's hard to
melt the ice without fully understanding
ice magic I should take a look at the
magic book that Luna gave
me all right so we're going to go back
once and learn that
[Music]
yippee basimo of course you hate it
you're literally a cup a a cup of coffee
coffee coffee cup of
coffee
[Music]
um two training
sessions I don't know I think I'm going
to go back to the staff so we don't have
to practice
uh
[Music]
anything I mean nothing
physical I
know let's just do this one as always
and um this
one oh that's it I thought that was a
third one oh I have a
third wait I thought I had three free
points mental physical
passion stage free
[Music]
baby a little bit of that spice oh close
and and a little bit of this and
that um maybe
perhaps oh bucket of salt
W didn't expect the
triple
sheesh oh 40%
extra let's
go let's [\h__\h] go
e okay where's the the ice magic
here aha okay we
can we can make this one at
[Music]
least
and
[Music]
yeah wow that was easy time to defeat
the ice walking away uh to dur I is
located could I have done it without
doing this at all or would did would he
not have spawned at all I wonder could I
make this
yet if I make can I make these other
[Music]
materials probably
not I would have not been able to fight
it at
[Music]
all it's
me you can find other materials in the
ice cave okay okay maybe next time
then um so I'm going to I
guess switch out this
one for the ice
one I can still put keep these ones in
that's
good okay now we have some ice attack
instead of two fire
attacks going to switch weapon again
though no not this one that one my epic
strong staff let's
go think we want to switch out for the
game
[Music]
maybe maybe this one look so nice in the
art yeah I like
it
um maybe sleep
[Applause]
once thank you
yeah the different outfits some of them
some of them are
DLC thanks for the membership gift and
another one thank you both of
you let's
go let's see what we'll
find
M where there's there's two things we're
looking for but we're looking for the
temple and we're looking for that secret
cave
so oh no whichever we'll find first is
this the temple or the cave this
door oh can't go
in oh wait it looks like it looks the
circle it looks like it looks like a
streaming streamer like
webcam window thing you know what I mean
I don't
know looks I'm like I'm inside of it
almost it's perfectly surrounding
me I need to use a key no there was no
prompt
even there was no prompt it's framing me
for a
crime thank you for the Super Chat
oh okay that leads to one thing that's
the crack in the wall that's probably
the cave right oh no didn't he say
something about the temple being beyond
that maybe both is
there you have to open your inventory in
front of
it what
ah okay
wait this is the temple
right oo look at those
monsters
[Music]
wow then I'll go back
first I think I want to go to the cave
first cuz this is this is main story and
the cave is side side stuff I
guess possibly a nice new pet or a nice
weapon or so
is hiding there which way was it again
not this way right it's just a house can
we visit her now
though no she wants me to go fight
okay Jimmy you
good you
good good night have fun watching the
vud when you wake
up over there
[Music]
right okay so
inventory
uh this one
yeah that's a a little bit weird that
you have to open up the inventory a
prompt would be
nice oh it is a pet to get
nickies oh my God it's cute wow what a
design it kind of looks like a neopet
though time to sit on a different foot
for
once just switching the
feet don't mention movie I don't want to
think about movie no I just came here I
can't already miss my
cats 1,200 CH I'm not going to bring
oh I mean I can summon mid fight
unsummon midf fight too but
yeah
oopsie no no
careful okay just the swing I think
that's still the the weakest thing I can
do
[Music]
okay uh please no accidental crit
either
careful who
oo it hits pretty strong
you do you think we can get it we might
not get it on first try so let me
heal
[Music]
um uh yeah uh
here there we go first try first
[Music]
try succeed it looks dead accidentally
kills it wow
pretty it totally looks like a Neal pet
doesn't
it a mysterious cat inhabiting the snow
field
yay snow
cat now we have a a cute little
cat wow
wow oh yeah uh wait where's where the
[\h__\h] is
now he's there
confusing first of all what what can we
feed you it already has half
Affinity but I really don't know I have
to go for everything
again I hope we have
whatever ugly bird meat
oh wait I I guess cuz it is in the in
the region where there's ugly birds that
kind of makes sense shock spel too let's
go it prefers to eat the ugly the
disgusting stinky ugly bird
meat not you guys no you're
beautiful okay what do you eat what
could you be eating this no
probably something related to this
region then right
but I don't have much whatever let me go
for everything what no
yeah I don't think I have what it
needs nope nope nope nope no yeah I
haven't explored it fully
true okay but
let's let's bring it
out cute can I ride it no it's too small
that's fine makes
sense
cute
cute want to keep
hug cute
[Music]
fluffy I want to carry
over my
shoulder and here The
[Music]
Purge it eats the drop from the ice no
Oh I thought you meant like just by
having it out it automatically eats like
whatever it drops what you mean the the
food drop okay okay okay and and not
automatically okay okay ice Giant
ice
giant wait ah I'm
confused that's my cat's new obsession
these days
what eating
ice I don't I think this looks like Fuki
Senpai and not just because she's not a
cat oh my cat's purse has been
considerably louder recently
a considerably
louder
nice I'm happy for you that is
special I want to try out the is
attack just to see
oh
[Music]
cool
uhhuh yeah this is still stronger it has
slow effect oh yeah okay I didn't real L
that's good very good look at this OAB
boa
guy
cute I like his stick old yey the oldest
of the yitties 36,000 oh okay he's a bit
strong but not strong
[Music]
enough yeah he's free right uh
then party
baby let's
go Fight Fire with Fire fight I no I
mean for the slowing effect I might use
it like
sometimes but only like once in a battle
Maybe
[Music]
he's almost dead
already are we just beating old people
now ganging up on the old
man are Yetis
humans they look pretty human actually
now did you say it they could be just
just humans old dudes who have been out
in the cold for years who haven't shaved
their beard and hair for
years and cuz it's so cold it it's
covered in ice and
popsicles yeah makes
sense humans who became cannibals whoa
where is that lore
[Music]
from former inhabitants of the ice this
is
[Music]
description why
are these enemies
named
[Music]
schitz
weird it kind of means
sweating just they thought of fancy
German words again I
[Music]
guess during the spelling be oh hello
what the
[\h__\h] W nice angle during the spelling be
uh like PR before during preparation we
were like chatting a little bit and I
don't know how we got to it but uh we
talked about German words and RPGs and
um
CC
mentioned uh as a reply uh to me I think
that you know AAR games also have these
German words and I'm like at mention
atar mention
n did she say in her debut stream that
she plays AO
games somehow it sounded like a first
time mentioned to
me don't think she said it in her debut
stream
now was
surprised I'm an expert on ice magic now
let's
fight this one looks cool question mark
question mark question
[Music]
mark a challenger
huh a Challenger let's let's do agility
cuz I have a couple of them and he's
going to Slow
Me So before he slows me I fasten myself
my seat belts and I slow him but
[Music]
wait let's bring out my
pets actually won't my cat also slow him
with her attacks that would be nice
she might do that right with her
attacks might have that effect by
[Music]
default I want to see let's pay
attention she attacks after he
attacks
o
o is he not it I don't think so if
anything there was a ice particle thing
icon on top of his on up up up on the
top right but I think Justice attack
cancel with fire
yeah and he's going to keep on attacking
with fire so there's no point in me
doing it
either
uh if he would at least replace it with
like a fire dot uh damage but no he
doesn't
ah okay
defense I think we'll be
fine it'll be fine oh cat attacks
last so we might get a slow slow effect
there and and he moved back to yeah yeah
yeah he moved back to behind me after
after my turn so I get oh wait he
move he canceled it cuz
ah and
then the order changed again you guys
can't see the full order properly cuz
I'm in front of it but yeah that was a
that was a
discombobulation man he's almost dead
it's okay it's not such a big deal
wait I forgot to do the arrow isn't the
arrow already
oopsie we'll hit him even harder than in
a moment I think the same thing is going
to happen because there's the cat before
this golem Attacks and then Justice is
going to be moved forward I
think oh but no never mind I'm first uh
and then the cat
mhm um what kind of the same thing will
happen Okay this one
uh he's going to die with my meteorite
judgment pretty sure that's
it ah he barely he barely lives ah there
we
go Yoo Hercules Stone ah wait that
sounds
familiar wait is there a Lightning
Dragon up there by any chance
[Music]
let's
go this is not where the temple is but
we're going to go there anyway Yoo that
was
easy good
fight how did I know how did I know I
mean the Lightning Dragon had to come up
sometime at some
point there it is
House of the Dragon last episode begins
here I hope you guys all watched the
previous
episodes my my freaking
intuition wow do we really need to fight
that uh yeah
[Music]
oh is this God is this a god
or is this where I would have to go
anywh to go into the
temple I thought there was another path
from down
[Music]
there I see the temple
entrance I but I thought there was a
path to the right where it would go into
the temple from a different path H hi
[Music]
looks like a
snack without spoilers I just want to
say what was his name Verma Verma was
sure having a you know Feast he was like
I have this snack I'm sure Vero in his
head was thinking like wow why why are
they like treating me to such a feast
Yum Yum Yum
Yum so nice of them what happened now
why am I being fed so much he just saw
it
[Music]
all he looked very entertained and um
happy
[Music]
delighted what the [\h__\h] happened to a
few arkman
[Music]
pathetic du so much for being perceptive
oh let's go let's
fight fight
[Music]
fight yeah yeah so you need to test my
power
[Music]
yeah only if you become my pet
afterwards with dur Temple I met its
Guardian animal because the other
Guardian animals became my pets but I
can't imagine this one becoming my pet
it's a bit too
big he told me that he knew I'd already
GA the blessings but that I couldn't
passive about defeating him typical RPG
stuff let's
go uh
unmeasurable let's
go wait but it says defense elements on
fire so he resists
fire is that
so wa I want to go back once and see
what was on the other path
though okay so we can fight him with our
ice magic and the ice
pet oh he's what the [\h__\h] he's back do I
have to fight him again to go up
there no no way
normally they take longer to spawn what
the [\h__\h] what they all re how did they
all respawn
already something must have reset
them no teleport up there yeah I didn't
see one yet so I don't think I can reach
it oh it's an ice dragon wait we can
have two Ice Pets wait I think we have
actually several Ice Pets already but
it's a a tiny wait we can bring this to
the lady
again ooh I don't have a pet out right
no okay Co it's it looks like a
horse I guess all dragons are horses
with wings
honestly
[Music]
yeah looks like a freaking horse it's
the tail I
think the body shape
generally oh one
[Music]
more wait a [\h__\h] second did you did
you see that graphic
bug
huh
huh the hole in the
wall well now you won't see it this on
the left here this part here opened up
is there a secret exit
no another first try let's go easy
so this one's still
charging why do I have to fight that
again
already huh that's not
normal I forgot about the recharging
[Music]
time
ah probably get there from here
maybe but okay I'll fight it again but I
was thinking maybe I should go home
[Music]
once do we have what it needs
yet is
it
uh ah it's this
okay wait now we can get the the drop
again actually that's good because I'm
sure that drop is necessary for some
craft right what you
[Music]
want what could it
be H ugly bird wait do all the dragons
the tiny dragons eat ugly bird meat then
oh Frosty rain stroll runs for the air
on a manually controlled path rain
raining down
ice cool they're all fed and happy
look at these cute e
Evolutions oh eeve not e in German it's
EV maybe should
[Music]
heal very cute nail pits
true there are they are in almost all
cases very interesting characters
dragons wasn't that fat one also
Dragon I love that one indeed indeed
interesting
character defense element wait they all
have the same element they resist the
same element that they use huh wait what
makes
sense wait does that make
sense yeah makes sense
yeah of course it makes
sense yeah that makes sense that just
makes sense what am I
thinking that makes sense uh sorry I had
a little brain freeze moment from this
ice cold
here can't blame me can
you ice ice
lightning okay give me that item again
will you
please now when it says Fire
Res it
means what does that mean that makes we
think like almost said he resists fire
but no
right it says here just ice Maybe
resists
both cuz it did say that for the other
ice enemies too but I I couldn't believe
it because it makes no sense to
me Lightning then lightning doesn't do
much I think fire is stronger
he just resists
the the bonus
effect yeah the
dot h you
missed let's
go this one is stronger by far wait I
forgot the arrow again I think I was
able to use it already
I got it again got to go sleep good
night see this is the problem people
need to go sleep even though I'm by far
not done
streaming critical at least by waiting a
turn the arrow gets the
critical
wow ouch
that Bell armor ain't doing [\h__\h] right
now you just came to the stream good
morning morning is
it got to wake up now what what do you
mean wake up now you're already awake
right cuz you're typing this
message and we got another giant head
honestly the Enemy being back here might
have been a good
thing I work nights so this's rules for
me let's
go sleep watching
Wawa well as long as you keep the stream
open I don't mind by the way you guys
don't know because you don't see the
exact sub count I think but we're almost
at
1.54 we're really close to 1.54
I think we're going to hit it this week
and I was kind of thinking of doing
another short stream I want to do a
short stream per week right for
algorithm but um I couldn't think of
anything good and I was looking for the
Olympics things if there's anything
that's really interesting to me I looked
at everything that the austrians are
doing this week but honestly nothing
really looked interesting to
me and also even if there was something
I would have probably needed to go
through
some some stuff Freedom management to
have the permission to do it maybe
there's something more interesting next
week but I don't know I want to do
something as a short stream
H
H yeah I don't know nothing looked
really interesting enough to me like I
think there was Beach uh volleyball but
I it was with the the
males I would have been into it if it
was ladies but I don't know if I want to
see men doing beach volleyball
necessarily even if it's
[Laughter]
austrians fancing I did see funny
fancing clips on
[Music]
Twitter maybe there's something cool
next week but it's not that long like I
might I might end up not watching
anything if I'm so
picky has Austria won any medals yet no
idea have we you tell me they got those
booty shorts I don't want to see their
booty shorts now don't tell they have
booty shorts
on no then I don't want to watch
it
no that to streams yeah maybe no
no cuz I can just JSU during my normal
streams
[Music]
M what's Bard what what's
that is that the
[Music]
thing no I will not make a cover of
booty shorts but there's a little short
up on my
[Music]
channel twerk practice fry
short yeah I could do it
Frey short stream but um yeah I'm too
lazy to set it up this week I
think but I I I uh was kind of waiting
on the
schedule um there's one collab I want to
do where I'm still waiting to confirm
the last Me Maybe I maybe maybe maybe oh
I was waiting for the last
participant let's see I got a DM from
the last participant it says
[Music]
no
okay
um okay okay I have to find a different
[Music]
participant this an off
collab I
[Music]
think okay
find someone
[Music]
else yeah and another thing I was
waiting for uh also still kind of
uncertain but it's probably going to be
moved
so yeah possibly if I get the
participant for
this uh yeah Tama collaboration then I
can put up the schedule but we'll see
how long it takes to get a repl
Bo let's
go show me your unmeasurable
strength so what he what did he resist
fire
right then I'll send out all my Ice Pets
I have so many right
now um do I have another one
no oh
okay shut I think I have to think I have
to
burp no no burping you might want to
heal uh what where my HP low oh
[\h__\h] no burp for the wa I'm a lady let's
let's summon this one we always we he e
four ah [\h__\h]
no that
[Music]
one
okay guess
not that's
sad I don't burp I'm a lady I can keep
it
in yeah surprisingly low HP right now um
what are we going to
eat this one maybe
no I don't no this is a lot of MP that I
don't need to be
recovering maybe just
[Music]
although I want to always minmax my
healing
items not this time I guess okay ice
magic let's
go split and FL him D ladies do spit out
their fle them
totally I say so ouch why do I not have
fire
[Music]
resistance I seem to be uh able to
attack again before he gets his turn
so I'm hoping that will not
change cuz then I don't have to heal yet
because I the bird can't heal me right
now
yeah he's resisting ice too
though it's not fair still going to use
it
though see
wonderful SM all right good well planned
everything is
fine
um this and the arrow is
ready oh right okay but maybe we'll keep
the arrow next turn my shield will
probably be
gone and then it will be critical
actually 3,300 is not that
[Music]
good Boon he gets 3,700 damage back from
hitting
me
wow there we
go strategic genius Takara
wow WAOW over
9,000 causes a frosty rain to fall where
is it show me I don't see
it hello game did it just crash from
that Pet's
attack
yeah move
him
oh
what
what that's a first how the [\h__\h] would I
know the game never worked like this
before thought
crashed how the [\h__\h] would I know
this how do you find the sound if you
play without chat
on you could control it and move it to
where you want the AOE to fall which is
cool but it said in so in the
description of the attack that you have
to move it with your joystick
[Music]
normally you just choose the the enemy
or
so shut up not everybody reads they got
to make it bit more obvious and maybe
make a prompt right now when it happens
don't assume that I'm going to read the
attacks
description all the time that's cuz they
never had this function
[Music]
before but that's why I have chat that's
why I have you guys
[Music]
mm
puny is that a praise is that saying
it's stronger because puny sounds
like the
opposite what does puny mean again tiny
she he is still saying my power is too
small even though I just I have just
bested
him yeah what the
hell the the the context made no sense
to me just
[Music]
now cuz I'm
weak why are you so such a salty
loser
[Music]
[Applause]
fore
[Music]
fore foree
wait what is he saying I'm having a
conversation
here guys remember when I
said remember when I said
[Music]
so he's done talking remember when I
said I I I don't think Ena wants to play
the Mario game anymore with
me she wrote to me that we should finish
it
soon when she comes to
Japan I'm like what
what
it
really all
right okay okay
[Music]
okay no I thought it would be too
frustrating for her with me
[Music]
he
h
[Music]
[Applause]
oh okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay
[Applause]
[Music]
okay okay okay
okay you
[Music]
sorry riding with
Ena
[Music]
[Laughter]
ton yippe
[Music]
oh no I think she's going to she didn't
know I was streaming I think she's going
to open up the stream maybe let me hide
the
chat okay she told me to go back to work
okay what was he
saying I'm trying to tell you why the
temple it's not because the temple
Lord's magic was too weak that they fell
victim to the
pope uh does that mean the pope had some
trick up his sleeve no rather the temple
may have chosen their own deaths it but
that makes no sense do you have any
proof the proof is in the pudding during
the Spring War I was immobilized by
durok it was like an unspoken signal not
to into fear with his
death I was ordered to help luciad
Escape rather than fight the Pope's Army
there's something going on that we don't
know about yeah this is really confusing
what the
[Music]
hell
chat who knows if she even opened up the
stream maybe she
didn't you don't even know if she's here
yeah this is weird perhaps the temp
prepared elian's daughter as the key to
defeating the
Pope I don't what death why did they
what
[Music]
I if if they if they have the power to
kill him then why don't they all just
gather and kill him together until now
anyway why do they have to wait what no
she's
here oh no oh no
no since when are you here just after I
told you that I'm streaming
right you didn't see
[Music]
anything is it too late for me to hide
as well
[Music]
um nothing I have nothing to
hide
[Music]
wi no no no I'm just embarrassed because
the chat U the chat just says says weird
things the whole time this
embarrassing no huh they're they're so
embarrassing they're going to get me
banned you know I can't show them on
screen does do you actually know what's
going on or are you just guessing from
weird stuff that the chat is saying and
you're not really understanding what
it's really
about
uh yeah oh hey you know
oh I I have an explanation I have an I I
don't know I only do this when I'm
abroad and I I I need to set up stuff
and then I don't have a CSS at hand and
so I just go back to uh one and a half
years ago when you gave me your chat as
CSS changed the color I don't know how I
don't know how I would have to know how
to do
CSS um and then bubbles are the speech
bubbles are so nice you know it looks so
nice and so I I I I oh we got raided oh
no I'm I'm going to be exposed even more
at least I stole nothing from Iris
nothing I know
of Hi H I'm so busted I'm so busted oh
no I did nothing wrong
you came a little bit too
late guys to know what's happening right
now so I can still recover from this
embarrassment yeah look core color in
the CSS let me see let me
see but it's so long
like background color transparent
background color
transparent background color trans
transparent
important well you can tell the CSS that
something's important so make sure that
this one works for
[Music]
sure
important
important oh thanks for the membership
gifts can you st rgf in here no you
can't
padding um where would it be color H
there's
a # 99999 that's just white isn't it for
the text
box uh here's a ffd 600 maybe that's the
purple give me a code for an orange
color I thought it's not that easy to
just write Orange in
here what give me a give me me a purple
one H uh uh orange one I mean 600 is
yellow oh that's yellow oh then it's the
who's yellow in here you guys some of
these are like brown
beiges 500 is okay wait uh ah what about
e84
F1 is that
it could that be the
color 5
e84
F1
uh what's ec5
F should I test this out now you're
going to mess up the whole CSS that Ena
gave
me willingly will willingly indeed
what's this F E Fire Emblem 511
years before
Christ what happens what
[Music]
changes nothing changed
here nothing changed did anything change
looks the same what did I just
change maybe did I change like
a CS Heist what did I
change okay that in any case that wasn't
the color that makes everything
purple what what would I be looking for
if I'm looking for something
purple font family f f
FF
yeah I can't find the
[Music]
purple I can't find it
what about there's a legacy paid message
render
b552
B7 what's
this no that's different too I don't
know what that
[Music]
changed Maybe
maybe
[Music]
waa okay I'll look for it one more time
and then I'm going to give
up avatars badges time
stamps
[Music]
badges well did you did your badges
change no
five message render no I changed that
already I think oh Channel names oh it
might be this
one
oh
no no
[Music]
again I I changed like five colors and I
didn't see any change yet
see I can't I can't fix
it were the emotes so small before
though I didn't change any
sizes maybe I should revert to original
CSS oh wait what's that orange that I
just saw the non-members the non-members
are
[Music]
orange that's fine too but there's more
purple and orange
[Music]
damn
it oh no now my members are going to be
jealous of your
orangeness why do you get to be
orange there's still an overwhelming
amount of
[Music]
purple if that was there then maybe the
one is
close maybe the other one isn't so far
but I don't know I can't find it anymore
can
i f f f f f f
f this one this this is the one I
changed Channel
names
ah
May no this
one different
right no I make you all orange now y yay
I mean I mean I'm I got the purple on to
be
orange let's go now maybe I'll make the
the non-members yellow I just have to
change it from 600 to 500 or what was
it and I think
moderators would also be orange now
oopsie oh
well uh this one channelm here this one
600 right let's see what colors you are
now non-members say something
non-members say something
non-members oh no oh you're still orange
what did I
[Laughter]
change
what I
[Music]
500 600 what what's uh give me a code
for um
yellow is it too
similar maybe um give me give me a
different color oh thank
you red orange no red orange a red
orange for you guys maybe
how about this
oh
non-members oh okay that looks good that
looks
good
[Music]
yes there we
go there we
go I don't know I don't know if
the badges the emotes always were the is
small though did I mess something up I
didn't I only changed colors was it
always like
this no I like the colors this is uh
Taki
Kiara outfit
orange they're so small yeah
H I wouldn't know how to fix that I
think they're always that small okay
anyway let's continue thank you for your
participation everybody
oh
what what I can summon you with that
let's
go why is he also becoming a pet
now yay my new Pets collection is
growing
what okay he at least he memorized
it Tamar sumon Sig
[Music]
Is this different
from I don't think we got this for the
other ones did we we just got them as
pets
right that one is op it's a magic attack
H eh a summon
sigil but
uh wouldn't that
mean El do work again
wait if I go back do I have to fight the
thing again when I go
back I didn't consider that just
now let's
see where is
he or wait do I already have the circle
and I don't have to build
it where would I put it we have uh
[Music]
uh no it's not in here I think I have to
build
it or is it its own
attack
like
uh where would that be
[Music]
again I'm confused it's in my I see it
in my
inventory where's my inventory again
[Music]
where can I see my inventory when I'm in
here God damn
[Music]
it yeah is it the same as like mind
control huh
probably probably
so oh all the mobs are back here here
okay but they they had plenty of time to
respawn so that makes sense which way
was it again that
way so this is one of our other gods
that became a pet I guess they were not
worthy enough
of of becoming something better than
that la laon
ooh
[Music]
ooh these are back what about the big
one y he's gone this
time can you visit Luna now since you
beat the ice Golem H probably but I'm on
a mission now I can't be distracted
again what's this isn't this didn't we
look down from here before did no maybe
[Music]
not another Temple for us to explore but
I'm also curious what's over here oh
no
okay yeah we can't go there now okay I
get it I get it I get
it let's go in
[Music]
let's go let's go let's go let's go
activate the
teleportation did you just see what I
just saw is that an Executor again oh
that one looks really
[Music]
fancy hello fancy hat wait
what yeah but she doesn't have white
hair don't they all usually have white
hair she has red
hair she's kind of fancy she's got a a
puppet plushy and a eye patch and fancy
ass hat
who is
this she's the same size as everybody
else
who may wait maybe she's not an Executor
at all maybe that's just how she dresses
I mean she's got normal hair
so ah she's wait she's the is she the
one what's her name again uh the the
stupid stupid lady that we don't
[Music]
like yeah Kate Kate Kate
mhm Kate
Middleton guess she she's not too lost
yet if she still has the same hair color
because Livia lost her hair color why
does why does she get to keep her
special or
something oh she doesn't get
[Music]
it yeah she talks
normally maybe they
improved their uh Technic techniques
[Music]
I don't know how you guys see Ollie in
that just because of the
doll you look like [\h__\h] Kate what
[Music]
happened I don't think that's that's a
scar isn't that the uh the string from
her eye patch in her
[Music]
face I'd be willing to turn into an
Executor if I get an outfit like
those so one thing I'll say the pop
is a good fashion designer maybe that
should be his job maybe he should stop
being a pop and become fashion designer
in Milan or
[Music]
something well she admits she had demons
that were tormenting
her which I would say is a metaphor
right
not actual demons tormenting
her yeah follow your true passion become
character designer make your own
game final boss goes to Fashion
school I will support it I will pay for
his
tuition
uhhuh for
[Music]
we have the same
skill oo let's go let's
fight I hope you're somewhat strong at
least
12, a man why is it so disappointing I
should have played this game on hard
mode pets maybe
like one or
two wait um what's the resistance I have
no idea
I don't need a full pet uh
lineup I'll just go with
this I've been cursed and slowed
no but my pets
[Music]
haven't H maybe I do need another pet
out here
[Music]
sick let's
go I I probably could switch difficulty
but we're so
far okay one down it's finally my turn
do I still have the curse no I don't
think
so but I would have put on an agility
thing I'll do
it wait that took up a turn [\h__\h] I
forgot
no okay at least we got the counter
attack no oh she curses me with
something else each time weapons are
weakened okay that's it's
fine
[Music]
um I think I need the
defense
yeah I'm a bit worried about my health
though for this upcoming
turn m M wait n i I think I at least get
to attack before she attacks again but
the soldiers will attack but my pets
maybe will take one of them down at
least so that I'll
survive yeah I'll be
fine I'll be fine
[Music]
right uh what what what this Eh Eh this
one and the executor too kill one of
them please no
it's okay the one one of them is stuck
and my shield is still
[Music]
there
critical but I can't use the Judgment
yet because of my shield unless I give
it
up right wait no uh was that not the
case I'm mixing up
things wait
okay judgment is from staff no blessing
what I can
use okay yeah whatever I'm
[Music]
confused I probably could have just
killed her
now what are you going to curse me now
attacks weakend
[Music]
okay what the hell cat why are you
missing why are you shooting your
icicles exactly where we don't need
[Music]
them J is
do didn't want to summon
him thinking
maybe one heal wouldn't
[Music]
hurt ooh six
hits didn't realize it was that good no
kill now
now kill the does the fight continue if
we kill her first cuz she summoned
them let's
see it
[Music]
does
h ah stroll stroll stroll we're
strolling
[Applause]
[Music]
got to pay attention for that
one
H okay that was uh not as fast of a
fight as I thought it was going to
be
bye-bye see you again
sometime probably with the Pope
[Music]
yeah cuz she debuffed me but most of the
things she debuffed me with didn't
really matter I
[Music]
think can you upgrade the ice spell now
did she drop something nice that I could
do it
with
[Music]
M I can check
what it needs when I'm back
home let's first see oh what is
this a
riddle
okay what
but there's only
one blue
cube let's go
straight ah I
see it moves with me okay ah it's one of
those
riddles I feel
like it would be too easy to
go
left uh all the way to the
well we might want to stay in here first
try wait
H when we're here do we align with that
[Music]
no I wait I think I got it I think I got
it ah no ah yeah ah [\h__\h] I think I
messed up
[Music]
think I messed up back to the beginning
huh
okay let me
cook I think first I went right here so
let's go left and then
there but H don't we end up kind of the
[Music]
same this took forever for
me ow
back to the
beginning it has to be here
first can we go down ah ah
ah the tiny spot where you can go down
yay yay I got
it nice I like this
riddle this one's more challenging than
some
others oh there's another one ooh even
bigger okay
[Music]
strain could they want me to go down
here
too if I go down and I can only go right
maybe yeah and then up seems like
something they would want me to do and
on here and then probably
up although oh well let's
try
left ah
no if I go right now I think it shoots
me out of the whole
thing wa is cute when she thinks oh wow
you're saying the most obvious thing
people die when they're
killed m
yeah know this is just a same dead
[Music]
end I think this was
good until here
is oh was it n wait what if I go down
now does that bring us to a new starting
point
yeah or not really oh
M now I'm in the
[Music]
beginning is cute when anything thank
you why would I go left
[Music]
here doesn't do anything
no wait maybe maybe I I can't no I think
if I go right I fall
out
right oh no ah okay the angle kind of
fooled
me I thought it was one
[Music]
above well then I could have solved it
in the beginning if there wasn't this
optical illusion
[Music]
how else someone going to open it
oh you praising me Black Mage I never
played this before it wasn't that
difficult am smart that's all there is
to it
[Music]
oh
Crown it's been a while I didn't
recognize him again he's huge wait has
he always been this
tall the hell did he
grow
thanks how is that not
magic okay
[Music]
okay then maybe we should pass through
now and give him a break
I was the chosen one I am the chosen one
let me for you let's
go okay
bye she's like okay bye see you later
sucker a cube another
[Music]
10 chosen one yeah do we pray to it Cube
what what pray is the cube oh yeah this
is the cube I knew there was something
in my brain something I wanted to
reference to I forgot what it
was who no more
Cube oh thanks that's uh
easy and sudden
wow sa
moon it's been a while since we got to
choose this stuff
um
HP D's gravity field unleashes a
powerful gravitational field oh in theme
with the with the whole dungeon that
drastically decreases an enemy's ability
to move up to three gravity Fields can
be Unleashed and stacking them increases
their
power is that a good
[Music]
skill
byebye yeah he doesn't really want to
waste too much time with me
seems I noticed
you're still here
Kate or
again probably wouldn't meet again until
we're in the
castle oh she's so mad
what happened what happened wasn't he uh
committed to keeping the door open for
me or like opening it again when I come
back like what does this mean is he the
god that's in here because like how else
like wouldn't wouldn't Kate and Crown
have met just now and Crown would have
probably overpowered Kate
H would he have tried to like tell me
like uh cuz he opened it for me he knows
I would I would be stuck if he just
[Music]
leaves maybe cuz the god in here doesn't
want to talk much that's why I'm
thinking that maybe he has something to
hide did he have the same kind of voice
I feel like they might have had the same
kind of voice is he the god of the
temple I don't know am I asking
something stupid is this stupid
[Music]
could that be could
be would the seal not be gone after
getting the blessing oh I guess I could
get out yeah
probably maybe that's why he left cuz he
knew that if I get the blessing I can
get out I just can't get in before I
have the
blessing
true yeah I know he said that and that
was kind of that could that speaks
against what I just said but still that
was my only explanation just
now yeah okay he just left because I
already went in
yeah
okay anyway let's kill Kate
wow P being actually
respectful to this
Temple whoa
[Music]
angry no I what else would I do would I
like I don't know take damage and have
you kill me bro that would be stupid
don't [\h__\h] with
me kneel before me you cowardly
prophetic
[Laughter]
[Music]
bastards oh sorry I skipped her devil de
devil devil devil laugh devious
laugh de devious evil
laugh H pop
Chan pop Chan you came to see
me I would have gone to
you oh
uh only two turns okay I don't know it's
actually two
turn I still have a
arrow probably
[Music]
what a great leader
definitely someone I want to support
[Music]
and because he's been watching the
stream kind of
obvious yeah I'm I'm in Japan
for a
[Music]
while well then why did you come
here I wasn't going to
say but the moment he showed up I was
like maybe he's
Crown but why would why would he be both
crown and pop
but he
he he also Hasam AR's power and he's as
tall as him I
think why would he makes no
sense we already saw Crown's face I
forgot what does it look
like maybe they can shape shift I don't
know maybe they're Brothers
[Music]
Crown is a DT witch too yeah but can
they be both I don't
know oh yeah Pope has no bunny
ears
no oh no
well this just reminds me of the time we
played fif
simulator
Michelle I forgot about that girl
too I only saw her like once
[Music]
I already she works for
them but now about to be turned into an
executor
[Music]
she has an excuse for everything huh
girl there's a key probably right in the
cell if this is like fief
simulator there always is
[Music]
take it
off take him
off did she just fall asleep
I do want to see execut a form of
pberry can I make a save here then go to
bad ending route check out what I look
like as an executor and then go back to
my safe file
[Music]
there is no bad ending route is
there that would be interesting though
yeah more games need bad ending routes
[Music]
yeah yeah blah blah blah I can't deal
with this chibio [\h__\h] right now
no what what are you going to do with my
bird oh it's just me okay they're just
putting him away to not
[Music]
disturb uh sorry my brain is I don't
remember many sir um I really I I plead
the
[Music]
fifth
well my
wait
that's that's
what that's what um
Magnus not
Magnus that's what that's what uh wa I'm
want to make a reference to Vikings
valala
um not uh what's the guy called again
that's like they're in
in
um uh what's the word
again uh the ones that are
in um the the place with the empress and
the emperor and you will only know if
you up to date with that
one they they were they were fighting um
ketting
everything um um you know the one with
the
sparta and and they in uh what's what's
that place called
again did you guys not watch the new
season uh
did you guys know what the season the
new season of Vikings
valala what's that what is that what's
that place called
again Conant yes thank you
Constantinople
so but they had that little war in that
other place and um and then the guy
there's the these two Sparta I mean
they're becoming Sparta but they're like
the emperor is like okay now we we we we
took over the castle but and we killed
the their King but let's keep the people
alive and that is the wish of the
emperor and then he [\h__\h] off and then
um the the one guy is like yeah let's
protect his wish but the other guy is
like [\h__\h] no and then he killed
everybody this is like this right now he
goes against what Kate is saying
basically just like the guy went against
what the emperor was saying and kills in
effect of that yes okay moving on
I don't watch TV I watch TK
wow
Sabotage by
H it's him he got promote dead D that's
what he's
doing I like how separately his low
armor is
moving hey you were a
Chad I didn't know you were a
Chad I'll tell Luna what you
did
[Music]
for oh
wow wow wow wow wow
how many more times will the things be
just shocked up as an accident
though one like
this is it that
easy ah
h no more
MIM Wake Up Little
Bird fat
bird let's go let's go let's
go
huh
huh ding suspicious
underpass
sus imagine the smell
okay
there's dead corpses all over here
ew we going to
do oh
qu let's
go seems like they knew how to spell it
the
[Music]
excitement Behind Bars while escaping I
found a hidden area in the Pop's Castle
is YouTube not doing so well right
now
bro I should rest here and Catch My
Breath not
a what okay we just investig ating this
place there's a dude
there peered Inside the lightville
Cage Regional
huh oh did it hit
Australia
Asia on sea getting [\h__\h]
[Music]
back not all of you huh
why is he wearing did he steal that from
am you don't put that on your eye you
put that like on your hair
bro he's wearing it
wrong
oh let's
[Music]
go I mention
a letter from Matt detailing the
weaknesses of the royal palace's great
weapon
wow lucky
yes I'm in Japan right now so my
streaming times are kind of
weird he they got to be more quiet than
this that was easy warri should have
passed by now I should head back down
but I'm curious can I not Explore
More found something
old spell book the highest stage spells
yo this
is I feel like not everybody might find
this really
expensive always got the wrong way first
yes that's the right
way
interesting expensive but we're
basically they they inverted the map
we're on the inverted part of the map so
if you follow the inverted paths I guess
but not everything like you can't go
through here so who would have known
that you could go there wow
[Music]
and that sounds like something Risa
would
say she 100% said
that wait we no we're going
uh can we go this way is that okay yeah
yeah yeah
yeah I remember that yeah it burnt
itself into my brain
t t
[Music]
t haven't gotten my magic back so
fighting is dangerous I have to escape
uh the cave without being seen okay
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
o can I use my
pets can I be on one of my pets at
least can I right
Jers no probably not he he could I could
piggyback him I can't summon him okay so
I have to walk for
this oh wait now it's so much easier I
got the right timing but what is this
can I go in
here what you're telling me there's
nothing
here is it just like a a point to
wait metal de
witch
yes just a
box just I'm just a box or just a fish
actually I'm just a fish
fish oh
no oh
no ah ah
no this is difficult okay it begins
fine oh okay okay the timing when you
respawn seems to be on point oh perfect
let
move
Smo smoo and
smovie tou my [\h__\h] back [\h__\h] I have
back problems
we're in clutch it
seems yeah I
will okay damn somebody help Luna or
Michelle or Michelle right Michelle's
going to show
up I thought somebody would show up and
save me in the last frame
[Music]
uh no I think that was not lag I think
that was just
a dramatic
effect you
guys ding
d
d oh my God I have not fought or heard
it
just because I
said oh my
God let me grab water from the fridge
really quickly
I have a cup I have a water o water
cup yum yum yum yum
water heavy bottle of
water
okay
wow hydrate
yourself ah
I want to cover myself in a blanket but
all I have is a towel I'll take the
towel i b a
towel a fluffy
towel from
muchi so now I have no more towel
problem yeah
there's so many nice looking things at
Muji I want to buy so much but it makes
no sense to buy it here I'm not going to
bring all these things back home but if
I lived in Japan I would probably buy so
many things from
Muji but I'm sure I can get similar
things in Austria anyway so this is
really just this kind of feeling of
wanting to buy things unnecessarily and
that you really don't need no we don't
have a muin in Austria I think I've seen
other ones and other places in like
maybe in London or
so I think or in Germany even
maybe I think I saw a mui maybe in just
of but it's really not common it's not
that spread
yet mic has a big one
really is it like Japan Ika not really I
wouldn't go that far it it sells more
smaller
things like smaller items like uh also
food food a little bit uh just small
items towels uh Cutlery probably
Bowls the kitchen
wear uh WR writing stuff what's the word
for that
again yeah lifestyle kind of things
yeah and they're all like simplistic
designs so a stationary
[Music]
yeah I think I got uh some tea there
before uh that everybody really liked
when I served it in
Austria cold tea cold brew
tea good one they got everything yeah
but not like big furniture
transformation unleashing our power
together protect me
Jo help me
yay it's the final pet
for thank you for the
memberships it keeps on showing up
now m
oh okay they're both here at the same
time so they can't be the same
person maybe they could be though maybe
they're moving really fast
this could be optical
illusion or green screens could be
pre-recorded and green screen in
there a mirror image yeah could just be
looking in a mirror or so I don't know
many
possibilities no baby
girl don't die baby
girl I like how the picture is still the
fat ass
Bird yeah pberry
[Music]
am that's not what he said
he's like what do I do from now
on now he repeats himself
okay a
[Music]
that's what you say when you say
go she's not dead don't
[Music]
worry a he so he's so
sad no no no no she no
no I'm recharging I'm not
dispersing for sure I
believe I'm charging up right now
[Music]
right they're trying really hard to make
me
think that she's dying I don't believe
it oh
I was wondering why he was right
there
yeah
[Music]
can these little
tiny dust
thing is going to be saving my life is
that what you're
saying okay
damn he's so
traumatic he's like losing his mind
somebody help
him I'm
gone she a whole ecosystem
um just
[Music]
evaporated
yikes oh oh no
no it's
j it's so black over
you little
[Applause]
[\h__\h] it's not
J not really he was just dramatizing it
[Music]
twerk to this
yeah if I wasn't Frey right now you
would see him twerking to it
[Music]
uh with Mom's blessing she means the one
that gives me an extra life
right I must
say uh I like how they're kind of
um
using these skills outside of the
battles cuz I don't see that much in
other games you know what I mean cuz now
like this is like anti antia
somehow they're they're properly
utilizing it and it kind of makes sense
the way they're using it yeah in the
narrative
H this is the best example the the fact
like cuz like you know how there's
Revival items but they just like in
other
games they just die people die if
they're killed and shouldn't you be able
to use a Revival item or so huh not like
they're using a Revival item here I
don't think we even have one if we die
we just die but there's the the skill
that we get from our mother and they use
it because I was about to die
so but that means she would have had to
activate it beforehand because you can't
no wait it's a passive skill it's a
passive skill never mind so nice now I
have been now now my questions about
that skill have finally been confirmed
for real for real it is really a passive
skill seemingly so that's that's cool
you know you know what I mean right why
that's cool that they use it you know
you get it you guys get
[Music]
it why did why did Jonah consider
this H I guess he thought it was really
over maybe I didn't think that the skill
could save me from that but like he
knows I have these skills so and we're
obviously able to use them outside of
battle he for
go he's just he's a drama
queen it's like you guys worrying about
me even though you know I can revive
[Music]
eh I'm sure they'll come back with your
dirty ass lifestyle
[Music]
you saw what I was
doing I was sinking up with her
[Music]
movement new Milestone chapter 7 is this
the last
one could it
be this might be the last one
[Music]
how long is
it could we finish to day if I wanted
to I'm close to the end
[Music]
right two to three hours
H final BS is quite difficult
really nice
challenge how long I want to go I mean I
could I
could don't know if I want to split it
up yeah I had a funny name for the final
stream but I can I can change the name
of this stream
[Music]
up to
me I have time it's still only 5:00
p.m. do I want to stream now
[Music]
it would not stop comparing it this
these kind of things of Skyward Sword
that was different
situation and has not since happened in
that form
[Music]
again I do have a little snack in the
fridge if I get hungry but even if this
takes four more hours like some said
three or four or two or
three uh that just just that's only 8
hours in
[Music]
total I've had longer
streams I don't know I just don't want
to like continue playing now and then
cut it off at a point where there's only
like 2 hours of gameplay
left you could spare everyone staying up
if you leave it for next time yeah I
know for a lot of you guys it's past
midnight or
[Music]
so Gathering all the pets I don't think
there's like that many that I'm missing
is
[Music]
there yeah it's oh four ah the esam
people oh my God there's so many EST
people staying
up holy [\h__\h] I feel bad for you guys I
usually I usually have good times for
you
see not good but like not this
bad
um yeah okay I think we split
it I guess we'll split L
it honestly if I finish this I don't
know if I finish this so early now I I I
wouldn't know like how to fill my my
schedule next week
maybe um one thing I want to do
though
is go to
[Music]
um here
join Arc no I think isn't it ending this
week anyway and I don't really want to
join it especially so
late New
[Music]
Vegas not right now I'm not feeling that
evil right now wait did she change her
location where is she
now where's Dragon Lady where did she go
did she tell me where she
went is this a hide and seek game now
where she
do you guys know where she is I think
she told me she went somewhere
else ah the reion where I find the other
one oh so somewhere icy let's explore
the Ice Area a bit more
then wait what
no at Le in Temple uh
where's
[Music]
that
maybe
heish what who was standing there just
now ah ah there she
is she turned her back on me didn't see
her for a
moment oh wait do I have to have to pet
out
[Music]
H this is her child voice is it
not
H the way she talks is this her child
did she forget that she grew up when she
was voicing these
lines is it because
[Music]
the VA for
Gore or can you get
here
right maybe when they were recording
this yeah they they they W like forgot
that she would already be adult at this
time CU this is a side quest so
yeah that's definitely a child
voice can you really do this
earlier even then if you're going to
make her grow up in the game and change
her voice you should consider that and
record two
[Music]
versions
oops they were a little bit
discombobulated
[Music]
oh rock climbing Pro I
see how
[Music]
convenient oh I think you're getting
those signals from me
[Music]
have to show her I
think look at this
little horse
pony yeah there we
[Music]
go
for observe the small dragon in front of
her
closely
okay you're
welcome didn't she ask the same thing
with the other one why does she want to
see it again later and at what point is
later can they
[Music]
evolve can they Evol ah thank you for
the Super Chat
[Music]
come but I maxed the Affinity is there
something else to
Max and as she moved places again
so
okay hey big dragon how you
doing what's up with him
[Music]
again oh he reacts to me being older
this is uh not main quest so this seems
to be a
thing that's optional huh
[Music]
Savage oh you don't know okay well
that's fine let's let's just let him die
guess I'll
[Music]
die no stop don't hurt my bird don't
hurt my
bird oh well that escalated quickly
I don't think he would fight
me he's easy at this stage oh there's
more than one stage
huh oh yeah everything's easy for
me maybe I accidentally untie his vines
with Fire magic
H could be could
be wa this one has base attack 4,000
this one only has 2,800 what
that's really
[Music]
strong he said in Japanese ah I got
summoned against my will again
bro oh wait
oopsy
accident what's this element
go just said
go
[Music]
for ah you know what I want to try what
we should try let's try summoning the
dragon dragon versus dragon dragon
de
go
go this one
[Music]
first
go so it should be
here this
one ah
this
[Music]
car so many
options okay let's try
what oh still it really a damn it now I
can't no I can't heal anymore no
[Music]
let's do a physical
attack go go go go go
go go g that was a
g g
oh no he
missed he's almost de I want to use my
dragon
no okay I don't really have to do this
can I afford it
now what 20% but
how 600 plus 20% of ah
if I have full
[Applause]
MP
oh even then you did the math okay well
then that is
unfortunate need to scale more MP
huh now I know what I need at
least
9,600 damage bro
[Music]
he needs physical therapy or not not
Physical Therapy but the therapy to like
relearn how to
walk I feel bad for bullying him
[Music]
this drop gives me 100
mp
um this one
oh H
[Music]
nice m
H wait so what happens now he's just
like recover recharging there for a
while good
luck I want to check one
[Music]
thing let's let's feed this thing a
little
[Music]
bit W this one this one's a
lot but
wait let's see if we need any materials
to make something ah oh yeah the old
spell book oh
oh don't think I can craft all of
this can I
[Music]
I could make this one but I'm missing a
few ones I could even make this
[Music]
one I need one more
of the schwitz arm okay I know where I
can get this one I'm going to go do that
really
quickly stalling the end
[Music]
why not just do this next time um
because I want to spend more time with
you
[Music]
guys p
why do you hate me so much guys never
mind it's just it's just a
[Music]
wo I got one
guard what what do you mean you could
write an essay on that didn't you say
you going on be nicer to me a while
ago what happened to
[Music]
that you'll be nice
okay hey I'm streaming at a good time
for you
or am I messing up your the sleep
schedule that you adjusted for me cuz
you love me so much that's why you pull
all nigh this all the time for
me and now you're mad because because
I'm giving you a normal time schedule to
live with for a while
[Music]
a great time for an East person with a
messed up sleep schedule that must be
really messed up
though I actually don't like this time
because I have class and stuff
a well as I said usually I think it'll
be more like evening time
actually I don't think I always stream
at this time
more like evening jst might be more more
common or earlier than today like a few
hours
earlier hey I can even get exp from this
one
[Music]
Yi wait
relocated to VOD gang since I moved to
night shift and know you're not VOD gang
yay
yipp I'm happy that I can bring bring
back some people who've been in VA gang
[Music]
forever I'm glad
can try to wake up more
early good good
good everybody gets a piece of the W
eventually cuz I am worldwide w
going to live in Japan time for 2 months
what for me I'm not I'm not here for 2
months don't think you need to do
that can I get him down with a krle
swing oh yeah oh the one hit already did
the
[Music]
trick okay
I wouldn't even say exactly 1.5 months
cuz uh
that's um
considering that's already taken in
account the time I will be gone after
Japan to a different place that I
mentioned if you
remember do you remember
[Music]
400 p.m. 4:00 a.m. let's
go yeah yeah the one with the other Ian
member soorry I really don't think it
will be a full 1.5 months in Japan
yeah maybe 1.337
[Music]
months
nice okay we probably got enough
stuff maybe I go
back that one still didn't
recharge how long does it take she now
it takes so much longer I think maybe it
was on
purpose for them to respawn at once so
fast because they knew I might need two
of the heads or maybe it was a
bug
H
weird should I fight the yeti
again he is protecting a path did I go
through that before don't
remember
[Music]
for
36,000 Oh
[\h__\h] forgot that was already out
there ah that was the dragon pet
path oh well okay wait I'm almost
[Music]
dead he has a nice
item which
[Music]
one talking to Luna again true we can do
that oh yeah maybe she also has some
side quest for me like the
[Music]
dragon die wait what the [\h__\h] just
happened did we
miss like we
missed I didn't pay attention H before I
go there I want to go back home once and
heal Luna has a whole side quest really
wait we have three training sessions
okay MP MP
MP and this
one which one do we get okay I don't
think we ever did that one meditation
did we did we how do I do it random
press oh okay pie pie pie pie
thinking of pie thinking of
strawberries strawberries and what was
that pie must have been something
else wow nice thoughts head
[Music]
empty it's strawberry pie that's all she
thinks
about pie pie strawberries M pie
strawberry pie I have a b pie I have a
strawberry ooh
strawberry pie
pie okay we finally got the mental
training stage
free let's go
[Music]
[Applause]
good job um need to
sneeze why so many sneeze
[Music]
today t
thanks nice
membership okay off to
meet
L stand
byai cat hair withdrawals yeah yeah yeah
yeah I need the cat hair in my lungs I
need it my my lungs are used to it by
now
side quest my friends Joe you have to
think higher and deeper and
further you simpleminded
K knock knock knock knock knock Do you
want to build
snowman do you want to hunt with me
what a coincidence I just killed
him don't tell me to kill him again we
have to wait for him to
respawn
no maybe it will automatically
respawn when she needs it
[Music]
maybe but what was the end of
that oh maybe we'll meet her
there sounds like we meet her
there I have respond for story
purpose yes wonderful all according to
Kaku actually not going to Kaku at all
if it was going by Kaku I wouldn't have
killed the yeti just before taking the
quest but that's
okay okay the other mobs have not
respawned the left one I just didn't
find she's there ah it's already dead is
that because I killed it just now or did
you take it down again
would be funny if it
was first I really I already killed him
twice before you
girl in fact did beat you to
it she is lacking critical
information wait where is she going now
where what did she say where she's going
now also I can't pass this is like relax
all over again what's yeah never mind he
was gone last time I I I already took
the path
before what's this
path H oh it's just the same said where'
she
go another
one get your poke
flu wa wait wait where's another ye
outside did I see that one before she
might actually beat me to that
one for
once ah The Dark One why would that one
be there
again wouldn't make any sense
honestly oh are these
yetties but not the ones that she wants
maybe past these
[Music]
ones I don't care I say relax because I
can never think of the other
name H
[Music]
it's a good name I agree Snorlax isn't
bad either though cuz he's
snoring and relaxing I think while
snoring that's what it's Snorlax
actually it's even that's like two words
we only have one word in it if you think
about it that
H not bad not
bad snow
relaxer yes
combination nice counter
[Music]
okay please tell me she's somewhere
there he's actually there again you can
fight that thing
again I beat her to it
then she just doesn't know she doesn't
know let's let her believe that uh she's
beating me to it
well it's not down yet the other one was
down when we arrived so it seems like
we're having trouble also his ass crack
seems to be going all the way to his
shoulder blades that poor
guy he missed you can counter you can
counter
[Music]
Luna wait that was audio B that was was
incredibly
loud oh did you Noti
this was not just in my ear right that
was in your ear too
[Music]
good
morning your reminder to not have
streams on max volume you might regret
it yeah I need
healing wait we can do the we can we
should can we do it
[Music]
now
yes oh oh
[Music]
8,900
okay for full
MP bar I don't know about
[Music]
that it should have been more
more if it was like 10K then
maybe maybe that would be worth
[Music]
it is a crit
yeah yeah the crit maybe it's worth it
[Music]
oh he's so slow we got so many turns
before him oh it's because of her ice
magic and nobody canceling
[Music]
it on everything yeah if it's a AE like
if there's more enemies on the
fields
yeah that might be good
is there any more yetis that we need to
visit I don't think
so
a but she does everybody needs a
friend everybody needs a
friend I will be your friend who was
inside of here again
ah this is what isn't this oh no one had
the Dragon one had the ne pet
[Music]
cat a purpose yeah she wants the the
item that they
drop she said it why you not listening
to
her chicken brain empty
it's okay chicken it's
okay I will do the listening for you you
don't have to think too hard you're
going to explode the last bra cell that
you
have we don't want that do we oh my God
girl is screaming while I'm being soft
with my and gentle with my chicken
it's okay chicken it's
[Music]
okay oh where would she be now is there
another
Yeti is she yet to be done with Yeti
hunting
but where could she be maybe she got
lost
[Music]
looking at the
map we went
there she's not
there
uh this place is a little
bit hard to get around cuz there's not
many connections to the other
layers what if I go down here
there was no other Yeti
though yeah we went here just
now there's nothing down here
right h
M try leaving the area and coming back
Really
okay I
goem I go
[Music]
him should I talk to her at the house
again oh what
what
what huh is she flexing her pet on
me where' you got that
from to be flexing
aace
[Music]
go okay
okay
sure sure am I I mean besides the turtle
I think all other pets are the same spe
right yeah yeah yeah wait wait let me
change I think they are all the
[Music]
same this one seems like it might be
fast is that fast doesn't feel very
fast there's
one there's a faster
one can we win with this
one
uhoh looka I don't have that one
right
straight uh-uh 3 2
1 E she got a head
start I think we're just
no she's faster she got a head start and
she's
faster H we need that other
pet where do we get
Thea
so can I get it yet illusion
[Music]
in the
temple in the plains
[Music]
a recipe written on an old piece of
paper oh tough soup was added to the
spell book wow okay wait the planes are
this small wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait I killed it the first time I fought
it oh ah yeah cuz I mean the name did
sound familiar to me so I felt like oh
did I not find it before
the world can wait we need a faster do
to race
yes
[Music]
soup where could it be
if Justice was the fastest Mount nah he
would
probably ah act all
[Music]
up this one actually feels a tiny bit f
faster than the other one but maybe
that's my
imagination go north from where
[Music]
in
here you scared me that jump scin cuz
I'm looking at the map and maybe if I go
past
him was it there I don't remember where
we fought
[Music]
it I might be
there I don't know
[Music]
ah uh up and down a really long path up
up from where though from here no right
I'm probably fighting this one for
nothing but we got another Hercules
Stone which is nice
where does this lead some cave
H what the
[\h__\h] wait this is the lightning horn
that I saw in one of the crafts wait I
didn't fight this one ever that's was
good that I went this
way
oh a light noer was blackened by a
taking a dozen lightning strikes to its
horns
wow the horn is like a lightning catcher
its entire body exudes lightning energy
[\h__\h] poor guy let's
let's let's free him oh what a chunky
boy let's free him from his
suffering um might be actually pretty
easy can we
summon him can we capture
him no right
you can't okay so we just want to kill
him and get the horn let's
go it is my pleasure
[Music]
another
one something in the air man something's
in the air
it
seems my nose also has been a little bit
more runny than normally when normally
is not runny at all thanks for the
memberships and what am I
[Music]
doing maybe my cats are thinking of me
I think
[Music]
so light noer horn let's
go can I ride you no no it doesn't offer
me rud you should piggyback me
[Music]
ah all right I shall walk like a normal
person um so where the [\h__\h] do I
[Music]
go wait
ahuh no I thought this was like some
kind of secret path
now is there another one there
[Music]
maybe next to the bird
stair over
here and then
there oh yeah that might be it there we
[Music]
go n that
thing ah yeah I can see why they might
make this the fastest
one it has wings and it looks a bit like
chle Boo inspired but also goat it's
still
go
um careful
now place in home
feed feed my human
pet that's
funny kind of messed up though the can I
even not kill him y yes okay uh wait but
what do I do now if I hit him again
he'll die but the mind control is not
activated
[Music]
yet
um
[Music]
um maybe I have a weak
bump no
no
ah
[Music]
yeah we can see how much
that
hits
okay okay there we go
smort stop hitting me
[Music]
we did
it okay makes it move very quickly Yahoo
let's go back to the icy Fields uh which
were over
here got him
I totally forgot about this one I never
tried catching it again after we killed
it by
accident there it
is I feel like the other artworks are
way
more now about this one not so
much must have been drawn by different
artists cuz this looks very
sketchy I wonder what it eats maybe also
ugly bird meat
do you oh
okay passes its turn to to its
master
I
okay
oh girl the moment she sees me riding in
with that she should know it's over
[Music]
what was that pie
Berry Yahoo
[Music]
bye-bye smell that stinky
ass
smell
I I like the way it runs it looks funny
from behind
mind well well well
[Music]
H didn't we want to tell her something
about Robin
or maybe not in the Side Story maybe
back in the main
[Music]
story never trust said to when she says
no I will not forgive you she's already
forgiven you at that
[Music]
point well seems like it's
working oh we do tell
her m
[Music]
fore is that what makes her join the
death squad too cuz he's
[Music]
there might be difficult to talk when
you freezing
[Music]
for
okaye for
[Music]
speci
oh because I love pie and Beres
[Music]
e
fore
foree
[Music]
spee
what
[Music]
for you know we knew already that her
name is
Lucia pretty sure about that
one
H okay going home
[Music]
can you Vis Duna now I don't know I just
left um I want to look into
crafting just doing some side stuff and
then we can go I wanted to I think
[Music]
make this
stuff I can skip this one and make this
one already should
I no point in making this one
[Music]
right Skipper
Skipper okay besides
[Music]
that wait what about the Horn uh I think
something was able to be made with the
horn this one oh aha
yeah that's the lightning horn that we
got right yeah
finally wait we could have gotten that
so much earlier I just realized just
because I missed that one mob I thought
I was going through things very
thoroughly what's the synopsis of the
game wait what do you mean the whole
synopsis or or what we did
today what do you need to know
soup the [\h__\h] oh it increases HP and
strength by quite a bit that's why it's
I thought it was a normal healing
item was
not we could totally make this one
couldn't
[Music]
we no wait where do you get ciron am I
able to get ciron yet have I got it
before
[Music]
Dragon
Valley Dragon
Valley what what do this
[Music]
do Dragon
Valley
Dragon huh
[Music]
uh we we just made
uh uh what did we just make this
[Music]
one nice slap it on
there um
[Music]
M ooh I don't think I did this one
before did I pushups ah I
did how's it work again
ah button
mashing push-ups with a stone on my back
I'm so hardcore
so
strong couldn't be you huh
chickens try
this try this and die
trying you're not going to do it you're
not going to be able to do
it easy show me then I want to see
[Music]
why not sleep a little
bit and
then I was going to check out the Dragon
Valley I'm not going to stop I may not
be continuing with main quest but
I trying to do some other things fire
cave Blackstone
cave do I know where that is Dragon
[Music]
Valley maybe
not near the dark stone dark stone what
[Music]
there ah here
near near is it maybe up there the one
point I didn't
explore or should I go this
way ah there was there two
paths ooh oh wait when he responds is
that when the quest continues with him
and we get another fight
[Music]
ohuh Ian conert live viewing let's go oh
Dragon Valley House of the Dragon House
of the Dragon House of the Dragon House
of the Dragon House of the Dragon this
Dragon Stone literally just Dragon Stone
whoa but probably with this many dragons
probably even before House of dragon
starts playing because like there's
still so many actually no no no this is
valyria valyria Valia
cuz uh that's where all like dragons
were right and the dragon Lords and like
even even more
dragons old Val
yeah the good old times oh look who's
[Music]
here thanks for the
ra drunk
[Music]
it sounds very dangerous it had its own
soundtrack hello
waiters
waiters fight some dragons with me come
on have you guys seen the new house of
Dragon
episode have you have you why not why
not you got to wow so many
dragons look at the one up there did you
see that's probably the one I need to
fight I
assume 12,000 okay
okay 12,000 per
Dragon bring out some amount
dragons and let's try out the new the
new one
2,000
damage total wait that's so [\h__\h]
weak what
why at least it makes him slower maybe
for the sake of making them slow I have
to give up
some some damage that I would
normally be getting
most of the spikes
missed
rip okay let's not get rid of the effect
let's do lightning
6,300 in
[Music]
total the spikes
missed okay
[Music]
two turns
baby nice
CR oops that's not the one I wanted to
use but okay it
works we got
cir okay wait I already have the mat
from these mobs
okay but might as well go to the top why
not right
do I need to
heal uh was there no healing stone
actually somewhere and I missed it
maybe no there a path here
too oh oh what the [\h__\h] is this T-Rex
dragon unmeasurable let's go skill
element
none skill issue
defense Element Rock sounds so kind of
primitive okay I heal and then we fight
this I'm sure whatever it drops is also
useful to
us
okay t-rex with wings
basically it's when dinosaur make love
with
dragon
yes what is why isn't there more like
stories where like there's dragons and
dinosaurs and then breathing with one
another maybe we need more of
[Music]
that m
[Laughter]
ah sorry brain
empty I don't have anything
[Music]
Rocky but that's
okay
uh only one okay
[Music]
how much wait this one wait do you guys
see he has over
100k ni question
marks are
six this is the first I
think
okay okay maybe youbye but should be
fun aim hard please
very
necessary uh yeah okay might be a little
bit rough looking how slow relatively
slow as HP goes down
but as long as we don't get hit too
often so that we can't keep up with our
uh healing or defense a
yeah we should be okay
okay still have the shield should be
gone next turn and we can hit with the
arrow and with a big
meteor
action and with a
crit wait wait wait wait wa who who who
W Who whoo
whoo yeah okay Shield is
gone straight into your heart right
baby
metor lightning straight to my heart oh
yeah now I'll let you go uh oh no never
let you go oh oh
oh but I'm not using lightning D's
gravity field is
ready
um this will make like his ability to
move means basically his agility is is
uh lower he already has pretty low
agility
so I don't know should we use
it doesn't take up
anything oh no his agility wasn't oh no
it is but he's I feel like he's still in
the same order but maybe he can't attack
anyway when it's his
turn extra slow that Stacks with freeze
I could replace it uh with my own freeze
but Justice is just going to cancel it
out I don't think he can move yeah
that's what what I would expect
now now okay
not sure for
Giants Well I just noticed dragon flies
up really high to attack him
cute did we just skip him I think we
skipped
him we're still active
he won't come back until his next turn
right we're fine I
[Music]
think I
survived okay okay okay
uh
hi pie pie pie p pie pie pie
please pie pie pie ooh by by
please should we wait for this until
next turn or is it worth it using it
now wait I do get another turn before he
attacks so I'm going to wait
all right all right he's going to die
he's so going to die I don't even need
this one but let's do it cuz we rarely
see it I wish lightning b
11k h he survived with one HP
basically jonia ooh I think I can make
the lightning armor of that probably
oh there's something in the back here
too they call a dragon egg I can be
Daenerys coner viewing reservation ah
you got it for because you were
reminded
nice you guys are going to be watching
it like in a in a cinema kind of place I
suppose
have fun with the other the other Korean
fans did you get the last dragon already
yeah I think so that was probably the
last one we got
um three of them or two
[Music]
three got this
one this one is there another
one maybe there's another one in here
but the Dragon Lady is here
so if there's another one then it's
probably in
here what's
here this this weird
spot a fire breathing
one did I get it
[Music]
already sideway ah okay see as I thought
there's one
here I should have summoned ah I should
have
summoned can I survive another attack
from
them I think
so One Missed
yay I think I'm just going to finish
this Dragon Valley and then craft a
little bit more and then we're going to
probably stop around there unless I get
another idea of what I want to do
urgently
okay Taki Ki Taran Ki Taran tary
Nashi tager Nashi Ki
I'm blind blind blind
here not
turkey or
Nene how dare you define
me I can't I can't get both dragons out
at once
no oh
[Music]
what is Dragon
B
[Music]
what
huh both far
what oh
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
what he I don't see any other path
besides that wait what did I go that way
why I see this path only
now okay that's where the little dragon
is
[Music]
oh Skipper
Skipper Skipper
[Music]
Skipper why is there nothing
here maybe something only spawns when I
kill the other dragons or the Dragon at
the
top would that make sense if I kill
these ones will they spawn [\h__\h] I need
to
heal Dragon Star strong
this wait I should have summoned no
that
[Music]
hurts right inside the entrance to
Dragon valy
what near the
dragon near the Dragon
Lady n
chance I'm not that blind to the map but
okay I think something will have to
spawn over there eventually maybe after
I kill the big
dragon but for
now maybe our return to find the other
[Music]
path with my face covering everything
yeah yeah yeah that's exactly how I see
it because I play for obs
yeah yeah yeah yeah well she was
standing I thought where was she
standing closer to the entry
h a that
one oh there's healing there okay let's
remember
[Laughter]
that no wonder she was sensing something
wait now there's both of the dragons in
one
place wow wow
wow and now there's
not unless you see my Kotori as a dragon
which maybe you want to see it like that
oh that one's cute that's quite the
classic simple design compared to the
others so that's
fine I'll take
it 500 damage so we should be able to do
one more
hit
okay accidental crit would have been my
downfall oh was that I didn't even
notice it this time
uhuh suddenly
what
Dron suddenly loud
sound hey I got it
lady ah [\h__\h] I need to show
[Music]
her damn
it it left
me it left me
[Music]
moment no membership
no
no come back
sne no
stks Trevor was already ready he already
had his finger on the
mouse that weak Dragon don't
worry doesn't does I I know I said
before she looks like she is like from
aier but did I say that she kind of
gives me the same Vibes that
um those
uh did they have a name not just a their
nam's name but the the the what they are
name they look like the ones that I
found the hottest with the thick
fighs you know what I mean you know what
I mean
right in Risa the hot
ones she looks like them because she has
this like bright pastel purple hair and
then the white ass
skin yeah you know who me yeah yeah yeah
yeah
yeah the Orin the
Orin loved them they were so
hot studying for 5 years suddenly all of
your progress is done in two days
because of me
[Music]
wa an ancient artifact imbu with
powerful mind control Power allows you
to summon a pet during comp a or all one
or all all
pets up to a maximum number
[Music]
or four pets no cost
a heart limit instead okay okay
okay what about four Pets Plus no
cost Justice or does he count in
that I think I'm normally able to get
four
anyway with
Justice might be good though
yeah the high cost
ones true
[Music]
that's also the child
voice you can't get here as a child can
you even if you can would
you go this far as a
child is that them in the special slots
please say yes yes okay I don't have to
replace any of these
nice
okay I shall go
up up up
for I've done it on ng+ oh
okay before she even knows about DS
interesting he
[Music]
oh it starts we're starting with the
little dragon one is already out
okay this one cost free even though the
base attack is
[\h__\h] fre
all my
dragons and and and and the
mask that isn't even what how much cost
was the mask also free maybe I don't
know
ooh at least with the upgrade even if it
doesn't do that much more damage it hits
a lot in this angle at least five of
them
wait if oh God they
might wait I might
die I might
die mask was four okay
okay I might
die ah yes I will
die I survived
[Music]
very very
dangerous
yum okay it's looking better now
[Music]
that one's still not Dead come on now we
got to kill
it
okay
oh y
uh this one's good wait I forgot that
was
no o that's a lot of damage that I just
wasted okay yeah I have barer
a no need to minmax every single fight
if it works it
[Music]
works crit
incoming watch this
17 17h
where's the
Healer where it go H
here wow wow wow w wow wow wow wow wow
wow w
w wow wow wow wow wow
wow oh it landed from me it came down
from me let's go let's go let's go it's
a Dragon
Star h
let's
go if the other the TX Dragon had over
100k this one definitely has two
but hopefully not that much
more oh my mouse
how how will I Faire
we'll be fine that Dragon looks pretty
tough the ancient Lightning Dragon it
belongs to the strongest p of Dragon
it's a little different to the normal
lightning dragons it looks almost
solemn you mean the dragon that lives
near all Temple that's a Lightning
Dragon is but it's one of the modern
generation that one over there is
ancient and original wow it has been
sitting there for thousands of years
guarding its Master's Relic
ah
wait wait
let is this the one that we need for the
uh beard
guy 220k o I'll give it a try
anyway ow that's interesting looking is
that a sword I don't use
swords Legend has that its Master died
fighting an evil entity
and just before he died he gave the
Dragon A Relic that contain his
powers I know that Legend I read it in a
book so that's the dragon it was about I
thought the Lightning Dragon I saw near
my house was a legendary one the modern
Lightning Dragon evolved by absorbing
the lightning that struck near a r
Temple anyway this is a powerful ancient
species Don't Go Near it if it can be
avoided it can be avoided but I'll go
anyway
[Music]
guess I'll
die oh it has
begun he did not even give me first
[Music]
turn
yikes can't use that yet so
W he gets two
turns
CH I have to slow him down wait they
didn't did they ask me if I H was going
to use an item did I skip it
[\h__\h] I'm going to unsummon the red
dragon because I I don't want anything
to cancel out the IR
nice and we need the armor
perfect cuz I'm going to hit him with
ice but I might not survive anyway so
I'm thinking maybe magic
Shields at
least for a chance of
survival okay slow down he only gets one
more turn and I'm
dead this might be difficult
cold oh oh she's bringing me back to the
battle uh okay thanks uh I don't think
uh worth it uh but
okay oh but look we're getting so many
turns
now what
happened yeah first time seeing it
m i can't heal unless I skip a a
turn I can defense
[Music]
still nice
this is
fine this is
[Music]
fine this this
fine this is
[Music]
fine this is f
f ah what oh we're
flying whoo whoa whoa I think all of
those hit cuz he's
big okay good stuff guys good
stuff don't lose your Shield girl don't
lose your
Shield after this you can lose it oh oh
oh yeah 11,000 * 4 he did he just do
44,000
damage or did I add zero to all of that
and it was actually 1, 100 I think it
was 11,000 per hit
there yeah okay you might need your
shield on for that but he's already
passed
50% okay okay okay okay
okay but does this come
back does this never come back I don't
remember if it comes
back uh but we have a crit with this
[Music]
one ah should I have tarred him with the
crit [\h__\h] I can still Timar
him Nexus dck um at least that uh stops
him from
[Music]
attacking is Tamar worth it more than
this
one maybe not because I will use all my
mp from Tamar and I might still need it
I don't
know but okay one thing I would do for
this
turn cuz I can't heal right now is put
on Magic Shield I have full MP so it
should protect protect
me I do get another turn though before
he
attacks maybe we're fine maybe I don't
need the shield
now nice nice there was one crit in
there I think we can do it I think we
can do it even though we we
um made a mistake in the beginning
[Music]
okay gravity field is
ready the gravity field prevents him
from attacking for sure right so I don't
have to
[Music]
heal
right slows him down massively
yeah should be
okay go go we can do
it I'm I'm surprised I thought it was
over right at the
beginning thanks mommy for Reviving me
and giving me hope that I can do
it believe in yourself
okay okay wait what's ready what's ready
what did it say was ready was anything
ready at all no it was probably just
reminding me of the the
durok will his his next turn will also
be wait he might revive until next turn
right I should heal up at
[Music]
least just in case
my friend is in love with me your friend
is in love with
me that's how I should have said it uh
thank you
friend oh let's go let's go let's go
let's go let's go let's go let's go
let's
go Dragon this
nuts no he gets no no no n we please a
was
close H spe no no no no okay okay I
thought I thought he was attacking again
oh [\h__\h] we made
it Max stage on the combat thingy
whatever that yep oh we did
it oh that could have really
ended oh right oo W
wo wo
W
camera we could have really died
there
she so this is The Relic the ancient
Lightning Dragon was trying to protect
and we we killed him for what for this
thing I feel bad this is
evil Legends are incredible I wonder how
such a secret fact was passed down as a
story when according to the legend the
blade should glow blue
h no budget for blue
e how do what what do you call it
again having a stroke right now
e LEDs
thanks perhaps it has lost its power
over time Mar Shield weapons have their
powers purposely deactivated
but why to prevent it leaking away over
time judging by the L of flow it appears
the sword is falling asleep it seems
like a strong weapon is there a way to
wake it back up I can feel the faint
magic of lightning how about a lightning
strike in that
case I'll make my strongest lightning B
ever
come did it work it worked
noise oh it
didn't interesting it's definitely
responding but then it's light fight
Fates again a lightning strike does seem
to be the key though do I need my my
most uh powerful lightning attack still
cuz I don't have it
yet except it might need the right kind
of lightning for the
sword oh while I got the weapon a rally
guarded by an ancient Lightning Dragon
that used to be Bel to its Master
currently the sword is slumbering and
has lost its light it looks still very
nice the fact that this monster respawns
maybe makes us feel less evil and bad
for killing this pretty I'm I'm sure
pretty
innocent ancient dragon that really
shouldn't be
killed because it's history
and you know it what did it do for me to
kill it I don't think it's
bad it's pretty [\h__\h] up if we kill
something that has been alive for so
long this it sad it sad it's been alive
since the beginning of
time you shouldn't you shouldn't kill
something that's so wise and
knowledgeable
and
valuable very very
stupid very stupid are we the baddies
yeah
yeah I would almost say
so now do you think something spawned
over there
no this is where it was right where
[Music]
H no that's not where it
was
huh I'm
confused maybe that is where it was
oh well what do you who was above it
okay let me let me let
me can't write you right
okay speed
[Music]
um this
way oh
yes nothing
H
why well let's kill this maybe something
will spawn if I kill them who
knows could be
[Music]
weak
disappointed for a quest
a yeah could be
the
[Music]
egg yeah it's weirdly empty there should
be something
there I'll try to inspect the maybe in
that place I don't know if you're saying
that because you know something will
happen or if you're
just
guessing we can
[Music]
try something spawn
now
no
um where is j
cannot use this tool
now
okay this must be something out of my
reach at this
moment it's a
tool
okay that's fine
P how Dragon going extin extinct yeah
let's not have her have a crossover with
House of the
Dragons although they go extinct
seemingly in that world anyway even
without her
help doesn't quite sound like something
you would say doesn't
mask
um let's see uh we're going to make some
stuff not
[Music]
this ah we have to cir but I'm still
missing the other things wait I can
make one of
these do I really have to go out to get
that ball that one single
ball can we get our hands on the on the
red flaming thingy there ever
[Music]
I think we can get the
horns or no don't know but
this ah we built this and we can make
this uh this armor makes me
slower it should be worth it
[Music]
right new armor finally
the normal Lightning Dragon have I not
touched or found the normal Lightning
Dragon
[Music]
yet well maybe that's something for next
time as well as getting that one
Fireball oops see
[Music]
yeah think I'm pretty
satisfied got to put on the armor before
I forget and will never remember next
[Music]
time
ooh plus 60
defense plus 20% of that other
[Music]
thing physical resistance probably minus
5% magical resistance okay and a minus
10 this one gives
Plus
M okay wait can I put on the sword
already oh yeah but it's it's pretty
much
[Music]
useless I mean the minus on the magic is
normal for the
swords but yeah
not a
h need to find a special place to awaken
is accessible maybe well that's for next
time so next time we awaken the sword we
find The Last
Dragon we finished
again how about
that and two of those things are
optional wouldn't even have to do it
would probably after being able to kill
that boss I'm sure I'm sure the pulp has
less HP that
Dragon I would
imagine am I wrong or
what
[Music]
although did I already craft it a
away or did did I have to take it
out no right I think it's gone oh it's
the ancient like ah he wants a normal
one okay
okay you're going to mop the floor with
the pulp
yeah
gladly it's will be my
pleasure well I already saved that I
didn't do anything so I probably could
stop
here did it get oh no wait I thought we
could back to the loading screen wait I
want to see I want to see what it looks
like
now it's become tradition let me start
the game
again let's see move
oh yeah Justice is there now and the
little witch and uh the goat the
Chad and Olivia is here in her new form
okay so that looks like three more
editions was the mask there before
W did you see something just
now whoa
whoa
wao wait which one is
that it looks light
thingy which one is that the hell is
that the it's not the ancient one we
just killed is
it w a
[Music]
Tim
uhhuh just my pet chilling don't be
scared guys nothing to be wary of or
nervous
about the wing flaps are creating a nice
wind that's almost like a tornado
perhaps hold
on just put on your seat
belt when is Michelle joining the
starting
screen yeah maybe when she gets out of
[Music]
prison s this
wonderful where so many where so
many there's barely any space for me
now but I belong here
too h
[Music]
looking for my
DMs okay
it's been 6 hours of this game we stop
game maybe we read Super Chat let's go
where did I stop I think I stopped
somewhere Midway
through I didn't prepare any other
screen yet so we're going to stay on
here
[Music]
Yi this fits better yeah I really like
it cuz of the music and all
that why
[Music]
not wait so did somebody
say
um I stretched two more did I two more
really 58 from K with guest thank
[Music]
you okay 58
Super Chat reading
time should I write it down
too
[Music]
text Super Chat reading
time it's super chat reading time Super
Chat reading
time super CH reading super CH reading
supering diing supering supering
supering diing
supering supering supering
diing super chatting super chatting
super chatting
diting super rating
supering
[Music]
oopsie la la la la la
Hey ow
uh can't change the space in
between I think
[Music]
here what is this ah a this basing
sucks does it look better in any other
font probably not
[Music]
this is okay this okay it's
okay
me on the right side but
blurry
me mle
[Music]
you mean
Livia also I don't think we I think I
know what you
mean don't think we have been confirmed
yet that that one executor is mle
[Music]
okay okay I'm going to
continue thank
Youk
you the pinky happy birthday k I love my
super ultra hypers Sonic
[Music]
Kam okay I tried to see if you spelled
something with those capitalized letters
but I don't think you
did
no no you didn't or did
you e e no it didn't I looked at it from
every
angle I'm reading too much into it
I guess you're not as smart as I thought
you
were thank you so much
B for your love I hope I can continue
being your Kami ooshi please let me be I
want to
be Canon exent oh
Sada thank you for the red super chat I
finally got my first limited set even
via geek check
oh the merch set is so good again I
looking forward to seeing all the K with
the happies and and fans at meetups yeah
the fans yes also thanks for everyone
helping out uh the other kfb oh was
there helping
people that's sweet thank you for
getting the merchandise you're lucky
getting the geek check one because that
was sold out
immediately oh my God good job I'm happy
for you well
deserved yeah I'm also excited to see
you guys in the happies and with the fan
using it when it gets too hot when you
watch
me now there will be so many so many waa
happies but they're all nice but
obviously I want to encourage you guys
using the official one of course but
until then still still going to take
like what six months so until then you
can use the other Wawa happy I guess
that uh they made
recently we got some extra unlimited
sets for people who can't get them now
but but it's still on sale right it's
still on sale or but you mean for people
who are out of money right now but maybe
they got their money after it's
done
selling that's nice so considerate wow
kfp so sweet good night boss are you
going to sleep
already no okay I don't know what time
it is over there but probably
reasonable thank you for
watching new eggs in the future
a thank you that's so
nice stons future
stons I hope you will be able to get rid
of
them yeah t thank
you milk and
[Music]
fringo that's of all thanks for the chat
happy fourth birthday kiaa even though
it's a day late that's okay loving this
K okay the birthday merch is amazing I
can't worry to wear the happy Cy meetups
come to day thank you yeah happy happy
happy happy looking forward to it
[Music]
too thank you for buying my merchandise
and supporting me with super chap to as
well really appreciate it thanks for
celebrating my birthday with
me as
always my sweet
jimins m
danop
[Music]
meatball
Rene than soon happy joyful birthday Ki
is a pinky worth staying so late for the
stream this merch is so beautiful and
the happy Art is amazing right I didn't
even hesitate to get it have a good
healthy happy day thank you no
hesitation I do try to always make my
merchandise worth
it yeah and interesting
the next one is going to be a little bit
dorky and silly for the anniversary but
I think very desirable as
well so happy you got hook Papa to do
art again yeah it was about
time and he drew me so
cool very
nice thank you so much for getting the
merch Renee
[Music]
thanks for the red super chat a
prolonged happy birthday Chef I actually
managed to order one of the limited
merch sets woo I figured out how to use
Tor time oh thank God so excited for
that well for anybody who hasn't set up
tel yet uh and would lives in Europe
just so you know now is a good time to
set up everything for the next merch
sales for anniversary merch if you don't
have any other way of getting it and
we're thinking of doing it but it was
too late last time or
so if you want to get like limited then
you know time is of the
issue anniversary well now that you ask
me I don't know if it I actually I don't
know maybe it will not be limited I
forgot I said I only want to do one of
them but then maybe I got
um something to doing it for
both time is of the essence did I say
issue
oops I try to limit my future super
chats a bit so I can save up some money
for Atlanta oh I wish you the best for
the coming months wa thank
you you want to go to Atlanta
oo traveling over
continents thank you for considering
that then it shall be excused the lack
of stons Super Chat stons ston
chats Atlanta sounds like
fun I hope you can make it good luck
with that thank you
Ro
[Music]
epic oh July 7th
congratulations nice place chicken thank
you for the R I love you my Kami oi
forever happy birthday W I love the
merch so much I got the limited merch
yooo yipp no regets following and
supporting you to many more years of kfp
and you thank you so much for being you
and creating such a wonderful Community
via
LP weren't you also at the L of dur
Rings
Fang hope you had
fun thank you so much chicken aab you're
so
sweet viala chicken
okab thank you for the big Super Chat
and for getting the limited merch yay I
will sign your name name no not your
name my signature no names for that one
but I'll sign it with my
love what was his birthday oh happy
belated birthday birthday on during the
Lord of drinks thing you mean right
congratulations let's go you're older
let's go
[Music]
MK
cross thanks for the red super chat
happy EXC birthday M
yeah I extended my own birthday cuz I
can no one can stop me thank you so
much you should extend yours too next
time why
not he had a kiaha cake did I see that
maybe not boohoo 72 fre dun py than
Flappy Boy Thanks for the red super chat
happy birthday take two to the best boss
a chicken could ask for you're are hero
and our sunshine and still we are the
ones getting presents look look at Night
Fever and bica hyped me into Oblivion
and I'm already in love with the rubber
chicken it was a really hype K wasn't it
I had so much fun good songs good energy
all
[Music]
over I was Unstoppable B during
bica I need to go ID don't meeting but
I'm
stalling to finish this anyway thank you
and have fun with the rubber chicken
when it wives take many baths with the
chicken the rubber chicken it likes
water it leaves it fries in
water Flappy Boy Flappy chicken
K the Dodge guy D thank
you and James love
D Hulu thanks for the red chat excellent
thank
you
Hulu thank
you may Fri for the r Jad your
orangeness oh you say it like that your
orangeness
it would seem to be the time for Jubilee
Ah that's what that means I forgot about
that
meaning for this day is the day of your
birthday but please we must not be late
for the Masters outside that are singing
in your name opens door look they are
tearing at each other oh tearing at each
other for and you happy oh one of those
is mine no no Panic there's enough for
everybody you can still get one link is
up and the pined
comment and in the description if you
want one of the happiest there's no need
to fight over
it your orangeness yes yes that is me
I'm I know I'm very very
generous with the clothing that I offer
to you I don't want you to freeze I
don't want you to suffer I want you to
to feel the warm embrace of the Phoenix
that is uh on top of the happy to give
you the warmth that you wouldn't have
otherwise yes I care for you
deeply let me hug you and maybe choke
you uh hug
[Music]
you yeah don't forget to wear
pants the Happ is not enough it's not
enough thank you for right girl nice
Super
Chat thanks for the red super chat happy
birthday hopefully you could actually
enjoy it even outside of the stream by
the way the fat is absolutely genius
merch idea but SAS tentu as
always to bad it will probably arrive in
Winter since you're just too hot I'd
kind of need it
now yeah me too I would need it now too
but how about you do a vacation in
Australia or so
then you can use it right
away in the sber or go to the mold defs
in the samber then you can use
it don't choke the chicken why not some
of you guys are surely into it but I was
just going to do it to kill you and eat
you well or you could just go to the gym
and then run and get hot and then use
the fan in the gym
huh will be useful for you yeah
[Music]
yeah the benevolent oress has thought of
you and thinks of you in her prayers
that the Australian Summers may be kind
to
you and has offered a supportive item to
get you through the heat waves
[Music]
Amen to the
Wawa eh what do you mean that means
something y
by what the
[\h__\h] why make something you buy out of
something just so random and and
sweet okay there's nothing sweet about
it but hi
that's not my fault we don't have to
follow all of these slang
things is that
sweet I know I know yeah
I same with the Cucumber B man I
didn't [\h__\h]
that thank you
pal Sly thank you for the red chat thank
you for the K this one felt really
special it was nice to see so many
quests join in quests join in
quests
guests
oh oh the que looks like a g and I still
read it as as a proper Q it didn't auto
correct in my
brain lots of vble love also you look
that gorgeous in the happy oh wow oh wow
I was lucky enough to get the limited
set from gej oh another lucky European I
couldn't be
[Applause]
happier or S is it more like e or
cin thank
you thank you thank you thank you I
don't know did I say rsh which one was
it who or
he who or
he or
he or first one H oh okay so it's smell
like
okay I'm guessing that means happy
birthday thank you so much diple looking
forward to seeing you dressed all up in
the Happ
happy I'm a team beep than than than
thanks for the chat happy birthday too
enjoyed a lot this K thank
you thank you for being there I'm glad
you enjoyed
it py D just another kfp d n thank you
for the red CH happy birthday VA my
queen and only Kami oi wow thank you for
always you're always hard work and I
really appreciate you for everything you
did for it wish you have a great year
V oh I remember that thank
you thank you thank you for the
support yeah Wawa's birthday also kind
of marks almost half of the Year being
over or like pretty much half of the
Year gone by it's like half
time thank you
for making this you're great so far
[Music]
than hi music thanks for the rested chat
happy birthday I'm almost finished the
second gift almost okay well now it's
been like almost the whole month what
about now hos did you finish
it did you finish it did I see it or
hear
it don't think
so you're going to wait until my
anniversary now or
what I wonder what you're cooking I'll
let you cook some more don't forget
about
it more orchestral music would be cool
anything I'm welcoming
[Music]
anything King of the prity I'm happy to
hear
so m how thank you motivational kiss Max
will the first D human Extang looking
for the top D seos oh I feel like I
haven't seen your name in a while in
here happy birthday looking forward to
another great year thank you for the red
super chat I'm also looking forward to
it I'm sure you're just lurking a little
bit or so you're definitely around thank
you so much for sing
here thank you soon
cute than G thanks for the red chat
happy birthday boss this has been such a
great birthday party once again I'm glad
you are my Koshi all of the songs are
amazing I'll treasure the happy as I got
a second so I won't risk messing up the
one for display
ooh always nice to have one
extra for display and maybe as a backup
h
smart thank you you could make a waa
Museum in the future maybe with your
contributions thank you so much have fun
with
it thank you I wish I have an extra
backpack now what did you mess up the
other one eh did it break you can fix it
maybe you can sew it when if there's a
hole or something you can sew it I don't
know the inside tour already what okay
tours can be fixed
chin creates the current gu
Museum possibly he is a walking kiaha
Museum
a a thank you Chris R I wish you the
best Chris
[Music]
R you're welcome anytime here for more
cheering
up uh did I give G in a kiss here's
another one just in case p t
auku thank you for the pinky happy
birthday t h this was so much fun really
enjoyed the show wish you to the next
year lots of fun successful events life
performances also new Banger songs and a
lot of new chickens in kfp we love you
than you so much I hope so do we need
more more chickens more more more more I
have big plans with these
chickens yes need more of those fluffy
butts around
me so let's try to get my name out there
huh with your
help KF be
strong Sil speed action thank you and
Unown thank you for the pinky listening
to you singing always makes me happy
your singing is just the absolute best
love you wa thank you I'm glad you think
so I did have lots of fun with these
songs thank you for being there and
cheering me on as always I can count on
you thank you
soon I finished these now
oopsie I
hungry and I want to go to Idol meeting
so I think I'll stop
here those were a couple more Reds and
pinks so think we made
progress
um
[Music]
Sal let me
see tomorrow
ah I am thinking of doing a member
stream tomorrow
[Music]
M
yeah in the
evening we could continue to watch along
or we take a break and do something else
I don't know
yet cuz I don't know I'm feeling maybe
you guys need a little break I want to
do something
else uh yeah around this time
this very
time a
[Music]
PA yeah no I don't know I
mean
n I'll I'll try to decide soon soon soon
soon ASAP
[Music]
yeah we're going to have to get for
regardless
y chocolate and Sonia thank you what you
stayed up this whole time thank
you how late is it are you PSD or estd
or
CSD
based okay so yeah members tomorrow um
just so you get an idea of the rest uh
thur
day uh will be the off collap I'm pretty
sure it's going to happen I just need a
fourth person right now and that
shouldn't be an issue too much um but
I'm probably not going to do it in the
studio but just
here uh in my current accommodation so
it might not be
like the most like it might be a little
bit
scuffed just so you know because I don't
know I need another chair like I have
three chairs at
most and we just have one mic but if we
cuddle close together it should be
okay
yeah um but headphones like only one
person will be able no wait I have
another check so if somebody else brings
also another set of headphones they
could use another head headset um and
also not I've I've noticed like for
example narissa she's not coming but
she's the type of person who doesn't use
headphones and I've s seen more and more
a trash can no so the thing is I have
the tiniest ever trash can only one you
can't even sit on there it's so low it's
like below my
knees so tiny not going to make people
sit on that I'm going to I'm going to
get another chair
thing I'm going to borrow it and then uh
Friday no stream I have the whole day
like
working
um and long long long long long long day
in the
studio
[Music]
yeah and then
so this the
weekend I had something there but seems
like that's gone up inin air so I still
have to think about what I'm going to do
in the on the
weekend okay so now you have a rough
idea
[Music]
maybe you still be able to bring out the
schedule today otherwise tomorrow
hopefully but for now that's it in
German we say V in thanks for watching I
had fun with first spring I'm glad
everything's working fine with my setup
too so let's have a comfortable
time this week
bye-bye guys good
night sleep now
[Music]
rest e
I
[Music]