[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
hello the tales of her eyes official
ambassador to the English region is back
y good
evening good day sir and ladies how's it
going welcome to today's stream
I am here to introduce you to uh
not released yet new Tales of game tales
of luminaria yay
this one is a phone game uh so I mean it
doesn't need to be a phone I guess an
iPad wouldn't be a phone but it's for
Android and iOS and it's currently in
pre-register this stream is by the way
sponsored by a Bandai Namco thank you
and Uncle for coming back to me
to uh you know show everyone new games
introduce your games to everyone I'm
really really excited to do it and it's
my honor yeah thank you thank you for
this occasion I have purchased a iPad
Pro
to give you guys the bestest footage of
tales of filming nowhere I hope again I
can stay true to that
it's looking pretty nice but first time
touching an iPad Pro or an iPad at all
and uh also fun games
um like you know mobile games are
um I don't I don't really have much
experience with them
[Music]
um but if it's about tails off then I am
in
yeah well well I'm still wearing my
Tails over rice sash because I actually
got something from Tales of her eyes for
you
as well to start off with to kick it off
with yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
so from Tales of arise I present to you
a really good looking
[Music]
celebration image
look at that would you look at that
let's put that here would you look at
that
gorgeous I think I'm the first one
showing this apparently
oh well
um
the good looking image obviously just
just because of hoodle down there I
kind of expression that is is he is he
pissed off or is he is sad or is he
happy I
or is he I don't know did he lose his
soul he looks a little bit lifeless I'm
not sure how to interpret it interpret
that uh face
he's also drenched though well we have
rain well uh playing around with the
water hose
and
I'm getting our dear kisana with that
water as well all right run well as long
as you have fun
this is some this is some uh fan service
we are getting here I don't know
about my interest in kisara and that's
why it is let me show this
[Laughter]
um I feel like I'm being targeted here
I feel like I'm also kind of a little
bit being exposed Maybe
uh but I I do be winning I do be winning
I'm the first one to see this picture
and I am honored
and I'm not sure what we're celebrating
I don't know if we're celebrating the
tales of uh Tesla Verizon sales numbers
or just the existence of tales of her
eyes but we are celebrating
I am actually going to be most likely
holding my last Tales of arise stream
um on the day after tomorrow and I like
I'm not actually like already at the end
but I'm about to get to the cutting off
point where I'm supposed to cut off
so yeah that's a little bit sad for me
but at least now we have Tales of
luminaria so
we can't like
um bridge over
our sadness of leaving Tales of our eyes
behind
the luminaria so I'm a bit nervous but
gotta be a good gotta be a good
Ambassador let me teach you about Tales
of luminaria but before I do that let me
show you a trailer this one is not new
uh but I have other stuff that's
exclusive and new as well just like the
Tesla Verizon image okay so Josh bgm
and look at let's look at this
[Music]
tonight
together
[Music]
Bandai Namco
hey
entertainment presents to you Tesla
filming area and I also present it so
did you like that trailer
looks awesome so far right yeah baby
so I've as I said I'm not like I'm not
like a big uh mobile phone game player
until now I've played maybe a few ones
but
um something with like a 3D graphic like
this is a first for me so I'm super
excited because that's like
so high level
so for tails of luminary I have a few
facts let me read them down from my
PowerPoint presentation
so this is the first
flagship mobile entry in the towns off
series The House of games have been a
lot around for a long time as you might
know from my fangirling
um and there has been like mobile phone
games before for tales off series but
and this one is the first Flagship type
and you get 21 playable characters each
designed by psychi who is maybe you've
known him who is the the character
designer creator of footballers
yeah 21 characters that's a lot of
characters normally like if you play a
tails off Series game you get like a
group of like around six people to play
around with maybe sometimes more maybe
yeah but usually it's like around that
number so for this game you get 21.
that's that's for a tails of Series game
a lot and there are a lot that look very
interesting to me that speak to me so
we'll try one or two out today
and also the game is fully voiced in
Japanese and English we're gonna play in
English today and there's a game music
composed by
and opening theme by Frederick ending
theme by kaina yes yes many credits to
tell you and
um I'm gonna show this later but because
I have a special special
exclusive trailer but there's going to
be an original animation from Kamikaze
coming soon
yes exciting
original animation and
so uh
I want to show you a little trailer of
the character that I will be playing
today
[Music]
um
after I think I'll show you this I think
I show you this first okay so next
trailer is one that as far as I know has
not been shown anywhere else yet so this
is a little bit more of an updated game
trailer I suppose please enjoy
all right here it goes
all living things in this world
are made from a substance known as Mana
there's only one way forward
that's to keep on fighting nobly now
let's do that
this is how it should be a fair and
righteous battle
you are the top-ranked student in our
newest Cadet class enemies and allies
alike fighting desperately to survive
[Music]
for the children Empire remember your
purpose and don't falter
this conflict has caused too many
tragedies must put an end to it
oh
[Music]
foreign
but I did hear it before
yes how did you like it
[Applause]
oh oh where is the cute yellow girl
do you mean do you mean ylc who do you
guys think I am going with today huh
who guys think I'm going with it was a
hard choice to be honest
um
the white-haired one the blonde one
the cute one everyone's cute blonde
sword night
Archer Archer lady
and purple purple
[Laughter]
lapless
blonde
interesting interesting well it's kind
of mixed um
ah so I went with someone who does close
combat because I felt like playing close
combat rather than uh ranged combat so I
am going today going to be playing yes
which I suppose is the giado that you
were talking about she does look a
little bit like a gather yeah yeah yeah
so before we get started last video for
now I'll show you a trailer character
trailer for yelsie there you go let's
let's watch it
time to unleash super ylc
come at me
how big do you think the world is anyway
[Music]
yeah you'll see here's gonna hit the
road
real soon I'll become a knight and a
flash
I'll even throw in a healing hug
[Music]
great primordial beast
please watch over me in battle
you'll see is back in business
our differences are what make this work
huh I can see how they make things more
fun
yeah food
cute cute cute cute cute
[Music]
there we go that was ylc for you you
like her
[Laughter]
I like her so now let's get into the
game where were the uh are zooming
through everything let me see let me see
uh where do I have the game there it is
done
this is the main screen I suppose
yesterday I tried it out a little bit
um just for testing purpose I already
played a little bit of like the
storyline from a character called Leo
who is this guy kind of gives me Yuri
Vibes
um he's a yeah a male protagonist type
of guy
he was very very straightforward very
easy to play
um so this is how like the character
screen looks like just to show you a
little bit you can like see what
accessories what weapons he's wearing
and you can like give him different
weapons different costumes and all that
you see his level his power his stats
and you can take a close look but we'll
do that okay I'll see let's look at ELC
so this is the character that I'll
mostly be using today
uh oh by the way this is still
pre-registered I have Early Access for
this so you can't play it yet but soon
and the link is in the description or up
above me There's the link for uh
pre-registering so I already like I I'm
not like like I'm very new to this as
well so I don't know everything about
this yet but I put like some costume
here uh that I had in my inventory
and I put like super strong weapons like
if you press Auto with clip I don't know
if everyone gets these super strong
weapons or if this is because of my demo
build
uh but I I don't know I equipped these
weapons they look so strong before she
had something else that looked weaker
and you got some arts and accessories
and dishes
uh is this a coincidence I think not her
dishes melted cheese lasagna
is this a
is this a coincidonk
um
did they do this in the demo build for
me I don't think so but that would sound
like a lot of effort to do
they know me or she knows me or I am her
I don't know I'm not claiming anything
nor am I denying anything so anyway
she's part of this uh group this um army
called uh
yeah we will find out how that's
pronounced Federation with all these
girls and boys
and yeah we can we're gonna start
playing her story but look this is all
the other characters and
um you see for example she
gorgeous she's part of uh the guildland
empire
very cool like they look a bit more like
um cool looking while the others look a
little bit more nice looking I don't
know how to describe it and then there's
some for example her she's so cute look
at her what the hell
her lover
she's not part of she's like kind of
like independent I think
oh my God oh my God look at her
I can give her a different weapons
oh whoa whoa okay okay okay
yeah she's cute she's an adventurous so
those are just adventurers that don't
belong to these groups yeah yeah
I'm playing I'm playing with the highest
Graphics setting by the way right now
a lot of them have like German names her
name is very German Anna Maria marshina
she's cute too
um is that a little bit obvious that I
keep on clicking on mostly
um girls
anyway I kind of was close to choosing
her as well I like her but she's ranged
combat and I genuinely prefer
um not really perfect but I thought it
would be better to have like close
combat for this one so let's get into
what uh no wait I'll show you a bit more
of the of the whole layout first I guess
also I'll be looking down most of the
time because I'm looking at my iPad
um but first of all well this is the
main screen right so you see like what
you can do here you can play the
episodes like the story lines and you'll
see that you can like for example roll
for something shall we do a daily summon
let's do a daily summon
daily free summons go what do we get I
did this yesterday too tap
oh wait are you guys not hearing this
oops sorry I think I had the audio there
we go sorry
oh Adventure review
that's already pretty good
[Music]
okay and then I got some clear missions
log in for two days in total let's make
it 500 days it's too loud now okay sorry
and then there's a calendar here login
calendar I logged in yesterday let's get
something for today
5 000 thank you I'll take that
and
uh wait do we have something here
no presents sad life do we have
something here no news okay well we got
news here
and uh we got this this stuff here
just so you know
and oh wait what is this
oh Mission rank up I claimed more
than Joe
okay and there's oh I want to do this I
want to do the release Memorial summon
shall we do that
apparently this stream is the news
that's true that's true
let's do this eh I can do a ten times
summon I think I only can't do that
let's go
show me what you got
the addiction I feel like coming
we got some fancy Stones oh was that
Phoenix
was that a bee that looked like a
phoenix
oh oh can I open one by one oh I can oh
black wolves blade
[Music]
oh combat wear that looks nice
daily wear
[Music]
one apparently because
they come different color of the Stars
no wait is that worse or better than the
silver stars I'm not sure we'll find out
someday I'll kill the Venture gear for
Anna
and daily wear got fired
I'm a uniform sale Young
then daily Roy Vanessa cool
yeah oh I got a mission clear thank you
for letting me know race GE character
profile
to over 9 000.
obtain five
guys did I do okay summon it summon do
it
yeah
oh I heard a big cow
oh is that those are good ones I think
let's open them
oh that looks nice
combat wear and so we're trying to first
try dance this one is all right let's
open the rest oh okay
oh
God
this thing that's new they show me like
this Stanley wears it oh this is
nice another one I'm gonna do another
one
oh I can't anymore okay thank you for
stopping me again thank you for keeping
me sane
into the episode now enough of that
let's get into it uh there you go here's
ylc
flowers for you
[Music]
Oh I thought I already downloaded it
this is gonna be quick
download complete there you go
try
oh let's get in some ylc
let's see what she's like
hello
can you hear me yes yes
the volume okay oh okay and I just I
just touched it I made you a bit louder
though in OBS is that okay Elsie sorry I
touched it even though you said don't
touch it oh nice legs
Toto
hey Toto Toto oh I can't find her
where I'll make it louder than pee
princess so this is where you were too
loud you must come see the great
primordial beast aruhan at once it's
time for your sending off ceremony
Grandpa you're about to embark on an
Arthur's Journey
you'll need greater rule Hunt's
blessings to see it through
that big of a deal
I'm just gonna go study to be a Stigmata
Knight stigma tonight what do you mean
just
you are to be the next next ruler of um
you know I'm quite worried for you
thanks Gramps
we'll keep that in mind
now please excuse me while I look for
Toto who who is the hotel is she gone
but I thought she was going to accompany
you
she is yeah I haven't seen her since
this morning
[Music]
awesome thanks a ton Gramps
I already love this song
[Music]
foreign
I love this opening song So Good
flowers for you flowers
or flower
okay let's get into it we start out here
in what looks like a castle is this my
mom mommy
mommy yeah I'll see where are you going
uh ouch I gotta go find her I love her
dress
ceremony is about to start
I love her hairstyle too doesn't mean
you can just leave Toto alone
you and her are practically attached at
the hip
she does sound like crony doesn't she
I'll find her real fast so just hang
tight
be careful ylc crowny
doesn't she sound like crony mama
[Music]
do I talk to you too try to find Toto
okay okay princess
we have a little time before December
okay okay
I'm on my way I'm on my way we don't
have that much time for the stream so uh
am I going this way I think I'm going
this way
this is so pretty yeah
it's so pretty when it comes to my new
school with me right
oh hello
oh you're in good spirits today princess
wait their clothes look so Germany
Saving Grace after all the pattern on
that color looks so German to me
but wait I thought your ceremony was
today
shouldn't you be back at home
yeah but Toto's gone missing I have
priority lady have you seen her around
probably not huh I'm sorry okay you're
you're not gonna help me yeah I'm going
to look for her right now but
okay let's go her she's a her by the way
guys okay fine can I find that no okay
in in the mail uh part I was able to uh
fight boxes and enemies
do I join it's so pretty here oh look at
that mountain in the background
let's go see oh what is that what is
that cute where is Toto
[Music]
the game looks so good though
yeah looks good on here I like her
design a lot I guess I gotta go here
not around here around here either huh
oh she's talking for me she's over in
the flower garden flower garden flower
garden
here
oh pretty oh I see something there
go over here
oh it's so nice I want to live here so
pretty oh it's like a maze
not here
[Music]
oh
who are you are you Toto
[Music]
oh
I found you total there you are
it looks all over for you it's so fluffy
oh my God
a flower
smells nice
this is a wind color
really rare
is this one for me
thank you so much
oh this is perfect I'll smell it
whenever I get homesick oh so Toto oh my
God soon
how big do you think the world is anyway
this is so exciting well these beats
travel the world all of it
I'll do it together
pretty flowers I think I made the right
choice with character I'm
oh my God
don't kill me
don't don't you dare kill me Toto
so you're finally awake
look around you
okay
there's no time to explain grab your
weapon come on I would say total
um abducted and kidnapped me and brought
me here trying to kill me but um so Toto
is the last boss
that we have to fight
over
I'm excited let's fight okay
whose fire was that wait is that my
firearm did they burn me I think they
burned him
yeah they burned me though am I doing
cat repeatedly for a combo attack okay
[Music]
and then I can do this again
dodging the Dodgers
[Music]
okay
I have killed them all a big victory I
think epic he fought well especially for
someone who just woke up okay
Battle Tactics at work
you're making me blush
okay let's eat some more lasagna fill up
that tummy
I would I would not say no to lasagna
right now
[Music]
oh that was badass cool too Nessa no no
I looked cooler
[Music]
maybe I can put that on Amazon crazy for
you
yo don't spit that fire at me you know
who you're spitting that fire at a
phoenix I think twice about that
is the audio too loud by the way I think
it's too loud sometimes
I fixed it a little bit why are you
mentioning
Lucy and all of a sudden what what oh
I got ahead of my lava rock what don't
worry about that where do I go left or
right hey hold on yelsea
[Music]
so they like throughout running through
this map they continuously have
conversations
so it's very entertaining I see it what
is this
attack
next time next time calm down y'all see
calm down
and also I'm ready to unleash my Mystic
art but I don't think I want to use it
yet
wait no let's go let's go
okay
you're getting distracted
this mountain path's dangerous be
careful
remember bees can't treat this like a
pleasure hike okay
I'll hold in air I mean how do I jump
I'm not sure
[Music]
so cool though
oh I missed again
yeah oopsie
Beast the new okay I got some items
give me some more of those coins
I really like besides me using my
fingers to move doesn't really feel like
a mobile game like this
such a pretty game
you use words
interesting ways it feels like a crap
and Tails wolf game no I like it it's
quite for now
sometimes
dip
she's using piano terms of less starting
to get a feel
wait I have a Exquisite and divine way
of talking excuse me angle takes my
breath away me that is true
it looks like any other volcanic path no
it's very not just the volcanic path
it's beautiful Apple
grasslands as far as the eye can see hot
rugged mountains like this are rare
yeah yeah yeah it was much more flowery
where we came from but here is a very
different scenery I wonder how far away
we are from home
that sounds like
German food called pool Beetle you're
from but I think that's uh
Austrian dialect
s
[Music]
it just feels so great yes that does
sound nice something here
okay now we go up here
in that case
wanna come to my hometown with me next
time I visit I think I'll pass it why
it's so nice though you're home I'm just
not good at relaxing I just can't bother
you just need to chill Nessa
I'm no good at making small talk
I've noticed
but I'm traveling with you now right now
nonetheless
oh I don't know where to go maybe right
first you'll kill
you I explore
was that the actual way to move on damn
it and I gotta go downstairs
damn it
I gotta explore everything
you guys know me
gotta go this way
what do we have here oh oh no ah this is
um I I tried this out a little bit
yesterday with a different character
I have a I don't think I can do this
it's like some kind of challenge
we can give it one try but I'm gonna
fail
secret mission yeah it's like a
challenge
defeat all enemies as soon as possible
the worst rank would be in three minutes
but my problem yesterday was that I was
uh dying
all the time
and once you die it's over we can give
it one try
okay come at me guys
wait wait I ran right into it
no I never died that early
no no no no no that's how it's supposed
to be like
there's gonna be a second wave too
though so
oh I did that though okay hey I'm
surviving on like one HP
how long can I can I survive with one HP
yeah
I'm scared
[Laughter]
my hand so much for that I think I'm a
bit too weak for that just yet
f
kill thank you very much
um
I uh for this we don't know because we
don't have that much time I'm gonna
leave that there we're moving on but
just so you know there's these kind of
challenges on the map
the stone is still not dead how come
yeah so you can challenge yourself and
see how strong you are and if you can
beat your own records
I'm sure you guys could do it if you
tried
all right open up next area
just so you know yesterday when I was
playing with a different character it
was a completely different area that I
was in
oh where where am I there I am
so depending on the cake that you choose
you start off in a different area and
you get different conversations and
different people to join you like with
with Leo yesterday I had two different
characters join me
one of them was that a bow girl
Celia I think her name was
lasagna
oh my God
I don't one at least I think
shoot
nice and that's that and that's Dad yes
yes girl yes yes let's go
y'all see y'all I don't see
oh no Shrek I don't want to go over the
bridge Shrek no no no don't move the
bridge no don't jump on the bridge no
no I wasn't particularly particularly
scared I'm scared of this bridge no I
don't wanna okay oh it's already over oh
wow
but I appreciate it that was fast that
wasn't that bad
tender Wing meat oh should we sell that
at kfp
I don't know do you think the guys will
the customers will notice that the meat
tastes different
[Music]
at least less of you guys will be harmed
so
never mind that
never mind I'm sorry what being alone
with me must be pretty boring no I'm
fine I'm excited
left or right left or right left or
right left side
I'll lay back and chill she is
and all that
you'll see
as a voice
I like her voice actors
are already dead they're so weak
oh did I do it did I do it last second
that was close the garage was close you
gotta react really quick with that one
hmm
and that
see
Toto just said we make a good combo too
does turtle ever fight still
fighting words you appreciate the praise
I'm afraid that I'm still unable to see
her sorry is it only my imagination it's
okay other people can't see total it
seems thank you hey
oh wait oh you can see her then no I
can't I just guessed based on where is
yelsea a little bit cray-cray could it
be
I can't censor presence physically oh
okay I wanted to give her my thanks
directly ah there's another challenge
um
I want to show as much story as possible
in this one hour
so let me skip that challenge
for when I play it privately we'll be in
dulcanor before long oh once arrived
there we're meant to meet me there's
something over here
[Music]
peace
I agree
but I need to pick up every item as well
no no it's not because I'm afraid hey
I'm not afraid I'm I'm a part down
Warrior oh
what is that there's some houses up
there oh
chapter 2 6 out of 20. someone fighting
over there
it's Lucian Lucian ah
one of those 21 characters
are we gonna help him or find him
no I think we're children we're joining
them
[Music]
oh there was no enemy left
okay
oh oh wait there are enemies left
let's show you my Mystic art I guess
maybe
um that was unnecessary a little bit
Overkill
what I wanted to show it anyway
eat that lasagna
yeah
[Music]
nice
[Applause]
[Music]
are we done
we're done
yes well done
oh
Lucy you're so strong
you protected the kids from all those
beasts by yourself
no wonder you're the head of Blaze sick
sick
thank you but where is Maxine
I asked him to go to town
and take note of any damages caused by
beasts
I Came Upon these children while
patrolling the area it's very elegant so
you start showing up this close to town
now
we need to address it ASAP sick but
first Vanessa and I should get these
children home
okay cool did he just say ASAP
is that the Town Square later okay
understood okay
there they have a quite different
personalities don't they
all right I guess I have arrived what do
we have here now then whoa where did
that Mackie wander off to
he didn't get lost pretty
we reached another city
you found something again
where where where where
oh no another Bridge oh what's up with
you who are you what do you want it
yesterday for the likes of you
oh is it dangerous here
damn straight if you get the picture
then get out of here hey
huh
that's so nice I bet you've held out
tons of people oh so thanks for letting
me know
God no I don't okay
I see what's going on they don't want me
to go there just yet story block
grandma grandma grandma
what are you doing did you get lost
again
Grandma every time you get lost
oh this is not not uh accessible yet
either I think
did I go the wrong direction in the
beginning should I have gone right
or is it all connected anyway this is
quite big
[Music]
wow oh I see something over there
PB fragment
[Music]
hello who are you oh what the beasts
have come that close
dang I requested
Joe we're kind of short Steph Curry
a lot of soldiers she is a perfect
choice isn't she
that's why they sent us here huh medium
sounds mystical yeah
foreign
[Music]
check out the city he says where exactly
do you want me to go
let's go up here and go up here before
what's at the very top
oh you are here
who are you I heard there were beasts
around here indeed there are please take
care okay right go inside your house of
course
but you'd better stay at home just to be
safe yes yes I'm counting on you
I'm not gonna push him Chad that's rude
what's the matter with you why would I
know that
oh ciao
[Music]
you playing hide and seek
huh
how did you know I was hiding
because Toto here found you for me uh
he's like crazy ladies who are you
talking about
anyway there are beasts around here
Chelsea so hurry back home okay yes he
needs to understand that uh how do
people don't see it
I will think she's like some kind of
nutcase or something
[Music]
but they forget because she's cute I
guess wait can I go over there is that
where I need to go
more PP fragments always remember to
explore everything properly but I wasn't
supposed to go here right
let's go just what oh do I need to
way to talk to more people God please
set the city entrance
there's no time to be selling skewers
then no please tell me schooling before
I become crispy myself
I make a crispy kind of food right
yeah crispy chicken wing skewers
I'll search some up for you next time
sort out this Beast problem and it's on
the house KFC is
a store here
probably
quite a selection no shoes what are
those
but there's no need for you civilians to
arm yourselves
why you ask
because I Maxime hustleman's I'm here I
swear on my family name and my pride as
a knight
I will keep you all safe totally so
close to him
Toto is sniffing on him
now who would be so rude as to call me
maxi
It could only be you Chelsea oh my God
what's going on
as well yes yes that's right she's
somewhere here there are bees showing up
around here too
what what
Lucy was fighting some near the Town
Gate
we joined in and took him out but
[Music]
how shameful of me
I've failed my comrades in their time of
need you're gonna meet up in the town
square oh ah very good okay I think I
was supposed to meet him first
let's go back this way
this way I'm maybe here now wait
wait
yes no silly why not
oh okay
how did I miss him before I don't even
know it doesn't look like Lucian and
Vanessa are here yet these things
you're absolutely right you're being
scrambled eggs with a lizard egg would
taste good
did I give it a try
ow rude
has anyone ever tried that before
lizard eggs scrap does anyone do that
why are you not doubting me guys you
didn't say nothing so weird if you have
no other choice of a food like I mean
[Music]
why are you why are you guys acting like
that as if I'm the weird one
well
who won
are you hurt yesi no never I got my
lasagna I'm all good I'm relieved to
hear that
I could never let one of my proteges be
and catch up any injuries with a sheet
of lasagna
wow my whole skin is like just layers of
lasagna because I patched myself from so
loved oh
imagine that young woman like you should
sure instead of a Band-Aid just put
lasagna on it and I'm good
[Music]
you're such a stick oh that no that's
not bullet that blood that's just the
sauce
tomato sauce there's Lucy
we've been meaning to talk to you about
that danger what's there to talk about
see you're both all right I like him
yeah Maggie really came through for me
all in a day's work right
you held your own as well yelsea
they didn't let me into place but
nothing confident
all of today's news is good
[Music]
what do you mean what's what if things
go on as they have
or long
this town maybe be set by hordes of
beasts
we need to take action before that
happens okay Vanessa to stay here and
watch over the town
so for now it'll just be us out in the
field
[Music]
thank you no thank you
oh was it like around here in the city
and I missed it I wonder
it's like you missed it but you can
still go later if you wanna
from a mine not too far from here sounds
like that's the source of our problems
sounds like a you problem not a meat
problem but okay yelsea is here to take
care of it
give me all those coins yeah
[Music]
all right we're moving on
the stage
we're gonna protect
people
and we're a free free party group now
but where the hell did Vanessa go this
gravel path can be a bit precarious
Alexa play on gravel rudge
we're out on a hike
you sure are full of energy
I thought I heard that you weren't used
to mountains
I'm not but I've always been the
outdoorsy type she's so cute
all the time I did a back step how did I
do that very impressive
thank you thank you very much Matthew
whatever your name was
Mackie I think that's just a nickname I
can't remember his normal name
never mind I'm sure he enjoys being
called Matthew by Elsie
you can't get to me friend
[Music]
try again
later I don't have time right now
[Music]
oh on the on the top left it shows me I
got six out of 20 somethings is this
is this PB yeah peeping fragments ah
so there are 20
um all over the episode I suppose
scattered
feel that breeze that's all right you
don't have a care in the world do you
we are the most dangerous Beast hunting
Mission here no maybe it was right after
US own your senses okay
guys
[Music]
must be like the poster boy for the
hustle I love the way she talks I love
the way how she picks up those berries
too
I am a parody
I want to eat lasagna
so I should just Act Naturally then
this slipped my mind but now that I
think about it
aren't you the esteemed princess
and princess yeah that's my title all
right
I guess Sweden let's build some pride
about that like she's one of those
princesses who just doesn't want to be a
princess one oh I didn't see that
oh
gotta be quick yo the time window for
that is pretty strict
handsome Pleasant
my new favorite game
surprise surprise surprise surprise
okay
[Music]
you can't control me I go where I want
when I want
ah totally I like that about her oh but
she also said that she likes the way I
talk she called it
it really is
the only person I know who says
Ayah and
um I agree I don't know anyone else who
says Raj
I wanted to and voila
you developed yourself got another one
of speaking for a unique person
very unique but I like her
Leo the one that I played yesterday was
more like a more like a typical
[Music]
um
as I said straightforward it's difficult
to explain but he was more like
fight fight
but the yellow
ish personality trait for ylc makes her
very unique I mean they're all very
unique they all have a very different
look to them
and personality so I think there's
something for everyone
[Music]
oh this bridge is broken down though I
don't know how we can pass that a worn
out rope Bridge cutscene
looks kind of dangerous
yeah you can turn on the Japanese stuff
too if you want probably fall
you're right but we don't have the time
or the skills to fix it fly
fly Toto you find something
for the rescue oh uh
Toto said to go this way okay speaking
to her invisible friend again
is this an outlandish custom from armor
cargo yeah talking to invisible friends
judging from how Vanessa described it
this Toto truly exists it has a presence
but
LC doesn't appear to be lying or joking
it's possible that Toto's some kind of
unidentified being
one that's yet to be officially
discovered this is I feel a bit sorry
for yelling now they think I'm a weirdo
what
Toto says it's this way this way I
already went this way follow me
ah
[Music]
are we really going to take this oh sure
are you a little coward Mackie okay
if I can do it you can do it come on
[Music]
off is opening up
let's keep going down it for now
it might lead to an entrance to the mind
yes it did I think
oh oh we're in the mine now oh and the
music changed
I hit both of them I would say that was
pretty in amazing incredible
hey I don't know which way to go ah hard
choices
I'll go here first I guess there should
be an item here yeah
aren't these the stones that are used
for good for the gacha
about Toto yeah see what I want to say
I'm crazy he or she near us right now
well I'm sorry
I can't even detect her presence
[Music]
it is
I've never thought to ask you this
before what does Toto look like exactly
good question like a bunny flying bunny
squirrel
and unlike most of the beasts we come
across this is not a beast it was really
cute this is not a beast
is that all the description you needed
because I got nothing from them
she should have used mine description
that they look much better I think
bunny scribble flying bunny squirrel
yeah I would say that it's pretty
accurate okay
okay
there
mushrooms mushroom Heap for showing some
interest guys
Toto's really happy about it
I'm not accustomed to that
how do people respond to her normally
well usually when I talk about Toto
oh but that's not your fault Toto
too far away
we're BFFs we stick together through
thick and thin I see
it's nice that you two are so close
I hope to form that kind of friendship
myself one day
I'm sure you'll find that kind of
friendship don't worry about it
a handsome guy like you
I don't doubt it at all
oh it's getting really hot in here
damn
foreign
oh
I was just surprised to hear Lucy unsafe
he always acts so Serene and above it
all
it seems familiar interested in French
how did you develop such a pressure
that's me
[Music]
can we go backwards
what oh so I didn't listen to the
conversation at all I don't know why but
something something was going on in my
mind I don't know what it was I was a
little bit distracted I'm sorry
um
that was a nice view I have to say
oh I know exactly what this girl
what is it I'd like to be better you
guys fall in love with her already
I did I know I did
I'm sure she feels the same way about
you y'all see
whenever she talks about you
the expression on her face softens a bit
I'm actually not sure if I can finish
the whole episode today I kind of wanna
prepare yourself
but
um
surprisingly long
and there must be something on the left
side
aha
oh why are you fighting sorry I couldn't
help you but you're fine alone right
you're pretty strong on your own
okay
wait there's some fancy items to Wolf
jerky mmm beef jerky
you draw out Vanessa's softer side to
loosium
[Music]
friends with you
oh Mackie this is really fun cute I
can't okay like nothing I'm not good at
multitasking but listening to the story
and to uh and five at the same time is
not doesn't feel that weird or difficult
to me
normally I I would probably struggle
with multitasking things
feel like yes we've almost reached the
eggs oh we have really is it this way or
the other way
oh I feel like it's this way
oh thank you for the membership welcome
so we have Maggie's kind of cute yes
yeah
it must have been an alternate path I do
like green hair
I just listened to what Toto told me
[Music]
um so where is she now here right here
my ghost friends
again I want a bigger enemy in order to
use it
go Bingo go home
what is that Aaron Juke is that you're
speaking riddles to me with these names
[Music]
oh my God I have a lot of money though
and she loves you guys even if you can't
see I'm rich I'm not accusing you of
lying
but it's hard to believe there's
something you can't accept those items
of course
do I sound fancy when I say that who
means there's more to this world than
what we see oh that's deep stuff yo but
please don't deny her give me those
chicken wings
yes that was rude of me as a hospital oh
by the way you can totally like
um it has like an auto save so you can
totally like quit Midway through if you
wanna
you can go back to it at any given time
thank you you'll save all the money you
made and all the the EXP you got through
the mission yeah
come on
let's go
[Music]
wind is a nice element
time for lasagna
insanely good
that is a lot of damage yeah very strong
I wonder I think
nice
I wonder if you can get like more
different Mystic Arts like if you level
up higher
or if you can get Mystic Arts from gosh
no probably not but
see I don't know what you got the game
yet if you want to know more I recommend
oh there's a challenge I recommend you
to find out more that's certainly
exercised by pre-registering are you
tired and trying not to give it when it
comes out
does all that stamina come from
you don't think any of those
things
Overkill 2 000 damage
back to town and either way I wouldn't
worry I haven't been playing the gotcha
game for a long time now so it's a it's
a welcome Edition
[Music]
oh never mind
I need something to get my mind off of
the sadness and loneliness
come on
let's take care of him and get those
herbs or whatever that is
there oh
seasoning spices can I get a she looks
like she would drink a pumpkin spice
blotter
I've never drank that before
who will always be there for you really
oh wait Are we almost done
oh my God oh my God oh my God they're
strong
very well oh I'll grant them the honor
of being slain by our hustlements they
were slain by Mita you gotta stand up
your game come on
[Music]
he got me good there
prepare yourself there you are
a burger out of you we're done
oh we did it
yay oops
y Sprite precaution
there's no need to alert these beasts to
our presence understood sir ratchet she
doesn't say radical ones that's mine
that's impression
still a good deal more casual than the
real one
what was that Toto
Toto find something again
she looks a bit excited I'm excited nice
find
a little excited about what
it's coming do you feel something can
turtle even talk to me and can totally
communicate properly oh look oh there's
something over that way oh green stuff
vegetables now
boss coming no way it's way too way too
Serene and calm here
oh
nah no way a boss will jump on that
flower film you wanted to visit the
flower garden did you oh cute
oh what's the matter well it's just
there's no wind in here yet the flowers
beside you just wait there's my aura no
it's total that's where Toto is real it
sure does
not or hear her and they definitely
can't touch her don't touch not that I
can see her easily and when I hold her
oh yes yes junkers
tell us more about Toto
[Music]
I really want to know don't you oh
they're very curious very nosy it
started
oh
to be continued
[Music]
now loading
all right wait that changed today oh
cute I'll figure that out after I finish
my walk eh I want to continue but it's
already been so long it's so short I
wonder uh we can look a little bit into
it and then I'll leave you with a
cliffhanger Maybe
is this the past
there's only four fragments here though
so maybe it's not that long
[Music]
it was so pretty I don't have to go back
into the castle that's supposed to
Castle right
wow the water is so sparkly I love all
the flowers oh no I can't go here yet
I've missed something
[Music]
oh flashback time yeah
her casual clothes look very cute she
always runs around with heels Sasuke
expect that
not everyone can do that and fight with
heels as well this way maybe
oh now I feel fellow field
Battlefield sus
Toto likes flowers
must be here
right right right wait aha what's that I
know it
someone
[Music]
nice to meet you small
ER
anyway
[Music]
I think it's kind of cute it is hella
cute let's get it let's capture it and
never let it go it's mine
mother
I chose you
hey hey
sorry didn't mean to scare you
look hours don't you I do too
smell wow
nice I just like to sit here and relax
no
I'll chill right up until the sun sets
oh hey you want some candy
ball
it's yummy huh
and I have more if you want
you gonna give me something oh crap
oh
you are a princess
[Music]
they're made for one another like sweets
as much as I do
let me tell you about my favorite shop
what not interested
oh don't be shy no way friends now and I
think you'll really like it
okay we're still continuing
[Music]
the gorillas
hey girl
sorry I'm ignoring you Toto is cuter I'm
so sorry
zooming
[Music]
uh yeah I can't stop I don't know where
to stop
I want to live here I want to go on a
vacation here right she wants to go to a
shop which shop
or shop that sells sweets
[Music]
it's not inside of the castle right oh
oh three on the floor
I'm guessing the last one is ah maybe
here is this where the county is
basically the candy is that
okay I'm fine wait could it be better
I'm happy hey let me introduce my new
friend I got cute skirts oh I haven't
even asked your name yet but anyway like
the traditional clothing of this
city slash country
oh wow
hmm
cupcakes hey hey hey hey I'll have the
usual
hello there princess
I have a fresh batch made just for you
here Stroop waffles
[Music]
awesome extra syrup because I know just
wait a minute
it smells so good huh wow yeah it looks
pretty or no wait did I say uh where are
they from oh
she really liked them huh I'm so glad
was that correct
yes they are real who are you talking
they're from the Netherlands have you
eaten them before can't you see
so maybe this is based on the
Netherlands a little bit it kind of
makes sense with the clothes it look it
does look uh kind of inspired by it I
gotta strip off
[Music]
those are ended with lasagna
my new best friend is the shopkeeper
none of them can see my pal oh and I'm
the only words made in the Dutch city of
gouda wait wait a second there's a city
called God is that where God is from as
well
that city is amazing if they came up
with Stroop waffles and Gouda cheese
then they are a city of geniuses
[Music]
I keep thinking can I keep it hey Mom
I'm home
oh
yes oh you see it I see crowny so that's
your new friend there yelsea oh my God
this is crazy you can see her oh I just
know just knew you would Mom
no
afraid I can't oh but your mother knows
nonetheless okay mom even if you can't
see it the wind is there
more to this world than what meets the
eye
[Music]
I can be
a grandma you know noticed her oh yes
yes I know what this must mean
it dawned on me because I could do a
bunch of voices too now listen carefully
Elsie
what I mean yes ma'am but you should say
Whoppers
what
oh mama you have a great destiny
you are the next Divine queen that is so
true girl the creature beside you now
it's made from Mana itself oh sheep your
perceptive abilities are surpass mine
and well that makes you special it makes
me special
so you must train you'll see okay
strengthen your connection to this world
of Mana okay Mama I'll do anything once
you do
you'll learn more about your little
friend including what she is she's so
pretty oh my God you think someday
everyone else will see her too nah
probably not yes
sure and we'll be the bridge to make
that happen I'll make those people
regret saying I'm crazy you must give
your friend a name
this will serve as an anchor binding it
to this world a name
in that case
I make this declaration I talk a great
primordial
I am yelsea of the fly 19 Family
Holy daughter of LG
[Music]
here in this land
of endless green she's making a big deal
out of it and of a wind that never dies
today I have sought out what is she
talking about the one who shall be named
well
I named her this because of her warmth
and softness
fine name but you didn't have to go that
far you'll see and Toto
may your journey be blessed all with
blooming flowers and to rule Hans Grace
oh
one last thing my love don't forget to
smile okay that's my girl oh yes girl
girl mom
I think we're done with the episode it
feels like it are we done
if not then I'm just gonna leave
and I
pretty much covers it
this is so long story
honestly very impressed with you oh
thank you voice is echoing Maxime
oh sorry attention released as a guts
okay they're calling it now for sharing
these stories
also I promise you this oh as long as
you and Toto are at the Knight Academy
your days will be filled with happiness
oh thanks Lucy okay and sorry for taking
up so much time we better get going now
yeah it's all right chapter four
but I am going to
end it here now because it's already
been pretty long so you can go here and
choose take a break
your dad will be safe but your stage
progress over to the most recent
checkpoint
and yes 42 seconds ago all right
[Music]
that was a lot of fun
I like Yoshi
so oh we got some
rewards okay
oh we got a lot of stones
he love PB stones
nice oh Mission rank up as well
cool all right so oh we could do another
some
fish let me quickly can I
[Music]
one special one open up
iron staff
divide again quite Exquisite nice
a lot of power up
not bad okay okay okay sorry I could
summon more but uh no more no more
was there anything else I wanted to show
you
oh
well here's the dishes
look at those strip waffles yummy
oh
I guess you can like equip it as the
like the item that she continuously eats
like the Lasagna
[Music]
bye I can buy the ingredients okay okay
okay
let me go back thank you marble Curry oh
I love this one
[Music]
it always looks so yummy
I mean I don't I don't know what this is
though
my latest level one rice ball big clump
of rice made by Anna Maria that's
devastatingly salty
oh
[Music]
oh I am so hungry I had nothing to eat
today besides cereal and that was like
[Music]
15 hours ago
I have one more thing to show to you
guys let's uh get rid of that
and
[Music]
before we end it here and I hope you all
liked it very much and I did
I I don't know if I'm gonna have to make
a new account when the new game is
actually out but I wanna continue
playing ELC and I want to try the other
characters as well I want to learn about
them and play with them around while
crying about finishing Tales of her eyes
so I have a an exclusive anime trailer
to show you guys
you want to see it
I want to see it
so this is from the upcoming
anime for Tales of luminaria Let's Take
a Look shall we and go
looks like our instructor was right
[Music]
she didn't post a very good guard both
know I'm more than enough for you
yeah well it seems pretty clear to me
you're hesitating so you're gonna tell
me you're not I am Resolute cause this
paths were my Justice lies
[Music]
together
it's time the Empire wins
[Music]
Bandai Namco
yeah
that looks pretty cool yeah some intense
fighting going on really really cool CG
so I look forward to that everyone
it's coming up sometime soon I don't
know what date but sometime yeah I'm
really hyped up so looking forward to it
and that kind of concludes the stream
today I think I showed you everything
that I needed to show you and yeah I
hope you liked it pre-register link is
in my description uh or above me up
there up there yeah thank you
for sponsoring the stream and uh yeah
I'm once again honored to
um be given the role to show you guys a
tails off related game because you know
I love the Tails of Series yeah
yeah thank you so much Bandai Namco it
was a pleasure I'm gonna continue
playing it hoping that my uh my progress
will not be lost I'm gonna ask them
afterwards
and the day after tomorrow hotels have
arrived thank you guys and in German we
say
thank you and everyone hope you liked it
you'll see cute
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]