foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
hmm
[Music]
laughs
oh no no
[Music]
meow
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
foreign
cats go away ah
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
[Music]
me in let me in
oh
yeah dangerous
[Music]
we will we will
give me one more minute please
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
um what the [\h__\h] is going on
what's going on
what why why
[Music]
that's cool
I I don't I don't I don't even know how
to explain this what is going on
they
I restart I always restart
um
I always restart the uh my you know my
my face app thingy
before the Stream
and now that I did the app updated and
now I had to log in differently than
usual
and now the when I looked down my head
looks up and when I look to the right my
head looks to the left it's in it's
completely inverted why is it inverted
what the [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[Music]
why yeah
no no now it's it's not last time it was
only
my eyes I think now it's my whole head
okay okay
please why
why is my whole head movement
completely inverted since the update
what the [\h__\h] what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay okay
let me try something
[Music]
yeah for some reason like this whole
different login thingy
oh my God
uh has like happened to the others
earlier than me for some reason even
though I always keep it up to date it
didn't do it for me and now it's doing
it and I don't like it uh because now
something changed
wait a second wait a second wait a
second
I has
idea
um this one
no no the thing is on my other on my
Camp let's just say camera device
uh it's correct
correctly reflecting
oh wow why did it stop oh
mm-hmm
but only on the PC it's the other way
around
I I never let it run that long
I'm sorry I'm so sorry
I'm so sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
sorry sorry sorry
I'm trying
trying
something no no I'm not looking at OBS
I'm looking at my own application
it's not that OBS isn't weird also if
you would invert it it would probably be
maybe horizontally flip but you can't
have it horizontally and vertically
flipped as well but turns out you can in
our application
anyway I just
got myself a different version but
because I want to
but then
but then I can't
[Music]
and then I can't do the thing I wanted
to do
how did I did I like last time when only
my
uh when only my eyes were
inverted
uh I said
the next day we're sold that only like
yeah I ran with it but the next day it
was fixed and I said like it just fixed
itself or what did I say
[Music]
that's so annoying
I didn't say it huh I should always tell
you guys what what it is would be
helpful
why must you update into something that
doesn't work
when it was fine before
[Music]
it makes me I have you know I have a
different version that works
but
um
but there I can't put my accessory on
[Music]
let me check one more time
this is really weird but I guess I'll be
inverted it would be accessory
awesome
[Music]
oh God
this is confusing
okay I'll just show you
[Music]
it doesn't even work the way I want it
to work ah for [\h__\h] sake
just look
so and I look up but I go down and I
look uh down but I look up and I look
right but I look left and I look left
and I look whatever okay we can't no the
teeth aren't working anyway
[Laughter]
um
things just already not going the way I
want them to go today
no tea for me okay
okay but at least my glasses right I can
have at least my glasses
we're gonna do oh
we're gonna do this
okay
[Music]
yes yes for some reason here different
version but I it works but I can't put
accessories on on this version like I
mean you know png's
so
you just gotta live with that
by the way
ah
yo I haven't used this version in a
while
okay
[Music]
um
chat where'd you go
chat
why does it not work why does chat not
work now the [\h__\h]
why
what what
there you are okay
today
everything is not working and you know
why it's in exchange for my brain to
work probably
how you guys doing I what's up what's up
oh
what's up
no no this one this one I know by it's
uh flipped this one I actually know when
I posted for a moment I was like what
you two you gonna do this to me too oh
oh
hey my glasses are not really
working with this hairstyle not really
but whatever I don't care [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh okay
I had to write to Gemma
what's going on
[Music]
is it is this supposed to sound a little
bit uh
funky
let me check the sound no audio what
really what about what about now
uh
you're really not hearing a thing on now
now you hear it though I'm pretty sure
[Laughter]
God damn it one guy that's one guy
that's that stupid one guy
you were hearing it this way I was
playing it for video capture device I
was thinking you should be hearing that
who looks I'm gonna scroll back up I'm
gonna scroll back up I'm gonna scroll
back up I'm gonna scroll back up who the
[\h__\h] was that
[Music]
I think I can't scroll that far back up
I'll find you in the archive
I'll find you
I will find you
it was you
how dare you why why did you just have
the whole stream muted and you were like
oh I wonder why I don't hear anything
must be Kiana's fault
um
[Music]
let's go
yeah must be my fault I mean I mean so
many things are my fault what the [\h__\h]
we recommend the hand I can't
foreign
that's unfortunate because if I how did
like the other members do this
why is it Japanese
why is it half Japanese leverage
a tutorial map
[Music]
yes they plugged in the USB mouse you
can do that
you can do that
what
you can plug in the mouth into
into the switch the [\h__\h]
this game supports it
and I know about the USB ports
all right all right all right all right
let me crawl under my desk
I was thinking like how if you have to
drop like it wouldn't work so well
that's
[Music]
the thing but then I have no mouse oh
wow oh well oh well I mean I have
another mouse but recently I bought
another mouse
hearing me
oh my God look at that weird
okay this is really does it really work
does it really work
is it really
[Music]
I don't believe it
because my mouth no it's not working
I have maybe it's not supposed to work
yet move cursor pain comes out while
pressing
oh okay
[Music]
uh-huh
no the mouse isn't working when you lied
to me
I change it in the settings okay
oh
wait
is there motion control
would work too
I think wait on there okay and button
button and mouse so uh the mouse can be
used in TV mode only drawing operations
as possible with a month okay okay okay
foreign
it doesn't work
eh it doesn't work what today
what
motion control is pretty bad really
good yeah it's even shiny it's like
glowy and shiny it's it's wired
try restarting
have you tried turning it off and on
again
I think I'm like going crazy like today
what's going on
Nintendo brand Mouse only
[Music]
no way what I didn't even know Nintendo
hand
you are one guy in me right there's no
way
no
[Laughter]
okay let's try
[Music]
no it's not working okay I guess I'll be
drawing like this which is like super
slow
I understand there isn't even like a
mouse setting here but I just says a
common mouth of USB connection can be
used for yeah okay that's what I'm using
um mouse that required require Drive
insulation no no didn't need that
operation is not guaranteed at all
why not
into Nintendo switch I have it on like
the side
or should it be inside because there's
another USB inside
maybe that one
[Music]
I'm going crazy
I'm already going crazy
I am doubting my sanity already
okay I plugged it inside not outside
[Music]
um
not working
okay whatever I don't give a [\h__\h] I'm
not gonna make this Nintendo friend but
[\h__\h]
Nintendo brand batteries do you have
another mouse yes I have another mouse
where is the end of the cable though I
don't know
oh
okay
I get my other mouse back nice
oh
this mouse works
why does the other one not work it's
basically the same shitty
shitty cute game around
and they're both wired
thank you for at least I guess
motivating me to try I was gonna give up
ah
this one is Nintendo approved I I I
don't think so I mean it says
this one maybe maybe it has to do with
um
I don't know
who knows
we will never get a logical explanation
okay let's I mean okay it feels kind of
funky but okay draw something and have a
touch the red ball
uh okay
that is too easy
next we're now we're getting really into
it guys okay finally touch the left wall
with the balls
okay
uh
oh
let me retry
um
[Music]
yeah whatever no need to oops no need to
overthink it oh oh it's going there on
its own okay okay
can't wait for level 25. oh is this the
one that uh Iris struggled with touch
the left wall of your drawing draw a
stick and Let It Drop draw a slope and
let something roll on it
choice is yours
turn
[Music]
on
this new questions appeared questions
[Music]
what there's questions
what the [\h__\h] is all of this
what is this
what is this I thought we were only
drawing balls
[Music]
there's more to this game
interesting
eh
different level types
there's one thousand to one levels oh my
God what anyway
oh I'm I'm I'm like I I I I I feel like
I'm I'm having a stroke while I'm
streaming today
[Laughter]
um all right
Jiro operation is also possible drawing
by shaking the controller oh what
please refer to the settings controller
okay what take the ball out
let's kill him let's kill this ball
let's kill this Bulldogs
um
oh oh good try that wasn't really what I
was trying to do
no no no wait okay okay okay we try
really
[Music]
there was a counter about to start hey
yo hey yo
mmm
Scoopa
maybe different angle like this
no no
no
bgm is making me crazy actually I feel
like we should change the PGM to our own
[Laughter]
you could draw more yeah I just realized
I can draw here too okay
[Applause]
[Music]
I don't want you here please leave oh no
what this camping is difficult what if I
try the other side surely the other side
will be on my side
oh
Nani what am I doing
I'm just I'm just I'm just um
um
I I I I have a big brain than this don't
worry guys I I know exactly what I'm
doing let me cook
um
I make a boat
no yeah
no can I not make it even heavier
ah go go away go away
go go go away go away go away
no no no
both almost break right maybe I make
both boots closer to ball
let's go
no maybe the sale should be not as
pointy
here but
oh
it was a good a nice build up though
nice buildup
oh sure you're sure
ah come on why why why why am I
struggling this much try gravity
I don't know much about gravity
here's a Kill
the kill kill not convincing
okay [\h__\h] it
oh it's like it's like peas why is it
not moving any more than this
supposed to go to the other side
try a shovel okay
here I make a shovel
[Laughter]
drop a rock light rock okay
here Rock
[Laughter]
what that was a big shovel you want a
small shovel
oh God it's so hard I'm actually
left-handed because of the mouse I kind
of always use right hand and it's not
good
[Music]
it's an art stream now yum
got a feeling to make it heavier does it
actually work
can you make it heavier
like this
oh
nah I feel like that even my first
attempts were better
oh
[Music]
yeah
why am I already having issues
oh
no no don't fall that way fall the other
way
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
this time this this come on
why why why why
[Laughter]
this is puzzle five yeah
I don't know I don't know
thank you
I make a flower
because make me happy
go flower go go flower go go
oh almost almost the flower I believe in
the flower power
make it make small flower
there we go
let's go
[Music]
oh thank God
make the ball touch the left yeah okay
that's already easier I think do these
puzzles increase in difficulties
oh [\h__\h] I blocked it off no
[Music]
no no
upstairs
no they become easier
sure
I I that sounds very relievable
then it will get stuck inside
now just gaslighting me why do you do
this
what if I just make small
um too small
but but but but but generally it doesn't
have to be that long I would say
why
wait I make it heavier on the bottom if
that really really really really works
let's see
flower
okay very ugly flower
no
I have another flower well of course it
doesn't work
hmm
[Music]
why
pink physics
what
what what the what am I what am I
supposed to take from that
how how
how about this
somebody said center of gravity so I'm
thinking the center of what I'm drawing
should be the heaviest
well I don't even know
even though it's over in the first place
in the beginning I don't remember
oh
okay
[Music]
now that no no way will make it out of
that
um
[Music]
another method I can't think of any
other methods
uh uh
okay
oh
[Music]
what
see eh what
you guys
have you even played this game would you
even know like if you were playing this
alone you know then you can use watch of
course you feel super smart especially
if you've seen other girls already
play this game and solve many of these
puzzles then of course you already know
the solutions and now you feel like
extra smart don't you
well I don't feel very smart
yes we're gonna get there we're gonna
get there
please why you know become heavy
ah
I I think the stones a tip it over is a
kind of a good idea though but
oh wait oh
no now it's kind of attached the wall
okay
but I need this hook form
next Stone smaller
music note but no that didn't work
okay
am I looking uh weirdly up I think I am
wrong Mouse
no need for a hook really what
did I go
hi
ah
let me fix my
positioning a little bit
okay
two mice on my table and no cat inside
doesn't that sound weird to you wait
want it bye
what if I go this way
what if I go that way
could that in theory work
we will see we'll see we will see right
now bye
bye try using a pyramid what
a pyramid
you mean a triangle why are you using a
fancy word for triangle huh why does it
have to be a pyramid
foreign
[Music]
keeps drawing as it falls okay but then
we need a game plan like what am I even
gonna draw
um
no
oh
[Music]
interesting
what do you mean
laughs
oh my God
I don't get it
how do you how do you kick it over
something
how can it kick it
here I draw a shoe
well you know okay I can't take it how
am I supposed to kick it
[Music]
make a ramp and roll a boulder
foreign
like you know even if I do that
oh wait maybe
oh oh you're right a ramp maybe needs
some support
okay here beautiful ramp
I must say
[Laughter]
ah
ah it was such a beautiful ramp though
foreign
[Music]
too long I guess it was too long
it's like a toilet seat
[Music]
okay it's smaller
[Applause]
no no no no no what are you talking
about
heavy part on the top okay
wow
but but but but but but but but
oh
for the way okay
further away
oh God sorry
oh my God
it's okay it's okay it's okay I'm okay
I'm okay so this is like this couldn't
possibly might break me
oh
no
[Applause]
[Music]
this is six out of a thousand well I
mean reaching number thousand was never
a goal in the first place though
that was unrealistic the moment you guys
told me it has so many I knew that that
wasn't gonna happen
what
do me like this ah
oh no no no no no no no no no no no
no
good idea bad drawing Oh I thought you
guys liked my art streams
I mean all right I was doubting it and
you you guys were like oh we love your
art do more do more and now you're
really telling me that
phrase that [\h__\h] feather rephrase it you
broke my heart
okay this is now a bird go back
off
malbert was not a good idea
um
foreign
like what do you mean reverse like like
this
like because normally five looks like
this right
So when you say reverse
do you mean on the bottom this should be
where the Scythe is
or or what exactly are we talking about
what do you mean
[Applause]
oh [\h__\h]
how is this not working
I'm evolving
yeah well why are you all typing these
yeah that's what I that someone said
what what are you typing me quackle
okay
um
[Music]
like uh the day before yesterday or so I
just randomly wrote at the end good at
Corazon
with no expectations but literally two
seconds later she answered me in caps
lock with quaso and I was so happy I
didn't think she would like jump on it
especially not that fast
but I'm so happy that she's one of my
people I told her oh my God one of my
people oh
I was so happy
yeah I guess I mean yeah knows the meme
[Music]
um
reverse size I mean this is all I can
think of when you say reverse size but
uh
this will be replayed in the years of
the room
thank you thank you like it oh no what
the [\h__\h]
try hooks again I don't know what the
hook looks like
the other d
ude
um
oh God
lowercase letter r
aw
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
I don't understand why am I having
so many issues
why
that's beautiful
what
[Music]
um
okay wait okay before we go any further
um oh I need I need there to be my own
music because this this doesn't even fit
the mood
if I'm going crazy by doing this then
you guys deserve to go crazy as well
thank you
why do I not here
Paul got some BDM coming for you guys
coming
okay don't worry I mean eventually we
can also like change it up a little bit
later on
I'm thinking all our frustrations on you
exactly
well
I still think
my original theory has potential
I I
still think
my original theory has potential
[Music]
[Laughter]
mom and me oh no
Nani
place the upside tip of our over the
pink ball and stretch to right side what
what
what what
what are you trying to achieve
um can you read
what are you even trying to
read
and they call me
it says here make the ball touch the
left wall
okay do that but execute it better what
a great advice
that
put execute executed better ah mamma mia
sorry let me read it again place the
upside tip
the upside tip
what
uh what the the the
UPS the upside where is the upside
what
what like if this is an R do you mean
this as a tip
uh yeah okay but like how
here there you go
should I make the bottom
stronger
[Music]
[Laughter]
is this is now grapes
welcome to my grape vineyard model
effort
oh
Chihuahua yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
I hate this game so much
fill it fill it
[Music]
feel what
[Laughter]
[Music]
everybody was like holding their breath
for a moment and watching as if they're
watching the the world championship of
football excuse me
[Laughter]
oh this like the last elf meter she's an
11 meter shooting what you call them
oh we call it literally just 11 meter
shooting because you're 11 meters away
from the goal and you have to shoot it
from there that's what we call it
they call it a panel that's such a
negative sound to it
why must you like you know physically
you know psychic psychologically
manipulate the players by giving it such
a negative undertone
wouldn't it be better if you call it
just 11 meter
shooting
ball shooting
11 meter happiness maybe even that you
know make it extra happy
foreign
challenge let's call it rewarding
challenge
really you're just gonna go back are you
now bonus
like mini game uh 11 meter mini game
it's been an hour what
what
why does this not work
[Music]
[Laughter]
whatever shut
why wouldn't that
we're doing differently
imagine it working now
oh almost
[Music]
[Laughter]
hmm
foreign
can we fix this situation
[Music]
make the weight smaller
okay
um I think I need a new awesome this
one's broken no no
no you can fix me
look too big
ah
okay it's okay let's just um
take it easy okay let's check it easy
try to stretch to left so it can have
enough power of gravity not down way
stretch to left
[Music]
Annoying Orange
I like your name because I am an annoyed
orange right now
I love you I love I love you
I love you
but you're probably just looking up
Solutions online or you played it
already
right oh my God why whoa whoa whoa whoa
rest
make the ball touch the left wall which
ball oh there's a ball
what what what what what touch touch how
how can you even what am I supposed to
save this
I think that says depression
or something like that whenever they can
do it catch them do I catch them
I like how they just fall apart oh
Melancholy
um
yeah
okay okay wait wait wait wait wait make
the ball touch the lift why is it the
left one again huh why must it be the
level and what I mean no no no no
stop
[Laughter]
ah
come on
no I don't even know what I'm like
trying to do eventually I don't I don't
understand
gravity I know I'm saying it right now
of gravity
with the air it's falling
I know
[Laughter]
don't release the click
it
oh
even when I'm not done drawing it will
stay there
can I push it no
um
[Music]
thank you
[\h__\h] I followed What
uh
hmm
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait okay
[Laughter]
that was good before
I had it
but then how do I should I just leave it
like this maybe
no
ah
[Laughter]
[Music]
let me just
yeah okay I mean maybe live in this safe
Zone we can make something we just have
to like you know
push it
and then ruin it
[Music]
um
cheese Strat
go go go
go pink ball go is this really like
there must be a like a nicer solution
than this
no
really this is ideal oh okay
oh more levels yay I am so happy to see
that draw something and touch the red
area
oh but I cannot draw in the blue area
whoa oh
go ball go
okay no no no
um wait can we apply like a roller
coaster no because it's only like one
dimension
no I thought it was like a side
Gathering speed here go down and then
with the momentum it would go up
um
like why not oh wait why don't that
can I
Mew
okay okay
easy
hey okay I came up with that one by
myself oh
oh
oh I watched a clip of this
um do I remember the solution wow
wow wow I mean
Maybe
[Music]
let's make something like this so what
you can't do is make your own balls I
know that
but we have to push them out
I don't know how
I I don't know how
um
okay
I mean the ramp was nice I would say
that was a 10 out of 10 ramp
beautiful beautiful
[Music]
um
[\h__\h]
the ramp has a state ignore the RAM for
now we can always improve the ramp the
problem really let me before we do
anything with the ramp let's let's uh
let's experiment okay
dear
oh
no how did I do that
I think like it's falling down is good
because it gives it like a bump
uh-huh
so if we make it rather heavy
and fall down
oh [\h__\h] oh wow I mean if I do that here
oh wait that was too close
yeah I mean I mean potential is there
let me cook let me cook
ah okay but again too close sorry I keep
on trying too close because it has to
fall
yo yeah okay that's a good that's a good
like momentum
okay okay
um let's start
um I don't want to start too much in the
front because if I mess it up I could I
could block everything
[Music]
that was like really it really
penetrated the pool of balls deeply so
that was quite something
um
I mean you guys are like yo but I mean
wasn't it like correct what I said
okay I may have ruined it now yeah I did
but okay
right right yeah right yes I would say
so too thank you technically you're not
only technically you just have a dirty
mind
we sure
I I by the way I I went shopping today
to buy some things
that I needed and I saw I went into
eclairs you know Claire's is this like
accessory shop that has a lot of like
childish accessories but not only
and it has like really cute things and
there was this girl in there she was so
cute the moment I walked in like I think
even from outside I saw like she was
dark cutie patootie
and she was like all pink
like obviously like Japanese fashion
inspired I would say
and and and she had
pink pastel pink hair like everything
was pastel pink not just pink pastel
pink huh
she was so cute
[\h__\h]
oh
interesting
uh one ball in let's try again
yeah she was so cute so you know what I
did I was like how can I not tell her
that she's cute how how could I possibly
not tell her I need her to know
spreads positivity so I walked in the
store I immediately went up to her I
poked her in the shoulder and I said
super cute you are like so super cute
and she was happy and she said oh you
too and I'm like nah I mean I mean you
the way you dress yo I
I made me somewhat try to dress like
that back in the day I can't pull it off
anymore but you are super cute
told her
I told her because I just I didn't even
feel
no I wasn't like flirting or anything I
just found the need to let her know that
she's doing a good job in terms of being
cute no I wasn't even trying to be you
know flirty or anything like that no
I was just making a statement
why don't you wanna do that
[Music]
what I am telling you
I have the solution
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
oh [\h__\h] you
let me try again like without the ramp
no it has to fall it needs to bounce
foreign
way around
no
it was a good bounce
what if I make it all this long
wow okay that was a huge bounce but it
holds them down we don't want that
what if it's like half the length
oh
wow wow wow
yeah they bounce so much over here can
they do that here because here they can
actually get out there's no wall
blocking them do it over there
just do it over there
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
[Music]
I thought you could stand on your own I
guess and I guess not
it works better if you don't block the
exit
obvious statements
I'm aware of that I'm testing things out
[Laughter]
wait what that's not what I wanted to do
that's not what ah no
oh
we'll get there
[Music]
oh
that was cool I need more
at least this is making me as crazy as
the other one
but that's only probably because I know
in theory this is how it could work
um two balls yeah do you need any more I
mean
you you guys want more than two balls
all right let me see what I can do for
you welcome to Dr kiwawa's office
I will try my best to make you happy
you don't need to feel
ashamed or anything if you want to
change your body
there's no shame in such things your
personal ideals is what should decide
what you look like not the worlds the
society's ideals no you make your own
beauty standards that's right that's
right
reason
what
you're called a cyclops for a reason
[Music]
[Laughter]
um Cyclops has only one eye right
oh my God
doesn't it actually just say put
nine nine don't do don't
don't put five balls in the plate below
because there's a nine and a German nine
means no
I am just joking
what's telling me to not do anything at
all
why why why why why why why why
the times it worked wasn't I basically
doing it the same way
obsessed with the team well yeah just
give me the team spill it
a different shape what's your problem of
a tea why are you guys so hateful
why are you gonna be like that um
well party
one more huh
this one how do we get this one
out there
I don't think we can I don't think we
can
we what should we what should I draw
um
[Music]
no that doesn't work yet no it doesn't
work guys
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
oh well
I am
I am quite happier at the moment
oh my God that was
not preferable
so let me tell you something guys
yesterday
this was my idea okay I wanted to watch
um Dungeons and Dragons in the movie
theater and I thought my mom might like
it because back in the day we used to
play pen and paper or Dungeons and
Dragons something uh as a family
with my bro
with my mom with my sister
everyone
together
and I thought my mom might like it
because every I mean I I just knew it
was Dungeons and Dragons themes I didn't
know like
oh [\h__\h] you
I didn't know
I only heard it was really good
um and that it's like I asked a friend
if it's like immersive like if you're in
the story or if you see them playing
Dungeons and Dragons no so apparently
you don't
which is cool wow Mamma Mia
I want to use that give me that yo
um
please
[Music]
oh please no please give me the ball
what do you think about this shape
I'm gonna drop it I'm gonna drop it
I'm gonna drop it
yeah more
[Music]
heavier longer on the left a little bit
suck it Iris
ah okay I will get the karma immediately
don't worry
take the ball out oh no
oh no wait we just have to take it out
we don't have to have it touch anything
laughs
[Laughter]
it can't be that difficult but this uh
it's so long like the this thing is
[Music]
if I prepare here
what am I doing
what what am I doing not here
so it like Falls over more come on come
on
yeah
oh wait I didn't prepare
oh it doesn't work anyway
pretty good attempt you like the idea
right strategy nice see um I just need
to warm up to this game now we're gonna
we're gonna get
Pro edit
like no one else
and you have to think I am playing why
you're not in the in the desert rolling
around please
I have a handicap I am left-handed and
I'm doing this with my right hand you
know
okay
yeah
oh oh oh oh oh
no wait I can still with some weight
um
first of all secure this area
[Music]
I feel like with some yeah big boulder
salvageable
[Music]
make me like this
I don't want to fight if I have it fall
to the right side
because we're doubting it
haven't we had this before
oh
deja vu
um
almost the same
I think we had this before
hmm
an anvil what does an anvil look like
like this
I think
why would that
maybe on the other side
oh wait no oh that was bouncy
read made the ball touch the left wall
what
[Music]
yeah
what
right kiwawa
no
oh [\h__\h]
the animal was just outside well I mean
same thing
I thought we already had the same prompt
not outside but touch the left wall it's
just because we had so many so many
times they want us to touch the left
wall
I don't know I know
foreign
[Music]
rocking it like a baby in a rocking
chair
[Music]
anyway let me talk about dances and
Dragons
so uh yeah I asked my mom and my bro
because I heard that my mom was coming
over
uh yesterday Monday
and I thought oh maybe she would enjoy
it and my brother watched it before in
German but wanted to watch it in English
so I also I didn't mind
I didn't mind watching it in English
of course of course
so we went to watch
dances and Dragons yesterday
start with a tease I will deliberately
continue with the tease
foreign you it's not even a tea it's an
anvil can't you see
how was it it was so good this it would
touch the right side and you tell me to
put it on the left so I feel the guards
what if I had the same thing happen but
the opposite way huh then we would be
done now
so close
um
[Music]
oh wow we flipped it wow there is
potential there guys
house is even working why are you
doubting things
you should believe in things not doubt
things
anyway so I came to the cinema my bro
and my mom also just arrived
easy clap and um
I thought it was a cockroach Alex
raise him oh okay and and and then first
things first
I wanted to get popcorn I'm never sure
these days if I want sweet popcorn
or salty
but okay I will go to the counter what
am I doing wait oh interesting
and and and I asked for
sweet popcorn and then they give me
these sweet popcorn that are so
caramelly and generally I don't mind it
but yeah maybe mixing could be an idea
at some point I don't know if they would
do it maybe they would
but
um
I don't mind caramelly sweet popcorn but
normally in the popcorn you get here are
just sweet and not caramelly
like no strong caramel taste but these
ones had such a strong caramel taste so
I was like disappointed afterwards after
I tried
and then my bro he starts like munching
on his salty popcorn endlessly
[Music]
and not able to stop himself
and then he's like hmm I want to get
another even though he ate like one
fourth of his popcorn and then we we
still had like 20 minutes until we could
even officially enter the room right
so he was worried that he would run out
of popcorn so he's like I'm gonna get
another one now
and you can have the rest of my current
popcorn so nice because I basically got
a free popcorn
sorry if that hurts bunny sorry Alex
sorry I'm just experimenting here okay
let me erase you
let me raise you
flavor towards bottom is very strong
listen though is it though
yeah I got some free popcorn hell yeah
the salty ones I really enjoyed the
salty ones suddenly you always enjoy you
always want the popcorn that you didn't
get
whoa ho ho ho ho ho ho
[Music]
can this work though
I feel like in theory what I'm doing is
correct though
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh
Alex Alex
Alex Alex please
much much momentum
our legs
why is your reset because I didn't know
where to go from there
anyway yeah uh and then oh yeah my mommy
said who's like Mommy you know not want
anything
five or two is Here regular chicken uh
totally
uh a chicken
because otherwise my lore would make no
sense
can I flip them over that
uh
what are you doing
I stand now
what
I'm doing all the things with him that I
don't want to do
um
foreign
yeah I am the only Phoenix in our
Dimension that's my lore so I cannot say
he's a phoenix I'm sorry brother anyway
my mom is like you know typical oh I
don't want no I don't want I don't know
no I don't want and then in the middle
of the movie she's like
she Whispers my brother's sitting in
between us and she whisp us over to me
she's like well can I get can I get you
a sweet popcorn that you're not eating
I'm like
yes and then she eats the whole Alex
Alto thank you
thanks for the pinky she eats the whole
left like I I basically only ate like
five popcorn from my sweet popcorn and
she eats the whole thing
I'm like well good good that I got the
the salty ones from my brother
ate the whole
Alex Alex
please yes why are you even can you just
like lay still not like in this form we
want
I guess I didn't then I couldn't hold on
to you
what do you think about that idea huh
when you think about it
eh what
what I raised him how was
it like my old child
Alex come on I raised you just like
Jimmy
I can't help you more than that can I
swear to God
laughs
I'm gonna stab you
I'm gonna stab you with this knife
so okay back to Dungeons and Dragons
I've never been in this Cinema before
like it it's like such a tiny Cinema
so tiny tiniest Cinema I've ever seen
um so until the movie started it was so
noisy it was like pretty full but I
guess well it was also really tiny
it was pretty full though and
I'm sure
come on come on
they were so noisy and I was like these
people were shut up right when when the
movie starts they'll shut up right
please please
then the movie started
and it still took them a while until
they shut up
um but it was okay eventually after like
a minute or two
they did shut up except for like four or
five really giggly girls
two rows or so behind me
I mean okay I understand that the movie
was really funny I was thinking it was
so funny but these girls two rows behind
me they must have been high or something
because they laughed at every single
thing really loudly really like the
whole time they watched they left 24 7
as if they were like hired to be the
Laughing track for this movie uh
although it's not supposed to have a
laughing track this movie okay this is
not friends this is not Big Bang Theory
okay
yeah
it was so annoying I mean good that they
enjoyed it but my God I thought it was
really funny too but these girls were
like excessively laughing
must have been on to something
or Alex
like Ed do you guys laugh out loud so
much when you think something's funny
when I watch something like I I never
like when I even when I think it's funny
like it has to be like exceptionally
funny for me to make me laugh out loud
right you guys too right it's like like
aha this is so funny but like my face
and facial expression is still resting
[\h__\h] face while inside I'm like this is
the funniest [\h__\h] ever
right this is normally for most people I
think how it is yeah
nose XL
what no success I just smile yeah maybe
a little bit of a smile
said to smile like you know yeah I
smiled a lot at the movie
but laughing out loud
you laugh a lot at my streams really
well thank you
thank you I guess well I almost had him
lifted come on
how did I do it how did I do it before
how did I do it I almost had it I almost
had it before I was like I changed my
mind while I was drawing it like this
thing
I don't know no that wasn't quite it
that wasn't quite it but I'll try
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
[Music]
he pooped
oh
[Music]
um
come on come on come on
oh my mama and my man
oh
um
how is this not considered raised
draw
why are you not raised
uh
his foot
I swear to God
come on
I can't I can't do any more than this
you little [\h__\h] you little [\h__\h]
who's that kid
[Music]
what what
ha
that already tips you over so much
excuse me
um
this is really like
too much work Alex
okay okay
I make a ball you cannot be
any further than this okay Alex
promise me
[Music]
set up
no no no no no Alex no no no no no no no
no no no no no no
[Music]
why Alex why why why why
why Alex hmm
[Laughter]
[Music]
Raise Me Up better I'm trying
there we go
foreign
that was unfair like you should give it
like a good amount
a certain amount of you know
[Laughter]
for a while okay he has just bad posture
[Applause]
it wasn't just raising it was making him
stand
hmm
oh in Japanese he's called a hero not
Alex
they here it's in Japanese in the
thumbnail says in Japanese
draw something and touch the red area
okay
it seems like there's a million options
to do that
um
I just thank you for the memberships I
just want to say
have you guys seen Dungeons and Dragons
it is so good yeah I think it it it's
maybe in my top
10 top 15.
favorite movies Maybe
attached it
it was so good like ah can I just talk a
little bit about it without spoilering
thing somewhere I don't think that any
of this is spoiling so uh I had no idea
what it would expect me because I did
not watch a trailer or so
[Music]
um
but the actors I liked the actors very
much uh like at least one of them looked
kind of familiar to me the the the
supposed King but I don't know where do
I know him from I wonder where I know
him from
it's very famous though I think very
famous face what am I doing I don't know
I just want to talk about Dungeons and
Dragons really quickly Chris Pine
oh
and since I played Dungeons and Dragons
and pen and paper and all that in my
life before I must say even though you
never saw you know people behind it
playing this out or so and it was never
mentioned that there's like you know
this is the Dungeons and Dragons plot no
still the way things are happening in
the movie is it's just very dangerous
and dragons like and and very funny
because like so many like random things
happen are not really random but like
absurd things happen it has the vibe
yeah like so many things are being
attempted and it's it's just so good and
and yeah it just feels very DND
um
I went to go watch it with the group's
idea for oh that is so nice that sounds
cute
um
I really liked the shape-shifting
actress she's really cute oh my God
she's
and and
um the the main character was very funny
like they all were really funny but the
main character yeah he was very funny
and then the one character who didn't
stay for too long the the really strong
one it was also very funny and and I I
like how in the like when they said
goodbye to him it was like they
literally said it themselves like why
don't you if you if you would like you
know join us you know we would have way
less problems achieving our goal hint no
no and then he walks away and he walks
in this straight line over the and then
and they comment on it oh he walks in a
very strange line is he gonna walk
around to the Big Stone or is he gonna
walk just over and then oh oh he walks
over it so funny
and then and then oh my favorite part
was the dragon the dragon was my
favorite part like oh my God
because it reminded me of chonkers and
ah no it's not it's not really a spoiler
come on a fantasy movie it's bound to
have a dragon
bout to have a dragon
hmm
and and and oh it was so funny I
couldn't stop laughing that was my
favorite part
um
spoiling no just watch the movie you
should be up to date yeah dances and
dragons in the name
[Music]
in the name don't don't don't you dare
it
feather me for that
yeah and and and oh I really liked the
um
I mean if I say
obviously there's gonna be someone evil
right if I just say don't if I just
don't say who
is it okay I like the evil person
um yes the evil person
I liked the evil person you guys are so
mad let me talk about it
and and oh oh oh oh
what can I even say when you guys are
like this hahaha
ah at the ending though the ending I
must say like my mom and my bro they're
saying that it was really obvious that
they were gonna do that
but
and I I saw that it was building up to
it but I still feel like it's a weird
Choice do you know what I'm talking
about you know what I mean why is my
chat not moving hello are you alive
hello
do you know what I mean
oh there he goes oh my God
yeah it has an ending yeah it was
obvious yeah I mean it may have an
obvious but like think about it think
about it is is that like the right thing
to do I'm not sure it left me with a bit
of sweet feeling just for that but
besides that it was it had everything it
had good dialogue uh like really witty
and fast and it had good like animation
and had good effects it had good uh
actors it had
um lots of humor it had lots of Dungeons
and Dragons Vibes and then it even had
like a little bit of you know a little
bit of like tear wrenching you know just
a little bit a tiny bit you know I
wasn't crying but I had like like this
oh
[Music]
again
that's what that's what I was like yeah
yeah
it's a DND ending fitting for the
setting
yo it was so good it was so good I
really really liked it and yeah it was
good length the only thing that was so
annoying was that these girls were just
laughing at [\h__\h] everything it was so
noisy
okay
um
oh
[Laughter]
back to the game
[Music]
no
don't overthink
foreign
why don't why can I not use my t-shape
huh
why does it not go up why can't it not
be in like a roller coaster
catapults aren't fixed in the middle
oh right right right
thank you thank you
whatever whatever uh
uh stand
um
no
I'm not gonna work with no actual like
mechanical tools
when you say triangle do you mean upside
down or do you want
you mean for my for my seesaw
seesaws do work really
all right how about this
[Laughter]
[Music]
ah
don't tend to please me I'm trying
[Music]
[Laughter]
to chat anymore and then it will be
worse because I won't get my advices
anywhere
I don't know just let me think just let
me think
foreign
thank you
chicken
[Music]
what I wasn't even done
what the [\h__\h] is this can I move these
things
well that's too easy don't you think
oh the ball's already moving
[Music]
wait it's already wait if you just wait
doesn't it go down there on its own
ah
[Music]
[\h__\h] no space
foreign
because apparently you don't have to
finish your line therefore you can defy
gravity oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] cheese cheese
cheese cheese cheese cheese cheese
cheese yummy
thank you
oh
[Music]
that's just smart that's smart
no because I I am smart universe
so me fixing that one so fast makes up
for all the time I took for the other
ones right
here I'll be so nice I'll even change
the vgm for you
so that you don't go too crazy
[Music]
this is worse or better
oh
I think it matches though very sassy
what is this again made the ball touch
the
left wall
we had this before what
what's different ah
what's it wait last time I guess it was
just let it out right okay okay okay
okay
[Music]
oh but this one this one was rough for
me wasn't it I'm not sure anymore
yeah yeah it probably was
um
no
[Music]
oh well
[Laughter]
oh good first try don't block the
opening it's all like I gotta say
well well
oh yeah right we played with like things
like this right yeah yeah
yo
[Music]
oh
no
no is that so have fun have fun
in Austria
are you alone or are you traveling with
family or with
a wife you know
hoons who's with you
tell me tell me everything about it
oh
[Music]
doctoral
friend
[Music]
we used to Steal Your Girl
with some friends includes chicks whoa
[Music]
you're you're traveling in a group
that's like
I feel like such a rare composition like
I either travel with like one person or
I travel alone rarely do I ever travel
in a group but it always sounds like it
was fun I saw I saw a friend of mine
traveling in like a bigger group it
looks like fun oh
um
as long as you all kind of I mean and if
you don't I guess you can split but as
long as you have all like the same kind
of Vibes like similar hobbies and things
you like you know
then it can be a lot of fun and work out
pretty nicely like if you're all like a
party people you want to go party in the
clubs let's go let's go
[Music]
don't go here don't go here
it's toxic here don't go there
can I save this
can I Salvage this I can you think
you think Andy hi how
it's like
maybe with some weight here
um do I need weight at the bottom too
no
[Music]
hmm
bite it push it yeah
[Music]
how
oh
[Music]
no no not not the end of the world
drop a rock but like onto once it's over
no
[Music]
and now it's over
uh how did I do that I guess I had
something here
I mean it's always the same basically
[Music]
oh God damn it
lucky
[Music]
foreign
so what what did I do what did I do to
make it work
the hook should be a straight line
you mean without weight
[Music]
but
when you had to lay it on the end it
doesn't have to hang down
King
[Music]
but it just ends up like this
come here
[Music]
um
foreign
just make a very long horizontal line
try
[Music]
are you sure
are you sure with the block down here
over that
[Music]
oh
I'm not giving up yet
[Music]
I don't know I don't know what's the
right thing to do
come out yeah okay
[Music]
Mamma Mia Mamma Mia
you blocked it you blocked me I'm gonna
block you on Twitter on YouTube on
everywhere
and you'll see what the real meaning of
blocking is
[Music]
I love you I'm not gonna do that don't
worry
hi karamba
Mario corrupted me what do you mean
Mario corrupted me Mario has nothing to
do with this
[Music]
I hate this
please please
um
[Music]
the tea is good the T
my T okay then what do you think is
the real problem
it's not a tea though
it's supposed to be an R
just just hanging on the wall
and I don't want to give it some weight
[Music]
come on
no way it will work just make the short
part of our shorter oh okay
if that does the trick Mr King of
depravity
you sir
are going to be
an honorary chicken
how short
[Music]
I don't
is this
[Music]
uh with wait or without
some people said you don't need the link
some people say weight is good
[Music]
oh
foreign
I don't even think I blocked anything
off there in the last moment I just
think it's still it still doesn't have
enough momentum so as long as this
Touches at once what if I just give it a
lot of momentum
[Music]
no no no no no no no
make it heavy
[Music]
yeah
I tried to make momentum
[Music]
I'm trying
that wasn't a lot of momentum yeah I can
see that
I can see it
[Music]
I don't know
[Laughter]
ah
um
[Music]
foreign
I am not interested anymore
[Music]
skip this one for now just let's just I
don't like it so I will uh oopsie
skippity scoop it fall now
here's this looks more like up to mine
smartness surely surely right
take the ball out take the box take the
ball out
take the ball out
for what for a walk for a date
for death
[Music]
what my chat broke probably because I
didn't have hyper chat on did I not have
hyper chat on
[Music]
to the movies I've been to the movies
like more in the past months than I have
in three years or so you know maybe more
like two years
yeah
my chat ah
it doesn't want to refresh all right
I'll give it some time I see you guys in
OBS though same same I don't know why
Eva just recently there's way more
movies that are coming out that are like
worth watching for me like my taste in
Japan I saw Sesame in
January
okay so in the past three months I've
seen like free movies in the cinema
and
before that I haven't I haven't went to
the cinema in a long time oh chat is
back so something was so good right I
think now a lot of you guys watched it
too because now overseas you were also
able to watch it
pretty good right it's very sad
and you know has some real life
references so makes it even sadder
um
you were busy sick over the last moms no
no even then like I'm looking at what
movies came out in the past two years
most of the time at least the movies
that came out in the cinema in Europe
just weren't oh no that interesting to
me no
that studio is very consistent yeah
make some tongs
foreign
[Music]
interesting
thing we hold it together
[Music]
and then
we Drop It Like It's Hot
I can't be too close to the wall
you may know you only hold it like your
dreams hold it like your dreams
[Music]
oh I don't know
I saw this on my back to back the same
day double swap loved it oh you saw both
versions huh
how was the English dub foreign
[Music]
vibes from this bgm
not too long
[Music]
great visuals as always but felt the
theme direction of the movie was
modeled model what does that mean
I really liked I said this before when I
watched it but I said again I really
like the the cat and the chair I have a
little merchandise of it thanks to
Canada
bought me the merchandise he I was gonna
find myself though
[Music]
mixed up let's clear
it's already been too long for me
um I don't even remember that well I
just know that you know there were like
you know
natural disasters and stuff
[Music]
I'm not sure what the message was
anymore but I don't think that's the
fault of the movie
I felt like the ending was a bit too
fast
I don't even remember that anymore we
can talk about Dungeons and Dragons in
the Super Mario movie that I still
remember
help
I like the cat more than a chair
um
speeches
[Music]
what a performance what a Flawless
gorgeous performance
not heavy enough
[Music]
[\h__\h] hell
foreign
[Music]
that is considered out I thought I had
to flip it completely all right let's go
sorry I got a dab that again
Alex is back put Alex in the container
wow
does it count if the container is like
completely like flipped to the side or
so
ask him nicely well he is very bouncy
right let's let's remember he's like as
bouncy as a bouncy ball
um
by the way today I had the courage to in
the supermarket
um go to the
members members who watch the member
stream yesterday understand what I'm
talking about but I had the courage to
go to the to the
um cashier's side where there's all the
magazines and I looked at uh one and one
did have the game with
with the little like you know it's kind
of water inside and you have these rings
and you have to shoot them to somewhere
um but unfortunately it has like
copyrighted was it Disney
I'm not sure that family with
um
uh what's that like animated superhero
family called that movie
[Music]
uh I'm not sure if it was Disney or or
the other one or so yeah The Incredibles
yeah it had that like all over the
device so I'm not sure if I could
actually show that
is that Disney or is that
Pixar what is Pixar Disney now
yeah if I find the device like that but
without this kind of copyrighted
copyrighted stuff well it's not too
obvious then
Maybe
[Music]
Alex in the container
don't make me do this again
Disney owns everything yeah why'd you
ever set because it looked like it won't
work
I mean
I mean what what did I do
let's let's let's just see
how he falls
[Music]
if we drop a big one
there's not much space here to
mmm do something fun with him
[Music]
hmm
what
drop a seven or a hook
okay maybe not that big
[Music]
um
but into his hand right
that's the seventh well I mean
kind of
yeah normally I would draw a seven with
a another thingy in the middle in Japan
when I do that sometimes people are like
what is that
because depending on the country
some people will never write it like
this and then it looks like something
else to them
so interesting higher okay
let's go
he was very affected by that but not the
way I wanted to
[Music]
uh
Alex teamwork do you understand teamwork
oh oh oh
okay Alex we just gotta go higher
we just gotta do it again
[Music]
Alex come on it's not over yet
maybe it is
oh
[Laughter]
Alexa Go Alex go Alex come on come on
come on come on come on
[Music]
[Laughter]
but now
same thing or because now I can't drop
it so much you know
make the top line of the hit his head
[Music]
we could try to draw something here and
on here and wait
oh would that work
is he stuck not necessarily I would say
I feel like you could still
make it work
his chin
I can't draw such a thin line
can this antenna be leveraged
you guys the way you talk about him
you're talking about him as if he's just
an object
[Music]
good I know
I mean he is
why what makes you think that because
he's on the screen
[Music]
because I'm awesome
admit it he's stuck no no
no no no no no no no no no no no
[Music]
he's stuck
foreign
[Music]
Alex we can't go on like this we have to
make compromises
life is all about compromises
you have to give and you have to take
or you only give but that won't make you
happy but
and then
at least you're not only taking because
that's definitely not gonna work that's
not gonna work Alex
[Music]
you'll want to make me happy
you have to
[Music]
huh Alex
Alex
what the [\h__\h]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
hey
God like he was literally [\h__\h] gone
he just he just needs to get some milk
some bad guys can I re-watch that
I wish I could can you re-watch what you
did before
[Music]
anymore
did anyone ever do this before like eat
him this hard my god
oh I need to watch it in the clipton if
you can't re-watch it
hey that was insane that was incredible
oh what is this wow
that's usually how it goes oh okay
I've been using him so hard he never
came back are you sure maybe you just
needed to wait a bit longer cause like I
was also doubting it but eventually he
came back he just must have really
needed him really hard
[Laughter]
she waited for him
everyone
they must like outside of the screen
extend the line so far that he cannot
possibly fly like away completely that's
not fair you can't do that
wait make the ball touch the red Ariel
[Music]
understood
no
no why don't you draw like I want you to
okay
first of all this
oh no no no no no no no no no no
no no why would you do that no way
these roly-polies what is a roly-poly by
the letter there's a song that goes like
rolly Pony rolly rolly Pony I think wait
what's that no that's not really how it
goes but it's called roly-poly a pale
bug a bug
that's a roly-poly a buck
yeah it's a tiara song
[Music]
it's a really funky good song big
recommend it just doesn't touch it it
doesn't have to stay there for long so
if it just and this stuff falls apart
huh
um
[Music]
no why must you go to this direction
no no no no no no no no no
laughs
I don't know if it's even smart to
secure this bottom area
[Music]
I could just do what I did first try
I can make a combination of that
[Music]
well I can at least attempt to do that
[\h__\h] now it's secured it too much
foreign foreign
[Music]
I want to draw the ball
more ball almost there
without the ramps but through the shield
on the other side without the ramps
[Music]
let me let me do this
and now uh
oh it's rolling over here
wait you can
[Music]
why is it on top of each other you can
roll it over there
you can just push it
what's up
oh
[Music]
y'all can't okay
yeah you're welcome guys what the [\h__\h]
made the Sumo wrestle touch the left
ball what happened to Alex
I guess they have no Alex's left over
because all the Alex's were like heated
into the void forever
okay I mean this is not difficult
this is not difficult
[Music]
not that difficult no no no
oh
um
it's scrambled it fell apart
[Music]
just watch and learn guys
go there go there
[Music]
whoa he's strong he's strong okay if
you're that strong I'm going to try to
use that to my advantage
foreign
[Music]
must you fall there
left side left side left wall
ah dos koi
draw just a tiny
he's balancing it too well
how can you balance it so well
[Music]
that almost worked holy [\h__\h] what
I do things the same way and they happen
differently explain
oh
okay this is the winning stretch welcome
everybody you're welcome
foreign
[Music]
I will not have you guys make fun of me
just yet there you go there you go there
you go
easy
ah
make the ball touch the left wall
is it is it is it easy
easy this may just be the easiest one so
far
[Music]
didn't think about that one did you guys
well
well I am just too smart for this world
yeah
you're looking outside the box exactly
no
yeah yeah you need that in life more
often than you think
outside the box
[Music]
oh
first try though first try baby
[Laughter]
I I you guys said it would get easier
ironically you said it as a joke but I I
am actually
I feel like I'm doing better in these
recent ones than I am in the first
couple ones
we just have to I guess get over this
one
I told you she was faking it this way
flowering I'm so [\h__\h] Gremlin today
why am I such a gremlin stop it stop
Kiana
yeah okay
at least if you go
to a thousand at this pace it will be
sure to seriously
that might be true but I am not making
this into series okay
um
kfp don't even put it into my
not finished games list because this
game was never like planned to be
finished and it's also kind of like you
know who the [\h__\h] finishes this game who
does such a thing
[Music]
it was a nice fall
no I need you to be round more like this
that was pretty good
try a long swinging Hammer what
[Music]
another
foreign
[Music]
triangle
I was my rock is too big it's my rocket
triangle I don't know [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] ah
[Music]
let her cook no no don't let me cook
although I do have to cook today I have
to cook I don't even know what my
recipes are this week
hope they're good last week I had like a
lot of really like easy recipes I would
just all whipped up in a second really
nice oh stop rolling away
[Music]
um
what is it about this riddle in
particular that I am not able to do
and basically what you did but make the
hammer longer to the left so it hits and
become the fulcrum as it hit the
container are you really using these
words
directed to me
[Music]
why don't you put a triangle instead of
a ball on the floor a triangle
at least you guys are not using
the pyramid board anymore
to sound extra smart
I
yeah
too big what the the triangle or the
hammer
it's not really a
hat
triangle
[Music]
that really was that so big
really tiny
and how far away does it matter
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
now
the weight was so big really
[Music]
okay
no no
I'm not a taller no my parents should
have been a little bit taller
[Music]
oh
I thought it was over guys
[Music]
oh come on come over come over
why must you do this to me
not who don't
no lesson learned
[Music]
uh no it doesn't feel like I could fix
this
[Music]
I don't think so because if I it's just
gonna roll into here if anything
[Music]
but I'll try I'll try I'll try Never
Gonna Give You Up Never Gonna Let You in
Tad last so one of the last episodes of
season two
they Rickroll you
here's the spoiler so you're ready
you're welcome if you're ever gonna
watch tadler so be ready for a Rick Roll
that's an absurd Rick Roll
thanks for the warning you're welcome I
was like what
we're doing this on purpose right they
know that this song that they chose has
this kind of effect on people right they
they know
great great wonderful
the audacity
yeah rude
[Music]
it's just gonna go in there again
foreign
[Music]
when you say don't curve it too much if
it's just that's pretty impossible
because then it can't work as a hook
foreign
[Music]
I'll make it heavier
but
[Music]
um we will strap the belly backwards oh
sorry
that's what that was just me on doing
things the way I always do them
[Music]
hmm
I think
[Music]
I think wait
just need some weight right just need
some weight
let me
make it safe
let me just make it safe okay
[Music]
but what if it blocks it
mm-hmm
[Music]
I guess they'll extend it
I'm not gonna reset don't tell me to
reset
[Music]
I need more weight anymore wait
I didn't block it though at least no no
no
[Music]
I feel like if I make a bowl here it's
just gonna go in front of it
[Music]
no no no no no face
when in doubt
send more balls
come on come on there must be a solution
to this problem to this dilemma
no no
no
it's quite stuck yeah
yeah duck stuck stuck forever
stuck this now
very stuck this one there doesn't matter
what I do at this point no no
I tried one cannot say that I didn't try
[Music]
this thing will not be the end of me
this will not be the end of me
[Music]
I hate this
keep the weight flat
um
did you guys know arm wrestling as a
sport
[Music]
I didn't
I don't know
until today
yes I was to casually explain video
yes ma'am I did
yeah
thank you casually explained that's the
first time I actually really learned
something from casually explained I
think
you can work with this can I
same thing again or what
supported from the right
hold it
can't make ramp at bottom
ramp
bramp what kind of ramp
so it doesn't go into the hole I mean
this one
like this
then can we really even flip it though I
mean
[Music]
so make sure it touches the wall
and now
hit it on the left side of a heavy thing
okay big rock on top okay
more on this one on the outer one no
more inside inside outer
a big flat weight so it doesn't roll in
the way
that is stuck admitted it looks pretty
stuck to me too
oh but the chat is hopeful I will do it
for the chat
don't question my weight okay [\h__\h] it
[Music]
come over here already
this is my Everest
I will be forever resting on this one
because I will be dead by the time I
could finish this
that's why the Everest is called the
Everest there's many dead bodies resting
on it no
[Music]
could work maybe
don't say stuck
it was named after someone called
Everest yeah that's what they tell you
what is that so dark that's based on
dark spots I know I've never doubted you
almost wow what's that almost about tell
me more explain yourself chicken explain
yourself
oh
did I think that would work no
foreign how far should the triangle be
away from it
how far is far is like good
whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa whoa
whoa no that was so good no that was so
good
[Music]
that was so good as close as possible oh
yeah that was so good that was so good
oh
[Music]
yo yo
yo
what's good
[Music]
it was red
I could have yeah my mouse it I was I
was about to do it because I saw exactly
this outcome happening
who's strangling a cat
[Music]
but getting closer to it I feel it
every attempt is bringing me closer
you you
know
I can
work
um no why do the balls never move the
ones that you want to move why do those
never move
oh
[Music]
chicken abuse
need different PGM need different vgm
need that's not the right Mouse that's
this is the right Mouse
needs different
[Music]
a little bit more optimistic maybe in
this one
[Music]
come on
um
[Music]
no stay stay
thank you
[Music]
I feel like I'm in a Zelda lava dungeon
you yelled so hard you started your
roommates cat oh this is coming over to
you oh no oh no you had a chance for cat
cuddles and I basically I deprived you
of it I'm sorry
I'm sorry
it's all my fault
and I know exactly how that feels
I'm knowing exactly man that hurts it
was rough [\h__\h] rough
missing out on that potential cat fluff
man
you're sure
I had a dream of cool by the way
and yo
I was legit treating her like my
daughter in my dream she was playing a
big role
I was I I don't remember anymore any
details but she was pretty much like not
my not really really really my daughter
there was still like this feeling of
okay I'm not her real mom but
oh
don't there
it was nice to see her in my dream
uh
maybe it's a sign that I need to take
better care of her because I see all
these clips of people trying to corrupt
Michael Ball
with all kinds of stupid things
so maybe maybe I'm telling myself in my
brain that I need to like be there for
her keep her safe
no
like they're not nobody is making my
daughter happy
[Music]
I was dying didn't work
I feel like it's cool wraps everyone no
no don't you dare
put the fault on my daughter she is just
a child okay
she has done nothing wrong
[Music]
thank you
laughs
it's happening again guys it's happening
again [\h__\h] [\h__\h]
why did you block it
like it
is
[Laughter]
[Music]
calm calm
positive energy Positive Vibes happiness
Serenity love
no
Chihuahua Chihuahua
you had to
it's okay we're almost there we're
almost there
I'm dying I'm dying I'm dying inside I'm
dying inside
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah I have to look at it from a
different perspective
just shouldn't get so salty at it
[Music]
leave flat
flat
[Music]
okay okay easy now um
this is the round is it though
I don't know
thank you Naruto
uh drop ball on the far right
here
[Music]
imagine yeah
it's not no this isn't
it's just gonna get stuck I think
[Music]
um
I don't give a [\h__\h] it has to no
[Music]
I know it wasn't the Run
drop something on top oh why did you
drop something on top
that was the wrong thing you dropped the
wrong thing on the wrong spot well you
didn't give me the exact coordinates on
where to drop it though
I'm having conversations with myself
there's people there's people there's so
many no no no no
hmm
what what caused and what cost hmm
well guys
we did all of these 20 ones I know
there's way more but I also need to read
super chats and I need to cook
afterwards so we're gonna leave it at
this because tomorrow's stream is also
early as well early early early for very
good for sea viewers um
I matched amen
what do you mean like in time or what
yeah tomorrow is two streams very late
in the uh evening for me at 10 people
like actually in 24 hours from now I
have an unearanced Carnival Cadet I ask
you to please come too if you got time
in 24 hours okay make it yourself an
alarm
but before that in 15 hours yeah 15
hours from now another alarm go go go
and we have Minecraft
maybe we will meet some Ian some
Japanese or IIT members maybe
um
I kind of need some time to practice I
don't know when
maybe some time uh some of the Minecraft
stream will not be forever long
um
uh it will not be endless because I need
to find some time in between somewhere
to practice practice a little bit
yesterday but
the Korean songs Take way more time than
the others because it's not about how to
sing it but it's about the pronunciation
worst case I will wing it I guess
I want to sing some Korean songs
K-pop tomorrow but also English songs
there's some English songs that I want
to sing
yeah yeah yeah okay tomorrow
yeah I know it will be for my
um sea Asia viewers it will be very very
bad time but if you're awake please come
anyway for the karaoke and if you're not
then please come for the rebroadcast Sai
hoso
probably uh next week somewhere next
week I'll be having the rebroadcast
how is your sanity my sanity
it was it's better now than it was in
the beginning
um
yeah the beginning quickly made me doubt
myself
and then I built up uh confidence
uh at number nine because I already had
like a rough idea and then it was
supposedly getting better not really
number 10 was rough again but then Alex
I think Alex
and yeah those ones and the third row
those were okay
yeah yeah you did get better as you got
more familiar with the mechanics
thank you very much
you guys were hopefully enjoying
roasting me and making fun of me
[Music]
anyone
I was able to beat hell levels one to
six but not primary nine or fifteen like
you did
[Music]
ah 15 was the one I was really
struggling with and nine was the one
other people really struggle with 19 was
genius
[Music]
and there was one that I even first
tried which was number 20. mm-hmm
I struggled with nine oh you too oh
yeah I mean if I haven't like gotten a
bit spoiled then I probably would have
struggled with it too
I mean yeah let's just say so out of
fairness
Alex yeah Alex
Alex I'm so happy I didn't lose you
forever I'm so glad
I'm so glad
I didn't give up on him
I believed he would come back
[Music]
what do we want to listen to now here I
have one that's I played this boom
before I think questionable super jets
here this is my questionable super chats
bgm
[Music]
goodbye Alex
you weren't a chicken anyway
you are a fraud
U dude
[Music]
foreign
fixes to the whole glasses thing that I
feel bad about requesting this as well I
feel like we can just ignore it can we
it's okay
it's it's all right is it what do you
think
where's my chat
[Music]
there
It's Magic I guess yeah
yeah
I am
whatever
[Music]
hey I'll move it how did it even go
there I didn't move it who moved it you
guys did you move it when you cleaned my
office when I was gone after hours
there we go was it y'all don't touch my
ears on my desk okay you're supposed to
clean the floor and the windows and all
that and get rid of the trash in the
trash bin but you're not supposed to
move the I mean you're supposed to
polish them every once in a while but
don't move them around please
just dust them carefully you don't have
to like move everything your fingerprint
time my talent
sorry that was a spider and I panicked
oh
are you okay did the spider hurt you
just remember the spider is probably
more scared of you than you are of it
okay
[Music]
hmm
we don't have fingers though
why did you lose them at corn on these
planes did you go to her and give her
your ubu means
so I'm not your first ocean is that what
you were saying
[Music]
first I'll see you
you lost your Ubi to someone else
[Music]
I thought I was special to you
oh all right you never had newbies are
you all right sorry never mind then
impossible was your first
she hot still I get it
foreign
oh man
this
[Music]
is cute
okay guys oh
what super chats are we reading I know I
read the members ones at least
um
[Music]
in the member stream
is cool too
[Music]
and here we go
if I have them the last one
oh yeah yeah that one scared me
[Music]
oh God so many reminders I fulfilled
like four deadlines yesterday
um today I woke up to even more like
okay wow this one's already passed and
this one too
this one oh please also fix this one
there was something in your recording
can you fix this
yeah
fill up time right now I actually I
decided to
I asked my Korean teacher if we can move
this week's lesson
just to another week basically
uh cause I got no time oh
[Music]
yeah yeah yeah
I recorded a lot yesterday
went quite well
some really
difficult challenging things to record
um but yeah
yeah at least it will be worth it
it'll be worth the efforts
still some things but since I did so
much yesterday I'm sure jenma will
understand that I need another day or
two for what's whatever is like left
over
[Music]
how did your throat feel after that oh
not so bad oh and
um recently
recently my throat has been overall
not feeling so bad
[Music]
most of the time
yeah
thankfully mm-hmm
yeah that's good
I think also probably a big reason is
that winter is over and so it's not so
dry anymore
um
[Music]
rant
it's spring time
[Music]
yeah
oh
every year in Winter it will be like
this
guys I received the finished version of
the members wallpaper for next month and
it's so good I really want to show it
but I can't until next week Monday on
the 1st of May
it's so good I want to show
I wanna show
I'm not sure if you know the artist it's
about
the artist has you know some following
but
I'm not I don't think you guys would
know
what's the theme
should I say
the famous
Onsen
now you will understand why it's so good
hey
[Music]
no but it's like not like you know crazy
spicy there's definitely spice there but
it's also just so well drawn like so
high quality the background is so
so high quality
it's so beautiful
[Music]
it's a spicier version no
no no I don't have like um if I make it
any spicier than that then I feel like
cover would have to stop me
[Music]
yeah you could like make it a little bit
spicier without
being stopped but you know this
wallpaper made me think
imagine you know Cali did you know
very spicy um nightwear didn't she
now imagine if I'm not gonna go through
with this but imagine if I asked and
they can't turn it down because it's
basically the same amount of Skin
showing if I asked for just a towel
wrapped around me like after bath
Chihuahua
with hair like up and like a like messy
maybe a little bit wet looking
and the towel wrapped around
yeah and then maybe a
an optional accessory bathrobe
that you can take off or on
imagine no I would use this all the time
it doesn't matter you know but I don't
think I'll go through with it I just had
this idea when I was looking at the
members wallpaper
a towel and the bathroom basically
it's cooking
think I think
I would cook really well
but uh
oh no don't know if I like the idea more
than my other idea
um
[Music]
you never thought I would seriously
entertain the idea
why not why not
now that I saw that wallpaper
now now I'm like
[Music]
um
whole alive who can get the spiciest
outfits challenge
Martin Cali top contenders
Here Comes new Challenger
where did she come from who is she oh
do not underestimate
Wawas
12 secret spices mm-hmm
extra spicy
down
[Music]
how can you vote when you haven't seen
my submission yet
what did I do
okay here we go I used one of the Holo
gura
expressions
for this thumbnail
cute
and I guess I had a good
idea of how I will be feeling today
already when making the thumbnail
oh by the way I wonder I've been
wondering like you know with some whole
life members not all of them but after
they had their 3D debut
the company like made their models like
public right for people to use and to
like do videos or whatever with it
and I haven't done it with milk yet
right but like they asked us like a long
time ago if we if we want that to happen
and I said yeah after after the debut no
problem but it didn't happen yet and I
was wondering maybe I should remind them
and then I was wondering if they would
do that maybe there's some talented
people who can use my model to make like
from the material for me like pngs of
kiwawa and variance poses and
expressions I guess you can do that with
like some MMD kind of programmer so I
don't know how that works but
no no
can't annoy him with stuff like that I
don't think so
I'm sure like it's probably not that
difficult to learn just to put a model
in a pose
there's like free poses I think
like you can download free poses
I think four other stuff like that
[Music]
um
MMD it's a it's a mess to use really
[Music]
if you guys you know want to challenge
that
I need to remind
management to
you know make my model public so that I
can have more stuff like this
more
[Music]
okay let's read super chattels oh wait I
put up the wrong thumbnail
I was gonna read Fire Emblem
superchettes
this is the one
the last part finale
here we go Jonestown hero thank you for
a rainbow
due to my work schedule I'm pretty much
certain to miss much of the stream but
I'm glad to have taken this journey with
utensil I've been a fan of Fire Emblem
since 2003 meaning this year Max 20
years old being a fan of this franchise
and no matter what this series will
always have a special place in my heart
nice
it's a series full of interesting
characters from the weird to the cool
and no matter what I always find myself
coming back for more and to me no matter
what I enjoy the interactions of much of
the engage Castle
hope you didn't you know
feel sad that I didn't enjoy it as much
while I have seen that certain parts of
engage have fallen flat with and that's
fair I'm so glad from the bottom of my
heart to both still see you have fun and
to see you keep pushing through
at the risk of sounding sappy I would
say that growing up and growing up my
taste in media and games tended to
differ quite a bit from people around me
yeah I can imagine like back then the
anime and stuff like that was not even
as popular as it is and as it is
accepted as it is now foreign
with my autism made it a bit hard but is
it's why seeing someone else experience
what I love means a lot to me
I'm sorry for roasting it sometimes
but yeah I did enjoy it and I'm glad I I
made another Fire Emblem gameplay game
playthrough happen on my channel
yum
it's nice I like playing long RPGs with
stories on my channel it's just nice to
live a freeway together and and
experience it together and think about
what to do together
figure out a strategy together
yeah
so I'm glad you enjoyed the Joe star
hero thank you so much for the support
and while there might not be a fire
emblem stream on my channel for a long
time from now on
hopefully the other things I do also
are interesting to you thank you so much
so much
engaged
and then Mall together at the ridiculous
absurd percentages
not being followed
by the game it doesn't do what it says
it would do
[Music]
a Panetta man panette was so opinion she
was so Opie
one MVP throughout the whole game
Jacob 47 attention
did I give Joe star a kiss I think I did
I'll do it again
soon oh wait Jacob was a pinky finally
hi thank you for being there hope you
enjoyed it too
uh at least in the end
I didn't unnecessarily extend it by
failing we we pulled through
surprisingly epically
was great thank you rad thanks for the
pinky as well At Last it's time for the
finale together with all of kfp's
mightiest may we slain the fellow evil
of this world though we have had our low
points we will prevail we shall win in
the name of the Divine Phoenix Kiana
glory to kfp and Viva
thank you
thank you for watching thank you for
staying with me through the whole series
from beginning to end my loyal ring
protector
and thank you for helping as well
your input was very very precious to me
I hope you
enjoyed lunch
uh thank you thank you for the rest of
the chat
how are you doing hope you enjoyed the
finale too maybe you couldn't stay until
the end because it went on really long
and late
you don't know maybe tomorrow is
Minecraft should be better for you
thank you for being here though
Jeff star thanks for the pinky
uh hi attention any chance you'll stream
Final Fantasy 16 when it's released I'd
love to see you play through
Jeff Jeff Jeff Jeff Jeff
[Music]
chef chef
Jeff Jeff Jeff Jeff Jeff
do you know
do you know Jeff
if I could I would
but I doubt it when is it coming out
there's a new Final Fantasy coming out I
haven't been following that kind of
stuff because I can't play it
no it's a Square Enix thing
[Music]
June
oh man I wish
I would
uh Japanese side can play it
in Japanese
[Music]
I think that was the thing
I think so wasn't that the thing didn't
they already play Square Enix games in
Japanese
besides Final Fantasy 14 MMORPG
[Music]
yeah it's some FF games already so
yeah it's different
yeah
oh man
I Really Wanna
like I don't know man
I don't get it I don't get it either
[Music]
full Japanese stream you mean the whole
series not just one stream because if
it's an RPG and it's kind of a
commitment
uh anir was exception near and Final
Fantasy 14 are exceptions yeah
[Music]
and I'm so glad near automata was an
exception because I'm really really glad
we got to play it
um
[Music]
oh
that is so sad not really I mean once we
get the
permission I will be on it immediately
trust me sorry Jeff for now it's not
happening
sorry to disappoint but thank you for
the support
[Music]
what
even even
[Music]
don't know if that's
correctly
translated
or like
written out
[Music]
uh where the [\h__\h] is the window there it
is
monkey thanks for the binky oh
I got The Big C Kiana oh I think I
remember this super jet let's go it took
a few years but I've managed to join the
sick suit hey
[Music]
[\h__\h] today I just can't get a good yawn
in came out of nowhere too so that was a
nasty surprise promotion Jokes Aside can
I ask you say pain pain go away and give
me a get out of the UR card did I I feel
like I let you get out already didn't I
[Music]
think I was like hey why are you in
there anyway
I think I did yeah I did how are you
feeling now by the way are you feeling
better
[Music]
Good Guys asking for cats much luck with
me
is she like doing a member stream right
now what
is she actually asking for that
wait you shouldn't be eh she tweet
she tweeted at me
when
what
I haven't seen
[Music]
reply to me on Twitter
honestly like
like no no shade or so but she doesn't
reply to me on Twitter often
I think
she's
I may be very clingy towards gouda right
now and and finishing her her presence
but I think she misses my presents as
well
for that wait it's five minutes ago hmm
look up
let's just
let's just uh
watch Lord of the Rings
uh together let's watch the rest of Lord
of the Rings together
switch
would she like cats
no she might because I mean
[Music]
I'm not talking about like a stream
watch long guys commit to the bit
ah
I'm scared that if she'd watch it and
then hated it that would lower her
opinion of me
[Music]
I feel like Lord of the Rings would bore
her no no no no she told me she already
watched the first movie a while ago
she told me that when we were in Japan
and she really liked it
and we were sending each other some Lord
of the Rings memes
she is based okay
[Music]
misfist what the [\h__\h] is your problem
what the [\h__\h] is your problem
[Music]
yeah
I will watch anything with you but let's
just let's just watch the rest of Lord
of the Rings together
that's
probably better
I I that's what I'm gonna write
[Music]
they're gonna send it I'm gonna send it
I can't believe she answered my tweet
foreign
[Music]
was about time
good
[Music]
baby
two years in the making yeah tuna yeah
yeah two two and a half two two and a
half
the fact you spare her of cats that
shows real love see see
I'm not a coward I'm thinking of her and
and her
her impression of me
I don't want to ruin what I have with
her now by forcing cats onto her
that would ruin everything possibly we
can't know I mean I I can see where she
would humor cats
[Music]
no but now she would nah it could really
go both ways but I think she would both
humor it and cringe at it both
Maybe
um
invite Ina
shall we let Ina suffer again
nah don't think you know what tolerated
whole Miss cats watch along
um
[Music]
well Kelly likes stuff like Shrek so
I mean I mean no I'm not saying that you
know Shrek and cats is like on the same
level no no not at all but I mean like
in terms of like you know cursedness or
or
chill out chill out guys chill out calm
down
come I don't know
I don't know explain my train of thought
there okay
just calm down I take it back I take it
back okay I take it back
[Laughter]
Pinky
[Music]
oh hey boss I have a question if you had
to live without doing one of these
things what would it be one eating meat
two eating veggies or three ketokatos I
do mean kids cats or cats
chat option free for you can be kiwawa's
content ah follow-up question is would
you could you willingly do it
[Music]
oh there's so many veggies like even
potatoes or veggies
I mean
wait do you mean are you here sansi Sean
do you mean cats or kitkats
[Laughter]
[Music]
is one here
they probably mean my cats
um
not owning cats or living in a world
that has no cats at all
that's also important because if I lived
in a world that had no cats and all then
I wouldn't miss cats
then I would go for that but if I lived
if I just you know wouldn't have cats
for myself
then I could still go elsewhere to pet
catch
so
maybe you know
um assuming that I didn't have trunkers
and smoothing it
if I had to like like let go of them
that would break my heart but if it was
before I got them and there was still
cats elsewhere that I could touch
then I would go for that option
um now
maybe
um besides that maybe I would give up
meat because I hear there are some good
tasting Meats
um
meat tasting Meats like options
[Music]
I don't really like like tofu and all
that kind of stuff though
when you say eating giving up eating
meat can I still eat fish see I have too
many questions Sanji Sean you have to
speak more clearly
because if I can still eat fish then I
think I'll be okay I guess I'll eat a
lot of fish then
[Music]
um
it's just me
I call fish fish
not meat
and many people give up on meat but not
on fish it is a thing
well
whatever this
this wouldn't even happen or it's not
like it has to happen anyway but
well if we if I have to answer
realistically where I cannot change the
way this world is
so you're just telling me that I can't
have my cats anymore or veggies or Meats
then
I wanna say I want to give up on meat
because it's just ethically more helpful
than giving up on bed that should tear
with vegetables
[Music]
um
so
that would be
a good option for the world
oh I suppose like that would at least
have some positive effect to it but
there's yeah there's really good [\h__\h]
meat like so let's just not answer this
question because I don't have to
um
I guess you know
[Music]
but I I think giving up veggies
was also very difficult there's like a
million veggies that I hate but then
there's one handful of veggies that I
really like
like potatoes
surely potatoes
so and corner
but especially potatoes
if I can give up on all veggies except
for potatoes
then we have a deal
maybe I make a religion where veggies
are not not considered potatoes where
potatoes are not considered veggies
and then I have a personal
excuse to continue eating potatoes
um
but in the end
who even decides wants a vegetable why
do I have to follow what someone else
says
that this is a vegetable and this is not
a vegetable
why can I not decide in my heart what is
[Music]
right
for me vegetable means
something I don't like
so
[Music]
cauliflower for example
so let's get rid of that and let's keep
all the veggies I like and then I'm
happy okay deal thank you
super SSG is
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
happy birthday
Thomas is
thank you
it's time for the finale though the DLC
does exist so as a loading screen once
said the end is never the end collab
yesterday was fun don't worry you're a
great YouTuber for our time limit good
luck tencho
ah
was I four hours oh yeah this is like at
the eighth hour almost
whatever flights
does she want to watch cats
please
oh
I mean
your choice
foreign
slumber party plans
for the future
hey
what's what's the phone what is what's
going on is she
she having like a
once going on
[Music]
she wants she wants to watch it guys
I tried to save her
[Music]
I really tried
she
wants it
when you if you and I but when if you I
then when you if
[Music]
draw
should I call 9-1-1
[Music]
I'm still okay
she okay
it's a meme I don't know the meme
not a meme teach me goodbye
goodbye these words are losing it today
as something is going around man
no finish Lord of the Rings by the way
if you haven't I still wanna
what you could ever
[Music]
heard an update on that
although I wonder if me watching it with
her would influence
her enjoyment
[Music]
because sometimes I feel like watching a
movie alone
let's you like take it all in better
[Music]
but
but I
I love Lord of the Rings
mmm
Maybe
if she finished all the Rings we can
watch The Hobbit
I mean you can point out things too
I feel like when I watch something and
somebody like talks in between points
something out to flex their knowledge I
often don't appreciate it
because it's distracting
and
tell me afterwards
or on the second watch through
um
[Music]
yeah I don't like talking during movie
at all
you're breaking my immersion
throws me off too I mean you know if we
do like a watch along as a stream or
especially as a collab with like a
double watch along
for those cases I think you know it's
different because if we were just silent
for the whole movie it would make no
sense that we're doing it in the first
place
that's a different story right
hmm
that is different that doesn't mean that
if I would watch a movie with someone
IRL that I would talk during it no no no
no no no no
[Music]
that's also why I got annoyed at the
people laughing so much
I hate chatting during movies but watch
Longs are different for me right yeah
otherwise you know you could you might
as well just watch it alone if I weren't
talking
so it's good that we watch a lot of
movies that you guys have already seen
and I haven't
because then for you guys it's maybe not
so distracting or disturbing when I talk
in between
hmm
[Music]
there are some people who watch the
second time and spoil on the moon in the
cinema yo my bro is really good at not
spoiling anything
because he watched a second time who's
sitting next to me and he didn't spoil
her anything
good brother good brother
is going through it eh did she reply
again
hey
she loves me
to my 9-1-1 call
if you when the eye and in when you feel
and in the well
from our
German teaching or Japanese teaching
hmm
[Music]
I'm starting to understand
I
I think
foreign
gift that looks
you guys need to bring more kiwawa gifts
into the search function because like
there's so many unrelated ones uh
I do not understand why they are here
infiltrating the takanasikiana search
just because there's this Kiana actress
get out of here
[Music]
okay I'm looking for a good gift
um
doesn't
it doesn't match the moods the vibe
give me something good
[Music]
foreign
double so nobody gets offended
[Music]
that one's cute oh
I'm just
I'm just gonna
use sorry guys I need to impress her
with my gift game
I need to be funny
[Music]
your friend in the pick aside people
hmm
well
just stop getting offended then
just stop
[Music]
all right all right let me see what car
garage search has to offer
[Music]
at this okay this is good
okay okay okay
gift search very good plenty to offer
plenty to see
many fish in the sea
Twitter always says tweets too slow now
because it it wants me to read something
why you always take so long now
many fish but only one shark
I'm pretty sure there's more than one
shark
in the sea but good might be the only
shark outside of the sea
the only live one
I mean okay if you ignore like fish
tanks like big fish tanks in aquariums
the only walking fish on ground uh well
only walking shark on ground that's what
she is that's the definition that I can
give her
[Laughter]
sharks what
oh I tried my best to make it work why
must you ruin it with a loan shark huh
[Music]
are
um
whatever let's continue where was I oh
wow where was I where was I where was I
where was I
um
ah here I think at Martin thank you so
once again for staying there for such a
long time
thank you for helping me keep my sanity
as always
sent a pinky saying meow meow indeed on
topic right now it's all about cats
right now
spanking time
gura meowed at me too
the entire Street of course you always
there the entire stream
yeah thanks very much another cats
appreciate them right right yeah better
say yes
boohoo 724
substitute
and I will try voting endgame's world oh
that's why you left have you bye now
watched the end
because it was epic
dance
Astro Temple aphrodangashion
love the game too much and I'm having
separation anxiety and dragging my
flavor like units with Tails will rise
you know
oh man you should finish it though I had
this really epic last hit in the fight
in the final fight I had this like
unexpected
life-saving last hit that was like so
epic
hmm
yeah
nowhere
free presents man
uh Peak anime
well it was wild crazy after things
[Music]
thank you so much for watching I'm doing
thanks for the pinky it's already 9am
here but who needs sleep when you can
watch chihuahua always here from start
to finish for everyone on stream no
so sorry unknown what what am I doing to
you I'm just making you suffer oh man
I'm I'm sorry I don't want you to force
yourself like that
oh
but at least this week you don't have to
suffer that much because I'm not
streaming that much thanks for the
memberships Tim thank you
looking for the top dance
[Music]
this is where it happens
yeah I got dumpstered on all stream yes
by the RNG on some of the highest
percentages possible like for real for
real for real and then that happened so
true eaglets not very thank
you and Bob Dylan Duncan you were here
yeah
Max Lola first thank you thank you soon
for the pinky and yeah why did you go to
an idol meeting at the very moment when
a miracle happens you should have
brought your phone at least
or turned up the speakers really really
really really loud
um
[Music]
yeah you still here thank you
no phone working mistake or install a TV
in every room of your home because you
your Oshi is someone who streams all the
time and you don't want to be stuck in
front of your like one TV Source all the
time
so how about you install it everywhere
it doesn't have to be a big TV it can
just be a tiny baby TV
or I guess just bring your phone
the same thing you just watch a new
phone I guess but then that's so small
okay just use your phone whenever you
don't want to be in front of your big TV
there we go
Pink Gold Daisy dungeon science
[Laughter]
I was here from the beginning and now I
have a flat ass like 3D kiwawa
or don't blame me from me for making bad
adulting decisions oh thank you for the
um for the raid
you could just
stand up every once in a while just
because I stream 10 and a half hours
and you decide to not stand up a single
time you're gonna blame it on me you
should like stand up and do some
exercise while you're watching me if
it's 10 and a half hours you gotta do
something
thing
[Music]
raid rate hello rain
I think I've seen this YouTuber before
foreign
[Music]
let me check
yeah yeah yeah you have this funky
tongue
you're the one with the funky tongue
[Music]
isn't that a an interesting way to
describe now you're all curious aren't
you
oh oh what the funky tongue do right no
it's just like funky colored
now that's a selling point
and where was I
[Music]
where was I am
I here soon
I'll be your face with a pinky thank God
for the three percent saved us another
hour good going you had a nice wig from
the game finisher yeah I wasn't even
like 100 aware
when I was doing it that if this
wouldn't work out
which I already thought it wouldn't work
out
um
that it would reactivate
all of the like Shields basically and I
would have to run around
to deactivate all of them again
like I mean I knew it somewhere but I
was just kind of ignoring that in the
back of my head
[Music]
thank God it didn't happen
thank God
it ended so epically yeah we dodged a
big bullets
killing too embarrassed
and where is she where is she
just walk Brooke thanks for the red
super chat congratulations game for the
show of En this finally was hilarious
and honestly I couldn't have asked for a
better way to spend a Sunday
thank you then I'm glad I put it on a
Sunday everybody had lots of time I hope
that helped you guys out was that good
should I should I try to keep my RPG
streams to weekends
would that help you guys I feel like
I already have a lot of viewers who are
like flexible with it
who can watch me during their work as
well
but if it helps you guys
no
yeah slightly harder for me really
only slightly
[Music]
no I wouldn't say it would take much
longer to finish because like normally
for this one
[Music]
we had like maximum two streams per week
and the weekend has two days so
[Music]
um
can't always do it on the weekend
probably when something comes in between
[Music]
for for the new Zelda game tears of the
Kingdom who knows maybe some of my
streams will be on the shorter side than
I can
squeeze them in during the week
in the evening
that sounds
like it could be taken out of context
kylia
just that
[Music]
spicy
but thank you thank you for coming and
thinking of me
cute why do you stream at this time
you're not in Europe are you
are you
from Europe
probably not right
she is
wait she's British oh I must have heard
her before
[Music]
because I think
I I listened to you before like to check
out oh what kind of person what kind of
voice does she have I'm just curious you
know
[Music]
that's why she says love oh you think
that's a British thing is it
oh how are you love oh thank you love is
that a British thing
[Music]
maybe I should say it then
what's love oh
wait now that you say it yeah yeah yeah
yeah I guess I get it
[Music]
cheers love
there's love
thank you
[Music]
thank you thank you thank you
British you say British England
England
[Music]
the classic
it's Tuesday love
all right let's talk in a British accent
shall we uh I haven't I haven't talked
like this in a while so I feel kind of
rusty love
[Music]
but it's a it's a pleasure
uh of course my love of course my love
what are you
[Music]
what's your problem mate
you don't like my English accent my
British accent you don't like it what's
wrong with it
yeah secret break that's me
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
you [\h__\h] walk me
you [\h__\h] what
almost Australians has Aussie really is
it the mates though
the mate
well for me to me I love them both it's
the i i although yeah I think
I can hear a difference yeah
I do notice like recently I've been
listening like hearing more Australian
accents and I feel like I can tell the
difference
yeah
because if thanks to new jeans
nude scenes has Australian member
and
somehow I'm getting deeper and deeper
into the fandom
and watching videos that are not music
videos
no it's not a teaser I have no idea no
Danielle is from Australia I think maybe
another one uh
Danielle definitely is
another one maybe two or like New
Zealand maybe I'm not sure they all have
like funny accents though
yeah yeah yeah
so
um
for me when I try to talk like them
I talk the same way when I try to talk
British as I do I guess when I try to
talk Austin but I don't know because I I
can't replicate the difference I guess
but I I don't hear a difference
mm-hmm so sorry I hope I don't offend
anyone
thank you filigon
me I'm almost Dance movie
[Music]
out to you too
recently it's moving like lets me fall
asleep with my face in her tummy and my
arm around her back can you imagine like
so often we do that so often these days
hard to breathe but like I'm literally
face bombing her tummy
and she doesn't mind and we just fall
asleep like that
it's so Heavenly man it's so good it's
like oh
[Music]
yeah it's heaven
so good
she just accepts it now I can't talk she
accepts it now makes me so happy awkward
sleeping position yeah uh I I barely
never fall asleep with my head on my
pillow eventually I'll wake up because
either cat is gone or I just feel I need
to change my position
and then I go Michael turn around from L
shape back to eye shape you know what I
mean
and then sleep normally more or less
[Music]
Zoo tier needs to update their list tier
list of things info what
I was I was just today I watched a tier
Zoo tier list
uh that he did a couple years ago
apparently of
um not mythical beings but what was it
like you know the uh for example what's
it called chupacabra and and Bigfoot and
uh yeah
cryptidscribed tits Cryptids those yeah
yeah so if he did a video on that then
him saying oh yeah mythical beings
interesting uh isn't really
like so far off a good night
like it's very very possible that he
would do that if he did Cryptids
yeah it's not unrealistic that he would
do a mythical beings uh video so I
didn't know he did that before so but
now I know and now I'm like extra
hopeful
um
[Music]
I'm off man
wait I still don't know I forgot what
thank God I forgot what is the Mothman
hahaha
Cryptid this is a man with moth wings
[Music]
most of his stuff is sponsored now so I
might have to provide more than just an
end like I don't know he will be
sponsored by someone else but he will
use my idea
hopefully
muffin is from Virginia
yes it's just a big moth
did you guys really clear me up about
what that was because I don't remember
is a possible extraterrestrial
from West Virginia what
[Music]
I don't I I didn't know what that was
you didn't really tell me
there's a there's a movie on West
Virginia folklore the Mothman is a
humanoid creature probably seen in the
Point Pleasant area really
did you really see it in 1966 to 1967
several times
the first newspaper report was published
in The Point Pleasant Register wait
[Music]
the national press
the source of the legend is believed to
have originated from sightings of out of
migration sandhill cranes or herons
oh
okay
[Music]
or maybe yeah maybe because I see it in
the Wikipedia
article it's Batman coming up what if it
was just a cosplayer someone in a Batman
costume
people in Cosplay yet back then in 1966
um I mean maybe no I'm sure they also
did like in a different way than just in
Cosplay anime
oh the pictures were funny if you go to
images Google images
there's some funky ones recreations
oh my God
[Music]
and Goofy
yeah Statue there's a statue of the
Mothman
[\h__\h]
okay okay let's finish these super chats
uh
[Music]
these streams have been so much fun as
an EU bro having a stream from when I
get home from work really makes my day
and this Series has really been a lot of
content oh thank you I'm very happy to
have some more EU Bros please make
yourself comfortable
[Music]
unfortunately you know these one these
streams always turn out long and I don't
like to
split them into even shorter portions
that's why I have to start quite a bit
early if I do it during the week
um
[Music]
I've always wondered how the life
sensory works I'm doing it myself
and yeah uh but yeah so I'm sorry for
the European Bros but I mean it's even
worse for the N A Bros I just have to
start a little bit earlier for my
longest dreams because I know they will
be long
and I don't
want like only two hours gameplay one
hour or okay three hours game place one
hour Super Chat reading then done I
don't want that
because
I would barely be able to accomplish
things on the stream and then it would
go on even longer it would drag it out
even longer
I don't think that's too late to go
[Music]
it keeps my sleep sleep schedule honest
not really
[Music]
I just continue doing it this way but
I'll try to keep it on the weekends if I
can
more often I'll do it like that thank
you krantek magnet thank you soon
thank you for the support action human
extension spice chicken
the Devin bear Duncan Glenn Duncan Rick
Raptor Duncan there's a bell thank you
for the pinky congratulations on
completing another game never
underestimate the Ian gamer I was mostly
both vodkaing throughout this whole
series and can't believe I was able to
catch up to see this moment live oh
that's nice
looking forward to the next one that's
great thank you for catching up to see
the last moment's life that is very good
worth it thank you so much desire hope
you enjoyed it even though it was a long
series
I think for VOD Watchers this is really
difficult when there's so many votes to
watch and then so many long ones too
now
good job on keeping up with me
thank you so much
Unity chat thanks for the pinkies
staying awake until 2AM before a work
day but it's worth it every time because
finishing a game Journey with Vala will
always be special true true
that crit was another legendary moment
that was so hyped
yo it was absolutely incredible
it was so insane
oh so hype so rewarding thank you Unity
chat I'm glad you were here too sorry
for keeping you up awake so long
yeah thank you so much
okay I feel uh tightness in my chest so
I'm probably gonna end it here because I
also need to cook and tomorrow we're
getting up a relatively early hopefully
to eat breakfast and then
play as a Minecraft game
um
but I finished this these big ones the
big super chats yeah
thank you thank you Martin
I don't think I will really do that
though
[Music]
what will you eat I don't know I need to
check in my hello box
check what I ordered for myself this
time
remind me what time for MC
um should be 1pm my time
GMT plus two 1pm
but if I can't sleep
early enough if I don't feel so loud
then maybe you
Plus
one hour
I'll try though it should be okay might
be a little bit tired but you know
because just because I just woke up or
so
[Music]
um
4 Am PMC
um there's a vlog you guys don't have to
be there
[Music]
ow ow my lips
[\h__\h] I need to stop ripping it off
[Music]
well my lips are like
it feels like they might as well be
bleeding at this point
[Music]
huh
oh it hurts you know when when somebody
has an algae somewhere you'll give in a
kiss right to make it feel better oh it
just to happen to the ouch is on my lips
okay I'll see myself out now
and in Germany
[Music]
now I got embarrassed