e e
n
[Music]
a
oh
[Music]
n
n a
[Music]
a
k
k hello oh my God I'm so nervous Hello
Kiki ah sorry uh I don't know what to
say um today is very special stream and
it's a collaboration between me and a
cute cute cute cute cute girl from Korea
her name is go you saw her on the
thumbnail probably and I'm really
stressed out I slept like four
hours um but yeah we're doing a pretty
collab and uh she's she's a really funny
cute girl I think you will like her I
like her very much we know each other
for like one year now and you will
probably find out more about that story
anyway uh in this stream but
yeah k
k yeah we'll do some stuff in 3D we'll
introduce ourselves and we'll try to
communicate in both languages and so
English and Korean I'll try my best but
I'm so
bad uh yeah feel free to like write me
words but we have staff helping us
changing the cameras and everything yay
and they they they can write like little
hints at the bottom and then later we'll
also play a game uh you'll see you'll
see but yeah it's a mix of
everything wait let me readjust my strap
cuz it's already I feel like wish you I
got a new microphone does it do you hear
me well
guys do you hear me well I didn't really
do an audio check with goig so we'll
have to see uh yeah
oh okay sounds good sound great I don't
know how it's going to sound when I
dance how's that sound do you hear my
arm
movement is it okay volume is fantastic
wonderful
yay okay my
heart is I think how I say doy doie I am
nervous so I'm going to meet go over
there I I think I'm I'm not mentally
ready but the time has come I heard
she's like dancing right now she's
streaming by the way on a site called
soap s o o p um that's like their main
site now but she also has a YouTube
channel which I Linked In My description
okay check it out check out yeah what's
so it's like the new name for this uh
stream website that was called frea TV a
f r e e c or k a TV yeah yeah yeah but
they changed the name so yeah
anyway my cat Chunky wony was like the
whole time oh my face shaking chunky won
was like running around here this whole
time kangi kangi is cat ah I I speedrun
dualingo last
night but okay I have so Notes too why
are you back chunky wony go away dony
wony no stay away I'm talking don't
don't don't you dare run over to no no
no no no no no no no and and and she's
so
excited did you hear
that I'm sorry no you're going to like
Press buttons on my keyboard no
no I'm battling my cat okay she's really
excited but
okay okay she's she's just going to be
there now I guess I'm uh I'm ready I'm
ready okay okay I'm ready to move
let's let's move okay I'm
walking I don't know what the song is
I'm moving I'm
moving or am I maybe not yet
waiting for go to be ready okay okay
okay ah ah Chad are you nervous does my
nervosity go over to you I'm sorry if it
does not nervous look at my Frey is this
with fixed butt what do you
think this my my new butt my new old
butt butt check not sure what are you
doing
we're vibing you're vibing good for
you I'm jealous you know when I'm so
nervous and before stream I always feel
like I really need to go to an idle
meeting but I already went so I I hope
I'm going to be okay also I have a Red
Bull but I this like uh current me is
really just because I'm nervous but here
let me drink a little bit more I'm
drinking the pink
one
uh Forest Berry I guess do you guys have
the pink one in your
country heavy breathing because
nervous at least I think she speaks
really good English I don't think we
ever really talked
directly
yumy yeah I'm caffeinated
[Laughter]
you got this thank you I don't know why
I'm so nervous I I I I think it's
because like um like there's like like
an an unusual audience
watching I need to make a good
impression okay let's make a confident
impression um
s oh oh yeah you go girl hell yeah oh if
I go too far my face tracking won't work
let me move this a little
bit okay I'm so confident have
confidence
oopsie have confidence I am
confident confidence is me wasn't there
a Sound of Music song like
that is me something like
that you can do it yes yes my arms are
still like super weak like my the whole
arm length when I try to like grab like
put some pressure in I feel
nothing that I do feel like strain it's
really
bad I hope I will be fine throughout the
stream it's really I was carrying like I
don't know like 30 30 plates or so from
the post office
like it was so heavy really so
bad yeah the I've I've ordered a lot of
things from Amazon recently and of
course the heaviest thing is the one
thing that like I missed and had to pick
up
myself yeah yeah very
heavy new
plates okay
the reason why we're doing this like
oneon-one by the way first is because I
think that's what G usually does like
she starts her stream like one hour
early and then there's one hour loading
screen and then there's like like
oneon-one time with her and her viewers
and then they merge you ready okay okay
we're ready let's go woohoo oh God I'm
I'm GNA cry no I'm so
[Music]
scared I'm
coming hi
he come on there I'm coming I'm coming
I'm coming ooh ooh ooh oh oh here I am
can you see me can you singing oh no
it's my MC bik no no no can you see me
oh I can see you no you have a
microphone yeah it's my
microphone you can smell this
uh M very very good very good smell yes
nice to meet
you is
fry
yay
go oh small baby small no small please
to no this is not uh 300
meter 300 M an not 300 M
yeah it's a mini version yeah mini
version no no always always small always
no I T
[Music]
you me too oh okay then please introduce
yourself Korean fans Oh you mean with
the
presentation no um
oh okay okay can yes simple
okay I
[Music]
am
yes no
no English perfect better than M my
Korean here go English here no you're
Korean here why English here oh oh no no
no we will see today today we will see
okay test our uh communication
skill oh good good oh you can speak
Japanese hi
Japanese and English which one better uh
maybe bu Japanese here mhm by English
here oh my Korean
here I know oh
[Laughter]
thank you thank you look look did you
see what what the Little
mascot mascot m chicken oh
chicken and here too here too us so cute
cute small small
like kid like kid no kiding is tall
right k k King K King King
giraffe no no no King giraffe
no
oh K Kitt like like this um kidding
sorry
sorry my
skirt yeah sorry
oh okay small introduction please in
English to my
viewers hello
everyone nice oh nice my name is
go I'm from
Korea but group is
ID I love you
oh now what time is in your
11 uh 21 a.m. oh
a.m. morning morning oh my god wow thank
you sorry it's
okay H in Korea
now um seven oh yes PM yes good
evening yeah best good streaming time
yeah good streaming time now now now now
ah oh
hug H oh my
[Laughter]
God oh my slow slow oh
[Music]
so
cute nous
nervous you too yeah me too
why um because you are so star you are
big St you too you too I watched h on
YouTube I watched is Idol
Festival oh yeah oh really it's so so so
amazing I like almost
cried why why why I don't know very uh
[Music]
emotional
oh Festival
yeah worldwide concert worldwide con
world world
[Music]
T when when when did you
go I can't
[Music]
go thank
you oh 3D camera is so cute oh no no no
not not cute wait let me fix my screen
okay Frey cute you have so many outfits
I'm
jealous oh oh or Co outfit uh this is
yeah first outfit default default Lally
sexy is it okay to show so shirt skirt m
m oh my God oh my
God oh my
God your hip move is so sexy dangerous
twerk do you know twerk go oh twerk you
could that twerk twerk twerk
twerk but you have more physics in your
skirt it's it moves it moves more oh oh
oh oh okay my my my my fan will be
like no
more about I like sexy oh yeah because
I'm sexy
too
okay
ah what i f why preing with
K what what I while preing is that she's
passate and shiny person Shin thank you
you're so nice I love you you're so cute
you're so nice to me I'm sexy no no yeah
yeah yeah yeah small small sexy oh it's
already been a year since we first got
to know each other yeah one year yeah
why it took so much
time but but I happy because we
met
hamb
hamb oh yes I say correctly
H oppa oh OPP
oppa where where where is oppa
oh oh my God
no SP so cute so we prepared a video of
our
narratives let's watch it together let
watch oh
oh where where where
movie prepare
movie now movie St y oh wait a minute
oh it's
coming a clip of our
adventures I just you know if they're
live now I might as well react to it do
they hear us there was a
Korean that I didn't hear of before so I
checked it out and she was so cute oh so
cute it's me Su one of the nominations
was a Korean twitch YouTuber that only
streams in Korean but and also only in
3D it seems like it she's so cute though
[Music]
cute oh I guess
like
[Applause]
it's
okay
[Music]
come so C
are you
okay because she's been reacting to my
music videos and stuff is she watching
me now
[Music]
cation soon
okay
[Laughter]
yes don't
cry okay let me give you a update so me
and go have been discussing collab ideas
and I told her though that I can only do
it after
my we can take our time a long time
[Music]
ago
exited I like four different collab
ideas at her we'll see what sticks or
we'll combine them all she's so sweet
she's so
freaking you love
[Music]
me you have to wait CU it will take a
little while okay give us some
[Music]
time I'm watching you every
day collection
oh also I think was a little bit worried
that when she saw in the Korean Wiki
that I'm apparently a wife collector
wife wife
collector oh but now I am a child
collector a receiver tried collector I'm
charx she was surprised she was like
like I I am wife something like that no
no no go you are child my new child
yes I'm
wife you want to be my
wife no
[Laughter]
I like blue
Ki yes
I'm yeah
yes stop asking about the
go time everybody ask or two people keep
patience I want it to happen she wants
it to happen but I got to set up some
things and there's got to be some
technical troubleshooting and all that
[Music]
tech oh yes it happened when it seemed
forgotten oh you watch
oh
[Music]
yay oh wait I have something to say next
week's special
collaboration is
finally
with from Idol it's been a long time
coming I've been busy I've been
traveling but it's finally going to
happen
next week in 3D I need to like urgently
brush up my Korean skills
ah I'm nervous it's been such a long
time since we first interacted so it's
pretty much a year since we started
interacting timing huh we can celebrate
our anniversary go k anniversary a year
in the making yeah this collab will be a
year in the making how does it take so
long don't know I'm sorry my knees hurt
cuz you're so
small
[Music]
no we met we
met oh punch my boots oh oh my God can I
touch this no my hand oh okay okay can I
touch your hand yes oh soft oh very very
soft very
hot first time uh I say the secret but
later you say the secret
oh please
please it's okay
mean sorry it's it's okay I was excited
too yes yes so
excito ah I was so happy at the time
really me too me too thank you for
always watching I learn it in my diary
you you have a diary yeah what did you
write about
me you are so
passionate and shiny person
stop you're so
nice oh H why did you think I was cute H
because you're you're funny and small
and no and your
face go
go you
can more more bigger no
no it's
maximum so cute I learned from you
excited your facial motion more excited
ah ah yes better better than before I
learned from you I do
research how to make face nicer and I
find out blend
shapes
wink yes oh very you
too can I I can't win you're so bad at
it no yeah here I I hold your
eye
open open I but can this
emotion this is
go okay uh how do you feel about meeting
after all
year m I also uh honestly a little bit I
also thought oh it's not going to happen
anymore so much time passed it's not
going to happen but
suddenly it was like okay uh by the way
let's let's do it so I'm really happy
but I'm nervous but I think one year ago
compared to now now I'm more ready
because I got more used to 3D stuff at
home so now I am I have more
confidence yes confidence yes wait let
me also do
something uh
okay okay how do you
feel now
yes um
take w
for glorious
glorious I honor
honor
you now I'm very honor me too me
too I love is your
idol oh my God I like a
[Music]
superhero
superer this yes like that
super oh very very sexy M oh I know
I oh my God very nice W maybe today we
practice dance together okay oh okay
okay then now since our
languages are
different let's introduce ourselves to
our fans okay no
problem I study I speak English and car
will speak Korea yes I try I'd
appreciate it if you think it's
cute okay yes please be
nice they introduce K first me first
okay okay yeah fighting fighting
fighting okay where is my oh
there uh I go here maybe okay who is
Kiana oh thank you thank
you self introduction introduce
myself okay
next next L okay yes okay
I am from H life English group group is
H life English myth is first
generation oh yes first generation first
generation yes myth My Generation oh Kim
yes yes okay and my debut was four years
ago isim and
yes okay
okay
long I am boss of and Phoenix P not
chicken not P okay chicken yeah okay so
cute okay understand go
no
chicken no okay next
is
okay okay
understand understand yeah really
oh okay okay okay so my fans are work
for me but we also sell chicken
chicken
mysterious where do they go the chickens
and ah yes
[Music]
a yeah yeah yeah I am
Austrian okay go
next next oh nice right go next in my
cheat cheat cheat
okay
languages
wow I practice Korean
sometimes wow okay understand yeah
you're so genius no go is more genius
than me I think cuz you're thank you
you're you're Japanese and English also
very good passion English passion
English and Me Passion
Korean
fighting it's good thing good thing
passion oh okay okay okay not fashion
passion
passion P ah yes P passion and my
platform YouTube
streaming I stream on YouTube yes now
now live on YouTube and then my artist
who drew
me
artist yes H Papa hook Papa he make
Stein gate and Black Rock Shooter you
know
oh oh I know yeah he draw my my papa oh
it looks very different but hook Papa
draw
me similar yeah really oh and you know
Stein skate yeah Stein skate also hook
Papa oh
so cool
[Music]
right next oh is there more was there
more ah yeah
okay uh more last slide chimy Hobbies
me is a Yoli Yoli cooking cooking
cooking H dance dance dance dance and
maybe RPG RPG
game you
know in H
how to
say I
see fun
facts
J fun fact I don't know how to say in
Korean
oh oh okay I love my cat
[Music]
cat and orange is
chunkers and this one is
Smoothie oh very cute very very cute
cute and I love making K-pop Style music
so maybe you heard
you know Kim I know yeah and Mirage
maybe one one or two months ago I
released
Mirage please
[Music]
listen yeah Korean style I love Korean
Style
music gaypop
yeah like
twice
[Music]
oh
what no no
no what okay go your
turn okay change with me
so cute oh cute I go here anywhere oh
why am I small now
am St St make me small I'm
taller okay I
grow
okay okay let me introduce myself
okay next
page
cute I'm a spe I 100% sexy and 100% cute
bber oh oh oh okay okay so call me
sex
orus
sucubus yeah I'm
sucubus I think uh other member in is
Idol yeah maybe more more
sexy no who
everybody no but but go number one cute
number one top oh really sexy
move I have really sexy motion oh okay
yeah sexy ni nice dance
yeah and next page okay
K name yeah K my name
is ah go means cat save the word in
Korean
oh I you like cats yes I love cat cats
do save the world it's true it's a fact
oh yeah smoothie c ah tuners smoothie
and tunkers ters tunkers smoth chunkers
yeah me too I like cat oh you have do
you have cat kangi h no why so sad why
my parents do like cat oh hey why
they're so cute you need cat or how
about how is that pickup line again
uh I have cat at home
okay please
continue ah I'm 17 years
old plus 10 no maybe I'm
17 17
plus yeah maybe at least the voice is
aha yes I agree okay 27 M good age it's
in demand you are in in
demand
yeah okay yes and I belong to a group
called is Idol a virtual Idol in
Korea very cute very cute very cute love
love King well thank you is ID is a six
woman group
with
Z Li
hereu pink pink
girl and
here and
here cute cute they have really really
good singing voice oh thank you and good
dancing very good dancing
oh and there are so many good songs that
lank high on Korean music
sites oh like kiding kiding
k
k I don't know the dance please teach me
okay
K
and next my nickname is
goose why because sound like go but you
don't make goose
sound how oh um maybe I because I guess
forign fence sounded similar to to Goose
ah but it's perfect like Synergy because
goose and Goose chck chck a chicken no
Phoenix uh you are chicken oh oh but
chicken and Goose yeah good nice join
H chicken oh very sounds
good
Korean Korean Kaki Kaki in Korean is
there a word
[Music]
like like this okay pass
P it's okay we can just say Kaki
everybody understands yeah
next page next page
down a
language um the language that I can
speak is
Korean and anime Japanese
oh a little bit of English oh money
money n n big
English um it's
oh thank you fashion
[Laughter]
English okay
sorry oh good thank
you and the Korea
translator Papo is helping me with my
English SK now oh I love Papa go I also
use
Papa
yeah and I am put casting on a platform
called soup
soup yeah now
soup
oh oh in Korea soups mean is um forest
forest
oh so go is hiding in the forest okay
okay I see
yeah um many Korean broadcasters are
broadcasting here so many pre
Tu I see do you like legal of
Legend I never played before but I watch
do you know
Arcane oh okay on Netflix I watch Arcane
but League of Legends I never played
before Oh you you play League of Legends
yeah I I like here really really really
really I like I like oh I think you can
make friends with my
colleague colleague yeah my colleague
she
play uh my my kohai my new colle she
play League of Legends oh oh wait my my
my doorbell ring one
moment
okay foree
[Music]
oh what
happened
yeah ah ch slowly
slowly
so okay okay I can
wait oh one second
please e
[Music]
now stand still to apply and finalize
the calibration the calibration process
is now complete you can move freely now
not good not good slowly slowly one more
time one more time bad calibration go to
a starting position you can safely
perform the
calibration oh
stand look straight ahead for 3 seconds
H good very
good now move around to move and rotate
all the sensors avoid rapid movements oh
please wait oh
no processing please
wait take your
time now stand still to apply and
finalize the calibration the calibration
process is now complet
good okay okay I was running around take
your no it's
okay I'm back I'm back I'm back I'm back
are you
back my hands work again yay y sorry
sorry I'm sorry no no where were we oh
we were
here please you want
what oh something cute if you are sorry
uh uh okay closeup please
close um
um I am sorry
oh okay so cute so cute
cat yes take me home take me home
okay no you take me oh I take you okay
okay okay okay
next next next
myself yeah
oh oh oh oh my God
okay and and I like sexy
Dan
and oh yeah do you know
this oh old
K-pop oh my God I also love sexy dance
we will dance sexy dance oh okay okay
yeah
okay and lastly my personality is like a
cat
oh okay I don't like the
obvious and I like the funny ones M
funny cat yeah oh I love cats so I love
go easy oh thank
you thanks for listening oh and if you
have any questions please ask oh
oh there is I think secret version of
this presentation that I
made uhhuh is does it exist did ston
prepare
it I I accidentally made a go
presentation because I Mis understand
please please hear Translate please
what I'm broken I'm broken I can't
please watch
[Music]
me uh maybe question to
sta it's okay probably it's gone oh ah
it's like a
sec yeah I made PowerPoint presentation
oh okay I'll show you another
time time I'll show you next time
okay
oh I think it didn't say in the slides
how long are you a
vtuber how
long um three ears oh so you are my Kai
I am Senpai Senpai
yes
Senpai and why why why do you start
[Music]
webing please please please I had a
feeling that I would do good
oh same same I me too good oh you too
yeah yeah yeah
oh but you know four years ago when I
debut there were not so many English
YouTubers oh and in h life we were first
so I was generation yeah I was like ah
how is it going to be will people like
us I thought people will hate
us oh no we're very very nervous and no
confidence but now I have confidence a
little bit
oh yes
you are
so shiny
person thank you V in Korea
[Music]
oh there were not so many right like
three years ago yes I think I only know
is
Idol I don't really know
oh thank you yeah yeah you're so very
good
Korean in Korea vber usually in
3D oh yeah
usually usually many
3D oh in in English speaking world is
more 2D 2D oh oh live 2D mhm mhm yes
I like T oh because
I'm but fry go cute because she can move
and dance oh okay then next
activity oh oh oh oh
yeah since we are here in 3d motion
let's use our
bodies bodies yes
yes why don't we warm up with a
challenge that's trending oh
oh yes okay okay what challenge do you
have what challenge what challenge is it
okay okay is it
the challenge yeah okay
okay you know ah I I watch I watch I
watch Go version and Jing Burger version
Oh sing was
[Music]
you
know yes I know but normally on YouTube
I cannot do this kind of
stuff today I do it today I don't
care
yeah we do what we want to
[Music]
do I love
oh
oh should I watch
Discord yeah oh I
watch yes
oh okay because sound
ah you oh I hope my internet is going to
be okay if I watch
say okay okay I I'm
watching I'm
watching listen to the song ah
[Music]
okay oh we're already doing it or is
test test test
okay okay where is so fast it's so fast
it's so fast
it's okay oh what one more practice
practice practice oh okay practice let's
go
[Music]
oh okay okay okay but I can't do
Angry
Angry good good good yeah I I see very
good okay I
try okay
it's okay okay home let's go
[Music]
special I can't do it so
well
you
shy well maybe a little little bit
little Kashi
[Music]
yeahi y we challenge go also do
challenge now you want it yes
please
[Music]
okay she's a pro
nice thank
you nice challenge complete challenge
complete complete complete yeah I think
it would be nice to teach each other how
to dance yes finally
finally dance dance
teaches you first okay I teach Mirage
recently I released my new song Mirage
maybe go also saw go you know
Mirage no I know I know okay I watch it
your shorts oh YouTube shorts yeah yeah
with Marine Senpai okay I teach you
today the
dance H can step maybe play the song
once and I I try to see what part they
cut oh I want to kak in check what part
can you play music one
time one time pleas and
please oh yeah and I I Chang outfit
right I
Chang wow oh nice nice technique
oh change out change outfit yeah
I don't understand but I
agree yes I agree
yeah what's
happening we're
we're now we
are changing
life yeah
Changing Life on stream getting
naked I know I know I
understand what what is your new outfit
uh uh the Idol
outfit yeah Idol outfit yeah oh
oh oh please me too please change yeah
yeah go a good Idol outfit why why you
just normal you didn't
prepare spider spider oh oh yes oh oh so
cute oh oh me too
oh my God but you can't change in front
of people don't look don't look don't
look oh my God
yeah very cute now we're both really
cool ready for
dancing
dark
Okay no Okay I come back oh you come
back you can
stay yeah now please teach me okay can
they play the music one time
please music music
please oh oh oh oh okay
[Music]
S A at
me
okay very
difficult are you okay but I was
thinking just this part maybe is easier
for you
me me me the second half me me only
maybe
maybe only second half okay because I
started like but I teach you from here
okay okay uh you know the part that
starts me me me me me
me okay so we start with like peace
signs on the side yeah peace and and
then you
go when
oh and then me and then up
here yeah and then you
curl yeah so
and and then you like do like
a and then here secret secret you bring
it
down and then wait
me me me me me Mir you ah and then this
hand also curl yeah and then back up to
change yeah and me me me me me you
[Music]
spinning when I try to remember I forget
okay but I think that was kind of
it okay
okay ah and then when you change you
go and then like this yes yes yes yes
and then
and like this and like
this yeah yeah yeah yeah and then shake
shake shake shake shake shake shake oh
my God and the hands also shake shake
shake shake
shake yeah yeah yeah and then we
turn and when on shake shake shake shake
shake shake shake shake shake shake
shake shake shake
shake and then you just turn again
and okay that's we don't du wa du up
down
up it's uh maybe easy because you are
genius yeah thank you oh okay we try
from
beginning
oh yeah
de de W yeah me me me me
[Music]
Mir this and on and on this me ah I
forgot this part this me cross me CR so
this me R I'm
lost don't when choke cross cross out
again and then like yeah and then shake
shake shake shake shake shake shake
shake shake shake shake yeah okay one
time with music maybe after you do shake
shake shake with uh turn and more shake
shake shake shake shake shake shake
shake shake shake shake and
then we J and J up down up
easy you can do it fighting fighting
figh let's go really ret try are you
practice yes okay of course we practice
oh she's so how does she learn it so
fast okay we
try you are so genius teacher no no no
no maybe you secretly practice
already no thank you oh my god oh you
say
something here
okay okay it's already gone and and
music for practice oh okay wait this is
first part okay and I no please you can
play but the first part is uh we don't
dance the first part go go go okay okay
let's go let's
go
[Music]
freestyle
W okay ready okay
[Music]
okay shake shake shake shake shake shake
shake shake shake shake shake shake
shake
down sorry it's so fast sorry so so so F
I can yeah y go go go go go go go go go
go
go I can't more better dance I Believe I
Can okay one more
time okay okay okay I follow you okay
okay please follow me one more time
go
[Music]
go I don't even know what to do with
this good play
a okay here we
[Music]
go
yeah ni
[Laughter]
but so dance no uh you can do
it no one more time or
finish one more time near
finally
only Mir challenge
yay
yes okay perfect perfect nice okay okay
starting good now
[Music]
you don't even know what do
[Applause]
oh nice
[Music]
Yay good job good
job wow wow wow fast
Le
no I no no no no no no no that's not
true because I teach uh better maybe
when I'm less nervous now I'm really
nervous no
not your dance is so very good like Kpop
now I want to see
dance but probably we need more time
more time
yeah please teach me do you know Kitt
yeah I think like something like this oh
already no only this part I only know
like this pie
piece okay let's go please once
example kiding hey please kiding kiding
sounds music cute
[Music]
it's yeah let me try the can I uh cheat
a little bit I uh I
[Music]
miror it's currently sorry just for
practice I
mirror okay one more time please with
music one more time yeah with music with
music it's okay okay let's go
[Music]
oh sorry I look wrong screen okay here
yeah okay why sorry why sorry it's okay
okay teach slowly
first
uhuh
King King King
King King Kitt
King
then
yeah like throw it back gety gety yes
yes oh oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah
one time one time okay oh yeah two time
oh yeah oh okay two time yeah mhm
and next oh no kitty oh one more kitty
yeah kitty kitty oh oh ah from from us
to them a first time to us and then next
time next time outside okay oh
oh oh yeah Kitt K Kitt
[Music]
Kitt one more
time aha I
see
then oh nice
nice oh oh uh
[Music]
don't
yeah yeah oh
difficult
[Music]
sorry oh oh one more time okay mhm uh
okay okay Daddy G
daddy Anna
Anna okay
hi
so get oh get get
k
no okay then um cute cute
POS okay okay yeah yeah oh my
god do you know do you know uh one this
step one turn this yeah one
turn oh I don't something like
that she's so cute she's so cute oh
swing yeah okay okay back to kiding
kiding back to kiding oh one more slowly
yeah okay okay
then hey hey you gotta be
kiding K
King
oh sorry sorry yeah kitty kitty
kitty yeah yeah oh yeah kitty
[Music]
kitty
okay oh yeah oh yeah oh
good and then and outside
[Music]
kitty
no don't
look and
then oh yes cute
POS okay yeah yeah
oh one more time kiding
kidding
[Music]
no okay I try
yeah it's so
hard tired but fighting let's do it but
but but happy I'm so happy because I
like dance
[Laughter]
please te
English
English a cute phrase in English that
makes everybody is ah
ah what's the Pok champ phrase yeah
aren't you my little PK champ or
something like that should we teach her
that what are you
doing okay okay uh uh
yeah close Zoom close Zoom mhm Zoom yeah
zoom zoom zoom and repeat after me yeah
fine I guess you are my little POG
champ fine uh leer F yeah fine I guess
you are I guess you are my little Pok
champ my lead Pok champ yes fine I guess
you are my little POG champ
oh fine I guess you're my little POG
champ Yeah Yeah Yeah Yeah
Yeah by I guess you're my little po
CH
good oh yeah very nice I I feel me I
feel excited when I hear you say that it
means it's it's English I
oh English oh stuff no no translate no
translate please
translate no no watch me hey hey watch
me I don't think translation po CH hey
hey hey please please engl please do it
do it translate love message love
message love
message that's what it
means oh so cute
oh I can't believe
you're
okay no I forgot everything
go because we talk about little Pok
champ can oh nice okay and let's dance
okay one more s yes one
more Kitty Kitt Kitty
kitty kitty kitty kitty
no
[Music]
uhuh
head
[Music]
okay mm you got to be kitty kitty kittyy
oh no
no okay
cute yeah okay okay let's try with music
oh okay let's go
oh fighting
[Music]
yeah
yeah very good one more time one more
time one more time yes okay then sorry
sorry wait a minute please okay I
also we are so
tired it's hard work but it's honest
work
yeah but I'm happy very hot because
dancing with you
yes one day dance together in IRL in
real life together in Korea together I
go to Korea oh and we dance together in
Korea oh oh really yeah yeah I won I I
wanton yeah please please L okay I go
maybe in
spring April or March okay
yeah yeah I go I go we dance and then I
take go home with me I I take I
take no no no I'll take you
oh o o the
r repeat after me one more thing
one more thing yes uh repeat okay yeah
close
zoom
zoom oh the
rary oh
the you know it you know it
oh everybody wants to be my
SK is it si
wait all the
rery everybody wants to be
my everybody want scity scity yeah yeah
scity okay I already forgot the second
half so I already forgot but this
perfect good
job thank
you okay every that's skid skid skid you
know skid
toilet no let see I'm trying to be cool
bringing out my my memes that I know I
don't know many memes
but English English
meme ski what's mean
uh good question sexy word uh
SK ah I know I know I know oh really to
it oh my God uh step please trans late
I'm trying to impress my
child are you cocky you are no no no you
are
Ki Oh okay then last last finally last
three last two last dance Kitty okay
okay kiding kiding okay can I unload
this uh collaboration dance on my short
yes what
oh maybe I record uh afterwards one more
time properly and I send to you if you
want and go Mirage challenge also okay
on my channel W
woohoo
[Music]
okay oh
yeah K King k
[Music]
K
KY a cute BS cute very cute cute oh you
good
answer then R to music C okay here we go
oh my God my my finger oh my God broken
broken sorry oh no oh
fix fix fix it fix it Rock oh no does it
hurt I can't about I can oh oh oh oh
nice nice peace okay let's go
[Music]
oh I make mistake I make
mistake one more time one more time one
more time one more time yeah yeah yeah
yeah I I M take the two oh really
oh I always forget the same part one
more one more one more please
[Music]
best take best take nice take
oh do you have sexy boys sexy
boys like this can I say a sexy Korean
phrase you teach
me now you can prank me okay okay I'll
teach you
oh oh
something about
cat yeah oh no oh no okay one more
another sentence yes yes what about the
L ra pickup pH oh oh you know
oh my
God why why you
that these are my Korean best
phrases oh yeah it's so hot hot sentence
yes I practice really hard oh I know I
honey hungry no I know H me a horny
horny horny oh what mean oh no hi honey
or I'm horny because uh marai say I'm
horny I'm
horny what's
[Laughter]
mean say uh I'm horny because she say oh
oh not not uh maybe not good
to hi honey is better hi honey okay
watch me
please right youri is marai
right uh JP
but if youri is man Senpai then maybe
you already
know no I don't
know what what you mean I'm fny
translator also write dot dot dot
[Music]
uh uh how to say I'm horny in Korean
uh I can I can ask
Pap I Pap
Pap because maybe St is is too scared
it's a funny
uh okay okay I
am
horny
horny no more like I'm h
okay I satisfied oh really
okay thank you
forever okay oh
then okay then then next finish finish
dance finish dance dance time finish it
dance time
good job good job good job I am
sweaty sweaty yeah me too then next
let's go play a game of dis manting bomb
yes we're going to play the bomb
diffusal game oh
oh Elite yeah do you play this
before no no first time yeah oh okay
okay it's it's uh easy easy easy easy
game really easy very easy no no
not uh we'll do our best okay uh game is
keep talking and nobody explodes we will
change location change screen okay yeah
okay and sit down maybe sit down sit
down oh so
swe so
hot yay change please keep want to wait
the the instruction oh instruction um
maybe go go start okay uh let me start
game are you excited we play game
together yeah really I am so honored
today maybe I take off my hand
gloves because I need to use the
keyboard keyboard
here
okay okay
okay oh oh my God
by oh my God
I love
K oh my God where where my oh my God
game very loud maybe I make more quiet
this is a variety stream guys we do all
kinds of things together
yeah
okay
oh game here we
go
okay
go you're going to show on your stream
the
manual
bom
manual let's go let's go um manual man
manual yeah wait I also prepare manual I
find manure oh nice nice yeah I think
maybe no no Korean
version PE
print PDF
oh
uh
[Music]
okay we're sitting together yay sitting
together slowly
take okay there we go I have manual
also
oh yeah worst case maybe staff help us
but but actually it's better if they
don't help so that we just explode and
oh
uh I find Korean B oh really
yeah
[Music]
uh sexy egg you one more please oh okay
okay no
problem yes here we go okay
then play game oh yeah okay
okay it will be
difficult nice nice oh bye-bye go
bye-bye oh my God
no no I don't have to do anything
they're big good service okay good
service I I I start game I do free play
I do uh H 5
minutes okay uh 5 minutes free modes
maybe that's easy okay restart easy easy
easy mode
oh no no no no
no no we start with easy mode easy
mode oh okay start manual okay okay okay
okay I don't look at menu and go is my
eyes
okay what are you doing I start Okay I
uh how to start okay it's been a while
uh uh uh top left so uh I have four
signs four signs uh yeah
uh how we going to do this uh I have
four
signs they look like m m m and maybe o
with
one one sign one one stroke downwards
and a e but other
direction yeah and question
mark oh you talking about KET yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I find oh it's
like uh
art art um um like
egyp okay okay let's go let's go okay
okay four I have four four yeah oh oh oh
I find okay uh what do you see
uh ah okay I have I have a question mark
upside down yeah upside down Quest oh oh
I I find I find okay and e but wrong
side wrong side wrong side wrong side e
with two
dots oh oh oh oh oh yeah I find and O
big O O
with one one little yeah and M like an M
but fancy
pretty no no
no I I I okay okay piss piss press yeah
yeah yeah which
one oh
then a big a big a no
a oh oh
[Music]
no
M oh sorry sorry please please oh oh oh
maybe
maybe okay let's go what can I do oh
uh
uh okay star star no star no star no
star oh my
God maybe maybe M could also look like
an h h h h oh then oh
first l e two dot oh okay okay okay and
Q oh Q okay okay okay okay okay okay and
like M okay okay okay okay okay and
question mark okay okay okay oh oh yeah
yeah yeah okay okay what do I oh we are
genius
s we
already
yeah what happen what does this mean
oh how's this
work
name
bom how does this work no turn the bump
around ah how wait how do you turn this
around uh ah okay
oh okay pe oh
okay okay
I I have one more one more it's uh it
says q v v n
g q m g but I can change the letters uh
five letters five letters five letters
yeah but I don't know I have a b c d e f
d h k l m n o which which
letters we have 1
minute 1 minute s okay okay let's go
what what what what first what what uh
uh no you you tell
me um five I I can I can change letters
up down and I go
IC seconds
H oh
no should I not have changed them maybe
oh no I die ah I find I find really yeah
yeah five yeah
yeah okay oh oh no oh no oh oh H maybe
it says NSA on the side of the it's over
it's so over
i di I
di see and you say hard mode is okay no
no no hard mode
piss then more it's okay or change yeah
yeah we change we change
okay then okay I take a look at the
[Music]
menu let's see if we can do better with
switch switch switch switch oh K is very
genius Korean genius so I will win this
game but I look at English menu
okay maybe I ask papao for help oh papao
oh you genius is is it okay with P just
a little bit a little
bit okay I played this
game let's go 5
minutes oh okay okay oh God it's been a
long time maybe it would be nice if she
has like
wires keep talking and nobody is
CL let's go
okay then when you start tell me tell me
what do you see
okay
okay fighting okay
[Applause]
fighting fighting fighting oh what
this you begin you start start
already start
uh a PDF main ah sorry I look
[Music]
okay
ah okay ah you are the tuto ah tutorial
tutorial fighting
fighting
okay you can do it
tutorial oh she's just skipping skipping
skipping I hear
it okay
okay good okay
this was what I was doing oh yeah it's
was supposed to be a word
the okay but how would I have known
which one it would have been or how
she only one combination of the will
match was it not was it not the full ABC
maybe no started
okay okay okay what do you see
Mo what's this what can oh oh okay um oh
oh oh oh
we big big H H Big E to dot ah it's same
like keypad okay uh yeah keypad big big
H yeah uh and two do e alab e uhhuh
uh-huh MH and Omega
Omega which one was
Omega maybe this side could also be
maybe she means this H it's like om
om oh okay and fourth one H uh uh
nine
ner oh
huh it's like it's like six but M mod
ah it's like six but M
mod so just six like six okay six and
like six
but okay try try uh six
six and E with DOT e and H and Omega
maybe
oh yeah first very fast nice nice nice
very fast
oh next next uh you you know you can you
can turn with right click you can turn
the the Box okay and look around um oh
oh so many blue and red and black white
lines oh wire Wire yeah wire o nice nice
wire black and how many how many wire
how
many um seven seven two height
seven one
blue two red one black wait seven ah
sorry sorry six six okay okay okay one
more one more one more one more time two
white two white one blue one blue two
red two red one
black if there's exactly one yell and
there
yellow no yellow no yellow M if there
are no and the last digit of the serial
number is what serial number is on the
side right on the of the Box chat right
uh let's check serial number of the Box
can you right CLI and look for a number
look for number MSA MSA a number
five jet 7 D E8 eight eight is not all
right one
more it's eight is eight odd eight isn't
odd so this doesn't
apply Z there are no and red red
wire red wire here on is so
oh okay okay cut fourth wire number four
1 2 3 four cut cut oh
oh yes good okay nice and now then
oh my God what what what happened there
is uh no more no more press battery
battery
battery yeah oh here is so many battery
many
battery battery
battery
MSA
MSA there is so many
okay
yeah uh turn stop B turn box oh my God
no no no
[Laughter]
explosion oh my
God because button ah yeah you didn't
press the the button
detonate and and change yeah
okay maybe 5
minutes again okay or more maybe 6
minutes how about six
minutes okay okay
okay because
[Music]
okay start start start start start I Le
h i yeah you manual go manual read
okay okay here we go let's here we go oh
why so
dark oh okay okay o uh let's start with
wire wire game wire wire game I have why
are they mixed colors what the heck I
never saw that
before I find why
okay why do I have mixed
wires what you mean and there stars too
this is complex wires uh I
have weird W not normal not normal wire
maybe I don't know you does it say
anything about striped wires
stripe stripe stripe mixed wire stripped
fire wire vertical mixed Wire yeah blue
and white wire blue and
white ah Stripes yeah you
have oh okay oh oh okay uh blue and
white wire and red wire and red
wire with star uh red wire with star
okay and white
wire okay okay and blue wire and red
white stripe wire with star ah white
wire also with star so I I don't know if
it helps with with the star star
[Music]
there is a star yeah there there are
star yeah
oh okay
then uh
okay cut red really which one I have two
red maybe up
upside up up up
L up
up it's uh from uh
wch
uh ah left to left to right left to left
yeah
really you trust
me no you trust me okay I
cut do they want me to cut more yeah
more maybe maybe more I don't know is
this finished okay
you then cut blue
blue
yeah
and you die but it's okay I don't die
but I think we still have to cut
more cut more then cut or H
what oh which
color white white color white okay okay
do they want me to cut more still one
more maybe really I don't know is this
okay okay no time you trust me time two
ah 2 minutes 30 seconds okay go next
game next game next game okay um what
what uh game with many many dots and one
red triangle to triang
triangle and I move to
position that you tell me
it why why
why like pman uh uh uh maybe I move like
right right up up
down uh there's green circles also green
green circle on the game M so
bottom
row bottom
row why is this so difficult oh I so I
am on second
row went second position one second
position e e e e e oh okay it's Lighting
Red Oh No 1 minute one minute do you
know which game up yeah I find but you
know okay and right right h no no no oh
you die uh maybe
soon uh you I think you need to know the
white dot is on the second row on the
right side second position from oh
really up up right no no
I don't think so no because I already
press
up no
okay oh my God I'm sorry K ah no problem
I am po
SEL oh
you Ki never die yeah yeah legends never
die Ki never die never
yeah okay then I men I do menu I think
Japanese
day but wait I don't have nongo manual
maybe I I I use English manual but I
translate to nongo it be it will be D no
problem okay okay anyway I think I can
do it better that
way let's
go maybe
when okay
okay so
many okay no problem there
n oh okay no
problem what color
yellow three oh mm blue two blue two mhm
F to one
this oh
oh there are no uh sorry yellow
no yes yellow no ah okay let's check
[Music]
and what are all numbers
[Laughter]
together is zero zero is not on
so if it is
EQ okay
okay okay oh okay okay
nice this
one and
other
[Music]
other it's it's like big H Big H H kead
again M yeah kead oh again and it's like
um Euro oh okay H and Euro Euro it's
like por pork
pork
por it's
like
yeah okay maybe again number six and and
and and it's like
om another is like om
yeah Omega oh Omega okay okay uh uh so
you say
Euro no wait wait wait wait
[Music]
wait it's
like yeah H you mean the
H yeah scar scar
scar okay okay
H okay uh First Press uh Udo Euro Euro
oh my God I no
no
yeah no
this you know scar fork and
Omega Big H and Euro and Omega and scar
could it be
[Music]
here pork not Euro Fork euro is pork
euro is ah okay okay start with scar
scar scar scar scar scar uh and then
Fork
and then H and then Omega oh okay
okay okay and then and then what what
can I do what can I do press big button
big button button
[Music]
ah maybe I should have asked what it
says on the
[Music]
button
or was there something
written
theate
oh AG one what do you
mean exped
I'm down one more page here mod yeah
this one you mean
oh ah when this
well I don't understand we try it's
after the wire section oh okay
oh oh page
six M next time six next time next time
the is
blue
will
ah there is so much
information yeah it's so hard game okay
switch switch but maybe more time more
more more more
okay how
about okay okay this time we
win okay 10
minutes
J J with with to
everything okay
okay
whatever okay start with wire but wire
wire but I have mixed wire again okay
with mix mixed wire
M stripe stripe stripe oh like like
before but we didn't solve this one
before so I have five five wires but no
star no star no star M but five wires
and one is mix so one is mix it I have
two
blue two blue one
white one white one
red one red and one mix blue white ah
five
yes
wi sorry sorry blue and white twister
twister twister mix there is no star
ah ah ah okay
[Music]
okay blue two white one red one mix blue
white
one blue
white oh there is blue W yes
two two
and and there is BL wire yes
one
and uh on
Led Led Led
yes one
okay ah ah on the on the red red wire
LED
light uh
on okay
then one
Stay Stay
Stay Stay what don't cut okay okay the
should we try different different
part different
on I I have one more game it looks like
also wire but don't cut
oh ah okay then other other yeah yeah
yeah one more other while yeah I have
three
wire okay two blue one red but it says
one two three
ABC Oh Come Le let's
go Le maybe I have to change to
connection
[Music]
or no
star yeah but it looks
different it's
it's
uh p uh no LED peace
P
me
yep I don't
know 5 minutes it's like a BC 1 2 three
and okay I find
oh I have blue red blue uh one blue red
blue yeah one red two blue blue blue
blue red blue red is in the middle and
it says one 2 three on W chalk and ABC
on Ur chalk oh
okay okay okay
red
wi yeah red red wire what's with the red
wire should I switch
something can I switch
something
okay ah oh oh oh number number one what
color blue blue
H oh number one is B
huh
ah I
don't I don't know how to use it uh I I
I mistake two times because I don't know
how to use it no oh my God
what I cut sh sorry yeah it's okay I
don't must to be
bomb well well maybe we can still fix
this
M
then number two number two oh
oh oh my god oh then
[Music]
on
maybe maybe we need 20
minutes yeah you want to ask translator
to help us go yeah yeah cheating
cheating cheating cheating
because so typical
no no no Pap
only oh only Pap yeah no human
trans I I follow your Discord yeah do
you want I I do manual
maybe oh okay okay but go maybe let's
do junun
again
yeah we can do it we can do it we can do
it but there's like sometimes there's um
like things games that I don't even I've
never seen them
before so it's hard to find them in the
[Music]
menu oh man okay
J
okay okay okay
okay this is like the fifth time or so
fifth time is the charm we can only five
minutes 5 minutes yeah oh is it because
maybe your game not so
experienced okay
time
limit let's go okay okay let's go let's
go 5
minutes you have it okay no
problem okay ah unless you finish your
tutorial oh my God okay she can't change
the time limits unless she finish her
tutorial oh my very
good ah H there
is um a Kad Kad
again yeah big a big
a and it's like thund thund uhhuh uhhuh
th yeah Kam and Kam
and uh it's like
C yeah yeah and one dot with one dot
yeah yeah and
what oh there is a
triangle and
okay
A
a then the the the triangle like the Y
turn around oh no not triangle
yeah it's like look it like what
triangle is like look at
maybe ah maybe this okay okay ah okay a
thunder Triangle C oh oh oh okay oh yeah
yeah next next good and next is six wire
mhm
and a black two
black yeah oh black yellow one yellow
one white two wait wait yellow yellow
yellow one uh white two uhuh uhuh okay
cut number four number four number four
number four yeah oh
oh yellow stop button this
yellow stop button
this the buttons hold the button refer
[Music]
to okay
okay so yellow button right yeah uh okay
blue St release when the okay H uh press
but don't let go uh and and wait press
and hold hold hold long time
red yeah H stop hold holding when when
uh countdown timer is number
one count
okay okay okay okay okay release when
number one any
position
oh oh what why
bomb
explosion why
no sorry
oh
but but we
can win win really really yeah oh what
did we do
wrong are you double click double
click what game
Ki and game she presses the button again
after clearing the game oh but in theory
we did it right
maybe
then oh
we do it again and we will bet we will
beat it for sure okay should I read the
manual again I think the game gives us
less challenging uh options when she
plays the game cuz she didn't finish the
tutorial okay
then I play game one more yes yes that's
best best
combination sorry okay no problem but we
only have five minutes so
fast fast then let's go okay okay oh
there is a three wire
okay blue one black
two uh
blue okay uh
second wire cut uhhuh second okay okay
go next easy speed mode next kead oh
kead again okay MH um it's like m i
popet m m
m
m it's like
pig pig T it's like pig tail P yeah P
tail is that the ah the m still you mean
the
M hi hi hi oh okay okay M with pigtail
[Music]
okay okay and it's
like it's
like maybe this one
maybe but
wait m m
and I like will
you ah maybe maybe it is this one okay
okay okay M and and it's
like yeah
and and it's
like uh one Circle in
c a
g one Circle in
G uh C in a circle ah Circle
what a g a g in a
circle there see see Okay C maybe this
again okay and and what the it's like
oh what what what what
water oh it's like X and I
mix it x and
I probably this one but wait X and I ah
ah it's probably okay can you repeat
again uh from beginning which ones you
have okay X and
I
sorry what what what first what wait no
no no no no uh tell me
J ah J ah one is one see in the
circle yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
and
like uhhuh uhuh uh and it's like
P okay okay and IP X plus I I okay press
uh C in a circle
yeah oh
no maybe maybe this one okay press
pigtail yeah oh
press oh
no then okay finish and
finish last button h P
button hi the P
button push button push white what um
big button one hide pushy yeah where was
it again here H it it says it says
push
yeah what okay
uh
press if the button is white and there's
a lid indicator with label c a r hold
button oh my god do you have c a
r car c a
r
i
y oh my god oh no you only one more
maybe should I play the bump because we
can have more time but maybe more
more when I
play but we can have more
time Li one more can I play
game okay okay okay okay I try to
focus okay
really fighting fighting fighting
let's
go okay probably we wire this yeah okay
six wires M Leed two blue two black one
white
one uh red red two blue
to
yeah black one white
one uh okay uh
uh did serial
number serial
number uh t b 6 Q S2 two it's not odd
right so or is
it Chad please help
to uh cut uh number
four number four
oh yeah
okay next another one is keepad M MH mhm
okay H one is star black star black star
oh I think that's only this one okay and
then and another one is like small be
small B yeah yeah yeah small B yeah yeah
yeah with t B with t like a t inside oh
yeah yeah yeah okay okay okay and
another one is like um snake um is like
number three okay and next and next and
next and next
is okay
okay hi uh B small b
b uh snake and Then star snake star
yeah nice nice nice nice nice and and
button button button button big button
blue and bomb
button blue blue and bomb bomb
button
button the
button what
is yeah oh the button is blue and the
button says
abort abort the
detonate there is more than
one
okayy hi hi more than
one yeah two okay press button press and
immediately press and and
go press really yeah yeah just press
anytime go
go
[Music]
[Applause]
finally oh my God we did it go
we did
it I'm
[Music]
happy party better that we end it here
yes we will end it here but yeah can I
give
hug oh
my if we do more we get harder
games be
cute cute my
child my child my my
mommy yes so
cute say with cute
voice hey h I'm Mommy
right say you are so hot oh hot Mommy I
Hy mommy
no
no under
bad
okay okay then let's go
um our oh okay program
okay oh we're moving
o oh I leave the bgm on it cuz it's kind
of nice oh I I stand up I I stand up I
stand up stand up stand
up okay
okay ready when you are oh is this
supposed to look like that ah oh
oh a there we go there we
go let go let's
go go was still Idol
outfit Idol face
M
yeah I had lots of
fun me too oh well I'm bigger than you
yeah why
no oh not fair oh okay now I think it
was optical illusion cuz you were more
in the front this is the
reality
you then um then and
then it's time to say goodbye now oh no
oh this has been the cooperation with K
and and
go from now on we are friends right we
are friends best friends friends Tomo ah
friend ah
Tomo so maybe we collab again
someday mhm one one another day we play
together some games or dance again
together oh dance I like Dan okay
another day cuz yeah this time we will
not forget maybe okay thank you very did
you have fun go yeah I was very happy I
was very happy I was very
happy how it for you K I was very
awkward how to say awkward in
Korean uh
awkward and
me me only me not
you but but
and my goal to collab with go has been
achieved so we can work on more
improving our friendship so I'm excited
this is the beginning of a big beautiful
story iagi
yeah right iagi is story
I learn in
dualingo oh me too see
translation ah see you again next time
Lally yes yes are you sad not sad don't
be sad we can meet again okay thank you
so
much and also to the staff the staff
were so helpful and they teach me how
everything and they fix everything come
on St thank
you Idol staff is
wow I see I don't understand
and everybody make sure to check out go
Channel on YouTube and on soap oh thank
you oh my
God in
Korea it's like daku
box
yeah
Boxx in Korea
[Music]
is like
hosting thank you you're
welcome every time welcome I welcome you
come back to
me ah water ah waterfall what w yeah
trickle down
hting trickle down oh oh trickle down
effect well I think also it trickle down
to me I see many Korean Bros here many
Korean Bros hello okay okay thank you
for watching I'm looking forward to
dancing together again and we do Mirage
challenge one day too
[Music]
maybe love
love
sexy byebye
[Music]
byebye bye
bye
byebye see you see you
later what did bye-bye bye-bye bye-bye
byebye
wo
bye-bye oh I'm in you
no
byebye
byee ah me too me
too
really I end
now I
n
[Music]