[Music]
so
do
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
hello ohayo
welcome i am uh back with
audio on both sides
of your ears
actually yesterday it was only on one
ear
and that while i was streaming i was
kind of thinking ah i think i know why
because the day before i streamed at the
studio
with nina and there was like all kinds
of fancy audio
setup uh where they also the staff
changed my
audio and streamlabs to stereo
and usually it would be mono yeah they
changed it
it changed it and uh i didn't think that
i didn't realize it until i started
streaming again
from my place yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
so now i changed it back but i realized
during the
during the manga stream i was thinking i
should
the staff might have changed some of my
settings so maybe that's the cause
but like it's a setting that i couldn't
have changed
during the stream because it needed to
uh restart the
the program but anyway
when i listened to the stream it wasn't
even that bad you guys are just making
too much of a big deal you're making an
elephant
out of a fly
straight you guys were i mean it's not
not like i didn't read the chat
uh in the beginning like you don't have
to spam it for like 10
goddamn minutes
stresses me out man nothing i can do
about it if i already know it
can't fix it and stop spamming god damn
it
bunk bunk the chat
but anyway
but okay well sometimes there's those
times where
i'm a bit late on uh realizing what's
going on so in those times it's good if
you spam something for 10 minutes
uh it's been a while since the last solo
stream
um
because the last three streams
where collab streams
and today later today i was also
planning
a collab stream so this stream right now
is spontaneous because reason number one
no bdm oh god dammit
thank you
hey what was i saying
uh oh yeah it was gonna be four collabs
in a row
but ah this stream here i
i i slide it in smoothly and
spontaneously
because i need to prepare some things
for the collab for later actually
what i'm preparing actually no what i'm
going to prepare
is not necessarily something i need for
the collab
oh but we're gonna we're gonna have to
get something started
and you you guys haven't seen we
we haven't been alone together
for a while now
[Music]
let's move let's move
is the bgm too quiet or like a
yes thank you guys and yeah now let's
let's
put this here let's make it a
celebrational
party party vibes
thank you for the super chat guys yes
oh it's actually also really been a long
time since i last logged into minecraft
it's been a long time and let's see if
my chickens are alive
[Music]
give me your eggs that's not many eggs
where are all the eggs
i bring you some seeds right
you eat seeds right right
answer me unbelievable
unbelievable
they don't they don't answer me
who do you think race you
who do they think raised them
good morning oh the door did you open
the door
how dare you okay sorry i love you all
i'm sorry they must be thinking all them
potential didn't you woke up with the
wrong leg today
okay eat eat this eat this
eat this eat it oh my god how cute they
are oh like
right next to me how adorable is that
close
no escaping you are all waiting here to
be
killed one day no escaping okay
eat eat grow big and fat and then let me
eat you
what they stopped eating okay i think
everyone was bad
maybe the babies need some eat
a cat
eat i think everyone
that what what's with that little boy
don't run
don't run okay they don't want anything
anymore
wake up wake up wait oh wait i don't
have any seats
i was trying to feed them but i ran out
of seats okay
[Music]
[\h__\h] how do i not hit them when they
were born
i didn't hit it though
that was not me
that wasn't me hey what what
what's the best angle to shoot eggs
okay floyd
i'm just if i do it too fast i'm scared
i'll hit someone
ah no see that's what i mean
go away go away
do you want to die
you have 10 seconds but you want to be
free i think this one wants to really be
free
wait okay well i mean okay
you're free bye bye i don't want to kill
you so you're free
okay
i hope you like it better outside good
luck then
okay bye bye
[Music]
well maybe i'll get you back someday
yes seed and wheat
party
[Music]
it's really been a while since the last
minecraft stream and the last solo
stream
is so weird it feels so so nostalgic
and we could talk about all the collabs
today
and reflect on them
don't what what
eggs don't actually do any damage so you
can spam them without worrying about
hurting them the chicken splash
red because eggs do knock back with a
hole
what
they do not wait so they hurt themselves
but
they are they're fine what
uh
okay does kiara post her stream schedule
anywhere i started this week
to do a stream schedule
uh even though i i didn't really
originally i didn't really want to do it
because like
i guess especially this week at the end
of this week i changed a lot of things
and i feel bad about it um but yeah
i i did post it at the beginning of the
week
oh wait where am i ah wait i was looking
for potato seeds but you just plant the
potatoes again right okay
uh but
wait now i don't see where i already
planted something
now i don't see it yeah
or where is all of this used
i broke what do you mean i broke
everything
wait
eh what about this like
i have to i have to replant the seeds
like always
i forgot how to do it
[Music]
it's been a while okay like actually i
haven't played it since the last
collaboration
i wanted to play minecraft more often
but then again i was like okay
everyone else is playing minecraft i
don't wanna
like like you know i don't wanna bore
you guys
so i i tried to play other stuff and
give you some
you know some some variation
but then i forgot everything
more wheat wheat sorry it's a bit
difficult to pronounce that for me
eh okay now let's put that doll
they don't need space right you told me
that before
i don't have so many potatoes
yes
[Music]
put that in this space what
what no
no no no no no no
save see i know better than you
someone in the comments said they need
space no no no no no no
don't lie to me
yo okay this is finished
so what are we going to do today let me
tell you
uh and also wait is that is
is is the chicken gone is this gone
did it leave just like where would it go
ah there it is i'm taking you back this
is all the freedom you get
my friend come
did a creeper explode here that's that
looks like was that that was not always
there
someone was digging here no chicken
let's go up
come on
yes go back to your friends isn't it
lonely without your friends so
ah no no everyone stay
come oh yes
yes and yes perfect eggs
everywhere wow i love how they're like
cuddling with me
are they never like full
this is so cute they're so fluffy
no no more
are you so cute what what what's wrong
with you
are they not accepting you or what's
wrong with you those are the courts
yes thank you okay a little bit more egg
gotcha
i see but they run into me eh
no
[Music]
that was very some unlucky eggs man
i'm sorry whoever i was hitting i'm
sorry
coming outside oops bye bye
that's it bye bye
yes so what we will do i will tell you
let me tell you
we are looking for sheep because
um i want to build a kfp
restaurant but i don't want it to just
be
you know boring wood i have a lot of
wood but i don't want it to be boring or
wood so i am
i want to like get a lot of sheep and
have them
in many many colors
oh that's what i need have them in many
colors
and then i can make color blocks like
these
and then i'll make a fancy restaurant
out of them
which i think is kind of weird that that
the only choice
uh to make the only option to make like
colored blocks
is these wool blocks or
wait or uh what was it like some
some mixture between gravel and
sand but that seems like more effort
than the sheep option right so we're
going for the sheep option because they
also
could give us meat eventually but wait
let's let's build
like a little area for them first like a
fence
does inna really not have sheeps yet
it feels like she would have them but
she has maybe only
only uh the moo moose
let's see oh
where are all the moomoos what the hell
oh she's raising them and in free range
now
did she change her mind about like did
me criticizing
her help criticizing her
her way of raising these mumus did it
help
oh while they're running all around
that's good
did they escape let's see we have so
many flowers here
like i can use all of these flowers for
um
coloring my wool wait someone is
building something they're not incorrect
what future library paperwork ahead
dentist coming what
tower of friendship what
what what
nani wait i see
i see something that doesn't really look
like friendship
i see um tnt
thingies what is this
good ass project get out
[Music]
yeah but you need it to like uh when you
place tnt right then you need the
redstone to
have like a line and then explode it
something like that anyway
anyway no one has sheep i think so i
shall be the one
to get us some sheep and i've seen one
sheep
living over there for a while now
several times i've seen it there unless
someone has killed it
it should still be there uh so
let's let's hope but oh wait what does
it eat wheat right oh goddammit did i
just use up all my wheat
did i just use up all my wheat i have
five
well that's enough to bring bring it
over right
wait sorry i keep on losing my my track
uh my my what my something
i'm gonna make a uh a little uh
space for the for the sheepy
before i get them here you know
yes
how big should it be we want a lot of
sheep but for now maybe that's enough
[Music]
you're imagining something i don't know
what you're talking about
where is my where is that watermelon i
keep on seeing
i hope nobody killed my that one lonely
sheep
there was a grey sheep around here that
has been living here for a while all
alone
so i shall i shall give it a bright
future
of being sheered
shared shoot eh
did someone kill watame
coco
[Music]
it should have been here right there was
always a gray sheep here
don't you remember guys
is it gone
cali killed one they spawn they walk
well well yeah they walk yeah but
it was still like around here the whole
time
well let's see
my hopefully this is like a
really uh nice area like it has
oh a cow has so many
like it's so fruitful like i was so
surprised because the world i started in
was the complete opposite
oh lots of cows have you seen any sheeps
[Music]
hello i need a sheeple how fast do they
procreate by the way how fast
i need a lot but okay maybe not right
away
um later on what i'm gonna do with
american we were either gonna make like
a hopper system
for my eggs or a grilling system for my
chicken
but you know i don't i don't
i don't want to i don't want to like
you know
i don't want to kill them
[Music]
i don't want to
i don't wanna
ah
many
[Music]
one two
is there more no
only two that's actually perfect that's
perfect can't pick young
but i can only take one at a time right
i can only take one at a time right
hopefully i'll find back here
you can take both eh amazing
okay let's try i have to just hold it
right
can i like feed it already where's the
other one
you two are going to be
the base of the first kfp building
your wool will be the pillars
of kf kfp's bright future
yoroshiku oreos
let's go okay
you free will be the future where did
you come from
wow
[Music]
oh they're so adorable they like my cats
when i have
some food or like even when i don't have
food
oh we gotta go slowly here they're bad
at swimming
bad at swimming
oh god we should maybe go more to the
sign yep bad swimmers
oh god it's night soon what do we do
also i don't really remember where i
came from
eh
[Music]
i don't want to lose these babies
already lost
no no no no come come come come
no more swimming okay also i need to eat
no [\h__\h]
where's my black sheep where's my black
sheep
oh okay let's go come on
come on come on oh you're back
don't don't fall in there
oh
[Applause]
there's only one or do i i don't i only
see one but i don't have a i don't have
a shield
god damn it oh god damn it i'm sweet
you can't you can't catch me i'm speed
i go so fast i zoom zoom
try to fight me boy
okay nevermind
oh okay he's coming back i think he's
coming back
my sheep my see
um uh okay
okay sheep i hear oh god oh god oh god i
still hear him i said i heard him
don't follow me where's my home
no leave me alone why do you swim so
slow but
dive so fast that's like not even normal
it's not realistic where is my home is
that my home
ah okay uh
would it be smart to bring a bed with me
would it be smart that should be close
to my home i've seen this before
maybe around there
okay
[Music]
take always bring a bed but like
if i sleep won't they run away
um maybe they stay in the area because
they also just stayed there while i was
like running away
from the pillars villages
is this is i'm going to the right
direction i see flowers
so maybe yeah
spare bed not main i have many pants i
have many beds because i
i am always ready to welcome kelly
oh god spider spider is trying to
come to me am i going in the right
direction that is the real question
[Music]
need to close it let's close those
fences completely
okay but i couldn't read the rest
something about terra cotta and wu
wrong way really
yeah probably
i have uh how where am i where are
minecraft
screenshots saved again where are they
because i tried to find them before this
uh stream i couldn't find them
go back to the lava you you guys just
know
our world are already too well
app data
wow uh but where on minecraft
screenshots okay
let me uh
i hope no one's gonna kill me is this
nope oh where am i
where are they um here here
3 0 4 3 0 four
uh so that that that that way
and minus four hundred fifty-five okay
maturity has a three hundred
for it itai
well i mean actually maybe it's faster
if i die yep thank you
no but wait
[Music]
oh well it's too late
well well well well my wheat is gone
all right let's let's sleep to the nail
okay so do i have wheat
um
[Music]
maybe maybe
she she would not
be mad also
wait look i can borrow that from her
maybe
one wheat i mean i can totally give it
back to herself
but one is enough right get your stuff
and but i don't know where it is
i don't care what did i have nothing
important huh
i think
two stacks of meat should i have oh my
god
one three five minus six you want me to
get it okay
one three five
what was the other one 306 one
one three five where the hell is that
and one free
oh lava ah were we there was that this
button
one no i don't think we were that close
one wait is it
yep don't fall into the lava don't fall
into the lava don't fall into the lava
one three five where is my
stuff where is my stuff
should be here oh
wait what was the other one what was the
other one 6
30. uh
[Music]
left
wait is it
this is so slow
is this the right way yeah i left cheap
here right
my shifu runway yeah that way
which way i think it's the right way
because i know this area
should be here
okay yay
okay oh my helmet oh i had a helmet
[Music]
and now do i have everything i hear lava
now we shall find the shibu
good that i took a screenshot very good
sugar
eat oh yeah one second
i took a screenshot of the shipu area
wait i didn't bring a bed
you
wow kiara so
smart so smart
go go home first okay where's my home
guys
where is my home
[Music]
i heard a chicken oh a lonely chicken
i don't have seeds but i would love to
bring you home
i shall rescue all the chicken
where am i going
am i going in the right direction
i see lava again hello lava
wrong way where you just came from where
did i come from
250 450
oops 250 minus 450.
you guys remember you guys remember
to like that's the wrong one
it died
[Music]
god i wanna like what
i want to tell you guys about things but
i'm too focused on
on like getting back to my home and then
getting to the sheep and then getting
back to home and then getting to the
[Music]
sheep
okay let's get up there what was it 250.
254 something
in that case maybe here
okay how did you guys like the
among us streamers i see my tower how
did you like the among us stream
yesterday
everyone did you enjoy
it it was fun
right 10 out of 10. thank you
ah i wanna play it again like
with everyone but also maybe with this
with the uh with you guys
let's take this one okay and now let's
go to the shape
now i have weed again right
you were the mvp translator thank you
and
yeah i'm just glad i could help honestly
because
i i was like
in this game we need to discuss things
if we don't discuss
um it might be funny for a while but we
will never
never really do any progress in the game
because it would just be like
polka screaming ames us
and the english-speaking girls
probably being like like like not saying
anything at all
because they're like not confident in
their japanese
yeah i was like i can't let that happen
i cannot let that happen
sheep one two three oh so i'm not that
direction oh god i'm so
yeah kelly was also really quiet but i
think she was like just really
really exhausted and um she
she just moved like right before the
stream
and like one two three oh
and man i'll be really close we're
really close
uh
[Music]
here uh
yeah she just moved she had just moved
and her
she had her old laptop again
but the new internet in i think in the
old place or something was kind of
confusing i see a sheep
and yeah i i know how exhausted hello
how exhausting
moving is hello you also want to come oh
they also react to wheat that's fun
why not where is my black sheep
where's my black sheep do they also say
in english language uh something like
like when you're the outsider or
something or the weird one you're like
the black sheep
schwab's is chef we say that in did it
die no don't tell me it died
it died thank you for the super chat
maybe it died just like that
oh well i mean two will do but um oh
that's kind of sad
black one seems to be gone you say that
oh
interesting black sheep sometimes i feel
like a black sheep
okay how do we get back home
how do we get back home follow me guys
follow me okay
i don't care about the cows i just need
the sheep okay
just bring me the sheep and there no one
will be hurt
am i going the right way guys
you guys help me oh they're like
actually like
choosing the right path and not trying
to fall into the hole or something
okay okay i don't even know where i'm
going i sleep
good idea maybe will they run away
hopefully not oh they stay there smart
no don't go away
hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey hey
hey whoo
no sleep only sheep
by the way i i'll be um reading a lot of
super chat
uh am i going to write direction majida
i don't know
i'll be reading lots of super chat after
today's stream
because for all the collab streams i
didn't do super chat readings
because that's just how it goes where's
my other sheep where's my other sheep
eh itchy
what are you doing let's bring the moo
moo too
come come come
stay with me
wait is it getting dark again didn't i
sleep
no it's fine okay okay wait what's my
coordinates again three hundred
minutes [\h__\h] thank you thank you don't
go so fast yeah okay okay okay
sheep ship one ship two okay
350 350 so
that way
[Music]
wait no not that way that way yep that
way
350. meh
come come come come come babies come
babies
okay so i'll be streaming probably like
until
[Music]
even half past wow yeah you guys aren't
in a different time so maybe for one
more hour or so
i just want to get some sheep and you
know and then i'll do the super chat
reading
because i i think i mean collabs
generally
don't shouldn't get so many super chats
but especially the collab with nene
you guys were so sweet you all sent like
orange super chats
like also like as a as a ticket i guess
for the concert
i really appreciate that thank you guys
it was really cute
all the orange super chats am i going
the right way
i think yeah 350 and
what was it my wait i think i think i
know i know i know where are they
okay okay i know i know i see it
i see it you love the concert
me and nina we chose some songs together
a few days before the
before the thing i think like four days
or so before
and then i uh
said yeah we should maybe like part the
lyrics so that we don't
don't sing the same part it's kind of
boring so
we sat together and did like a
lyrics parting session
we did it all together but though the
part
parts parting lyrics parting
really went very fast and then yeah i
think
we both actually didn't really practice
because both of
those songs are songs we both sing very
often
so there wasn't really any practice
necessary but before the stream
when we were in the studio we we
practiced it a few times and tried to
like
adjust the audio and so on
but in the end it orange really well
just i only messed up in the very very
beginning
because i sang the wrong part in the
first line or something
but after that everyone everything went
so smooth
so i'm really glad we did it it was lots
of loads of fun
the only problem was maybe the
disconnect but
wait someone told me i should will they
stay in there
will they stay in there
where did my wait isn't there one sheep
no okay one sheep is not missing
everyone's here okay they will not stay
in there okay so i have to do
this is it
[Music]
come back come back how do i build the
fence when they run away once i built
the fence
how do i do it even it out
ah okay i mean
[Music]
how will i get out that's the question
no no no no no no no
see what i'm holding
well can you come back oh
stupid sheep oh yeah okay fine
wait hi
can you get out now no right
okay and now i marry you and you and you
and you you can also have some fun oh
baby
[Music]
wait is there also a baby cow
how do i get out i don't have
did i need anything else oh they're
trying to eat the grass
there's not really any grass here i'm
sorry oh wait i should give you
hi kawaii
so cute look at their eyes
[Laughter]
ah kawaii and how do i get out
oh oh they're eating so cute they're
like chumps
but could you not escape when i
okay quick get a gate
hacking into the gate
okey doke oh a car maybe carpet is
better because every time i would
open the gate they would probably run
out and that's hella annoying i had to
get some
a carpet somewhere oh
hello good morning sunshine
yeah and then the bracelets were that
was so sweet actually
um nana wrote that tweet and made me so
so happy that someone appreciates me
but also inna wrote me a private message
right after the stream
and she was like uh she was like
what did she say she was like
like having really i wanna i don't wanna
get
wrong she said
it made me so happy she was like
uh she's always so amazed at how much
energy and good translation
communication i bring to collaboration
[Music]
it's so sweet you know
i love inna
[Music]
it's just like she she thinks of me
that's so kind she's like the sweetest
girl ever unbelievable
yoshi okay we got sheep now we just
gotta wait so they make more sheep
and but what else could we do
we should probably mine a little bit
because uh oops
for what i'm making i need i need
hoppers and for hoppers i need a lot of
iron right
probably on my head a lot but still i
gotta get some on my own
right i think okay so basically
i wanna i wanna do the hoppy thing but i
don't wanna
like like completely change the
structure
but i can just do it underneath right
sleep oh okay should sleep in my own bed
thank you for the super chat
okay got you
ah it's not light okay yeah and
i can do it under okay take too much
iron
i mean but there was something with
water and then i would only need
one hopper but then they would be they
then they need to be like constantly
swimming right
but okay so i didn't take a close look i
just take a
took a rough look so basically if i fl
flood the the thing
the building the room and then put like
one hopper in the middle or somewhere
and then have like underground chests
that collect it and that's that's it
right
uh and yeah someone also sent me away
with like
cards but i'm not too sure about that
um
underground chestnut
rails under and minecraft minecart with
hopper replace
all all of the floor poppers mine
minecart hopper
hopper minecarts
you can also rig the hopper to dispense
what the cards are pretty simple
okay if so does that mean um
i wait so there they
are they're they're like on this level
so i oh i heard that i heard the egg
flop
so i go underneath that level
i don't know i'm not really good at
looking at instructions
how you doing guys
why why why why why what's happening oh
my god it's like lagging
egg egg and egg and thank you
thank you blah blah blah blah
i did not want to hurt you right i have
16 eggs down
they're so close i don't want to hurt
them
your eye you're too close i mean that's
kind of ah no sorry
gosh how much damage can they take
i hope a bit more than that
that's all
one more ink
oh my god it's getting like kind of full
in here ah
welcome to the wood ah sorry
eggs don't do damage it but it looks
like they take damage
oh my god okay
okay i need to get out of here
it's stinky in here stinky stinky i'll
tell you
it's just the animation okay
all righty well done
uh i guess we do some mining for happen
shall we then we can also have some more
conversation
a pig eggs and the big eggs and the
pickaxe
that should be enough and some torches
and an egg
egg goes here
cool should we do mining
like uh over there
inside the thingy or just a random place
i wonder
i have torches we're not stinky
feet again
i need wheat
why is the door open you guys okay
there was an enderman
and there's a skeleton hiding behind the
tree you think i can see you [\h__\h]
alrighty uh there's a a bit wait wait is
that finished
this one's finished i think
um this one's finished
what what what the hell
wow you're wearing a lot of things
a zombie pillager zombie pillager
oh wait zombie zombie witch is that a
zombie witch
holy [\h__\h] i don't know the nose looks
like
give me something giving me nothing huh
what the hell useless
well i'm glad that's probably the
pillager that that killed me before
or tried to kill me
so
from there
that's going going very well going very
smooth here
and nice nice
okay
at least though the weeds don't run away
from me
when i open the door
okay now feed the sheep wow this is
you're so busy in minecraft you gotta
feed this and them and look
hello how cute
wait it already grew up and now they're
like breeding
in breeding like breeding each other
don't know how
if i like that but yep
another another cow
but i want more [\h__\h] that that one was
just born right
um
okey-dokey enough of that should we feed
the chicken one more time
okay yes
[Music]
wow okay wow so many eggs holy [\h__\h]
collecting eggs every morning just like
my mommy
okay let me out bye bye oops sorry sorry
sorry oops oh oh oh
wait that was just an egg oh god oh god
you're in the way
oh you're born um
inconveniently no get out of there
wow
oh god oh god oh god
get out of there back
okay little chicken i don't care
you run freely or something oh oh nice
okay are you stuck
on the wall but when i did it on the
wall i don't know one died
one died when i did it on the wall
anyway let's go digging why do we go
digging
what is this wait she has like a rails
she has rails now right so they made
rails right
i never used this before how does i get
into the front card probably
how do i get oh and then i press this
but where do i go where do i go
huh
it's not moving remove one
do it it's gone down
god damn it
how does it hit the button and hold ah
upside up sorry
maybe now the speed comes
what where do we go now
maybe the girls already like
dug out everything that's interesting
wait
maybe i want to go here where does the
card go
oh god where did the card go oh there it
is
watson's shaft oh my god
can i not go into watson's shaft
isn't this where i died
[Music]
can i go into what's in shop
i'll do some independent digging here if
that's okay
oh whoa
there's stairs
by the way we're looking for iron
let's go let's go that way maybe or
whoa
oh oh oh chomp
it down she's amazing oh
oh too much lava i'm scared
too much lava oh too many creepers
ah i don't like the shaft after all
you
i did bring a bunch of pickaxes yeah
i don't know why i have the pumpkin
[Music]
i'll dig here i'll dig here
right here but we're already pretty deep
right
uh ma 14 pretty deep right
so maybe we just dig straight
or go to 12 or something
what do you think guys
sound plan thank you
i'm a smart bird after a while
i hope we don't suddenly run into lava
smartbear thank you well let's go one
down
[Music]
i have uh i haven't played that much
minecraft really
recently so besides streams really not
not at all
so i feel like i kind of fell behind in
progress because every
every one of the other girls they were
playing so much minecraft like so much
minecraft
i really fell behind
it
are you guys not getting sick of too
many minecraft streams
mina michaela
no wow
okay i was really worried about that
like if i
i really want to do more minecraft
streams but i was just worried that
everyone would just get sick of it
strangely enough hey but like
interestingly me too um
like i watched like every single
minecraft stream from
piccola senpai and i also didn't get
sick of it
i wonder why like usually you would get
sick
at some point no
that's what what i would think let's go
one more down i mean i'm not looking for
diamonds but whatever
i shall be naked
on it yes to be honest oh you didn't get
sick of it
oh yeah use torches shield smart
nice zoo
who said that bottom left side
one person it was bottom left
but like eventually i want to do some
rta stuff you know
and like going exploring to find like
like a wit
not a witch house what was that that i
saw that in pekuda stream one time
you young
like a mansion yeah it looked like a
mansion
yeah i want to find that the other girls
didn't find anything like that yet right
i went i went you saw oh
thank you
i saw a good eye good eye oh what
more iron iron
is the right pronunciation don't believe
anyone else who says anything
they're all wrong this is the only
only right pronunciation yep
praise me more nah i keep on looking for
the torches but they're in the other
hand
oh diamonds this is a
iron okay
[Music]
so many diamonds
bye yay
normally you would look like there's
there's times where you look for hours
for them no
like the last time i was looking for
some i never found them
hey
what the hell what was that
wasn't it like right in front of me and
then
now i understand i think i understand
just ignore the lava keep on digging or
should i
go a different direction go
i'll go back yep okay yes yes good idea
first diamond super chat thank you
please run back home and say
yes they're really rare now
like actually like
because i've never actually got one
myself before even in the time when i
played
in solo when i played it on a solo
server
i never found one even after hours of
digging
i only found like stones but there was a
chest here so i'm just gonna
make use of that chest for now so let's
call it
thank you all right let's put the iron
there
too why not
just don't die you have
one mission don't die
where was my spot lower lower limit
eat yeah yeah keep on forgetting to eat
in this game
why they have to eat so often
[Music]
okay yay
do you guys want to know something about
polka
want to know something about poruka
senpai
even even when she's not streaming
she's playing instruments randomly
because we had like fun uh conversation
on discord right
discussing the collab and stuff and she
would just randomly take out instruments
and play them
this is so funny man it's
like oh yes this is polka no one else
is as crazy and funny as polka
skip
[Music]
that
me
it's so random like suddenly she takes
out a random
instrument and i asked her
where is the shamisen shamisenwa the
kitakito shamisen vanayashi
foreign
it's kind of weird for me in english
because you normally
in english obviously there you don't say
chan or something hello
[Music]
but yeah in japanese it's really rude to
just say someone's name without
but since i have like japanese uh
viewers
i feel like when i speak english and i
don't say chan
or something like that it's uh it sounds
very rude to them
ame was here
as expected from our detective
what i drowned myself in front of kuda's
house what are you talking about
did i read that right
ah that was ames house
you mean ami's house oh what the hell is
that
easy to get lost be careful
but there's some irony i want to take
that
good prediction amen let's see if i get
will get lost but what if i just stick
straight i'm not really i i could just
stick straight no
muscle
[Music]
where did i come from though where did i
come from
did i come from here
no no no it's not here but there's iron
yes sure
nicer so much iron
thank you but where does this go
where does this go disco disco body
[Music]
uh i didn't want to fall down though
okay
where does this go
funny this was like a ina
level pun really batman where
where are we
in
the last obsidian mine
nanka what a fancy name
did we come from here
danger maze what
is
is this not where i came from small mine
am i going the wrong direction ah no
wait isn't that where it came from
chest oh yeah that's where i came from
hi hi hi
hmm hi
well uh let's go dig somewhere else what
the hell
where did those suddenly come from now i
don't want to go in there anymore
let's go let's go to the small mine
maybe
there we are perfect don't go stop
okay
dead
there's nothing well i saw mine here
all right it goes down
wait wait no right oops that's where it
came from
i am confused
okay that's wait that's not very that's
not very obvious
ah whoops okay left side left side left
side left side my friends
i also don't have many pickaxes left
where are we
44. that's so
high wait but we're not looking for
diamonds but still let's go lauren
[Music]
fisher
spiders
everyone is so nice to me recently
what's happening everyone is so nice
[Music]
anyone's so nice
like yesterday i was overwhelmed okay
i was overwhelmed everyone was sending
me so many positive messages
he did it did it tell you
i like it when people praise me
so yesterday was a good day a good day
for me
good translator but like everyone i was
only praised for being a translator
kind of kind of would also like to be
praised for something else but maybe i'm
asking for too much
well no it's it's fine it's fine i i
appreciate the praise
but i need to i need to have a reason
i'll give you guys a reason to praise me
for something else too
thank you for the super chat i'm looking
forward to all the
super chat readings after today because
i missed so many from all the collabs
i'm sorry about that like honestly i'm
so sorry
i don't know i'm like really bad at
lying myself
so uh yesterday i was also really bad at
detecting
foreign i didn't think of that until
yesterday i thought
i thought i would i mean i'm not good at
lying but
i i think i was good at catching others
lives but amen
i'm always i don't know
but don't worry will forever
exist oh
i i want we're not going to this band
because i want to see the day
where me and nanatang
will give a 3d concert
together
i want to see that day thank you for the
super chat
and good night though
oops that's not what i meant
wait i'm running out of [\h__\h] that's my
last pickaxe
[Music]
i should have brought more pickaxes ah
where are we 19. huh
why is there daddy what is daddy in
english what is this called in english
dirt dirt okay that was not so hard
oh grab oh my god that's gravel
let's grab them
where is it where is it
yeah i need a shovel i know but i never
bring a shovel because who needs a
shovel
3d cardboard no no i want a proper
3d concert and i want us to like also
dance like
have a choreography and stuff
so one day one day i'll make it happen
i'm telling you one day just have to
survive until that day
you know i often die
just have to survive
oh i thought it was lava for a second
oh gold again gold gold
[Music]
nice i actually came for iron i'm not
getting that much iron
man
[Music]
um
i almost have to go back iron is higher
goddammit really isn't it everywhere
isn't it everywhere what about here
what about 29 or so
iron is area right that's what i thought
but i also need some coal i need
everything because i'm just
i didn't play so much minecraft i need
to play more minecraft
i like did you guys see that um when ame
uploaded her schedule for
this week she deleted it but um
she had a my a schedule up that was like
minecraft every day
and i believed it because i was like
yeah that's a thing that ame would do
yes i
i want to do a whole week of minecraft
too catch up with everything you know
okay which direction this this direction
now
i think we need more pickaxes wait wait
wait wait
hi
no but next week i have some i already
have uh
planned it out in my google calendar
i already have it planned out but i'm
not sure how it will go because
finally on monday there's something
happening
can you believe it uh people who
watch all my streams they know
that i'm currently streaming
from my manager's place manager internet
because after i moved and there were
some issues with setting up the internet
there
they um yeah they
delayed my internet setup like many
times
and so turned out that
it would only be set up three weeks
after i moved into my place
three weeks oh diamond time
what is that button even for
what does that button do yep
so obviously i mean yeah a few days
without streaming okay but three weeks
without streaming
sounded impossible i tried to do it with
my with my mobile
portable wi-fi and it kind of worked but
only for
like podcast style my my body would not
move
so that that wouldn't have been uh good
for three weeks
so the only real
good choice that i had was to stream
from my manager's place but she she was
very
very kind she offered it to me so
that was very very kind of
standard
foreign mvp manager yeah
best manager i love my manager
not in that way okay i love cali in that
way
but um
really really helped me out so much and
tomorrow
i'm supposedly
finally getting internet in my in my
house
so in the evening i should be able to
stream
and oh wow those stairs
i only remember those shitty stairs
damn nice days probably that was ame
right
america today
amazing are they having like a
party over there there's like four mobs
like talking to each other
or five even you want to fight
you want to fight oops i have a shield
where's my shield did i lose my shield
aina you did it why are you crying ina
why are you crying did you do it close
your door
no
[Music]
no no no what inaudible what did you do
what did you do i gave you credit tell
me what you did
the initial one oh
[Music]
you know i have to say um i i've said it
before but your setup here is beautiful
and amazing
it's like beautiful like you have the
prettiest house and it's so organized
and and and and you have so many lovely
pets
and i i i i respect you for setting the
cows free
although i don't know if that was on
purpose or didn't mean did you eat all
of them
and also like giving them free range i
think that's very very human
very nice of you to like let them run
free you know
you know and i really respect your
system here could you please teach me
could you please teach me how to do this
i need to learn how to do this i
you're you're so skilled oh you didn't
know
you didn't know yeah wait eh
i thought you like ate them all or set
them free
you didn't know i was like when i
started the stream i
went over to your farm i was like where
are all the where are all the cows like
it was fill you didn't know
hey it was not me i swear you have to
watch my archive
and did not do it gura did it
ate the cup guru ate so many cows they
were like hundreds
but um i actually i i brought uh
a bunch of sheeps and cows over today
i didn't want to want the cows i just
wanted to sheep but if you want you can
take my cows look i made a little
oh i should put torches there
i made a little uh
i made a little thingy here so i have a
bunch of cows and a bunch of sheep but i
only want the sheep because of the wool
so you are welcome to take the cows if
you want
uh but also could i could i borrow
your shears your scissors
eventually i mean i i could just make
them myself but
yeah some some were like just uh they
just escaped from the
oh there's someone on my roof ah
oh hello hello hello
oh my god i'm scared
i want to fight them i don't want to
sleep i want to fight them but where's
my oops
where's my shield
ina joined the game let's sleep
oh [\h__\h]
anna was so shocked that she had to
check it out
you know
you i don't know if she's listening but
they're running some are running around
here
maybe you can re recapture them
how do i chat again i forgot oops
how do i chat
[Music]
that's really sad
oh why was the gate open or
was the gate open
oh we're glass block
oh
wow but many of them are running around
so
wait is she looking for wheat
do you need wheat
holy cow funny
are you can't read the chat yeah why
why am i like overlapping that much
okay
you want to see the chat log how can i
okay there you go this is the chat lock
freit here read now okay
my diamonds what's with my diamonds i i
should probably put them away yeah
ah she got lots did she
did she
bottom right yes i mean
many people said i i don't belo after
yesterday i don't belong into bottom
left anymore
people have finally acknowledged my
intelligence
very nice i need another chest maybe i
need more chests
bottom right yay
my mom was a bit worried that um i
i take uh that as an insult or like too
seriously but no no no no no
i'm fine don't worry it's a joke it's a
nothing nothing too serious
yes
okay oh oops
let's see what's in what is doing
gold so much gold wow wait i should let
me
let me get the gold
i need more
top right emote
oh yeah whenever i say or do something
that's top right you could spam that
yeah why not
okay oh wait i still have the
card
okay okay
good uh
um
she could tell me how to do the humper
thing
don't you have something to do
could be misunderstood could be
misunderstood
well if ina teaches me the hopper thing
then ahmet could
teach me the grilling thing if she knows
how to do it
but i don't
which one is more effort guys the hopper
thing or the grilling thing
is she listening
the hopper thing is more effort here
i think she's listening
to
[Laughter]
but if the hopper thing is so much
effort maybe we shouldn't do it now
because um
i want to read super chats and so on
uh but wait inauthon why
why are why were the two cards how does
that work
do i need to put the second card back
there were like two
next to each other you know
out
ah in case if i go with one
i don't get it there's no need to
you can leave the cards anywhere in the
storage near the track ah
well gotta put it back then i'll i'll
bring it back to where it was um
wow these beautiful stairs these
beautiful stairs but ina
your stairs were also beautiful
beautiful very beautiful
wait i wanted to get more pickaxes
actually
oh yeah that's what i wanted ah and i
needed i i'm feel of iron for the
pickaxe
do you wanna give me a little bit of
iron
maybe please please
thank you thank you
wow expensive you didn't say anything
about me having
to pay for that
okay uh pickaxes pickaxes pickaxes
right there
sticks we need sticks
stick
just kidding just kidding oh
it has a carrot
[Music]
haha sticks wait i hope i
do i have sticks oops no no
no no no no no no no no no no
oh many sticks no needs to make sticks
have sticks very many sticks
one
okay is that enough
yes i should put sticks back
put sticks put all this [\h__\h]
here
iron pumpkin
[Music]
all right what is inaudible honey
yes chicken run oh yeah yeah that one is
free
hey they they escape you only one escape
no
don't tell me thank you that's fine i
still have lots of chicken it's not
not a big problem that one is like can i
you know do you have a name tag can i
like have it like as my baby
i wanna i want it to be my baby actually
i wanted to be in my house
i want one chicken in my house okay i
have decided
i want one chicken in my house
oh you're cuddling it's my chicken
though
wait it's not moving why is it why are
you bonding with my chicken
hello um
[Music]
why doesn't it follow me anymore come on
okay oh cute
[Music]
coming are you too cute
you know do you want the chicken she's
looking at it like she really wants it
wait i have an idea
ina don't let the chicken go out don't
let the chicken
escape where's the chicken
did you let the chicken escape ina you
had one job
you had one job inaudible
yes you're not done
you know there's no why is there another
chicken escaping
there
you know if you want you can have that
chicken
oh you're cute hey where are you going
perfect okay
this is my pet this is my pet and stares
at the wall helping to escape but no
you cannot escape
bye-bye chicken
now you shall go back to the farm
you are not the chosen one
you're not the chosen one dear chicken
you're the chosen one to to become a
phoenix burger
that you can do oh my god help help me
come here oh [\h__\h]
can you push the chicken inside
no where you go stupid chicken
chicken i have better things to do than
this do you think i have time for this
come on why does it keep on looking at
enoch
she doesn't even have any any any food
in her hand
that's really looks like popcorn
oh my god oh my god look at them
take it i don't care about that chicken
anymore
no no no no no too many
oh my god
oh my god i killed it almost
i just maybe this is maybe into the air
is the best way
yeah yeah that's the best way
now i finally found the way
i thought oops oh well whatever
oh perfect perfect perfect yes
okay i wanted to dig
so many chias what are you talking about
i mean i'm not a chicken
i don't know i'm going chicken
uh the carpet thing that i can like if i
put a carpet there i can jump over it
it's not what
is that what you mean or is the carpet
from the thing where monsters will not
spawn
but that seemed fine
seemed fine to me let's go
we need torches i have torches
who do you think i am would you think i
could go unprepared into a mine
no no no no
but yeah maybe i'll change the defense
gate into a carpet it just looks stupid
it looks stupid
you know i want it to be a aesthetic
that's why i don't want to do the easy
hopper thing
where it's like really small i want it
to be aesthetic so that the
chicken can have a good life you know
and like live in a nice cozy home
yes a space in between each letter
that's how i want it to be
that aesthetic
oh i have so many eggs with me why did i
bring all those eggs
we can make like a scrambled egg party
i'm back my friends back to dick where
are we
at 13. wonderful okay let's go one more
down
and because i've been having luck with
golden diamonds apparently
let's see if that luck continues
now let's go one row
or should i go two rows i mean it kind
of gives a higher chance to find
something now
actually no what what if we do the the
thing where we go like like this
ah no actually like this yes
smart smart canada
enough
ah here we have iren hello
i need to drink by the way everyone
hydrate one second i'll get the iron and
then i will hydrate
hydrate myself
yes
santa hydration check
wait now i don't even need iron anymore
what am i digging for
existential crisis what am i digging for
i guess we can look for diamonds
more diamonds i'm in a diamond rush
now the reason why i wanted iron is to
make many hoppers and like shares and
all that kind of stuff and like
everything you know everything how far
do we go with this
until we make the next row
and i just wanted um
more more sheep
but like that takes a while
[Music]
too much time
okay
[Laughter]
[Music]
i come from here right
thank you
uh here we speak german so
can i have a gesundheit we speak
german in this stream
[Music]
oh thank you for the sneezy super chats
iron in japanese is a tattoo
by the way guys
did you see uh
did a stream where recently when she
mentioned
that she would like to do a stream where
someone teaches her
uh keep on mixing it up when someone
teaches her english
and someone sent the kitty
clip to me damn it i keep on going to
spots where some
something already was dug
[Music]
no out here um it will all end up like
ah
close it up
okay anyway uh right after i saw that
clip
messaged a message pickle and wait i
shouldn't er
i messaged pickles i told her if she
wants to do it
i'm ready i'll help her with the
planning and so on oh we're back here
we're back here that's
oh that's the other place where i
started digging i'm so confused now
anyway she was like okay thank you
yeah i'll tell you when i want to do it
so i don't know maybe in five years
i probably i probably have to really
like invite her
by myself on some kind of collaboration
where should i go dokonika
maybe i should really maybe i should not
use this mine shaft
maybe i should find my own mine shaft
where no one went before
but she seemed to appreciate it and also
she saw that the
she saw it when i she said she watched
my
manga stream and she uh saw that
moment when i when i swiped the card
when i swiped the card and i was like
pick a lesson but this is how you do it
i'll just i'll just stick here
maybe i should go one down for diamonds
[Music]
foreign
i wonder if she watched my perspective
though because she said
she wrote to me that she watched the
amanga stream so i wonder if she watched
my perspective
even though mine was mostly english
maybe she only watched a clip though
who knows who knows it's a mystery
after after the stream i was looking for
the
hashtag the among us hashtag
and i saw that um
i saw a clip of lammy's perspective
that she was having lots of issues with
that
uh card reader thing too nakalami
why is everyone having so many issues
with that she was trying and trying and
trying and then she gave up and went to
a different task
why is everyone having such issues with
the card reader
they like probably the japanese girls
they don't realize that it says
too fast or too slow
you know how
we weren't uh allowed or supposed to
look at the chat
so she probably couldn't even get the
advice
uh how it was supposed to be done
well i like how everyone has the same
issue
at the same task
oh where are we now
doko
this seems familiar this looks familiar
i don't want it here
i don't want it to connect
and that means if i if i do it like here
it will connect again
because it's like like parallel if i do
it here it will connect again maybe
we'll go that direction
[Music]
i want to do the super chat reading soon
maybe one more half hour i have to take
a break before the collab anyway
otherwise i'll be streaming minecraft
literally the whole day
but i wonder how long it will take for
me and ahmed to get the oops
to get the hopper thing done how long do
you think it will take us
i think ame has like she said she
studied
and wrote down a lot of things when she
was in the
in the japanese oh yeah i should
now that ahmed and guda were in the
japanese minecraft server
i should ask bakura senpai for a tour
not gonna have guru chant
[Music]
anyway let's ask the corazon five for a
minecraft tour on the japanese server
but uh if i ask it's probably gonna be
on my channel and it will probably be
in japanese because i thought that um
after all these collabs of subaru senpai
and with save your diamonds here one
second we're fine
with somebody senpai with nana zenbai
and among us
too um i've come to a conclusion
and i already wrote about this on
twitter
[Music]
so if it's a collab like with subaru
senpai where both
personalities are like really energetic
everyone talks a lot and we play a game
where you talk a lot
and then there's not really
any time to translate for me
so if it's a stream like with super the
senpai i will not
translate and maybe like only a little
bit in between
well like at the introduction and so on
but other other than that i know it's uh
funny because the super chat back then
that made me cry
said it but that actually does ruin the
flow i agree with that
uh so yeah but if it's a
if it's a stream with like uh like the
one with nana
where we were mostly singing and the
talking isn't that much so i have enough
time to translate it and it's
it doesn't really ruin the flow and when
a nanotub
is energetic but maybe a bit less
energetic than super senpai
so it worked fine in that case
and um so if it's a stream like that
where it's not hundred percent talking
then i will translate
as much as possible so that uh the fans
that come from nanette john's side who
don't speak english can understand but
also
the fans from my side who don't speak
japanese can also understand
you know and we found something that was
not explored yet
but i don't really want to go there oh
so if it's a collab with piccolo senpai
ooh
i feel like oh diamond i can't
how do i do this oh [\h__\h] i feel like
probably translating is not really much
of an option
m
how do we get that diamond without dying
how do we get it
get water inaudible you listening can
you bring me water
wait okay uh i'll find this place again
you can always put translations in the
archive um she hears me
do you think ah please please
do you think i have time to
to sit down and translate and
subtitle a whole stream
no subtitling takes much more time than
live translating
where did that come from
oh wait market
diamond diamond diamond diamond diamond
diamond
um i don't think that subtitling a
stream would ever be a thing
maybe subtitling a video yeah i could do
that maybe but
i'm actually um busy
you might not think but i'm actually
busy
i have things to do wait is she coming
really to bring me
water is she like
where oh what
what's this mine called wait uh
hmm next to the small mine which what
was this one called
ah watson shaft thanks chad
you guys are so informed
damn you guys know
the names of each goddamn shaft
how do i get back out there
are you guys taking notes when you watch
our streams
i'm getting so many diamonds holy [\h__\h]
holy [\h__\h]
damn safety eggs safety eggs
what did i do it's floating how is that
how did that work
you can do that
anyway so hey um but
okay i'm thinking about something i have
hinted at it before
and i want to do this soon like really
soon um
and i didn't tell anyone like exactly
what i'm doing until now because i don't
want anyone to steal my idea
but people already when i hinted at it
on on twitter people already kind of
guessed what i'm going to do
[Music]
i want to do something every two weeks
or so
is uh and it will involve my translating
skills
so what i thought about this already a
few weeks ago but i just i wasn't sure
when to start
so what i'm doing
i am going to
uh
[Music]
hello you want to listen to my idea you
probably know about my idea i don't know
do you know about my aunt yeah
you go yeah i'm going to
i'm going to interview
every single whole life member and life
translate
their answers to the english viewers so
that every english
whole life fan can get deep knowledge
about our whole life japan members that
you would normally
never know i will ask them the deepest
of the deep questions
i will ask them about all their
experiences
and and and and everything memories and
plans and
everything and this will not be only
enjoyable
for japan viewers because i will be live
translating so everyone will have fun
and that will actually give people some
good knowledge
i don't want this to be like a like a i
mean we will have fun too but i want to
ask them like good questions i don't
want to ask them
what's what's what do you like to eat
what's your favorite food i don't want
to ask them those shitty questions i
want to ask them
some deep things i want to go deep you
know
and we will do this like two weeks
eating one member in two weeks and once
i
went through all the whole life japan
members we can also go for hollow stars
and hollow id
and we can talk with all of them but
once i'm done with all of them probably
another 500 members joined so i will
never run
out of content
so i will be the interviewer that will
give you all the knowledge about your
favorite idols
she's listening
so i actually i wanted to commission
someone to like do like a
like a fancy room like draw me like a
room
or like do a 3d room or something
you surprised me
and yeah i wanna i want like a like a
room that kind of looks like a like a
talk show room like i want like two
fancy chairs
and so it looks like we are sitting on
like
comfy chairs you broke the rail you know
oh wait i have the rail
there you go she's looking just staring
at it
it's okay it's okay i'll fix it i fix it
no no i fixed it right it's fun right
well thank you
thanks angel
no sorry i don't know how to use this
thing
i shouldn't hold it
i still have water i still have it thank
you
[Music]
where did where did i go okay so that's
my plan
and yeah going oh we could do that too
oh yeah
yeah i think he would probably not say
no but we first have to interview some
members so he understands what that what
the hell i'm trying to do
interviewed
but i was thinking um first i should
uh go for the older members you know
they have more stories to tell
i should go for the older members first
and
since i already have a good connection
with marin senpai
i was thinking my first guest could be
madin senpai
she's the she's the oldest one that i
have a good connection with like old as
in generations
wait wait where am i going this is not
where i am this is
but it will not be like pure comedy guys
i actually want to ask some good
questions
and get some some good answers you know
so i will prepare the questions and i
thought to
to kind of like
[Music]
let's lessen the the amount of
translation that needs to be done i will
prepare
the questions in english and and put
like a graphic up
but i will ask the question in japanese
so at least the
the the question i don't have to
translate but the answer i will live
translate so you know i'm gonna
understand what i'm trying to do okay
now how do we do this though
like i will put up a graphic of the
question
please look forward to a genius
genius uh live stream series that only i
can do oh by the way i was thinking
maybe this should be
uh a video series but i don't know maybe
live streams what do you guys think like
video i could subtitle if it was a video
i could subtitle it
i could cut it and all that
but against like probably it's more
fun as a stream because because
then i was thinking uh i could also take
some live
questions from the chat like you
you english viewers could throw in some
questions i i randomly pick some
questions from the chat
and yeah anyway do i just throw water
but what if what if i then start digging
and there's lava right
underneath the diamond
what happens then life is better okay
but what if there's water under the
diamond and lava under the diamond
water on the wall here like or here
here
okay
do i pick it up again
do i try to pick it up again
does it does it just flow yeah i pick it
up okay
ah oh wait wait
i can't pick it up it's gone
i just placed a bunch of torches [\h__\h] oh
wow it's
uh it's fun
by water well um
now i'm scared that there's lava right
underneath that will like
take away let's see no okay
[Music]
ah
bottom left shut up
this this one should be fun
okay okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay okay okay
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
india
okay where did i come from where did we
go where did i come from cotton i joe
for real where did it come from
okay
i'm not lost i would never get lost why
oh wait save my diamonds save the
diamonds
wait i got so many diamonds
[Music]
foreign
you for the super chat thank you where
is the
where am i
i got the diamonds i think we're done
for today i'll
read super chats i go home and then i
read super chats
[Music]
i'll go home to my house
i'll store everything and then
i will read super chats because i have a
another minecraft collab later
on
all day minecraft never get sick of
minecraft
aki9
yeah fire emblem
[Music]
oh
i get
go
i'm like i actually have tears in my
eyes right now
lol you died again shut up
there's nothing funny about it my
diamonds
but i think i also have diamonds in the
i think also diamonds
[\h__\h] creeper you piece of [\h__\h]
wait i am underwater
[\h__\h] creepy die
bastard i wonder if something fell down
there
wow there's like scattered everywhere
stupid [\h__\h] creeper
on my cake my exp are down there but
that's it
it is fixed was it like this
where the door is gone
wasn't there a door here oh wait i have
the doors
[Laughter]
what the hell was that timing though i
just wanted to go home
put my diamonds in the chest
no
and i died here before my goal
where is the car
well that was a nice timing but to
answer the question
about uh about the fire on black stream
there will be one next week so i think
i'm gonna do it like every week once
go
diamonds are safe
a glass is gone it
i don't have a glass
can i just um wait stop can i like
uh cover it up with a stone for now
i have to cover it up right you missed
two diamonds if
you mean like they were there
foreign
is it like down there i'm i don't want
to fall down there
think i got them all i i i at least got
enough
oh should i put torches
there's like really not enough torches
here
not enough torches
oh my god this is i'm not this is abunai
thank you for joining the membership
welcome to kiara uh
fan club also known as kf
c
that doesn't mean anything doesn't mean
anything
i'm sorry but you have to wait is there
maybe glass here
no okay i eat bye okay
bye ina thank you for helping
where are more armor wouldn't have saved
me from that explosion
kentucky
hungry i wonder if she did something
about the cows while i was
mining thanks for joining their
membership
yeah no my first language is bird
my other first language is german
yeah there has been a mystery about this
so let me make it clear my second
language is english
my third language is japanese and oops
my in english i learned in bird school
in japanese i thought myself
god
that's how it is i think hopefully with
this
the mystery is solved
no no no no no no i don't have no no
no no no no no no no no
no not now
[Music]
we got a lot of diamonds i just came for
iron but i got a lot of diamonds
amazing
wow wow wow
holy [\h__\h] no i'm not gonna throw this
gold into the gacha machine i'm saving
this gold
okay let's do some more field work
what inspired you to learn japanese
hmm what inspired me
maybe the uh
maybe the goal of living in japan
i guess
just made sense to me that if i want to
live in japan
i should study japanese
makes sense right
and now i live in japan but i'm leaving
again
soon
the time is like passing so quickly
so yeah
it's sad though because if i leave japan
it means i'm leaving cali
the only member that i can like actually
meet
sparkly
[Music]
that's kind of sad are these potatoes
done
you're done oh you got two
don't just pick up
how about redstone dust why should i not
use pig
why it seems to work fun
thank you for the super chat okay
now replant and then actually
yeah replant and then we're getting to
an
end
[Music]
is this one done
why would kiara need never plans to stay
forever
kiara only wants it to stay for a little
while
[Music]
it's always sad to leave
and actually um
i i had so many like plans
and goals for this year but it was all
ruined
and i was really really sad
about that i hear weirdly
i was really sad about that but
now now it's like
i have something else wait that's the
wrong thing
i have something else that i'm enjoying
to do
but yeah it's still sad you know
oops don't eat them
there were so many things i wanted to
accomplish
so i was really sad about this but then
holy life
came into my life and made everything
actually so much better
actually everything is so much better
now
[Music]
foreign
are you happy my chickens are so happy
don't stay stay inside
no okay follow me
this side take my love take it all
love me back i love you oh oh these are
you guys
this is these are my fan club members
you have to like social distance
you have to take some space ew i will
never do a fan meeting again if you get
this close to me
yo i'm getting like anxiety attacks
you're too close
where's my bodyguard where's my body
going
are you done with like eating my seeds
ew that's like weird
that's weird very weird
no no no no wait
come here this is difficult
okay what is with that chicken though
people's face why don't you have enough
space
you mean you want more space this is
enough space
this is enough space i mean if i make it
bigger it will be a bit
annoying because i'll have to like
like keep you guys from escaping which
is such a hard thing to do
okay now let's feed the babies
this is this is a small space i must say
there's too many cows
let's kill the cows i need i need food
anyway
okay thank you oh god they're panicking
it's all fine oh god i killed the baby
almost
oh how do i not hurt the sheep
uh
uh here's an axe
why is it like
safer
oh
[Music]
oh is it one hit kill with an axe
chill chill chill oh
hey i feel so sorry for doing this
but the what about the small ones
i will i will keep them alive until
they're uh
big and strong okay
i don't want to kill them now anyone who
hasn't eaten
oh wait i'm holding the wrong thing
hi
okay bye bye thank you
for joining the kfb farm you're going to
make me help help me make a big
is that a tooth
gonna help me make a big kfp restaurant
sometime soon sometime
soon we're gonna make it together with
you guys you will the good thing is
the good thing is let me tell you i will
never eat you
okay i will never eat you
because i just want your wool your wool
is precious to me
no no i will not eat the sheep believe
me why do you not believe me chad
i will not eat them so let's take a look
what inna did you not fix her farm
no i only i don't see many
actually where is uh does she have a
gate
because i could help her recapture that
thingy
um but oops i don't see it
i'm actually okay
is there any gate feed them
okay
oh they love me they love me here take
my wheats
from my wheat farm yay
make babies oh yeah that that's actually
a good idea i can re
repopulate in a spam
okay okay small one
[Music]
because she helped me too good idea
okay what about you guys do you also eat
wheat no
she's coming pretty close though seems
like you want to eat it
what do they eat what do the llamas eat
don't spit on me
okay i think we found
a good place to end it we have made
progress what is happening over there by
the way
what's happening here
what is that
i'm miss tower
what does she wanna like tell me that my
tower is [\h__\h]
is she trying to prove me something
what's wrong with my tower amy
is it is it too slender
you wanted a thick tower is that what
you wanted ina
ami why was my tower not good enough
wait is that what material is that is
that white wool
what is that can you not uh
oh i thought it would make a hole there
it disappears
no not that
sorry i wasn't aware of what it was i'm
[Music]
sorry
is there a reason why she
is there a reason why she built it
what is she trying to do with that no no
by the way i saw an image i think on
reddit
that compared like like our our
minecraft server with the japanese
minecraft server
and like ours was like a an image of
like
the stone age with like humans like
doing something with with like barely
any clothes on and like
like uh using stones to build something
i don't know
and then next to it was the japanese
minecraft server
being like so amazingly futuristic
well yeah of course i mean we're gonna
be futuristic too one day especially
with
amelia watson uh
she will lead us to a futuristic future
she's like improving the service so much
so i believe in amelia watson
she will help us graduate from being
cavemen
what's in industries industries
industries
let's read the super chats um there's a
lot i think but
there's a lot to catch up and
there's a lot to catch up thank you for
watching thank you everyone who's
leaving now who doesn't want to stay
with the super chat but if you want to
stay there i'm sure we'll have some fun
together
and and i hope you will come and join
the
minecraft stream later that i will be
doing with ame in approximately oopsie
goddammit that's no why did i no
no no no in approximately uh
3 hours and 15 minutes
[Laughter]
i clicked something wrong
so
minecraft okay but
i have
let me see how much it is i uh
uh i need to check
and get my manager to check it
let me prepare please
but by the way are talking about
collaborations before about uh
collaborating with japanese members i
think next week there will be no nothing
uh i did two two collabs with japanese
members this week
i did one last week and i think
the coming week i will not do any uh
holo ian holo japan collaborations
it was too much so i'll prepare
something for the week after
and
but there might be
i'm thinking of challenging emilia
again in chess next week
[Music]
what's wrong guys what what's wrong
don't act as if you don't want to see it
i know you want to see it
wait i did read uh in the fire i'm live
stream i did do a super chat reading
right so
it starts from the stream with nene chan
no hai shinkada on the icona
right please no chess oh shut up you'd
love to see my chess match with
ame speech
yes but no paying to nazi chess i know
you want to see it
i know you want to
wait
[Music]
okay
i think i did i just didn't read the
ones from the collabs right
does anyone know
just okay okay thank you
let's see how much we have to reach
today
[Music]
let me prepare the sheet for
the super chat
okay it is
671 super chats plus the one that will
come
while i am reading and the ones that are
just coming now that i did not copy
so maybe like i don't know 700
700 super chats
yep no problem
no problem
okay send it to the check
today's minecraft stream combined with
all the
collabs with the
nanotown collab got a lot of orange
super chats
thank you everyone for being so
supportive
all the time really really really your
support is amazing
and i'm pouring in some lemon tea
to hydrate defend the bottom left why do
you make what i mean what do you mean
i'll finish before i'm a collab for sure
but i have to kind of
kind of eat something before the collab
i think
i hope that i need to kind of uh
study how we're gonna do it before
we get into it because otherwise it
would just be too chaotic or like too
too unplanned we have to kind of
um i mean i did get sent
how how i'd have to do it so i just have
to look at it just have to take my time
and look at it
i'm i think i'm is awake right now
she i think she already slept oh wait
maybe she's not she just wrote
ah she just stopped her stream right she
wrote to me on discord
because i sent her the thumbnail but
maybe now she's going to sleep
oh and she wrote to me over an hour and
a half
hour and a half ago so she's probably
streaming now
sleeping sleeping sleeping i mean she's
probably sleeping now
yeah but she will not
get much sleep huh
because we're streaming and it's just
amen you awake wanna sleep more
you can move the stream
to two hours later or so if you want
she's probably i don't know if she can
if she's gonna read it but
because i'm a bit worried about her
sleep schedule i cannot
i need to sleep like at least eight
hours to function properly
she's probably sleeping
i've heard of this sleep
i want to go to sleep yeah go ahead and
go to sleep
i don't know what time it is for you
guys what time is it for you guys
4 00 am 4 pm 3 am
3 am 2 a.m
[Music]
four am yeah are you guys yeah you
should everyone who is like
at 4am you should go to sleep so you can
catch the next stream
i hope you're planning on catching the
next stream
are you planning on missing it
you better not be missing it
she had a rough stream it what happened
is she okay what do you mean like
technical problems or
okay wow eh
my manager just checked 700 super chats
in like what two minutes
i use speed
are you speed
kayaking
manager sent me a picture of a car
racing the the red car from cars
where subtitled i am speed okay manager
is speed indeed
it has been confirmed planet manager is
speed
[Music]
and you guys know what to do don't slack
off
on spamming the duncashers keep on
spamming the duncan
here we go starting from i think
collaboration
how about a switch of music
[Music]
are you already spamming i didn't even
say thank you yet thank you
okay i'll be making hoppers and stuff
with amelia
but my papa will join me in a stream for
creating the kfp restaurant
okay
vegan murphy 11 thank you
[Music]
oh wait wait this is
it
ah oh oh wait i'm at the in ina collab
right now
looking for the top right i'll super
chat each time you fall in rainbow road
potential
okay and now here we go looking for the
top thank you shannon looking for the
top thank you shan looking for the top
thank you shin looking for the top
dankeshin looking for the top tank
hashem looking for the top thank you
shin looking for the top dunkishin
looking for the top down kitchen and
looking for the top duncan while next to
zankashin looking for the top dunkishin
looking for the top dancing
[Music]
okay
ah we are i think now uh we're already
at the at the kiara and
nene collaboration uh super chats
up sixty-seven tnt triple
foreign
uh
today we shall look to the endless sky
above the clouds and into space to watch
two stars
whose souls eliminates the night in our
hearts
let us watch kiara and nina as they sing
and dance amongst the
cosmos of fantasia wow
wow wow i guess today
we were not marching mr pekkorini
thank you
[Music]
on behalf of those who want to do super
chat but can't please enjoy this orange
carpet of super chats for two of the
hardest working business owners in our
life
thank you i hope neither of you mind
that we're using
our who that's more than four million i
don't know what comes after four million
four trillion four billion yen then
april
wages to pay our for our kfp employment
and working overtime
bank is in
it was good fortune that brought the
pair of you together some quirk of
fate that lines your songs up perfectly
yeah
if you believe in it maybe it was
destiny yeah
the duet you showed us before was
already wonderful thank you
thank you the elemental 98
krishna
[Music]
regardless you both resonated strongly
with one another and whether it was
meant to be or pure luck
we're all excited to see the show and
support two outstanding survivors so
swingy
[Music]
daniel h thank you and so in the name of
all kfp and other pro employees thank
you both for your hard work your
continued excellence and general
awesomeness
why is everyone so sweet
thank you
[Music]
the super ceo of one of hololab's mega
corps and the owner of
the popular kfp chicken franchise taking
the time out of the busy schedules to
sing to us
how are we all so blessed to the both of
you thank you
true we're both busy
excuse me
well i'm sneezing a lot today
i feel very blessed
okay i sneezed again okay i sneezed
again
there's no you have no choice you gotta
send me more more bless you super chat
sorry sorry for sneezing so much
[Music]
i can't help myself
thank you thank you
[Music]
i hacked the system
it works it works
see my head hurts from sneezing too much
[Laughter]
right this means also i need to read
more super chat
okay you can stop now i don't want to
read more than 700 super chats
thank you i feel very blessed
feel very blessed thank you
[Music]
even my papa sent me a blessing for chad
oh my god
you guys are too easy you guys are too
easy to hack
the system is is rigged
and
[Music]
okay
might need to see a doctor thank you
ah okay thanks guys
you can stop you can stop you can stop
you can stop it was just a joke it was
just a joke
i did actually um to be honest i that
those were fake sneezes
i don't know if you've noticed but those
were all fake
but no i will not refund the money
[Music]
[Laughter]
is
well those don't work on me because they
were fake
number one sneezing phoenix
thanks guys general piccolin stop
sending super chat stop it
stop it
[Music]
oh i'm glad you're i'm glad that our
streams are helping you
please cheer up mike maslowski your
local hall of fame
and kashin sanji shondan kashin memory
of twilight thank you
mind blaze thank you katie mcdonald
super chat number eight hundred oh no oh
[Music]
no
stop stop stop
ah
yo i need to take a break before the
ammo stream
don't you want your your ceo to take a
break you're
your boss don't you want me to take a
break
no wow that wow i thought you i thought
you guys care about my health
eh don't you want me to
take a break
i thought you cared more about my health
i i actually i do have another stream in
three hours so
please i'll just ignore it then it will
eventually end
magically make
[Music]
go
i uh i disabled the super chat
machine
i actually yeah i have to like tap it
i have to end it somewhere
i have to end it somewhere you know
kaiten
and you guys you guys just keep them
coming if not even though i tell you to
stop you just keep them coming so
read faster excuse me
time to become a member oh yeah you can
spam with me with memberships because
i'm not reading them
maximum ramirez mkk 2004
i recall when you debited that you were
worried that you didn't have a special
skill
but your fluency in multiple languages
is a very special skill
we can see that in full display now and
we fans are proud of you or friends
thank you oh
yeah i'm glad
thank you well there's
there's still times when i when i doubt
myself but
generally um i'm glad that uh people
are appreciating what i do
lazy march thank you david thank you
frosty thank you
lucio cipher dan kashan guidance
[Music]
it's nice seeing you so happy during
these streams you are so very talented
and it shows your hard work is paying
off
we will continue to support you forever
love you
thank you
for having me
[Music]
my papa even stays for the super chat
readings
[Music]
i have the best papa ever
oh my god
actually before my debut
i was hoping that i would get a papa
that
interacts a lot with me because i see
often
uh
[Music]
if
commenting on her stream so i was hoping
that
i would get someone that also comments a
lot on my stream and like
like talks to me let's see
[Music]
let's
i'm sorry because my english is too poor
to say something you both are great
don't worry about it thank you
thank you looking for the top
thank you for the red super chat then it
pays me
40 billion yen daily
what the hell is that
[Music]
i guess yeah that makes sense if you if
you're a member of neneporo if you work
for neneporo and get that much money you
can easily join me and pay me money
wow another nanoparous salary is like
damn
where does she get though isn't that
unrealistic she's probably like really
in the in the minus and going bankrupt
soon and then you will all lose your job
tonight
oh funny
money laundering
it's a scam maybe it's not real money
thank you for the rest of the chat thank
you thank you
really thank you for so much support
always
looking for the top it's weird to try to
address you with a name but your name is
not real your name is kind of weird
maybe i call you lftt lftt
sounds like left bottom left
what
[Music]
is an old capitalist she still pays her
employees
new capitalism started potential is the
way
there will be no more unemployment
because every cao will want as many
employees as possible
yes whatever that means yes
and number one
thank you
[Music]
um
thank you for the red
[Music]
had to send one more i was able to catch
the last half of the stream and need to
make sure i sent an orange super chat
for orange orange orange since
my last one was the wrong color thank
you
for watching
thank you for all the orange super chat
it was really
fun to see that during the stream all
the orange super chats
super vincent
i'm not getting a break so you're not
getting a break
foreign
amazing collaboration to both you kiada
antenna this was a really enjoyable
concert for me
it you certainly gave us a good show
with your beautiful singing looking
forward to another collab thank you so
much
let me let me drink
and let me take a
noodle cough drop
cough drop time cough drop time
clock drop time
i
it's not coming out
okay
moving into later
i mean i guess i could once i'm done
with the
i'm a collaboration once we say bye bye
i could read super chat alone i guess
[Music]
is that what i should do and now you
care about
why if you care so much about me taking
a break why did you send so many super
chats for the sneezing
and did not stop when i told you to stop
which one is it you guys are as tender
as kelly
don't question it
yeah okay i think yeah
i'll stop it here and then i'll i
probably eat something
and uh try to look up
how the hopper thing goes and wait
somebody said in the chat when i asked
it's probably gonna take me an hour
to make the hopper thing with ame
you guys think so an hour
when your next collab 2 hours and 30
minutes from now
2 hours 30 minutes it i already have the
reservation up so if you check out my
channel you should see the reservation
slot
two to three hours that much
30 minutes and that's why we uh everyone
has a different opinion apparently
one plus hours okay setting it up might
get tricky
i hope my chickens don't escape while
i'm doing it
15 minutes to five hours what
is it
10 minutes to 10 days what the hell are
you talking about
what i ah
one person should attract the chickens
while the other pla well
since it's called kfp employee training
ames should be placing the hoppers and
the tracks and i should be
attracting the chicken
amy should do the work all right
well she also knows more than me
well i'm the chicken mom mama
i'm the chicken mother i should be
taking care of the chicken
and ame is uh from ame industries
or what amelia industry watson
industries
so i think it's pretty obvious
who should be doing what
no i don't mean that i i don't mean that
i am the
ah i don't mean that i'm the chicken i'm
i just raised them but i'm not a chicken
no no no no no nine nine nine nine nine
nine
nine nine nine nine
i i just raised them they see me as
their mother
but i'm not a chicken i'm a phoenix
all right then uh i'll continue super
chat reading starting from the among
us super chats
including the minecraft ones
and later if some come in the amelia
er collaboration as well i'll be reading
this
thank you everyone for watching today
and
i really really love you all so much
i'm so happy to have you all here
thank you for always being by my side
thank you for believing in me thank you
for supporting me
thank you
i'll keep on bringing you the bestest of
content
and soon i'll bring you a regular live
stream series
as i told you where i interview every
whole life japan member
yes
[Music]
in german we say
in
[Music]
i'll be done
hey
see you in two and a half hours ninja
gan hang go
now don't be late
be there or be swept
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no not
[Applause]
foreign
oh by the way guys guys guys guys
are you still here
[Music]
oh yeah she wrote to me
she wrote to me i dreamt that you
rescheduled by two hours this is weird
oh my god you should be sleeping
if
[Applause]
anyway can you guys send me
can you guys send me uh send me
recommendations for
horror games that are quick that i could
do in one stream
halloween can you
send me on twitter possibly something
that i can do on pc or switch
and maybe something that i could do in
an hour or something
okay i may think she's fine
[Music]
bye
foreign
[Music]