[Music]
oh
Kik Kitty
key ah
hello oh my God I'm Big K I'm starting
earlier than the collab because I never
played this game
before uh ever and I'm generally very
bad with FPS games as you may know
embarrassingly
bad so I wanted to learn the game first
I have I wanted to I have that's me I
wanted to uh play the game alone first
so to say alone just to figure
everything out maybe after I play I'm
guessing there's like a general tutorial
right uh actually let me let me hide the
game screen first I don't know once that
uh I don't really care about my name but
once that uh popup is gone will it
show other girls' Steam namesh capsu
hied yeah there a tutorial right so I
assume so so I'm going to play that
first and then maybe we'll get together
with herb
yeah takak
Chan who is oh chunky wonky is sniffing
smoothy's face who is sleeping not
really sleeping with her eyes open she's
very very very
[Music]
awake cuz herb also never played it
before and figured oh might as well get
some practice in together yeah okay uh
I'm really a noob I'm really not good at
shooting games so please don't expect
anything but people have told me that
two of the easiest beginner classes are
pyro and
medic and I used to love playing healing
roles uh whenever
I uh what was what was I going to say
whenever I play like
MMORPGs but but wait is there a tutorial
I assume so
please I think
so herb told me she's currently trying
out training
so yeah um oh M Mia to people
already being
delusional
uh let me because I have a feeling this
is going to be annoying
I'm getting friend invites let me just
ah stop spamming me how do I turn it off
again
settings FR
[Music]
stop sometimes you know I got to turn it
on so that I can you know be invited by
other members Hol members
why is it so difficult to turn off your
friend uh requests
[Music]
H where do you do
it where do you do it
again it's difficult it's
difficult view my profile is it there
I can't why is it so hard to find Ed it
is it
here is it is it is it is
it privacy
settings
um
um I don't know can't find it
[Music]
H not going to friend
everyone you guys are going to mess with
me only whole life
members oh steam settings
notifications steam settings
notifications aha it's not under
friends okay
[Music]
uh but that's just that's just receiving
notifications I don't want to
receive friend invites in the first
place
uh yeah my I think my account
is
private it it says my profile friends
only okay let's make it priv private why
was friends only not enough
though
okay
hopefully that will stop some
people
okay shouldn't there be one setting that
says uh turn off ingame voice chat and
get picture or something to hide the
ingame chat oh where where where is the
ingame chat going to appear bottom left
bottom right
[Music]
wait what turn off ingame voice chat
ingame voice chat okay bottom left all
right then I'm going to why don't I just
overlap it with my own chat I wonder how
big it is though for now you shall be
big oh yeah okay it's good that I didn't
show that
um um
options multiplayer no voice enable
voice in this game uh I turned that off
I wonder if Am wants to play with that
but how to un enable other people's
voices Advanced options I thought so
enable voice chat no enable text check
should I turn that text chat should I
turn that off too
then we just won't see them at all
maybe yeah yeah turn it off
okay any other settings you recommend
also am I going to after each game am I
always going to come back to this first
screen because that's going to be
difficult turn off sprays decals oh okay
okay
no will will we not come back there all
the time I would hope
so
um where is
this
decals sprays where is
that miscellania
maybe what is that setting
yeah I'm in advanced settings but
there's just a long
list oh is it not an advanced
okay ah is it uh do not
[Music]
no it just says under multiplayer spray
paint image I can import my own spray
and I can say allow allow all custom
files from server no wait there's
another Advanced here huh a separate
Advance oh there's a lot of settings
here hi custom I found it okay disabled
sprays is already on
okay okay okay
[Music]
okay hopefully that's good
enough okay apply okay hopefully that
worked okay how do I uh play the game
let's
see I've received
items uh how to play game how to play
game find the game but is that tutorial
what is this sorry I'm not showing it
yet because I want to show you once I'm
where I need to go uh there's a
contractor that's probably
not ah [\h__\h] I opened the Team Fortress
twitch am I blind is the word training
right in front of me I I
see well let's click find the game ah it
says training there okay okay okay okay
learn the ins and outs of the [\h__\h] what
no uh Team Fortress
too uh basic training learn the in okay
get started okay
and there's no pyro to choose
here what should I choose first
then E I don't want can I turn off that
it shows my friends list in the starting
screen Soldier okay but one
second how do I turn off the stupid
friends list in the starting screen is
that possible I
cannot
bro bro for
real for real
how
to remove as
[Music]
friend we're not friends
anymore yeah chat but then I always have
to like resize is
it there's there's a streamer
mode there is a streamer
mode where is that true I'm looking
through advanced
settings a2d
options don't see um performance
miscellaneous options
no
okay all right uh then well if it
eventually accidentally gets shown it is
what it is but let's go training you
guys
said um
[Music]
Soldier oh stand up episod primary
secondary me okay let's go
[Music]
why the hell is that showing
underneath oh it's not
on cuz there's no
streamable so
loud h d 3D
[Music]
character my is I know okay this which
is not recommend for old machines that
can't be
talk yeah reload often use LOLs LS what
continue okay welcome to the soldier
weapons course
oh to look around the environment move
the mouse wow so good
use dou to move yeah yeah yeah leave
this room and proceed
okay so
down okay even more
quiet that's all what the
hell I mean I guess explosions are
supposed to be loud
crouching
jump oh
what firing range move here okay it's a
rocket launcher let's go cycle for
weapons using wheel down and wheel up
confirm selection using Mouse
one
aha I am on a rocket launcher okay let's
use a shot
gun uh aha press one two three h I'll
use the mouse wheel okay what am I
shooting oh they coming up here okay
taking too long cute to SW yeah whatever
y was the weapon called out for each
Target to destroy oh I have to switch
like that
okay still loud
okay uh I turned it down a bit more what
what what does that mean switch to
rocket launcher here we
go use
shotgun oh it's coming up right in front
of
me
shotgun oh
God I'm probably just going to use the
same weapon throughout the whole time
later on but good to know
reload when I have a spare moment okay
hi hi hi hi rocket explosions can damage
multiple targets try hitting two Targets
with a single rocket oopsy sorry
okay oh on the
floor
M you oh here
too critical hit
okay good good
good what what does it does it not
matter
anymore oh no I didn't
reach
what how do I know which one it wants
now is it just the second row I guess is
rocket launcher and the first row here
is
shotgun shot gun and then shovel coming
up no
okay oh
okay I get it I get
it
bam uh
shotgun yeah
kapow uh rocket launchers like a memory
game wow oh jump scared me oh I could
have given him a a head Bonk not a head
shot try out your weapons on a few
moving targets oh no opponents will move
around the target range you know what to
do it's a real person I shouldn't shoot
him also looks like he has a gasoline
tank on his back I don't know if that's
really safe if I blow him
up wow he took a lot of hits of a rocket
launcher I think I would die immediately
H
uhh ah oh aim aim that that looks like a
medic I I don't think I should be
killing
Medics that's just brutal oh God they
move so fast they're going to move even
faster
later it's okay as a pyro I can probably
blow everything up and I'll be happy
wait I maybe go
forhead ah why do you have to reload why
is that a thing it's a Game Stop
reloading ooh oh of all head shot oh why
so
far no head shots with shotguns what
spray and prey baby you got to move over
there right yeah yeah yeah I already
know your line movements
wa
okay y oh it's still not over oh I
thought I cleaned up already
[Music]
yeah thank you for the Applause uh I've
completed training
yippee good job you've completed Soldier
training and unlock basic training
return to the main menu by pressing done
and select basic training to explore
round of Team Fortress
[Music]
2 let's try yeah let's try to still keep
it uh
safe as long as they're warning
me okay then the second
training offline practice sharpen your
skills or
yeah ah is that a real herb oh oh oh
herb herb invited me to her
party I guess it's time to party uh uh
already okay uh uh wait let me think uh
uh where where to call uh CL
[Music]
no going to go into
VC oh go Gotta balance the volumes to
when I hear
her
hello a beautiful voice
voice tell your voice to look in the
mirror shut
up all right all right voice test I got
to turn you up say something something
something something something something
scream
scream okay then hopefully the game
volume I'm lowering it right now
hopefully that will yeah be lowering up
the game is very loud
okay it wasn't just me I was like damn
so loud I can't connect it to my goxlr
either it's like d oh did you also just
play the like most basic tutorial ever
yeah wonderful um I did that and then I
went into the offline practice so we can
go into that if you want to try I'm
going to put up some PNG of you I'm
going to Google it uh oh do you want me
to give you a
reactive yeah that could work
too I do
that that would be wonderful so so much
preparation
who I give you the thing
um I well this is kind of isn't this our
first kind of collab yes M well I guess
we played Minecraft but
well we role played yeah
mhm yeah I mean technically yeah yeah
yeah yeah what do you think you're going
to uh
play I want to I want to have a go at
the sniper guy
sniper yeah there she is cute the
Australian he's an Australian mhm yeah I
remember like from yonks ago these
little
animations mhm cuz the voice acting is
great in it the the guys yeah so I
remember these little like animations
they brought out with
the the meet meet the Scout Meet the
Pyro and all that jazz I never played
the game I don't think I've ever seen
that okay I'll accept your
party nice I see you have accepted the
nickname I have given you uh uh
maybe might have it it was just you know
shorter so yeah so much shorter was cuz
it's shorter it saves you a lot of time
yeah we'll do have you ever played
OverWatch cuz this yeah I think so
practice mode seems similar so it's a
payload thing so we can have a go at
that first oh we'll do it on easy wait
uh are you choosing something for us mhm
yeah okay doing the did it change for
you are you loading with me no nothing
loading I wonder if I'm supposed to go
to a mode selection
uh I can't practice together we can't
practice together what the offline
practice doesn't work with
friends what we have to find a normal
game uh we could create our own server
but then it's just us too
right oh I guess unless it lets me add
Bots oh but no uh the viewers could join
right is that a problem I uh am told me
is that a thing if like am it told me
shouldn't be like a problem because the
only problem that might be is if I join
someone
else's server enable voice in this game
I'm just going to untick that yeah I un
take that too apply multiplayer I did my
Crosshair mean won work maybe start with
Bots oh okay yeah I can I can promote
you to party leader and then you can
decide okay you guys mean
uh Bots that the game provides or Bots
that come with like people who don't
want to play
themselves you mean Bots that the game
provides
right your chat saying don't
risk it should be all right least at
least they're truthful okay wait so
maybe casual play a match of TF2 with
other players is that is that where I
would get bots m
can use
training see I thought in the training
bit but if your chat is saying it's only
for yourself then it doesn't work for us
both when you queue up for a casual mod
you will be matched into a 12 versus 12
game oh my God that's
hectic blah blah blah selecting Maps
saving you can do it in we can't train
together
what go to training what
first you're saying we can't train
together and now you're saying we are we
can what the
freak casual has players Bots will only
be for offline practice ah we could get
bots if we do offline practice but then
we wouldn't play it together oh that's
what I clicked but you said nothing
happened your end so yeah yeah no cuz we
can't play together we only can play
with Bots then oh what you know what uh
let's do like one
um training with
Bots uh playing against bots yeah and
and you know we're not playing together
but we hear try to scream so that's nice
um we can just chat uh and try to
understand the game together and once
we've done one bot practice maybe we can
go into you know like a
casual uh or no sure no mind after that
we'll make a I'll make a server thing
and people can Jo join mhm okay that
sounds good yeah okay are you should we
there's two worlds that we can choose
George and dust
bowl what did you click have you gone
into the training bit Yeah the training
with the off which one are you doing you
doing control points King of the Hill or
payload I didn't wait where was that I
didn't get that yet oh are you on basic
training or offline practice offline
practice okay so when I click get
started it gives me
control Hill that uh ah let's see I
think I understand what payload is
because I play
paladins control points ah I think I get
that too King of the Hill most control
single point uhuh uhhuh uh Let's
[Music]
do
let's do STI to Casual oh okay let's do
control points sure okay and
difficulty I'm going to just click easy
yes yes yes all right three two 1 start
practice start start okay I'll show the
game again t Team Fortress
2im
[Music]
Yi oh you're on your way to the Dust
Bowl our map ration I'm going Dust Bowl
too
wow so insane
ah would you like assistance from
another player in your current
game okay my my my brother said no when
I talked to him about this earlier he
was like
no wait no chose no okay there we go
Blue cing random Mission begins in 60
seconds know wait are you already in I'm
going to try the
Spy I got to make you
louder game loud turn down right it's
okay I make you louder I turn this down
generally okay where's where's uh pyro
where's pyro uh was this this
Minun is this this probably pyro right
pyro here uh yeah the guy with the Mosk
is pyro all right looks creepy in
seconds so disguise I can disguise
myself are these doors going to open
later how do I pick things up
or maybe I I don't really know I've just
walked I've just walked over things
mission begins in 10
seconds okay 10 seconds press G it's
automatic okay 1 open why are they
waiting back
there oh they all going that way what
the hell oh now they're going Bots be
like it's all loud over here
I'm sorry but there's no Friendly Fire
I've
heard
I I'm trying to figure out this spy
guy okay you'll figure it
out I'll you can hand I swear oh okay I
have a shotgun too all right let's not
die
anymore H A Team
but when I one it goes
to bur
alive is
confused I wish we could play in the
same
server but I I've heard this is well I'm
I I've heard this is a very old game so
there some
like little UPS it looks fine for being
old but um I me my little brother used
to play this a lot but I I never had the
the time to have a
go but he he used to play his all the
time there's so many dead
bodies there's so many dead bodies
you're winning you're doing it I don't
know if you're doing it
win how do you change if you want to
change character can you change
character h
kfp KP tell her can you change character
like a bit like in
OverWatch you
can press oh oh thank
you I figured it out I'm going to try
and
heal yeah yeah you offer your body off
your body
press comma for changing
character apparently yeah the comma yeah
yeah yeah
M are you winning over there
herb um well I'm trying to figure out
how the med character works oh the medic
so yeah I'm trying I think if I'm
healing people I'm winning so I'm
healing oh
how do I die so fast why do I have such
low
HP oh
gosh this is so silly destroy the turret
yeah why is that stupid turret have you
ever played like OverWatch or valerant
uh I think I've played OverWatch like
once in my life
H right yeah and then this game called
paladins was Amelia Watson has an
announcer pack oh wow yeah so I had I've
not played paladins it was fun and I
think palins was also free Hallelujah
free
games oh why is he
ter oh I'm being healed that's why I'm
Not Dead Yet ah good
bot good bot FOC my private healer good
robot ah you failed healing
me oh gosh uhoh
attention Mission ends in 30 seconds
left in the mission already in 30
seconds for you yeah oh you started so
much before me
I don't think I saw it too too soon
before you you still have five minutes
almost what oh friend of
friends why are you guys
running
fire oh my God I the [\h__\h] turet no
it's so rude why is
this I feel like almost every time I
died
well red team wins so I wonder when we
play this later with the girls are we
all going to be on one side team
together or will we play against each
other H oh God maybe we'll do a
mix that' be cool oh I have the medic
with me I'm so scared
I've heard I've heard some of these
lines before the big guy just went kiss
me and I was like oh wow I've heard that
before kiss
me seems like there's a lot of famous
voice lines yeah yeah spammed it in my
chat before and I was like what are you
guys talking about what I saying is this
just Spam or is this does it have a
meaning I've definitely heard some of
these lines in like MiMi videos before
me videos me me the M the me
do you feel like you can keep up with
today's
memes yeah I like a good gigle I mean I
I don't I still don't know what really
skibby toilet is but but I don't
know I'm alive oh go I still yeah I
still don't I don't really know what
skibby toilet is I know of skibby toilet
but I've never really looked into it
maybe we don't have to know yeah the
thing I'm like I don't know if I really
need
to then it also makes me think of that
skib song that was in just
Don
w w are they [\h__\h] kidding with all
these
turrets oh yeah there's a lot of turrets
here too damn I guess if like you're all
the engineer that would be
crazy I want to just burn them all out
the Phoenix
call worth it worth it set him on
fire I still have 2
minutes turrets win games which class
does turrets I need something uh I think
it's engineer that does the makes the
turrets Engineers is kind of overpowered
huh oh I die you die oh you're in
another game G yeah I got killed by
delicious cake I think this is fine the
way
we're the way we're doing it this is f
oh no my
medic we can play a while for this
because we end up playing later anyway
together I would like to play on the
same team try it yeah true oh my God
that was like I was out there one
second BR is there like a secret P where
they maybe can't find me
I need
to what are these bots made of this is
easy
mode pyro can't deal s yep BL team sees
his area
man Mission ends in 60
seconds man I'm
dead what the freak Mission begins again
oh
[Music]
friends
please
someone Miss ends in
seconds stupid Engineers I hate
engineers
did they have engineers in your game oh
yeah yeah I didn't get killed as much by
those I think it's because of the type
of character I was trying to
play mostly got killed by
soldiers now I'm trying I'm going to be
sniper again I like sniper overtime
overtime I don't want am I going to get
paid for
that oh it's so loud
oh red team
boo shut up let me let
me oh wait what oh my gosh wait oh
continuous just keep going
Oh that's oh oh I'm red now I just said
red
[Music]
sucks okay there's two best of threee
all right all right I am fully char
we got a the best of we got to push
that's an engineer oh he's we have an
engineer wonderful Mission begins in 30
seconds how far do I want to
go time has been
added where do I
[Music]
go Mission begins in G is that just
voice
lines I pressed I pressed G as the
sniper that was a very interesting
[Music]
line oh I'm on defense oh all
right oh yeah pyate doesn't
speak o
[Music]
I what have I
done you're danger what what
Fried Chicken you shall
become
kill so er did you have a wonderful day
so
far oh yeah I've just been uh just
working
recording
uh it I was trying I was trying to get
stuff done so we could uh do it little
do the practice cuz I I really want when
you mentioned it I was like oh yeah I
want to practice
too I know yeah I
know always wanted to try it
though what about you how is your uh I
slept a lot because I woke up so early
for a dishwasher
engineer come over and then it turns out
the dishwasher was fine already by its
own oh uh and then I went back to bed
and slept a little bit
yeah but I mean it's good to
rest then I slept again
later so I had chill day that's nice
yeah three days in one day I I think I
deserve a chill day oh I mean yeah yeah
you definitely do thank you with
all all dancing and recording and stuff
no I failed again I think
the Bots are too good try right click
you can like
rockets the B are too good they une easy
yeah what the hell how come they're so
good on easy how good are they going to
be on like hard mode that's true how
they going to be on normal what the
freak but you probably at least
generally a little bit better at FPS
games than me I feel like you have a bit
more experience than me right uh I mean
I enjoyed them it doesn't it doesn't
mean I'm skilled at
them oh enjoying it is all that matter
begins in yeah yeah I I yeah I usually
when I when I play OverWatch or valerant
I tell my audience I'm
like yeah you're not here for skills
just
warning there's no skills here that's
fun skill comes with Mission begins in
10 seconds yeah I I just have fun
playing them I never thought I would to
be honest like if you said to me years
ago that I would be even like enjoying
playing valerin or overwat I would be
like really a pew pew game are you
kidding me what the I'd be the same yeah
but for me I think it's stands
through I think I liked um like valer
because they had powers I think when I
tried out a different what with them are
they like in the
ball where do I get
Theo okay give me ammo I found
ammo all right get wrecked Get
Wrecked he
vacuuming getting
good sorry it's hard to have a
conversation during FPS games oh true
and you're no you're Gucci just chill
and have
fun never
mind what do you think about as a Koka
lover what do you think about your uh
gen ma having sung uh 21st of September
a million times has is she
okay oh she's fine I mean she she has
that Gremlin energy
so Gigi has that Gremlin energy so I I
knew she'd be fine um but I love I love
that's probably one of my favorite Tunes
so I thought it was cool yeah it's a
great song I love it a lot too actually
the funny thing is I was going to do a
Koka stream singing that endlessly too
um all right but then I just changed my
plans but I didn't even know that P was
going to do it herself no so now I'm
glad I didn't do it because if I would
have done it I definitely would not have
laugh as long as her that was not the
plan oh God oh God
B the Life Book of Records the Guinness
Book of
Records you can try and uh beat her next
year no how long went she on like 7
hours or like8 hours oh my
God that's too
much like it's not just my own sanity I
feel bad for the sanity of my viewers
yeah true
they're
traumatized I mean when I when I found
out like um cuz I saw that uh cuz
obviously I couldn't watch the whole
eight hours but like I saw in a clip she
was explaining that there was a YouTuber
who basically did that as a tradition
every year I was like oh that's really
cool that she took inspiration
oh the only the only issue is that when
I when I sing September now in my own
karaoke people have like
traumatized yeah why does September have
so many of these kind of songs because
there's another one that I really like
it's waking up
September September like what does it do
September well they don't like September
either
[Laughter]
one I like
September maybe when they were making
the songs they were like oh there's too
many April songs May songs there's many
April songs really
I don't know maybe that's probably a a
song for every
month yeah there quite a lot quite a few
calendar songs as
well I remember when there was a there's
song called calendar girls the
[Music]
girls what other songs are there to do
with moms I'm trying to think now now
that I'm thinking about it I can only
think of September right um there surely
December songs at least oh my
god oh I mean Christmas songs would
mention
December November Rain
oh I need healing I need
healing somebody healing
yeah I can't think of other
one yeah I guess maybe September just
also works
lyrically as well it might work
lyrically like yeah do might work
lyrically better when people are making
these songs they're like ah April
doesn't work do you remember the 21st
night of
April that doesn't sound good sound good
a lot of a lot of months end
something the B
yeah well pyro is fun so
far I will say he's he's tough every
time a pyro comes over to
me like I die
instantly yeah don't let him get so
close to you yeah don't he just runs up
towards me and I can't even snipe him
quick enough
I'm just I've just resulted to no
scoping wait explain to me no scoping
it's just when you don't you don't scope
you don't like zoom in you don't zoom in
yeah oh you don't Zoom you know the the
long gun where you can like zoom in to
snipe ah um yeah yeah yeah that's when
you Scope what that's no scope if you
don't zoom in if you don't if you don't
do it yeah
no oh oh because you know that you know
when people say like 360 no scope is
when they jump out and do like a 360 and
then they just shoot a they don't they
don't zoom
in where the heck did that come
from thanks kiaha Senpai I never thought
I'd be like explaining that to someone
else cuz I was in this position like
even forgetting many times like cuz I'm
I'm not a gamer gamer so like every time
I'd be like what does that mean again
what does that mean
again well I maybe in German I would
have understood oh
[Laughter]
damn I love that like Elizabeth uh I
would have understood that
if my I'm like a I'm not
sure wait let me I thought I had
something
there I'll I'll give it to you no I I
honest think I probably wouldn't have
[Music]
known
T war aan war no okay maybe no that
sounds see so this game is just going
from oh this is a very long version
of right longer than I thought yeah I
think I think goes from place to place
you know when it had a map up at first
and there was a different circles I goes
from place to place I guess
so oh the medic is German I
see well but I have this problem I want
to create fire and
destruction the
Temptation being a fiery
[Music]
lady start to fire today thank you so
much for singing my songs by the way a
really
happy ah makes me happy too I'm I'm so
excited I want to learn more uh cuz your
songs are amazing thank you they're such
Bops I can't wait for you to like in one
year or two years have like huge huge uh
discography of your own songs that would
be epic you can then you can you can
sing some of mine I exactly we can
exchange our songs like exchange
students s exchange students just
10 yeah have you ever dreamed of like
being an exchange student
somewhere cuz that was my dream when I
was like in high school I really wanted
to go to Japan as an exchange student
and I signed up but they turned me down
and then I went on my own without an
exchange programs I didn't have those
options when I was younger but I've
heard about it you know from American TV
shows and stuff yeah um so yeah I think
oh it' be cool to be in like see what
American school is like because of you
know school and stuff like that yeah
yeah Americano would be interesting yeah
when I got in then when I got into anime
I was like ooh that'd be neat the the
school uniforms are really cute too yeah
so
true yeah oh I hear a positive sound
[Music]
what do that
mean I'm pushing hard by the way should
I be this up
front I think CU a pyate probably yeah
right cuz my range is so
low oh my healer is
good that bot is doing a great
job what oh you're my medic
okay I'm probably going to die soon oh
what the heck is going
on oh You're My
Healer I'm so
confusing yeah was that some SP thing
what is going
on I don't understand anything it's very
chaotic yeah I love sleep talking and
yeah I honestly I honestly can't wait to
sing mom you work so hard like with all
your songs too like with the dances and
everything yeah it's it's really
difficult like I tried to create this
like K-pop image yeah yeah so that means
I got to do some intricate dances uh
come
come very difficult this
man you speak wait well what language
would you to
speak I I don't really I don't speak
fluently I need I need speak uh English
I only I only know bits and Bobs from
like friends bits and Bobs friends from
other
Realms cute that's fine it's one of
those things where I I just ask oh how
do you how do you say this or whatever
like I randomly know
like you know
yeah that's enough to make someone go
[Music]
oh but you know um people I think people
who speak more than one language
especially like Europeans maybe they
like to you know flex and boast and make
fun of people who only speak one
language but I will say that English is
it it just me knowing English brings me
so far everywhere like usually I can can
just res res resort to
English yeah uh and have a good time so
at least the one English that the one
language that you do know is super
[Laughter]
useful I love well I love singing of the
languages um so I find that a lot of
fun there's a lot of beautiful songs out
there so I try not to let you know me
not be fluent like tear me from it
a lot of great
te oh my God but I I always make sure I
like know what I'm singing
about oh yeah yeah yeah cuz that's uh
First Step yeah some people like you ask
oh what's that song about and they'll be
like oh I don't
know it's a good thing to know what
you're singing about well sometimes I
don't even know what my songs are
about and I realized later oh wait this
is kind of a horny song huh
I mean I I I feel like music and songs
are like you know paintings it could it
can mean different things to different
people true true true yeah what do you
think sleep
talking was
about that's just about sleep talking
you
yeah little bit snoring and you know
sleep sleep issues like there's you know
illnesses for when you know you can't
sleep where all kinds of
conditions it's tough It's all you know
it's a you know you like someone so much
you're sleep talking are you a sweep
soer uh I no I don't think so um it's
been very rare that like cuz I've been
on lots of missions uh like where I've
like done tours and things like that so
but the people I've been on those with
it's been rare like I one where because
we were singing the same song throughout
the whole like two weeks like I sung
part of it in my sleep but the first
thing I said to them was was I in tune I
didn't mind I didn't really care I was
talking I was like was I in tune that
would have been very
embarrassing um and then I think it was
just probably one at the time but I
think I only said like one or two words
but I have been around sleep talkers me
too yeah Nissa is a sleep talker but she
makes no
sense okay she just like speaks she she
mumbles free words and that's it pretty
much like it makes no sense I think most
s talkers probably are making no sense
though where are we supposed to well I
one uh one girl I was on a mission with
she um said she's really into like
ghosts and and stuff and she said she
was possessed by like a ghost child at
one point what before going to sleep by
the way I'm just like oh that's
nice okay and then um and then yeah she
starts singing a little bit of a nursery
rhym in her sleep and I'm there
like and in a different language too so
I'm like oh
lovely that's that's that's
scary yeah yeah and then above me uh cuz
I was in a bunk bed the the girl was
laughing in her sleep so that
was a mixture of like a little bit of
nasty rhs little bit of lter a good time
for everyone um so
I so I'd like kind of like lean out with
my foot kind of nudge the the the the
beds well actually I kind of wiggle my
bed so the bunk bed shook because maybe
like I said I don't want to wake them
wake them just want to kind of nudge
them so they kind of move themselves and
maybe stop with the
theing in the nursery rhy
uh you've got some good
[Music]
stories uh yeah
I in the moment in some moments I do
sometimes I forget but uh yeah I've been
on many
missions it's like when uh what is it
like
uh uh when um like cover asks you
questions and in the moment you're like
uh and then you remember later only in
the the
[Music]
moment what do you
like what do I
like or like when uh I don't know if
you've ever been asked this well but
like when uh you ask oh what uh what
slang words are like great ex AR in the
moment I'm like can't remember cuz I
just say them every day until someone
else tells me I'm like oh oh yes that is
abnormal what I say there
like when I said the booby prize thing
and I was like British
language yeah yeah oh yeah yeah well
British slang words are very very
similar to Great exia sorry yeah
sorry no no no it's very similar so I
don't I don't blame you right yeah yeah
I thought so mm it reminds me
of that
place oh God yeah the two Realms are so
in sync it's crazy except uh over here
there's no like I don't know no Wizards
and not many people that walking around
in the UK with like big swords
like where'd you get your big sword by
the way I was thinking of purchasing a
new big sword I was wondering tell me
your supplier you your like actually
slots into a shield I think that's
that's pretty doe gu but it's so small
people are always since the beginning
calling it a a candy corn or
boy
weapon it's not about how how big or
small it's how you use it ah but I see I
didn't even know how to probably use it
until recently apparently I didn't even
know I could slot it in
there we you know sometimes great
warriors you know learning
time you're so
[Music]
sweet at least I have a shield I guess I
can't you know use a big ass sword like
yours if I have a shield that would be
difficult never know maybe your your
weapons could evolve someday who knows
that would be awesome like recently in
those myth voice packs I don't know if
you've seen but we've we've done some
cool uh group voice packs uh and they
did some special art for
that and yeah my my attire and my
weapons everything looks super
cool where the hell am I I love your
armor thank you what do you mean the
armor
from ah you mean my life to De armor mhm
oh thank you I got
lost I got lost you're lost where where
are the
people what I hear
shots
ow oh oh healo can you guide me bot
you're just going to stay with me huh
yeah when it comes to slang and stuff I
don't remember until someone points it
out I'm like oh
yeah that is a bit uh
[Laughter]
quy time has been yeah I should have
turn somewhere else ah I found someone
burn you found me with my healer burn
baby burn too bad for you oh I found
some more people yeah I'm going to yeah
CRA some bones
now all right I I think uh I've
understood now thank you chat that when
people are blue but like like the
special blue that means that uh they
will not take the
damage not at all or just like are they
blocking part of
it yeah Special red too okay okay did
you know that
herb when they're glowing they're not
taking damage
oh you know that weird glow they been
having sometimes I noticed the glow when
be yeah it's a medic bu but I guess wait
you're learning medic right now so oh no
I switched to pyate now oh oh you're
trying all things spicy just a just a
moment ago I
switch I've been mostly liking the
sniper stop shooting that at me
stop I wasn't even trying to sound like
that but this time it was natural
Ru do you listen to any I do that I do
that too any by the way do I listen to
K-pop
yeah uh I not as much at the moment but
I have done I I I like uh my favorite
song is nice very
nice nice is that from a boy gr uh it's
17 if I recall ah okay I'm not well
versed in the boy groups only
the I I listen to F bit and B I have a I
have a friend who's like very very very
into care pop so they'll send me like
random I mean you're more than welcome
to send me like hpop music I love
listening yeah
[Music]
clip because of the the clier that
has you in my brain it's stuck it's
stuck
she you sound like
her do it
again sh
shella W At Your Service I can't
remember where what is she doing in this
room with me
watch how is this
possible nothing is
impossible think of the old uh thina
movie no my teammates are all on
fire oh my God everything's on
fire I'm starting to get a little bit
motion scky
a okay maybe maybe I don't like pyro
anymore cuz pyro runs around a
lot yeah well I haven't having fun
running around leave it to me yeah I
think I'm going to be the character that
stands still most of the
time screaming that's
chill who stands still the sniper I
guess uh
yeah it's cuz I I get sometimes a
motion games and stuff oh that can be
really bad in this game I
suppose oh yeah engineer just lazy
Engineers placing turrets
[Music]
everywhere that's the way to play
huh you want some go and get some get
them
I have like those
bands that feel like when you travel
what you have bands when you travel up
see you have the there these wristbands
ah
wristband like when you go on like
fairies or airplanes and if you get
motion sickness
like for mhm yeah so what Sailors would
do on on the is they would get a rock
and they would put it um like on their
wrist in a certain place and put a rope
around it like on the pressure plant and
so they have these like sticky bands
that you can get but it just kind of the
same
thing they probably have a they probably
have a name except for sticky
B it's a cute
name when I was
younger black um I think they
help I need healing I need
healing I need healing oh wait I didn't
I don't think they I don't think they
like fix it completely but they but they
definitely like do Something's Cooking
W's going on thank
you I need healing I need he going back
to OverWatch can every class do the the
deflection that I I've been doing
oh my God I'm
dead no a pyro only oh that's special
then I got to use it I didn't realize I
thought everybody had
that then I would have been probably
pushed back a lot more open Open Your
Door leave my game opening door I wonder
if I can watch
you how many times can I do that what's
the what's
the the cool down
I thought maybe it might be like other
games where you can just like I can just
watch
you yay wait am i r yeah we finally won
W because I get good I got good get good
how are you are you getting good I I
left my
game I'm going to I'm going to watch you
for a little bit oh that's F okay you
can learn from me
you have learned from you learn from the
the master the P the fire and the
brimstone yeah
exactly
yippe all right we're now attacking what
was I doing before I feel like I've been
attacking on this whole time even when
they say you're defending I'm still
attacking I like the the cute happy
noises I'm glad you're having
fun yeah it's okay press with
a maybe you could try OverWatch with me
one day play it too for you
okay I don't when you feel like I I
would I wouldn't pressure you into like
a PP game I know it's not for everybody
it's not my game of choice but if you
invite me I'll be there I'll be there I
barely get invited to FPS games probably
because people know I don't like FPS
games oh I mean I mean with me like as I
said I I didn't really play to win so
you could like if you if you joined me
then you'd just be just I don't know
whatever you want to do have fun yeah
play would be T
yeah that at least I'll let you know
I'll let you know when I get like a who
I'm while yeah while back I played it
all
Invincible I'm going to
die oh fabulous
too I like that name for it especially
with all the cuz I know the meme to do
with like hats and stuff oh yeah what's
this with the hats I haven't seen any
hats yet uh yeah you can I think there's
a lot of different like hats you can
like
get I know there was a meme to do with
stacking I don't know if you can do that
in game though I have no idea I don't
have hats yet M pf2 hats
economy oh the player the one player
customization is hats is that what it is
oh I
see there's different
weapons oh my God this is so difficult
hoty I don't know how to go into this I
need a
Healer heal
me oh no no no
no no no no no
no I refuse oh no no get to the point
where is the point get to the
chopper press e to call the medic I can
call the medic that's probably their
choice whether or not there you can cool
them no
apparently oh we're pushing now I see
all
right just get out
of fried chicken
let's go let's
go we don't just sell
chicken we're really pushing
now I'm such a
bully stop stop buing
him yeah weak as medic die oh no no more
ammo what do you mean they're like um
shiny
said they Glide
yeah um is the game
continuing right now I'm not sure begins
in 60 seconds I think it ended there
okay capture both control points to win
the round and advance in one
minute
crazy oh wait what why are why are they
waiting here oh it's setup time okay
a one minute of set up oh I see I see I
see
okay oh
up
chills what's this duel called 11 herbs
and
spices herbs and
spices spicy crazy spicy
wings that's too good the
fire spicy
H all right fire fire light fire
Leroy
janking
janking I can't move something there's
an invisible wall that's pushing me
me see old memes old memes and that I I
mean you know I it's because I played
World of Warcraft have you ever played
World of Warcraft no I've always wanted
to you've always wanted to I never I
didn't have a a good enough PC for those
games well I didn't have a PC I like a
very old La uh but yeah I can complain
but uh I have seen the World of Warcraft
movie I really enjoyed oh wait there's a
movie oh you didn't know yeah there's a
movie M we should watch it I enjoyed it
but people who have like played world
Warcraft and stuff like they have ity it
on it but I as someone who's not played
it I enjoying it oh I see I have a
similar experience with like not having
read books and therefore feeling okay
with unless you read lorded rings I
don't know no I
didn't but but I'm very interest I've
even been to a musical for lot of the
Rings that was pretty good wow that
sounds epic I I didn't I traveled to the
uh Great Britain for
it oh gosh epic oh my God I didn't know
that
was yeah they I think they are not
anymore in England like they uh have
ended it there and now moved on to
America
M yeah yeah yeah cuz they did so
well it was so cute because it was like
on the countryside more or less I had to
like travel quite far uh from London
onwards and it was in the middle of
nowhere and it was so cute though
because it was like not like a typical
like glamorous glorious this Hall where
they performed it it was you know a
little like Cottage kind of style with
oh wow yeah was a little Pond what did I
get myself into
here I remember uh cuz Death Note the
musical did well in the realm of the UK
London uh they uh back in April did the
your line April musical oh I see you
yeah April
perfect yeah April and April is was
great I I didn't see that one I haven't
seen the anime but um the Death Note
musical was brilliant oh mhm I really
enjoyed it I have actually not watched
death
notes oh it's it's it's very good like
it it's definitely one of those animes
got watch at some
point it's a legendary one I know yeah I
mean there gosh there's a fair few on my
to watch list still like I've not seen
uh i' see I've heard songs from most of
them like like
G I've heard songs from it but I you
Haven watch itly watched it no oh it's
time herb it's time it's time I think
well it's cuz uh when it like had gosh
it had a lot of hype when it came out
but back then like um it was hard in
great Exodia to find episodes and stuff
so but to this day it's one of my top
five anime oh wow and I think CI would
say the
same like I know quotes from it like
believe in me who believes in you that's
why I say believe in me who believes in
[Music]
the it's really cute I love that song um
you on my star the the redhead girl s
uhhuh mhm I really like that one yeah
Yoko yeah yeah I really love the um the
music video to that one
too it
got to watch it I will at some point F
year and I never because I didn't have
all the episodes I never finished um
zero no Saka yeah Saka I never finished
it but I I was just so happy that you
knew it oh yeah yeah I love those Tunes
it's so good and it just reminded me as
well I was like oh I need to finish this
anime
someday cuz the characters I really
enjoyed the characters I like the
animation Style too I feel like if I
never watched it before and I would
watch it now perhaps I might I I there's
a chance I wouldn't like
it never
know you get a Nostalgia hit and he's
still alive I um I watched I rewatched
preer what which one preer if you ever
had a pre sorry it's hard to hear with
all this noise oh
preer preer preer
it's a magical girl PR okay I really
don't know what you're saying cuz I
don't know it prer yeah yeah yeah it's a
it's a a great great
Ammon Pretty Cure Pretty Cure no Pretty
Cure no I watch of those it's it's
called Prett um and uh like the m so
it's about this girl and then she meets
these like uh male Warriors there's a
bunch of
and the way she like uh like magical
girl transforms is it like the anime
where like people become like weapons
and stuff like that they kind of fuse
together and then she has this like
different outfit and everything and
they're all all these guys are different
elements and it's really I
enjoy do you guys know that I don't
know I need to that's another one that I
I watched a few episodes of back in the
day cuz I really love the Paper Moon
opening
paper
yeah interesting you probably recogize
Paper Moon if you heard it that sounds a
little bit familiar yeah the
name oh suar Cara that's my favorite ah
I only know um some openings because I
was a huge fan always from this idle
company called hello project and they
their members did a
few uh uh did a few
songs heal
me I died CU of you we die CU of
you hop step
[Music]
down yeah cute now I can put another
like song on the list that we could sing
together and probably a lot of other
people wouldn't know
oh
wasn't buo buo did a lot of them but oh
my god do you know it wasn't that also
for sh they made another group that was
called I think four guardians or so and
and and oh my
God like they called like sugar car
they're literally called like suar car
egg or something Guardians four or
something yeah you know them you know
them oh my God those were like really
not like that's one of the least popular
least successful units that hello
project put together um but it had my
Oshi in it recyle that's why I love it
so
much a that's cute yeah I love the
tamago no egg song I really like the one
C you and me in
Japan oh God I have to look up the
romanji oh that's fine that's
fine we can look it up on the phone and
and we sing all the old anime songs yeah
super that was my favorite bit going to
the Far East uh like going to karaoke of
course it is of course that's your
favorite it blew my mind you can even
order food and you have your own room
and like yeah the room thing is awesome
yeah most P here are just like open bars
I hate that yeah yeah open yeah pubs and
things like that yeah yeah so having
your own room like with a like a comfy
setup and you can book like for hours on
end and I I mean heck I mean I said to
um like my manager and stuff I was like
people like look it to watch movies and
stuff I feel like this would be a great
to watch movies if you like attach your
La hon yeah people do that for a lot of
things
yeah yeah what are we doing man what are
we why are they going back
oh yeah i' I'd uh I definitely like had
my manager go go CaRu with me a fair few
few times partially cuz uh they like had
these H live drinks too ah yeah yeah
yeah yeah we do have a lot of
tie-ups especially around Fest time yeah
it's so
exciting and it feels weird like you
know I travel to Japan a lot like
several times a year and I love to go to
Koka and sometimes I go to k and I just
see like this is not just in Koga but
walking around in Japan in general
seeing advertisements and like kind of
you know stuff from our company and I'm
like oh cute it blew my mind yeah I saw
like um begins choco flakes Chloe choco
flakes yeah I saw those too in the
convenience store also I walked past the
uho uh tayak yeah yeah yeah
yeah I love tayak
game I like um so I really like uh so in
the realm of London they have they kind
of and they have this really good Bakery
and they have taaki there but they put
in the tiaki uh Nella [\h__\h] in in in
London what sorry it's got really loud I
can't believe what I'm hearing in the
the Chinatown area oh really
yeah yeah it's very good and well they
they have a Nutella option so and I love
Nutella oh let's go
yeah you know the most like common one I
guess is anle the red beans but the
second most common in Japan I think is
also
um uh uh custard just normal custard so
I usually go for that cuz I prefer the
custard but having the kayaki would be
dope yeah I think I went for like
chocolate last time and I got these like
meiku ones from a uh an arcade one point
but when in the bares but I think next
time I'm going to try those custody on
as much as I like chocolate I think I
probably might like heal me
thanks me just pushing people
around push them push them well I feel
uh at least I feel pretty prepared at
this point already for this collab mhm
yeah I still suck but ah
as long as you have fun yeah fun
with oh my
God were you also joining for the collab
herb of course she is yeah I'm joining
are you just joining the first one no
I'm joining uh Gmod too isn't that at
the
end yeah oh my God but so in between
you're going to stay up or you taking
nap uh I'm going to try and see if I can
fit in
that that's it yeah that's it uh 3:00
a.m. great exi
in well uh
respect I specifically chose this one
because you know it's the earliest one
yeah
yeah Gmod I only played G with before so
yeah I wanted to choose uh the old the
group
ones have you played Gmod before
no I have not I've always wanted to play
the I think you mix GMod
and games yeah I don't want to play that
I really don't understand it quite well
but when we played it was Counter Strike
with
Gmod like we had to download both of
those things I'm I don't really get need
to check I haven't down stuff after
after Team Fortress is done uh
yeah you were playing prop on yeah yeah
yeah yeah but like somehow we had to
play we had to download Counter Strike
too for it Counter Strike as well for
it it works with Al kinds of source
games okay so I guess the map was from
Counter
Strike hey I want the B
too I'll probably need to lay down
anyway cuz I I have a feeling that Team
Fortress is going to make my tummy turn
oh
no okay that's fine I are you think
you're still going to come back for when
we're actually playing as with the
others oh no I'm going to I'm going to
stick around I'm just saying after Team
Fortress I'm going to probably like I
think I probably will don't overdo
it we don't want you to throw up on
stream oh I mean luckily I don't I I
just get a really bad tummy I don't I
don't actually throw up luckily which is
is great because of the singing and
stuff like cuz cuz throwing up is bad
for the vocal oh yeah I I would assume
so
yeah I I just get really bad
tumy oh my
God
die I can't I'm too far I need to be
close range
guys can't do this kill me
at least they listen to me the
Bots that's why I part went on my game
so I can take a break I watch
you
yeah glasses I Don't Want
To Oi
yeah pyro pyro she loves pyro yeah and I
I want die a few words no words even
want to be decent in it so I got to like
focus on it
setting is that one in is there
something like that in in Team Fortress
what what's let me
see sometimes in games you can change
the the field of view and
it yeah does it guys don't in advanced
settings Advan oh that's where
I'm advance
damn there's a lot of advanced
settings who would have
H
um oh my
God y yum yum yum
[Music]
the stupid sent tur why doesn't someone
just get rid of the S
tur I can't even go around this
[Music]
corner find
it I'm trying to find the fav I could
find
it guys do you know where exactly it is
help help looking they said Advan they
said advanced settings but maybe it's
just a me
thing I think it's a Elizabeth thing uh
oh
again in regular options visual uh-huh
now it's regular options really options
video Advanced ah so yeah right cuz
there's Advanced within the not Advanced
ones if you get it oh yeah that was
stupid yeah go to normal options and
then to video and then to advance video
[Applause]
then I
now the struggles of being a pyro player
versus Sentry
mhm there's more options upon the
options set your fov to
90 well it's currently on 75
now
it's go back return to where you came on
go back don't you dare go around the
corner oh
[\h__\h] 75 is too low
okay yeah thank you kfp kfp is the
best I love they a lovely bunch yeah I
love chicken oh oh thank you question
mark
you you just mean
yumy not for eating I love some cheeky
cheeky
chicken wait hold on I love me some
Nando even though I haven't had nandos
in he
a Nando have you ever had nandos
never what was Nando again it's a it's
like a mostly known for like chicken
it's like a Portuguese
restaurant it's just a spicy chicken
spicy chicken and chips I'm so sick of
this spicy chicken and chips M yeah so
yeah you never heard um in the realm of
the UK people saying oh I'm going to go
for a cheeky Nando ah yeah yeah yeah
yeah what a funny thing to say yeah it's
cuz it's you know it's it's cheeky it's
a cheeky thing to do because people
loved it so much that's why they'd say
oh I'm going to go for
Chey it's still pretty popular
um but yeah it's nice I like it spicy
chicken if you like if you like spice
but there is like different spice levels
so you can have like lemon and hub or
you can have't plain to be honest but
um it's good can we end this [\h__\h]
already it's reading us what's the
[\h__\h] point
tell me there's no point end
it I'm going to go get some water yeah
you do that do the best for your fro
because your fro must be
protected it's good to hydrate
hydration hydration foration
[Music]
ra
ra XP is she
gone are we among
ourselves
I no I'm not going to change guys I'm
going to stay
stubing just end it already please Mama
Mia
I'm
[Music]
way
bro it's so dumb oh look at us getting
blown up Miss ends in 10
seconds four
C you
failed shut up
shut up I win because this whole chat
cheers for
me and all of these [\h__\h] are butts
you're not winning Mission begins in 60
seconds how much longer is this can I
just drop out at some point or like is
this forever
like I got 20 more minutes until L
collab this is for oh it's Eternal what
oh because is it always Eternal or is it
just because it's with
B what it's
forever oh train Oh I thought this was
normal Mission begins in 30 seconds I
see all right endless practice makes
sense that's what I
need building a Sentry aren't you that's
what I'm talking about
oh myem motion is boring Mission begins
in 10 seconds the end is never the end
is never the end 5 4 3 at least I get to
know this map very
well at least I noticed
[Music]
him get him
push
push why can I not push oh what out of
ammo need ammo to
push wait friends or FS I don't I'm not
sure uh friends right
oh come back come
back now come
back let's have some
fun spawn
camping cuz I'm
red I'm
red Solo solo ah
ah out of ammo
again never turn your back on the enemy
[Music]
I can't believe smoovy is sleeping in
this room again while I'm streaming I
feel like she has accepted like she's in
the stage of
acceptance
normally until recently she would never
be with me in the room when I stream the
moment I start talking she leaves the
room the moment I stop talking she comes
back she just realizes oh she's
streaming I'll I'll leave the room cuz
she's loud but now she's here here she
just loves me too
much she accepted it she loves me more
then well today she got two breakfasts
so once when I woke up at like 7 a.m.
for the dishwasher guy and then I went
back to bed and normally she can't fool
me and I I knew she had breakfast before
but when we woke up again at like 1:00
p.m. she was like meow meow meow meow
meow again I was like okay whatever I
I'll give you another breakfast if that
makes you
happy almost time for 11 seeds
am I invisible why are they not looking
at
me YouTube is YouTube doing something
funny oh oh nice shot
bro where did he go
ow dead in North America oh well then
you got to move to Europe come
over come
over we welcome
you lag
flickers this is maybe we should take a
little of
cuz the collab starts in 15 minutes
maybe after this round I'm going to take
a little break because it's too loud
it's too
much it's over over
stimulating yeah yeah yeah I'll I'll
turn it down a lot more a lot more for
the
collab it's hard to balance the audio in
the middle of all of this sorry and I I
thought I was just like kind of waiting
for it to finally end for me to adjust
the volumes and everything more but it
turns out it never ends oh welcome back
hello how's the
water great the final control is being
just what I needed you know uh what's
the place again where you where you from
great Exodia Exodia so i' I've been to
Exodia too it turns out oh
and wait how do I get out of this you're
not mistaken it with the realm of the UK
n it's
exciting begin no I
mean the UK realm exist it's real
they're real some there are people
probably in
chat well I'm just saying I'm from a
different
place similar Exodia okay
but do you guys have very wobbly Waters
there
too wobbly Waters yeah I feel like you
have like your countries have a lot of
similarities so it must be wobbly water
very wobbly water very wobbly
what heard of smart water not wobbly
water no very wobbly I've been to uh
this like nice hotel in okay it was
London um yeah uh it was a Hilton hot I
knew it she was on about the London UK
realm I knew it surely is
similar it is very similar mhm and it
had an indoor pool yeah but it was like
underground and first of all getting
there you had to walk through these like
corridors that were like really run down
and had a million unused uh lockers and
everything looked like it was built 30
years ago and it was weird prob yeah and
then
and I like the voice you're putting on
for this like it was a dark dark room in
a dark dark cave in a dark dark H in a
dark
dark got to paint the picture you know
yeah yeah it was so weird and and the
towel the towel that I got had a hole
and everything and so anyway I get to
the pool and what's the hole for well it
shouldn't be there I don't know
man and then the pool you know the pool
it was just me and my friend and I was
like alone in the pool and I wasn't even
like trying to make waves but it was
just so wobbly it was the wobbles water
I've ever experienced in my whole life I
would just like stay in the water and it
was wobbling on its own it was wobble
wobble wobble it was so hard to swim
because the water kept on going into my
face more than any other water in this
world you sure you went out like a a
water park no no really no and it had no
like wave functions or anything like
that
and also the walls were moldy
and a lot ofing
yeah you're a brave to still getting
that water thank you right actually true
but I just wanted to swim I chose the
hotel because they had a
pool and yeah you know Hilton Hotel
should be nice normally oh true yeah and
then they did not even understand how to
make scrambled eggs don't even get me
started
gosh that's odd for that hotel yeah that
brand yeah yeah like what the heck The
Audacity Of serving me the usual like
okay so I will explain Hotel breakfast
they usually like you know at the buffet
they will have scrambled eggs that are
from like a box like it's a mixture a
pre-made mixture which is understandable
because they have it to make it in big
quantities but it's like not real egg
you know and that's why it doesn't taste
like anything tastes so Bland and so I I
usually avoid that uh kind of egg but in
nicer hotels you can usually ask them to
make like an omelet for you or or
scrambled eggs or a fried egg or
anything with real eggs and they will
make it um so if you ask for an omelette
they will make something proper but I
just asked for normal scrambled eggs
fresh basically and they just brought me
the same [\h__\h] from the buffet container
like bro can you make me some real eggs
and they were so confused they didn't
understand what I meant I guess and they
brought the same again
yeah huh you didn't get sick after that
did you with all the mold and everything
no the mold was like more not it didn't
seem like it was like because pool
waterers like you can like Po water po
p po
water
no but yeah the chor the chor in the
pool water will make it like clean right
so yeah but I would say the mold was
more like on the walls of like outside
of the water and all
that so yeah I think when it comes I I I
like going um like if if there is like a
which is quite rare if there is a pool
at the hotel like I do like to have a
dip um but a dip a dip uh but it's uh I
always have to make sure I'm not like on
a mission or something oh ah so in case
you get sick because of yeah because you
know that's the you know with everybody
getting in the pool and all that you
never know yeah but it has chlorine it's
I would say it's fine not need to worry
so much about the
pool but do you have a weak immune
system no I I mean it's rare I get sick
that's why I get like a bit like
I used to never get sick before Holo but
then I joined Holo and by just doing my
job at home all the time and like rarely
going outside the few times I do go
outside I always have been getting sick
and I've been getting the worst
sicknesses of my life while in
Holo yeah Holo made me sick yeah Holo
life is causing me illness
[Laughter]
or for real though I think that's
something you got to be careful when you
know now I don't know I don't know if
you are going out less than before ever
since you joined Hollow but it's the
case for me and yeah messes up your
immune system I just got to make sure to
take my vitamins and my vitamin yeah I
was going to like take vitamins too and
then I keep on forgetting and I just
don't commit to it yeah that's the thing
yeah I I forget too I think it but but
since joining this I got to try and
remind myself I'm like you got to take
them you got to you got to you need one
of those like um like pale containers
for every weekday like the seniors yeah
yeah oh you know what's funny I actually
got one of those in the past um they're
cute young ago cuz it was it was very it
was very helpful um I'm sure it is
actually and then you'd know what days
you missed too when it came to like your
vitamins I I I I tried one of those like
a long time ago and I put my stuff in
like uh supplements and stuff but then I
noticed it was like I guess because it
wasn't like as well contained as in the
original container so it was like
falling apart
crumbling oh and I was like okay I guess
I'm not using this again I
guess oh no is that normal I don't know
if that's normal no well I mean I guess
it did I when you order something online
it's 50/50 you know
so yeah you never know I mean I I got a
package today and it was uh it was
busted so on the outside only or on the
inside too h both oh no yeah so you
never know Mama Mia please give my S
packages
safely
M those were yeah yeah yeah I think it's
the humidity
mhm yeah it got through the container
somehow oh well so I'm taking a little
break now because that was apparently I
didn't realize herb that it would just
go on forever and ever and ever as long
as you're playing with Bots I was
waiting for it to end on its own I think
my I think one of the other well I don't
know maybe I left that too I think I
left that too I was doing the payload
one mhm before joining
you about think that carried on oh I
think that restarted too but um yeah
gosh excited to play this with with real
people
yeah real people yeah I wonder how
they're GNA do how many participants do
we have
many um oh wait they're in they're in
that disc okay I don't know if I I was
like wondering how I'm going to do this
there now cuz they're probably
prepping
um I can
probably like give it a like two more
minutes and then I'll mute everything
until the stream is really supposed to
to start or something like
that yeah no I'm a knows that I'm
streaming beforehand and I said okay uh
when do you need me there 5 minutes
before or so yeah I'll put you guys we
have a minute then before 5 minutes yeah
apparently there's not much set up to be
done I guess
oh
don't should we head over H uh
sure yeah I'll put you guys back on the
loading screen it's not ending it's just
loading again and then I'll see you in
probably well well 5 minutes and then
another like everybody's loading screen
never I don't know how long they'll need
I'm ready
whenever all right see you in a hot
minute look at these advertisements that
I have for you to
[Music]
n
a
[Music]
he n
no
[Music]
oh
w
[Music]
oh
a
[Music]
n
we're
so made it hello hello hello
hello wow wow all right thank you guys
for joining my the valve collab Marathon
thank you for
[Music]
play a lot of you guys are new to the
game right oh yeah yeah played before I
didn't even play the
[Laughter]
tutorial
easy we ski the tutorial yeah we skip a
skip a yeah
yeah all right I don't know if we need
introductions there's a lot of us here
so that might take like five or 10
minutes oh but just maybe for audio
check for the
balancing Speed Run speed run all right
fine all right we'll go down the Discord
list I'll go first hello everybody I'm
ailia Watson a number one detective from
Hall English
[Applause]
M hello everyone
[Music]
leader
Justice what did she
say
here I'm I guess oh hello it's different
than my list
[Music]
it
[Laughter]
[Music]
y
j
[Music]
y
good speedy
[Music]
y
[Applause]
okay from H English promise nice to
[Music]
meet sorry I couldn't tell what people
are
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
it's wa here I'm gonna play
Pyro good to know start a fire today
yeah oh yeah
true all right so we are going to split
up into different teams uh I I randomly
what oh what and nothing so I just
killed me oh wait how am I dead why am I
not why am I looking at people I think
someone's
cheating you can cheat in this game no
no you can't you can't
ah are we
starting uh yeah yeah yeah okay if
you're on Blue Team we'll go into the
other
voice okay
okay and then it's Capture the Flag yeah
any questions uh where's the flag
somebody kill where's the flag
blue team hold on let's all meet up in
the bridge meet up in the bridge bridge
no I want to be a red
team uh uh I don't understand is it blue
here blue blue
team let's go blue team has it begun I
don't no has it begun oh my God the
pictures are so big now maybe let me fix
that so cat sen pie
oh shouldn't there be more than just us
free there should
be I believe soy I think is on
Blue oh who who is that blue person
smack who is that who's that count on me
I'm the best at this game are we are we
are we playing I don't know
hello are we playing are we playing is
it game time I guess yes yes yes cuz
it's so chill right now I don't know I
don't know if it's okay to attack them
it is a CH game Let's attack them
where's the flag I'll impress them with
my
skills hey what's up guys
[Music]
oh are we complete now in our team oh
wow I was left at the other team oh you
were spying kind
of well I didn't mean to I think they
wanted me there oh oh oh okay they
wanted you there I want you too I I can
pretend to be wait you what I want you
too here yeah oh I'm here I'm here stay
us who you're just I will I will eating
up people with a bag
I
accident I'm
lost where am I don't worry I lost hello
can someone pick me up I'm scared
machine
G what I exploded where even is the flag
yeah how do I all chat oh that's my flag
how do I go I found our flag I guess you
found our flag where's their flag it
didn't look like a flag though hi who's
that who is that running around so
energetically a gigy I'm running I'm
running oh oh crap don't die all right
maybe I should change it the different
class wow CeCe really hates me I'm
scared get him get him I'm
scared how we are we like in the lead I
can never tell in these games I don't
even think we started is it a catchup I
have no idea what's going on maybe it's
warm
up it's just warm
I do Air Blast only good strategy right
who oh that's you okay that is me hi
hello sexy
ladies oh oh oh oh no stop killing me
this my
team we need to capture the flag okay so
we need to get deeper into the system
get him get him get him get him get him
get him get him get him I'm respawning
oh crap where are
you I I don't know what I am I don't
know who this person is but I don't like
them of the enemies but I'm not quite
sure I don't know what this disguise
thing is my intelligence has diminished
mine has picked up they got the I think
that's the flag what I think we need to
kill
Watson picked up our intelligence are
they all in our base right now yeah they
all our base here oh we need to defend
def I'm
coming attack attack attack okay okay I
got her I got her
nice how do you run in this can you even
run oh there you go I don't I think you
go your movement I know what happened
but I think I killed someone don't tell
my
parents uh uh where is everybody ah hi
this
intelligent okay I'll okay I'm going to
go look for theirs it must be deep in
their they're spawn I'm running under
Nest
yeah I'll stay in a corner
here y too bad we can't pick up our
intellig I need healing I need healing
do we have a Healer at all no right we
do not have do the others have a Healer
oh do they
haveo they're healing man we need I
don't think they're in our
team yeah who's this oh hi cron hi nice
suit thank
you I can't find their intelligence oh I
think I found
it all right I'm heading in there just a
kill oh oh I didn't mean I thought they
meant that we got some like smartness
buff or
so no we don't flag oh picking of
intelligence means picking up their flag
I I'll defend okay I'm running back nice
watch I got your back I'm so lost they
got our intelligence you're going the
right way you're going the right way I
don't know what I'm
doing they're shooting me back up back
up back back up is that my
intelligence there you
go I'm confused no she
ENT I have no idea where to drop this
off do I bring it to our place I think I
know base or something yeah probably oh
maybe the spawn
point it's okay at least you're still
alive we'll spawn in soon yeah at least
we together oh I got it oh oh you got
it
goed nice oh yeah we both have one one
now y y good good job d y watch out
there's a Watson in our base oh sorry
that's you oh yeah she killed me I'm so
honored y her huh uh let's see good job
Amy all right I'm going to go with the
Healer
oh I got it I I think I'm going to
protect the that's myself why do I see
myself over there
Jee she's just miling
everyone she's so
surrounded it's okay you did
great get away from me there's an
impostor with my name a spy don't trust
them kill them kill them I'm currently
dead
sock yay our intelligence has been
picked up which is not a good thing I
learned no we have to stop them stop
them yes H this s gun really sucks where
are they there's two of them there's two
of them there's two of them there's two
of The Help they in there
intelligent guys guys there's two of
them I got killed by B Liz no look for I
think I see your dead
body I can't tell where they are I think
your character is
smoking m
hello anybody Here I need a mini
map I'm where are they is
there go from here no this place is so
confusing I'm
little yeah I think they're over here
come on come
on where are all of them come
on oh no oh was someone trying to heal
me I I
died I got revenge on fun oh yeah
yeah her has cap the intelligence I must
heal someone it's part of my
job oh you're healer now she I can heal
anymore actually you can switch Yeah you
can switch with comma scroll wheel oh
where's your intelligence this is their
resupply why is the blast not doing I do
not like medic you don't like medic
think so I don't think healing is my
nature I think I need to stay with
killing all right I can become a Healer
eventually if we can't change the rules
I don't mind too much oh yeah yeah you
can change you can go with whatever you
want
oh and when you die you can switch
yay
oh oh I'm right behind
[Music]
you protect me owie I'm not really the
type to protect uh cuz I'm not a tank
but I'll
try kill her kill her I protect you f
has it out for me get out of
here oh it was a double it was F and
killing me that means free people ganked
up on me free people all right we're
eating hot dogs tonight
oh I like hot dogs me
too oh I can't walk through all of that
we need a Healer get her get her get her
get
out healer later for
you again the that you deserve she hates
me oh that's where you go I see
gy what class are you playing the really
fast one that has a bat that way I can
bat people yeah Skin Man you a baseball
player Scout yeah that's why you're so
fast I'm going for the big guy now I'm
going to
intelligence I'm a big guy with a little
ego that's a wrong place oh really
oopsie I like the big guy it's fine hi
let's go to Battlement fast they're
shooting me they're shooting me how dare
they was a false spy our intelligence
has been dropped that's good giggy good
job giggy where are you
giggy they dropped the intelligence
right by their spawn I don't know how to
protect this no no
stop I got like why are they so
good oh I got two timed I just air
plastic because I'm too far to hit them
anyway with my fire
guys oh there's I'm trying to protect
our intelligence that
oh all right I'm going to try to be less
aggressive
now you can change how do you
change use the comma and then press a
random number comma and a random number
random yes we must make sure they don't
they don't take this wait how do you
grab the intelligence you have to wait
there's a circle above it and then it
shows was assigned to team
blue a can you shoot someone who looks
like a spy no she's in
Spectators oh crap there's two of them
all right what the hell F stop
[Music]
I like how Cron's just chasing the guy
hey nice job good job
[Music]
cron yay now it's personal
yeah I don't know who is gu gone sh
together we're
strong let's go
to maybe she needs backup is the med gun
the
healing uh help help bro
help yeah you're you're a Healer now
yeah let's go three people defending
intelligence wait wait guys I got the
intelligence to our base but I got
killed someone picking
up where are you oh I'm in the big open
area kind of the one that have
stairs okay I think I see it a there I
am
in oh and I died here there there like
three people intelligence has been
returned
oh I oh God I see no I can't do this
alone y yum they're coming after
me this is not your
GH I like I need to go
back hello oh
who is that where oh that's how it works
nice oh hello ban oh no an intelligence
guys okay their intelligence is gone we
just have to we have to get we have to
get it again I'm close to it but I'm
alone oh no oh is there is there even a
winning side right now they're winning
they have two intelligence yeah they to
they
winning I'm just uh staying here
then I'll just pull out my switch and
play a game or something going to eat a
salad tonight for
dinner good job ow ow help oh okay sorry
the
N spy is evil don't trust the Spy the
Spy is evil hm they keep on Faking me
it's [\h__\h] it it's [\h__\h] it oh hey
medkit nice yeah intelligence is
here is there anybody here oh nice good
job team good J good job team oh oh
sorry I thought you were someone I was
about to
shoot oh no oh nice
job I didn't kill you right oh crap
they showed up there's three of them in
our base our intelligence oh no they got
our intelligence oh
no I burn the intelligence
person got nowhere to go was not enough
oh you got the intell I got
the run
run what's trick stab I'm trying to find
my way to you stab trick yeah I don't
even know where I'm going
I need
something help help help oh I see you oh
I will help you are you one of us s will
I I will off of my
body okay I need to bring it to the
intelligence right yeah to the
intelligence room run further inside yes
yes oh man you're doing
it I'm looking for not that way not that
way come back come back come back this
way up oh [\h__\h] but they have our
intelligence too I don't know where they
are let's check the back no no come back
come back come back back back back back
back she was following me oh never
follow giggy giggy
understands this should be here over
here over over here yeah this is
intelligence about that way works too
intelligence let's go okay it's testing
our intelligence
day for this yeah and then you
follow the sign thank you
nice we did
it no
no no we almost made it see we got to Dr
did we got to drop it off no think we
didn't like literally in that moment or
it ended by a
second I think oh they got hours first
cuz they were a little bit faster
carrying it over to their base I see
just let us go kill okay it was close
same thing right know hates
humans hi I'm here to check you guys I'm
just spectating oh hello okay hello you
guys did good without I saw you running
around what the the case for a long
time she tried her best I was trying to
find the intelligence room but I failed
it's kind of it's hard I was going to
show you guys very
confusing yeah at least I picked it up
and it killed someone which is better
than
nothing if you guys need any help or
questions I can
[Music]
help not sure am I don't know this game
is very simple
[Music]
yeah I'm infiltrating the enemy they
have our intelligence again we shall
take theirs okay what if I just Camp
here wait am I blue or
red get out of here what they have
another spawn too there's one on the
other side where's the intelligence okay
we'll we'll camp out at one of them you
guys are all going nice nice yes
te together
strong yeah oh where is it there Cony
come back I don't know where it is I
found it I think we should stick
together yeah you take it you're faster
run run run run we'll protect you we'll
protect you
I'll actually oh they can come back down
and take that yeah case okay never mind
ow oh if you're carrying intelligence
you should stay back so you can defend
okay yeah stay back stay back I'm just
going to keep shooting my oh no oh no
no I kill it I kill it I think I got
it oh shoot oh shoot I dropped it don't
give up no
no you got to run no good nice nice I
don't know where anywhere
is that that dropped it kind of by their
spawn area oh thank you
oh I don't even know where that is I
like how G's just standing there I'm
making sure no one takes this
intelligence yeah I think they forgot
about it oh my brain cells are dropping
thank God they forgot about it they
forgot about it no she came back but
it's gone
fool oh I see the red intelligence there
[Music]
people pick it up St pick it up VA every
time oh no I got you my buddy I got you
ra thank you I want to go grab the yep y
intelligence I refreshed the timer oh
let's go is that
good here we
go nice there's too many of
them yeah they're they're not even going
for yeah that's good they're going on
the def
H they feel threatened oh maybe they're
using it to lure
us they're threatened by how good we are
what are you doing down there yeah we
let them win the last
round why are you down
there swimming you can go through the
tunnel here I don't know the canal yeah
the tunnel is
easier but it's stinking there's rats
where where oh whoop
sorry uhoh you guys need a medic they
have a medic
yes
oh okay I can renge I'm not good at it
though don't die don't
die backstabbers everywhere y I'm
killing
myself with the
Rockets no all right I'm IC now who
needs healing I'm going to stay here
though
um well if you're just standing there
then follow me and heal me okay I got
you uh where's everybody else right now
everyone out of
heels uh I think you you got to like
pick up those little packages on the
ground that refill your ammo like this
one I think refills your ammo I see I
see okay oh there's someone we are yeah
but with your healing we can do it
maybe okay good we can get our
intelligence too I'm you weren't healing
were you was killed medic was
fried oh healing is infinite you have to
use the medic gun medic gun is
infinite all right I'll stay put in a
random area then
okay oh quason where are we going quason
someone has our intelligence too oh you
guys traded you guys traded it's okay oh
it's
returned oh
no does someone have ours where they
head
to I such you like this
game
yeah okay I'm going to join you guys
healer yes please help us we're
losers no no
no now this pretty strong we are pretty
strong I'll protect all right everyone's
at Bas I guess
oh yeah
wow wait that barely did any
damage to the battle Ms battle mes
battle
Ms
heck we need to see some
fire
I'm see during the centuries I hate the
centuries my face
follow me at the entrance they're inside
I flamed them put a Sentry on the
intelligence
case I can't where are we going oh I
think they did they already take the
case oh not yet not
yet yeah that is yeah this is super
messed up but uh not going to that's not
messed up it's SM
I'll just I I'll just leave it at the
middle upgrade uh the small one
appreciate the help thank you ow
ow nice
nice you should you should you could go
with the the other team into the base
and then it'll help them a lot I
wherever they're going making sure
you're not a
spy
oh where where to go what where to go
where where them
fire is good versus F yeah I'm going
with the Enemy area anyone who's there
you're going with the
Enemy oh no no no I me like if anyone's
going in I just can hear people I'm
running let's go oh they're right
there
yeah oh everyone has died pretty fast
I'm running for their intelligence I bet
she loves me though thank
you seems like she had some practice as
an engineer I can build teleports so I'm
going to put a Teleport into their base
from our spawn okay wow yeah yeah this
will give me like a few minutes
Andy no KY no no KY no don't die no
gy no no on the
it's okay it's okay I'm still I'm okay
I'm okay I'm okay I'll go the other
way I it's okay thank you in our base
they're in our base it's okay I got a
Sentry down
there they're still in our base rage
swap a they R the way I'm on the Xbox my
mama said I'm not supposed to be here oh
crap oh no I got sniped help help help
ah
yay
no so
tanky
yay is that friend or
fo I just shoot them
anyway they're on the
ground we'll figure it out
later GG let's
go I need to get used to
this I don't understand this yet M oh
it's why did you shoot me just in case
you are
CC where where is it I'm I'm l i this
way idea you go to intelligence to drop
it
off drop all the way to the desk again
yeah you know the architect of this
place kind of sucks cuz they put two
enemy factions near each other hey guys
I put a teleporter by the main spawn and
if you go into teleporter it'll take you
into their
base who are you can I trust you okay I
can trust you can trust me I'm friend
okay oh fa is in our base intelligence
kill
her how do I take
this thank
you I got their intelligence I'm on my
way back good job
oh oh
no it's okay it's okay yeah yeah I think
they know they know they know I'm here
they know I'm here watch out spy spy
Spy I sense your
presence where are them all right I'm
now without protection I must stay with
someone where are you where are you
where are
you oh you need
yeah hey if you go into this teleporter
down it take you right to their base all
right guess we're going together cool
down there like what
the all right don't die have minute to
not die the Spy there's a spy it's not
me but it's them but they're acting as
me which
one not yeah I'm just healing everyone
currently the real wa is not
anymore I'm an eny I saw spy behind the
scout who's the Scout on the bridge turn
around we got it we got
it oh it's you okay it's me it's me okay
I'm who is that thank you okay making
sure that it's not a spy the
intelligence can we even teleport back
from here I don't think so okay oh no no
it's only one way sorry okay be safe
everyone me he me I'm healing I'm
healing you have Uber if you have Uber
you can going to turn you to a kfp don't
worry don't worry it's me it's
me all right oh my god let's
go everyone else crazy
girl oh
we have to go back we have to go back sh
yeah
yeah where am I where am
I I don't know just make a this way this
way okay this way who's this okay oh
crap wait wait fall this way I'm healing
I'm
healing lit
Unstoppable MVP I hear the screams of
the damn inside Halloween
[Laughter]
cover my shoulders Shin I need to find I
am I am I got both your shoulders
there's an enemy here I was
stuck good job what is the intelligence
oh my gosh you keep losing I I don't
know I'm not intelligent enough toig
that way
out let's go let's go they have our
intelligence they're running they're
running anyone even if they look like us
at this
point that's a good
strategy yeah shoot now ask
later so
[Music]
true let's go to the all voice chat all
voice CH
okay
yay hey yo hello
ti ti all right we're changing
Maps do random teams again this
time
okay did you guys have
fun it's chaotic he hates me
yeah so fun what why you bullying us h
no I'm
not no you're the easiest Target no you
were just walking around
I random you walked into my bullets yeah
random you want us to hit random yes
yeah yeah random let's go random move
the
C yeah so this one uh one side pushes
the cart the other side tries to stop
cart how to die I had a heart attack oh
no how do you know if you're on the
pushing team or the defending team red
is defending blue is pushing okay I
cannot open okay okay do you want us to
move in a different
voice yeah yeah okay uh blue team or red
team go to the other voice chat okay
byebye goodbye oh fa is in my team so
she can't kill me anymore wait did I
kill you I I I I left the room by
mistake I mean they kicked me out I
don't know what happened I'm trying to
we can wait for you II to come
back I guess we should uh memorize the
map really quick that is true can we
just push oh it's not letting us through
this one C
animal oh no okay but seems like is
kicked out of a group yeah yeah I'm
trying to log in again
okay begins select person can you like
stop we
[Music]
doing
okay press G wait am I in the right
party do we just red team move red team
move red team in okay bye okay no moving
no moving I'm pushing I'm pushing
later no moving no moving ferara help
someone's
here
sniper there's a crazy sniper BL
team what's AO
Balan oh is that what youa did okay yeah
yeah yeah okay I'm in I'm in I'm in are
we red no we're blue I'm blue what
happened so guys we have to stick close
to the car in order to speed up the the
card I think the more people are closer
to the car the better oh I got
sniped are we or are we connecting wait
I don't know where to go I'm so confused
being blue now because we were red the
entire time oh my God so confusing okay
okay so we're blue we push it push the
card okay
okay got this what I put put on a
different team what uh what she
I'm red now I've Been Changed I didn't
realize oh yeah I think the teams were
balanced up when it started hello
welcome welcome to the red te I had
absolutely no idea that that
happened hi hoko we're here re
no yep yep are you fre the B I know
where to go uh oh I see the car the car
is really wait am I going the right way
no I'm going the wrong way it's this way
don't follow
me you I'll follow you in
okay it's coming it's coming it's coming
Soul oh there's somebody there I'll heal
[Music]
you oh what
what I should have be here I should have
be here okay okay I need
healing I'm healing she will I'm going
to go in uh oh C's behind you
oh she's spying do we need two healers I
don't know I think we need same
person I'm going to get this orange
gun first
time I'll heal if you heal that Cecilia
I
think we need
heal no
risks there a dangerous that fre I can't
I want something that goes more like the
other side other side this is
[Laughter]
hard it's fine oh they're doing well
they're going to next
Point get them away from next we shoot
that we shoot it does it explode how
does it stop I don't know
I can I shoot the
load oh
at least there's a attack over time can
we use the youing just
wait medic
medic where're
medic why are you just jumping in front
of me that's you
are does she want to die all right herbs
needs
healing come over here by the car the
car I'm going to shoot the car okay I'm
to
BU good there over there come over here
if you want
healing wait what color am I H red keep
on forgetting that way I'm up
here uh uh keep oh dang it's okay and
pray on fire come over here if you want
healing they C they're cing behind you
push I have Push okay we probably need
to move now no I'm staying right here oh
we got a spot probably fight us we going
to fight us we're going to die yeah yeah
yeah yeah we're not going to make this
we're not going to make this we have to
[Music]
jump I don't want to
hurt I'm going to do it
yeah do it's a good strategy
yeah I don't want to hurt her
we need an what happened to you I got
sniped by
cicilia a medic no dad oh they're there
defend the payload shoot them from
behind wait there's still 8
minutes watch out we can't survive that
we can't survive
that oo
flying going
off D GG I will
try oh it's coming in oh is it
over
okay we
tried we tried good
[Music]
top defense is always so hard again
again
I'm going to try and oh we're attacking
now yeah we're attacking
now okay I'll stay together here done
I'll heal you our bullets aren't that
strong we should only use it when we
really need to so let's focus on healing
yes yes FOC different from what you said
just a moment
ago take the take out the I see
aggressive Target so we need to respond
aggressively yeah okay get he
get healed let us let
us we got 30
seconds let's just think about like our
family probably to
die how do you look at what all the the
doohickeys do on each character I like
is there a button to click the is
ready do I have to press the Uber and
then attach to someone Miss begins in 10
seconds 10 seconds what was that oh oh
you got to be attached to someone and
then Uber
yeah I've changed character how do you
look at what the character does uh
period and then do numbers just keep
holding the period them oh okay always
telling me to kind of get out good job
good job good job go for it go for it I
can them from
here freaking okay I'm just going to
focus on pushing yeah push push push oh
we're dying we're dying we're dying so
it's comma and then if you hover over
the characters it'll say what they do
can I why did my weapon change wow I
really like those ging guns we should
heal
everybody it wrong way wrong
way oh oh I still can shoo
it oo to the
C I'm going back to the other voice chat
good luck you guys have questions out oh
thank
you all right they're in the tunnel
right
now oh it moves on its own oh that's it
I guess it moves faster if we're closer
to it me oh
guys heal all right we're he heal
[Music]
harder get that Sentry down
yeah they might come from behind us so
careful yeah we got to be
careful I'll tell you if you're getting
shot at
M from above from above above above
above yeah thank you it's going to be
all D just like everyone's a
Healer okay they're up
here down here too nice
this is way better than defending oh did
you die
no no not
again got him oh nice good job herb we
got revenge BB needs healing I need
healing we're almost there to the first
stop
okay
uhoh we must push littlee healing you
K
[Music]
the O we have
MP all right I'm just going to sacrifice
myself
no stay safe she will we we need
you watch up for the big
bullet the biget
I need
healing healing I'm going to running
GG's in him careful I'm going to die
G oh I'm dead now hi
dead healing yeah yeah yeah yeah thank
you just in time in time it's fight
between you living and
dying he
he good job
Elizabeth I'm not there yet yeah can I
got if you can too thank
you all right now we're talking let
those big bullets what's up with the big
bullets oh crap
bomb they're doing bombs now
watch out watch out watch out bomb Strat
I see I keep forgetting we're blue team
yeah me too so used to Red oh someone's
flanking us from behind it's a SC behind
behind oh I'm from above and above
behind and above above and
below nice nice
nice good jump good jump jump good jump
good jump good jump he good good good
thanks
I'm dead yeah so locked in ah ah it
hurts it hurts it hurts oh yeah yeah
yeah nice
good above
usone oh the mines not the
mines okay I'm on my way I'm on my
way okay careful they're above us to I
was on to kill
above below
yeah who stop pushing the
car I think we might have a spot they're
behind us oh okay okay I'm want to shoot
my gun I'm on my
[Music]
way how's it
going are you dying long way to
run we trying to get together with
everybody make it over there all right
all right okay we're on our
way I try to heal you thank you okay
it's a fight between healing and
dying indeed it is it always
is can I shoot through the payload come
back a bit come back a
b okay you're good you're good exploded
but you're thanks for the warning I'm
following you I'm just making sure yeah
we can get them from
[Music]
angle oh I saw that coming that was that
was another bomb another bomb another
bomb another bomb go down watch bom lot
Get Wrecked
Revenge okay watch the bomb yeah nice
one Shi I'll
you I have you thank you thank
you get the car moving keep an eye
behind yeah yeah they might flank us
anytime got here in the front in the
front we're Ving behind
you
spine make sure
everybody no it's
fine make sure we heal heal the
happies okay we're good we're good stay
behind M go down watch out for bombs
watch out the front B is in the front
Okay B is in the front how big thing is
the rang they behind
us Sho
them oh God I need
help healer look at this we need a
Healer we need healer job okay I'll heal
in the
front thing okay there's a spy okay I'm
healing you kill him what do they what
do they pretend to be K nice got him
nice
o okay let's r
o okay keep an eye am I going to survive
this you shall survive and as long as
you know how to love I know you'll stay
alive ping this we got to just be around
it yeah
yeah us behind us get the medic got to
get the medic oh
yeah
nice
oh
beautiful draw
[Music]
36 it's fun when you
win got to defend
now okay we're defending again let's see
how this goes okay defending be hard mhm
it is
uh
hello I'm going to change the game mode
one more time but if you guys want to go
into the other chat for this round just
do whatever oh sure okay
chaos ohop
[Music]
hello hello let's have a
party
part come on good game good game Big G
good
game how to defend
successfully I'm overcharged wait let me
just watch a 1 hour video real quick I I
I looked up like a guide and was like
how to play this one it was a 2our long
video guide oh my God that's a try
Harding everage Team Fortress no I
didn't watch it I mean
it's that's a that's a try Harding video
I cannot believe you try hard
yeah is everyone of a different
game oh okay okay
yeah can you in this game Guess while
we're switching game
we
[Music]
each let's
go take him down I know come out guys
come on blue team are we playing again
team death match I'm a tank I need
healing I'll do this of
course oh oh I don't know where I am
team death mat am
lost I'm a little bit
lost might go the other way by the way I
die
already hey I love these sounds is a
sniper
where I get
itow my how could this happen you've
been revenged by
shooting I don't have for this actually
can we shoot through
them you shoot through people like your
teammates all my teammates eat my
missles the bullets go through the
blocked invisible wall oh don't think so
okay run run run run we're dying oh wait
is this the new game I'm sorry no no no
it's not yet oh
it's
ohing okay
oops how do I get out of here we're
[Music]
lost oh this way I thought you were my
friends what you guys prefer to stay all
in voice chat or still separating for
teams I think separ
PE okay okay okay yeah otherwise it' be
too chaotic and we wouldn't be a over
everyone SC
yeah but every once in a while getting
together is fun
too in
between you're going down we going to be
in a team again oh wait there's no video
oh my God yeah where's the
video it's raining I don't like this oh
we're free of the same uh character
that's
fine oh no wait how can I change uh
comma we can go over there oh hi
short what's up
losers same team now stop oh so what up
Withers
yeah voice CH te going into the second
voice
okay two medics okay not bad oh totic is
nice sometimes I could be so what's
what's this game again what's his game
mod oh yeah sorry this is King of the
Hill R blue team what this is what kill
the hill blue King of the Hill King of
the Hill what do we do yeah yes so
whoever it's like a control Point type
of map ah I see I see okay where is the
where's the hill I'm on a hill uh I
think you should be able to see it in
the map oh I see map map uh I mean like
through I think I see it now sorry you
gave me a this you gave me a FR what the
frak Yeah I'm sorry I was on the
[Laughter]
hill
ouchie they suddenly appeared out of
nowhere my oh I need healing oh thank
you you're
welcome now you're healing me
fire fire like
fire start of fire there's so many fire
songs in Hol life hey fire oh I can't
walk into the razor
blades no got interesting better not
blades careful with
those we
learn we leave a we learn ow we live and
learn G and we die and we learn I feel
like I learned most from
dying that is so
deep whoa I'm on
fire fire light the
fire firear fire I need
healing every
day oh God they took the Bas it does you
have to go to the cabinet in the base
there's like a medicine cabinet yeah
yeah wait is this the wrong
room fire I need healing they're still
maybe the enemies will heal me oh you
guys don't have a medic huh I tell I
think La is a medic right yeah yeah I am
oh okay g c
ow I tell you what they're on the hill
when you guys say nice medic pick does
that mean good job on killing the medic
is that a slang for this
game nice medic pick hey stop trying to
Bonk me hey yes okay I mean Medics are
always pretty popular nice good
job he no you should heal yourself
you're dying I'm can to heal myself I
don't know probably not at all find
there's Med packs like on the map in
certain places you see like little
Dam he was
beefy say you guys can take the point
nice nice where's where are we wait
where's the point oh there's a going
that way and then if you make a left
into the building I didn't see anything
cron huh ah yes exactly if you turn left
in there the point oh you guys going
toward their spawn their spawn are we
camping spawn camping are not on purpose
oh that was close going the right way
watch WR way no you're going the right
way going the right way there's somebody
right behind me I
see you got
saw I guess you didn't see that
coming guys I need to someone we're on
fire got the thank
you oh can you heal me too yeah yeah
yeah AE heal
when L turn on your AOE
heal no AOE
heal there is if for engineer he has
like a little kit he can put down AOE
healing I'm going to
[Music]
get Dam
ni got him for got don't snipe me don't
snipe me get the sniper spawner he's
running he's running he's running don't
forgive him are we controlling it need
damage uh if you look at the top yet so
if the timer's going down oh ah uhoh
that's how it works we're not
controlling oh so now they they're
getting it they're getting it oh you
guys still have it you still have it if
it's blue you guys got it
[Applause]
[Music]
my G always kills
me scout
scout roasted Phoenix
down has been fried I walked right into
all them we just need 16 more seconds
nice no that they have a minute left
until oh wait so are they in control of
it now or we yeah yeah they are are
they're in control they have to hold it
for another 50 seconds a we only need 16
seconds yeah yeah if you guys get it and
you hold it for 6 seconds and you win
that
one GG is dead
nice oh my
kills okay stick close to the base so
that we can secure it faster Miss ends
yes wait it's not going down got it you
guys have to cap there it's going it's
going oh let's go it's ow the fireal get
the fireal get the fireal and the
Minun wait that's not
teams's back's back okay she's dead it's
fine we
[Music]
won
y this one I'll let you guys do best of
three see who wins yeah be ice work
team good
luck thank you we won once we will win
again I
believe confidence is
good taste
ofum have confidence exactly tastes like
r o did you have why you mentioning
risoto I don't know did you eat it
recently no but I'm in the mood for God
no capturing at this time what the heck
well actually I think I made something
that you could eat FAA recently the
other day I just got to supplement the
milk with water which is also
possible the Austrian caspr noodle it's
like what is that it's like
a I've never heard of it it's good I'll
show you how do we capture this things
oh you stand on
it for how long uh there there should be
like a little timer that pops up what
what color are we shooting what what
sorry there's somebody behind you oh I
see I was like what's going
on someone behind me
huh was there really someone behind me
there was there
was screw you don't
worry oh we got it yeah nice
nied
it you guys yay thanks
you very
welcome red is the enemy
Al is thank you for the
reminder
oh
nice nice medic pick good job good job
behind us GG she's so fast nice oh
somebody through here spe going
give me something to
shoot
enemies where are you here we don't need
enemies no the fire they're up here
they're on side they're side there side
here oh
wow it's okay medic
meta I I
died
uhoh still doing it
yes oh okay yes oh okay no shooting for
behind me it's it's just there's so much
blood on the field makes me think we're
all covered in blood makes us red it's
true you look like the enemy oh God I'm
dying oh close I'm like fighting two
people out here oh I'm dead okay oh
thanks for you they're around the side
there we go
[Music]
k wow that was a
[Laughter]
a they got some ant I got control point
is being
captured no no oops God please no oh
gosh I lagged and I walked into a wall
lag oh gosh what is happening with my
game it's I'm stuck lagging I am stuck
oh we're all stuck I'm stuck I cannot
walk stop the timer oh oh there's a
there's a guy that killed me because I
was walking into a wall oh no no let me
move okay lag is over no not over no are
you still lagging yeah I was crazy
lagging very much
lagging
oh oh what's happening now I cannot
move me too ends in seconds are we are
we I can't move is this bad for us or is
it bad for them we're winning oh okay
but it feels a little bad because of the
lag
true oh oh now I can oh I can't move I'm
having trouble I wonder is it lagging on
their side
too surely it
is I feel like we we deserve it don't we
we're doing so well
yeah we do oh oh I can't
move uhoh over time oh okay over time uh
oh it doesn't say that for me uh oh can
I get timed out interesting server is
not responding oh no yeah the server is
bad for me is it it's making you feel
sick cuz it's kind of making me feel
sick too yeah I I can't I'm just going
to wait at the not going to attempt to
move
yeah it's making me motion sickness go
back oh no I don't even get motion
sickness sometimes usually I
mean no I got kicked out of the game and
it says the server is not responding I
can tell yeah it's definitely wait it's
I feel like it's responding again fing
in there it's responding it's responding
now it responded for sure red team is
responding go k go h
I believe all right all right all right
all right all
right I'm
[Music]
dominating oh nice one ammo we did it
all right stand on the spot yes more on
it it will go f
recapture nice nice nice it seems like
pyro was not for me it's doing it's
doing it again no no why why would it's
our turn
okay
yippe nice we got Ned man we should
reset the server
somehow
[Music]
maybe your call was Heavy I can
tell come pick me up I'm sick oh man and
I'm in second
place good good
game GG
yeah oh that was
laggy wait a
minute GG oh I get it now okay
weirdo never too late never too
late never too late never too late is it
still isn't it still lagging should we
like maybe I can't move at all yeah yeah
it's lagging lag has been really bad can
we restart somehow yeah it's but us is
not lagging it's just stopped yeah oh
it stopped the server stopped uh before
it kicked us out it disconnected and now
now it's just nothing's going yeah crony
also got kicked out and for me and
Herbert's just like moving us back and
forth move right
now I see okay yeah um I think I could
reset the server or also I mean we
pretty much played for the amount of
time we were going to play oh yeah true
Did
We that was so fast it was fun
[Music]
[Applause]
I learned a new if anything we learned
how to differentiate colors which
is did we learn that we're not colorf
you guys feel better about it yeah those
[Applause]
fun thank you I'm looking forward to G's
mod thank you yeah
yeah thank you so much yeah good luck
with the rest of your Marathon you still
got so many games up
[Music]
ahead see you thank
[Applause]
[Music]
youe oh is she like taking a break for
half an hour or so who
is the next thing happening in like half
an
hour ended a bit earlier than I thought
thought we were going for like 45 more
minutes that was fun and good that I did
like play beforehand
uh well well in the end I'm surprised
like pyro worked well better against the
bots so I thought oh I just I just need
to believe in myself but
against the girls somehow pyro was
really the worst
choice but yeah then I wanted to try out
sniper because in other games I feel
like I'm pretty good at sniping in like
GTA and so
on but uh it's because there's so much
going on and they're moving so much it's
difficult and they get so close and then
obviously I can't snipe them and and I
didn't know the maps well enough to be
sniping I guess
[Music]
but once I get the
minigun it's
on yeah was more fun when I was actually
killing
people that's the lesson I have
learned I think um I would have time to
read super chats but at the same time I
want you guys to watch am Miss rest of
her Marathon I don't know did she like
is she ending the stream or is it
continuing in the same
stream I'm not
sure cuz if it's continuing then I'll
like move you over there in 15 minutes
Counter Strike
two I don't think she can play too no um
uh if it's like it's all valve games and
if it's like you know if they get
permission beforehand then it should be
fine especially if it's games from the
same company then it's
usually with something like this this
yeah not a problem so I assume she's
doing one long stream mhm okay she is
continuing all right then I think I want
you guys to go and support her stream
and and the rest of the marathon if you
have time and tomorrow I'm continuing
Zelda which I'm so addicted to I'm so
excited to play more Zelda oh my God
it's been so much fun so uh hope you
guys will be there for more Zelda we're
starting around the same time I
think more zeld I'm I'm so excited I
realized I missed a heart piece in the
desert somewhere so I got to go pick it
up hoping for more TF2 H yeah I don't
know like maybe someday play against you
guys publicly but I don't know how that
would
work it's it's an all right game I don't
know like to me they all feel the same
like paladins and OverWatch and this
game they all feel the same uh I can't
really tell the difference
so anything is fine I normally don't
play FPS games but every once in a while
it's okay especially for a collab like
this I'm not wrong right thank
you gasp how dare
you paladins with Al my voice back yeah
I will forever have am voice pack in
Paladin so it will always have a special
place for me in my heart I will always
be able to hear her voice and
flex she's talking to me personally
directly towards me
yeah yeah
yeah Gmod no Gmod is like 4:00 a.m. my
time and I'm just uh I thought it's it's
good enough to just participate in one
because a lot of the other members are
participating in the later ones
especially like uh people residing in
Japan they're joining in on the later
ones I think so it evens out it balances
out yeah the ailia Watson talking to
me what am I going to eat now for this
dinner I'm going to make soup out of
those caspr noodle that I offered fora I
think I can I could legit make that into
vegan uh dish because it's bread wait oh
no cheese damn it well well there's
vegan cheese so bread vegan cheese and
then the milk can be changed it's just
the milk just makes the bread soggy so
you can form it into dumplings so the
milk can be changed to water in the in
the
recipe and then it's just like salad and
stuff salad is
fine yeah yeah yeah yeah oh yeah I could
host my own server sometime for you guys
I
guess soy milk yeah soy milk would work
exactly yeah she probably knows how to
vegan ify things I forgot about soy milk
cuz I don't really like it no no
but as far as I know as long I as I as
long as I am the
host uh like only if I'm no chill oh my
God you don't have to
spam it's not like I'm doing it right
now at this very moment oh my God
chill I was told that only the uh the
host would see that so if I'm the host
then I see your
IPS but
anyway it's not like I'm going to it's
not like I'm so hooked on this game that
tomorrow I'm going to start my own
server for you guys no no no no no no
no okay I'm going to see you guys
tomorrow for Zelda thank you guys for
watching uh sorry for sucking at FPS
games I tried my best had fun with herb
too on our one onone learning
time thank you see you I'm going to send
you to the advertisement screen again
all the links are in the description if
you're curious about the voice packs the
second myth voice pack comes with uh
like an extra uh table round talk thing
which is pretty long on its own which is
like CH chatting about the past four
years and recent uh things and this and
that so I recommend getting both of the
voice packs they're really good they're
like you know not solo voice packs
they're full myth voice pack with a cool
lore a cool
story yeah and cool
artwork yeah yeah yeah Link in the
description here you go byebye have a
nice evening I'm going to col a smoothie
she was here the whole time
w
[Music]
what did I not say
it in German we say be
[Music]
also look at look at the new emotes not
emotes but the new badges there's four
year member badges now they're golden
look at them Flex Flex
[Music]
it they've been dipped in liquid gold
n
[Music]