[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
I am God
I shall guide you
[Music]
follow the light
follow kiwawa
#woke
#yolk
Hallelujah
Hallelujah indeed
since I am God
I normally you know have an echo a
Reverb on my voice by default
but for you guys
I will turn it off
yeah
oh my God I'm suddenly so ungodly who
would have known that you know God
God is made up out of 60 Reverb
40 is you know a lot of other things but
six percent is the Reverb
um
how disappointing man
[Music]
wow holy music uh thankfully it stops
when I tap out
[Music]
let me
was that too loud guys
[Music]
okay sounds very holy yeah
holy moly a game fitting for a God don't
you think
oh oh thank you for the memberships
thank you tad bit loud okay uh
oh look at all those people this is what
earth looks like from my point of view
uh
[Laughter]
we turned it down
maybe even more
what do you think now oh it's still kind
of wild isn't it although I'll just turn
it up down and OBS a bit and
I love that
okay
so I thought this game would be
relatively short turns out it's longer
than short
um but it's still short it's like medium
um we're still in beta oh uh are we
though is this game released
is released right
could you make the game full screen you
want it in full screen
my my okay
it's released out uh well I got a cold
thank you Humanity for giving kiwawa
code that's why it's beta beta
it's better because it's beta beta but
yeah
code thank you soon
where do we put chat I wonder where
there will be space okay you want you
want the full screen here you go you're
welcome
is it better now
yeah okay
released a couple weeks ago okay okay
yeah I saw like a little bit of footage
uh it looks fun
um need a little bit of a short game to
mess around with so why the hell not
don't know if I'll finish it but I've
said that about many games before that I
ended up finishing
uh even though it was not expected
neither by me nor by my viewers
I wanna eat another Cherry did you guys
know it's cherry season
um
I I
I'm a genius for creating cherries
um
okay let's go story mode whatever that
means
tell me what was that
why not cat why is dog a god um because
dog the other way around is gone
laughs
I awoke one morning to find I was a dog
I Heard a Voice inside my head and it's
not the meows from smoothie who is a cat
ah
a dog right now
um
good morning
we have been waiting
there is work to be done
you must guide the people to the light
but that is death isn't it
oh but they also came out of the
light which kind of also makes sense
because you know you you were dead
before you're born
anyway let me turn off my Reverb basic
controls uh the wheels need to move
press space to jump cool wow dog
like a sheep herding person uh turn what
turn
um for now we just
go straight is that what we're doing
again I heard the voice
well will you not lift up your voice
how else will you guide them
placing turn commands the turn command
allows you to turn to point the people
in a specific Direction hold Mouse and
push wsd in a desired direction to use
your command cool okay okay
Mouse and wsd right
on wherever I am
what how how
is it where I am it starts doing that
okay thank God I didn't do it one time
earlier because I was trying to with the
mouse
I went ah ah
[\h__\h]
okay that was uh we lost some people but
I think we're gonna be losing many more
and then here we go right okay I love it
tutorial but not too many
it should have a counter somewhere
telling me how many people I've lost
okay
off day blue after blue up into the sky
and into the light can I join
stage coupling up up and away
[Music]
okay is there
wow so this is what we're gonna be doing
we're gonna teach the people where to go
and get a lot of um sacrifices
Goldie retrieval yeah okay
huh I'm not a golden retriever though
I'm obviously a Shiba Inu
holy Richard fell oh what's there's a
golden person there
there's a golden person
a gleaming figure floated in the air
behold this is Goldie
Goldie is all that people desire and
value and worship
Beyond even my reasoning
lead Goldie along with them into the
light
do so and you will be rewarded uh will
he just join me when I oh God
can I go up though this
oh this can they go they can go down
right but can they go
no no they can't
they can't can we build a human bridge
wait
what's up
you're ready creating a big problem for
me here
what
[Music]
try the other way okay
um uh
because maybe because there is a
question mark that will teach me how to
do that or this specific oh God the
specific pile of ah okay they can climb
here on these blocks okay wonderful
should I try to bring these people back
on it they can't I think they're lost
it's okay at least they're not a lot of
them are not even falling down
Goldie descended and walked among the
people
[Music]
Goldie mine stays completed okay they
didn't they didn't really tell me about
the blocks but maybe the question mark
uh would have taught me
um
go next go next
golden rewards collect gold needs to
unlock various rewards visit the goldie
rewards we need to see the rewards
you've earned and to check your progress
toward future rewards okay
ah you guys keep on mentioning Lemmings
but I have never heard of the game
before
hello guys
Sam's cute Halo Ryan
oh God
you already said it that way I heard the
voice inside my head ah this is a too
big of a fall huh oh [\h__\h] you need to
fear for them nor you need not to fear
for them nor mourn their loss you heard
that guys
though their bunnies are lost their
Spirits persist that's kind of sad
because I imagine their souls being lost
forever and not being able to be
released because the death they they've
lived is in a place like this neither of
nor Heaven somewhere in between
and thus
it will be lost forever
and soon they will walk through the door
once again are you you tell me they just
keep respawning okay
okay I like that part
nice okay well done uh okay we uh what
about what about Goldie though
far from a safe height if people the
people can fall safely from height of up
to two blocks any higher than that I
don't think I can lose the Goldie
and they will perish but have no fear
they will soon walk back for the door
hey I'm scared of losing Goldie
oh [\h__\h]
I can't even jump that high but I'm God
wow wow let me uh create the path before
because I don't I don't want to lose
gold uh wait what am I doing
left left left
left and then up
and then
uh
no too early
but there's a tree Okay so
uh-huh
and then go to Goldie and then go
oh sometimes it's confusing me the
direction because in my head when
something's right doesn't seem to be
right in the game okay left and then I
would say
we probably have to go through the hole
flatting before doing anything is the
smartest way to do it isn't it and we go
down here
wasn't there enough gold at all yeah oh
God okay this should work though
we go here
right that should work and then we go
pick up the Goldie Locks oopsie
no get rid of this one
and then
uh-huh
what is this question mark
don't worry ah thank you if you lose a
gold you're otherwise fail to guide the
people as you wish simply retry from the
pot oh so you do have to kind of restart
okay
that's why I'm guiding you
because I know the way
trust me I don't want to restart
so we make it smart I think this should
work okay and last but not least
uh here let's go down
fall safely guys be careful one after
never maybe even hold your hands
you don't wanna why not
there's nothing loot about holding hands
trust me we got the golden
and we go down one more level or two
more levels actually the goldie is huge
it's like two times the size did I just
hear a monkey oh I guess well humans are
monkeys so yeah that's one what you hear
sometimes okay come down here be careful
don't break your kneecaps or anything
you know follow follow turn to monkey
using
worship iduru kiwawa of course
yes
I think this game is easy will there be
more difficult Parts because if you just
look at it calmly
[Music]
then it's pretty easy what the hell
hey
yeah we need two times speed but I think
normally the funny thing is you do it
while they're walking and you lose a lot
of people maybe
but I don't want to do that when there's
a goalie involved
they just throw him down
the the this little stage I don't want
that no
[Music]
yeah they'll keep interesting
introducing more mechanics fast ah there
we go you can now use shift to
accelerate the flow of time there you go
perfect
the snap
switch hitter ooh switches
hmm
what what kind of switch
oh we start oh okay we start here
uh well let me check out the switch
don't die what is this
people switches
guide enough people onto one of these
switches and something interesting will
happen however the fact will only last
as long as there are people on the
switch
okay now I understand I understand they
can climb that so all right I would say
they can they can climb this right so we
need to uh down here
then up here
then
ah then over there
and we go right we go through this hole
just like me do just what I'm doing uh I
got a left
up oh
wait we'll have we'll have to go back
but won't that be a problem
there's glass yeah what there's no glass
in here since I can go through right
I know there's glass up here and I know
the the switch will open it up
yeah but try and see if it works now and
I'll I'll try it here what if I do it in
the middle of you guys
[Laughter]
um
a what
[Music]
and then I don't think that what then
well I don't know okay we'll test it out
a minute I mean it has to because
there's no other way
okay uh right and back oh but if I do it
here then they will never even attempt
so I have to do I have to place it
once they already passed so I'll I'll
I'll I'll wait for that I'll wait for
that
and then and place it live and then I
come here and I'll place this one live
too I guess
uh
yeah I have to I have to and then go up
um and then go this way and then go
it's like
and then
yeah and then go up
um I suppose okay I'm gonna test it out
you're not sure
why not
well we are going to start here right
okay
the way he climbs
he's a he's a big Golden Monkey come on
uh once they reach here I need to
quickly place up a shift yeah okay
they're coming they're coming they're
coming
baby
okay and
then
are with me and then we go up let's go
let's go
yeah
I think I said you don't know about this
idea but I think it's perfect come on
look at this oh
he loves people
where did this one come from
how did what where's he go
oh maybe there was no space in the
middle so he went I don't know
[Music]
that's why you got God exactly that's
why you guys are praying to me every
night
because live concert when you'll be like
oh they're all wearing Aussie t-shirts
because those clearly brightly colored
t-shirts I think they're all going to a
concert yeah the whole life
said
is there orange t-shirts I'll see yellow
I see like salmon
I think I saw yeah I think I see orange
Skies
thank you
free camera you can press F to pause the
game and view the current trial
via a freely controllable camera
yeah okay it's a reward oh I don't know
if I want that
jump start will we teach them how to
jump
my puppets
okay it's getting more complicated
to the end of the world for you thank
you Carefree on the way to La yeah we go
to camera
I will guide you I'm your tour guide
just follow the uh the holy
holy moly circle on my head
we Grant you a new power
well we'll fight the power jump will
make the people leap into air
take it and use it well
acquiring new commands oh I get the
command to I get I get to place it
press left Mouse to pick up new commands
I take I take
wow wow
okay how do I place this one oh God the
people are already coming uh
uh what how do I I switch okay
um hi guys how did you decide to make
that turn there oh oh uh oh God okay
um okay we would go up I think and we
collect him oh there's already the
lighting oh there's two different
oh
okay we can already bring one home
uh but we'll have to place the
the jump yeah okay
and the turn oh my God so many people
are dying
okay
and then there's like one more jumping
platform there
does this work
and they have to jump to get him
oh oh can you guys just quickly
uh
wait uh
oh they have to jump earlier
yep okay okay okay
uh uh jump oh my God
okay be careful jump jump jump yo
oh
is he that double yeah he's crowd
surfing he's crowd surfing I want a
crowd surf too uh okay yeah gold gold is
there only one seems so okay now uh you
guys
uh no no don't jump no
left
I'm doing it live now but it's not not
ideal
um
no more need for jumping here no money
oh God
no no no no no need to put jump in here
maybe maybe yes maybe yes
yeah they can make it out loud make them
jump too oh there we go
they're using this Crossing is a little
bit dangerous with the amount of people
but it's working isn't it didn't we get
everything everyone yeah
stage completed
easy easy peasy
one more tutorial I think crap I I was
just talking about that okay okay we're
really going to a concert here
there's two golden mans there
oh dear
oh dear what is this it looks
complicated
uh turn and jump
here I noticed a much larger pillar of
light oh indeed
onward now lead them into the light and
to us you come as well it is time we
meet oh
I am God and I meet with God God God
bless what's going on here
we shall Grant you a new power only this
time the power is within you the power
to dive into the people
oh
you have to join them because I can't
really climb but I can't jump that high
either use it now use as well okay
uh how take me
take me
what
oh wait teach me
diving what
jump and then press space again to dive
into a nearby human into diving into you
move between humans with wsd and press
space again to jump right okay that
sounds kind of difficult oh my God okay
uh
okay take me
um
okay should be should be uh easy no no
uh here and good luck I guess uh because
I don't know what the [\h__\h] is gonna
happen
jump here maybe
oh they swim
whoa
[Music]
yeah I think this looks good
eh
what was that does it open other things
too
[Music]
there we go
like Hallelujah good for them
[Music]
yes that is the way the path is almost
open uh-huh uh-huh let's take care
let's take care of them oh wait they're
already
ah all they need is a jump
here
oh that's a ooh that's a dangerous one
never mind jump last minute last second
because you got a little Gap there
actually they didn't even need to jump
over there huh
okay
and here
I guess they should jump early to pick
up the golden guy and then jump again
yeah
yeah okay okay
we're not quite done yet okay let's go
let's go I think
I think we did it
all right yeah it's opening up it's
opening up
die yeah yeah
Goldie you are under my holy Divine
protection
time passed who knows how long
I awoke in an unfamiliar place
all the humans said I already dropped
and they're angry at me
it looks like it
uh or it's the people that are led to
the light
[Laughter]
I heard the voice inside my head
ah you finally made it
wait that reminds me of
huh
portal or or uh the other one uh
not portal
do he recognize them
yeah hey you're finally awake yeah that
one though
they're the people you led into the
light there you go okay okay I don't
want to talk to the ones that I didn't
lead into the light this is where the
light delivers them
it's [\h__\h] empty is this Heaven it's
[\h__\h] the [\h__\h]
I'd rather be walking all the time
because and jumping over there and
respawning because that seems more fun
than to just stand around here
I had a thought what is this place the
voice somehow heard me
these are the testing grounds it is time
for the trials to begin let's start
[Applause]
trials
trials that you will oversee
the people lack what only your guidance
can offer so true so true for real for
real
you will bring them here to us
I had I had more questions voice
who are you how are you inside my head
treats please can we do a walk
don't pick up my poop
I want to pee on that tree
you know just dog phones
answers given
of course where are our manners
think of us as this a blue core
we are the first to watch over you heed
our instruction well
now come let us waste no more time
take the first step prove you are worthy
it feels kind of dark man concerning
bye
whoa
Awakening
a statue-like object prepared before me
oh I did everything no wait that's no
that's the upcoming chapter
sequence one Awakening there's 19
Goldies
I don't know if I'll always care for
when for picking them all up but
we'll try
this music
Crossroads hmm
oh
I found myself somewhere new this is the
place of Awakening both of new powers
and of understanding as always you are
to guide the people to the light they
will do as you command they seem quite
fond of you
we now grant you your first new power
jumping one high jump will cause the
people to LEAP even higher into the air
[Music]
wait let me pick it up guys wait
I need to pick it up first
oh [\h__\h] oh oh [\h__\h] oh oh that kind of
works one even went even higher did you
find the golden one oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
here oh God don't lose the golden one
I think I think that's okay okay yes
there's a light there's the light go
towards the light guys oh thank God
see I wanted to always land everything
out but I didn't but we're good well we
were forgiven
okay you guys also jump
when you go straight through this one
and ah
Maybe
and uh jump uh not here
should be fun
ripped off no dog is okay dog is gone we
all know that
and thus once again I have enlightened
everyone's path let's go
it was only one Goldie
what
first what
when did that
yeah you can now we try to travel
without having to reach all your
comments okay thank you excuse me no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no wait what the [\h__\h] what if I say
something where is it where is he where
is he
I don't I don't see him
foreign
[Music]
okay okay these ones are already going
uh the button
how do you
I guess I could try
can they go up there no okay
I mean the level is called Crossroads
does that mean something to me
jump is not high enough but here here
maybe if they jump again can they jump
look here
yeah they could uh but let's do a normal
jump
don't you think
okay uh but then somebody still gotta
pick up him it will be fine I'll pick
him up
um
[Music]
is this okay are they still fine yeah
yeah okay okay they're standing what
does that mean where does he spawn
in the middle
is he in there yeah okay
they're flying yeah
why did the chicken cross the road the
road costume first yeah
[Music]
oh
interesting
[Music]
next week ones oopsie what
what did I do
here loop the loop is next
a loop loop the loop
that Loop okay I see looping potential
we hereby Grant you a new power
long jump will cause humans to LEAP
further than usual oh dear okay
looping a leaping further okay
um
probably here
jump can they jump
over there and then do
okay
wait we're out right now I only have
long jump
they don't make it okay okay we'll have
to get closer get rid of that
go there
go up here
oh wait oh [\h__\h]
it's uh can we do both or do we have to
go down first go right go up and then
long jump
[Music]
okay
we want to go right we want to go down
we want to step on this
and then do a long jump
oh
okay okay okay so far so good
mmm
number this one oh wait uh oh that's
that's too far that's too far
it's not
I miss I I underestimated you guys
okay
and that opened another opportunity no
up another opportunity for us
they can actually make that jump too
wonderful
and now
um possibly we don't even need the
middle sections anymore I don't know
let's lead
no no no wait guys wait wait wait wait
uh hi left
lost him
uh
[Music]
I wanna redo can I redo
[\h__\h] ah
[Music]
um
okay let's do let's get at least do the
one shall we try to know how to reach
right now
uh because I pressed T and it doesn't
work right now
maybe at the end uh
uh okay this is activated again our flow
is
starting again
um
they will come back here
no
[Music]
uh and do a long jump here and then
they're looping but
it
but but but
do I just then eventually at some point
give up the loop
and change it because as long as they're
looping for a little while these these
uh walls will stay up right so we could
potentially
go this way straight now
do a long jump here I think
wait what what what
oh which seems enough but no we gotta do
the long jump earlier so that they pick
him up but it's kind of hot yep
okay we shall retry
I cannot accept this this awesome is
trippy it's it's a good OST I think
um well my arrows are already set
um
but I did something wrong
what did I do about him maybe I just
pick no wait
uh first of all
uh why don't we just um send it like
this straight away why did I go down
right up and just go right right
this way
and then this goes here thank you
for the minutes thank you wow I think
first let's just create the path again
okay for safety
uh this was fine
Liz comes back okay
okay
and now
now this would be looping
which is good we'll we would just I
would assume Loop it for a while show me
just before I do this one let's do the
other one first because that one makes
sense to me no nah
if I just now create a group of people
that goes left up right and this way
then I see no issue
right
[Music]
okay okay okay go go up
that's already enough uh
straight again again I'm gonna mess with
the flow
but wait what they die wait wait I
didn't create the I
uh uh what did I do to eventually uh
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait
is he stuck in the loop okay as long as
he's stuck in the loop I mean that's
okay but uh uh uh uh
[Music]
is already [\h__\h] up
forgot the last up near the thing
ah this wall here should I just ah right
I should have sent them
straight up
okay
create the
huh overall path
again
yeah but okay uh why do I do it while
they're doing that uh here that jump
wasn't that too
two why is that here
but the most recent command stained
right so this should have worked
apparently
that jump was on point okay ah
okay
then I go
uh let's go
go go
oh just it's getting difficult indeed
the thinking
yeah okay the problem was that
I'm picked up because this is too early
that's okay
that one's already there so yeah
now he's in
he was walking Golden man walking now
Golden man is in the goal
foreign
[Music]
what is this uh why is this bar not
golden
because
looks like I got both I don't understand
oh wow three towers
okay we do turns and long jumps in here
think kiwawa think
we have three buttons we have three
dudes
oh wow
Let's test it out
let's go left first
I went out
and here we go app
and that will create what
ah what
[Music]
how does that help me I cannot even do a
high jump
that's okay maybe the other side should
be first
and maybe it's preparation for later
you guys
can you actually just like stop walking
and
gather here
now they don't stop walking do they
let's send
only one didn't make it Abby and me I
didn't make it either
okay
and we see what this does
creates the same thing does it
uh okay
ah well does it
this actually currently is looking
pretty good over there but we're losing
people we're losing people
left up climb
and and uh right and uh let's see what
that creates
it opens up that okay
is the long jump ah
[Music]
maybe maybe
um
maybe if I do the jump earlier
if I do the jump earlier will they land
on the platform
what they're dying they're dying
this is why the gods have forsaken the
humans
and now you're left with a with a dark
god
[Music]
um oh God oh God okay let's let's let's
go
let's do uh uh the buttons again and
then once both buttons
once both buttons are activated again we
can send them up here again make them
jump over there right right right
um
sounds like an improvement to me and
well you're you must be a dark person
how are they
how are some of the actually ending up
on the other side I guess they were like
pushed
pushed down there
by the crowd okay
let's let's send them left too because
there's plenty people there
and
um
thing is I can't get up without their
help let's send them up now
might be a little bit too early
okay and then and then and then uh the
jump maybe here
okay
are they dying when they fall down there
oh no a bit
[Music]
Okay jump with I will jump with you guys
yeah babe we're losing him we're losing
him because ah I'm stupid
we'll have to redo it anyway
[Music]
and then the problem is we're still we
still don't have this one so we'd have
to leave some boys down and then back up
again okay now I can do this
micro managing humans
let God Brew yeah okay well what was
that do we need that no
first of all
let's send them to the left
you guys
oh you're already activating that
oh no need for that though
too early for that
uh
make a loop on each button oh wait
like this oh
[Music]
sorry it took me a while to get there
I thought that wasn't uh possible
because Anna makes it kind of easy don't
you think
and thought we were in for a challenge
okay okay
and just use the whole what do you mean
use the whole
okay I think we did that so they're
looping right I don't have to send any
more people there
I think yeah they're looping fine okay
okay okay hole in the middle
I don't understand I'm I'm busy I'm busy
guys
okay okay let me go with you is this
okay is this okay is this okay uh it
should be okay it should be okay
you go get the golden man
I've got the other Golden man
okay okay I'm not done yet wait wait
wait
wait I'm not done game I'm not done I'm
done let me out what happened
[Music]
no no
no no no nothing I'm not done
[Music]
hey hats what why do I have to apply for
that
no leave me alone no
no ah
[Music]
okay Plenty
um
[Music]
we'll fix it we'll fix it we'll fix it
ah you mean the hole for me
was the hole for me guys
why are they climbing clapping boys
wait I can't join them
it's rude
I'm gone
I can't do that jump if that's what you
mean it's too high I'm just a dog okay I
mean I may be God but I'm just a dog in
the end
I can't even climb up this wall on my
own
in the middle Vlog there's a hole
I mean who the [\h__\h] would see that huh
sad it's working the way I'm doing it
I like my Loops okay
I just need to
speak faster
dude you're pretty fast on your own
why are they not ah it's not enough
people not enough weight okay
once they actually stop moving that's
interesting
I cannot not more more been to him
we gotta be fast now
[Music]
okay I'm already sending them now let me
go uh
[Laughter]
yay
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
how dare you how dare you suggest
something else you are just mere
chickens I am God
I got them all these are like my Golden
Globes
yeah I could ah you didn't even have to
do this one apparently you could just go
to this one straight away
goalie fish
goldfish I never had a goldfish before I
like in in movies and TV shows everyone
always has a goldfish
like even in Seinfeld probably Seinfeld
is the reason why people started having
goldfishes
I don't know we're probably can I do
this in the water anyway no probably not
I have to do it outside
oh this one I think we have to pick up
from the top
uh level
uh and actually yeah that one's pretty
low so I don't think we have to jump but
what did we do then and then we go left
and then then then then we do here maybe
a high jump how about that
yeah so far
first try no probably not
um but I'll try
I'll try it
oh this will have to be activated
will there be a ground platform then we
don't even have to jump I think
why is there another one on that side is
it like option you can do whatever you
want
oh no
no Captain only opens up the glass cage
[Music]
bye bye golden guys
oh that means
[Music]
make sure that some of the actually
uh go to the left or maybe we should go
to the left first
maybe no don't jump uh I mean okay sure
sure jump
uh because that like the sides
the height that they will
uh swim in and currently looks pretty
good
I can Loop them again on the button sure
but can we do it in other ways as well
okay platform has been why are you guys
dying just stop dying ah
oh okay
okay
uh and then when we get to it
it's closed
ah it's closed
[Music]
Union sent me some send me some people
yeah wait wait wait wait wait wait was
there a button here no no button here uh
let me Loop the ones that are over here
ah ah
stress
um okay Loop is created what are they
doing
don't question it don't question it
don't look
don't look what why are they oh oh there
ah okay
she do be climbing
let me go with you
hmm
and they're probably too low to pick him
up so we swim kind of high
will they lose height no it doesn't
doesn't look like it
okay
yeah no turn necessary here the top
level is kind of chill whoa look at them
swimming they're actually diving are
these really humans because I don't
think I can hold my breath this long
they might be mermaids half mermaids wow
I don't think this is humanity in this
game this is mermanity
okay now now we will have to redo it but
it shouldn't be too bad now that we have
our base for success
trust me trust me the merfolk girl okay
uh I cannot afford to lose people
let's see what did I
this is okay
[Music]
no wait
we want to go up first
or or not oh [\h__\h]
um I don't know
immediately send them to that side maybe
that's already enough I don't know yeah
[Applause]
well I'll send I'll send some extra
people
[Music]
but what about him
nobody gonna pick him up
wait what about what was I gonna do
about that one
let's join them
[Music]
oh God uh where's the where's the one
other golden guy
where's that
is he is he is he on is he looping
okay
as long as he's looping he is safe God
sure panics a lot well look at this
reason to panic but
we're still we're still going but oh by
the way there's so many that oh [\h__\h] uh
where
what what what what happened what the
the other big one is already going there
though what happened ah
oh
man
yeah that's that's better that's better
and we're about to lose the other Goldie
[Music]
um yeah let me just I just want to redo
it
ah
[\h__\h]
[Music]
I guess I guess I could reach right like
this okay
yeah yeah
this sounds not as bad as you make it
out to be
okay uh
that that is probably fine
but I want to go this way first
is my Loop intact let me check no it's
not
no problem I'll go with them
uh
why did I do that that's really
stressful
that's really stressful
wait let me do my Loop let me do my Loop
let me do my Loop let me do my Loop
uh
uh uh yeah uh no look look just look for
now because I'm scared
the other one
okay two two
golden guys
is wrong
[Laughter]
okay okay let's not have it to be be too
many people uh go straight move straight
go straight go straight
please please let the golden one survive
at any cost it's it's very important
oh [\h__\h]
I have my eyes on them I have my eyes on
them
okay the containers have an open
and we can we don't have to Loop here
okay okay stop the loop here too uh
[Music]
I think I did it I think I did it
I think I did it what do you think guys
did I do it did Lucas run I mean
something's wrong there but it's okay it
was looping okay it was weirdly looping
but when it Loops it Loops oh
[Music]
why ah
oh God oh God oh God oh God oh God oh
God
um
okay let's ignore the um golden guys
first
um
make one Loop happen first
[Music]
correct Loop
okay
I got jumps you don't need to look what
whatever whatever the jump is not long
enough if that's what you mean it's a
high jump this time
and that's that Loop is now actually
correct
okay okay delightful stream screams
thank you thank you Mr Star Fox
Adventures
[Music]
okay okay okay okay okay
um
these people if I just never send them
down and only
use the ones that go over to that way
to complete my mission
and then the loop should always be
intact
I think
are we trying to make you more like a
dog I don't think a dog thinks more than
me
I don't think a dog thinks more than me
okay look look look
they have arrived
ah
and now how do I make it so it stays
wait oh
wait right now it's okay right now it's
okay it stays and and and then the
golden guys are passing but it's uh yeah
there's a flow so we're good okay okay
the flow
pretty sure I did it that's it
look at this beautiful
Humanity example
swim towards the light is here
you can have a dog as you pet you can
give me belly rubs
and so thank you
that was quite something hey
oh that there it is there it is there it
is don't cheat me don't cheat me out of
my free golden guys
oh I'm so proud oh my God
switch effects switches viewed in F for
camera mode display what they activate
oh okay new reward
yeah yeah
yeah
very stressed out uh shall we shall we
do this one or should we just go stream
I guess let's do it why not
waterfall
your hats you want hats the hats all
belong to mean guys you don't get heads
oh only turning and swimming
okay
all this music
wow
no wait it's not that way it's that way
that way and then
they have to swim oh that's that's
actually kind of cool
oh
because I can't make them turn in the
water but they're on different levels
we'll have to
show
I don't want to lose people
perfect run let's go
we'll have to guide them
through the water without jumping
they will arrive there really
wait wait wait wait what's wrong what's
wrong
wrong direction I know I missed one one
I missed one
um but
could also lead people
now
okay they go pick him up [\h__\h] yeah it's
about time I think about the solution no
no that's okay that's okay
that's okay that's okay
we'll leave him there uh and the other
one the other one
um the other one uh uh uh
um uh
uh I would say the other one uh I have
an idea I have an idea have an idea but
it will be too late probably
no
here I think they will if they go back
wait wait no no no no no no wait no no I
don't wanna I don't want this to be no
okay no problem we can retry
I was gonna stop any more people from
walking in but it's okay it's okay
um
yeah once that guy was caught we would
also lead them
over there
and now oh we could actually
answering them in just to have less
stress directed at me Loop them right
okay I think you had to write it yet I
think so too
what's even happening that's why you're
not God because you are incapable of
understanding this grasping this with
your brain are they gonna come over here
yeah
wait no there's they're swimming
straight back oh wait on it
if I created an endless swing what
what what what what
uh some people
ah what what
we accidentally I understand I don't
understand we accidentally got one of
the golden guys but
I wait I think
um um
this way this way
yeah yeah and then this way I went
this way and
and this way and then this way
and then this way
oh
okay
uh dangerous amount of people though
because what if a little nah I mean
I should be okay
now we can go
yeah
yay
uh yeah
look them love let's go
this is fun
acceptable losses yeah you have to deal
with it I mean it hurt me a little bit
in the beginning but
sacrifices have to be made for the
golden guys you know they're worth it
it's like you know they're they're their
Rihanna's and the Lady Gaga's and the
Ariana Grande's of the society you know
it's okay you guys would like to be
sacrificed for them wouldn't you
happen is the latest true
airflow oh no
oh no
okay it's a puzzle oopsie that was a bit
too early but okay
um there's two golden guns can we go oh
but there's a lot of things to activate
too
where oh oh there's no wind here uh
maybe eventually we'll be able to make
some wind
wait there's no uh
wait there's a button here maybe that's
the wind turbine
[Music]
that should be it right any more Cliffs
you want us to dive off then sure no no
I'm just kidding I don't I want you guys
to be safe
wait is this also like
will this work if I don't have to do
like this whole like rectangle right I
can just send them there and only send
them back
to work
oh but oh
well okay never mind I'll do
um
well Theory it works but we'll send them
there
and then they'll go
[Music]
back
what did that activate it did activate
the turbine didn't it
whoa and then and then and then we can
go left here
and um
we'll go up here
we'll go right here sorry that you had
to die
would anything for kiwawa
um
they just go back and forth yeah okay
okay
all right
just continue going straight here and
then that makes a platform
[Music]
okay you guys keep on dying now I want
to think ahead because now we're talking
about the golden bullets okay
oh
[Music]
well
eh they can't make that jump
so I'll have to send them
foreign
off by creating the final path okay
well that was you guess I'll die
thank you forever hey I can meet jump
why can't you make the jump then
um
I'm gonna I'm gonna Loop some
people after all
is that enough people
should be okay
and then
you guys you guys
uh
we'll need a loop on on every
of these platforms
for safety let me add
God's sake
[Music]
oh it's back
hey
why is it why is that why is there not
enough people coming back to me
well these same people these people on
that platform okay like we don't need
any more people it's a perfect amount no
one's falling off
um
the white it seems pretty stable now
but yeah I didn't make this this Loop
yet
um but I don't think we need it
do we or maybe we do
maybe we do oh God okay
um
looping oh that's a lot of people over
there wow
okay and now
now now now
what now now we send
it through here right
uh
big brain kiwawa oh but how do we ah
they gotta go straight
but wait
how did they make that jump is that a
jump they can make when when the wind
comes first and then no platform I think
they can make the jump or no it has to
be it has to be like that
right
probably
I believe
wait there's no way
wiggle oh
what about the other one
oh that was close though what about the
other one
I mean they can't make that jump from
experience
what what up
oh
um
well let's test it out then because
we've already lost
um
what if
I send
some
straight over to this side
R.I.P I tried see they can't dump these
idiots
foreign
[Music]
the wind has to be first
so
wait can I
no I can't turn on the Wind platforms
well if I send them back
after the golden guy was retrieved
and we're done here
they he they have to go straight at the
point
but you know what I have to do
I would have to probably lead them one
level lower
so that they don't make too much of a
mess you see it
um
turn the platform to stand and try to
make them jump using a fan what what
what what what what what what what what
what what what what what what what
I do not understand what you just said
[\h__\h] this is the first time where I'm
really lost is it the switch then I'm
not supposed to actually turn on because
it's something
that will mess up this
um
[Music]
uh [\h__\h] hell what yeah that platform
but uh okay the way it looks currently
they wouldn't be able to get up wait
guys no no don't pick him up
I mean
no no
no
tomato
um let's let's let's let's let's let's
go straight first
ah God the God is losing confidence
right now
we shall make our Loops again except for
the last one how about that
we will make the loops mm-hmm
one Loop
finish
what was that
it's a good look right only that this
one over there we don't want I think
okay
it's kind of Cloudy up there uh
Eva cool to hurt or sterilize half of
them they've long since exceeded they're
carrying what the [\h__\h] are you talking
about
what
I don't think of my children like that
that's terrifying
okay
these ones these ones these ones
Loop is working
[Music]
and windows turned on
now
[Music]
why did we why don't we how does this
help me I guess they could jump straight
over there
I could wait
let's say we bring them
over here right
we pick up the first one
then we make a turn because there's no
way we can make that jump we make a turn
we go here we can't jump over there
either
see it how do we get him
ah from here
ah I do send people there but I don't
Loop them yet
and I don't want to create the platform
either yet so I have to send them over
here
right and then send them up
oh I figured it out I figured it out
guys I got it don't lose trust in God
just yet and then they'll do a little
jump here
and here
and then we turn around
we bring them back
and they go up and they go up here and
then they're back up here
and
but one of the platform actually
accidentally gets activated before
Goldie makes it is that possible
I'll just have to uh change this again
once they come back I'll change this
Arrow
to start looping and I mean I don't even
need to Loop
uh then let's jump over here and jump up
over the platform when they arrive here
and then that's done
gold is probably gonna be the first one
to press the button I would hope so yeah
okay
um
are my loops okay do they need people no
right uh so
so all I need to do is flick the switch
to go right here I think
um but I think it's uh wait now let's
not start with that one let's start with
the other one right I should start with
the other one
um
Let's uh let's just let's just uh in my
head repeat it one more time uh I I I
switch
so that they go right here
[Music]
and then
they pick him up they go up here they go
here
and I'll do an upturn here yeah then
they go here
they return
and then
what do I do with them
should I send them up
what uh uh up up
and and maybe Loop them for a while
here maybe should we just uh loop them
I tapped out
ah my
um oh my God okay
um
let me let me prepare a loop uh
you guys just uh stop just go away now
just go away go away go and too many
people too many people
whoa whoa whoa whoa let me let me empty
it we need but but it's better it's
better because at least that creates you
know some some time for me okay okay
I'll just do it I'll just I'll just do
it
um
oh
follow me
follow me we'll be fine I think uh yep
yep yep
get the guy they get the guy they got
the guy they got the guy
they got the guy um
we got the guy so we don't actually need
them anymore right these ones there's no
buttons to press
okay and
yeah
okay okay oh okay okay
um
and then we send them we send them uh up
uh
you guys this Loop is safe right okay so
give me a moment to think I need a
moment to think
and I don't want this many people uh
stop stop stop stop stop
stop
okay okay okay
and then we send them oh oh no okay here
here here I get it again
but we'll do it uh when Goldie is close
I don't know for what reason what
what ah
[Music]
ah
they're coming back they're coming back
they're coming back and now
should I make it look should I make a
loop I think I should make a loop oh
there's actually a solution videos what
uh we're cooking we're cooking
I'm so stressed out
and they press the button which creates
the thing uh so actually we don't need a
loop I just need to make this up I think
so they walk around and once they turn
around
the platform should be there right
okay
[Music]
but but we have fought everything
through okay so oh God uh oh God this
looks different to me is it still the
same thing yeah yeah okay
um okay guys follow me let's create
another time Loop hey
[Music]
we make the button Loops I I'm prepared
I'm mentally prepared for once to come
I think
[Music]
time Loop
time lap done skyscreen lesson that is
not true that cannot be true
then go straight now ah
I dare you I dare you
I dare you
okay
ah
oh no
[\h__\h] off [\h__\h] off no no
no no no no no no
[Laughter]
I guess I could have looped them oh well
um
ah
let me fix that before that happens
again
I mean right now I don't think it should
happen
oh wait okay
God has a really tough job oh yeah
I don't think I don't want to do this
job anymore after today
I think I'll I'll quit immediately
why am I looping them because I well
because it's necessary I I think it's I
think it's necessary oh my my stomach is
grumbling
[Music]
okay
I get it
no need to show me each time
okay now
sure
okay now it's time to take care of
the first golden man
saw this now this way please follow me
follow the white dog let's go and then
and then
should I set in place that yeah but
there's no time to think
um and once I did that where do I listen
to
him oh god
um just down just down here that's okay
that's okay that's okay let me go let me
go let me go let me go let me go let me
go uh and then here how about we make a
little Loop for now uh
right down okay
no no
thank you thank you thank you
actually I want some of you guys to
leave leave leave on
[Music]
there's no rush through this desert days
rest with this imaginary Rush
I take it very seriously you're doing
better than I would really
okay
foreign
dangerous okay okay okay
uh I think currently we are in in a safe
safe position right
[Music]
okay next step would be to lead these
people over to where I am now
and and then we go up
and uh no
without jumping on the button then we go
up we pick him up we go right we go down
we go over there back again
and then we
cross the button
and this time I will not [\h__\h] it up
I've
[Music]
uh they come back they have to do one
turn on the butt button right
Maybe
[Laughter]
wait wait ah
this is fine so you come back this way
there you go here to jump over the jump
over here to go up to the platform I
quickly have to make a sign to go right
and then they go down
yeah
okay oh okay oh okay
oh am I ready are we ready
it's okay though right is it okay is it
okay I don't know is it okay
we got we got a golden guy
oh my God
[Music]
and then and then and then
one of them made it
I don't even
I
I don't care anymore
I don't care I don't care whatever
[Music]
fall in Winter practical yet but no
not close can we check the solution I
think I think it's something like that
but I don't care I don't care it's okay
I give up on Humanity man I mean what
did you think what did you think I would
do this forever [\h__\h] no I'm I'm I'm I'm
I'm I'm I'm an apprentice ah this is my
trial day I I won't work here tomorrow
so everything I do as an apprentice it
doesn't matter you know the the real
Gods will have to clean up the mess
tomorrow I don't care about it
it was his problem it was his fault
you know like
why why jump so far ah have a little bit
more control over your body okay some
other people made it actually
impressively we hereby Grant you a new
power
float lightens humans increasing the
effect of fans and jump
[Music]
it remains active until humans return to
ground
Nani
Duck Go
I'm going to hate you
I don't even want to
Witnesses anymore
float
so but when they touch the ground it
loses effect does that mean I have to
place it on a wind turbine
no
it's okay if I do it here
I wonder
and they would they would float like a
goat over there maybe let's test it out
good finger chicken yeah I haven't given
up on chickens yet chickens are smarter
than humans sometimes
I really really they're not but um oh
wait
wait I have jumps
ah see
I see watching ground yet but uh
oh no oh
[Music]
like this no wait they're not jumping ah
I'm confused
how
to jump sooner
maybe activate the floating here no it's
not working what
[Music]
what they're kind of dying though at the
same time is what it looks like to me
what
oh they could already fill up the light
but no I don't want you to I don't want
you to oh wait wait
um
ah okay uh and we should we should stop
them from and let me go back
[Music]
oh man I mean I mean I guess we don't
need to stop them but
to stop them
um
what about these ah just a long jump is
enough I guess
okay
uh wait
no
switching between the tools is a little
bit stressful okay
same jump same jump same jump same jump
[Music]
and oh then they fill up that path oh
we're both golden guys oh yeah
cool both going guys are here in the
middle
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
because I'm not filling up the other
light okay so we have time to think
and the floating maybe yes I get it I
get or
or if I just make them jump earlier and
then I jump again really
wow
really
that's not
[Music]
oh they stopped get taking new people
um
but the float only works with the wind
turbines no
I understand I have to send this [\h__\h]
off send these people
um
so this way because oh sure
uh
ah you guys are
confusing me down here and up here
long jump here I'm gonna lose him I'm so
gonna lose him
then uh
they're doing
insanely huge jumps here
wait there's wait never mind maybe I
don't need them maybe I need the people
who are here
on the right side I didn't see them
I didn't realize there's even more
people here
spawning
uh
on there
they could be the solution too
float works on jump two really I thought
it said only with wind
really are you sure
it works on jumps too okay okay
um I don't know which script of people
to use
I guess
if you guys are really right then I
could use this group of this this group
of people right
oh
oh okay
okay now all I gotta do is release the
ones over here okay
okay and we completely ignore those
those are doomed I suppose
those people here they're just doomed
okay
why does no one care about them
[Music]
isn't this first try did I restart
something
wait am I missing something are they not
this
I don't see another
light that I have to fit away
wait at the beginning
oh
oh excuse me I thought you guys didn't
matter
oh excuse me
sorry see I'm getting the caramel
already don't worry guys it's not your
fault are you guys capable of jumping
that way now yeah looks good looks good
God looking good
yeah okay
and now we wait
so you guys are you I value guys as much
as I value all the other ones
barely
we bridged the cap look how beautiful
this is
it's a piece of art
a work of art
and we got the Goldies yeah yeah
okay the final one
trial six Goldie artists
some of you may die but that is a
sacrifice I'm willing to make
why have I heard that before
where was that from
and we have turn long jump and Float
okay
a Shrek yeah how very dark
oh Baby that
um
uh this must be even more difficult than
the previous one right
because I mean
it's the last one
cat hair in my mouth
if we accomplish this
they're gonna make me a job offer
probably but I don't want it but it's
these
floats yeah the float command enables
the people to jump higher and further to
be blown further by fans and to fall
from any height without perishing oh its
effects will remain until the fact that
humans reached it okay so it will make
it so that this doesn't hurt
okay
I know now it will hurt oh
does it
wait wait my beloved test subjects oh
wait oh
where are we going
where aren't we gonna go
that that's not enough anyway
I don't want to go there uh I thought
we're gonna activate these platforms
first
so maybe without
a jump
oh
yeah yeah yeah without a jump just by
floating they make it one space further
ahead okay
now we make some Loops because kiwawa
loves them loops
okay
wow oh they could even climb up if they
wanted to oh I don't need to Loop them
okay
no need to Loop
um
[Music]
okay
now now
we do big jump with a float bun oh you
guys yeah keep on doing that because I'm
confused
they're just circles oh
these are not even real people
wait this is a scam
it's a scam
they're all fake it's just circles and
lines
what the hell
okay well I I will try not to be
bothered by it
let me um okay nah it's okay we'll we'll
lose them the first time it's okay and
we just we just gotta test it out uh
this way please follow the dog to a a
long jump here
but with a float please
sucks
oh
and then
wait I don't know what I'm doing but
trust me I got it
or do I
I can't turn there
excuse me
uh
I haven't lost it yet I haven't lost it
yet
okay okay I'm going to fix it I'm gonna
fix it
um
this person doing all alone
moving the wrong direction
do we have to go up there in the end oh
wait we do
okay
I want to float but I want to float this
way
but how can I change
I don't even get those
oh
I think I know how
[Music]
we gotta go back to the start back to
our roots
no
no let's see
um
I think
no
I think therefore I am
can we send them up here
and then
that's impossible from here let's just
sacrifice those people for fun
um
[Music]
I take it back I take it back I take it
back I want to recreate it let me oh
but where did that even come from ah
okay sorry
sorry sorry sorry sorry let me go let me
go and go
uh I'll fix it I'm sorry for what I
attempted to do
I don't want Humanity to fail
purposefully and in particular
sorry if I gave you that impression oh
the human I got an achievement I think I
I let too many people die
okay I think the platforms should be
back anytime now
oh no apparently not no of course of
course of course it will be back
yeah all right
um I don't know how to get those two big
golden guys you guys have an idea
it's hard to see too I want to like see
how high up they are
I mean obviously we gotta get them with
the Wind turbans
uh and then return
yeah okay that's possible there are I
think they're on the same
height
so how about we send you guys
[Music]
um
send you guys here
and then float here is it floating
enough or do I have to make them jump to
oh
it worked
and I think they're already on the right
path to then join I mean currently it's
looping but to then join them once the
dude is here maybe I'll make another
look because I don't know how else to
function
ah [\h__\h] sorry guys
hi uh hi
hi
[Music]
let's let's let them pass we'll sudden
pass
[Music]
that's enough people I think I think
okay okay I got the next
next okay okay
then my looping
no I'm not panicking I'm well good I
have everything under control as you can
see it's just uh too many people is
freaking me out
go away
go away go elsewhere cool that's right
and um you might as well die
[Music]
look for now look for now
okay okay
now we got everybody so die thank you
thank you thank you
you're destined to nothing to the void
I would just have to send them up
just have to send them up which will be
with a floaty jump
uh
but I just don't understand because if I
I have to make them float first right
and how how can I when I will have to
send them down here and then turn left
that so the first the last sign will be
going left I see the climbable wall but
there's a gap ah maybe the long jump is
enough for it to fill it up never mind
I'm okay I'm scared I'm scared I'm
scared how does it look up there it says
uh
oh okay okay okay
let's let's try first uh oopsie
okay okay
[Music]
oh it's like
okay
I'm a [\h__\h] genius
um
wait
oh my God that was close okay
um but they're not gonna wait okay wait
as long as the golden man is walking I
think even when the light fills up
completely
wait do they need more people
wait what if it's not a continuous flow
is it is it not good
it
okay fine fine fine fine I can make a I
can make a continuous flow oh no problem
they're all in anyway
I thought the cousin previous ones it
looked like wait
uh
uh no
up we are there we we I'll just I'll
just keep on uh switching how about that
hi hi this is that good enough I don't
know
is it filling up
is that it's like traffic control yeah
oh right is okay
but for how long you'll be
I'll not
it's not gonna
work
it's a thing of timing I know I could
split the people but why make it so easy
yeah I can make this work too say it's
filling up oh oh oh
oh I wouldn't wait there they're gonna
arrive now she's wait for it wait for it
there there it is
told you believe in me
hey
stage and the whole trial link whatever
I think it's complete stop time you
cannot you can use Ctrl to stop the flow
of time
oh really is he peeing when he's
downstairs
because he stretching his leg well
that's helpful then I don't have to
press Escape but anyway
18 out of 19 I get the golden statue the
next thing I knew I was back at the
testing grounds
oh big circles now I heard the voice in
my head as I always do
more and more arriving thanks to your
efforts
you sway over the people remains
impressive
I asked the voice
but why why bring them here
[Music]
so they may become something greater
The More We Gather the more the facts
change
[Music]
this is the way of humanity
then I noticed the increased numbers of
people had caused the Blue Core to grow
now go the next sequence of Trials
awaits
test your wits and lead the people
onward
[Music]
I think that Doom is upon us but it's
not my problem I'm not working here much
longer
oh
choice
a new Statue appeared sequence of choice
but I won't be playing that I'll end it
here and I read some damn
we're satisfying though to finish a
level get all the golden guns so I'm
just a part-time I'm done for today
two hours I need a short stream today
you know
because um yeah
I I wasn't higher I'm not being pets to
play no
jumping paid to play God for much longer
hmm no it's not a permission condition
or anything no no I could play longer
but I don't want
a short stream because it's evening
so we go here
it's very late uh got back to kiwawa
normal human form
[Music]
does this mean I lose my halo though
I would like to keep my hair long
can I keep my halo
[Music]
Maybe Just For Today 91
Angel am I not considering how many
times
[Music]
perms I have perms for that Halo
um
yeah
it's my halo I have written permission
sure I do
[Music]
demoted to angel from God
and Angel's pretty nice too
you're not an angel not enough eyes
what's that mean if you add a red thingy
it's acceptable what does that mean a
red thing on my halo
what kind of red thing
I'm your angel so I can keep it hey
thank you
in the Bible angels have a lot of eyes
what
that's creepy I thought Angels was
supposed to be you know
not creepy but like
soothing a soothing existence
Bible Angels well I'm not the Bible
angel I am
I am a b angel
okay
we are gonna put on some music what do
you want to listen to guys
soothing yeah yeah she's nah I don't
know if she's soothing but she's [\h__\h]
cute
he's really cute
I love her
okay let's go music music what do you
want
stream Sparks High challenge no no no no
um
Maybe
fitting to the game we played
[Music]
sounds good to me sounds fitting to me I
don't know about you guys but I think
this is perfect
okay I'm gonna read them
before I go
[Music]
you think my Mexican lasagna is still
good even though I cooked it two days
ago and I didn't even eat it yesterday
because I was
not hungry
I think I can still eat it
it's a Mexican lasaga you want to know
what a Mexican lasagna consists of
according to hello
unfortunately no meat but it's with
beans and corn
and onions and bell peppers
and some spice and uh topped with cheese
oh and in between there's like two
layers only but in between was also sour
cream and and tomato sauce so it was
tomato sauce no first thing yeah no
first tomato sauce then
no maybe first two to you I don't know
but basically if I over the tortillas
it's first tomato sauce and then the all
the fillings the beans and all that
and then the sour cream
and then the tortilla seeds and then the
same thing again sour cream and then on
top the cheese
now
I know I know it's not like a you know
how you guys make lasagna actually but
it's an idea that hello fresh had okay
don't don't it's a it's a cool idea
because it tasted okay I made an extra
salad even though it wasn't included but
I had a good a cucumber left over so I
made a little salad and that really
balanced it out well
um
hmm
but I thought
[Music]
um
I never tried this before and I thought
that
um
the tortilla seeds
I thought that when I put them in the
oven
that they're gonna get really really
like
Steve really hard no like no
like you can't bite into it anymore well
no they stayed I guess thanks to the
hotel to the tomato sauce they probably
stayed
um really soft because of that
um
are you eating it now now I was eating
cherries I have a little Bowl of
Cherries here
um
yum
so it's actually like if you happen to
you you want to make a lasaga or you
have ingredients for Lazada but you
don't have like Saga sheets then but you
happen to have tortilla sheets or you
want to use up your tortilla sheets uh
because you use them for wraps but you
have left over
you could make a lasagna with it
that's why I learned now that uh they
actually they work quite well to make a
lasagna
um are the chairs still fresh yeah I got
them today
what do you mean French of course
they're fresh
got new new cherries cherry cherry
cherry boom boom Cherry Cherry yeah now
I pronounce
Italia tortilla and I was being careful
though don't let an Italian hear that
what does that mean that I can make a
wrap
with lasagna sheets
if I can make a lasagna with tortilla
sheets can I make a tortilla wrap
no of course my girl I must be able to
but I feel like
the texture because you're supposed to
hold a wrap holding like noodles with
your bare hands
I don't know I feel like the texture
would be weird right but in theory it
could work
pasta burrito
I'm thinking it will work because
honestly I think I've had pasta before
we pretty much with like those
ingredients that you put into a wrap
so and that tasted yummy
you can make pasta with anything really
so it's just about the fact that the
pasta may be used as a wrap sheet may
not be the best experience ever but it
works it could work and it probably
won't taste disgusting
finger would taste good
um
I reinvented ravioli
[Music]
no I don't think so I think ravioli is
different
I had a Korean lesson today by the way
hey
and yeah my homework was fine
I had Korean lesson what did I learn
today I learned uh
uh I think I learned the Udo
[Music]
a couple more words of like buildings
like Pharmacy
and
stuff like that
to tell like to tell people directions
like go straight from here and then turn
left and turn right and then the
building is between or uh right next to
Etc
um
oh
oh and then
what else oh my God brain empty it uh I
think I learned more than that
I definitely learned more than that
it's not equal cheating guys
help me with my homework they were just
bye bye my side behind me looking over
my shoulder okay I did it oh my God and
and helping no it's not because there
is difference you know back in back in
the day you know you ask your friend or
your mommy hey can you help me with my
homework and they would help you they
wouldn't do everything for you
you don't understand
you just wanna
you just want to call me out
[Music]
um
well I didn't cheat
I didn't see it maybe like oh
[Music]
[Applause]
oh nice
no I will not I will not be brainwashed
by you guys no [\h__\h] that
um
no
I will not have that no no no no no no
no no
ma'am wow
uh but the Zelda after that maybe not
or did I
oh no I don't think I did
I not read whole talk I didn't answer
oh maybe I didn't okay
talk I'm still kind of behind oh man
okay
this stream I'm gonna read those chats
should I write this down let me write it
down text
that creep
guys there's this cool function that we
have now in our uh app they added a new
function that's actually something I was
trying to figure out
with OBS plugins but I will test it
tomorrow
I'll test it tomorrow
remind me if I forget remind because
I'll probably forget
[Music]
this
uh reading Super Chips
[Music]
remind me
okay it's making I mean I like it but I
think it has potential to make me go
crazy too
eventually
[Music]
um
okay we're ready I'll just eat one more
cherry cherry cherry cherry boom boom
Terry
Jerry I want I want if I ever have like
a garden I would like to have a cherry
tree
hmm
[Music]
gosh these are so good
you like the music
most people
have been brainwashed
I have an apple tree and it's annoying
why
why why is it annoying because there's
too many apples
and you don't know what to do with them
or or because it gets like it's
difficult to treat it or
[Music]
I have to harvest them well
and it needs a lot of treatments for
bugs or bugs eat them
I see yeah
I think back in the day
oh
when my grandma was still around
well I had two grandmas like any other
person but one no the one from my
mommy's side
um
it was like more more reachable so we
would sometimes go to her and she had a
garden and she had
at least one fruit tree and I think it
was
apples
was it was
not only she also had other stuff but
yeah it was like
we always had that
too much of that and and I feel like
when you have a certain fruit tree you
have so much of it that you then stop
appreciating it and you don't want it
anymore because you always have it
but I think that's especially in the
case of apples
I have two cherry trees in my garden
the biggest pests are birds or
shoot them no
just kidding hmm
yeah but you you gotta get into baking
if you have an apple tree you gotta get
into baking and then make apple strudel
and apple pie and all that if you are
able to do that
then I think everyone will appreciate
your Apple donations your Apple creation
donations and you yourself might be able
to appreciate it more as well
[Music]
um
oh you know what I love an apple lizard
that I love and barely get to eat
absolutely I mentioned them before
absolutely is apple rings you know you
cut them and they're like donut shape
and then you fry them not uh not with
breading but with like batter
you fry them
um and then you eat them with hot
vanilla sauce and possibly a
scoop of vanilla ice cream
[Music]
um
that is like my favorite thing but I
they don't deliver they don't ever have
it in restaurants and they don't have it
anywhere to order it and
um but making myself too much effort
hmm
ah but it's so good they're easy to make
I even have an apple
um whole creator
the the whole
Earth
um
the holder for the apples
why am I bratty
bratty Acora okay close enough
I even have that I really get to use it
though
[Music]
I should try the Apple thingy whenever I
can but vaguely remember seeing it
remember where did you see it
have you guys ever seen it somewhere
when I just described
[Music]
foreign
That's Where It's At rhubarb and
strawberry jam or rhubarb and strawberry
pie
that's the good stuff
revive and strawberry pop is like um
[Music]
it's like it I don't know
it does something with the strawberries
to balance it
speaking of apple pies I actually was my
hello
uh box that came in yesterday they sent
me like butter sometimes they send
really rarely they send like free
samples of some food of some company
that you know wants to work with them
and this time it's butter and they send
a recipe
with it
uh for apple pie that you have to use
this specific butter for
you have to use this butter and then you
can make apple no it's not it's not no
wait it's not normal apple pie it's um
and an apple almond is it even Apple
yeah I think so I think it was apple
apple almond
uh
something pie
like the there's like a like a filling
[Music]
it's not not what you think of
but there's like a almond cream
I think it's an apple almond cream
inside
pie
once you add other stuff you lose me huh
and it's probably top of apple slices
probably I'm not sure anymore but I kind
of want to make it I kind of want to
make it
they sent this recipe and now I want to
make it but all I have is the butter
maybe I'll make it hot apple desserts
and vanilla ice cream is my favorite
combo yeah that's such a good good
combination right like even if you don't
go all the way like you know I explained
with the but the batter frying the apple
rings no you don't even have to do that
I think
um a baked apple
was something me and Callie had in the
snow in Hokkaido in this in the in the
ryokan in the spa while bathing our feet
in hot water only the feet in that case
mm-hmm
like one little snack they had like they
had hot drinks and one snack they had
was I think baked apples
no ice cream though I think but it was
fine because the like we were outside
it was cold it was like there was like a
little waterfall in the pond and and
snow and we were sitting in yukatas
[Music]
and we were sitting with our feet in the
hot water
and next to each other buy some
Candlelight it was pretty dark overall
by bubbles candles and and lanterns and
oh there was snow I made a little snow
bunny
[Music]
again please
she finds good places to stay at
I am flexing that was like thinking back
man you know one of my favorite fan arts
ever
is the one where
um
I forgot the name now but the one person
Drew uh Drew us
uh like in a really realistic way on top
of one of the pictures yeah Jolly Jolly
on top of one of the pictures that I
showed from our trip
um yeah when we walk into the Onsen it
was actually that was the building that
you see in that picture was one of the
Onsen buildings within the whole yokan
grounds
and it was the one that I I felt
comfortable going into because it was
the least popular one
oh man
Good Times
uh thinking back
I mean you know we stayed in the city
and then we went to the countryside
to go to the the winter snowy Village in
the mountains to a fancy yoga and a
really cool ryokan
um and the the city part was rough
because we went skiing in the closest
place in the city and
I got injured and then our travel to the
countryside when we were trying to leave
the city it was really rough because it
was like
I swear like it was unbearably cold so
much that it was hurting
incredible pain but we were walking
around with our suitcases in the snow in
the snowstorm trying to find the shuttle
couldn't find it we were going here and
there and here and there and oh
then we missed the shuttle even after uh
trying to call them several times first
we tried with Cali's remember the story
travel callus phone call this phone died
because of the cold had to drive with
mine I couldn't even get my hand out of
my hand it was so painful to take out my
phone and call but then I had I had to I
had to
um and and and they were trying to
figure out what we were and that we
couldn't really explain well and we were
in the wrong spot apparently uh
so everything up to that point was so
rough
and then finally yo when we finally made
it into the normal bus not the shuttle
bus just the normal bus because we
missed the shuttle bus
we
um we were like I think it was like
maybe an hour bus ride
and it was cold inside the bus too
and we were just like sitting Cali
behind me
on like single solo seats and I think we
were just quietly
waiting because of all the suffering we
we were just like
I know turned off we were offline our
brains were offline
okay
[Music]
yeah we were like two stunned from the
the the the pain
I think right before we set off we had
that Ramen no doubt that Ramen was
incredible oh man I really missed the
ramen
I should go eat ramen
sometime this week ASAP
uh now I'm in the mood for ramen I wanna
oh whenever I eat ramen
the Warmness and the fullness the rich
flavor makes you feel like you're back
in Japan a little bit
food trip food trip to to Japan every
trip to Japan is a food trip
it's okay I'll wait my my next Japan
trip is not that far away
you guys know that
um
[Music]
for my next Japan trip Dome
um
it'll be ravish short
really short some it was supposed to be
longer and now it's shortened again
because some plans were changed
and because of the shortness
[Music]
um
uh I don't think I'll be um staying in
you know like a like an environment as
before
so for streaming I'll have to
uh I'll have to use the studio again you
know book slots but it wasn't really an
issue last time like every time I wanted
to book the the studio I had to ask uh
in advance but it was always available
for streaming you know alone in in like
a small room no 3D streams but like
normal 2D streams it was always
available so the only problem is that
there's a cap in how late I can stay
[Music]
because of Staff wanting to leave
but even that is pretty late
could uh yeah I could stream at her
place too worst case but anyway it's a
short trip so I'm not too too worried
about that it's very short you guys
won't be missing me too much don't worry
hmm
there are there might be a longer
follow-up trip
oh
but all of that is still up in the air
yeah
maybe maybe there's even more little uh
streaming Studios than before now with
the new studio like not only maybe they
didn't only expand in 3D rooms but also
in 2D rooms who knows I don't know could
be as long as they still have one small
one we're probably good because it
didn't seem much in demand because the
Japanese members don't use it why would
they
like willingly
go out
outside of their own room and Stream in
the studio like a normal stream why
would they they would not do that so
it's only like people like me who make
use of it when I'm in Japan
and usually you know there's not much
overlap
[Music]
makes me think and as you can see
uh in the like the audition
Hawaiian audition page
they were like some sample streams most
of them were like big like big 3D
streams or debut whatever anniversary
streams and blah blah blah one of them
the only normal stream
was my perfect
unscuffed perfectly planned my organized
uh
collapsed gym with myth unbelievably
believable I was asked if I was fine
with
um them adding it there and I said yeah
of course no problem
but it seems like
my stream was the perfect example
it to show off
so proud
I knew I already knew it was a good
stream but yeah if they want to go that
far to use it as an example for a good
stream next to all those like like
management planned 3D streams or
whatever you know you know that tells
you something ah
yeah
it was a good stream right yeah I'm
quite happy with it too
[Music]
I love the logo too because it legit the
logo looks like it could be from some
board game
hmm
[Music]
prove that Kiana has a rope new gents
into her shenanigans
he went into my collabs
it's well deserved it was so much fun I
hope thank you one of the best book
clubs so thank you yeah I tried I really
wanted it to be good because I uh yeah
that time we had some scuffedness and I
know fans wanted some something
um that went smoothly for once
wasn't it also the most recent phone no
no ttrpg was the most recent one
but you know I guess putting like a
ttrpg there would be
but weird because it's like a
like a whole thing a series
yeah yeah it was very important for me
that everybody got to um talk more
in the end it's still their own choice
how much they want to talk
in a stream but I think
um
it's still important for someone with if
it if it doesn't happen naturally I feel
like a lot of Japanese members when they
have collapsed it just happens naturally
they all throw in something and and
people get mostly equal amounts of
talking time
um but with me finals
I don't know with miff sometimes it's
just like some some girls are not quite
there or or they
um feel like there's no no time for them
to talk or so so well I think for us we
need someone to make sure that you all
like everybody gets to talk and that was
very important to me
um
yeah yeah
yeah and that worked out well
like a host yeah like a low-key
invisible invisible host
[Music]
that's what I was trying to do all right
so let's read the subject for real for
real
is that like does council have the same
thing I don't think so right
they don't have this problem do they
is it just Smith
because I don't think I noticed counts
do they have this problem
when I do a full collab and and uh no
they're all
oh equally chatty
it's just sniff oh
oh Council
oh we're just weird but it's just us oh
[\h__\h]
oh
something
from maybe it will happen to council too
with time hmm
and I mean now they're four maybe with
when they were five
now even with five I remember watching
but did they do that many five-member
collabs
because in the beginning our first five
member collabs
our first tour so how many five member
collabs did did council do anyway two
for real how many did they do
because if you only do
they do in the beginning of course
they'll go well
[Music]
they did monthly collapse oh yeah right
for how long
dance
at least five really
[Music]
and did they all always have good good
like talking balance
I'm feeling competitive because I had to
find to make miff look a little bit
better
uh
oh man
all of them are talkers
okay I I would have thought maybe or
fauna
you know there's sometimes they could be
more quiet they have potential for that
well no I guess they're all kind of like
pull it out of each other
damn it
Smith being weird
what do I do what I do with this kids
[Music]
no it's okay I think you know
maybe though
maybe the awkwardness is
um
something
lovable
Maybe
yeah yeah it feels like the special
child it's great yeah yeah that's the
charm it's part of the myth charm
[Music]
yeah we just have
a full group of weirdos man I mean
we have a lot of introverts that work
better on their own I mean Amma has said
it many times that she
[Music]
um
she's not much of a collab person I
think she said so
[Music]
no she will do it if she gets invited
but she doesn't even invite people
herself and you know and then yeah
Ina likes to this is I think mostly with
Ina I think it's mostly a problem of
like off collapse
because it was off collapse she will
just sit in the back or lie on the
ground Nah if if I don't like put her
like in unbelievably believable in a
chair and a signed chair
and make her talk directly into an
assigned microphone
yeah
[Music]
um because yeah she was lying on the
ground during that collab that I'm
thinking of
um
but this I don't think that happens with
her in like normal collapse if it's not
if it's a normal online collab
then
yeah I don't think she's ever chosen to
lie on the ground
and just
say sayonara
during a
normal online call out right thank God
not that I know of hmm
yeah yeah she's also she when she's
there then she's talkative
[Music]
ah well miss miss
you two have great Synergy and collapse
really I hear that a lot from you guys
and and I don't know if it's really true
but I guess we make it work
you have to get a few drinks in Lina
Lina in Ina like Lamy did
[Music]
no I'm not gonna support
alcoholism
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no
I am straight edge you guys know that
um
[Music]
if anything
maybe Callie would would be able to get
Ina to drink but I I cannot
no I will be the last person to suggest
that
[Music]
I am exaggerating of course of that but
you know I don't know it was fine
without alcohol she doesn't need alcohol
no no no no no no no
no
I really liked what Mr together I think
it's a good way I actually just thought
about that
today I think or yesterday
that you know we have a lot of artists
in myth
and even the not so much artists draw
cute art we're all artists
and and I was thinking it would have
been cute if the first myth shirt wasn't
just my art but like five girls art like
combined
that would have been cute like each
character is drawn by a different person
or so
I would have been cute
is what I was thinking but it's way too
late now
maybe for a future merchandise you know
collaboration art
[Music]
okay let's go let's go
uh Jacob 47 hours
foreign
[Music]
oh that's right I didn't think of that
you guys can now drink your favorite
beverage out of the whole talk mug
during holotalk episodes
and if you happen to be a collector of
acrylic stands
um even from like Japanese members
then you can put the fitting member on
the stand because most of the acrylic
stands work with it you only have
Kiana's dance well that's that's a
problem but if you have like you know
all the other members too
there might be like a couple people who
have that possibility
you could put the for example for that
episode you could have put the last
empire
on the stand
yeah you can recreate the Kiara on Kiara
episode is there a small piano
uh acrylic stand
acrylic stand
because then you could put a small
quinoa
on the right side where the host was
supposed to be
no what
no official one
oh wow you're right I don't have one
oh
[Music]
you're about to create palonesia
okay well maybe with you creating that
you will like kind of like what's the
word
will it into existence
could future funnels be pictures of
stance
no
no manifested yeah yeah anyway
thank you Jazz vlogberg I like that
thought very much studio wrappings with
a pinky too is it wrong to hope for a
key who Tova song Club oh I don't know
I'm currently like you know very busy
with working on the album and then on
the side I'm trying currently to
um plan out
a song cover with someone
but all of this is taking my time so if
then it will be father in the future
yeah
but not saying no
thank you
foreign
of course we'll get Luna on the show
soon because we're already in her
generation
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
you want an official ducky we don't need
an official valadaki the one that Akira
Drew is already perfect
I don't need any other
can you die penguin Subs donkey soon
Kimmy pH thank you thank you
so I am thank you soon
thank you why are you on fire
what's going on
what happened are you okay
I am kfp and ssrb thanks also for the
pinky whole talk awesome thank you
for celebrating
[Music]
thank you for another great whole talk
episode with digest allow me to say one
last time
he has my whole check mark just arrived
in time and able to enjoy this episode
yeah number one that is so cute you guys
drinking out of the whole plug mug while
watching whole car that is so perfect
man that makes me happy that fought
makes me happy
hey for the ones who didn't think of it
next time next time wait actually junkie
chunks
are you here
chunks profile picture I wanna look at
it bigger
but I can't go to your proof wait how do
I go to your profile from hololizer I
would need to go out of hololas but I
see my mug and I see the acrylic stand
in your profile picture
what's in the background though is it
whole talk that would be funny
[Music]
glad I got the mug right
I wanted to but it didn't arrive yet for
me you missed the mob no
oh no
[Music]
no that is very sad
Big Jack hasn't shipped it yet nah
eventually
wow all the geek check people haven't
been shipped yet I guess
it was broke when it yeah you weren't
broke when you when it was on sale oh no
um
[Music]
well well thank you Jackie chunk wow
thank you very much
[Music]
BMW
see kiwawa it wasn't so difficult to
read those super chats
get your [\h__\h] together please
[Music]
which one is this
Ahoy
this one
[Music]
what
is next
oh yeah
let's read this
check up with some now thanks for the
pinky it's a good thing Zelda means
Kiana doesn't read super chats anymore
or she might see me saying that she is
so cute and sexy and funny in the Super
Chat
it doesn't mean I'm not reading them
anymore it just meant that I'm uh not
reading them right after the stream most
of the time but eventually you should
no and I don't completely ignore my
super chats and I say oh I won't read
them today it means I won't read them
today but I will read them another day
you should have known you should have
known
[Music]
but I read it delayed
maybe you changed your mind maybe in
your mind
this is not even accurate anymore
maybe I'm not cute and sexy and funny
anymore
to you
am I
am I I am the Super Chat finisher
[Music]
foreign
have an idea
[Music]
he could be trying to disturb or annoy
or or say hello to froggy Wawa up there
he's trying to say hi
or he's trying to break the glass to let
her out
please do not tap on the glass
he cannot stop himself from tapping on
the glass I I tell him every time
mm-hmm
Kalina
foreign
[Music]
make a big one
slam that keyboard you go
now let's make some more
small is cute
um
[Music]
oh
goodbye well that's understandable wait
all right holy [\h__\h] La it's got like
everything Nintendo World too right
she is you guys if you don't want to go
to ax while you're in L.A because you're
not a fan yourself ax
is might as well try to go to Nintendo
World
that's better in my opinion
hey X it's just ugh ah sneeze
[Music]
I mean I've never been there but
um
I would imagine it to just be
I don't know
too many people
for the membership
whoa
[Music]
did you see the new PS mobile what
well the PlayStation Mobile phone or
what
position mobile hand holding one plant
blizzard portable
what
what what what
how did what what how did that
[Music]
huh
slip what how how did that come
information what
it's not a what what is it it's like the
steam neck it's not a portable console
it's an adapter for phone what what oh
yeah don't worry my hype is lessening
right now
why don't they release a new PlayStation
Portable or something like that why not
I really liked pleasure she bought a
boat
has PlayStation completely given up on
that kind of stuff
you still need a PS5 I have a PS5
why don't they like Portables anymore
because it's not lucrative
[Music]
okay
whatever then leave that market to
Nintendo I guess I don't know if that's
a smart business
decision in the end you know
[Music]
the switch is working well dude
Nintendo handhelds work well
foreign
so what if you attach it to your
through your phone
and then what you can play Playstation
games on your phone
[Music]
it streams from your PS4 it's not for
the phone it's a streaming screen unless
you play PS5 games
[Music]
a Wii U gamepad for PS5 oh
like a video game okay okay
so you attach it to your PS5 but
probably without a cable evil
huh but then does your PS5 need to be
close
because for the steam deck you can use
it anywhere does this thing have to be
like in the same apartment or so like
close by to your PS5
oh okay see that's already like um
[Music]
it has to be the same Wi-Fi well
um
when would I use that
I mean
I mean if I don't want to move my PS5
from my office to my bedroom to play PS5
I guess I guess but like most people who
are not streamers like me they just have
their PS5 wherever they would play the
game
and yeah
oh well oh well okay you got got me
shook for a moment I thought that was a
new places but I wouldn't I wouldn't
have missed that right if
if that was the case
I see the only thing I really saw is
that Pullman was hyped about a remake of
the MGs game and I saw a dragon's dopma
2 trailer which looked really cool
I just don't know if Dragon's Dogma one
is necessary to play
to understand the second one
foreign
[Music]
I didn't watch that I just know from
Twitter
does she scream as much as I screamed
for 1080 snowboarding
because if she didn't then there's no
love
did she cry
though
find the list
okay
okay oh well anyway let's continue
where was I
ah
um
thanks for the pinky I can't watch many
streams live due to being cursed by the
Australian time zone along with not
wanting to disrupt my boyfriend's sleep
by staying up all night watching Wawa
but I want to send you some love before
heading off to bed for the night thank
you
thank you
so I guess you're watching vods most of
the time
as long as you're able to watch the
bullets I don't see a problem it's okay
even if you can't be there alive all the
time no worries
um thank you for the support
thank you soon
anyways to make a video about guessing
stranger star signs correctly cutting
out the wrong guesses for example what
oh
I recommend everyone to watch Captain
dissolution he makes informative and fun
to watch videos explaining viral fakes
but the one that I watched was real
it was real
really
but sure that could be interesting
you guys are fans huh
it's always real
no of course not
but that one that was was real
it was real to me
uh j h d f h j k d k j d k j h
foreign
[Music]
recently you
before the streams even start so you're
not even you're not even doing it when I
would notice it
one time I noticed was just because I
just so happened to be at my pc at the
time
but you're sending so many memberships
is your goal to make my whole chat green
or what
probably not even here right now so you
won't even hear this
but thank you you crazy little chicken
thank you thank you thank you thank you
you're single-handedly raising my
memberships like crazy thanks thanks
very Noble yes honorable
very very sweet but I feel like at some
point he's here ah I'm feeling at some
point
you'll run out of like people to gift it
to
see how green my chat already is
I feel like everybody's a member
really really
what really actually happens then
like let's say okay in the Stream like
this is more difficult but let's say you
go to a stream that has like five
viewers
and you gift 10 memberships
what happens does YouTube tell you
that there's not enough people watching
to receive the memberships
I I really want to know
if does it refund you
[Music]
random people yeah but I mean when
there's literally only five people when
the when the view counts not just the
chat but the view count actually says
there's only five people
and you give 10 or 20.
[Music]
one child goal please and test it out go
to a stream that has no viewers
even if you don't watch them you can get
a membership gift for real
[Music]
oh if people open the chat before the
stream or gone away before the end there
you can still get it but what if it's
like a really really like what if it's a
new channel that streams for the first
time just started Streaming new streamer
in its first stream
you know normally if you don't have a
big audience audience right away but
thanks for the memberships Abby let's
say they have their first five viewers
oh they won't have memberships
what an argument
ah
[Music]
one of their monetized through
previously uploaded videos
and they just start to stream for the
first time
[Music]
and and and and and and
I just
[Music]
as well
um
they want no what if they don't come
because they don't wanna I don't know
because they don't get notified by
YouTube and they didn't uh they just
started streaming out of nowhere with no
stream reservation oh man
[\h__\h] whatever okay anyway thank you
blank that's what I wanted to say
uh no science for me
[Music]
um
test your German Channel since it hasn't
streamed in months
[Music]
no that wouldn't work no it would
probably get more viewers than that
what the German Channel isn't even
monetized is it is no way is it
[Music]
I think it wasn't monetized yet
anyway anyway
Captain coconut donation
[Music]
happy belated birthday
thank you for supporting me and being
here on your birthday
uh you you have to
[Music]
eat the real Ramen and the real Sushi
while you're in Japan because like
overseas sushi
especially Sushi I think is very
different
Ramen there's some good ramen places but
from what I've heard
um like for example Austrian Sushi or
european Sushi could never compare to
what you get in Japan
and in terms of activities I say go to
karaoke
find find maybe some people to go with
though that would be nice
[Music]
where's Chihuahuas gloves haven't seen
quias gloves in a while Jim Tracy Duncan
Belden Alexander
thank you
oh stop being so sweet
[Music]
conduction
and
um
thank you thank you
the whole life English gamer that's me
don't think karaoke alone actually
I love going to karaoke alone in Japan I
love it I used to do that a lot but if
you like there for the first time then I
think it wouldn't be as much fun alone
[Music]
but I like it because then I can just
sing you know however much
I want on my own you know I'm paying for
the time so if I get one or two hours
karaoke time then I want to fill it with
uh songs and not wait to sing because
someone else is singing it's nice to
sing in your room at that point no no
it's very different it's more satisfying
to sing in a karaoke place than singing
at home where there's no uh no Echo no
Reverb no atmosphere no food and I don't
know it's different it's more satisfying
to sing trust me
hmm
yeah
and I feel like with color okay you know
how mirrors
depending on which mirror you look into
you feel like some mirrors are
flattering you more
and then you go and look in other
mirrors and you feel like suddenly what
the [\h__\h] I was this ugly
so with karaoke I feel like karaoke
flatters your singing
when you go into karaoke rooms
and sing there
I always feel better than I feel about
my singing elsewhere
and Beer Week
six guys uh yeah the blasting blasting
audio
[Music]
and the atmosphere
it's only words
thank you for the red super chat
congratulations on overcoming your Zelda
addiction
next we need to work on your waking up
early to feed your cat's addiction I
can't help with that no no no no no no
smoothie I had had has had a couple days
where she was like
unbearablely annoying and I had to get
up for real early to give her breakfast
and then go back to sleep but now she's
back to normal I think she she will wake
up and meow but not for too long so I
can continue sleeping but the Zelda
addiction I don't know about that
I don't know about that
so not overcome
yeah
I do have like a
H I thought still I'm I'm I'm low-key
considering
[Music]
canceling tomorrow
I need some more extra time I think to
figure out some things
uh got some things done
and record my
and practice my [\h__\h] my
choreography and the teal Kai stream
would take up the whole day
ah you guys are so sweet
[Music]
then you guys have even more time to
catch up because you guys were saying
that I'm
too far ahead
yeah you guys have things to do anyway
this channel sounds kind of that Sunday
to me
I have to visit my sister
[Music]
well I have things to do anyway too um I
also have things to to do
um
yeah would that be okay for you guys
because I'm kind of worried right now
like it's stressing me out
foreign
I need I think another day
[Music]
um
thank you
oh thank you
yeah
then you would see me on Sunday
and we'll stream really long on Sunday
and I won't drink super chats cause I
will play for 10 hours
thank you
no it won't be an endurance stream
there's nothing to endure
it's just a fun stream anyway okay
okay
if you guys are so sweet about it then I
shall do it
perfect time to upload the clip which
one
you mean the German one
give me the German one
okay remind me on Twitter
[Music]
okay okay what what what what what what
channel
no okay okay okay okay okay okay
why bother uploading it what
why are you man man
so pessimistic
so edgy just upload on the main Channel
no it has German subtitles it's it has
it's it's been created for the German
Channel that I do not own
[Music]
okay
what's the point shut up
here's a kiss insulin questions
hi akiana it's always a fun and relaxing
Sunday watching you play through games I
never got the chance to play uh thank
you always for being our beloved angel
also it's almost been two years since I
joined kfb I should go
yes whoa
you know I thought you were here since
the beginning but it just feels much
longer
[Music]
this is a really really long time thank
you so much thank you soon your time
flies
yeah
time flies so fast and you're welcome
I'm glad you don't feel like you know
um against watching you don't feel bad
about watching games that you haven't
played yet hmm
because you want to play them yourself
someday or something like that but you
know I'm glad you're still making it to
my streams I'm playing it for you just
for you thank you so much happy to your
anniversary thank you for all the
support I hope you will continue
supporting me
thank you soon
I'm off work tomorrow and I'm on the wow
stream you surely have a lot to watch
don't you just ask that it's live just
just pretend
foreign
[Music]
live tweet old Verizon board sure sure
there's a perfect no commitment playlist
yeah but those are kind of short maybe
you have a tltk though to want to catch
up on or so you know you know you know
[Music]
is not for you guys you guys are
committed to me
it's not for you I made it for people
who are not with us yet mostly
but if there's something in that list
that you haven't watched yet okay then
you can go watch it
you can you can I guess
I guess you were loud okay
thank you Anthony
[Music]
you never saw the first horror games
that even I had to admit that wasn't
even scary
happy
happy why don't you report it earlier
two weeks ago so now we're like even
later I
thought you sent it on the 21st now it's
25th not that bad
um
next time you better be on time
I want to say happy birthday as early as
I can to you
congratulations deeply thanks for the
pinky since he wanted to know my
birthday was four days ago so hooray I
guess I'll be on time next week why
you too
happy belated birthday there's actually
so many holy [\h__\h] so many birthday
announcements
you guys are all getting older
congratulations
I help you all a healthy and happy
you asked I did I did thank you and four
days late isn't even that bad
that's not that bad
um RS also sending a birthday pinky it
was my birthday on May 15th
it's always a great time watching your
streams it's I've been so busy lately to
think of a good message but I'm happy to
spend time with you and kfb
thanks see you are pretty late you're
six days late uh uh for your birthday
announcement
how was your birthday what cake did you
eat if you didn't eat cake then what is
wrong with you
did you say that you're not streaming
down tomorrow thank you for letting me
sleep late
sleep late sleep late
I mean not wake up early yeah yeah I I
guess we're not doing it tomorrow
I feel bad about it but you know I I
think I need some extra time to get my
[\h__\h] together
um
tomorrow's a Friday so I can also like
still call DHL if I want to
um
oh no maybe I could also on the weekend
I don't know
[Music]
I'm just a bit overwhelmed right now yo
thank you guys
oh birthday donut a birthday donut what
the [\h__\h] it's not a cake
St bass also birthday superche but
you're saying yours is on the 26th no no
no no your 26th birthday was a week ago
oh oh oh the other way around oh also
late
[Music]
yeah thank you for watching my streams
thank you soon my lovely chicken
soon can you not swear please oh [\h__\h] no
you look chat
[Music]
my new job has been keeping me away
along with catching a bad case of David
oh no
hopefully I'll be able to be around more
often
man
maybe well at least during the video
you're not going to to your job right so
you can watch me while you're getting
healthy yeah
ah I got laid off what
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
are you okay did you like the job
I hope you didn't
why did they let you off how long were
you wait it was a new job and you just
got laid off like immediately afterwards
what the [\h__\h] man I'm so sorry you
probably had a rough time finding a job
man
[Music]
unlocking but yeah I mean on the bright
side you have time from me
something about not meeting expectations
but I'll be okay finding one was rough
man I'm sorry that sucks they suck but
but yeah the upside is you can watch me
until you find a new job sorry
you can do it I believe in New York they
say whatever they say don't get link
um
don't don't bet it kill your motivation
[Music]
or your confidence
the only end just opened some spots
perfect time to change
what you mean like staff position I
think we're always hiring staff but I
think they have to be in in Japan
hmm
[Music]
no discouraged please
I think you are surely very capable of
what you want to do
so you'll get another chance and the
next time will be even better I'm sure
[Music]
Virgil Fox thank you okay
thank you these are those super Gents
well thank you
[Music]
I'll do the last past part two stream
s
memberships you crazy okay
[Music]
thank you
whoa
wow wow wow
[Music]
foreign
like a salad
chicken salad
chicken salad isn't really green is it
now it is
oh thank you more memberships thank you
thank you
[Music]
Jacob 47 hours
of chat as much lately due to moving to
a new place oh nice I hope you like the
new place but I officially not had a
drink of alcohol and over a year oh I
think I reacted to this just wanted to
thank you and the community for being a
part of my motivation and to take better
care of myself and turn things around
I I am
I'm surprised
yeah
[Music]
Brandon's pain this is bigger than your
previous one
that's always pain
yum but I'm really proud of him that's
so yeah that's so awesome
you did that you did that
even even if you say that we're helping
you with the motivation but you did that
it was it was your actions and your your
strength
that made it possible so whenever if you
ever relapse or so
just know that you did it once you can
do it again
[Music]
you had to get a bigger place for the
flowers right okay so it's more
expensive but also bigger for the lava
Shrine well then
well then worth it
yes
well good luck in the new place I hope
you're getting comfy there
um
but water around water rub water rope I
don't know how to say your name but
thank you thank you I'm glad you like
roast rule Richard Richardson well I
don't think June
put commitment into making the zero
commitment playlist thank you thank you
hello
[Music]
ah the NBA finals start right after my
stream is done there's no time yeah but
that's maybe like a one-time thing right
it's not throughout the whole year right
not an excuse
[Music]
me
Jim Tracy thanks for the pinky so
excited for your EP even more now that
you're working on some of the lyrics
very cool that you're taking this
opportunity can't wait to see what you
come up with thank you but what I'm
worried about is that people will over
analyze it
um
that's the problem
don't think too much about it guys
[Music]
oh oh oh
cause I kind of wanna I I want at least
you know so far the songs that have
lyrics that I've already been working on
like recording
um
are like you know pretty much just like
you know happy and love related and all
that
so I want some songs to not be like
super happy
maybe have more like struggle topics
[Music]
edgy emo [\h__\h]
yeah
so if I do that
just
just know I'm okay okay
don't over analyze
[Music]
but I also feel awkward like when I'm
gonna talk to my lyric guest like hey I
wanna I wanna I wanna do this kind of
topping this kind of story I feel I feel
embarrassed about
um even bringing it up
for not heal
um
something edgy
[Music]
yeah cut my chicken into pieces
this is my last combo meal
[Music]
chicken nuggets
oh yeah right that had kind of like
um Sadler lyrics too
[Music]
I need to look and do those lyrics again
no need to read them again what they
were about
[Music]
[Applause]
bullet a bucket bucket ballistic bucket
Ultra reckon King thank you
[Music]
thank you
that story will out of thank you soon
oh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] oh no yeah
and yes said YouTube and I looked it up
before andaline does not the ambulance
you mean Natalie Dormer Natalie Dormer
does not have a Twitter account there's
just like fan accounts so I could not
tag her hmm
volleyball is
I've got a big race oh sheesh at my
other job today and I wanted to share my
good fortune with my favorite boss also
we almost ran out of cheese at my kfb
Branch fortunately I keep a backup
Supply just in case
that's a German
do you think of this
German English pun
how
[Music]
did you take it from someone
how did you come up with it
that's cute
maybe
people never make their original jokes
these days anymore they all take it from
elsewhere
[Music]
I think that was chunky wonky
but the cute joke even if it wasn't your
own one
well they caught me off guard thank you
and congrat congrats for the raise yeah
so loud
[Music]
wow
I'm here mommy's here that was a
concerning meal that was like Moro
it's not a normal meal
[Music]
he walked in
come on you don't want right oh man
a chunky wonky
orange cat hi baby she walked in and now
she's just standing there confused
okay
simply thanks for the pinky stickers wow
thank you I appreciate it thanks for the
support and the diving double Jones
thanks for the super chat too we're all
done we're done we're done
[Music]
more memberships we're already so green
a big
what are you doing
thank you
oh yeah I mean I mean we're pretty much
fully green now oh my God are there any
non-greens left
one one
[Music]
two
three four
oh
okay there's still a couple
there's still a couple of them or if you
active and you come to my streams often
then you might be lucky and get a free
membership at some point
oh scratch scratch you're doing a screen
Squad
homes
happy
mommy is done more memberships thank you
oh yeah you have to allow you know
membership gifting and your settings too
to receive it as well
seems like it yeah okay I'm really
hungry so I'm gonna eat my Mexican
lasagna now
thank you guys for watching and don't
worry I I will not play it tltk tomorrow
so also not privately not not outside of
the stream ever so I I won't be like
super silent
on Twitter I'll keep you updated about
what I'll be doing
thank you thank you
[Music]
get rid of the Grays green only
where the Chunky Monkey Go
she's behind my chair looking at me
[Music]
you want to say hi
do you want to say hi
thing is once I like move a little bit
she will run away
it's hard to catch her
yeah she comes when she hears that sound
use your hair too
oh
hi
no
hmm
[Music]
yum I did this the other day you know
that 7 A.M recording that I had there
were quite a few members present and and
staff to
and you know in when we were like on
standby like waiting uh for things to
start happening
chunky wonky was like running around
meowing and everyone was like okay your
cats are so cute
and then I picked her up and I made her
parallel into the microphone and
everybody
everybody in the voice chat went like oh
all at once
oh
[Music]
everybody melted
my cats cats are powerful
yeah everybody was happy hmm
Ohio
[Music]
Peppa
okay
thank you guys for watching today played
God and now I'm quitting God I don't
want to be God anymore
I'll leave it to you guys play the game
and be God
yeah but I was fun
it was fast fun while it lasted thanks
guys for watching
I'm quitting this job
um
thank you have a nice a nice Friday and
a nice Saturday and I'll see you on
Sunday my beloved timkins
[Music]
months
foreign
[Music]