[Music]
n
uh uh Kik
King
it's
broken 43 why is it on
43 K I'm so sorry I'm so sorry
uh I was going to do it with hard rate
monitor and it worked for a moment but
then it disconnected and then I tried
like a million times and it didn't
connect properly again I know I know
we do without we do without because in
the end I mean it's just like a one of
those like uh host Host Club kind of
streams uh or like just see it as you
need to revive me um and I'll just tell
you how I'm feeling I'll just tell you
how I'm
[Music]
feeling if I feel doy doie I'll let you
know um I'll I even tried like normally
you put the thing on your on your chest
but I even tried on my on my wrist it's
not supposed to be there this one
particular but it reacted to my wrist
too but still it wouldn't connect
properly whatever I think I don't know
maybe it's the Bluetooth maybe it's um
like I don't know the Wi-Fi here I don't
know but we got to get this party
started cuz the girls want to flirt with
me and um just as a reminder the
Valentine stuff I wanted to advertise
this originally it's still on sale so
feel free to uh go get the Valentine's
merchandise of all of us or just of me
however you want
um
yay and let's get started Kik Key by the
way Kik key probably going to be like an
hour stream or so and I forgot or like I
was too stressed to set up the stream
that comes after this but whatever uh
let's just um yeah
enjoy I'm going to go into the uh thing
hopefully hopefully the audio will be
okay do you guys hear the
bgm do you hear bgm starting tweet no
whatever I I don't I don't have time for
anything I'm too nervous everything ah
oh am I supposed to hear
you oh I see I don't I don't oh wait no
what say something keep talking hello
hello hello it's me oh wonderful
narissa revive
revive me oh oh okay wait no I should
have had a heart rate monitor on
yesterday when we were in the
onen honestly because I bet your heart
was going doky doie so hard very doy
doie can you guys hear her should I make
her louder I'll make a little bit I
think this should be yeah sorry I'm on
my phone it's okay phone is fine yeah
you can hear oh okay
okay well sorry to keep you waiting
yeah no it's okay um so I don't have any
pickup
lines uh that's cuz I don't want to pick
you up I want to pin you
down oh pretty good pretty
good where did you where did you get
that one from huh um I don't know you
don't know I don't know how does it make
you feel though is your heart pumping M
it was a little bit short so the doie
doie went away quickly I think oh oh
yeah yeah yeah I you got some more uh
yeah yeah I have I have two
more bring it on no they're all short so
I'm sorry you can also just flirt
naturally of course uh do you like
raisins uh no I actually don't oh well
how about a
date how about a date oh that's another
like similar uh fruit or so yeah a date
is yeah fruit so that's under the
assumption that I don't like
raisins yeah which I indeed don't like
raisins but did you know I don't like
raisins no but who does like
raisins it took me a moment to
understand what you
mean that's a bad pickup line if I have
to think about it oh apparently Callie
had Callie also had a pickup line like
that oh no me and Callie she got she has
a look up a new one now yeah it's it's
sorry cie now you have to change
it that didn't make me doie
doie okay okay okay the first one got
you though a little bit so uh yeah yeah
got it caught me by
surprise yeah okay here's here's my last
one I'm trying to revive you uh K I'll
be the pen and you can be the
highlighter I'll write our future and
you can make it
brighter I'm
[Laughter]
dead wow I can't believe kfp you
shouldn't rely on pickup lines like that
you should like just use your natural
Riz H my natural oh but I mean I Riz you
all the time you're just like you call
me cute too
much anymore me I still like you're
looking awfully ravishing today I still
go doie doie when you give me
compliments oh yeah it makes you doy
doie simple but I like it oh I'm still
thinking about yesterday and the Onsen
together I really still thinking about
as the
on yeah cuz K to sit next to you while
both naked there's something inherently
uh very fun about that very personal
made me feel very close to
you um yeah uh that that that was we had
a a lovely time in neon together and uh
completely say so totally yeah it was
completely say
so uh yeah it was also very very awkward
for me but uh I was I was doie doing so
I feel like uh if if we were to count
the doie doie from yesterday you would
probably be the winner of the hard
Challenger challenge today well I guess
if I ever want to bring you back to life
I'll just take you to an
onson yeah yeah yeah that would probably
work get my blood pressure Rising
too it's very hot did you also doie doie
in the
uh not not of excitement but out of
because of how nervous you were you made
me so nervous she was not excited to see
me nak do a lot no I was like cuz she
was like don't look and I was like I
wasn't going to look it
to so then I was like well I got to make
sure I'm very very careful to not
accidentally like make it seem like I'm
staring because I'm not you know but
then like I my eyes like looked she's
like were you staring at me and I was
like no I was just looking around I'm
sorry you made I was like I can't look
at her unless I'm saying
something so
yeah it's it's difficult but we did a
great job we did a great job fun I just
realized
something maybe I'm still by the way I'm
still I still have the strap on my chest
and I'm still trying to get it to work
um realized something that might be the
issue but I don't think it's the issue
either um yeah sorry sorry narissa you
don't my dookie doie was not very strong
well it's okay takamori is real so when
Callie gets in here I have full
confidence she's going to bring you back
to life maybe she'll even get my pul
Arts to work yes well I'll head out
because uh I need I need you to be
revived so Callie it's your turn goodbye
K goodbye no
N I guess you're not Nisa anymore
officially guys you got to stop calling
her nisla wow I try to be punny for once
and it doesn't work all right do your
best kiata don't die thank you bye oh
byebye bye it's oh byee it's beeping
byebye you guys did you hear the beep I
found the device again but I don't know
maybe C can instead of flirting give me
technical
troubleshooting hi Callie
oh
oh okay
Callie Callie I heard some noises
but hello
hey wait wait wait wait are you going
for like shock value no I just I thought
that if I like rolled around like the
throat candy in my mouth it would I
don't know you'd find it like
tantalizing or something I I didn't know
what it was no no it's it's a throat
candy I don't know I thought that like
you know you just imagine the throat
candy like rolling around in the mouth
look I'm giving it an honest try all
right the hate the hate didn't make me
go doie doie just out of
shock I like where where is she is she
here is she not and then suddenly
hey hey it's like a
scare hey girl how you doing hi hi hi hi
girl I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm doing I'm doing
I'm I'm nervous I'm nervous how are you
how are you I'm good yeah my name isn't
girl though uh oh my name is Microsoft
Microsoft
Can
Microsoft I said can I crash at your
place tonight get it cuz I'm
[Laughter]
Microsoft no all right you know k i find
that I wish I was probably the same
website that narissa used to be honest
um I wish I was crosseyed so I could see
you twice oh I mean you can probably do
that
yourself just just watch do you I guess
all right that's easy do you do you I
you want do oh get it man kar's already
come up with the best one dang that one
on purpose I should have used that no
dang it uh do you know do you cuz I want
to do you f can't believe I miss that
one oh [\h__\h] my my songs some of them I
don't write the lyrics you know but like
some of them are horny because Mooney is
uh apparently a little bit you know you
I get it now it makes it oh I get it now
was that on purpose the I think the do
you part no it's not supposed to apply
that but I think they were uh maybe not
in doy you but in other recent songs
yeah
[Music]
well I'm not done yet Kar she got more I
sure do hold on a sec I need s to Help
Me Hold
on Me
Up
yeah oh I mean I understood
that nice German nice
German
in in in
you are a hot
chicken you know I'm not so amused when
being called chicken that can't be how
about this one instead all right how
about this one
uh oh thank you you too Mr Microsoft
you're also very charming and
beautiful yeah oh yeah you remembered my
name I can't I can't forget the
Microsoft
true here's my best one though
okay bis do
Shrek well I think I think I'm supposed
to be
donkey okay well bisu
Shrek are you Shrek because um hold on
this one's kind of hard hang
on
how did you just translate a a English
Shrek line to German because in German
I'm not sure if it works what was it in
English I I translated because I'd let
you in my
swamp oh get it are you Shrek because
I'd let you in my
swamp do you get it is how would you say
I let you in my swamp get we have to
we're meeting later you got to tell me
what you mean with the
swamp I'd let you in my swamp that's
literally all there is to are you Shrek
I'd let you in my
[Music]
[Applause]
swamp shre Kara but I'm donkey I'm your
donkey fine I sh because I'm your
donkey oh that's that's kind of cute
actually what are you okay hold on a sec
are you donkey hold on I want be your
donkey
yeah amazing
German thank you because I want to hold
on I I think hold on this is big this is
big okay not is not
micro
maybe
uh I want to make waffles for you oh
that's so
sweet we can't German so hard Kar I
don't know how you speak it
oh that you you're doing like amazing I
don't think you're struggling with it at
all and it's very I think I guess it's
pretty um Charming if someone's trying
to learn your your language your own
language so yeah I'm very flattered I'm
very Charmed by your efforts yeah the
Microsoft one is probably the the most
doie doie and the hey in the beginning
the hey
hey that's pretty genius hey anybody
else who's coming in today I'm going to
give you a cheat code just just give her
a shock be like yeah he baby don't have
to necessarily flirt I
mean just surprise me jump scare jump
scare is the way to go yeah well it's a
it's a shame that we couldn't be there
with you to today in the studio to like
maybe feel your heart and like report it
to everyone no you you probably would
have fixed my my thing maybe I don't
know may we could have put our heads
together we'll see each other later yeah
see you later it's going to be going to
be weird trying to explain my Swamp
Thing to you know we're just going to
forget about that entire situation just
forget that happen me Microsoft isn't
coming over C pimi is coming over that's
right Microsoft is a different entity
and Microsoft is going to leave now okay
are we ever going to hear from Microsoft
again you know M she might show up maybe
one day when he will
be what's the opposite of
micro um macro macro soft macro hard
yeah that's right macro hard baby I'm
expecting you bye see you later macro
hard's on the way
[Laughter]
peace oh man I would have been curious
about my heart rate for that
one
but alas it's still on
43 how
unfortunate macro not we have another
micro um lady
here hey hey Who you calling micro huh
you you tiny aren't you like the
smallest
now well being small doesn't mean oh the
the the entirety of me is small I may be
small but I have a big heart oh you do
SM very different my heart is is looking
at you
today oh yes I like Hello you do good
because this is the the real me and I
don't usually bring myself out for
people but today is special so hello
um now I've been watching the other two
and I feel
like you know they they're lacking in
something and that thing is spice so
today I'm bringing out my mature self
and I want to ask you are you into rocks
do you like rocks
um
yes I I like when I like rocks because
they are very very unlike
Microsoft good yeah because I'm glad you
like rocks because I have something hard
for you you got some hard
rocks wholesomely of course Maybe not
today maybe not wholesomely today not
wholesomely today all right just for you
cuz where we're being mature today yes
um oh are your rocks ever not hard no
I'm always always hard always it's an
issue for me so you are micro hard 24/7
yes I am the micro hard yes um oh wow
you should go to a
doctor maybe but it's okay for this
situation I
guess good job good job people so far
and you know I don't I don't mean to
ruffle your feathers but I would like to
Peck a kiss on that
beak cute
wow and and you know I really wanted to
tell you that you know kfp is my
favorite restaurant because it has the
juiciest breast and thighs oh
[\h__\h] she is 100% correct she is she gets
it she's wow what a
rler be be be be the bz she's got the be
RZ
but are you sure are you sure you're a
bird you sure I think so why because
you're kind of looking like a kitten and
I would like to make you mine
meow yes meow yes meow for
[Applause]
me I I I'll be a kitten
B this is really weird I never I never
have seen you as uh like this kind of
person I know it doesn't come out often
but but I make it out for you you are
special that's why I I make it come out
for you yes wow I'm I must be special to
you yes you're you're so special
um B you people you got any more where
that came
from
um it's okay you already did plenty I
did a lot yeah don't make I'm tired
don't make me do anything else what else
do you want you're so you're so
demanding women be boo small be boo you
know the only problem is you're yeah
pretty small like I'll have to you know
bend down for the
pick it's okay
I'll I'll come up to you with on my
tippy toes and push you against that
wall tippy toes won't be enough I
think
oh what are we going to do
well at least I'd be a good height for
something else they say you can fly I
don't believe it oh oh yeah I can fly
yes I can fly so that's no problem what
makes you what gives you the ability to
fly I kind of doubt
it I have wings where are oh don't you
call those
wings yes I have wings wait wait
where the the things like the aren't
those like stones
gems on on my back I mean they're not I
don't I have waist call swings I don't
know you got to show me you can fly but
okay if you if that's possible then I
guess anything is possible then then
then we have no problem with you being
so
micro
yes don't have have I made your heart um
doky doie as they call it so I I will
say so far like narissa I'll give her a
a one out of
10 cie was probably like a six or seven
out of 10 let's say let's give her
6.5 and for you wow must say that was
was like 7 7.5 out of
10 yes I mean I mean
um naturally naturally my my r power is
just that high obviously so you didn't
even
try
yes thank you people you're welcome
think of me when you talk to the other
girls how could I not I think I think
all the time I think from now on all my
thoughts are filled with your
Stones
yes my Stones I will not you yes harder
than anything on the most scale yes do
you know what that is no it has hardness
and I'm the most hard damn one can only
aspire to be as hard as you yes damn
okay I must go but think of me wait wait
wait wait what what what what what what
what okay I thought of I thought of a
spontaneous pickup line tell me about
how hard you are again oh I'm so hard
as a rock I'm rock hard tell me how
nobody else is
harder no one else is as hard as
me no one else could top that except for
me I'll top
you wow wow that came out of my natural
rib brain y'all SM do I get a 10 out of
10o I must
go
was that good I think that was a that
was a flirt I attempted a flirt did I
defeat her I fought
back okay okay okay oh
oh oh
hello wait go back to the sensual go
back to the sensual
[Music]
B that does things to
me no go back to
theual you keep on reverting
[Laughter]
back yes how could you what did I
do how could you do this what did I do
did it's so hot my eyes feel dry when I
look at you for too
long I'm I'm sorry that's
just I I feel I feel uh somewhat of the
same about you how could you do this to
me oh your eyes feel fuzzy you're so hot
you make me feel like I have
allergies is it
cun
something makes me feel something
funny funny yeah do I make you laugh it
seems like
it I am I funny to you do I amuse you
no yes I have a problem too you have a
problem what is it I've lost my feathers
thinking about
you away with me you don't yeah you
don't have any feathers to begin with I
have fluffy feathers thank you where
show me I don't see them Just Fur te
feathers like cut right just don't touch
my tail feathers they're there you just
don't know okay no no no no no no you
only a f don't don't don't try the
person
B no no no b b b
ball well done oh I are you food for the
soul because whenever I look at you my
heart feels so
full
huh but then it's heart food not soul
food what is it soul food and I I like
my
best
okay yeah we didn't use any websites
like from
my came up with it on your own yeah
but do you like
raisins did you just say you came up
with it yourself you raisin oh I hate
them because I'm raing your
children what what oh oh cuz you're
racing I thought you were going to say
the same cuz narissa was narissa she
also said a raisin pickup
line
oh date okay you're going to raise my CH
I think that one's better than the other
raisin pickup
line myself when said
that that's what she thought the the the
part would be I thought that was the
natural progression of that
one maybe there's many raay in pick up
lines
maybe damn so many raisins
off very Charming aren't you I've never
done this before am am I your
type oh well kind of scary so
but
but I want you I love
you oh oh
that
just my my heart rate may still say 43
but I I think it's going up over
100 are we are we even better than b oh
no best B was a nine out of 10 a you
girls you girls it's kind of difficult
because you girls are it's not just you
know one versus one it's two versus one
and that's that's wow very very that's a
lot is that not allowed is that cheating
it's allowed it's it's very welcome it's
new you know what makes me doie doie
more than your your pickup lines huh the
thought of meeting you
yeah
soon TM soon soon are you also doky
[Laughter]
doie okay I'm looking forward to it bow
bow but Discord Discord Cuts you off
when you're so excited so you should do
the sensual bow bows
again
bow is that you wait are you sure yes
you're I just saying that yeah I me that
I mean it I like I like theal B
[Laughter]
balls they keep on rning back to the
excited B okay when when
last I guess I love you too I don't I
guess
so have fun better bye
by byebye feel
better I'm going try to get yeah my
heart rate higher cuz this is really
concerning thank you thank you yeah we
wish you luck thank you bye-bye by
bye thank you for visiting me in the
hospital I'm getting so many visitors
it's it's visitation hour in the waa
Hospital they're the first to
acknowledge it
yeah I mean jenma also acknowledged it
she was like what is this I'm you oh we
have a Japanese
guest
oh my God please let us know I want to
hear
go did you think I was pretty girl Jang
I'm my name
is nice to meet
you um actually guys uh I I did not like
give Japanese members and open
invitation I just wrote to her in
particular because I I thought like she
she must be good at ring I hear she
Rises up other
girls
please make
me
yes handsome handsome
owl
fore
for will you me I love you
[Music]
[Applause]
yay
show
fore
[Music]
for
for I you will you Mar
me
[Laughter]
for for
for
[Music]
[Applause]
foree
please yes okay I
don't
[Laughter]
for
bye
bye I love
you oh oh oh oh that yeah um maybe you
guys need to wait for subtitles for this
call but she was very quick on uh uh
yeah proposing to
me uh I have another guest who I need to
get the picture of really quickly I got
it I got it I got it I got
she was the only one like the other I
was just like hey who wants to call in
but for I was on I I directly went to
her I was like hey we never talked
before but do you want to call in and
yes this is the next
one doo doo she's still in the waiting
room ah there she
is
hello hello
hello
hello Mushy Mushy there's no no audio
coming
for hello ma
ma
ma your microphone is like broken or
something it's okay I'll fix the picture
in the meantime oh I'm sorry oh there
you go
I'm sorry I'm so nervous it's okay
because I can't take it it just so
nervous to meet the most
perfect person that God ever made in
this world so um I'm sorry so do you
have the time I uh I have all the time
in the world because I don't ever
die oh thank God I'm so sorry I suddenly
come and call you I just I just want to
remember the exact minute I got a crush
on
you oh that's where you were going ah I
ruined your your attempt in flirting
sorry the excitement okay it is it is uh
1 p.m 14 minutes oh write it down write
it down I
mean you know I saw you right now in the
bat yes but I I don't know
why I I don't I don't know why right now
I think I think I'm really glad I just
bought life insurance because when I saw
you my heart
stopped oh [\h__\h] well then we should get
we should I think I need a CPR do you
have a CPR yeah I think you just took my
bread away with your beauty yo the the
the hospital bed next to me is empty so
you can you can take that one we call
there they have to fix both of our
hearts I mean I mean why do I need to to
lay down on on a bed next to when I can
lay down the same bed with you
oh okay okay okay I mean in the first
place it's kind of concerning that
strangers are coming into my visitation
hours I mean no you're not a stranger to
me I this is not the first time talking
about Str do you remember when we made
that the first time you know is this a
serious question or is this like a yeah
yeah this is a serious question uh I
mean I used to wear glasses all the time
before but I think when when we met the
first time I didn't I didn't wear it
right I didn't wear any glasses right no
no yeah you do wear glasses no I don't I
don't I don't think I need glasses
anymore because I can clearly see what
we're meant to
be I think I was like is is she
seriously asking me I don't think you
were seriously asking just you're just
trying to go down your
script yeah I mean I prepared all these
makeup lines on NS because I need to be
prepared to say it to you to such a most
beautiful and wonderful oh my God I
don't think that she's on the wrong I
don't think the world is fair especially
on how God made you I mean he was surely
showing off based on how perfect you
are I mean look in the mirror L same
thing applies to
you w you
know I have a pickup line okay wait it's
just coming out of my brain so okay give
me a moment it's like are are um are we
are we uh uh wait how do I build this
coming up with your own pickup L is
difficult I'm waiting yeah okay
um ah ah ah are are you
from uh are you from Game Freak because
I think we are Pokemon Sun and Moon
uh I don't know I don't know I need to I
need to write it better but that's where
I'm going that's we're a Pokemon game
you and me we belong to together we we
we were ah no wait I I got it I got it
are you on the are you on the DS
Nintendo
DS because I think you're Pokemon Moon
and I'm Pokemon Sun oh nintend I think
that's really
sweet somebody even though make it
better somebody surely even though we
are the Sun
Moon even though we are the Sun Moon I
don't I don't get it why we never took a
selfie together I mean we didn't didn't
you think we look so good together
especially on white dress did we did we
really never take a picture together no
we never take a picture together don't
you think we look so good together
totally imagine we together with own
white I have one I have one I have one I
have one I have
one well no you're you're the the moon
I'm the sun maybe we should
Eclipse holy [\h__\h] go go on top of me I
don't mind I don't mind to collide with
you wait
I'm wasn't that amazing holy
[\h__\h] we can we should make a collab song
that's called
Eclipse oh yeah let's go oh yeah let's
go wait that I cooked you cooked too MAA
let's go we're meant to
[Music]
be oh my God I don't know why I mean
it's seriously I my heart is beating so
fast really I thought it was I thought
it was on zero I thought your heart
stops so beating so fast I okay then
you're healed now you you can leave the
hospital
then oh do you think so yeah cuz do you
think I can leave the hospital when
you're at the hospital I mean I should
follow my dream right so wherever you go
I should follow
you okay okay then for now I guess you
got to stay wherever you you got to
follow me wherever I go that that is
also kind of like I mean I don't I don't
mind uh when your bad is well I don't
mind you sitting you know laying in a
behind or above you oh thank you thank
you
okay I think you I think you're like
you're you're done like we I think you
accomplished what you came here
for well I think I think that's all for
today I will come again guys wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait what
guys um did did you check did you check
the the the calendar guys I think
tonight is an eclipse a full
eclipse oh
really check the sky tonight and you'll
see a full sun and moon
eclipse why did I become the
FLIR why why should I check the sky if I
can check on you oh yeah you don't need
to check you're part of okay
okay okay I'm going by no no no you're
getting a 10 out of 10 because uh you
actually okay I you got me doie doie
because you made me flirt with
you
heyun yeah byebye have fun thank you
byebye oh my God okay wow
wow that was amazing okay uh so
guys I'm not bad at coming up pick a
blinds either am
I um I I remember one thing I wanted to
do uh oopsie up up up that's my stream
um M previously wanted to call in right
I think she did tell me I think maybe
she forgot let me try to message her
otherwise we can watch her YouTube video
on it there was a clip I think hey are
you are you there you wanted to call in
the Stream is now
[Music]
she for Gore let me try to call she's
offline in Discord but I'll give it a
[Music]
try what time is it in North America
like
roughly I think it's it should she
should be awake right yeah 9 10 whatever
p.m. yeah this a it's awake time she
should be
awake yeah but no she's not she's not
online the call did not go through so I
guess I'll try watching her uh what was
it m
flirt uh
yeah there was a clip and I purposefully
didn't watch it
uh what do I look on YouTube to find
[Music]
it do you guys
know maybe watch it at the end well it's
um I uh that's that's probably uh uh cuz
yeah there was one more person planned
but couldn't come so and then mum but
mum not here so I think this is pretty
much the end
it's on her 1 hour stre yeah but like
what what was it m pick up blind I think
that's what it was a is it three weeks
ago that makes that would make
sense how long is this okay here I'm
just going to listen to
this
and going to see if I I feel
something
wait is this it no that's not it that's
just her listening to other people's
pickup
lines wait don't go yet because I have a
reveal I have a reveal M quotes for K's
Valentine's stream ah okay okay thank
you m kada
Valentine's there we go found
it
uh-huh uh-huh
uh-huh well you could have said it to me
but you
forgot she talks so fast you can't hear
oh I think it's too quiet because I can
see it uh oh wait maybe it's because of
the B
bgm it's just too quiet I think let me
let me try to I thought she would call
in so I didn't download
this
YouTube I can try to download it really
quickly all I don't remember what my
usual YouTube downloading
program was but I'm just going to do
this
one it wasn't audible okay okay okay I
got it I got it
720p hopefully he
acceptable oh don't spoiler me on her
pickup
lines oh sure okay okay oh my
God okay I got it I got it I got it I'll
throw it on on on the
stream uh hopefully it might be a little
bit loud in the first moment one thing I
thought I could do okay okay okay okay
okay and then we do we
do Monitor and output I think okay this
is
M mum wanted to call in but uh she also
revealed her pickup lines on stream
before so we'll react to this
say drink y stream which had to be to
tomorrow but I'm not free tomorrow at
that time because I I have a lot to do
tomorrow um so instead of doing it in
that stream perhaps I could show you
some clotes because I did a lot of
research to collect things that would
make her heart rate increase I wrote
down some quotes it's not going to be
nearly as funny because she can't
respond and it's not funny to say it to
you guys because I don't know it just it
just wouldn't be
funny guess what K's responses were
going to be so maybe what I could do was
tell you guys what I was going to say
and then do the responses that I think
she would have responded with oh she
will do the response too no it's fine
time to pick that up so I'm going to go
to my notes app I had so many tabs open
earlier again a form of procrastination
I was collecting things for the stream
last minute um but then it didn't happen
but that's okay because because it'll
happen tomorrow but maybe it's for the
best I do these things they're pretty
bad I was going to say hello baby girl
you're looking fine today and I wasn't
going to call from my computer because I
was going to be probably in my bed uh on
my laptop I was going to say like sorry
I'm using my phone right now and then
she was going and I bet she was going to
say oh you're on your phone where are
you and I was going to be like
in and um go it's okay and then I was
going to at some point I was going to
bring up her uh wide pelvic bones and I
was just not as funny here I was going
to make a comment about them and say
like bir for scientific reasons I find
those attractive for scientific reasons
what the heck and I was going to be
like 20 questions I was going to ask 20
questions and she was going to say okay
and I was going to say okay you ask the
first question and the question she was
going to ask was going to be something
like um like what's your favorite bird I
was ask say you of course okay now it's
my turn what's your bra size and she's
going to be like what and then her heart
was going to
go she got it all planned out but it
didn't go according to K over and she
was going to say no and I was going to
say well that's okay because no matter
what a real Alpha will do whatever it
takes to achieve real Alpha and that
it's fine and I can walk away um I can
walk I can walk alone I can walk away
and I can walk alone I was going to walk
away before she fully rejected me and I
was going to tell myself my education
career and money will never wake up wait
yeah yeah my education career money will
never wake up one day and decide to
leave me so it's fine if she doesn't
want me wow I did a lot of research for
this so that's what I was trying to say
to her but now I can't because I'm not
available during the time that her
stream is tomorrow but be sure to watch
her stream tomorrow apparently she
wasn't available for sure
that g up if I was there no doubt what
do you guys think okay now I will engage
in conversation with the chat do you
guys think that I would have have um
made her blush and that her heart rate
would have gone up and I would have won
the
competition that was very
confusing the ending makes me think that
she's not much of an alpha when she
thinks when she assumes that it will go
badly and then she has to leave in a way
that makes her seem like she doesn't
give a [\h__\h] she doesn't care just
doesn't she's not bothered at all by me
rejecting her no no no although is that
an alpha V I don't know
but her insecurities were
showing Alpha probably have a lot of
insecurities I don't
[Laughter]
know um she should have um gone
deeper into the hips I mean she should
have gone deeper into the topic of the
hips because she quickly just dropped it
she just drops that and just moves on
immediately but hey hey here Cooks Wawa
again with another
flirt maybe I'm the heart Challenger
after all always has
been all right now guys I want to reveal
something uh this the stream will only
be like an hour uh but I want reveal
something and then later we're going to
have another stream which will be in
offc K it will actually be in like 2
hours and I need to prepare it so I'm
going to move uh some
stuff here I'll just go all the way to
the
front because I'll just show you
something I'm going to reveal something
I'm going to bring the bgm back do you
hear it do did you ever hear it I'm
going to I'm going to take up the whole
screen okay is that
okay here what I'll bring I'll bring the
chat to the front
though I was um going to possibly
revealed this already a month
ago but uh you know I don't know I
didn't really have a after that one time
where the stream failed I didn't have a
good opportunity to uh reveal it new
accessory oh he
what could it be what could it oops oh
did you see that no
okay okay I have a reveal we'll start
with something small and again I have uh
added accessories to this outfit which
already has so many
accessories please close your
eyes did you close them a this feels
like a flirt doesn't it maybe I
bamboozle you with oh who I'm cooking
imagine I tell you I have some accessory
to reveal and I make you close your eyes
and then I'm
like
wow wow oh my God I'm I'm such a heart
Challenger wow let C okay here we go
close your
eyes and
open wow I am looking at all the the I
don't know the cute chickens and super
chats and I don't
know bling bling oh
good cute K
eyes and they move they do you see they
pulsate unlike my heart apparently
because my my heart rate monitor didn't
pick it up um but yeah and then close
your eyes one more one
more are they
closed
okay and three
two
no you that was just a chew okay one
more time close your
eyes are they closed 3 2
one I got hard
eyes cute
wow maybe they're a little bit small can
you see them can you see my heart maybe
I should have put my heart rate monitor
on my
eyes they're also pulsating by the way
and maybe I should have put it thereare
that's the only place where I seem to
have a heart in my
eyes donkey donkey
D okay y I have one more one more one
more one more one more one more keep the
heart eyes though though for now what
could the other thing be it's a it's a
bigger one it's a pretty big one it's a
oh lot HEC coming kind of
Chunk three a two a one
oh that wait that's the wrong one you
know that one ah no
no it's this three two
one I got a proper
timin
look wow
cute it's you guys it's you you're cute
yes
[Music]
actually a BRB because this is maybe not
the best version of
it oh my God
don't don't don't look uh yeah I mean I
can also carry you without without that
uh yeah do you want to be carried while
I'm wearing the bikini
fine I knew you wanted that t I'm
covering up my
tatas with the chimpin yeah this is the
better version okay look
M ah it's you guys really
looks
perfect
wow thank you for um letting me use you
as a censorship uh method
oh look at the feet look at the
fies they wiggle wiggle they wiggle
wiggle it's a kfb
plusy yeah which you guys also got as a
merch item
recently yay look at you look at you a
cute AR too cute I can't go that low
unfortunately I can't give you a chew on
your forehead I wish I could um but yeah
so if we um
combine uh oh never mind I can't combine
it here yeah but that's it that's cute
cute Cy jkin I actually have another
accessory uh that I like so to say
commissioned together with all this but
that one has a special reveal another
time anyway so take pictures of this
cutie pouti I mean you of course now
me wow the is
wow uncore accessory oh soon
soon selfie
selfie
selfie wink wonk wink
wonk uh there you
go cute okay guys I'm sorry and in the
end even now I brought my heart rate
monitor all the way to Japan it still
didn't work out I'm so sorry about that
uh but we got some flirts we got some to
I don't do very
[Music]
often my it was it was a silly one a
little stream now I have to set up the
next one it's in 2 hours now less no
yeah 2 hours and 20 minutes uh at 400
p.m. 4 P.M 4M jsd we're gonna have a k I
still have to put up the reservation
it's archived because we're going to
sing whole life songs uh participants
will
[Music]
be
and mov and
I'm and me so uh please come by we're
going to have some fun uh in the spirit
of Hol Fest coming up uh uh we're going
to sing some Hol songs and yeah be
wholesome
together and with that being said enj
but also don't forget about the
Valentine's merch that is still
available right now in the Holo shop and
I think maybe also gek Jack I don't know
um but yeah wa has the charm and the
towel that is for all of myth and the
emblem badge and you get a handwritten
bonus message if you get the full set I
guess
y look at it the towel is really useful
in the summer when it's a sweaty
spaghetti you know yeah thank you for
your support happy white day Happy
Valentine's Day and the Polaroids
actually I didn't I so occupied with the
calls I didn't uh see did you did you
all guys get in your polar WS if you
wanted to get some and they are special
white day
version and I'll be signing them uh yeah
you have I give you like if you didn't
get it you get one more chance one more
minute or so a pinky for uh one of those
Polaroids this time they'll get like a
white day it's the same the same kind of
like uh chickens but the the frame is a
little bit different this time it's like
a rose rose frame where I I I could show
you but uh this is not my computer so I
don't have it saved right now but uh
it's the same as for Valentine's the
menu is on the
community uh board from like a month ago
okay I didn't prepare it uh well to
advertise it to you forgive me but
yeah Happy Valentine's and happy W day I
hope you enjoyed the white day which
normally I don't think I've ever
celebrated white day before thank you
[Music]
naan my first time so to say celebrating
white day who is is the best Razer by
the way I forgot to give everybody a
ranking uh I would say our our
[Music]
ranking four out of 10 I think if she
gives me that kabedon IRL then it it's a
different story but yeah uh MAA MAA MAA
made me flirt back so it's 10 out of 10
yeah people was good really good did I I
think I ranked her nine out of 10 did
I I think so and M mum is hard to rank
cuz it was so fast and like uh not
really you know she wasn't talking to me
directly she was talking to the stream
so a little bit difficult but she had
some good
like lines that could be worked on if we
had an actual
conversation uh we could like extend the
conversation yeah she was
rapping she was
moving m
got to give her a chance and I don't
know if I can rate her fairly uh I I
could see something you know happening
there but like the ending with her just
like like defending herself and reject
like after rejection or just assuming
that there would be a rejection H got to
work on her
confidence yeah I wanted her to dig
deeper into my hips
exactly Mo out of 10 exactly nice nice
the doggles did I not rate the
doggles wasn't one of 10 har R has a
better flirt game day by day I think
when she was actually trying to flirt it
was like I can bump her up to three out
of
10 the b b did I not rate them really
did I not b b was the the Cal bow BS
were really good the pickup lines were
from the heart I give him a six out of
maybe yeah K I already
rated that I love you yeah I love
you I want you I want love you yeah that
that surprised me that caught me off
guard too what do you thought what did
you think about my random I think I I I
came up with my own pickup lines like
the whole Muna pickup lines are wow the
Pokmon
the eclipse the Pokemon game I couldn't
find a good way to say it so if you guys
figure out a good way to say it let me
know what do you mean no
comment W out of
10 kind of cringe excuse
me
no Pokemon once lost C no I'm sure
someone talented could probably figure
that one
out so MAA wins with a close second
place for the heart Challenger people
but the number one heart
Challenger was Mo H NOA from
ID doy doy doie
doie thank you so much it was kind of
last minute um uh notification to ID
they uh didn't get much of a heads up
from me
sorry about that so uh don't don't take
it as the other girls didn't want to
flirt with me oh you know me and I are
BFFs forever
so
yeah natural r sun moon let's
go yeah ah the prize is a eclipse song
Perhaps I maybe there's already an
existing song that's called Eclipse I
feel like that would be already exist
okay sorry for the short stream but you
know we're streaming again in 2 hours
and 15 minutes so in German we say s
second
time have a nice day see you
[Music]
later and hope you guys are hyped up for
holo Fest and Holo XO I'm getting really
hyped it's getting closer and closer and
closer let's go Al in
bye-bye
wo cute chicken C cute chicken
wow cute hi peekaboo a
[Music]
peekaboo