[Music]
H promise ladies a m oh so cute thank
you
Sensei
I thank you so much B get your head out
of gutter man oh be it's not a face Goda
is
real what we're known for big deal man I
love F don't you it is on over
[Music]
Che everyone so cool man I
yeah uh
uh
uh you're now listening to FAA FM this
ain't your granny's radio
station I'm your DJ Kieran FAA and get
ready to J out
go power
[Music]
1 2 3 go there is spot with a blow we
are Hollow promise I'm famous heyo I am
a big shot look on TV gaming Idol here
in as me bucket we ball never punish
never greedy no i' win
[Music]
I want a what a dramatic
entrance go H you win have I won already
did I already win did I win
everything go hello you've caught me oh
you've caught me I don't remember
anything oh my gosh all my memories are
gone you've caught me at a very sleepy
moment which I feel bad about
[Music]
I'm feeling I'm feeling I'm feeling
sleepy which is not the the mood that
you want to be in when you're about to
start such a hype program so if you guys
could wake me up that would
be much
appreciated I know it's a little late
for granny fauna but it's like not even
that late it's so much later for some of
the others so I can only tell you that
right now because if I complain about
being tired later it's going to come off
the wrong way because they had St up so
much later than
me I don't want to be
my princess self complaining when I've
got it got it
[Music]
easy my tired this is valid we were
setting up for a while I mean we weren't
doing anything of the sort we're
just just woke up and we're all We're
All in This Strange room right now Al I
have voice chat muted right now but
don't worry it will be unmuted
later I'm just not ready for the full
chaos of full 19 person trapped in one
tiny room just yet
but we're in we're in this this sorry
bumping into people we're in this white
room it's so bright in here oh
God if you weren't awake now I bet
you're awake now if you weren't awake
yet I bet you're awake now do I remember
how to talk I forgotten even the basics
of the English language
uh-oh The Flash
B hold on hold on can I do a bit I mean
what's the like darkest thing I can look
at I mean shy probably works the back of
sh's head no she's on to
me just stare into the void and then
this one goes out to everybody who's
watching on their phones in bed this is
for you this this this void is for
you sleepy debuff adds to the
immersion maybe we'll see I hope
everything works I'm a little bit scared
because I'm kind of a control frak and
they're like not telling us
anything they're like oh it's it's going
to be fine don't worry everything will
be explained to you in the game don't
worry about it it's going to work
perfectly and I'm
like the Scuff the scuff though I don't
know just go with the flow I'm I'm bad
at just going with the flow oh this is a
little easier on the eyes
[Music]
maybe oh perfect for amnesia
well if anything goes wrong at least
it's not my fault
[Music]
today but I'm I'm a little do I have the
brightness filter on wait do do I it's
been so long since I played no I don't
we could turn it
on how's that I mean it can't get any
brighter in
here
right get that get that out of here no
more made it
worse can it really be that much worse
torturous you're already
blind we could turn the brightens down
[Music]
okay I'm I'm checking the Discord right
now I'm
checking yeah like I was saying they
haven't told us anything they're just
like everything will be explained as you
play I'm like I I hope
so I hope so what do I know I know that
that there are four guilds and we get to
go to a sorting ceremony today which
even that I was like but how do we get
there like are we going to have to Uber
to the Sorting ceremony or will we be
teleported or is it walkable distance
like how are we going to get to the
Sorting ceremony you know yeah who's
who's driving do they know I don't have
my
license it's like that so but they're
like don't worry about it don't
worry you'll find your way
there does the Sorting Hat have lice do
you think it does I feel like it would I
mean it just takes one right maybe it
has a spell on it to not give it lies
definitely does the magical sorting lies
wait maybe that's how it works the lies
eat your scalp skin and that's what
determines what house you're going to be
in the Sorting Hat is used by literally
everyone in the whole group right so if
you
imagine I mean I what from what I've
heard like kindergartens are rampant
with lice
so
imagine like a whole univer wait are
they in college or are they in high
school wait are they like 10 wait aren't
they like 10 at the start I don't know
much
about Harry Potter it's elementary
school they're 11 dang they're already
going to like magic school at 11 years
old
do they also have to learn like
algebra at Hogwarts I don't know I guess
in my brain I always think of it is more
of like a university experience that way
you already have your prerequisites
taken out you don't have to learn
algebra magical
algebra you don't need algebra when you
have magic I mean that's you can use the
same argument for when you have a
calculator in your pocket right oh wait
is it starting
soon are they some people are you can
see who's muted and who's
not I don't know if it's starting though
I'm
scared I don't know yet if the cut scene
is there I was told about a cut scene I
haven't played much mod in Minecraft I
don't know how I'm like okay but like
the cuts scene are we going to have to
like look at it or will it be like
beamed directly into our brains you know
I need the details of how cutscene will
appear will it appear to us in a
collective dream or perhaps
hallucination I don't know I don't
know imagine I was unmuted by accident
the whole time when everyone else is
trying to have a conversation I'm
talking about if the Sorting Hat has Li
in it or
[Music]
not is it is it on a giant TV or is it
more of a projector situation because if
it's a projector then I need to make
sure that I'm not blocking the beam with
my horns or else the the silhouette of
my horns will be projected on to
everyone's view but if it's if it's like
a
screen well then we have to ask is it
OLED or not because then we might have
to worry about something like burning if
there's UI elements perhaps that could
be a that could be a concern as
well q l
d they're
fighting should we talk to them it looks
like most of them are out I'm shy though
[Music]
when I when I unmute that's the that's
the end of the oh wait we're going okay
never mind no
[Music]
one this is this is what I mean this is
what I was talking about if they had
only told me if it was a CED or an OLED
I could have prepared for
this okay did this happen everybody else
or is it just
me oh it was everyone I
think you see this is this is why you I
need to know if we're taking Uber or if
it's a taxi does the taxi accept card or
do I need to have cash you know these
are
important
details Bann for
gapping Gap
related
crimes need gold coins
okay I we may or may not be able to
rejoin I was afraid this is what I was
afraid
of did I not warn you okay we're back in
the the
room you can
hear their
punches the darkness is so nice well
here you go this one goes after
everybody watching on their phone in bed
trying to go to sleep how do you feel
about
[Music]
this I'm sorry they gave me too much
power okay hold on let me let me unmute
let me be
social we still asking
God the last 24 hours as well all right
seems very
together St
as you look like you look fine not you
look fine wait why you fine fine not
good
great is the thank you you look good
enough you know your name
[Music]
hello I swear the voices were not so
loud in my head
earlier how would you know I cover
your kind of L such a big bra coming
back that's Cy it's that
I feel like I've heard that before why
are you so
quiet like everyone's loud except you
too I called you reverse
proximity back up back up no it's
okay oh I don't think it's reversed at
least I don't think it's revers I don't
think it's revers maybe you're
see all these numbers as perhaps I was
trying to balance it before and maybe
somehow it didn't my name is I'm trying
to get you in my right
ear okay let me whisper into your right
ear
hello would you
get I'm supposed to be a cute girl
right I attuned my ears to the frequency
of of this one's
Voice have you adjust oh did you adjust
it like in your
head I think I have to do the same for
you please please speak
helloing directly to you you are but why
who why is B also in my ear I mean who
the heck is that she just looks like a b
she does maybe it's the letters floating
above her
head oh are those letters is that what
those are I know seems like your your
deletion went pretty
deep I forgot how to read need to go
back to the elementary school
classroom I think so I my head pretty
hard the alphabet C
circus you know I'm having faint memory
of like those little paper pamphlets did
you have do you remember
those there were lots of paper
pamphlet I oh
oh okay okay press sneak key echo of
forgotten
me which is
Sneak control uhoh is it control who am
I wait I feel like my music selection is
wrong hold
on I I came prepared for
this wait maybe maybe this
one who am I the world I live
in and more than
anything it's next to the Gerald button
oh gosh don't accidentally push the
Gerald button more than any did I
already read that more than anything the
people I hold most
dear ooh faced with Oblivion I feel
empty oh I feel like my DJing is on
point so far
relieved perhaps
distraught I'm just feeling sleepy I do
not know
so much I don't know and yet
oh that bright light it call don't go
into the
light is anybody else concerned about
this symbolism of going into the bright
light I've gone into the light before I
guess it wouldn't hurt to go again I
everybody is going yeah you might be
right yeah yes if everybody
else go to the light follow the
light go to the light I feel like
falling into the void must be
worse the are we going to shoot up do we
shoot up like
Las me up I'm
ready I like I don't like that want to
Ali take me up take me take
me
me too many voices do we go can we go up
can we can we go we don't go up should
we go towards the light are we already
failing our Quest that that looks like
an egg this is much yeah
right that looks like a it's like a
broken egg what is a soul G a hole but
what came first oh my God don't turn
around it's not a hole it's not a
hole which
light you think we pick the wrong way oh
never mind the sun's out to you
everybody watching from home in your bed
in the darkness and the light
deol
Castle they're
cute you there what are you doing
here you tell
me you have the look of Outsiders about
you this Rude the thing to
say wait could it be am I the chosen one
quick send word to his majesty I knew it
I knew it I'm the chosen one oh I'm
sorry my crop hold on I'm professional
streamer we can fix
this you're going to sacrifice the other
side
though right
away already meeting with the the Royals
King Li wait I feel like the music I
hold on the music is wrong I forgot it's
not part of how about how about this
one
instead wait this one's too
quiet this is very
important you
see sorry what did you say your majesty
what was that the gods who brought you
here have informed me that you remember
not but your own
names FAA and
FAA a side effect of travel between
worlds no
doubt he's thinking this must all come
as a surprise to you but hearken well it
was I who summoned you
here oh sorry I have sticky keys on are
you supposed to turn it on or off
disable
it I never
remember ah it has sewn the Earth with
corruption and driven us from our
homes never on I turned it why does it
keep popping up then
uh-oh
beep this blinded land now gives rise to
creatures of Shadow known as
stains why does it make such sounds
oh
no the kingdom of lib and its
surroundings are now the only safe place
left to us in the
stands but should the Calamity be left
unchecked is only a matter of time
before it consumes the entire
world you're so cute faced with this
Prospect I scoured the ancient tanks for
a way to combat the Calamity and therein
I found one night 19
[Music]
oh one one ritual 19
Heroes the ritual of hero
summoning disable
it it says okay it says disable the
keyboard shortcut yes or
no no
yes yes I clicked yes and then it
started beeping even more
yes beep
only you have the power to save our
world why is he beeping at
[Music]
me turn it off and disable
it search sticky keys on wind Boop I'll
search it in a
minute I like the beeps I'm just
imagining that's what the king sounds
like and so I asked will you
P it's kind of cute
oh
green your
majesty what is it a great host of
saints has broken through our defensive
line
no we are rushing to mount defense but
the situation is Tire Your Majesty we
must get you somewhere
safe hold on disable
it sticky keys wait it says it's off
oh but the keyboard shortcut is
on okay
maybe
t hold on I need to zoom through the cut
scene they're going to be waiting for me
what say you Heroes will you accept this
Destiny there is a great power within
you will you use it to save us to save
this world
[Music]
yes a little tiny bit little B this one
over
here we don't
remember don't remember we don't we
don't
remember this situation is so funny to
me I'm no
hero exactly you oh my go
in the same
situation I
am why is every King has made the great
mistake wait the king said you were a
hero propos to me said will
you got cut off I think we were in the
same spot but you were L for the thre I
not realize I'm in the face of royalty
your highness yes honestly your highness
could you maybe go back to
the because the is I am I just want to
find a cabin in the wood live a quiet
life for the rest of my days I don't
think are they going to let us in
however knock
knock I I was going to be crowned as
Queen but like I said I was r interruped
by one of their servants I mean what are
what are K you like the kind you used to
open a castle door I will make you have
a
good oh a damel in
distress
generous he's a damel in distress we got
to go save her I regret that you must
face such danger so soon after you
[Music]
now that it's gone I kind of miss
the why do this this using so
many we come from a land of simple
words too late to see well destruction
this is our Dy to
Def your duty not my duty this is not my
K feel like I was strong once upon a
time I I can I I can do
I I think they've got it I think they've
got
it I know how to play Minecraft hey they
put a wall here and I'm pretty sure the
first thing you're supposed to do is
punch a tree wait wait I I'm the DJ hold
on I forgot we have I have music for
this
uh suddenly it it makes much more
[Music]
sense is it a scripted
loss oh oh
[Music]
gosh they're kind of strong not that
strong why
[Music]
uh-oh you think the king is
[Applause]
questioning everyone's dying this is
just like my
e651 this is
crazy I feel as though that one has got
an iside with an Xbox
microphone I don't think this lad has
taken any hits uh-oh but I am oh oh I'm
going into the light
oh hold on this calls for a music change
wait does it hold on hold
on uh this
this shout revelation
left
click this is the left click
right louder
Revelation
[Music]
um
um can I move
um um
um
Revelation oh it
worked don't never mind never mind hold
on I have the
perfect music for
[Music]
this I'm get prepared
you know DJ fa's got all the right
[Music]
music The Curse of
Ian
see see what I
[Music]
mean where did I find this
song Wait didn't think I can go back
yet
maybe nope not yet same same place I
find all my
[Music]
songs audio
stock audio
stock audio stock 19 wouldn't don't
blame us this time don't blame us they
wouldn't even tell me if it was an Uber
or taxi this
time what were the Search terms I don't
remember comic comedic um I looked for I
looked for clown music but it was only
like creepy clown music which I hope I
won't have to
use I
[Music]
hope must have been OLED
the server will return in about five
minutes for
shadowing
okay what music do you think we're going
to
need cuz we have 5
minutes to browse for new
[Music]
music see don't say see
bet none of
that Adventure music oh I have Adventure
music oh don't that was like the first
thing I downloaded of course I have
Adventure
music going
Spanky boat
[Music]
music sad Tavern Tavern music okay maybe
I don't really have Tavern music yet
give me a Tavern
batro theme the batro theme does
go go
hard hold on there's no Tavern
loop I think I encountered this
before when I tried to search for
songs what's a what's a word for Tavern
a bar but but image
fantasy uh do you like sad Jazzy
vibo you don't have to ask me
twice let's let's hear
[Music]
it I mean yes I like it how could I not
Persona music but I wouldn't say this is
Tavern music
[Music]
it is a Vibe
though it's not
sad it's not the music that makes you
sad it's after you've had two drinks and
you're sitting alone at the bar thinking
of all of your decisions in your past
that led you to this
point as you stare as your ice cube
slowly melts into your drink and you're
left wondering why did I order this why
am am I still sitting here at this bar
am I expecting someone to walk through
this door and meet
me
sorry different song different
[Music]
song Get It
Twisted heartwarming RPG Village no I
want like how about like a gambling
music oh we don't have that casino how
about Casino we don't have Casino
music um
parcore I don't think the thing is you
have to you've got to you've got to
negotiate
because audio stock is
translating what you got into Japanese
so do you think that Google translate
can handle translating the meaning of
bcore through the server to audio stock
Saloon music well Cowboy is a good
idea there could be a time when we might
need to pull out some cowboy
music let's
see
yeah Texas Road House ye titties
oh
oo this one's pretty
[Music]
good the restart looks like it might
take another 10
[Music]
minutes just your
update some Shop music would be
good we chilling we have audio stop what
more could we want we have got time
actually we could like write a whole
another coffee rap right
now get the wi Shop music I wish okay
what what genre is we
shop which genre is
it I never know I think it needs its own
its own
genre is it Bosa Bosa Nova
but like video
game BOS NOA and then can we do like
application uh
wedding boss Nova
wedding wait there's like too many video
game
options action game how about just
game hospital music
[Music]
okay it's a little bit we
shop but then you got to put the titles
on top of
[Music]
it Super Mario RPG I just want to go
back to Wi shop though
did we get put on hold
yes
[Music]
essentially
essentially a little sentimental boss
NOA oh this one's a little
Jazzy is very important to
[Music]
us this one instead of sitting alone at
the bar watching your ice cube melt into
your drink this time you're in a coffee
shop the fire in the fireplace is
crackling next to you you're reading a
book not on your
Kindle but on glorious paper you turn
the page and you feel that
Papyrus between your fingers you sip
your machiato wait is that a madeup
Starbucks drink or is that a real drink
you can get at a fancy coffee
shop you sip sip sip a coffee shop a a
tea house I mean no no no scratch that
scratch
that
uh scratch that you go to
you are
in a tea
house desperately tries to search for
tea house music what is tea house
music uh
image
stylish and relax
this is Japanese chillhop
[Music]
one server is back wait that wasn't 10
minutes I didn't even have time to do my
new new rap okay not that I'm
complaining I was told we may have to
restart all the cutscenes
[Music]
get I'm going to eat one maybe I should
got to keep your energy up I need B I
mean that babe over there
over there
yeah good good thing you stole my
[Applause]
[Music]
sword is under
control everything out of this my
food let me help
you we all powerful
stand on stand on
there let us out of these walls
man are we working together to escape
the voice is in my oh the voice is in my
hold on hold on we need we need change
the music uh this this one
okay I feel as though I'm in a Time Loop
Echoes of Forgotten memories
who am I the world I live
in more than
anything the people I hold most dear R
faced with Oblivion I feel relieved
perhaps distraught I do not
know so much I don't know
are we supposed to be able oh oh okay
oh I I oh I feel like the bright light
me
hello mad I was afraid seems strangely
familiar I will say would you call it a
sense
ofu D Vu is absolutely what I would call
it it says of deja you took the
word thank you you madam I
just I'm trying it's it's the
first told me to call you B boo I I does
that ring a
bell yeah I don't know what a b boo is
either I have no idea where they got
that from a I'm a never heard that's
what I thought too they said that you
were my wife that
stop I really thought I was going to
make it over
there can
[Music]
you know the first meeting I'm not ready
I don't know who she
[Music]
is I don't
know the vo in my head said that you my
wife oh that might be uh because I find
you very
oh my goodness I thought I was
witnessing some master gas liting but I
think I'm just witnessing the birth of a
new
relationship no wait let me turn you
up I love you you want you turn me you
want to turn me down that's what it is
rejection
rection let me boost you fa I also
cannot hear that many people there's way
voices let attune my ears specifically
for you
oh my thank you green green
woman what is your name
beautiful what about you because you're
so fun yeah exactly you got the
real I'm I'm sure hold up let me take
you here FAA it's a little L more
private I need some privacy hello some
privacy and so soon she was taken from
me oh oh did we get new music yet yes I
suspect so hold on hold on I'm ready for
this now I know bring out the Royal
Palace music and remember it's a little
quiet so boost that up a little
bit yep
yep I'm back thank you well this time
the text is not cut off look my sticky
keys are
fixed please my sticky keys they're very
SI no
more skip a
skiper no we read we just read fast
really
fast thank you King he is asking will
you marry me right there before he gets
interrupted your majesty what is it a
great host of states is broken through a
defensive line
no who knows what will
happen next we seem to have no way to
deal any damage I think I need they need
to let me make something better than a
wooden sword if they just let me out the
world her hard was going
toing at
this Roy every wait I know what happens
there's going to be you know what
happens yeah there's going to how you
remember she's clear W remember remember
you guys don't remember there was a
battle right here am I crazy no I
remember
[Music]
too I thought I had figured it out I
thought I cracked the
code thought we could get in here
yeah that would be nice I I don't really
feel like fighting
again just take shelter behind the
castle wall yeah we can
hide M
yeah can we destroy this green
stuff not with such a dull
sword yeah how do they expect us to
fight with these I
know that
and oh come
on why you want
to if they were just let me out this
tree for I have I have no prior
allegiance to
trees all I want is to destroy this I
see this and it brings out just the
desire to wipe it
[Music]
down just
kidding I stand it and it brings me
joy hold on maybe the royal power music
wasn't that
[Music]
quiet wait is
the I thought the monsters were back
already instead there's just some hero
you must defeat the stage my family will
be
gone don't worry we'll too powerful
[Music]
but why you got a zipper in your back he
shut he was
don't touch
me I'll report you to the king king is
you're unlike the other great great
great
[Music]
Grandad do send me to The Gallows if I I
have a tattle on
you I'll tell the captain captain I'm
calling him right now hold on can't hear
you from all the way
down what is that what is
that how are you doing that
yes we've been here before
I'm that bige you what is
this you're some type of sea animal
[Music]
AR
fungus she looks pretty fungal to me
smells like it too I was about to say
smells walking about there's an imposter
FP right you
areu what are these stains coming in
hero hero we need your help hero oh no
the voice the dialog Is
Res knew what he
said please save my
[Music]
family's translating atast hero help us
hero that who are
you hello you look awfully out of water
to
honest you're not the first person to
say that any idea why my ears to your
voice why oh wait I need because they're
unoriginal please listen please
listen you your head hard Oh no I got
run over by last thing I remember such a
beautiful H you get run over by like a
boat or
anything perhaps she Meridian
I anyway Time to Kill The Bu don't know
what that ver
ver two arms my green
fellow yes F I'll definitely fight I am
too humble just as soon as I put on the
Boss
music maybe we
should hit him from the back and make
sure you
jump jumping is my specialty after all
hey I don't
[Music]
think they're only going to get in our
way well we got the the right
music not
[Music]
as he's very
strong cute do we have to why did they
have to make them so cute
[Music]
die I'll protect you die cute thing no
no no no you
don't see why you might feel bad fix we
can fix out I believe pacifist run is
there
a we must help I don't remember what
[Music]
is IOU wait this is like totally just a
cutie right here
do I have to okay you you're kind of
cramping myself but this one right here
is just a
[Music]
cutie
ouch okay I can I can tame this need the
fluffy one I don't
[Music]
remember here boy
here it's an evil cute oh look at that
wow
Revelation look at
that the stain post has what should that
say has been
[Music]
routed first try hold on do we have wait
I have something for
this uh
[Music]
wait do I
yes press
[Music]
sneak oh here they are hold on I'm
probably holding everybody up let me
[Music]
just you fought bravely kind Heroes I
pray you are not injured andm Mighty
armored one must be their leader the
stain King fascinating Most Fascinating
well I see why they call you it oh so
this one has a British accent huh well I
see why they call you arrows it' be a
right pickle without
you we sustained minimal damage thanks
to your Valor our kingdom is in your
Dent thank you I must hasten to inform
His Majesty of our Victory will you
accompany
me sure
thing do you think they all have
freck hold up we're back in the Royal
chamber bring out the Royal Palace
track I heard the
news it's too loud DJ FAA needs keeps
all
tabing where is he that's fine would
interest be bover is the strange power
he manifested during the battle with
which were able to defeat the stains
that power May well be the key to saving
our world from
Annihilation according to the heroes the
power came to them like a forgotten
memory when they spoke the word
revelation once they are used it to
Route the stain host it seems that power
vanished Without a Trace well that's
bloody brilliant a it so what are we
supposed to do the next time the stains
attack revelation we must uncover the
secrets of this phenomenon if we are to
Prevail against the Calamity many
questions remain but one thing is
certain the kingdom of liestal still
stands today thanks to you dear here so
Heroes I ask you once more will you lend
us your strength to save liel from
ruin
nod marvelous on behalf of all lion SS I
thank you we're blessed to have you
allow me introduce the four Great guilds
is it time for the ceremony which are
responsible for ensuring the Kingdom's
peace and
prosperity The Haven for the the Curious
where knowledge and creativity are
valued above all the Scarlet wand the
home for Glory Seekers with ambition and
vision where closest allies become
fiercest Rivals the Amber
coin the sanum of healing where the
spirit of empathy and devotion thrives
the Cerulean cup the beacon of the
righteous and loyal where great threats
are faced with even greater courage the
Jade
sword one of these guilds will become
your home during your time
here this is
time beyond the story lies the room of
Truth therein the will of the ancestors
shall decide your guild fear not
introspection is a vital step on the
road to Enlightenment excelsor as I
always say even higher St roll the door
be saying some you lock down at the
Amber cool Guild
Hall please let me be the Amber coin
please let me be in the Amber coin let
us save this world together the room of
Truth awaits go forth with Valor do I
need I need new music hold on maybe this
[Music]
one step on the it's so bright in here
step on the platform and receive the
will of the
ancestor okay
[Music]
okay and so begins a journey to find who
I am is
red who would have thought not
green am I in The
Scarlet is it
one not
green snake
Scarlet
[Music]
wand on the
cloak oh wowee
wowee for
me we're red now look at look at
this look at this and then wait hold on
I'm not ready don't show the not
yet and then look at
this wow my
immersion
wow armed with an unwavering will seek
to defend the soul of Jade Jade
am I green after all oh hey what's up
beautiful lady hello oh what do you have
I an apple an apple Golden Apple I have
whatever this is you got this giant
weapon and I just got a golden apple you
got a fork and you just got a feather
what I have I have a feather I'm going
to tickle you guys no tickle tickle wait
the most dangerous of all
I know no one ever suspect IED oh crap I
just used it
sorry fa can you click on this guy here
and tell me what happens click on him
how yeah right right click on him cck
yeah we don't understand the language
without the power of privacy settings oh
a good morrow welcome to the humble
Guild Hall of the Scarlet wand I Am The
Guild Master
rubius um I think that's all he has to
say oh no he's got more thank you for
joining the battle to save Lial so soon
after your summoning at that you will
henceforth be working with us to mount
resistance against the STS and save this
world hey oh what's
up Scarlet wand
people FEA man I like your Trident
that's sick yeah thank you I like your
I like your wooden sword yeah I thought
I have something cool too I have this
this cool thing I'm cool too what your
thing do oh
cool welcome you have a what a c oh hey
what do you
have I have a cloak I have um red a
cloak I got a cloak a cloak a I've got
one more thing hold on guys Al look oh
you got a giant like uh Christmas
or I got a feather I'm going to tickle
everyone's death
no oh that was thought this better go in
your nose and you're not going to like
it yeah this guy right here rubius
rubius
rubius cuz he's red like a
ruby we're all on the same team it looks
like yeah my B we're going to crush
everyone else we're going to deat them
they're done for oh yeah for
sure speak to your M up should I keep
reading yeah you got to right click him
yeah just go through all all of it but
first would behoove you to learn more
sorry I missed that one going it down
and you should find a quest
board why don't you go there and speak
with the quest Master it would be a
Prime opportunity to explore the town as
well
okay yay thank you so much okay we got
to go to the quest board yes we have to
be in a party or is this fun oh maybe we
should make a
party how do we do
that oh wait are you to able to join a
party I I I let's try it can you attempt
to invite us to your party um yeah can
need to look at the tutorial are we not
cool enough to join your party you may
forming
parties right click on who you want to
invite and then just press the blue one
okay I'm going to invite you guys I I
can't press anything actually okay well
we can always be
unari how do you expect yeah I guess I
guess I could
solo let me let me solo it you know oh
yeah how do you accept it'll be kind of
sad but how do I accept the party
accept it's not like that I can't press
accept accept let me see accept oh wait
you click on you click on accept oh hey
I'm in the party wait I'm in the party
wait wait wait wait wait how did you
join how did you join I didn't I I
didn't do anything I just pressed random
buttons please please invite me again
uhoh wait is it is it the max about this
Guild something about
it is
does anyone know where the social menu
is wait why is bi in the party because
she's been we bi and I were in the party
from the beginning but how do I like it
says click um on the right it says when
the person if you click on the person
you formed a party with again the right
of the oh I have to find B in order to
kick
her
oh there it goes Shi
wa okay it's fine we don't have to be in
the party in the beginning I'm sure it's
fine okay
yeah see them at the quest board I'll
just follow you guys how about that is
my horse tired you guys want okay you
like my horse yeah where's the quest
board how do I actually I don't know we
have a map but oh shoot is it this way I
don't know what did he say did anybody
remember what he said he said good job
go to the quest board and speak to the
quest master is the quest board this
looks so cute it does maybe it's inside
it's so pretty oh wait wait what's this
question
[Music]
mark there is a question
mark the question mark this this thing I
think it's supposed to be a question
mark because it looks question yeah
wait oh speak to speak to him uh
to the right click oh okay yeah yeah I
think you have to just Spam it next look
at the question speak to The Question
Master on the
map it's like somewhere over here follow
me town our new
leader yeah I used the map good good
reading
skills thank you it's my talent
we might have to go through this big
building or go around it yeah is this
like all the Scarlet area or is like
over there or that that maybe that's the
yellow yeah eventually we'll I think
we'll cross into other areas I think we
lost two
people should should we go back for them
we we probably should oh okay let's
let's go grab them
[Music]
all
right oh hey is that town this way yeah
yeah yeah we're we're all heading this
way it looks like the The Guild Master's
or the quest Master's here so I I'm
leading the way but we we lost you two
so we're heading back I see my bad I
took no no problem I I would have done
the same
thingi yeah where is Shori
she took off towards the Middle where
are you did
she uh well do you think she made it to
the the quest area let's just go without
her she'll catch up okay okay okay this
[Music]
way
turn what's up
you I would say she was the one who
snuck in no it's it's going to be
further in the corner it it looks like
it's kind of far away I I'm looking at
it on my map it's marked oh I see it is
marked yeah you do have a
[Music]
talent I about this magical goodness I
need to have something
[Music]
okay somewhere in this house maybe no no
no no no sorry
around around the house this is the long
way I'm so sorry I am not being a very
good Navigator I trust you completely
I'm so sorry I could not even manage to
see the text on the map
okay somewhere back
here oh my God it's that red Lady
Elizabeth yes that is
[Music]
I okay Quest board Acquired and we found
Shori too oh good wonderful pure hearted
stallion hey what's up
girls we go to the quest board first
we're winning know where's the
we need to go to
tired I'm The
[Music]
Apprentice
Master somebody's May right click
[Music]
for this looks like the perfect job
we my
[Music]
thees thees up thees still in the party
we are going on a quest do you care to
join
us join us now I'm lost I don't
know
ising with
them let's go
to side okay wait how do we know what
the side quest is
the only one available on the board yeah
materials needed at the Smithy I'm The
Apprentice at the Smithy and my master
says we're running low on raw materials
if you can help us gather some please
stop by the
Smith to to reach
anything I think is there a way we can
fix our group chat because it would be a
lot less chaotic if we were the only
ones yeah there's groups party I don't I
think apart from just turning everyone
else down probably
not isn't it isn't it a radio in my
party leaders can kick oh there she is
oh my God okay okay okay okay okay okay
stand still do not move I shall free you
I will kick you from my
[Music]
party oh no he's actually we how do I
get off the horse where's the Guild
Master
now is it Shi oh pretty Prett lady
where's the Guild
Master how do I The Guild Master click
on it yeah I never talked to the Guild
Master I wandered off like a Lost Child
Guild Master he was way at the beginning
I spent time with my horse please show
me The Guild Master Okay um thank you
you're so wonderful is it this way I
guess we can take our
horses I I have to talk to the Guild
Master I skipped them I shall be back
wait which way did we come
from don't know I don't remember wait it
must have been this way
[Music]
right I think it was this
way
yeah is this the red area yeah yeah I
don't know it must be this
way been bald follow the red banners
oh my horse be
lagging oh my wonderful Majestic green
lady my wonderful Majestic
Oreo yeah I'm edible too
oo yeah you can can I can I try or it
can split me apart you can do whatever
you
want can I turn you into the faces of
the Moon as a
demonstration oh wait
he was by the
question okay so where master um over
here this guy r rubius no wonder I
didn't talk to
him oh crap I keep riding my
horse please talk to
me will he talk to you he refuses to
talk to me actually no I think I have
the same issue as the Final Fantasy
looking girl had oh
no yeah I think he specifically hates
goth
women he should hate me too then he just
must not be able to see inside not a
very good Jud you're pretty you're
pretty why the goodness of your heart
you're pretty oh wait wait thank you oh
shs it's okay maybe he just hates pretty
girls but you're you're beautiful you
you look at you you look so like homely
with your piece of bread and your Apple
homely yeah homely good homely good it's
like the opposite of a home recer you
know H is good like like a
hobbit Hobbits are good too they they do
things I don't know what they do we
watch we must know what they do I I
already forgot most of their names like
there's like what Frodo there's like uh
his best friend don't tell me his name
it's not Peter Sam Sam is his
name I already forgot the blonde dude
the cute elf boy don't tell me his
[Music]
name I don't know his name leg
lus was close
Laos I I I was pretty close managed to
join oh that's good too bad like I don't
know the quest is um oh okay you could
you could follow along with
us okay and we can we can explain to you
and hopefully they will fix it for
you I will relay my thoughts to this
voice head and push shift a bunch does
it
work oh oh yeah yeah you're so you're
such a genius you're beautiful I'm so in
love with you right
now hold on let me let me relay this
okay I have related to this uh entity in
my head head called staff okay good
good I I I did see completed and now I
can never see that that word again now
we can now we can go back wait which way
was
[Music]
it this way I think it's this way other
no I think it's this
way we went the long way before lady
this this
this way oh I'll just I'll follow you to
the ends of the world okay I think it's
this
way yeah I think they leave to the same
[Music]
place don't want to go too fast the
horses are faster than the speed of
sound you can't hear
anybody oh wait this
way this way
where is everyone did they
die maybe it's just us left on this
earth oh man okay now you need to click
on this guy and also spam
shift
okay oh crap I keep riding my
horse uh sneak key this is a quest board
I understand your main duty you must be
tired I died no maybe you I I think I I
did it
CL um wow well you shouldn't try to like
get stuck in high places let me just say
that I see I see you think this world
has Wi-Fi how do you accept the quest
properly I think you talk to him and
then click on this and click on the the
thing oh click to order thank you so
much you have my gratitude Forever Green
lady and black and white oreo lady thank
you so much I'll remember that for the
future when I come to collect anytime
anytime I shall honor my my
promises
oh not now what okay do you have the
side
quest yeah something about a Smithy yeah
we can go to the
blacksmith okay we should be this way oh
you're so wonderful you're showing me
around I'm not used to Fantasy settings
I'm pretty sure whenever I came from it
was like a really hot place with a lot
of to gri dark setting oh I see yeah
yeah yeah there something like Halloween
world for all I
know that sounds
nice yeah a lot of candy a lot of work
for the dentist yeah are there a lot of
dentists in your
world um there might but it might be
only one I I don't remember I don't
think you're licensed either that's a
scary idea too oh it's you well it's
good to know we have a dentist in our
party oh I'm not good though I'm not a
good dentist better than me oh wait is
it here did I go too
[Music]
far
oh
oh oh hey it's boo boo oh who a't she
boo boo what' you call me what' you say
I called you Boo Boo
Honey yeah hey what what what what
weapon do you have you have like rock
candy wow delici
I have show me your Revelation can I use
it
on you gave her a
t instant
TP oh nice I cast instant
TP I think my feather's failing to
tickle people right now I can't tickle
you oh oh how did I how did I do that oh
oh crap I think I just went
off oh I could with you and I can invite
you to
party no not don't invite her again
we've been through
this where are you sorry you're not fun
at
parties no no I got fun on the phone I
don't know where fun sure we are what
okay have fun where are you guys we got
lost we leave the
r okay we're coming back to you up the
phone call
goodbye my fellow party members what am
I buy they need material oh they need
material wait do we need to bring
materials oh I don't know The Apprentice
we talk to The Apprentice must oh they
gave us
money
10 how do I hang up with the phone phone
okay I don't know wait you're still on
the phone with
me I don't know I didn't even know how
you called
me wait who are you calling I don't I I
I guess
you don't not you was D I got fig how to
hang on the
phone no
you do I want
dou do we need 10 right oak logs oh
maybe we just find like a random tree
did he say they were outside
[Music]
somewhere hey we have a lot of trees
here we have a lot of trees here fa are
these I these are available
a you're right you're right they they
don't let us do things with normal
practical way how do you accept a party
though outside town where is outside
yeah I think I think we have to be
farther
out is this in town what what about this
this tree this tree is almost certainly
still in town
right okay I guess we got to wander out
where's the exit there's a big gate over
here gate yeah
yeah it's a awfully big gate for tiny
people do you think it has a tiny door
inside it I really like when giant Gates
have have a tiny
door
yeah otherwise you're going to have to
go like climb up the walls or something
yeah I mean interesting you know weird
this place is so big but like there's
not a lot of Li lion what are they
calling well maybe they all got murdered
by the stains right oh true that's what
happens when you don't do long laundry
STS kill
you I wouldn't know couldn't be me oh
yeah I trust you I trust you tree lady
what's this oh another location I guess
so oh yes why not
[Music]
yes oh heck there's stains here oh no
can we chop down these trees they seem
friendly yeah I think
so they seem friendly enough think I
could chop this down I want to to steal
like a land oh cow
I let you live oh I let you have that it
works hey oh are you okay down down
boy bad dog bad
[Music]
dog is he making us sound like a
puppy that's this is so sad 13 wait you
get money from them that changes
everything
huh oh never mind they give you money
when kill
them I feel like I need a
new we need a new a new music what a
very good
world this one think they're hurting me
I can't hey what what is this do does
this work yet can I have your memories I
hope it I'm collecting it hey I got
coins that's
nice ouch Co okay
are you okay is that you no no no it's
this this thing yeah they give you money
oh that's like a bull here you go get
your wood I'll K things
okay I I'll take them thank you te I me
I can't really hit them on the
SE get away from her where is chopping
down nature hello
hello where are you guys we're outside
the town chopping down oak trees for the
quest oh okay how about how about we
meet you there we're going outside now
too okay okay okay okay okay good talk
okay oh by the
way okay good good job hold on can I
give you some logs too oh I have 12 oh
you already have it we found you hello
it's been so
long won we were we were on an adventure
got W finally we've been reunited dude
yeah it feels so good it does here eat
my memories at least I'm hoping it's
tickled tickled 20 coins see they give
money are you getting tickled you are
not getting tickled does it make you
just want to
farm ouch that's right I'm the tickle
Master here your feet get tickled your
nose get tickles I would like to farm I
would like to farm coins right how many
coins took forever to die holy holy
quack
128 I got
171 do some catching up you got some
heavy pockets that's right oh there's so
many stains this one is like a cute
bunny this one has horns and they kind
of Hur you feel familiar I think you're
my sister why am I not using this about
10 I okay
11 how much you think we
we need 10 I have like 15 15 that's
like 50% more three better get to
chopping I think we're good do we each
need 10 I think so I don't know oh my
goodness yeah you only need 10 you only
need 10 but each personal or we all
together uh I was I think we should all
get 10 just in case oh no sharing I have
some spars if you want Oh may have my
opinion summoning egg mayhaps who well
we should probably run I think they're
after us uhoh they come out at
night Revelation I think there's a lot
more
Revelation it doesn't
work quick let us return return oh
crap Scarlet one red red team is hurting
me I was
wondering red team back inside wait does
every already have all their
logs here you have all of the logs that
you need I I have 14 okay do we have
enough for everyone
[Music]
10 make case team how does one summon
the
gate oh we have returned she get
stuck okay please say yes 1 y we're back
yay what up
hooray let us go back to the blacksmith
yes we can have horses if we use a
summoning seed egg that is
true and the
horses pretty brown I must do it
myself she has to Hur the very do not
remember okay right here we go oh the
more things to be able to make done we
completed the logs thank you so much see
my master over there if you bring the
raw materials all the tools and it
Cobblestone
Cobblestone too many people are speaking
to him at
[Music]
once wooden
Pi is this all of our money am I am I
using all of our money I do not think so
my money has not decreased I think
that's your money okay I'm rich
I how much money do you have three craft
a wooden pickaxe now I have 9s I'm
richer than you three
ha to
purchase requ materials completed
collect 10 Oak speak to the black create
a wooden
pickax I
see
[Music]
PL what did you say pickax
you said wooden pickaxe not work oh wait
the pickax did not work why did the
pickaxe not work sticks oh he needs
sticks he need scks do it
coins Master you have to
pay Y and
money we can use okay you TR to The
Apprentice no
oh oh pretty sure it's the other one
though Timber how do you make a it wait
is this one
F I've created the wooden pickaxe I have
also created the W when you find new
material stop and talk to my master the
more different materials you find the
more things he'll be able to
make see my master okay I'll talk to
your master then speak to the black okay
could you bring us 10 Cobblestone a you
can probably find some lying around in
the same place you dro the wood
wow I sure crafted this wow great yeah
10 Cobblestone okay wow I don't feel
like a hero I feel more like
a I think I think what's it called like
an intern yeah yeah right he going to
ask us for a cup of coffee
again
this I don't
really off we go
oops way to travel
yes I'm
I'm how much I need why just need 10
right this is this is
unusual well I guess I'll win it
oh I don't know how much material weird
yeah this is different
10 foro what oh once you got it I feel
like I'm I'm stealing all of the
resources for the team
yes uh should I'm getting
Cobblestone me too I have collected 10
Cobblestone I I'm going to get enough
for both of you I already got 10 I have
also yeah I was thinking why we take all
the Cobblestone so no one else can do it
yeah we should prevent other teams from
getting any yeah okay let's just do the
outside
so they won't know byee yeah let's let's
R she on the phone
oh yeah they call me they ask where I I
was talking to you like you were talking
to me I'm so
sorry okay do I've got I've got 31 so
let's head back oh hi okay hi you think
I I got enough for you too I response
darn it thank you I got hit by a orse
how do I throw an
uh yeah I think you have to trade you
have to left and right click at the same
time wait I have to trade you're done so
you can't throw things n oh my God okay
I'm sorry I can't share with you after
all maybe here I I have some uh I trade
oh never mind you're trading with
someone else I'm sorry who are you
trading with I'm stuck in the hold on oh
no wow I see how it is no chaed me I see
right click
no that's this one just
makes kind of bad what do you
mean you guys tra sorry it'll it'll
leave maybe it'll cancel no no
I'm collect C the last hits for you so
you can get all the gold just make sure
you get your bkb up you might as well
just col if you could yeah I was I was
basically for a very long time cuz I was
confused so you
know that thing's
clingy I'm going oh it's
expired cool you friendly
oh it's okay it's okay that one was for
you have a
recharge did they go back
in does everybody have their cobblestone
oh I'm working on it okay
okay
you fear
me All Shall love me and
[Music]
despare should I use my Apple I'm
running out of
food do they got food in this place
coins revelation
look at that dude you made
a it isant t perfect for all your
camping
needs you can probably light it a on I'm
not sure it might be a
heal oh a heal an instant TP heal
ooh okay go back okay
team yes go Scarlet
one yay now I guess we got to go back
and make something again yes Smo
[Music]
something wait is it this one did I go
too far oh that's not the right
one this what this one this one this
one all right we're ready let's go get C
all
right you should be able to make you
stone tools to give it a
try that's all we needed thanks for
responding to the question that's so
cute please
it okay wait what are we supposed to
make eight
sticks I don't know wait are we supposed
to make
something or are we done with the side
quest now it just say stone tools that's
all we
need we might as well get some upgrades
though
yeah indestructible
ooh St it was 100
coins do you need do you need
[Music]
money no you need of
Charity no I'm not in need
well oh I'm so stupid the shift is weird
to be honest
complet I guess that's everything yeah
do we return where did our other members
go did they make it
okay I I don't know oh okay just going
to okay I guess not that one any
any
shies can I phone them do I use the
radio Quest Master Quest yeah yeah oh
Quest Master this way yeah oh he's this
way he's this way he's this
way make a group
call can we make a group
call we're still going to be able to
hear everybody though
party
call I think we're just G to end up
hearing double
double leave them behind
[Music]
byby oh
well you the duty of finding the
Calamity but I hope you will stop by the
time you're in pressed for time why not
have a look around town There's a mighty
fine shop
he has money
500 okay I don't have any money none he
didn't give you
any I have 125 coins did you talk to
this guy if you talk if you talk to him
we should give you money yeah he'll give
you all the money you're rich he say
your pressed for
time why not have a look around
town give me money give me your money
little hit him did you press shift
afterwards again after that okay he gave
he gave me the money he just hesitated
but all is good
[Music]
now do not all is good you encouraged
him with your sword you're a
shopkeeper hey who what's this I called
you I I'm next to a shopkeeper oh where
did you find the
shopkeeper he's like near us Tavern
probably getting drunk there's a
Tavern yeah yeah okay so go go from this
blacksmith and then just go across it's
across the street from the blacksmith
okay thank
you no problem you're cute you're
cute you the king are you under cover
with the
King it's called is why is narissa red
is she okay I think she's disconnected
oh no was a shop make sure you got
enough coin ski a skipper skiper Skipper
skip a skipper Skipper holy crap that's
a lot to
skip
dialogue just select what you want
completed thank gosh speak to the child
in the
gardens why talk to me I'll show you
what I've got in stock I want to I want
to get lot of
money maybe we can buy stuff from them
and then we can sell it with an up price
you know
I think we should steal his stuffff and
then sell it to them so we get money
yeah yeah your
heart I like his top hat should be mine
okay now we got to find a random
child what Vis the
garden this way the children attending
to them why are the children working at
the Garden all right you guys ready to
find a lost
child yes okay the child should be
around back hold on let me ring
her give phone
call you
can hello where are you I'm I'm trying
to fix my game wait a minute I recognize
but I'm by the lies in child in the
Gardens at the moment okay okay we were
about to head there I'm here I'm talking
to the child I think my issues might be
fixed okay we'll meet you by the
yeah
children for it oh all right are we
ready for finding we're going to meet
narissa in the
garden okay the garden should be across
there
yeah hes
across where's the garden wait I don't I
don't know where the gardens are I
thought she already do where'd she go
well this looks like Gardens it's green
should we try it does but it's kind of
small for a
garden these horses are fast wait is
this the child oh no that's that's
not wait do you know where the gardens
are I don't think this is a garden I
don't think this is like a
[Music]
maze I think this is the the the the oh
wait it's marked on our map it's in the
bottom yeah right corner I think it's
like
here I'm going then now that I've
learned to read the
map
oh
here wow wow this is
beautiful hello yeah look at this child
he sounds like a cockney person oh I can
certainly voice act that and please
do goly you're one of the heroes must be
my lucky day right well this year is the
Gard feel free to come and use them
whatever you
like but AC is in
it my j keep an eye on him tin stare
away the birds and stuff if you don't
like gardening you can also try
building there's an empty lot just past
here where your arrows can build
whatever you like
earo you and your guild mates could work
together to make a voice if play to stay
stop by any time if you want to do some
building or
gardening oh say can I tell you a secret
did you know there's a place in town
called the
pit says these kids aren't allowed to go
but I hear you can play a really fun
game there sounds what would a terrible
way to advertise towards children it's
so fun but you can't go you're a hero
sry but don't let you in maybe you could
go check it out and tell me what it's
like anyway hope to see you again let's
Rush there okay what a charismatic child
able to be loud talk in front of five
people very
impressive okay did we rescue him oh
finally he's finally talking to me oh
thank go oh good oh thank
goodness to the it's okay FAA read it
for you let's
run to the pit ladies to the pit wait is
this is this the way the pit this is the
way I Follow the Leader oh hello hi you
think they finished all their quests or
are they just fighting each
other see I want to
know oh oh our horse is allowed in here
I don't think they
are okay
lucky lady lucky lady I've got a game
for you oh says your new face don't tell
me you're one of those Heroes who save
the town aren't you you want to get rich
I know it could make you a fortune wait
don't guy promise it ain't nothing Shady
look about how I tell she something
useful see I used to run with the Jade
show before I join the Amber
coin jumper out onto some I don't know
what he's saying I can't
read just point yourself at your make
right click on her from there you can
select whatever to invite her to your
party a trade with
her now you can aveng it together swap
items and coins say told you it was
useful didn't I you'll thank me for when
you're
adventuring uh I know you're very
important Mission World C you be a lot
easier if you add some extra coins know
I'm saying give us give us the money
then too light or too heavy maybe come
down here to the p and play around or
two Shake him Shake him bro I don't care
ju just stop talking to me bro real
quite simply I don't care shorten it
yeah bro quite simply shut up yeah
literally let's beat him up and take his
wallet okay oh does he have one that
your bow tie instead hit him hit him
excuse me wait we're committing crimes
against
another it's a misunderstanding I think
I talking we got to speak to we have
drama I still haven't talk to P I am not
activating him oh no Amber coin it's
okay you guys can go ahead without me
I'll just just hit just hit shift a lot
there you go finally yay I got it okay
all right
Jade come this way is that's verish yeah
yeah yeah it is that sounds like
ver birthday
salsa I wonder if there's a connection
there brius where are you hiding
oop feel the greed man make me there
this get in
[Music]
here
oh cannot I feel like that is a
suspicious for the
horse what is this the the Gladiators
Arena oh that's so
[Music]
cool they drink blood guy though don't
you die if you do that
unless you're like a vampire yeah but
you know they're dying
anyway I guess so I guess so
yeah it was all for a jolly good
show do you know where you're going
dude yeah is he under the
Coliseum I don't know how to get to him
cuz they're the like they're the fighty
ones so maybe fighty ones yeah iy ones
they're FOH we don't know about
you see you returned Brave hero they're
pretty fighty fighting get in between
them oh they all look the same learned
about
[Music]
adventur I have not familiarized myself
with town at all that's a pretty yeah
same must be shaking suddenly find
your
the I was like what is this
sound hey you just got a you know you oh
here that's a sort why can't I talk to
you but notam the plan right it's
horrible okay well
hat Mumble Mumble what's the mission
after
I still have to talk exit the Town Gate
head to the planes and speak to a
Hostess of the Jade sword
got I'll keep spamming here I'll see you
guys out go
okay hardest mission ever trying to
socialize it really is though please
socialize with me Guild bastard please
begging you regain your powers of
Revelation that end I maybe I'm not his
I don't know
of Poss
car speak to
H on the Jade sword oh he he's still not
socializing no you read an Italian
accent have you skipped everything
again then read wherever what you're
seeing right now
okay uh go for it with Valor I finally
talked to him go to thank the M bravery
he really hates flirting with
me were you trying to
flirt I was just trying to socialize man
I told him like how you how you doing
good look you know well maybe you should
Le a little a little softer next
time oh maybe like how you doing yeah
yeah
so yeah that works they come
here guard
all right I'm going to follow you other
okay this this the is this the right
gate I think so
yeah let's
go this head of a planes why is it
morning
here took us a while to
leave oh I guess so
[Music]
to the
ruins surely if we follow the path we
will make it there
right
ooh did I lose them already
oh this is
cool oh hey is this hus yeah ow it's h
hero you are
arrived 1 2 3 4
5 strange
voice The Souls of stains open the
way okay okay we have to kill we have to
kill 10 stains I understand
okay this makes perfect sense to me you
cannot proceed
yet I'm not trying to proceed
I'm trying to
murder plus
five finally
violence plus 15 why was this one worth
so much
more are you
dead you will be sued I'm starting to
feel
bad I feel like the corruption of the
land is reaching me my inner soul
this isn't this isn't
me I'm not usually like this
goodbye I mean what what evidence do we
have of these creature oh not that way
of these creatures
crimes have they truly done such wrongs
to deserve
this if evil why
cute feel bad I'm the hero
I can do no
wrong as the hero I swear they make the
creeper sound effect when they die and
scares me every time oh it's
not I did it Miss okay may iow
my this one just sounds so sad I know it
makes me sad I'm not sure we're the
heroes after all I think we might be the
villains wait was the last sentence what
might have mean by that that was the end
no worries yeah okay slay 10 stains
let's do this let's do this let's go I
wonder when we're in the party Under
World key it should normally
[Music]
count the secrets of the ruins
wait I have a key
how many how many have I killed wait for
the Center Bar okay who's I need healer
who dirty clothes wait do you need
healing it's like destroy it no no wait
can you heal Revelation did it heal you
you're the Healer I'm the Healer
actually you just full healed me you
healed four Hearts
yes yes wait that's actually
awesome okay I won't use it on enemies
then that that good information to
know
wait okay so you do
healing what does everybody else's
weapons do I wonder I don't know she
always
tickles so we have a Healer we have a
Tickler we have a a mop revelation
investigate the underworld dungeon then
speak to the Jade swword Guild
Master I wonder how long this will take
oh a bird bird girl because bird girl we
must attend to a meeting in our heads I
know I'm
aware a am man you and I have great
minds huh we think Alik well but I I
really want to keep playing
I really want to
enter do do the three of you think that
you will be fine without me and lady
shiori I think we will be we can do it
we won't let you down garlet wand we'll
be we'll be back we'll be back for the
next one okay okay we're
sorry thank you guys we can't wait to
play again or I'm to fight together
again again are you leaving my wife we
miss we must
away yes we have Adventure the fireball
man the Phoenix of the fires and the
oranges hello lady of water all right I
will water I can put out your
flame out my you're on cool down where
my beautiful underg green
woman good luck my beautiful beautiful
lady Lady of the woods yes you wouldn't
know a thing I must I must into my
mind okay I must have a a meeting with
the council feeling I will know well how
about you prove to me not see you in
this wonderful wonderful world thank you
for showing me around you're
gorgeous well you're beautiful in there
back I'm back to Diamond how you go get
that diamond back into the into the
water like are you done with the class
and if I sink what will come of
it I shall save you by then because I am
a hero I'm a green and I am go on go on
do not be scared oh she's walking on the
water I'm in the
water we're both walking I'm
sinking oh this is nice so try
swimming uhoh
I what did you do to her I I guess
accidentally kind of uh killed her
indirectly um but
like why um well what guil do you belong
to traveler all I that is none of your
business uh out cat what Guild are you
part of
with tell her I everyone
he my heels
sorry my bad
AFK where's
my sorry uh sorry kitty cat
uh um we will Adventure yeah done the
now it say you have any idea where she
no I don't wait it still says slay let
me let me call her
let's see
um hello oh hello hello wait you're
right there oh I'm back okay I died back
hello hello shall we enter the
dungeon okay okay let's do it I think
I'm ready I won't die again I promise I
I'll heal you next it wasn't your fault
it was the hea's fault don't take any
blame wait wait wait wait wait proba
believe the wouldn't heal you wait wait
wait wait one job has one job couldn't
do their job honestly the name well
maybe maybe maybe I shouldn't heal at
all then maybe I'll
just where would we
be let go into the dungeon wait where is
the entrance it's here it's on the map
oh of course okay okay
oh yes
the I want to change to Dungeon music
yes are we here oh wait good idea
Dungeon music battle music for the
battle yes are we
armed I sure hope
so do you have both your
arms I hope so I can't see them I'll
have to take your word for it wait let
me see yeah you have THS you good we're
good this doesn't seem like a dungeon
does it no it's kind of too Airy and
yeah especially if for an underworld
dungeon yeah I thought it would be I
thought it would be under the world this
feels very Overworld we'll see are we
are we the right level for
this level
zero level zero it's okay I'm I'm sure
we can cheese our way through it somehow
yeah wait what does your weapon do
Cecilia um mine is okay automaton
assault oh okay is that
damage yeah okay what about your
DPS I think I'm an
AOE
oh that is an AOE that looks crazy does
that make me a tank you're a tank she's
a tank okay what
oh
my I think it also holds enemies into
place but I don't know if it heals them
too oh that's really cool wait let me
check do how do you guys know this this
is like an item description or am I
supposed to know exactly what mine does
no I'm guessing I'm guessing yes I'm
also guessing I was a little bit worried
I miss something it's like a 10 page
document the intricacies of the of the
weapon it was the eth PDF not the
seventh one
man I missed it oh ready to enter
oh ready ready
ready oh standing by wait
today wait ready ready you are already
standing by for this dungeon do we need
to kick the others
out oh no and it says two out of five
enter enter wait don't enter for me two
out of five oh enter
dungeon I'm also two out of five well oh
damn it yeah it's say two out of five it
says gura is
yellow on my screen am I not cute are
you not ready did you push the green
one
ready
ready status not
ready I'm ready up I swear I'm ready up
I readed up I
swear believe material thing let me read
the PDF real quick the 50
P enter dungeon when you approach your
dungeon ready to enter dungeon click on
the green box on the left and ready up
if you're in a party all members will
need to complete this do you have the
key G I have the key
okay I'm ready party
members oh okay I can't kick the two
that aren't here
so players already clicking on the
diamond sword on the right will allow
you to enter the dungeon over the enter
dungeon button will let you know if any
members are not ready hovering over the
enter dungeon button will let you know
see how do we can we should we make a
new
party we can we leave this one and make
a new
one
okay maybe try doing
that yeah let's try do that click to
leave click to dispense yes okay I left
okay the party has been
disbanded okay let's make a new one
okay
okay inviting you both thank
except except okay we're doing
it and now we
ready it says I'm ready every's
[Music]
ah oh my god oh we made it we made it
this is so bad this now this is an
underworld
dungeon it's still not
really
[Music]
well oh that's lava oh there's a lot of
lava don't jump don't
jump there's there's a beacon over
there this this one like starts
something the under World a domain of
boundless oppressive Darkness as feared
as it is unavoidable it holds the final
resting place for every creature that
walks the Earth yet even in this realm
of the Dead there are those who live and
call it home so we're just invading
their home yeah
essentially we're the king out the
locals we're just enriching the
experience we can put like a Starbucks
here or something oh o
[Music]
Starbucks I think we have to
jump um not this way not not that way
not that way not that way not that way
here scary I'm not
sure
no yah
easy maybe this is a baby level
dungeon they wouldn't they wouldn't go
all around on the first one
right J
it okay first one to die um to do
something
painful
like I don't
[Music]
know I'm fine I'm fine I'm fine think of
it wait not yet wait I think that healed
me did it heal you I think
so I think it did oh
have a Healer nice final
healer it healed me thank you very much
even with just three we've got a balanc
party oh no oh we had
[Music]
checkpoints okay oh there's another one
there were we over there already though
or we couldn't access it
before ah oh I think we've passed the
stone monument before are we going in
circles Maybe
no surely it's this way do you see that
oh like a castle castle that's cool wait
I don't turn up your R distance doesn't
show
up I thought you got a new
GPU I bought a used one it's not that
good wait describe it with a small words
a castle booms in the distance with the
pointy spires piercing the heavens or
the hell blood red leaks Through the
Windows I can see it with my inner
eye yes so this is the creativity of the
J sword huh that's right we are the
creative team right and the smart
team Scarlet genus Scarlet scl Scarlet
one we came of geniuses creative and
very smart honestly very good
combination
creative and smart right what else do
you
[Music]
need oh I'm getting a phone call one
second guys
hello we can do it should I try turning
up the Rend
distance maybe depend what do you have
to sell me crank those chunks all the
way up
[Music]
oh
wow it feels like I just saw for the
first time in my life oh my God it's a
castle guys the livian charity donation
is calling me should I give them any
money um we're not the charity teams no
we're not the charity we're the creative
genius I don't recall that being part of
our said I can't I can't tell them to
call The Blue Team instead mom me tell
you to call The Blue
Team the ceran cup says they're the nice
on they're the charitable ones they
should give the
donation
mhm they also we can draw them a picture
instead if that's they also said that
your team is is
Shelly this is another this is the
Scarlet one team
seruan
cup I
[Music]
mean no one's getting it's getting
scary it's okay they don't need to know
they don't need to know is this going to
hit my am I going to hit my head no okay
we're fine we're fine what's happening
in the wait do you think we canes here
can we what no no we can't ose the
horses Maybe H is are band in the
Underworld oh Fair Maiden if only there
was someone who could heal me oh are you
in need of of healing oh I Tak Dam o I
feel thank you wait you guys sound
similar when you say ooh ooh do we have
the the green ooze the green ooze the
green o if we move really fast she can't
tell us apart
fast my vision is bluring
the fade of
green the green ooze ah the artists are
going to like that
one when you say like that it sounds
like ooze like o o z
e the green ooze ooh the green ooze
oozing the green
ooze very appeal really cool though the
castle is yeah you think there's a boss
in there I hope not I feel like we
haven't fought anything yet so can you
imagine fighting enemies during this
parkour
no you're right what if they're flying
on top of oh no please no we should give
them the ideas for like next next time
next
dungeon and don't give don't give the
devs any ideas they're listening they're
watching they're actually more lava lava
everywhere oh
no oh no there's a checkpoint though
right did we forget to get the
checkpoint oh no no no I got it did you
get it get it is she there I got it I do
not see her my random distance might be
too low do you see her I don't see
her okay let's just wait
hello where are you where did you
Spa I'm at the bottom of the Castle I'll
be I'll be with you shortly sorry the
bottom of the castle there she is there
she is I see Cecilia hi I'm waving do
you see me hi okay okay good in a sec
okay okay I'll be
back the phone calls is a good feature
yeah it's so handy it does make me want
to try to like scam some
people
oh how what do to scam people we could
like pretend to be their grandchildren
and tell them that we're trapped at the
airport and then we need them to wire US
money
oh do you think these phones have like
MMS features so you can send pictures of
their credit cards oh I hope
so stealing credit card what are you
talking making a a creative way to make
money stealing credit cards no no no no
no no tricking people into giving us the
credit cards they're different willingly
willingly giving them it's not yeah it's
uh hello can you give me the last three
digits on the back of your I bet you
can't remember the last three digits of
on the back of your credit
card I do because the other day I had to
put it in and then I kept putting in the
wrong one open and over and and over and
again and now I know it's uhoh uh oh
okay I'm
sorry I thought was going to
this is scary I don't want to anymore
you have to we're almost there make it
to the top you can do it oh a checkpoint
if I get it does count for the whole
[Music]
team did everybody else already do this
so the little I don't know surely not
right I think it's just separate
instances ah I see oh I see
oh
oh hello oh inside okay is this where
the boss
is oh no is this a
maze
uh how the left tank please lead the way
pull the
enemies the aggro pool are you kidding
me you're the tank you're the tank look
at me look at me I'm the tank oh look at
me look at me I'm such a big tank
oo o
yeah he that wasn't that bad do I heal
everybody with that look yeah I think so
oh be careful oo ooh thank you for
protecting us tank nice tank my job
don't fear do not
fear I've got a pocket and a DPS with a
very sharp pointed got triangles watch
out I mean I'm on cool down DPS go DPS
go you can do it go go go uh-oh uh-oh
the Healer needs needs heals the Healer
has no heals
nice why is he holding on to a store
they've got
geometry not the
geometry no not
M oh he has a
circle wait wait wait do you guys have
keys I've got a Circle Key did you guys
perap key oh I've got a
star they're coming in waves
team they're surrounding us okay oh
thank
you uh-oh oh nice wait Which Way were we
going don't turn around we going we're
going this
way which way this way I believe it's
this way oh
my try Triangle
Man Triangle
Man does whatever triangle
[Music]
canip this way for sure is it this way I
I don't
know no there's too many use your AOE
it's on cool
down cool down stad of it stay ahead of
it you see why is it cool down
too oh God oh God okay wait
okay thank you thank you thank
you
ow I feel like we're in the corner uhoh
it's okay I'm no longer on cool down
okay
[Music]
wait one two 1 two
three we're here we're
here where is this it one two one two
three oh it needs oh can we like each
put one we need
keys that would be nice I have a key
okay I put in oh oh oh
nice very
good nice exellent you guys need food I
have food if anyone needs food thank you
I still have looks like Dark
Souls yeah Traverse the white
light I don't want to do this did we get
a save do we have a save point no
bonfires lit this is hardcore mode
there's no safe it's okay we can do it
first try this is a hardcore uh
something
something um ra we can do this team got
this Scarlet wand Scarlet wand Scarlet W
Scarlet wand Scarlet
[Music]
W oh look oh my God a
checkpoint looks cool that is
cool it's Scarlet just like us yeah
actually what's this say oh info Point
another life expired leaving behind a
tiny flickering light a soul
representing both a legacy and an ending
the veiled figure cradled in her hands
and with a hint of melancholy she
whispered is that the right thing to do
oh I don't know is it we have to ask
this mysterious veiled
figure
H who Could It Be Who Could It Be I
wonder oh I like the
chandeliers yeah
hit the hit the chains and make it drop
on the boss for extra damage we can put
oil underneath so they
fire smart this is this is the
creativity of red team oh and the genius
yes just bu different and everything
here is red so it's like it's made for
us have you guys figured out a way to
remove like the ingame overlay because
it's like kind of
cluttery what overlay ah you know how it
says like coins your party in
investigate I just I just have it on
there okay I do too fine I can look past
the distance is this a
puzzle
oh guys this is ours we're the Geniuses
someone take the wheel okay quick
somebody else do it quick someone take
the wheel I believe in you guys what
what kind of puzzle is it oh no is it
the oh my god did you play Pet V
it's it's the pets vits game oh it's
like the ones around it turn the color
rever
puzzles
revers wait it seems like you know what
you're
doing I
don't I feel like you're doing it though
I think you're doing
it I think you're just saying that
no no no oh
[Music]
almost wait so does it like compare does
it do it from the other side as well or
you got to look up the rules of
reversing is it 3D I guess it is so if I
touch this one oh it is 3D okay okay
let's see how about this there's a
there's a single
oh each piece played must be laid
adjacent to an opponent piece the
opposite the opponent's piece or a roll
of opponent's piece is flanked by the
opponent's piece of a new piece and
another piece of the same color did you
get
it yes there just one
left oh never mind it's more than one
oh one uhoh oh okay let's just go move
with the flow so we so we activate this
one
okay and then this one no not that
one oh is it like one of those slidy
puzzles too okay okay I think it is like
flipping them on and off
yes let's
go genus
genius I bet we did it like at least
five times faster than the other teams
cuz we the
absolutely
[Music]
100% now Sur that that was the final
boss the puzzle and then that's all and
we win
right I think we win
[Music]
trophy trse wa zom being fought wen't
even stains do you think we're being set
up by this Kingdom to just like fight
their War for no reason yes maybe cuz
they weren't stains they were like ooh
the stains are attacking us they weren't
stains they were just people in a
dungeon they were just red guys that's
[Music]
suspicious something it's a foot it's a
skull I don't like this I I don't
like oh dear it's just like
dark run Rock and Roll Baby
Run um I don't know how we can take the
giant the giant there's an invisible
wall there's an invisible wall
um oh new checkpoint unlock was it a
scripted
death oh no I was able to stay alive on
the corner of the
stair I think it was scripted scripted
rock
band
oh what's this a skeleton is he friendly
he hostile he's hostile give him a hug
come on give my phone okay okay actually
wait no wait
no ooh oh o his bone
crumb did you
get w wow
ow oh nice DPS DPS okay maybe we have to
use the B thingy oh oh can we make it
grow yeah I thought so but was he just
spawned out of it so did you get the the
damage I want ow I want the I want the
Boney give me give me give me can you
attack it or can you might did you get
one no a bone crumb oh ah I'm
dying
healer I'm on I'm on cool down you're on
your own save yourself
okay you have to kill him on top of the
mushroom oh that's a good idea
genius
oh it worked well now what oh massive
brain maybe
again can we break these blocks and use
them uh
[Music]
yeah come here yeah come here come
here do not drop
[Music]
Decora yeah can we feed it again I don't
know yeah maybe we can try bring it here
come here has the
F oh we can oh maybe we have to fill we
have to fill this place maybe then it's
like stairs or something ah
[Music]
okay ow I was standing in that
sorry my
bad oh oh all
right he's on me he's on me on me on me
on me oh
nice that enough ouch oh we have to get
up there oh maybe I think we maybe not I
think we need a little
more more oh
[Music]
W here you
oo okay where is he
oh there's a button ises that do there's
buttons oh you can climb the vines over
here to get
[Music]
up there always buttons on trees
here oh there's more butt the buttons
will show you the way
[Music]
follow the path of the
buttons okie dokie press the
buttons If you want
button o another button o another
button button oh is there
more do we have to do it
[Music]
again hey
you come over here
I guess
we
[Music]
more come here there he
is ah I'm
dying wait wait wait I can heal you I'm
the Healer oh my God that heals full
that's really impressive actually that's
crazy pretty good power really wait we
should try to see can you heal two
people at once do you not get healed by
too I thought it was a but it might be I
haven't been that
close okay next time do you
a let us know when it's un cool of cool
down again so we can do it come here
here okay I'll let you
know ah we have buttons buttons OU ouch
ouch ouch ouch buttons oh I'm going to
die any
buttons oh it hurts it hurts H
away no come this way let's see just how
scary these do you
mind okay I'm off cool down are you guys
damaged yeah I'm damaged can be okay pay
attention
hey baby I got
heal I think we should be able to climb
up here oh
[Music]
not I'm climbing
oh there's buttons oh there's buttons
are we done I don't know if we have to
do the other one
too um I think we can get up on this one
yeah I do I do Cece
[Music]
C you wait she was slay by a skeleton
uh-oh the Healer was not there
um um ring ring
back see see yes hello where where did
you where did you
spawn I'm on the other tree I'm coming I
see you I see you okay I'm sorry I was I
was there to save you from the skeleton
no it's
okay I was trying to take on the enemy
on my own I shouldn't have we're we're
stronger as a team we have to stay
together okay I'm back okay okay I'll
see you in to you guys okay
goodbye how do
we oh do we need the other
one
no maybe
how good is our
parkour I
think I mean would they just make it so
that there's two of them but you only
need one would they do
that
no maybe maybe we need here you you work
on the parkour and I'll go feed the
other tree uhoh
I'm
dying here here
here thank
you thank
you I think we need this one
too for some reason I kept trying to
climb the vine but it wouldn't work oh
no I think we need to feed the other
tree too did you manage to get up though
no not all the way oh
[Music]
okay okay sorry I just want to heal and
then we can go here
yes ow no luck or did you
fall I did I think we need both yeah I
think we need
both excuse me hey boy come here come
here come here come die come
[Music]
die was that good
maybe anybody need
heels you missed did I miss well I
didn't miss myself
[Music]
um I'm
going I don't know where my team is are
they alive I'm holding it I swear don't
I'm holding I swear I
am are you having trouble with the
vines I did but I'm here nowo I don't
know if this is the
way I think so the buttons are here
yeah we the buttons
mislead
um oh she made
it she's
[Music]
fast we have we've done it you did
it we all did it emmer
[Music]
green I'm green over
here they're doing green to Green
[Music]
Communications you might need to go from
the other
tree try the
[Music]
left left
left
wait
right oh no wait did
she
hello oh wait you're here I'm here I'm
here oh speed running speed running let
go I just wanted I didn't want you guys
to wait any longer so I like you know
what I'll just skip it Scarlet one
genius that's why we're the
Geniuses creativity
okay read it for us you see
yeah to the Denis of the Underworld the
light imated elminated by Souls was
vital they needed it to survive in this
ever cold and dark environment yet among
them there was a heretic who called the
Customs into question do we really need
to take others lives to sustain own own
is that how it works I think so no no
there has to be another way and so she
stepped into the plane above oh she went
on a trip she went on a trip what
happened to her yeah what could have
happened I don't
[Music]
know let's open this
door oh did we do
it
oh your power of Revelation has grown
stronger wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait
[Music]
[Applause]
wait this is what we
need the level up give me give
me maybe this
one you've received a portion of your
memories
amazing okay I'm not going to I'm not
going to click there oh but I will show
you the
video later we will show you the
video should we do that now or I I am
down to show it now where is the video
it is it is you can you may download it
from the announcements
channel oh I may need 2 minutes then to
log onto Discord oh
no oh dear
okay let's do that real quick okay
please hold as we access our memor yeah
takes a while to remember it's so
fuzzy have any elevator music oh I do
you know I've got I've got the
music the L juke box oh yes oh
yes um please
hold oh one
second oh my memory is so foggy guys I
just have to remember your passwords
have to remember
everything I have finished accessing my
memories should I should I wait for you
guys
or um let's let's play it together we
can wait right more time my memory
download speed seems to be a little bit
slow
my mine my existing speed seems to be a
little bit
slow
no we will get there yeah that was a
cute dungeon I like the puzzles I didn't
like the tree stuff but I like the
little triangle maybe maybe two too many
trees but yeah but the blocking was fun
yeah the light was really cool yeah and
it looked super impressive mhm okay I am
now
due to my weird memory setup I am
transferring my memory from one data
machine to the somebody said Cece's on
[Music]
[Laughter]
dial it's funny until it's not until
you okay oh God this is so slow this is
a big memory
well it's good right regain faster if we
get him in bigger
CHS oh yeah if you guys want you can go
ahead without me I don't mind how how
how much longer for your memory to
download um so I'm currently at uh so I
have a stick and then I'm putting M on
the stick and it's at 80% and then I
have to put it on the other data machine
and then uh this is really a tomaton
technology right here yeah this thing is
like when I was created they wanted like
it to be really secure you know so they
they didn't let any like my brain is
Split in Two and they yeah it's very
complicated imimi and Engineering very
complicated lots of gears and cogs
spinning
around yeah it's
uh
[Laughter]
um looking oh okay
and now I will put it
here she's in the second
machine
yippe the sun is
rising it's almost there
okay
okay oh
nice okay somebody asked if it was a
floppy
disc no no it's a oops it's
a hide scen it's fine it's fine it's a
floppy disc is it's a floppy disc no
it's not a floppy disc it's like
completely different okay I'm at
90% nice well Papa thank
you okay okay okay
okay I got it I'm here okay oh I'm
remembering so well are we are we ready
to play it are we going to are we ready
to remember I'm ready to remember guys
okay me too I'm ready to remember let
remember okay let's
[Music]
remember oh God wait hold on it's a
little big a Reaper's job is to end
people's lives and take their
souls the a the spirits of the
underworld
okay I got the audio oh it's loud okay
ready but I keep wondering oh wait Haven
started we all start wait should we
start on three let's start over let's
start over let's start over Okay start
over Okay
okay who's counting oh wait wait hold on
I'm not ready yet hold
on okay
okay okay everybody
ready one three two one
[Music]
go a Reaper's job is to end people's
lives and take their
souls that's how it's always been the
spirits of the underworld need their
sustenance sorry but I keep wondering
it's not
[Music]
mut is this the right thing to
do no wait
she she was the lady in the veil she was
the lady in the in the in the Flav
Tex a shoot what's going going
[Applause]
on look at
that there's another one we can also use
people's emotions we can do it we don't
need their souls at
all she's being called back Reaper
should help the
living that take away their future if
the others can't accept that that's
their
loss yeah
oh she mured them
all I'll do things my
way
cool that was cool yeah Cy
Mor some cool Reaper right
there so was her dungeon her under mhm
her underworld
dungeon oh no I don't want to go back
into the dungeon no no thank you oh I'm
good I'm good I'm good how do we go home
though yeah we need to go talk to Quest
Giver let me see go fast with the horse
oh gosh okay wait do you know the way
can we follow you will you lead us oh I
see yeah I can I'm looking at the map
okay okay onward Scarlet one let's go to
get you a stone sword let me make
haste yes yes oh wait this way oh I said
no let me
in one two
three okay are you with me yes let's go
you say so away ouch
violence
it's the voice is in my head are calling
they calling for copy
more and then we go
inside
[Music]
okay and then back to you guys want to
person's
names oh did they change color or that
was the
same is it a new horse every
time Brown from the start I feel like
mine changed
colors yeah mine definitely changes
colors
what wait it does what the they're
calling a new horse from the void every
time how can we get attached to our Pony
that
way it's a magical pony okay just a
magical pony
here here hello here you here
you here
here okay we made it done your bidding
green man yeah what's what's say
you where's our
money please read for us someone I'll
read Brave hero I am hardened to see
that you have returned unharmed pray
tell what transpired at the ruins oh cut
scene oh no no we just explain I see to
think the ruins held such Secrets a
crystal deep within that when touched
returned a fragment of your memories to
you memories which in turn reawaken to
the power of Revelation albe it at only
a fraction of its potential oh yeah do
we level up our power stronger now yeah
at the end of the dungeon in that white
room yeah that your summoning in the
discovery of these ruins should coincide
so closely there must be some connection
between the ruins and the power of
Revelation Brave hero seek rubius The
Guild Master of the Scarlet wand his
Guild that's us his Guild has also been
searching for strange ruins in the lands
of leasel maybe they have discovered
[Music]
something oh my God oh my God we get to
go to our Guild we'll see our Guild now
okay okay well I mean this one's fine
but I bet ours is way cooler because
it's creative and stuff
yeah 100% okay let's
go north
okay lead the
[Music]
way oh wait is it right
here oh it's not that
far oh look at it though it's a big
question mark yeah cuz we're seeking
knowledge knowledge see see how potencia
s Scarlet
wand how do we go inside
I don't know do we just talk to him out
here yeah let's talk to him and then
let's go inside and check it
out can you do like a what what do you
think rubius would sound like you do
it a a good day to you hero return the
the the text went away hm yes I now
sense within you a trace of the power of
Revelation fascinating Most Fascinating
one might hypothesize that I don't know
how you that's the word that those ruins
are the key to unlocking your powers we
of the Scarlet wand have also been
investigating near the Plains and
wouldn't you know it just off the coast
we aspired a light with a striking
resemblance to Revelation good hero
would you be willing to travel to the
coast and Aid in our efforts there of
course members of our Guild are already
there hard at work I'm quite sure they
will appreciate your assistance good
luck and exelia
spells
Fireball is it more powerful
now but I feel like mine was already a
full heal does it get much better than
that maybe the cool down bigger
[Music]
TP T
XL we have rooms yeah do we live
here
oh still cleaning up the
mess oh let's
[Music]
go do you think it's bunk beds a big
table Yeah are we just small cray
folded look you can't even see over the
table this little guy a he needs to
boost the se he does tiny
cute okay I
mean I don't see any rooms but we could
just put our camp
here good thing I have I have instant
tee we can sleep in summon
tee I cast summon
Tepe might be a little hard to sleep in
it if it's there but actually oh I have
some hide can we build it all here I
don't think
so let me
see yeah can we build stuff someone said
we can build at the
Garden uh yeah I think that's like a
house area but we're not allowed we
don't have the contractual like licenses
to build on their property we don't
which is weird cuz we're part of the
team but okay
well we have a lot of money we can go
see what they're
selling yeah a good
idea cuz I think wait what about the pit
do you think there's like some death
tournament that we can parake some
illegal gambling ring maybe ooh that
would be cool play some dice that would
be cool
o okay we can check out the shop does
anyone remember where it
was maybe
here across from the
blacksmith oh
okay the blacksmith was where was at the
tavern oh it was it was a it was oh wait
we have a map guys is it is it
labeled um yeah we have a what we have a
in our handy magical document we have a
I have
a so we need to go to the town Gates
Scarlet wand is here why is Jade
everyone else's bases are bigger than
ours it's because ours is creativity we
don't need a lot of space to be creative
that's right they don't know about the
secret bunker ours is mostly underground
they're over compensating for the
smallness of their brains with the
bigness of their houses oh yes so true
okay I think it's here
no
[Music]
yes oh someday I will know
you were you actually The Bard all
along I'll be The Bard hell yeah
please where is
c um there she
is here we are this is the district and
there should be the tavern should be
across here's the
shop
money he has a lantern a fashion
surprise box fash surprise Bo we have
did that I bought it let's see should we
open it on three yes okay one two
three click to
choose
oh what this is not
fashion
what I didn't get any fashion at all did
you ask
fashing fashion I got a construction
supplies box I got a construction
this might be good actually oo wait did
we get 64 of whatever we choose do I
only get one
really never mind the gacha is
Bountiful what did you get I got 64
Cherry
logs I'm making a pink house pause I'm
going to buy one moreti head
watch your
[Laughter]
mouth watch your mouth when you talking
to
me you call
head you you
this point oh my God you do have a
point has a point I've got a garden for
you to s
in I will guard you oh no your neck be
careful it's going to break from W oh my
shoulders
a could use that as a weapon if you look
down really fast you can
SL forwards with your face
down
Jud no she's too strong
so that is impressive yeah it's because
your brain is so big cuz you're part of
the skullet want yeah it's all hiding in
my head please don't take off my head if
you take off my head I'll
die I bought another one oh you had the
money I need to sell some 700 oh I only
have 300
left okay wait I got hats again what oh
we could use it to impersonate another
guild oh
oh and then the I give you guys one of
these back on the
[Music]
table wait what did I get oh I didn't
get it oh did you get the just shows you
what you didn't get it's kind of mean
like that how do we sell stuff I see oh
yeah does he buy stuff 300 coins I'm
going to
cry it's okay you can maybe we you can
sell the stuff you get inside maybe I
didn't get
anything nothing not even consolation
prize I did I did I got a box the box is
actually pretty good yeah oh gives you
item take from
it what' you say what' you say what did
you did you say what did you say hello
ladies she say hat hello greetings
greetings I am the appointed
point the point get it are you now of
the Scarlet
wand I
speak we had a side quest and she took
over leader of our guilt m w that's
cool how we are wearing hat like this it
looks like you're wearing like a red
velvet cake on your head what is your
name blue
creature it um
um I don't know the leader of she forgot
you still don't know the point of the
scalid W hey you aren't you the one that
hit me with your horse oh my God there's
there's lots of
horses her and you are the one that
drowned her this
yeah wait a
minute wait who don't worry I'll kill
whoever what what they do you hit me
with your hores no no no
no no no who her right what what Guild
are you a part
of hey be with your horse we will never
know um
uh
yeah for you would you want 6 22
Mangrove logs if you tell us what color
your guild
is
really here I 24 I'm opening I'm uping
it no I want I want the big hats or
nothing no you're not going get the big
hats nothing it's okay goodbye you TR
with you wa wait let me reason let me
reason you don't
understand if I take this hat off I will
die so it's a it's a trade your life or
this
hat no that doesn't no her life and the
hat for
what I think I'll W the Hat anyway but
what if we give you uh wood
instead I I I don't I don't want a wood
I want I want this hat specifically well
you're not going to get it how about how
about I can offer you the opportunity of
a lifetime have you ever needed shelter
and you had nowhere to go well what I
can offer you is instant
TP any time or place anytime or place
restrictions May
apply okay let me tell you I'm a white
cat so I don't actually have a house I
don't need a home so oh I am okay thank
you but thank you for the uh for the
offer it was actually yeah yeah no but
you already took it you now in her debt
no no it doesn't work like that that's
she gave it to you and you
agreed I have I offer you a trade oh
okay you give me 500 coins and I tell
you what you need to know I do not have
that kind of money
M I can give you five no 500 and the hat
five best best I can give you 500 and
the hat she's not to be reasoned with no
hat no
hat okay no hat but I want 500 coins I
give you five you don't have any backup
who's to say we couldn't just quietly
make you
disappear yeah
what do you mean hey that's against the
rule leave me alone leave me
alone put her in the house put her put
her in the
[Music]
house I need a cool down reduction on my
TP
stat it's okay who else is in the team
maybe we can ask someone
else is that
I don't know what team I actually don't
know the guild yeah me either that's the
problem it's the yellow
coin the blue cup then it's and the
Amber te and the green sword oh yeah
uhhuh it's okay I'm sure we'll figure
out with time our
next and um the next time we meet her
we'll be plentiful do you guys do you
guys want to wind down in the local T
maybe you
yeah we go to the tower did we did we
complete what we were supposed to
complete
today I think so I think
so wait there's a bar made wait a minute
a save the kingdom brick on the house on
the house on the house he's charging me
100 coins wait yeah where where'd you
get it on the house house the left one
set on the house well he hasn't given me
anything maybe it's just like ad lip you
know he's just he's just telling me to
talk to the bar
man night vision on the house if you can
really save the kingdom oh
oh I spent all my money
fun good what I'll buy you a drink I
like everyone czy names and then this
like
yeah what would your preferred drink of
choice be can we
loot like like
Rob no no no no no no no loot it's
borrowing oh we can still simply
borrowing yeah do they have anything
they don't have
anything or somebody else gone here
first there's a chest
don't steal
from we
are we're saving their
life anything do you think they made8
bit versions of the songs you can listen
to like this
[Music]
here oh yeah did you buy one
oh they have the records
right the records
yeah we can Farm
gold we could do you guys want to maybe
try checking out the arena do you think
there's gambling there yeah I can do
that let's gamble the rest of our money
away GI yeah I still have 335
oh you could have bought another gacha
that was some restraint that you showed
I wanted to save it for possible
gambling I think it's brilliant SAS God
genius I think everybody else is doing
the the thing we already did are they we
just that fast we coordinator it says it
says
duel o can we fight each other RS okay
the first participant presses the duel
button whoever wishes to challenge them
also presses the duel button the first
par speaks to the arena coordinator
again after pressing the start game
button a countdown will begin after
which The Duel between the two players
begin you can also dual party versus
party well in a party one representative
of the party should press The Duel
button representative of the other party
must then also press the okay well we
know a party okay if you guys maybe you
guys can duel and I go onto the steps to
look at your commentator wait wait why
not why not you why don't I go on the
steps um to Comm and oh wait wait wait
wait wait wait we should have green
versus green no no we are team we are
the same side I think we should find
another party to fight it's just it's
just a need to to do all this infighting
right yeah no I feel like since we have
it's
practice maybe we should do one fight
and then do one with an opposing team
okay somebody duel me I'll Stand still
I'll be your punch
dummy okay you two go I'll I'll watch
okay come on man come on find a join
come on find her come on joined the red
team could not find an opponent ah I
think it has to be against
opposite oh oh really you think duel
you've joined the red
team yeah we're all on the red team
oh oh okay I'm calling I'm calling
someone yes call them
over ring
ring private call Who's online
are they all busy in the dungeon oh they
might be in the dungeon yeah okay I'm
going to I'm going to call uh okay so we
one two three Let's us I think Elizabeth
and mor in the dungeon okay I'm just
going to try
G where the other players is already no
call okay I'll try my German we just
stand our party and fight each other
then oh that's a good idea okay okay
let's do that goodbye
oh
red
blue seems
backwards 3 2
uh-oh wait where's my
apple and
green I have a wooden sword are you
kidding me
Apple you don't get an apple now where'd
you go stop moving you stop moving stop
stop the Ping Man stop ping sure yeah
sure it is the Ping it is the Ping wait
wait I'm going to die I'm going to die I
heard I heard I
heard green
[Music]
dominations y green wins
now Fork over all your lunch
money
um I can't i' have to trade you oh uh
tra okay okay give me all your
money this is all I have but I don't
believe that it's all I swear to you
it's all I have I swear
okay fine how much was it one
scaffolding okay okay that's no no bring
the bring the scaffolding
back my scold this cost me 300 gold yeah
exactly plus oh wait hold on what
[Music]
we okay fine
fine bring
this bring this back wait I'm thinking
though we could use this at some point
I'll use it I'll use
it what do you think I'm going to do
with it I'm going to use it to make
something
beautiful no we have to use it we have
to we're on the same team it's only
fair it's only fair you lost it keeps
going down there's no ke okay fine
fine enjoy your wheat seeds I will
you'll see I'll be I'll have a whole
Farm soon enough I'll be feeding all of
the Scarlet
wands how do we do cost any money so I'm
going to spend my last money on one more
loot box I think wait what about the
pit this is the pit this is not the pit
right this is the isn't there another
pit no the pit is where they sleep this
the pit there's some shady guy
at the pit
right yes oh right you're right pit was
yellow okay let's see the pit
is is the pit from here it is on this
side okay lead the
[Music]
way okay wait so they have like a casino
and then there's also like the Coliseum
what do we
have the
library go
[Music]
studybr can we gamble bookie oh we can
gamble make a
bet oh I'm going all in on
green green I got to do blue all in on
Green work got how do you do this how
does it
work 40 seconds okay green is there a
roulette wheel or
[Music]
something
20 how do I do this ah okay uh you right
click him yeah and then press on the
make a bed the golden button and there's
a a window with four colors
[Music]
what a window what happens if you right
click him I have a hammer and a piece of
paper oh yeah Click put your money in
the piece of paper however much money
you want to bet just PR in like 100 or
whatever how much you have and then
press enter and it should do like
aing aing okay nice you color Cannon is
firing where's the color Cannon where's
the color Cannon oh there there it's is
it red oh the
wall uh-huh oh wait maybe not is it
deleting the
colors uhoh uhoh wait I put I put the
last one standing wins yeah
maybe blue blue blue green green green
green green green
greenen green green Green
[Music]
green green Green there's no way
green 10 times how
no that's not normal this was a scam it
was green was a
set they saw us walk in and we green and
blue and they were
like wow that's that's that's
I can't believe this would happen okay I
have some more money I'm broke went all
in on green I'll give you a little bit
of money and then you can let bed one
more time
okay except yellow oh sorry
there's nothing quite like bonding with
your guild
membering do you think do you think we
were oh push I think it worked if you
push the red
one okay oh thank you
okay what did you guys bet on oh you're
Bing green
green
yellow okay
you bookie you better not cheat this
time yeah we know it's green one more
chance all right it's over oh god oh
colon
firing please please I need this all
green are standing how am I going to
collect all my funny
hats
uh's gone that's good
come on okay
GRE green green not I
I come
onance hold hold yellow come
on goodby yellow green green green green
green no it's blue is it blue it's blue
wait no it's not it's green green green
it's green how much you make I got 300
bucks you got so much money from that no
way okay I'm betting what you guys do
you guys are
lucky than are
we are we betting
green I'm betting
green is it really going to be green
again though of course always believe in
green it's the strongest color
it
is okay
okay I did 20 on green only 20 not much
Faith there help I've lost every time
old man I'm running out of
coins okay I'm fine I like the little
tables it's very cute oh yeah oh we
should sit we should down on the table
oh oh sorry sorry my bad you can on my
lap I don't
mind oh
okay wait I can't see though I might
beat the table up wait you should be on
the on the front then I can't see
anything with your head on oh sorry oh I
see I see I see oh okay
sorry no you go no you go excuse me oh
no no no you go no no you go no you go
okay it's green it's green it's going to
be green again
it's obviously confident it's obviously
confident red is already gone that's
good it's obviously
green has to be
green
see I'm seeing it's green it's green
it's green
[Music]
mhm see it's green it's green it's green
it's green it's green it's
green it's green
just your wait it's
[Applause]
green no way how much wait how much did
you guys make now I have 700 bucks I
have
955 oh my
gosh green means
money green The Color of Money dollar
bills happens again right it has to
happen again I think
green you have to always trust in green
you have to trust in
green it's never disappointed you so far
I I definitely I definitely trust in
green I trust in green
too you wouldn't you wouldn't you
wouldn't forsake green would you no I
wouldn't I would never you wouldn't
suddenly like turn around and not go for
green never never never after everything
it's done for you never never
I believe
[Music]
you I got to make some money back I sure
hope this Green
Works it'll be green
definitely 100 on red I don't have H I
don't have the
money no do you need a Lo it's going to
be green no not yet
there green green green Green it's
definitely green green come
on see okay red is gone again
green
okay yeah okay terrible
mhm now yellow just has to
perish blue still
W yeah okay yes it's
green it's green oh my God
green there's no way
green surely can't
300 are we green again I'm green yeah
we're
green did you lose some money earlier
for no no no no no you went to Green
okay okay I simply regret that I didn't
put more on green I am all on green if
this doesn't work
broke so I'll put a little more this
time if this doesn't work yeah I'm going
to hold it against the members of the
Jade Spoon or whatever their Guild is
called yeah the Jade
Spoon yeah the
merian it'll be over for them
yeah okay I'm starting to I don't know
how I feel about this one okay green
it's green it's green it's green green
definitely
[Music]
green I
I see okay it's green alive all green
standing
okay yeah yes that's still fine it's
fine mhm stay up to mytic it's
okay mhm my optimism is wavering what no
no don't waver believe in the green okay
I
believe it's
green see how far apart they are there's
no way can you can snipe all of them see
mhm Goodbye
Blue no
I have to go my knees are weak I can't
my legs I have to go I have
to I have
[Music]
to wait you did this I'll be back I went
all in I'm
broke I'm broke um how are you doing are
you broke I'm I'm at
700 that's pretty good should we ask for
a small loan of 10 coins oh just 10 yeah
oh 10 just 10 I just need
10 oh thank
you I'll I'll do you one
better
more I'll extra zero just for
you oh oh I am ever grateful thank
you but you will only spend it on green
right yeah I will always spend it on
green how much do I owe you in return
what rate on this oh it's just it's just
30% okay that's
all I feel like
the the like the
percentages are they like accurate or is
there a way to numerically game the
system based on like the numbers
of the many is
this is this I it has to do with
confidence it's all a a brain game if
you're really confident and you believe
I think you can
win 99% of gambl quit before they
win I think you can do it oh the house
always wins does it is it actually
rigged against
us wait what color did you guys do are
we betting I'm betting I'm betting I'm
sorry I'm beten green I went 500 on
green 500 oh my
God that's how it goes we lost last time
we'll win this time is is counting
colors the same as counting cards am I
going to get thrown out of
here um they are very small and don't
tell them bookie the bookie can barely
see anything so it's fine if so I'm
going to be able to
tell okay
okay okay red is
[Music]
out
okay very good good so
far
yes it's so green it's like a hat
it's an arrow pointing to the
Moon okay to the
moon to the Moon
green green no
5050 green to the Moon do we believe in
it yes believe in green oh
no it's rigged it's rigged it's rigged
they hate us they hate us they hate us
specifically they're like two3 green and
they're attacking us for it okay I'm
going to go all in on this last one
I mean we're do we're
do a green green Green is
do what about red no red is not do green
is do a number it is a number could be
red though
no it could be it's going to be
green could be all in on red f it could
be oh it's 500 Max
okay can't go more than 500 that's fine
500 explain this to sh and Nissa oh well
if we make money we won't have anything
to explain right yeah true and if we
don't if there's like which won't happen
then we can say that another the team we
burglaring us yeah yeah
[Music]
green
green Green please you don't
understand yep it's a green
yep clearly this they can only be
one this time it's a arrow that points
down down because what is that me
because you're going
down my
red see El wait you went all red I went
all in red oh
no why
no it's not fair it's not it's not fair
believe to us I'm drowning in the
fountain yellow oh no don't come in the
fountain don't shouldn't be enough for
this please
okay I don't have I don't have that much
money left I'm going to think it's going
to be green this time oh okay one it's
all I knew fun I got I actually believe
this time we're actually
do I'm going all in you said last no
last time I was wrong this time we're
do because it was yellow last time it
will absolutely be green this time okie
dokie it's all probability really
yeah get my
head I can't
see we can even go upstairs to the
cannon oh can we tamper with the cannon
I think so maybe to make it so it's
always
green we can talk to it very very you
know enticingly listen you have to make
it green this time make it green make it
green please make it green green who
know you want to green green Green
gre gre love green green color of money
color of
nature color of
success Color of Love green green which
is is the opposite of green we'll see
how this
works color of leaves color of crops
color of hurry nervous is
coming color of
everything it's okay we're going to make
it all back green green green green
green green green Green okay okay okay
it's looking good you want green that's
what you
want listen to your heart I never
doubted the green I never doubted the
green I'm sorry green green green green
Green
[Applause]
[Music]
never never
coins oh my God I have a thousand
coins yay okay with that Victory I think
I'm going to go to sleep oh my memories
are coming back to me it's almost like I
have to sleep oh me too memories of
bedtime memories of bedor of bed
memories of my comfortable bed with a
pillow that is cool on both
sides and a mattress that's made of
money sleeping on a pile of money wait
what's my mattress made of I'll sleep in
my hat don't worry about it never
mind yeah just flip it around it is like
a sleeping bag it's a sleeping
bag actually it's long enough for that
you look like a you look like a
caterpillar c c a pillar or like a a
pastry like a cornet do you remember
that scene in Lucky Star where they're
CH talking about the chocolate
coret yeah
yeah it's like
that I believe but it was really fun
thank you for hanging out yeah thank you
I mean Scarlet one Scarlet one Scarlet
Scarlet one not Green Team
team maybe
the oh yeah te but red is the opposite
of green so it makes sense yeah about it
yeah it's like complimentary callous so
it makes a lot of sense okay see you
guys again for so we can kill all the
stains and destroy the Dungeons and win
at gambling good night good
nighty wait can we have like a slogan
like a battle or cry we should that will
cry I don't know any good ones
though
Scarlet
want uh wait curiosity and
creativity creative
curious
uh wait guys we the cre come up with
something this is a bad look maybe maybe
the other two can come up oh we have to
wait for the others that would be nice
if we just yeah that's why we have a lot
of good ideas but we're trying to be
inclusive okay bye on green bye
Momen goodbye everybody good night good
night
[Music]
bye okay I have left the
game I think I'm going to read super
chance
though before you head
out I mean you free to head out
still I'm going to stick around a little
[Music]
longer let me go over
here ah I'm floating I'm not
floating was I floating I'm
normal no more double audio
can you see the cloak okay but I feel
like it looks weird at the bottom I'll
show you it but I feel like it looks
weird I don't know I don't know if it's
supposed to look how it looks at the
bottom you'll
[Music]
see well this it looks
normal but then it it's
like it's like suddenly my skirt is
transparent I don't
know maybe it's cuz you wouldn't be able
to see the cloak
otherwise or maybe it's
a an error I don't
know but you don't really see the bottom
[Music]
anyway Callie's sleeve did that in the
cut scene actually so is it
Canon maybe it's maybe it's Canon then
it's magic
the magic of the
cloak perhaps why do I get two cloaks I
get to
cloak thank you guys for hanging
out thank you thank
you this was a fun first stream I hope
there's
like I don't know I want to like do
stuff that's not like just the quests I
want to like build stuff you
know I want to go off Off
Script you
[Music]
know may a world tree can you imagine if
I somehow managed to make a world tree
in this game I mean it seems like you
can get materials I like kind of want to
grind and get materials and build
something cute well actually what I want
to do is break the game but I don't know
how I need to use my Scarlet wand genius
to figure out how to break the game okay
well with the gambling you can bet on
multiple things I
think
so does someone who knows numbers no did
they code it right so that they cannot
so that you can't win every time by like
betting a certain amount on each one
does the house actually have the edge in
this one
let's do the math you
can't how rust works too it's not
possible no numbers three is a good
one the house wins red is one out of 25
but only gives 10 x so never vote red
but what about the others what about
blue and
green all options are bad are they
green is N9 out of 25 but gets times
three wait what is 9 ided by
25 9 divided by 25 is
36 but it gets times three so it's 36%
wait isn't that
bad yeah I guess they still
lose dang it did they code it properly
so that they can't exploit it
I was hoping you could exploit it for
infinite
monies it's
decent how could they how could they
they Cod it
[Music]
properly green is just slightly less
than3 that means that if I play forever
I will eventually lose
get it
twisted 99% of gamblers give up before
they win big I'm up right now though
I've got 1,000 gold burning a hole in my
[Music]
pocketses so I'm feeling
optimistic House Always Wins how do I
become part of the house
then I understand and what I must do I
must become the
house all right let me read the super
chats what time is
it okay it's it's late but it's okay I
was sleepy but I woke up a little bit
and I'm hungry I'll read the super chats
though thank you for hanging out today
thank you thank
you late
o00 who was the first to defeat the
dungeon was it us was it us don't tell
me if it wasn't
us did we win are we
winning it was us
really good
stuff all right let me read the Super
Chat thank you thank you snip redn Sam
ghosty hi CDR man misery sakur ktie na M
shark Paul K hypnosis SP hidden man AR
Spirit event ziply Co shiping bad NE
Matthew
Benji wolf hound King Shar Luke
Oro
place
and
pizio hogman of
time REO Alexander our the Bon Bishop
CTI and jaoo bed great move my GL cons
Works Plum Plum got to PL them all got
to PL them all s round thank you seven
happy Saturday is it Saturday I barely
even
know happy weekend Elian thank you thank
[Music]
you him and Evan thank you
I feel
like my my role playing could use some
work to this
one I was I was just I'm just playing
I'm just
playing wait is it Labor Day
weekend perfect role
play Oh happy Labor Day weekend you guys
have a long weekend I hope you
do happy long
[Music]
weekend thank
you Glover thank you very much daylight
cuz but I couldn't not send a post
breaking Dimensions to but doubt I'll be
able to properly Express all my feelings
I wanted to say how proud I was to see
you up there performing live in person
in my home City I was blown away by your
singing and dancing my voice is still
recovering and my heart is still full
from it all your you're always going to
be a goofy gaming here in first to me
but thank you for showing me what it
means to be an idol too thank you very
much I appreciate
[Music]
it I know it's a it's a wild Journey
I've been on I I really do enjoy the the
idle Parts even though I do I think I am
mainly a gaming goofy silly Kieran it's
fun to be able to do these things that I
never thought I would be able to
do be faction thank
you yeah is this the first like full
Hallen collab since Justice
joined was everybody
here and we do roll call
[Music]
yes good
stuff Jessica thank you I'm glad you got
your merch my
[Music]
merch keep thinking the golden apples
that 20 would actually that one I know I
mean you could just lie well it's bad to
cheat at the table but I won't hold it
against you if you say that the the
golden apple is also 20 then you yeah
you get
22s Bishop thank
you bird thank
you thank you Mr re thank you y thank
you Sean thank you nor thank you
unregistered hyper camel thank
you
no this is my nightmare I was have you
have a final exam in 5 minutes for class
you accidentally registered for and
forgot about you didn't attend the whole
semester and you're like panicking like
what do you do and the thought of like
talking to the professor never crosses
your mind it's always somehow I have to
I have to get a passing grade out of
this I have that nightmare all the
time oh that reminds
me I don't remember if I talked about
this but was were we talking about it
there are like common dreams that people
have and apparently one of them is teeth
falling out and I had never had the
teeth falling out dream but I had it the
other night I had a dream that my teeth
fell out and it was very weird and
disturbing but it was my first time and
now I feel like I've I've joined the
club you've never had that one I never
did either but I I finally did it was
gross I
like felt something weird in my mouth
and I like pulled on my gums and my like
whole gums peeled off in a line like my
bottom team
teth from like one side to the other and
almost all of my bottom teeth went with
it and then I was just like holding a
strip of my gums but it didn't hurt or
anything and I was like looking at it it
had my teeth in it and I was like wait
teeth don't grow back do they oh god and
then I was like do I need to keep this
string of gums like to go to the dentist
can they put them
back it was like I was like a shark like
molting my ring of teeth you
know it was
weird sounds horrifying it was pretty
horrifying I was like looking at my my
teethless
smile and I was like I mean I was
already going down on the the roads I
was like can you get like fake teeth can
I am I going to be Toothless the rest of
my
life yeah and thank you green tea thank
you you Nick thank
you thank
[Music]
you Elian thank you Microsoft windows
thank
you I don't know I never know it's it
feels like whenever Windows asks you if
you want to turn on sticky keys it's
always like a double negative question
it's like do you not not want to turn
off sticky keys
[Music]
it it's like I never know what it's
asking me and I barely even know what
sticky keys
means Grimace thank you I did like the
sounds it was making
though Ren thank you Evan thank you
Elian thank you nongo thank you as a
Daniel and a metal head I never thought
I'd one day find myself emotional at the
side of a sea of green pen lights
roaring there improve an anime girl
crushing a city pop classic seems my
weird old man with an ushy arc is not a
face I'm glad to hear it I'm glad I have
so many people to cheer me on thank you
it means a lot to
me Sean thank you Matthew thank you Jeff
thank you George thank you need more daa
thank you spicy Cheese Nips thank you
just got the D&D mer said on Wednesday
and the timing couldn't have been better
cuz it's your birthday happy belated
birthday just want to say thanks for the
gift I guess by the way bringing
Dimensions is great and your cover stay
with me was amazing thank you I'm really
glad you guys liked
it let me play a birthday song for
you happy birthday to you happy birthday
to you happy birthday dear saing Happ
happy birthday to you happy
[Music]
birthday evil darkart catfish thank
you is thank you Matthew thank
you evil cartoon Moon thank you Scarlet
wand with an ARL
scar
scar Scarlet wand Scarlet wand Scarlet
wand W okay I'm getting it I'm getting
it Scarlet wand you just have to say it
dramatically and it helps Scarlet wand
Scarlet
wand you know thank
[Music]
you thank you congratulations Scarlet W
sweep that's
[Music]
right Elian thank you cappuccino thank
you Senti thank you cappuccino thank you
thank you B thank you let SC team
Slytherin no we're obviously the
Ravenclaw analog if anything have we we
have not been at okay maybe we've been a
little bit villainous today but hasn't
everyone been a little bit villainous
today
[Music]
Slytherin is green that's true that's
true all right thank you that's all I
have for you tonight I will be back
again
tomorrow for probably more of this but
maybe something else also I might
do a stream at PA a standard time like
short stream and then also stream this
maybe we'll see we'll
see cuz they want you to play at well at
the time I started
today but then if I do like if I start
streaming at Fest Standard time and then
I stream again it's going to be like
really long stream
so we'll see it might be like short
stream at Fest Standard time and then
yeah and then another one later but I'm
not sure we'll see we will
see grinding stream I know I do kind of
want to grind in this game I want to get
the competitive
Advantage yeah I do need to catch up on
super chats also that might happen too
all right I'm Miss hot and I'm hungry
I'm going to go thank you very much for
watching please take care and I will see
you
later bye-bye F Well
[Music]
M this ain't your granny's radio
station I'm your DJ Kieran FAA and get
ready to J out let's go
[Music]
1 2