go
[Music]
one two say no
oh so
[Music]
one two say no
dream dreams
[Music]
Kitt I'm sparkling j h English event and
sorry I didn't start stream
early but uh what is it um I was going
through my art tag before stream and um
I saw I saw I saw uh someone made made
really cute cute beo uh emotes and I was
like oh that's so cute I thought it was
so so adorable so I I went and messaged
the artist Dei I was like hey can I put
these on my channel hey can I can I use
can I use these cuz I think they're so
adorable and they're so perfect and they
said yes so thank you also thank you for
answering so fast thank you for thank
you for uh replying um so fast as well
thank you thank you so I was able to put
the new emotes on on the channel very
quickly
um but uh so yeah we have we have we
have be boo and we have a thinking B boo
cuz I've always wanted to thinking
people that was that was the one I saw I
was like I I need to use that and we
also have some P em we have purle cry
and purle Bo so now when you B you have
a representation of your Bo so thank
thank you thank you than for the emotes
um so I was just rushing to put them in
um on
time so welome Z D6 on another s Days to
Die uh goal today is collecting bullets
and money cuz I think I'm almost out of
bullets and The Horde is today uh and I
need to collect
bullets I think to to
to be ready for the ho the
hord okay going in uh going in game
in
h oh oh hi people
hi how you doing OBS just died oh
no oh is that why you're running in
place am I I don't know I think my
computer is exploding oh no oh no
it's okay we got time let's see if I can
restart
this oh there we go is my game broken
too oh gosh I'm going to restart my
computer much good
luck
yeah uh bio yes tell me about your armor
what parts what levels are they uh okay
I only
wearing assassin boots level three
Ranger gloves level one Assassin outfit
level three and then nerd goggles level
three M okay okay okay I feel like um we
might not get
everything uh like improved but I want
to try at least maybe your gloves or so
making you better ones um I wear medium
armor that's my that's what I love out
okay uh but they're all like different
armor parts right like different yeah I
do have I do have Assassin Boot and
Assassin outfit so if I can get assassin
gloves then oh you want assassin gloves
okay yeah I think that'd be good
H cuz people were recommending preacher
gloves but I don't know it doesn't
really matter that much is prach light
armor
I think it's medium to or tell me chat I
don't remember but the preacher gloves
are really
good let me see and the set bonuses are
not that worth yeah my preacher gloves
are just on level three and they still
already give me plus 30 damage to
undeads oh okay 30% I mean I'll take
preacher gloves then if the if the
bonuses don't matter too much yeah I'll
take preacher stuffff okay I'll try to
make you some preach of gloves then um
might not be on the max level because
armor kits are oh let me give you let me
give you armor parts I have 10 ah armor
parts are not that important it's more
the armor kits oh okay and therefore
duct tape but yeah if you can find any
duct tape before the raid that will make
you three I need 10 for my weapon but
I'll give you three oh okay yeah nice
nice nice that should help um yeah and
when fauna comes back we should discuss
our battle plan for today
okay is it just the three of us in
hoorde or do you think more people are
coming I think gigy will at least come
okay so it might just be four but the Z
the amount of zombies that spawn depend
on how many people are online so we
should be fine okay um I think I'm going
to do quest to load up on bullets then
um because I'm running low on bullets
and I want to get enough Bullets by the
hord starts so that way I can cover
people's
butts that's good if you find some of my
ammo that will also be helpful I'll I'll
do quest to get ammo for
everybody okay I think I'll just try to
focus on Crafting most of the
time cuz quests really take up a lot of
time and we're already o already at the
end of day 26 yeah okay I will I will
spam Quest then while you guys get other
stuff
ready
okay guess I can make two for now I need
more sewing kits even can I make those
myself sewing kit
no oh
ah Callie wrote in my chat I'm so sorry
I wish I scheduled my thing on a
different day I'll make up for tomorrow
don't worry like I was just concerned
that maybe they'll spawn Too Many
Zombies but no should be fine don't
worry we'll be
fine we'll handle this the Nerds got
this
yeah um I don't the surely the Traer
sells
um seinging kits and stuff let me see
what they we have not much time left to
reach
them should I go to w or
Jen may be
wrecked boom boom boom
boom The Clement and their adopted child
yeah biboo is our first
born got to protect our firstborn or be
protected by
her I a solo the bear you'll be fine
well yeah I guess we'll be fine we'll be
fine if it if it spawns based on how
many people it shouldn't be that
bad I say is bad and left the game
uhoh that's her pattern she does that
every time she logs in really yes
interesting oh oh I had a quest to give
by back to him no yo 150 times 7.62 ammo
thank
you oh she made so many meals okay I'm
going to take some food on the road with
me um yeah she did make a lot of
food get this for fun and then I
will okay good luck
I could buy a couple of these but
wait ah
yes he only has one seing
kit yeah people if you find seing kits
duct tape anything like that okay you
know who needs
[Music]
it look at my SO sewing kit
oh is was m
bike
go I put it in the PO I think I
did I'm out of
money
okay onward to Quest
[Music]
shut up
guy so rude uh actually well uh you're
going to a trade direct right now yes
are you getting a quest or giving back
one I'm giving back one and I'm going to
grab another
one do you actually quickly just want to
do one quest with me the like one I
still have open it's kind
of somewhat close from here okay not
really um where sure
[Music]
was he complaining about me not tipping
well excuse me I'm European we tip here
too but
just 309 mimet you are
amazing yeah yeah he gives I think we we
got the same we gave the same Quest back
huh cuz I got a lot of ammo from him too
yeah very
nice let's make a
well don't just stand there with thumb
up your ass bye or bye all
righty is that the is that what bike is
this that's not mine you buy something
next time oh that might be my bike oh no
I took the wrong bike this one doesn't
have an extra seat oh
well that's fine then I'll go towards
the quest hello welcome back take me
with you oh okay okay we're just doing
I'm just doing one quest with bio now
you can join us but I won't be questing
the whole
time I think um there's a there's a
there's my tier three to the north
that's very close to the house if you
got to do that one to the north oh yeah
true oh we can pick fun up on the way
okay oh you're already going towards
mine huh yeah wait I think our bike
should still our mini bike should still
be there for now oh should I bring
minike yeah I took the wrong mini
bike ours should still be
there it's okay I can pick you up mine
has the
seat oh okay s I'm trying figure out my
inventory what did DC oh he DC no oh no
what's happening
to's
[Music]
Happ nah unbelievable oh
no it better behave during the the hard
night I know
yeah well well at least you girls can
hear me right now so let me actually um
bring up something for today's
raid I think one thing that would be
really good to f on because in this
R oh you cut out
uhoh uh-oh
uh-oh Mama I am outside the door with
the seat warm and open for you whenever
you are
second I'm trying to fix my inventory
okay no
problem no oh welcome back so you cut
off ah you cut I cut off oh God I want
to wear a cut uhoh uhoh
uhoh oh your wait bike locked uh I can't
get
in uh what the bike I made is is locked
oh okay no the one sorry the one bean
boo she's picking me up
Chihuahua
[Music]
Chihuahua what's going on today they
don't want us to play
[Music]
today it will surely stab stabilize soon
I believe I believe yeah I was saying I
think we should focus on modes not on
spikes because did you see how yesterday
during the digging Quest everybody was
falling in and that was so
op that's true that is true yeah yeah
yeah and now the zombies can probably at
this level really easily destroy our
spikes especially the vomiting
guys so okay I'll more spes more Moes
you want to loot this house while we
wait for kiaha yes okay
can we fight the boar is the still
dead where is the
boar um I think it's in here it's
probably still dead though I
think
a are we back in stream okay okay where
if we make Moes and then put spikes at
the bottom of the mo oh wait is this is
this the quest Quest for the bo oh oh
good then it will respawn when we start
the quest
oh I
think okay I think it's
stabilized knocking on
wood oh there's stuff
here okay I'm coming back into the game
[Music]
okay I have a book for you
ooh armor piercing round thank you o you
don't use Point 44 ammo oh I do I will
when I make my uh Magnum gun I just
haven't made the gun yet thank
you so the boy is not down here it's
supposed to be down here oh yeah it
hasn't respawned it'll probably respawn
when I start the class
yes okay okay I'm getting in I'm getting
in I'm coming okay come back we're
[Music]
waiting let me
in oh oop
[Music]
okay there we
go wait isn't there isn't the raid
starting like really soon no I think we
have one more day 28 2 at 10 p.m. so
it's the divisible by seven so yeah but
one thing in order for the modes to
really be useful for us we have to kind
of stand behind the modes so I know
fauna you like to really go out there
I'm going out there I'm really strong I
fought a
bear all on my own she's confident she's
I'm conf yeah okay I'll stay behind and
then try to shoot them while standing
yeah we we'll cover we'll cover your
backside
okay where's my
bike where did my bike
go
oh I'm poor pigs maybe it was a
mirage my bike was a mirage it's gone oh
P we didn't take it did we no that was
mine this is weird are you girls on two
separate bikes right now or no just
just shouldn't it show up up
[Music]
there that's so weird I guess I got to
walk home and pick up another bike oh no
wait you don't see the icon anywhere no
oh that's
weird uhoh weird things are a foot today
yeah mhm oh
conspiracy well there was another there
was another yellow bike uh at the at the
mini bike at the at the house yeah I
think the yellow one is our FAA wa
bike h
yeah I know I was driving there
but I wonder if something happened while
you
DC uh well chat is saying I should still
walk towards where I like got kicked out
of the game maybe the bike is there even
though it doesn't show up on my might be
there navigation
okay also so F you weren't there but I'm
going to try before the raid to get biu
better armor
and if you have some really lowle Parts
ideally I'd want to improve your armor
too the
only head are level one okay that's yeah
we'll improve that for sure especially
if you're going to go to the front
lines I'm strong though as long as I
have beer to drink that's all I need
just give it the beer she'll be fine
junken fist all the way exactly it gives
me 300%
power damn and you have that perk that
negates the effect right that's
crazy
by why doesn't it show it on the on the
big
map I put a lot of resources into that
bike why does the map not show it yeah
so
rude I think I was already kind
of in this
area like in
between oh oh zombie
hello it was on the
road I was what do you mean it was on
the
road was I following this I wasn't
following a road I was just going
through here
[Music]
right
you okay I'll go back and look around
you want to go to the house across the
street fin yeah and resty okay let's
go I think I I killed the boes in here
too yesterday
ah ah you girls are in the party right
now oh we are let me add you you you uh
left when you disconnected
[Music]
okay
okay lots of corn seeds
on I feel like potatoes are better but
you can make steak and potatoes yeah I
saw the the stack looks so good maybe
instantly
hungry I know I feel like we go through
the food so
fast I really want to level up enough
that I can make the Sham
stew can have
infinite shams
do it's not here why would it be here
chat are you one guying me not the one
[Music]
guy I'm so slow my
stamina I mean it won't re uh despawn
right so maybe just for now I'll go get
the the other bike you could put a
marker on your map where it where it was
so you can come back later
yeah not sure where it really was but
yeah I know the rough
area okay I'm going to walk back and get
the other bike okay okay unless I
accidentally find the other
bike stamina I wants more
stamina it doesn't despawn
okay yeah I was near to Burnt
Forest oh well well we'll find it one
day yeah yeah one day you'll just be
traveling the road and boom there it
is hopefully hopefully cuz it was going
to be someone else's
bike um by the way generally what I
think we should collect before the raid
is uh ammo and maybe more repair kits
yeah I'm going to spam while you guys
fortify or something I'm going to spam
quest for ammo for all for all of us and
ammo parts so I can make ammo Parts yeah
yeah yeah and also uh we were thinking
in my chat before we started today uh it
might be good to make turrets and I
think people weren't you kind of like
starting to learn that stuff no I'm
explosive I I'm learning turrets but I'm
really far off I think is that robotics
I think it is
robotics yeah I need 51 and I'm at
16 oh okay oh wait where am I going I'm
going to go towards your girls now okay
my quest is up on me to at the quest
Point coming
okay so maybe no turrets this time then
unless we find a lot more magazines I
have I have explosives though so that
will help yeah indeed okay I have fists
so yeah that'll help
definitely we'll see oh are we
doing oh bores and bears bors Bob's bors
yeah oh fight the again ah speaking of
fighting FAA
there you go I got these for
you
okay is is it is the starting point
okay oh we got to go we got to go to the
library before the rage
FAA the library yeah Library mhm wait
did you find a new one no the one that
you found oh okay we can go I think I
got well I don't know how much do it
take to
respawn probably long maybe after the
raida after the raid yeah probably wait
is it over here hop the
fence I can't hop that fence oh you
can't but it's so
easy I'm I'm tky
okay ready I've got ammo for both of you
oh o
thank you nerd
boots any wants nerd boots let me see if
they're better um no they're not better
I'll drop
them we could bring him home and then
give them to someone else like if
somebody joins us tomorrow also without
armor okay play here we go play oh the
piggies oh
no the poor
pigs do we need more meat should we get
their meats well always always have more
meat
handy okay I'm going to get the meat and
the lever oh a
lever there's a lot of corpses
in
here make cows fat again cattle
feed why is this going so
slow
oh hello piggy I'm
sorry are you already upstairs I am in
the
middle or pigs
piggy defenseless
pigs oh hello
sir it's so dark but it's like not dark
enough that I want to activate my knife
Vision your night vision oh night vision
is actually really nice here I've been
using
it yeah it's all right I just don't like
the oval
shape
ah bothers me I want to see the whole
screen oh wait with my fire it's not too
bad
yeah oh yeah remember curtains and stuff
curtains and
toilets every
is
important mattresses I
suppose sideways egg Vision it do be egg
Vision
huh oh wait we have to look for supplies
too yeah oh I see
realize ah chemistry session did
somebody open it up and was some
something inside or what was inside I
don't
remember I heard that the chemistry
stations they sometimes have a really
valuable item I think it was like acid
or so oh should I wrench it okay let's
wrench
it
okay ooh steel and forged ingots good
good okay
okay oh okay
okay I can't find my
thing is it upstairs perhaps it might be
mine I think is on the third
floor oh no it says it's
down oh I wonder if it's like where the
where Grace is Grace is at the bo yeah
that's the big Bo no will they force us
to go
there don't they know it's easy ah you
want to go there anyway huh yeah we got
this she wants to test her fist I
already killed the boar One V one
wow it's easy we've grown so much
yeah ooh
ooh
W what is this more
boys be boo good
job is it through the wall I feel bad
they run away from me I
know it's sad but we need the food I
guess
oh there is another
room I think my Satchel is in
there I haven't really paid attention to
mine um it's probably not there but I'm
going to take your
path it was an unlocked
door maybe we could have come here
without breaking the
walls
maybe maybe it's on the
[Music]
Roof oh mine's here I missed it hear
hiss where is he
and they oh they
there
oh maybe we yeah maybe we have to go to
Grace because yeah mine's like
farly I'm too stupid to figure these out
where is mine does it show on the big
map um no oh is it the red dots no those
are the zombies
it's probably in the basement
huh yeah I see my compass but do you
really think I understand that when it's
moving so fast does it have an arrow at
the top or
bottom
uh ah bottom and it's below you oh I
didn't realize there was an arrow
there yes oh another chemistry station
oh the super corn super corn yeah the
super corn is
back who's there I hear hissing but I
don't see that oh yeah they're down with
[Music]
me I'm busy can you guys leave me
alone stay down oh this is that type of
puzzle that I
hate there's a puzzle puzzle that you
hate it's a a light
puzzle a light puzzle you the puzzles
where you push something and then like
the two buttons next to it oh I love
those you love those I love those I hate
those I'm so bad at
them okay how to get down fa can you
show me how to get down uh down
yeah I'm not sure we can we can look
around I only know how to get to Grace
from the outside father come back where
to where you just uh the stairs look at
this did just see this
picture oh my gosh the cat is photo
bombing the
dog cute so cute that's a good one yeah
a good one I think so too 10 of a 10 I
like this picture can relate yeah can
you get the gra from here like this
house well we can go from the outside we
know where the exit was yeah I think it
might be locked
though yeah it's locked oh it's locked
from the outside
yeah okay wait oh wait um okay oh what
if I just dig down ah
you surprised me I'm just going to maybe
dig down from
here oh yeah my statul is right there oh
on the
ground oh
easy ah wait
spikes wait is it this way oh but it's
locked I think it's oh it is it is on
this
level oh metal Spike
welcome I'm just breaking the walls
there's no point putting a metal gate if
your walls are going to be so
flimsy this one isn't that flimsy
oh I don't think I'll get through it
what what about just next it just goes
over
here
oh ow spikes oh wait there's oh those
are spikes
yeah when the door is too much to get
through just break the wall that's right
next to
it let's are you guys going down oh yeah
wait there's spikes that's scary yeah I
fell into one it
[Music]
hurted hi almost there almost there my S
definitely
there come
on I'm out of stamina
[Music]
ow oh the stairs are
here ah did you find
it was easier like this for
me can't orientate myself we're just
going to BR force it okay yeah I found
mine I found
it mine should be I don't know where am
I oh oh that was mine too okay I'm done
oh really yeah we still clear the right
right oh does that include the bo
there's a there's a orange dot that says
to the distance that says below so I'm
assuming that's it we can take her oh
there's a there's a oh there's a thing
here oh yeah yeah yeah yeah we went
there
before that's where you get to the boore
[Music]
oh it's kind of crazy in
here oh yeah yeah ammo
[Music]
fertilizer oh
nice okay I want to eat some more food
you need food I have
[Music]
food I'll survive a while longer ah I
see her I won't engage yet I'll let the
Tank come tank I'm really slow right now
I'm very
cucumber
uhoh can't run away from the hold on let
me sneak attack her once since she's
asleep okay I'll get the bonus for
[Music]
that okay never mind she woke up she
woke
up she already dead no yet oh ceiling
board yay
easy easy
easy what's inside some knife books some
armor part oh you guys look at this m
I'm full uh I will take the ammo I will
take knife that's so different from
before from the first try oh we're
strong have faith biker outfit I might
take that it's medium
armor okay here you go there's some more
for
you oh yeah okay
nice well then I'm already cucumber uh
me too we should go and drop stuff off
yeah and maybe just one more Quest and
then I'll go prepare armor and stuff
yeah I guess we should reinforce the
base yeah maybe make a few more modes if
possible
POS let's get out of
here yeah we could go to the bookstore I
feel like I got a lot of the books
though I mean maybe there's more in like
a basement or something but it's pretty
far away is the
thing
true feel like that might lose us a lot
of time yeah
and I the better sh if we go like after
the raid everything will
respawn I'm so slow let's
go oh shamway foods and Savage country
seed chipping
grave come on lockpick do your stuff
let's see
o does somebody want to take these
things in the weapon
bag it's a scope and Knuckles
mod oh I want the knuckles I thought so
five do you want night vision yes okay
here you
go thank
you what's this polymer stram oh I can
only have one
my my water you're GNA just switch them
out you know combat use night
[Music]
vision how do you use the night vision
F
oh
cool thank
[Music]
you oh CH is it better than one of these
worth
replacing
[Music]
oh let's look at it later chat okay
shall we can we go to the the one that
Wawa had uh okay it's a little bit can
we drop stuff off at home yes yes it's
it's kind of on the we can stop there
for
sure okay where was the bike there
okay I'm so
full it's okay we have mini
bikes and they don't take stamina can
you drive the bike over to me and pick
me up I'm driving
it hold on I'm coming
mama he e go thank
you this door is a
little
thin
narrow we'll get through it there we
go okay I'm heading ahead for you we're
going home
first the Nerds the Nerds
I'm no longer nerdy my ex oh no she
outre us she's what level what level are
you
anyway
I'm wait where do you see that again 28
28 okay yeah I'm 26 oh bio's 29 wow I've
been killing
things uh oh yeah came
for dropping
off oh I got so much meat from the
pigs I
know me
[Music]
too okay maybe some
stuff what's this forth bites damage
mitigation mitigation does that mean I
get less damage yes potentially yes Fort
bite Fort bite fortnite
fortnite I think I'll use one of these
for the hard
[Music]
night Sharp oh maybe I should make a
repair
kit there there's a lot in one of the
chests there's like s are there yeah and
maybe I don't need to make one then
okay I'm ready I think to go to the next
one
okay
[Music]
okay can I use this guys to like wrench
the electrical
things seems like I might be able to
[Music]
why is this stuff in here
anym oh we have an armor chest oops I
was yes I'm not or we oh we have it's
new might not remember it cuz it's new
it's
for what uh connecting traps and turrets
to power sources if this this bottom uh
storage crate FL there's six repair kits
if you need one oh I was just going to
bring some in case I think one is enough
for me for now
same or
two m m m
where do the bones
go the ingredients chest oh
okay
okay connect lights power door okay for
now then I don't think we need
that can I wrench this
yes
oh some of the crops grew
FAA farmer is back farmer FAA farmer FAA
not much but it's honest
work I have just sold our microwave in
our um fridge online
secondhand we have no more of
that I'm sure we'll be fine without yeah
oh man no we're spending hours in front
of the microwave watching it turn my
favorite pastime it wasn't working
anyway I think we're ready I'm ready I'm
ready
F get on my bike okay you must are we
going to the tier 2 infestation one yes
it's a bit far but I want to get that
out of my system
let's go
Road you still have tier one clears too
oh when will we get to those
funny maybe once when you're really
bored for some reason and rather do a
tier one quest which will never happen
o oh we're so
fast I love not having to drive
I can just look at my inventory and
should I start an Uber business you
should what is that what do they call
your a passenger princess I
am oh sorry
oops you can stay on the bike even if I
got off interesting oh am I on the bike
yeah you on I got off by
accident uh I hope this road will lead
us
there surely
[Music]
M oh yeah we're
close I love how my arms are around your
waste it's
ticklish she's tickling me I
can't can't can't drive like that stop
tickling me f where are wait actually
this is not a good
path oh this this is not the place oh
yeah this kind of a dead end uh H the
road ends here maybe we just power up
the
hill I'm doing it I'm powering up the
hill
oh oh okay I'll try to from here might
be
good do your
best come on come on it's
working the are going to catch up come
on come on oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah oh
you're also
there oh
no catch up we're vertical it's working
can't you push us it worked just just uh
just trying really just could pick up my
bike for a few meters I'm pushing get
back on get back on it's time to go down
oh oh gosh it's like a roll roller
coaster oh ow I'm hurt that's
fine all right four shadowing I'm a
little scared I'll be careful I I'll get
go I'll go off the gas now and I'll just
let it
[Music]
okay come on come on come on come on
come on come on come on back
up all right I feel like my game wants
to crash so bad
oh no it wants you to crash with the
bike or the game itself no I feel like
the game itself wants to crash so bad
cuz we're doing illegal physics things
okay I made it wo this is
spooky Oo we made it too
oh have we been here spooky yeah does he
have any
resources he does I can make some sham
out of
this oh this guy too
well let me just get this car wrenched
and
then we can
start yum yummy car materials Yum Yum
Yum
yippee my inventory is already filling
up oh I've got I brought a lot of food
just in case let's go
o what do we have
here
no
oh
oh oh feel like I can get metal from
this
too a doke yeah can we have it oh it's
destroyed this is destroyed oh watch out
behind you oh there's a lot watch out
watch
out oh nice
it oh oh oh w
w put stuff in mini bike oh the mini
bike has storage
huh does it have a big
trunk maybe just a small one but better
than nothing
yeah what is my holy hammer called I
should give it a name huh I I still name
it watch out
easy my
beloved radio station woohoo radio
station oh the keys are here keys keys
we found I've never found keys in any
before no I didn't know they were actual
keys but makes sense
I'm rarely fighting in these quests it
seems I'm always wrenching things oh
there's an Air drw Supply drw will this
hurt me
no it's kind of
far they usually hang on the wall oh 400
m there's a a roof yeah there's it
upstairs there's a
l nope hey he jumped right on to you
nope
nope you guys are so
funny zombies scare me no
more spooky at
all oh did we finish it yeah oh we did
feel like there's more to explore and
more to oh I got armor crafting kit oh
good oh I think I'm done with that level
maximum level so you can use that oh no
the armor crafting kit the ones that
make armor yeah let's go oh here's
here's some ammo for you and I'm going
to drop the armor C in kid you can hold
on to them oh there's ammo for both of
you in there woo invested
cash invested cash in here too ammo pile
clean my cash thank
you clear out your
cash
okay I guess if there's nothing else
interesting we could go
[Music]
pumpkin pumpkin what the katana the C
mentioned Katana Katana
Katana Katana oh that thing the tempered
blade schematic
oh increases block
damage do the keys work only for one
specific door for every I think it's
specific door cuz I had I found the key
in the board house and it opened the
board cage so I think it it's
specific
okay oh do you want to get the air drop
where is it yeah we should it's not too
far right oh I don't know if they're
even
good I think I will go back home and see
what I can start crafting okay you guys
can go home I'll just go grab it real
fast okay
okay actually first I'll go to the
trader but F we can go together okay the
trader you want to still like get some
stuff
or uh what do you mean like from here
wrench wrench
stuff maybe this
my
tires I mean right now I don't think I'm
like I don't need it that urgently
oopsie uh tires I think yeah they can be
crafted can I get it like
this no I just got some scraps what
World level are
we oh oh Som how far oh you're 93 how
did you're 95 how did we I feel like it
went way up I feel like the last time I
it was I think it also depends on Armor
maybe cuz you guys are wearing like high
level armor or something or maybe it's
skill what's what's mine you're 91 f is
93 I'm 66 no you're 95 oh I'm 95 on my
screen you're 95 oh on my screen it's 66
so I thought it would be an armor
[Music]
but oh what that wrong way wrong
way oh it depends on the
biome it interesting I don't I don't
even know what that means at
all me
neither we're just living our best life
yeah does that mean the raid will be
easier if we go back to the starting
location maybe oh the supply quate game
me a bunch of books okay oh nice books
oh what kind of books I'll bring them
home any workstation let me
see any bar brawler level five
no Barbara traps and
B my German brain rot
yeah you know that song it was on Tik
Tok saw it it
was yeah you did you know that was
German yeah the the whole song I mean
yeah the whole song I trying to learn it
you should learn it so difficult you
should do the dance
too I want to
see wait oh is this Quest from Trader
Jen I think any any MPC can finish the
class
right or do you have to go
back yeah I think I have to go to both
according to yeah I think we have one
and and one and Jen o okay I'll try to
be fast well we can check see if they've
got anything good for sale although I'm
kind of broke right
now yeah I see you have to go back to J
okay okay oh but yeah speaking of Tik
Tok people I made a Tik Tok yay Tik Tok
to you should follow my Tik Tok I follow
do I even have a Tik Tok on mine yet I
don't think so maybe I should make
one if F you you you use Tik Tok no I
look at YouTube shorts sometimes but you
YouTube shorts is literally Tik Tok but
a few weeks late like everything you see
on YouTube shorts is just out put that
was reposted from there but late so you
guys are late to the trends I'm fine
with that I tried to watch Minecraft
Parkour civilization and I felt like I
was losing BS and then my bones were
turning to dust I to love 8,000 years
old she was like live tweeting it last
night when she
was who was streaming it I was was live
creating she was watching the parkour
civilization the movie will state your
business fool oh Iris I don't get it is
it how what level of irony are we on
when we say that we like Minecraft
Parkour
civilization do we like it ironically or
unironically we like it
unironically
yeah is that like a level one un ironic
or like a level three ironic oh c I
don't know can you be my
GPS um oh I got I got a motor motorcycle
part
bundle no no sorry wait yeah
yeah I wish I could have the map open
while riding icon on my map is like
backwards it's like facing the opposite
way that you're going
confusing but yeah everybody who has Tik
Tok please follow takanasi yeah follow
takanasi Ki she's got some cool dance
things up thank you yeah thank you
people do you think a lot of your
viewers are are like Tik Tok users I
don't know they always seem really mad
when I mention it oh no
same I'm personally not a big fan of
alling no no heck no no be no no no I
see
uh
oh absolutely not I feel like some of
them are lying though just to sa
face there's nothing to also I got I got
a my
motorcycle parts box from the CL what's
it going to be huh
oh well how about oh I led up right out
of my store
yippee do she's
have you read urban combat volume 6
fa um let me see cuz this one says armor
doesn't slow you down when in combat and
that might be good for you that okay
I'll use it then yeah I
[Music]
have your how much money do you have
1,000 no 2,000
can you buy the
remaining uh duct tapes that she's
selling why we have duct tape at
home but not enough we always need more
we can make more we should instead buy
do collector Parts if she has it then we
can make even more duct
tape duct tape at home how much duct
tape do we have at home we don't have
that much duct tape more duct tape yeah
we have so many we have we have bones
and we have so many bones in water so we
can make glue yes yeah it's better to
buy the do collector parts so that we
can does she have them yes she does do
you want me to
get a dual collector part oh water
filter is is 7,000
yeah okay good though I'm going to get
the The Gatherer at
least okay
our first uh and I'll get I'm going to
buy tarp our first quarrel between wives
about how to spend our money we have we
have duct tape at home mom D duct tape
at
home low
quantity we'll make more if we it's we
need to invest our money instead of
spending it as soon as we get it don't
fight in front of your child I'm going
to get traumatized
[Applause]
she doesn't she doesn't understand
because she's not in my position I don't
I need much more duct tape than she
knows she doesn't
realize just we'll be fine just wait one
day we'll have so much duct tape
hopefully who is this Kiki I literally
just saw her spawn in front of
me
G G my third parent is here
here I'm eating right we Jo call off
okay where's my
bike over there we're going to wait
don't leave I don't have a car yeah yeah
I'm just trying to find my bike and then
we can go to the other Trader wait did I
sell
something
no wait did I sell
something I sold the magazine back oh oh
my
gosh I TR oh
no oh my gosh she scammed
me I got so distracted wait did you sell
something you weren't supposed to yeah I
bought a magazine and then I tried to
use it from my inventory but that just
sold it back to her
no did did was it was it Den did you
just you distracted by you know was
distracting I see
it's okay it happens to the best of
us oh no is gig going to be left here
yes yes no that's what she gets for
leaving us behind
yesterday she has to walk does she even
have a bike she doesn't even have her
bike doesn't CeCe have her bike what is
this ra kill these zombies yeah what is
this
ra action
baby out of stamina already okay
Bonk oh I got I got armor piercing kiaha
bullets I'm going to put it in the
weapon and ammo it's armor piercing
can you use those with any uh uh machine
gun or does the machine gun any seven 62
it's just different type of bullets so
you should be able to use it oh
[Music]
okay well that was easy that was
easy I think we got this yeah tonight
well actually soon wait what day is it
wait we have one more day we have one
day oh spam quest for
bullet okay we're going to go through
the village here but we're not stopping
for your quest F
now that's fine or should we no we don't
have time it's almost the end of
today we really got to get
[Music]
home we got to make more
modes oh no
oh should check out if the mailbox is
refreshed could it be could it be or is
it too
early they're empty a maybe after the
raid
okay you
need F you you answer I need to control
the bike sorry I was in
my my
thing wa what resources do we need uh
maybe iron
oh duct
tape du tape at home and and suing kids
so but that's just randomly in the house
I I think more cloth would be
useful cloth is like I feel have a good
amount now well we always need more and
also cloth is helpful for explosives too
so can always use more
more Mo molds at the base so that they
fall in so a good
shovel yeah I wonder if you can make
iron or is it iron or
steel
um wait I'm starving um I think food
don't star it's okay driving first so
much food
driving comes
first has level so she should good I'm
going to make some B good water since we
have a lot of water now too oh yeah
please
please are you where are you bo boo I'm
at the house oh we should save some
water for glue though yeah I won't do
too
many see we have to share the water for
different things fa that's that's why we
need the water upgrade part I I put more
water I put I put a water upgrade part
in the in one of the things so one of
them has some upgrad I'm going to make a
third one okay a third do collector
mhm okay you're getting off you don't
want to give the quest back oh I guess I
do it's dangerous to get off while I'm
high speeded driving funo you're right
you're right my server lagged a little
bit it looked like you were slowing down
no no oh we don't have
qu are they the yellow ones or the red
ones the red ones we need more red ones
for me to make
the
oh I can get a bunch
okay make sure to crch
cars I
uh here we
are wrecked we are so
back can you welcome us back friendly
we're still coming back to you even even
after we have other Traders yeah I think
he'll still be
[Music]
mean I don't know about these
rewards could give these two oh
I have collected 56 chrysanthemums oh
that's
useful what's
chrysanthemums it's a flower
yeah I'm very
slow oh wrong
spending all my
money not on duct tape I
hope no no he didn't he didn't have any
duct tape
sadly food please
funa
yes take take this pumpkin
[Music]
pie
pie pie
I don't need this I want like to confess
something I actually don't like pumpkin
pie really yeah it's so good I prefer
like
apple Apple's good
too yeah me too weoo have you R pistol
peed Volume 2 um where do I check your
inventory in the books tab
[Music]
inventory definitely that
way I think I never had pumpkin pie IRL
before we never mhm we should try
it I'm not too I'm not too big
on pump the pumpkin spice I'm not a
pumpkin spice girly dang me neither
really I love
pumpkin Pistol Pete which one volume two
no I have not okay I'll get it for you I
didn't ditch father I'm just looking for
the other bike in the meantime oh you
can ditch me I can walk home it's
fine I want
tarp but I can't afford it I my money
gone maybe they my money glitched out my
bike out of this
world they won't give it back to me hobo
stew hobo
stew yum yum I what that
is oh no I should have bought beer wait
I can still buy one beer it shows my
bicycle on the compass but it doesn't
show the other the
bike
rude very
rude are you still at the tra
I'm done okay I might pick you up
now I'm just going to be punching
flowers okay wait I want to Ranch car
really
quick no problem oh no ah my game
crashed I think that was just a crash
not the internet okay that's good it was
just there oh my I passed my bike oh
really they don't want to have the
bite game Bo are you doing this to
me okay
well I'll be
back in a moment I'm going to get that
bike actually F do you see the you don't
see the bike on the map do you the one
we were driving around with wow I didn't
think you had it in here Yay good job
don't think I see anything okay okay no
problem I think I see my old bike my
regular
[Music]
bicycle nope still no imps here okay
okay game is opening up
got a lot of
stuff I'm going to make so much duct
tape Dan has three books of serious fist
by the way that's I tried to buy one and
I accidentally sold it back to her oh no
oh that's a big loss of money huh I know
she sold it for me to me for 300 and
bought it back for 20 don't let her her
good looks and charm fool you she as
ruthless as all the rest of the
trainers is it possible to like K Ju
Just in theory is it possible to kill
the
traitors I wonder cuz they have like a
skull rating right ooh the last boss are
the traitors Maybe maybe when when we're
done with the tomorrow we can
check that's scary
though I don't want to ruin our whole
game what if we can't go back anymore
because we've ruined it killing the
traitor
true okay hey can I get a party invite
oh yes
where did you guys see
it the bike was here stuff need a little
fix me up we have so many
bones do we have gas cans at
home I think uh
uh maybe I think we out of them because
I filled all the bikes up as much as I
could I have eight of them I found the
bike oh
good oh it's not bad okay trust me I'm a
doctor you're never leaving me
again it's weird that the icon didn't
show up you yeah don't know
why okay I'm coming home
preparation time uh oh we really only
have like one day left yeah 24 hours I I
can just punch them
anyway I'll just I'll make you better
armor what should I prioritize uh your
gloves right
f um no no no I have good gloves it's
mine oh my hat in my chest ah your hat
in your chest and you want the same set
I would assume right yes okay and then
for Bio I wanted to first of all make
gloves preacher gloves I think yes
please
okay well I I'm I'm going to go get
cooking going to go
cooking let her
cook okay we do have a bit of cloth
now oh me too me too I I think clo is
like okay now in terms of yeah ever
since we started destroying everyone's
curtains
yeah g
g uh what was it what was it preacher
gloves preacher gloves maybe I level
my delicate hands full of
knives oh despite all the Ping they're
still super smooth and non- callous yes
I don't know how you do it what
moisturizer do you
use I'm in moisturizer
what was for an infect infections what
was honey honey and antibiotics there's
antibiotics at the house and
honey should honey only work uh for a
specific percentage 5% honey Works 5% at
a
time awesome so it'll still work if
you're high percent it just takes away
5% at a time
okay I need to ask gigy to gy are you
coming to thec
[Music]
soon he's num
noming I want to num nom too
okay maybe I can make a Max
Level maybe I should be it not careful U
do I have to run all the way to the pond
drink can I just drink water at yeah
just drink
one expensive though I could just go to
the pond and
drink I don't know you you've been
working hard to get us water I feel like
you deserve a nice sip
sip without making too our time is
precious okay every second wasted is a
second closer to the horde so don't
waste your
time so what about the duct tipe do we
have more duct tape at
home definitely we can yeah I would
appreciate a couple more duct
tapes I'm on
it wait I can make a couple too just
threee yeah if we have more glue I can
do we have more
glue we can make glue we can make glue
with the water just
no how much water do we have I'll make
glue
okay I need to save some water make
food here I'm putting another de
collector out
H guys what level should I make it in
cuz it already takes even on level five
it takes five armor crafting
kits oh my internet died oh no oh no but
I didn't get kicked oh
interesting oh we're back okay that was
just a short Maybe YouTube issue or OBS
only
okay perhaps
I'll make I'll make I'll
make I'm going to let zombies kill me
don't be alarmed I want to be full
health for my
quest
okay more sewing
kits
Dam um what was that uh fun you said hat
and
shoes no hat and chest
okay I'll just I'll just make the
maximum now
or yeah with the
materials oh I'm still infected wow
okay second to last it doesn't matter
we're going to do this again
sometime and then I have to continue
with the stuff I
have yeah the steel steel I even bought
extra Steel
okay uh but then I probably can't make a
new I'm out of
armor oh well for
now I don't need to make I have so many
corn seeds already
[Music]
I can't make beer for a long time cuz I
need the chemistry station or something
oh really it's going to be expensive
yeah but that's okay I have I have
enough for now
yes look at
this I'm out of armor kits
now thank you for it's maximum
level so that should help I don't think
I can improve your helmet uh but that's
okay
yeah and then I got the gloves well
thank
you let me know when you're home B boo
okay I'm just doing one
Quest h
my own armor is okay it's okay oh I
can't make potato seeds
yet I could make a few more
armor she has duct
tape for one
wow duct
tape oh the shovels are
expensive I can't too stupid to Ty I
can't
typ I pressed some weird stuff
again oh okay is do really
good I don't know what's it made out of
you don't want to know don't ask
questions you don't want to know the
answer
to it's the healthiest ingredients for
sure um what's that sound whoo whoo whoo
whoo oh oh was that a
tree I put some glue in your
chest oh a little thank you and
cloth glue
glue free glue how much I can make free
duct tape with free
glue um
oh um everything needs water of course
oh but I'm lacking seing kits
now and seing kits we can't make
[Music]
ourselves if only I had more sewing kids
maybe the old house still has some seing
kits oh can we not craft
those no I guess
not
ah
yeah
there's some nice minor boots and gloves
for you in the armor
chest in new
house I think cuz
her her equipment is probably also not
the best so that
should I mean it's for mining but it's
um decent better than
nothing the nerd boots look
funny okay I'm going to check out the
old
house okay
okay and pray
for suing
kits they will always be rare items R
Savage country house cuz they usually
got py yeah I did get a few ones from
the one
house oh wa I'm going the wrong
way actually maybe I'll check over
here I'm going to go raid a
house okay good
luck thank you you got it I need that
I'm scared don't be scared you're
strong I don't know you're
brave
okay I believe in you in your words they
better be true if I die then I will
cry yes I got gim and my machine
gun it's just with
gimly it's taking up my stamina so fast
that's kind of bad so I'll use my
machine gun I love how you call it
gim
yeah best dwarf
ever oh oh this doesn't really look like
it would have seen
kids face the Bears D free I don't like
that advertisement hi hi
hello how is your
meal yummy hard to play and eat though
don't get don't get crumbs on your
keyboard what are you doing the ants the
ants I'm summoning them
no please ants come eat my
keyboard it's not the place I was
thinking
[Music]
of are we going to be fortifying today
yeah well a little
bit uh the thing is like spikes might
not be so useful anymore because we're
going to get probably more of the vomit
guys now and they destroy the spikes
easily um so rather than that I was
thinking our strategy should be modes so
that they fall into the holes they fall
into those pretty easily and they don't
seem to be able to get out of them so we
just got to lead them into the I'm
thinking we should do spikes yeah spikes
in the modes best
Strat um so yeah we already have some
modes but maybe adding another row would
or like filling up the areas where
there's no modes
okay okay I'm going to see around
here maybe this one
leting e fa what's your experience with
two two skulls houses
easy easy do you need help though I can
help no I'll be
fine I've got someone blue for you
that's
nice that much
H better than nothing
yeah
wow
nice G are you streaming no I'm just
here mhm take for a good time hitting
trees nothing else just
chill I can't use any of these bicycles
I can't unlock
them and the bicycles or the
bikes none of them none of them not a
single one but I unlocked them maybe I
have to unlock them every time the
bicycles yeah
bicycle I think they auto lock because I
had to unlock mine when I didn't
before swing kids swing
kids um uh I'll unlock it for you when
I'm back can you think
mine oh my God thank you for letting me
use your bike it's so
green she has ve so such little quality
on her is she
okay do you want a repair kit I'm scared
of hurting her even further I think we
should have repair kid
somewhere I saw you I see one I'll
repair her I'll go fix her right up she
can fix her her I'll fix
her that's so nice of you to return my
bike with a full tank of
gas I did press all by myself I feel so
powerful I knew she was alive just
sleeping but I had a
feeling yeah head shots definitely make
things easier
microwave okay I mean we're we're
cooking we're cooking I got cooking
magazines I really want to get to the
Sham stew Shams
still sounds
delici I think I'm far though am I far
wait fish
tacos oh my God fish tacos I can't make
them yet maybe someday you wanted you
wanted sewing kits right yeah okay I'll
bring
[Music]
them why is so noise oh dog no not dog
you sounded like a
dog spicy
okay I'm gaining
confidence good you should be confident
yeah thank you so synced up
girls so would you guys ever possibly
need like more
wood no I think we're for now H Maybe
you could make more spikes though with
the wood
um always good to make more spikes even
if they can be destroyed they will be a
line of defense yeah yeah yeah yeah this
stack oh and can I how come I can't use
armor plating
mods H they I've noticed that I cannot
use them on my chest but I can use them
on for example the feet I think oh
really
yeah damn oh I can't use them on either
oh they don't go on heavy armor what
works on heavy armor oh probably
different plating the heavy plating I
think there's particular plating for
it oh no can't put any armor mods onto
heavy maybe oh really oh maybe it's
already strong enough
without maybe that's the trade off
no I'm crafting 400 spikes don't worry
nice let's put them in that moat yeah
yeah yeah
yeah what is this
for I never know what any of the
modifiers are
for yeah me too oh I can do customized
spinning
[Music]
I think I'll go to the next
house find another sink kit
hopefully how many swing cats are you
girls carrying around have right now
okay o the hobo stew is good but what's
it made out of no don't worry about what
it's made of
what's inside our hobo can I have can I
have the nutritional facts please I'm
watching my
sodium um 2,000 MGR of sodium wow
per
yeah ooh machine gun parts
H I don't have any vehicles
to
use you can can you unlock the stuff at
home I'm a bit busy why are they locked
again I unlocked all of them
yesterday I think I think they auto lock
I think yeah okay I I I'll come home I'm
not that
far every time you pick one up or use
them they lock oh
oh ah so each time a different person
uses it it blocks for them I
guess
oh ah they belong to the person that
sets it down makes
sense I guess today uh we have enough
bikes for everybody to have their own
maybe fa can use the C bike or so the
golf bike okay golfa uses golf
bike makes sense is this one right
okay unlock try it thank you oh it has
like no fuel oh I can add some I think I
have some this person returned this car
with no
gas it has not that much fuel can you
unlock a bike I'll just take a bike
instead have I have more fuel I have
more fuel try to sa me save the
environment everyone I don't think the
environment needs to be saving there's
more we have to thank
you
dead yeah and we'll die next if we don't
save the
environment come
on what am I lacking
another couple of seing
kits I have two but I'm far away okay
well I'm slowly heading back yeah I'm
heading back now
okay yeah when should we start
fortifying maybe around early
afternoon okay
just put these in I have time
yeah to do stuff like kill bears
yeah beep those
Bears I guess I could go back to the
bookstore we could go after
though be good to find all the
bookstores I think they can be in in
many biomes
yeah they seem like a good find yeah
have you been in the biome with all the
special little things the special
zombies special zombies all the throwing
up zombies spawn much more frequently in
there yeah the desert the desert spawns
a lot of throwy upy ones if you want if
you want a real challenge fa go to go
north into the snow there's a lot
yeah that's where I was scary creatures
when I killed the bear that's where the
bookstore
is that was the Bear's bookstore well
it's my bookstore
now botar has has a magazine section
[Music]
now Finders
Keepers that bear was going after his
master and you just ruined his
education so be it
then okay I think I'll go back to the
house one more
time oh oh oh where are you guys
going is there a party that I was
invited to I'm just soloing some stuff
oh no no you zombies around our house or
oh walking around in the
group looking for something to raid it
seems maybe they're telling us that we
should
not be so easygoing the day has
arrived yeah they're kind of right they
are right it's the day the Dooms
day oh yeah let me unlock the other
bikes
okay o why am I why am I so slow okay oh
oh two Forge
heads should we have a
another mini
mic they're so loud these
zombies someone has to teach them
manners I know can't even get any peace
and quiet even when the zombie
apocalypse I thought that would help I
know
[Music]
ouch if you want uh there's
an unlocked bicycle or do you at least
have a bicycle I took faas she lent me
hers okay I thought I have another mini
bike
but I don't know where it
went but we do have some seat modifier
thingies on the on some of the mini
bikes so we can ride together
yay I they so cute I know I didn't
realize the mini bike had so much more
storage this is so good
really I got to check it out
too how about this house
or just going to raid one more house and
then I should maybe be able to
make a new armor oh yeah gigy how's uh
can you tell me what level your armor
pieces are um a bad feeling for yours I
took I have an Assassin outfit of level
one and cool sunglasses of level one but
I took the mining things that are level
four um wait do your chest piece is
level one yeah what are they going to do
kill me I'll make you a different Jess
um is there specific set you're
interested in no I'm just I like hitting
trees and and
Mining yeah but those things are outfits
you shouldn't really wear for fighting
but only particularly for the actions
that you're taking um so maybe I'll make
you I'll just make you the The Meta
chest trust
me that was easy
I am stu okay I'm ready for the hoorde
okay I put your gloves into the armor
chest B if you can just leave the sewing
kids somewhere yeah I'm coming home
right now the the the armor chest yeah
anywhere oh no you guys oh no are you
the zombies are no the zombies are not
okay they're stuck in the barbed
wire they're oh no they're lowering our
red get out of
there oh no I'm
fatig just take a
break
oh good job you made
it give me something
good Hi friend
come on down oo water's fine they work
out so we're building an even larger
moat I mean you don't have to go
overboard but just one more row of modes
would be cool maybe with spikes build
with spikes
Moes filled with
spikes got it oh I have tier four
now oh oh here they come dues huh you're
as Brave as a bigamist good
luck oh oh the next Traer is in the Ice
Area ooh yeah up
North I'm excited for that but I don't
know if we'll see that anymore I don't
know if we'll see it today but
yeah we need to play another week
right yeah I'd be up for that but a
little bit of a break would be nice I
want to play some different games too
that's true I've been itting to play
games but then I'm like this is too fun
as well I know I'm split
so true and like you get so committed to
it I think all of us are like super
committed to it so we want to show up
every day I'm
committed oh wait did I do it I think I
did it we are not scared of commitment I
feel like I have to do my
part yeah me too I
know isn't there loot in this house
somewhere apparently the Japanese girls
played until day 49 or so
but they didn't play in one go they they
had like several sessions of several
days so that's how they got so
far we should just continue at some
point are we are we was it going to do
it longer
tomorrow uh yeah we start uh 1 hour
earlier though uh if everybody's okay
with the CI already said okay y I'm
totally fine okay cool and then yeah
we'll just go however long I was
wondering how long it will be maybe like
5 6
[Music]
hours really depends when we end
today cuz our raid is
soon but we can still maybe yeah I want
to definitely end on a
hord okay today you mean oh I mean
tomorrow like because it we might need
depending on how we end today I don't
know how close will be to a
hoorde uh tomorrow but I definitely want
to end on the hord tomorrow cuz I think
that'd be like a nice
Bang Yeah agreed yeah I think that's why
we're playing like longer just to get to
a hoorde on the last day I think so no
sewing kids
why what is this house how are you going
to fix anything if you don't have sewing
kids at home
can't from
par I feel like I'm using so much
fuel it's bad for the environment you
got to
stop it really uses up a lot of
fuel I've been I've been ranching like
so many cars to get some more fuel but
it really is a little bit of a limited
resource so if we can
use bicycles more
often or car poool we can Carol yeah car
pool saves the environment exactly yeah
true we need the we need seed
modifications everything on everything
and I'll make a car as soon as I
can from four or maybe four
people want to be in a car so cute yeah
family road trip yeah
road trip to the infested bookstore
yeah and we stop at every bear we
see s k s k come on come on come
on oh but a nice
magazine thanks for the bus sorry people
how many s kits did you bring again
two oh she has Forge head book
oh do we still need that very much need
those are the workstation books I think
so oh Dan she does have them does she
also sell sewing
kits we have sewing kits at home no for
real don't I really need more if she
sells them please tell me we don't have
so kids at
home does she we could
though she does I'll buy some please
thank you thank you how many does you
have two okay please buy both I bought
both okay thank you I love you I'm
expecting somebody's going to have to
Fork up the money for the water
purifiers
though much just a waterproof I I'll buy
it remember remember how much money I
invested in making everybody mini bikes
and stuff where the gratitude for
[Applause]
that youing on to my home which water
thing do you want me to buy I'll buy it
um I what do we need I think we need
water
filters I think I can buy a
gatherer wait no I need to save money
for
beer I have $9,000 on me if someone come
to me wow in
my in my
trenches oh water filter is to
much The
Gather oh The Gatherer let me see do we
need the gatherer still we have the tarp
I can't remember if I bought the tarp or
The Gatherer I bought the Ice Cube I
think we need the gatherer we need
another Ice Cube we need another one I
already bought one well we made a new
water
purifier okay I'll buy one more gatherer
there go thanks for letting me take care
of you thank you sure to tell your
[Music]
friends thinking about what will not
stack
probably
well whatever okay I'm coming home do
you want to ride home oh you have a bike
too never mind I do have one wait do you
want do you want to get on so you save
gas but then how are we going to get
this one back home you'll pick it up how
I walk
what what put it in your inventory here
before was I
oh first that's so
smart oh your bike is lock Oh see it
locks every
time
okay thank you
yeah I know how much you like being a
passenger princess I do I do
is it getting dark and scary
yes I have six Forge ah head magazines
yay what six for ah head oh my God
amazing you're so
lucky it's all skill no luck
100% skill I would say those magazines
are pretty
lucky and power will or whatever the
song
goes yeah exactly remember the name yes
fun something yeah
yeah why are they so rare
where are we where are we doing the
defense
at Old House
okay that's that spooked
me I just stepped on a zombie and it
woke
up no this game was a jump scare happy
Halloween happy Halloween
God my heart I'm
old can't take this
anymore okay we're
home
yay thanks for the ride yeah oh you did
make another one okay I'm going to put
the thing in here yes
boom making lots of food crch everything
I just want to I put the sewing kit in
the in the crate next to
thees I put the magazines in the
magazine
okay
D damn that other house gave me false
hope I have ammo too for yuk kiaha I put
in the ammo
crate thank you
we're so prepar short on ammo this
time bless you thank
you oh I have ammo for you bi boo I'm
drop it the crate is full think I'll be
fine with the
ammo last time I had to share this time
it's all mine all yours these zombies
we're going to kill them before daytime
again yeah
easy knocking on
wood wood
where that's your favorite word
huh where is it what no wonder you like
fauna so much she's literally a tree
pulls out my axe no not a tree I'm
this might be dangerous if gigy gets
drunk and cannot tell apart is
that is that why this happening why
that's why she punches you no yes it's
because I keep falling asleep I've never
been punched by gy that tells you
something yeah yeah sorry I have um I
have narpy oh wow that's not an
excuse that just fall as sleep and then
I imagine that I'm punching a tree and I
wake up and I'm hitting you I don't
needan
it
tough married life is tough huh we're
going through counseling it's
okay hey shouldn't I be there
too yeah but I I keep beating her I
don't know
how I'm going to be so traumatized when
I grow
up all right aren't you already a little
bit close your eyes I'm already I'm
already very murderous it's I get it
from my parents play play on your DS go
on go back to
bed sneak downstairs while you're
fighting by the staircase looking down
into the into the living room oh they're
fighting
again oh
no no don't fight
going back home
unsuccessfully I'm should I check one
last time in
[Music]
here
hello
hello mhy
M
zombies where are you
I feel like we're procrastinating again
on the hord no don't worry I'm working
really
hard you're going to be really impressed
when you get over here oh are you making
the modes and stuff yeah thank you nice
once again I don't have to do anything
in terms of
fortification leaving it to the others I
am the Gopher the goer I thought you
were a
beaver right now I'm digging through the
dirt do that doesn't that make you a
mole I'm little mole naked mole rat
cute oh why why is it empty was someone
here
recently o
what was someone in the what house is
this uh B bore barnfields recently
everything's empty yeah probably I mean
it doesn't have to be recently right
it's just yeah true yeah I can never
find any small
stones do we have them we should have a
lot I would feel like I can never find
them am I just
blind well you can always Farm them
outside hit some Stones dig for them or
do you have to just look for them no I
hit the stones yeah rocks five sewing
kid in her personal storage we
we be it'll be fine I'm taking those if
she's not showing up like two raids in a
row or so I'm taking
those she doesn't know how valuable they
are it's okay it's ours now yeah no I I
I think a lot of things in the storage
they might like not need anyway
so they're just putting that there for
safekeeping but we're one big team yeah
that's
right one dysfunctional family if she
does show up again I will make armor for
her so
exactly what comes around from you have
three armor crafting kits in your
storage yeah those are like you know I'm
gathering them for another piece of
armor for
G and for myself maybe we see how far we
get I'm just looking in
everybody's now Noy yeah is what is
going
[Music]
on
be interesting you're very buggy for me
very glitchy yeah her shoulders are like
off her shoulders you see it too
huh H is that better oh well you're
constantly in like a shooting and
walking
position um but yeah now the the should
yeah they're floating again looks
funny looks very
funny is hoing too I'm calling everyone
else wait no I'm I'm holding stuff for
my Magnum gun okay so that's why there's
tape in there that's the amount of tape
I need for my Magnum gun picking it to
everyone's inventory what the hell are
you doing with this
call from
us
unbelievable all I'm going to say is I
don't even have a personal
B
everyone oh we're getting close to the
raid so now everybody's like so tense
and everybody's fighting I don't like it
it's not good for my
development our child getting a
part-time job we're like oh you're not I
I'll keep a better job at your money
than you
will I made this money on my
own here let me put it in their bank
account for you but Mom I wanted to buy
a new game games you have to study no
how will you get to College like
this question uh the the
shieldy things that you found did you
are you still carrying them I put them
in the chest next to the forge okay
thank you I was able to make a couple
duct tapes
now
so I can make more armor crafting kits
oh oh I'm getting a good amount now
let's
go looking good oh I'm so hungry in the
firsty oh
God oh maybe it's time to eat my banana
banana banana wait don't eat the banana
put it in the chest eat it home you
ban ZL
oh I'm really going to eat
it I'm like I can make banana bread out
of that I don't even think there's
bananas in this
game if there are I'm sure I can make
[Music]
something
oh I could place the timed ch charges
into the into the Moes so they'll
explode in the mo o oh that might be do
you have to activate them I don't know
it says timed so maybe it just oh it's 4
seconds okay I drop it and then explos
in for
[Music]
second there's um 440 small stones in
this top chest FAA what I missed
it I'm just blind I went out and
collected
some too
bad 15 minutes before blood moon what
oh but the H will not come yet so oh
right um I think it starts at
22:00 yeah right yeah
22:00 10 p.m. yeah
F what did you drop off from
shieldy uh sewing kits
oh you don't have it anymore
right no I put it by the unless somebody
somebody took it mayy no I think I
already took it then you should do
another sweep of everyone's chest I
think I
will someone's hiding under their pillow
no is my game stashes there don't take
it away from me that's all I
have I remember grandma sent you some
money for your birthday you have
to fauna yes didn't you need bar brawler
magazines they in the chest oh I only
need volume
five
oh did anyone take the stack of forged
iron can I have like
25 oh um what
um let me see uhoh there's some people
outside oh
hello yay the party is starting
yeah I'll let you guys handle
that more
more okay I put some uh forged iron back
in the chest for you and I'm forging
some more you don't mean steel right you
mean just iron yeah just iron okay okay
that's good um so where making one Nomad
outfit for there more out there gy a yes
there oh there's a lot
oh oh are they going to try to come for
the back
again
maybe let me know if you need help I
think we got it what am I looking for oh
watch out Le it's pain being melee
okay I think we're
good
storage ah
more so nice when you forget you have so
many things in your
bike that will make you happy when you
see
them where do we have lever I know we
have lever somewhere oh I have it I'm
just going to make a thing real quick
and then put all the stuff back into the
chest
okay who's out
there oh the spikes hurt they can I
delete these spikes that are right
outside yeah please please do I think I
put those there you mean the one spike
in the back of the house that was me cuz
I was trying to achieve something I
see and I a che okay I'm putting all the
ingredients back
in the chest the leather's in there
thank you thank you so
[Music]
much all right then can we craft some
forged steel do we need more no we need
a crucible we don't have Crucible is 15K
we need yeah oh wait it's money yeah you
can buy well it's money or me crafting
it but until I can craft it I I still
need a few more workstation magazines oh
did you get the six give
15K did you get the six that are in the
magazine box I already read them I still
need
um 30 no four 40 more oh yeah I have
4K 40 more yeah 40 more books of
workstation but I can make a cement
mixer now which with that we could make
cement
walls and
fury but my next reward that I can uh
make is a chemistry station and then a
crucible so it's very far station's good
for me yeah it will be
good let me put that in
there
and
uh oh it's loading up slowly
okay car not enough steel so I
think I have to make a lower level
one which will be good
enough chemistry station will be great
to reduce material consumption okay
everyone donates you'll get to buy the C
yeah but I haven't seen a Trader selling
it yet maybe the one in the in the next
Zone will have it yeah probably like I
it wouldn't make sense for them to sell
it so early in the game when wa I can't
even like I'm way too far from crafting
it myself they probably want to balance
that out so that you don't get it too
early so yeah probably in the mountain
area there's a chance
Bob usually has it Bob really Bob gotta
check Bobby more often I think we could
farm that much money easily it might be
worth it yeah yeah the the higher the
tier Quest the more like Quest if we
have start getting like 2K ah 2K now and
stuff so doing do we have more water
because I feel like the the food chest
doesn't have any water right now um
there's some in the output let me put it
in oh okay I'm also cooking some uh good
water that's being cooked
currently I should keep
those hobos do also hydrates you a bit
oh really yeah this D has everything
yeah it's good uh gigy I have your uh
level five Nomad chest okay okay I'll
give it to you when I meet
you um thank you if I were to make one
more
thing what could I make but I'm I don't
have any more steel watch the time by
the
way it's 5:00 p.m. 5. yeah we still have
five ingame
hours wait GG do you have a wood
splitter Mod on your axe I do not wait
you oh you should have this let me bring
it to you thank you more damage to
wood can I just take this bike I don't
know who this is take it if you can ride
wait wait take take my bike if you want
since I have the which ones is yours
here pink it's locked okay it's unlocked
oh wait let me put this mini bike
back gy what's your hat again that
you're wearing cool sunglasses just
remind me that that wait where's your
bike by the way don't you get has my
bike oh
okay the we're just trading bikes
yeah ah people your preacher gloves are
still in the armor chest don't forget
about those okay thank you wait should
we bring food yes I think so
I'm going to head over to the new
house okay me too I'm going to come soon
I guess I'm I think I
done enough crap I got enough
ammo I got some well I made as much
armor as I could but with the lack of
Steel it's difficult to make more good
stuff so for
now maybe we're done I think we should
as a group try to get 15,000 I bet we
can yeah I have 4000 token on me Clos
right 9 10 11 12 13 we need 2K more
that's
it h 2K more yeah cuz she has 4K I have
9k or she has 9k I have 4K so we need
like
2K yeah I used up all my money yesterday
for something what did I buy something
really
expensive what was
that did I buy
no not just does anyone have bandages
okay maybe I did no we are yeah we need
bandages we don't have aloe is the
problem oh I guess it's in the desert
right dang it we have we have three aloe
in the inred you need four make one
bandid wow I have five Band-Aids I'll
bring those no it's okay you can you can
use them cuz you're going to be on the
field anyway I I just might have someone
kill me before the raid starts
okay I have to go to an idle meeting
I'll be right back and I'm going to go
to the new house okay have fun we're
back
okay
actually is this mine
[Music]
repair kits do we have repair kits yes
there's repair kits in
the thingy
thingy new house or old house new house
there's like in one of the unnamed
boxes oh oh
[Music]
okay ah it's all one no free
nice I'll just take all of them with me
for now we might need them
there make a better
Sledgehammer no it's fine do I have any
skill
points free okay
um oh I have four thank you for
reminding
[Laughter]
me
uh what's where should I I'd like more
stamina I was also working on something
previously was
I over
here stamina what was stamina again
stamina
[Music]
is it is
fortitude and it is Rule one
cardio m
a thank you
yeah then I need more in here I'm back
why is my bike on
fire uh you're on fire do do you see
this my bike is smoking uhoh is it okay
well maybe I should repair it better go
catch it it's only for
running oh yeah you want to do you want
to give me my bike back and then I'll
just drive you to the place oh
okay your bike's over here
can I just get more of these
points I'll just do you want it over
here I'll just put anywhere I'll just
pick it up okay I'll just put it over
here want be something like this oh can
you unlock my bike oh
yes weon skill thank you oh wait uh
where machine gun y you
ready yes we're going to need more of
these okay I think just North yeah just
North okay where then I would need skull
crusher to we're coming
D I'll focus on the gun anyway I can't
wait for you to see my work oh hold on I
have to take a tea break cuz I have I
have the no nose oh no what are you I
don't want I don't want to be stinky are
you eating sham sand I was eating sham
sandwiches I don't want any I took all
the food out of the
chest you want some steak and potatoes
it's okay I still have some I was just
trying to like clear out my inventory so
I was just eating whatever was in my
inventory we don't have to live like
that anymore
I wonder how long
this uh buff
stay let getting
spooky oh R R I feel like we're always
down to the Wi when we're running to the
new
house yeah I forgot I wanted to go into
the desert and punch aloe
I can get a t cuz I have the perk
now will this be able to go through the
river yeah okay wow
Easy E are you taking a minibike to dive
into the water yeah it was
right thank God this game isn't too
realistic all right I'm on my way too I
bring some some vitamin and stuff
too do you have beer FAA yes I have
beer drink up and go crazy yeah I am
you're the alcoholic now I know I know I
was afraid for you to come back and
realize I've slipped into bed Happ
things have
changed it's because you weren't around
when we needed you we we we don't have
to live like this we have child it makes
me three times as strong I need this
what about her
future you want to have a future of she
dies to
zombies these are special
circumstances I don't need to be I don't
I don't need bullying anymore I learn
from my mother oh my gosh this is a
scary
pit does it look functional it does it
looks scary scary if I was a zombie I
would be very
[Laughter]
scary all
right sounds
promising ooh
yes
oop I am also very scared of
accidentally did you fall
in almost almost I'm scared of they have
the aloe seeds here I'm Ying these oh
yeah it's so much faster with the bike
let's
go very nice wait where's Gigi in the
hole what you're in the hole I still di
right digging herself a hole where
there's my head out cool layers do you
see me
yeah
here a gift for you I'm so excited
yay thank you you're welcome wait take
some take some food one more
hour and take what one more hour in game
hour oh my
God so last minute
again oh yeah g I have stuff for you too
okay where is the entrance oh wow nice
wow yeah that's uh that looks very good
the only problem will be if people go
through these doors and then let people
in again like me last time then you
fall don't fall down no no falling no
falling guess we could have made like
iron doors or so to replace these by
now um G where is gigy in the hole okay
there I I'll put your uh stuff into the
armor chest there thank you I will take
my
perch kiaha M have some food oh thank
you I did bring a little bit for myself
but that's good have a
Band-Aid oh thank you oh yes can I have
one Band-Aid maybe yeah
yes I'm over
here take this take one of these one of
these
than oh thank
you thank you wait wait wait take take
take one of these oh thank
you
okay all right I'm excited let's see
what this will bring us yeah today you
think I can keep digging while they're
here
it done yet does he still need more
actually actually finally quickly kill
me that's funny really yes okay are you
sure I'm sure are you going to spawn
here what yeah I'm going to spawn
here I got some
[Music]
XP
ooh yeah the front and the sides are
very well protected I wonder when the
zombies come from the back if we'll have
any problems but should I take back
there too no no no no there's one one
line of mode and a line of
spikes it'll be fine we just always need
to have an eye on where they're coming
from but it won't be as many as last
time cuz we're less people so we'll be
good wow it's going to start soon
20 seconds 20
seconds what do these do again damage
mitigation disease
resist region I see see if I go out I
have to eat this and this only if I go
out I'll stay up here if I shoot someone
by accident I'm sorry I'll try to not
Sho you if if I set you on fire by
molotovs I will I will I will call out
when I'm going to use the molotovs okay
smart smart giggy are you coming out to
fight or are you going to keep on
digging I'm going to see if they bother
me down here okay Mom my bike is oh my
bike is in danger will they hit it I
don't think
so I'm scared to go out now they're
about to
come they could take they could take my
my bike will die oh fun I'm going to go
grab my bike can you give me like
coverage yeah I don't think you can pick
it up I I'll cover you with shots I'll
watch you thank you
my oh
god oh it's lagging com go go go go go
go I'm watching I'm watching
okay no I didn't want I
want scared with me my
be leave my you I'm leaving they where
in the pit with me I'm going
[Music]
inside okay okay okay I got my bike I'm
bark I'm throwing a moloto just say oh
sorry oh that's gy there's a lot of them
aren't
there lag lag I'm throwing a Molotov
watch out I'm throwing a
Molotov on my
way let me just go in please let me just
go
in door
maze okay okay oh lag
all right all right I'm throwing a
Molotov
again he's
[Music]
spitting oh there they're all burning
and they're dying by the
spikes they're dying yeah they are dying
spit at
me fire
try let's try to always prioritize
killing the police guys first yeah big
big big yeah okay why are they hitting
the trees that's my
job how dare they I know stop taking my
job I like how they're all Gathering
nicely some I'm fixing some of the
spikes that I
can that's nice of you ouch yeah they
seem to have a hot spot over there yeah
get off these spikes and the trees why
are they hitting the trees I know the
trees alive is it because
you oh yeah they got
doggles my aim is not the best forz
them I'm on Tom again F watch out F
watch out okay what's inside get in
where how did they get get in he just
red a Spike oh oh hell no oh hell no oh
my God I'm going some more spikes over
here I think one wave is maybe over cuz
the music calm a little bit maybe not I
hope that is the second wave please I'm
placing more
Spike uh should we have stacked them
upwards the
spes oh they they're coming com in
through the the doors they're coming in
through the doors oh they can use those
[Laughter]
nah
nah there's not too I don't see anyone
in actually there's some in the spikes H
there's a few there a few inside but
they're dying from the spikes inside too
that's good all right they'll they'll
die
eventually yeah let me fix some of these
spikes okay New Wave is coming new wave
is coming watch out uhoh oh what was
that just having a
snack ow the spikes are hurting me
too oh oh need repairs there are birds
watch out they brought animals
uhoh let me just repair my arm my
w
um come back come
back okay it's chaos here are you okay
I'm going to throw a moloto I'm good
find a run find a run find a
run there's a big wolf thing or so um
inside I'm taking care of it don't worry
about it I'm taking care of
it I'm bleeding out I'm
done I think my stuff fell into the SP
in the mold going to retrieve
that I already used okay the are dead
it's fine
okay um how am I going
to
stu oh
gosh oh there is so many there okay oh
gosh thank God okay let's don't look at
me don't look at me oh I broke my
legs oh
no they are punching the trees why leave
those trees alone I
know good good line good job leave it
alone get a
job using Focus oh gosh there's a lot of
this all right I'm going to throw fire
again run fire run just run keep running
I'm going to keep
throwing okay bird
down keep running F keep
running keep running oh my God how much
fun at Staying Alive with all of them
well I did die
once spray and pray spray and
pray come
on keep running keep running keep
running oh is that where is fwn I can't
tell which one's F bird watch out
bird no keep running keep running I'm
taking a
break good idea oh no the keep running
keep running keep running let me
barricade they're kind of getting inside
watch out I'm resp
spiking I'm resp spiking the
entrance good
job I'm in a rough Squad right
now don't worry they will die this Spike
nice nice nice nice nice we're doing
good we're doing good I'm dying this
fight oh to come through the door okay
hold
on I'm going to throw bombs at the door
just watch out zombie behind watch out
they're theying for the back behind
you oh no oh my God there
is oh no
they're parkouring soon please be over
soon parkour
civilization parkour
God I need I need a heal I need a
bandaid oh
gosh uhoh I also need to
heat let me
try our defenses is it still is it still
happening yes okay things are very much
Happening Here I we'll put another line
of oh God how are they getting in oh
it's broken in the back I see okay
okay just get that they're hurting me
wait I'll try to be your uh back up here
okay
ow wait oh what was that the car
exploded oh there's a lot coming from
the back oh goodness I'm going to throw
bombs again watch
out does anyone have any spare
Band-Aids with that I used my only
one oh god oh yeah we need some hold I'm
throwing bombs just I'm throwing bombs
let's
out ow ow what're kiding
me owie
owie popping
pills let's go for B my arm is
sprained my arm is also sprained from
all this
punching resp
[Music]
spiking there are so many coming from
the hill just be careful okay I'm
throwing I'm throwing my last bomb watch
out watch out it's going to be close a
watch run
[Laughter]
maybe maybe I should have made
give me ammo oh that was that someone
else oh God okay Hammer Time baby
although I'd like some free ammo please
oh he dropped ammo he drop
ammo the back
side I'm fresh and ready to
go no more sprin
arm why' the music stop
oh it didn't
stop they killed the Tre sorry sorry
ouch are you okay it's only half my
health it's
okay do you have a like a a healing
thingy nope I have one I'll be okay
though I have one okay I I can drop it
right here on the floor right here where
I'm right behind you thank let me take
the guy I'm out of ammo okay I'm not
going to stand
is it
over oh one more one
more oh wait it's not over it's not over
they on the hill the hill the hill the
hill there's some more they're coming
down the
hill
ammo yeah if we pick some stuff from the
M they give ammo now it's it over I
think it might be over no no
dogs hi
doggles glad you're joining us after
all that's a fauna is just fine she's
just
fine stop stop burning the trees get the
tree down
please those are for me that one is mine
doggle incoming doggle Running Dog fast
big doggle or small doggle small okay
good big dogle then we we scared we very
scared
nice okay why did stop the music I think
it's over
now yeah ow
seems uhoh one more com maybe these are
just regular zomes maybe I think
yeah oh it's so quiet now wow I actually
used all of my
ammo oh gosh me too still attacking the
trees let's
loot there's a bird coming oh Bird's
where can't they read the room from the
back from the
back talk
[Music]
ow yeah it's over good job girls good
job we survived we did that was
definitely the one yet yeah okay there's
a few more wait no no there there's more
around doesn't feel like the raid
anymore way less
than of the dogs right oh big wolf
coming big
wolf wolf is attacking tree bark bark oh
dear there's a wolf yep I'm scared I
don't know who he's going for oh he's
going for you
gigy something's hitting me oh hello
hello live I'm so sorry it's okay I was
dying anyway from the spikes at least we
know the spikes works really
well leave me alone leave me alone leave
me alone leave me alone leave me alone a
lot near you
help thank you Father thank
oh no there there's more there's
[Music]
more
oh I'm
exhausted that's why I'm not a tank
usually can't deal with this
stress tank is low stress you just walk
them no
I from the co of
what fire Friendly Fire yeah Friendly
Fire okay then I will not real kill I
did not really die guys yeah it was not
a real
death
undeserved
I'm they're still coming I know it's
okay one more hour I
guess did anyone bring any repair kits
you're getting attacked by a bird uh I
did but it seems like they're used ow
the dog too oh my my gun is broken
uh-oh uh-oh I don't have repair kids
either I'm I'm putting spikes down watch
search the loot search the loot maybe
the loot has one
yeah I need I need ammo if this
continues strong hold strong 40
seconds I didn't
knife
[Music]
die level
31 oh they really hate the trees huh I
know I don't know why
[Music]
ouch I'm going to die Goodbye
World you have served us well FAA best
tank alive or
dead oh God oh God oh God good thing
there's
no right yeah thank God they took that
out thank people thank y y watch out I
don't want to stab you
oh there's more
[Applause]
jeez a littleit late never going to end
is it over it's not over 20 seconds it's
not over
[Music]
yet I'm so exhausted 2 minutes actually
okay two minutes two minutes the music
stopped though yeah it stopped a long
time
ago oh my
B I need to make these modes
better oh so they were
wonderful I don't know how many fell in
I feel like they were we killed a lot of
them before they could fall in again so
we need to make a mode on the back side
though yeah didn't expect them to come
from
there y we did it I need a lot more ammo
for tomorrow I used up all my ammo yeah
need to prepare more ammo glad we found
a few for you already
collecting the when the when the
magazine has an open book that means I
read it already right yes
yes these are all not really
funny well is it over it's over over we
did it won we won let's got it we won
with just four of us but that's honestly
I it didn't feel like they sent us much
less than a lot they did yeah also how
do we get all the loot that is at the
spikes I think we might have to break
the spike I have to break the
spikes okay gy get going this door
is where do
we maybe we can burn it down with a like
Molotov cocktail or so the spikes I
don't have
anymore if I had one safe spot to get
get down there I could Hammer
them Place boxes on the Block
oh good
idea definitely don't want that to
despawn let me I don't I don't want to
ruin
it at least we got a lot of loot yeah
G do you have some
wood um I have 200 on me can you make
me a few
blocks okay just like maybe
10 or so okay crafting right now thank
you oh I'm so full
yeah me too walk through here ouch time
to get out my bike and let the bike take
things how come I'm I'm like
too too wide to fit through this door
frame you've bulked out from all your
fist training I guess so where do you
want the
blocks um I would like go uh around the
modes and place them on top of the some
of the spikes to pick up
the thank you let's
see I don't know how that's going to
work can I really reach them from here
found a treasure map oh I got super corn
seeds more of those that's good that's
good I still can't cook anything with it
but hopefully one day
I can't reach it from
[Music]
here oh
no PE
PE is that the block or the
spikes it's the
spikes that's the block
maybe ow you okay I'm in the spikes oh
yeah those
hurt hurt even when you just graze them
they hurt I got rid of one one block of
spikes at what cost oh wait there's oh I
see there's like a lot of loot down
there yeah so get them in the trenches
yeah we need to get rid of those spikes
but it's difficult and I don't have an
axxe I don't know if we can get rid of
these we can we
can here I got rid of that one block
already uhoh
goodbye goodbye goodbye goodbye
goodbye hey this SM pretty good just
don't
[Music]
panic parkour civilization flashbacks I
feel like I just missed a chicken
jump
shameful ow yeah I'll get rid this
some we'll leave it to you
Eggman ow the
spikes oh no my
backpack oh no
ah oh I see it okay hold
on yeah going to be breaking a lot of
these spikes I'm
sorry my trees is it it's the blue one
down there right yeah
yeah
make at least it gives me wood back
so oh oh oh oh it's two layers of spikes
oh really good right yeah so good so
good no I was testing no actually this
time a building block suffocated me I
guess oh no I was testing it I wasn't
sure where the damage was from we might
have to just say goodbye to this no no
your stuff back I mean definitely the
backpacks but
no I wonder is there any axes that I can
use in
here can we not set them on
fire uh yeah I was thinking that like
throwing in the molotov clock s or so I
don't think burn the loot I have some in
the new house but I don't know if it
will really efficiently
work chat do you have experience with
that dig the dirt oh yeah we could use a
shovel I guess I'm dying to the spike
no we not already learned from this why
does it keep on
happening can when when we dig can we
fill the hole that we
dig or anything I don't know whatever
I'm going to just dig anyway to get F
his backpack
back stop touching
me
oh
well goodbye goodbye
no hey at least atast I died exactly
where you died so our bags are in the
same
place
H learn the
schematic oh wait didn't I already know
that one this one I can
learn a it's the nerd outfit that's
where the cage comes from
are you digging naked people
hello what if I just jump for it no no
give me my bag my bag stuck in this bik
is it Spike
free just we were almost there okay you
can't pick it up with spikes on top of
it anyway I tried mhm oh it seems like
so
I can't even reach the spikes almost
there almost there it should be pretty
reachable now oh oy o it
hurts wait is this mine this is mine
okay did it
work yeah you can go get your backpack
yay all right I'll I'll continue with
this
then have extremely
effective this feel so
wasteful let me get out of here and then
restart somewhere
else yeah I want to go home wait the
loot this spawned there was loot here
like a lot of it the he spawns after a
few minutes I took too long oh
well maybe modes with spikes are not the
best thing cuz we can't get the stuff
well we did it did save us I mean yeah
it was really effective and things were
getting into the house anyway
so I think it was still
good but here F you can take your bike
back B oh is it because there was no mo
here they all went here because there
was no mo here oh I was I was
crouching everybody check the magazine
box for ammo and magazines cuz I put
some in there okay uh here is your bag
Kara you're done with armor right yep
okay I'll start but workstation still
useful start learning
armor maybe maybe the spike should be
around not in the mode even though I
like the
idea but it's not very practical when it
comes to picking up
loot what about
survival we can survive and get mood uh
mood
loot
ah well
they had so much ammo in their loot I
want that
ammo I used up
everything did you check the the
Box uh well not recently I put some in
there okay I picked up lots of ammo in
four stacks of ammo and I used it all up
I'm also putting uh the 9 mm ammo into
the box thank
you and some shotgun
shells car have you learned the Pocket
Mod armor Pockets I think I did Y how
what do you need to craft
it uh let's
see
pocket armor double pocket mud um
scrap polymers which we should have
plenty mechanical parts we got a few the
the materials that might be not plenty
is duct tape and sewing kit sewing K I
see I see those are good apparently if
you haven't yeah I have a couple of
those too mhm two I think I put two in
my armor you have
two it opens up quite a
bit but still I would like a bigger
inventory even
bigger good
job motorcycle
motorcycle oh I I I just unlocked
another vehicle it seems oh I I have
motorcycle parts I got from a class in
my test at home but I literally just
made mini bikes yesterday I'm going to
immediately go make motorcycles I
think yeah and they need a lot of Steel
H yeah we need we need get that Crucible
first I think yeah we should see if we
can buy it yeah maybe tomorrow when more
members are online we can gather all our
money yeah I thought we could get it
today if you guys want
to yeah oh yeah here take my
money good job take all of this really
yeah thank you I'm going to be
digging are you digging more
yeah got to make sure the back side and
the other side is all
covered anything from home we should
take yeah oh sorry you didn't take the
nerd hat in the end did you no I didn't
take it it was going to give you more
exp yeah slipped my mind I was so busy
digging oh we have more treasure maps we
should do that oh I want to go on a
treasure hunt okay I'll hold on to them
and then we can go treasure
hunting whoa whoa whoa whoa he you think
we want to go today or tomorrow anytime
I'm just going to bring him to the new
house I'm just seeing what's here so we
can move stuff over
people box has five seing kids oh take
it take it really yeah did you know that
you had these over here
no a nice surprise found a couple more
seing kits in an unnamed
chest they go to the armor because the
armor needs it most for everybody's
purpose
treasure chests have money in
them that could be good yeah money is
always
good M wait isn't everything supposed to
respawn today or no so not how it
works who a crony Cron's
chest okay I guess I'll go back to the
house I'm I wonder how long we should
play cuz the raid ended and tomorrow CI
wanted us to do to do like a a full
cycle more or
less
wait a full cycle of s
hour I don't know if that's what she
meant I feel like it's it's honestly
better if we play a little more that way
tomorrow doesn't have to be
yeah 6 hours tomorrow yeah six is
already plenty how manying it down how
many hours is it from now from the next
[Music]
day hour or the next or not not the next
time the next time so like 7 hours okay
seven hours yeah so yeah we could we
should play a little bit more to like
bring that down yeah I think so I don't
think I don't yeah are we Addicted by
maybe just a little bit
just I'm not sure it feels
like we just want to make sure we're
really prepared for that big final raid
yeah yeah yeah we want to make it into a
an easy fight for our girls who haven't
been here every day so the experienced
ones are preparing it for the less
experienced
ones plus it's going to get even
harder yeah yeah right I'm scared of
more of the Wolves showing up
mhm I guess it's
not dead though the the wool wasn't
actually bad I just jumped and it
couldn't hit me and I just shot it while
jumping jumping is kind of op I
see the more Shooters the better for
Wolf yeah unless they shoots the one
tank that is tanking the wolf
oh I guess I'm the only one who can do
that to wolves though cuz I have
parkour I got parkour too oh nice yeah
parkour is good if you jump they can't
bite you so you just keep jumping in
place and shooting them from below or
above and easy kill but usually when I'm
out there if there's a need for me to
jump then I'm probably already using my
sledgehammer and my sledgehammer will
use up so much
stamina that I'm not even able to jump
anymore most of the
[Music]
time bad weapon but I already committed
to it and it's pretty cool I like it
when I can Hammer their heads open yeah
[Music]
satisfying my armor is breaking huh do
you guys want to do the treasure chest
today
then yeah sure okay but I mean I guess
not everybody has to go it well it's uh
be productive and split it's helpful a
lot of people come
huh huh huh huh did you not did you not
see I don't know how to describe what
just
happened you I got to show you a clip of
it later yeah someone clipped that I
don't know what happened
uh but I I to say uh the area for the
treasure is actually quite fake so and
um you know it's the same thing where
when you after you dig enemies spawn so
it might be helpful for a lot of people
to come here
okay right I am
bik oh no did we leave you
there I I willingly CH to
St I'm just saying I will need a ride if
it it's okay
I uh I'll come pick you up actually are
you ready to come back no okay let me
know when you now me know when you're
ready to come back and I'll come pick
you up okay I I'm I'm I'm almost done
digging now one thing I realized when we
were fighting rather than food I was
more in need of medkits yeah I want to
go get a bunch of aloe from the desert
if we can make stop I can collect a
bunch really
fast okay that's a good thing to put on
our list tomorrow or
today
yes beer excuse me
excuse I'm trapped thank you
sorry it's okay small house I know we
should knock some more
walls make it a big open space I got an
Al aloe vera
seed we we have four yeah I already
we're out of a gardening
CLS
oops did do you need to come here and
bite the walls down please okay
I'll knock all the wall in the house
yeah yeah I had to tear down these walls
because I was going for a much more open
kitchen and then that way it leads into
the the patio as well as the bathroom
and you can see the bathroom from the
patio what I was going for
yeah I see the vision oh I don't like
the Privacy you know that's why I like
going to everyone's chest
best hide yeah that's exactly what I'm
thinking we're already in a zombie
apocalypse why are you keeping secrets
you hate us
yeah do we have any repair
kits no I can make
some okay my bike still has stuff
right we got
oh
magazines um Salvage
Salvage is anybody learning repair
tools uh how much do I have to let's see
I only have five that's more than me so
I also have a little bit around that but
I thought somebody might have
higher Ste
Bo don't forget to periodically check
your
challenges oh yeah
[Music]
nothing
new except for
one cop zombies yeah I killed plenty of
those oh I need more big mama
zombies is that a thing yeah I got the
cop zombie too 10,000 XP wow does it
give you a rare item
rare item no I thought it
said I didn't actually read it I just
gled that it said 10,000 XP and rare
item did I get something rare items I
didn't get anything where's my rare
items I from the trader oh do you have
to turn it in as the
trader hopefully any Trader
not the specific
one I'll just learn
these I'm so smart in this game I'm so
smart I have read so many books I'm so
well read
wow my brain is exploding and
expanding yeah more books more
knowledge knowledge is overpowered
knowledge is
everything I'm making a bunch of repair
kits for us M thank you Mommy oh no corn
[Music]
Ready
corn corn for
dinner it has no nutritional value I I
have an eyelash in my
eye I need to use a knife to get 20
steel am I
[Music]
crazy oh it's not ready oh is did it say
growing I just can't could make a better
one of this I can't read
maybe
five it looked ready it wasn't ready
don't want to use a do
it steel I don't have enough steel I'll
just make this little five one first and
then in the future I'll make the best
Ste I can make how about that steel is
just too rare right now guys give up
you're too hopeful but we can get The
Crucible
right yeah indeed generous
donation yeah for my wives do I have
Parts I think I do you have my entire
life savings in your
hand you have enough I have I have some
more money I have 10,000 oh if we I have
4.6k I'll give you all my money for one
repair kit
okay how about I've got a bunch of
repair
kits where's a be boo I
stairs if he does sell it right now then
we should definitely get it from Bob
yeah I don't know if he always has it
but we should
check a here go here
go first doesn't matter where thank you
oh I have exactly
15,000 again but I want to make it
higher level
chat I think I'll just make this one
first I I be right but I got to wash my
eye out there's like a oh no a
a i in it an Aly I'm Aly be right by
okay
I think that's better before I'm like
wasting all the
steel so going to make it this one
lever
lever should have made this before the
hoorde came but
no lots to
do oh gosh the steel Knuckles are so
expensive wa the cop zombie reward might
be really good huh
really chat keeps on spamming now that I
should go get it
now so I'm going to go get
it wait take me with you
[Music]
okay if you don't tickle me okay I won't
tickle you okay otherwise I'll crash us
oh no tickle
tickle your Uber bike is outside oh can
you unlock in the doors what I have to
do that
again unbelievable you need a fob you
need a keep maybe I should just put
codes on everything then I don't have to
unlock it right does that work
yeah most common code okay yeah it seems
like it might
[Music]
work all
right here we
go oh I see yeah go to any Trader to
collect your
reward for cop Slayer okay I'm backc
back better you I'm better yes I washed
it out
guys please write me high ranking uh
Stars yeah please do you back very good
thank
you spread the
word what he gives us water filter able
a I'm Tak
a wait these are really good these are
super good he also gives legendary parts
and solar cells you didn't have to buy
it no uh it's a reward for killing 50 c
zombies oh you should go to the tra too
oh yeah I check I check I check do we
only need one Crucible yeah only one I
bought it I'm gonna get the water filter
then okay
okay nice noise noise you guys can have
your money your money back okay
although
maybe he sells something nice something
else what does he
have I I mean you sell steel no wait we
don't need steel now I can I can forge
steel with this
Crucible if sell rocket Parts handgun
Parts I would really like
those I don't I'm already is he selling
them I don't know
um no he does not
no I wonder how much steel I can make
right up the bat wait can I give you
your money back oh yes here take your
money
back it seems some of it is missing is
it no it's okay it's okay don't worry J
congratulations here's your reward in my
it all
combined oh I can also take a water
filter and a solar cell and a
crucible what what do we what do we
need do we would be good but yeah or
legendary Parts
yeah maybe giggy can also get a reward
gigy did you kill 50 cop zombies no I
need to kill 20 more well we have we
have a lot of legendary parts and we can
loot those right so I don't feel I feel
like legendary part we could make a
second for we have three right
now um I used some for your guy is armor
and also one for myself I think so we're
down to threee what's what's a solar
cell it must be for some other cool
machine but I have yet to find what it's
useful for yeah I guess you can get
power but I don't know what it's used
for electricity okay maybe maybe I'll
just get another water filter yeah let's
get a water filter it will be useful
yeah
okay all right Steel is in the
[Music]
making off for turrets solar power for
turrets maybe is what it's
for I already got the water filter
though by the way people you were able
uh to make ammo right yeah do you make
those in the Forge or elsewhere no the
work thingy the work B
is it difficult to make big amounts no
oh I might we might need extra tomorrow
you can make bullet casings in the Forge
and then I need gunpowder and the the
bullet thingies which I've been
collecting a lot of though not too bad
okay cuz like even with four Stacks I
ran out today and
tomorrow you know a lot of people need
probably much more ammo so we might want
to make some ourselves
tomorrow
M send GGY to collect
gunpowder yeah gun gunpowder would be
nice when you get that I don't
know what rock do I hit for
that uh explosive on no iron they
they're saying you should rather collect
iron iron iron
okay I have 1,000 on me right now I can
get
more more more
more after I finish this
moat oh you're already making the next
oh I feel so much
better it hurt so bad
like no I like him what about what about
one one one Spike you know instead of
double spiking what if I do one Spike oh
okay so you mean have the path to two
Fields but only one in spikes that could
work yeah single wall spike okay ah also
they're saying make free Block tall wall
of spikes on the outside for jumpers
oh I guess we're going to get some high
jumping enemies next
H
[Music]
concerning there we go I wonder if we
have more I'm just not seeing
it iron iron iron iron iron
[Music]
iron oh there's a bunch of gunpowder in
one of our
chests yeah
but you you can make bullet casings in
the
for mhm with the brass brass and clay
and we have so much of that
so that's
easy so just bullet tip and gunpowder
bullet tip
uh is lead and
Clay so you can make that in the Forge
as well so basically just need gunpowder
I think that's craftable
too maybe I should put out a second
for I
could I could maybe I win oh I have a
lot
of I can make some bu now if anybody
needs any or I'll wait
until people log on and see what people
need I mean we could already put it into
the
queue yeah let's throw in
some chemical St I don't chal I can't
make it yet no no not yet oh I can make
high
power ammo too and armor
piercing I would already be happy with
just normal one I think think cuz I'm
guessing that takes less resources okay
I'm going to make I'm going to make some
762 for you first
then
okay and then once we get
more materials we can oh yay do
[Music]
collectors that will be
useful yay we don't have to boil the
water
anymore
yippe I also want want to stock up on
explosives again because explosives were
very very useful for that mhm
mhm sounds
good okay I'm making a second Forge so
that we can um smelt all the stuff
faster the brass and
everything I'm going to put it also in
the
[Music]
kitchen maybe here
where's my
wrench renovating the kitchen a little
duct tape oh yeah just put it in put it
in for now I'm just collecting a lot of
uh stuff so that tomorrow hopefully I
can make some armor for the less covered
up
girls so lude I would scantily
clad I would like to go to the desert if
anybody
want we could do some quests I want you
want to Alo get the treasure chest first
I have two treasure maps
on there is oh there's one by G there's
one by our old house and then there's
one in
the dead fire
area yeah let's do it okay I'm going to
go to the one by GG first and that way
we can pick you up as well you're going
right
away
one where is it please bring me some
food and water okay
thank you wait I I'll I'll should I go
too yeah we we should all do the the
treasure cuz together cuz it's a big
circle and M enemies will
spot okay is it digging do you have to
dig for it yes you have to dig yay I
know how much
yeah okay I need an iron
shovel uh I only have a stone shovel I'm
coming to pick you up GG
okay let me know when you're
here I will come out of my
hole hobo stew take so long to cook but
it's good got to render down all the
stuff you put in it all the mystery
meat just wonder what you're feeding us
what are you feeding
us is it worse than rotten
flesh um no it's not worse than rotten
flesh
nice
nice how about
BR there's so much clay over there um
sand when will we need sand and stones
is it crushed
sand for
cement I don't know should I prepare
it I don't have space
anyway trying to forge forge
on ah
okay could craft in a
bell
um I think I'm ready to head over when
you are
kiaha
[Music]
uh I'm just looking for
six pieces of
wood check the check the fire the
cooking pot take it out of there I don't
want to cancel it but I I could just
yeah I'm canceling it for a moment we
canceled the water one the water one no
no I already have wood I already have
wood oh
okay um is that that's it I got it just
reach into the fire
crap
[Laughter]
wood as a phoenix I will be
fine I'm
here come out of your hole come
out do you like what I've done why is
there a dead when did this dead animal
get
in
um oh no see this where did it go I
didn't even I didn't get glued it how
did it
die it just died and
disappeared it's not
fair Al are we waiting for them to
arrive are you going there keep working
on your hole here I'll give you I'll
drop some food in your hole y
yummy drop some food water in your hole
so that way you
stay
yeah okay
that'll make me thank you you're
welcome okay okay okay uh um uh yeah I'm
just putting away a few things and then
give me two one minute one minute
[Music]
you okay bless you
you BL
you oh I can make seeds potato seeds
now it feels so expensive though you
need five potatoes to make one potato
sced and I feel like you plant po back
so it's like only net two potatoes what
a waste I
know
[Music]
oh okay I'll just leave it
behind ready to
go this okay although I don't know where
to go oh you didn't take these five
sewing kits in my
box me yeah uh in the old house yeah oh
no oh I'll just bring it with me just in
case okay but right now it's not too
urgent probably tomorrow I'll be making
a bunch of armor but then uh until then
I don't need it are we going towards the
old house now or where old house there's
a I don't think you guys can see the
where the treasure is but it is by the
old house
okay okay is this the right way no
no is this the right way yes
[Music]
okay
what are we going to run out of
fuel
maybe I feel like we are should we take
our bikes h
we can always wrench a car on the way
and get more
fuel where's the gas station when you
need one
yeah what always the save the
environment huh
GG I'm going to use a plastic
strong somebody saying we should do the
last raid in the snow biomi because it's
more fun apparently for some reason you
mean it's more more My
M yeah she works so hard on her hole
Yeah I think we should just stay there
at least for this last raid and if we do
a second season then we can resettle in
the snow biome maybe well I mean the
Wolves the wolves from the snow biome
still came over here so we didn't see
any bears at least yeah uh fauna hold
your breath
okay okay there you go
if I was there I would have tickled
you that's
evil what happened to my caring husband
are you just you're just so cute when
you're
giggling but I'm
drowning if you hold I just want to see
how well you can hold your
breath it's very concerning I I I feel
like there's some murderous intentions
yeah but only towards fauna like what's
what's with what's between you two that
I don't have with gy she doesn't want to
seem to kill
me yeah can you explain
yourself
lust wait I'm out of gas but there's
some gas in the old house I
saw I think unless I took it uh no I
took the gas in the old house no I
already play in my in my
bike thingy there's no gas in
here okay next car we see I'm going to
wrench okay I'll help you there there's
a car by the house you might be able to
r that
way 6%
guess I have 15,000 clay in my inventory
everyone aome that is a lot that'll be
good for making yeah that'd be good for
making bullets and stuff but we already
have several
thousands of clay are you still in your
hole no yes are
you
yes I like it in here okay it's time to
time to come out come see the Sun come
on it's okay you get you get to dig
another you get to dig another hole I'm
taking you somewhere you can dig
too okay do you like it so
far it's very nice thank you I worked
really hard where is the extra hole it's
on on his side oh yes you have you have
made it longer beautiful why does B have
a floating
plate do you see what I
see that for a while am I glitch or
something yes oh yeah wait F do we have
a tube no that's just
beo
yeah all right I'm going to come here
follow me I'm going to bring you
somewhere where you can dig more
okay favorite hobby but I like what
you've done with the place thank you
I'll put spikes outside of the hole and
a little bit inside are you going to
remove the spikes that are there
no they can stay for
now can we can we siphon gas out of mine
no no it's okay I filled it back up to
30% okay oh mine's at 30% as well
maybe if I don't step on the gas it
won't use as much huh yeah does does it
work that way I'm not sure think so I'm
not stepping on it now and it doesn't go
down or maybe slowly
maybe I step on it oh yeah it goes down
right away oh but oh not that
much I'll just we're going to have to
walk home no no no no no the Traders
have some gas maybe we can stop by
no a or just wrench more cars we'll be
fine okay it is close
by aha okay Okay g stand right
here okay stand right here I'm going to
stand right here this is the this is the
width of the thing okay yeah okay wa did
you take your money bike yeah oh okay
you don't want it you gave me more than
I gave
you must have given you some of
someo they don't give oh it's okay I
deserve my child's
allow what nothing don't worry about it
my I got to save up for college I'm
doing I'm getting A's because of you you
told me to get a so I
did that's why I'm putting in your
college fun you'll see it once you get
to College okay I believe
you all right F I got some money for
your alcohol
addiction what oh thank you but Papa
please oh no don't worry sweetie we'll
get it we'll get it back we'll just go
to the casino and we'll win it
back how how deep is the treasure uh if
you hit rock that is too deep that's too
far okay but girls I was um I wonder
what you think about this before I
started the gaming portion of the stream
today I was um discussing with my
viewers how I would love to take a like
a trip with everybody to like Las Vegas
or so and have a casino
night
black like
it but we all have to set like a maximum
budget just so that we don't over spin
Gamba
Gamba I'm putting it all
in yeah but a maximum buget maybe maybe
like
$1 okay okay that's very very
controlled you can't go a scent over
$10 and then in roulette we'll always
just bet on the same thing over and over
if we each bet on something different
then that means one of us will always
win or sure for sure is how it wins will
they kick us out you're outside the
border now oh no I'm just sing for
fun oh my shovel is going to not hold up
for that long I've got repair kits M
okay just Stone here oh okay
the the perimeter got smaller m okay
which which way toward towards
bble
yeah I'm standing pretty much in the
middle of
it we have to dig in a circle or just a
line I think just within the circle it's
somewhere within the circle perimeter oh
this better be worth it yeah
mhm I'm enjoying this this how many
Treasures do you have I have two maps so
this one and there's another one in the
okay fire fire light the fireplace but
wen't there zombies going to
spawn zombies spawned last
time H maybe that was a natural
spawn
maybe oh hey you wait the time when the
uh spawned are you referencing to the
time where we had the digging Quest no
it was I had another quest in the ice or
not a quest but a treasure map in the
ice place and things were spotting quite
a
bit we already dug so much where is yeah
we
did imagine if this was our
moat we could just move
here I have 200 spikes on me oh God 200
did is that what all the wood was for
was this your like Grand
Design it wasn't planned to become
spikes it just so happened that they
became
spikes I have a good
plan G how about you connect this tunnel
okay this way this way towards B towards
people again
face yeah
yeah so until tomorrow's fornite giggy I
want to see a connection between these
tunnels can you do
it kind these are our secret
tunnels it's absolutely necessary for
our survival okay once I get an iron
shovel I'll start working on it it will
be our emergency exit tunnel yeah yeah
they'll never know yeah we can bunker up
somewhere
here these are secret Denver Airport
tunnels are you very familiar with the
Denver Airport Denver
Airport I've looked into yeah okay I
need a repair kit okay what's special
about the Denver Airport here you go the
horse with the glowing eyes is very
special and
interesting the horse we could take a
field trip to Denver airport and check
out the horse
on the way to Las Vegas yeah oh wait oh
I don't need a repair kit for this shity
shovel nice oh I guess you don't yeah
Stones
yeah
awesome B's pretty close to Las Vegas
amazing let's combine the
trips let's go see the horse and then go
gambling Lucifer yeah it did give me Las
Vegas Vibes same area I guess
M are we still in the perimeter yeah
we're still in the perimeter it got
smaller but you're still in it
okay this is crazy this is crazy this
better be good this better be good
yeah we could be
questing I could be digging the actual
hole
wait when's the next day
30 oh the the wall is right right here
so like Fawn is right on the edge of it
I see it oh you see it it's right here
oh it's locked oh hold on let me no I
can uh lock pick it one
second
yippe yippe
this better be worth
it what's
inside oh 5K okay it was worth it oh 5K
money 5K money yeah it's not bad is that
it no there was a lot of stuff okay here
I will drop some it gave me a lot of
materials for bullets
actually and then here's some kiaha
bullets
thanks yeah it gave me Bullet and um and
weapon part at 5K so that was worth it
that was so that was totally worth it
[Music]
yeah no it's all right it's all right
was pretty good pretty
good let's get out of this oh and I got
I got gold
too gold gold and apparently that's
worth gold is extra money okay so we got
even more money okay that was worth it
oo all right do you want to go to my
second one yeah okay uh I don't know if
this thing has any fuel in it no no it
doesn't only the full cars
oh well but those parts are still
useful all right lead the way all right
Ro
CH I'm here
help help
[Music]
help I'm on
y dangerously close to her
face all right
um we're
[Music]
going west for a while okay w w
we could check out the bookstore too oh
yeah it's books books it's in the snowy
area it's Northwest from
here you want to lead the
way um let's go to the treasure first
Maybe
and then see how close we
are wait can I share the wayo is that a
thing shared way points wait
how I'm going to stop by Trader W get
some fuel too oh okay so we're going to
get tra wct is on the way but I don't I
don't think my mini bike is gonna make
it see
oh do you see my wa point now oh
apparently
uh as you shared it but I have no idea
where it is yeah you shared it but I
can't I don't see it
North I see it yeah I
see Bo North nor
north of Home North of
home
what north of the new house oh I see it
okay I see
it I don't see it but we'll go there I
guess I do want to go to the desert to
which is in the opposite
direction it's okay we need to stall for
time
anyway
yeah we do MH you
mean we need to install longer today I
feel like we could and I'm not just
saying that cuz I'm addicted yeah
anybody really want to do a like seven
hour
stream well it's we need day 35 for the
hord day
okay we should save around at least 4
hours is maybe for the
tomorrow so we should probably we should
probably stop at
yeah oh I got a challenge oh we got some
gas I got some gas yeah me too me too
thank you car for your donation
free gas refuel can you refuel it or do
I have to do it let's see D can you make
us some
gas
yeah creates it yeah make us some gas
please oh yeah you like some steroids
what about the car right there I don't
have a wrench though oh I don't have a
wrench I have a hammer does that work I
don't think so does the hammer work or
does it have to be a
wren how a ranch oh
well I'll guess where's the trader at a
genen no I'm going to W cuz Rex's the
way am I going the the right way father
Yes
okay I can't look at the map while I'm
driving just follow this road the
direction you're going okay and at the
fork take a
right okay nice oh you know the roads
now out no I'm looking at the
map she got the map app out I'm in the
the passenger seat
navigating passenger princess but we're
stopping for
course oh nothing inside okay give us
the
guas fill up our T give it give it you
greedy little minivan oh
wait the house is here you can grab a
bike if you
want no oops sorry I didn't
mean yeah I like sitting here oh you
know what how how full is this one oh
this one's more full okay we're going to
we're going to swap we're going to swap
we're going to swap time to swap
bikes oh hold I have to mod this one so
it has a seat hold on I'm going to drop
off all my clay
okay put it uh next to the forge oh
[Music]
so much clay my inventory is oops I got
off sorry
oopsie I'm sorry dangerous it's like
you're trying to become an action
hero can I Craft on the back of the bike
oh I can't I wish I could the back seat
making cloth Oh I thought maybe I can oh
let me store some stuff too
[Music]
we're going to JMA right now
huh no we're going we're going to we're
going to rck not okay we're going to
pass by this house so we can drop stuff
off
oh right I feel it's close right over
there in the The Forest of tree
pleas home sweet home the Clementine
house
yeah we have any
water we should have a lot we have a
little bit oh my hammer is
ready
Yi I feel like every time I come home I
just get stuck doing stuff so it's like
dangerous it could be like that here I'm
going to get rid of these
walls aggressions are being let out
again I want no privacy in our
house why are you worried about cheating
when you have two wives I'm worried
about my child hiding stuff in her room
no don't take away my door I need my
door I don't feel I need my privacy my
door you need a door bu stuff from us I
agree she doesn't need doors yeah yeah
she does not need a
door how I take away all of her
furniture all of take away her bed too
she must sleep on
theed anything you do in your room you
can do out in the living room too I'm
running away from home I'm going to my
friend's house I'm not when I turn when
I turn 18 I'm out of here dang it I
don't W what is that
screamers
jeez hammer time I want I need my Hammer
Hammer so many of them give me some give
me some good thing we opened up the
place good thing would have been
punching each other yeah
I love toilet they're breaking our walls
you see that the
kitchen oh my God I thought you were
breaking the
wall oh she's there huh in the back okay
W wo wo wo wo
W what's
happening maybe I should put some spikes
outside this house too oh there's still
more there's still more coming
oh oh oh oh
oh like a mini horde mini wave yeah mini
oh there's still more I like
this and now it's
daytime how
exciting come on come on stamina please
hold up hold up zombies please wait for
a
moment oh my God I have like five 10
zombies on me
help and dead no back the
kind of Y of the house
okay oh my head
hurts oh wait honestly uh I might leave
soon cuz um I've been streaming before 5
hours and my head hurts oh okay we have
been here for a while we we we can um
stop since it's day 30 5 hours isn't too
bad and we're starting ear any
I do want to like give the other girls
somewh you know time to play we
shouldn't like do everything for
them even though we'd love to do so many
things
yeah but surely a season two will come
one of these days and then and we can go
to all the biomes that we missed that we
didn't see yet mhm and go do all the
things that we still have available to
us I'm going to build a mod outside this
house too uh
oh
by you just want to dig no I just I just
feel like we need the
protection that lady busted through our
wall do you see this she did look think
she didn't take our oven oh oh because
oh that one that's yeah there's no wind
or anything there she just should Place
something
there she broke
it building block you're not the beaver
anymore you're the
mole a fixer my Mo life nak Mo
rat once I go back to hitting trees what
am I the beaver again yeah yeah
the Gopher now our house looks stupid
our my wall doesn't
match I need look at it we paint
it sting
I'll keep those and make things for
[Music]
people we have a lot of forged
steel that's good what do we what does
it take to make them anyway oh my God uh
what what does it take to make for steel
anyway uh just
iron as well so it's it's the same
ingredients as for making for
iron but it takes a couple more but yeah
we're making
plenty I me make some more
50 yeah too much what how many 50 50 50
sure we'll make more more I didn't
somebody have a lot of iron with them G
um I put 1,000 in did we need
that into the forge yeah yeah it goes
into the forge that's fine oh okay okay
okay
okay the more the
Maria I need five leather do we have any
we do it's in the uh next to the
forge
take I need
to sorry a little bit of safy
haard I'm crafting an iron
shovel iron
shovel I'm making level five
Knuckles
ooh I have level one right now I'm
skipping a
few I hear something why is there
another zombie yourself but you
they can't get enough of us best I know
alive chill I'm busy like no one else
plays with us when you're offline please
play with us now did I not oh right you
have to use the the
bench feels
good nice
oh 50 50 stamina per
hit
wow good stuff she dead right yeah okay
did you
upgrade yeah better Hammer
nice I didn't make a max level one I I
wanted to save for the next steel Hammer
so for now I just made a good iron
Hammer but
eventually season two will be my hammer
Life season two in full bloom my hammer
life
oh my head hurts I really really hope
that we can keep our character
[Music]
progress my
shovel
woohoo what did it break no you made one
see it what kind of shovel did you make
my iron shovel my level five iron shovel
iron shov you like it okay let's dig a
dig a mo around this house too see how
fast you can do it oh my God two hits on
this block it's pretty
fast
[Music]
oh stop playing now
right that's just how it be so curs I
hurt so much oh no maybe we should force
it we should just all log off for your
help but I need to wait 15 more seconds
for my steel but I need to I need to go
to the trader to check the items on the
trader
though but there's also an infestation
Quest on the way that I might want to do
on the way to the trader oh no no more
Quest I'm just going to the tra then oh
my head oh God oh
God where's the zombie I can test this
out
on you you know where you can test it
out on you can test on this tier four CL
that's I'm right next
to oh you're
far oh wait my mods I
[Music]
forgot
um uh
I'm
dying don't die don't die don't
die thanks that was all I needed yeah no
don't die you're so
sexy okay I'll think over it again I'll
Recon it it would be a waste of such a
good butt
yeah that is true press for Mirage to
look at her
ass I think they all already did but
thanks maybe we can get some more I
actually I uploaded the dance version a
few hours ago can we can watch it take a
look
yeah watch my ass in that one um does
press four go get to a butt shot I I
think in the dance shot it might not
align perfectly we we kind of
purposefully shortened the song and the
official music video by like one or two
seconds so that it would align
perfectly I don't think it works for the
dance sh but it's more about you know
the overall video than just pressing for
on that one that is
true I do love dance versions of songs
yes right I love watching those
[Music]
too it does work still oh it works all
right
oh perfect four always works no the boar
isn't
[Music]
here I just wanted something to fight
what were you
no the really really big one you guys
kill it again
yeah it's
easy
now maybe we should just AFK on the
server for maybe 10 hours no it's not
everything
it's not
productive yeah wait what the what what
didn't respawn the boar book oh the boar
oh
sad I have to go fight a bear in the
tundra it's the only way that bear is
trying to get his
education wow I think that's worth
repairing and El fighing
[Music]
then yeah these are still
good for
tomorrow
done I have a point
[Music]
available I hope you get feeling better
maybe one more in
here was worth
it what' you get I got T gum Parts Jen
was nice also she has a lot of fuel for
cheap so I've just stocked up on a bunch
of fuel for everyone since I feel like
we'll be needing it that's
good that's not a bear
points two points
okay I'll save up still pretty good
though it's not going anywhere that is
true the game is not going anywhere it's
true we'll play tomorrow yeah fun
tomorrow but we're playing after we're
playing right
now we play tomorrow but also we're
playing right now
what was that the one
uh Commando
boots should I make these two
[Music]
chant the weighted head mod for your
Sledgehammer than you so much weighted
head mod
why are we still online I'm ready to log
off at any moment yeah if you tell me to
log off I will we can stop any moment
right we have power over
it all righty then stay safe out there
sure I can loog over what is that is
that a mountain lion wait I can't fight
the cat I can't are
dangerous very dangerous are they but I
don't want to fight it cuz it's cute oh
there's a bear I could fight the bear
are you saying are you saying the bear
is not cute no the bear is cute too but
I have a weakness for cats that's true
oh that's that's the one thing that you
will not do in this
game
understandable what is this chat what is
this buff de puff do you know
how do I fix
it SNK uh oh I forgot to bring bandages
I'm going to die
uhoh that bear toughened up since the
last time you saw it did I forgot to
bring
bandaids
no it's
over well I I mean I guess we need to
find more bandid for you so
like I'm Invincible nothing can kill me
nothing will ever kill
me I am so
strong oh I didn't bring anything I
didn't bring any food
either
ready to find this bear there's another
bear
[Music]
I mean if she's fighting your health is
very
low yeah but I
live I will never die I'm Invincible
yeah that's what as long as long as you
believe it it is true
yeah I should go to I mean you're you're
you're fighting bears right yeah okay I
was
yes
M why am I
missing one
more
no duct
tape it's the usual cycle of do you need
more duct tape crafting no I made a
couple but you know probably will'll
need more tomorrow for the other girls
now we have lots of water so should be
should be better okay yeah we improved
our
situation okay W treat herself with some
nice
boots we girls we like shoes you know
yeah yeah shoes oh my God
shoes love shoes pretty pretty How many
pairs of shoes do you guys estimate you
own 30 yeah I think I'm around 30 what I
want to see your
shoes maybe 40 I I have like uh
like eight pairs but like five of those
I bought in Jaan so that five of those
is like
recent yeah bibo you were really decking
yourself out Japan
whole
yeah
way you know those TV shows where
somebody gets like a complete makeover
uhhuh in terms of cloes like fashion
everything bio almost did that huh no I
pretty much did that
because because I got I got like the the
hair treatment and then I got the nails
and then I got the new wardrobe in head
yeah a nice that's how it feels Japanese
fashion is just yeah on another level I
dress like a pretty princess now yes oh
no I feel like you go outside and
everyone's dressed up and I can't
looking like a rat there
I'm really excited to meet you and see
how you dress and everything it's always
so interesting to
see we'll
see what I dress was our first time
Vegas let's do Vegas trip I want to go
Vegas but I'm going to wear my pretty
princess stuff in
[Music]
Vegas I was saying I'm kind of hoping
that if we have another Ian concert
since we already had East Coast West
Coast maybe next middle of the country
kind of Las Vegas you're not going to
hope for
Europe like come on let's go gambling I
I would love to but I don't know if wa
is it is it Vegas west
coast is it it's pretty close West I'm
pretty sure Oh I thought it was more
middle I mean it's more middle than LA
but yeah right there's no ocean touching
Las Vegas yeah so we should
Cleveland
Ohio
concert
Cleveland exting oh oh let's go go oh oh
it's it's 6:00 a.m. over here it's time
to end it
oh yes I I'm happy with what my progress
I've made some extra stuff I'm ready to
end it y I will do what's good for all
of us me to me too I am almost ready
give me like 5
minutes
I good job that's the first step what
this is what we need and now I'm going
to leave this call too so you will sit
in silence and
think okay I'll wait I'll wait
wait I'm almost done
okay okay looking over my Forge are you
okay are you ready to sleep Forge John
let me put weird how you log in and
nothing has changed like no time has
passed like the next time you log in
like your stuff is still cooking I'm
glad it is I don't know I'm like I feel
like I should log in and I should have
like 18 hobo STS
ready you know no but that would be
concerning cuz that would mean somebody
else logged in when you weren't online
and let the time pass that cannot
happen we have to be online at all times
that's
true okay I put some brass in the Forge
it's cooking I'm going to log out doing
it I'm doing it guys we're doing it
goodbye game see you tomorrow for the
last time it will be such a sad farewell
but a nice yeah it'll be better sweet
but we did so much mhm well
deserved it was quite the
Ark last one out run egg I'm a run egg
EG okay I am the Run
egg what run egg rot have you heard that
that phrase no it's like something you
do with your friends when you're like
like getting somewhere it's like last
one there's a rotten egg you're like you
them
somewhere oh have you also successfully
left the game V yeah yeah so it's like
last one in is a rotten egg I the root
an
egg
laughing don't laugh phrase in German to
that probably when somebody gets left
behind or stays behind on
purpose have to look it up f as I yeah
but do we ever say that like
that I don't
know uh
well well well we were so today exact
same yeah oh really that's what somebody
in my chat
said rotten egg oh but probably well
rotten wos rotten
wos whoever
podo
podo whooo
[Laughter]
H I heard that before the last one will
be bitten by the dogs oh oh yeah that's
a good
one I was bitten by I was bitten by a
dog so it it worked
out careful they're going to eat you up
I'm almost done I think I'm
almost well I want to say thank you
girls it's so nice even though people in
know small group but I think we did our
best I'm happy to spend time together y
our family the Clementine family yeah
just a little
abusive little toxic family
Dynamic we will get throughs together
it's it's normal to get a little bit
toxic in a zombie apocalypse it's a very
stressful environment after all
G I had a dream about you what did you
dream about I dream that we were in the
zombie apocalypse and you were sad and I
was comforting you and I was hugging you
and then I turned into a zombie and
started eating
[Music]
you did I just smell so good I mean I
couldn't help it I I turned at that
moment that was my time to become a
zombie what part did you fight first I
think your neck my I see
vampire yeah vampire in the
G okay I'm done oh she doesn't want to
hear the parents' love stories you e
don't tell me you e i
don't
e this is how me and your mother met no
ew ew it's the birds and the
[Music]
beans I can't marriage this is how it
[Laughter]
started okay I'm I'm logged I'm L I'm
logging off now are I'm gone we we'll
see each other tomorrow um 1 hour
earlier than usual yes Mark it in the
calendars and we'll hopefully have a
good last final episode
yeah let's pull the noobs through it
yeah with with with the Seven Days to
Die God
[Music]
Pros see you
tomorrow
byeee good
night
pleas
pleas no
man
hey good day day very
fun one last day tomorrow oh um
schedule let me talk talk about my
schedule this week I didn't make one yet
but I will make one maybe tonight and
post it
um tomorrow last day of s days die
Wednesday we'll do War hmer
Thursday we'll do um I have one collab
with kiaha Gigi and Sh the new Mario
party and then
also Avan collab fasmo so that's
Thursday um so double double collab on
Thursday um Friday gig birthday I will
be taking a part of part of gig
birthday
um by my
[Music]
Saturday we will play
something Saturday and Sunday I don't
know exactly what it is but Saturday and
Sunday we'll play a spooky game um I'm
still waiting for the perms I have a
backup
game if if the Silent Hill doesn't
happen then I'll probably play like dead
space or something so I have a backup if
if Silent Hill
doesn't get done in
time or doesn't accept so I yeah I have
blobs too um
just the heads up some games might be
put on a um
pause until spooky month is over because
you want me to play spooky games right
and since you want me to play spooky
games since we only have a few weeks in
October some ongoing things might be put
on a pause so I can play Spooky game um
so just so you
know m a ky spooky collab is next Monday
so not this week but next Monday cuz she
wasn't available um so we're going to do
the 21st
for Kyla spooky rhinestone collab
panacor
yeah so yeah that's my schedule so
far tomorrow 7 Days die Wednesday
Wednesday
Warhammer uh Thursday double collab
Friday collab birthday Saturday Sunday
be stream normal uh probably spooky game
yep yep yep yep yep yep
yep that is
the schedule but I'm still waiting on
the Silent Hill thing so if not Silent
Hill then maybe dead space or something
like
that yeah but yes just so you know I
have I do have a lot of ongoing games at
the moment but if you want me to play
spooky games uh if you want me to play
spooky games for this remaining bit of
October then we're going to have to wait
a little bit to continue those
games
yeah it's already halfway Blue October
already
so
[Music]
um the other call MERS are playing it
hopefully it goes through yes it it most
it's it probably will go through it's
just a matter of
when
so I'm just waiting for my turn to be
accepted so yeah it's just individual
perms we all got to get
accepted
uh for Silent Hill separately it's
individual perms it's individual perms
so you know if one person has it they
requested it for themselves so we have
to request it for ourselves as
[Music]
well
okay in today's episode of how long
we'll be able Yap for let's go to super
chats
first every game company is different
oh we got to go buy the the perms of the
game
company ya ya time more l
hi car thank you for the super rock rock
um you got the title The Wrong Way
Around be that was on purpose because
it's
like what was women love me fish fear me
or something like that right so it was
on
purpose
uh man St think for super rock
rock where do that mean from anyway
where where do that mean from
from fishing hat oh yeah fishing
hat
um Moon demons thank you for the super
rock rock Pebbles when be was gone for
one day now we have a proper emote when
we say she hates us oh yes thank
you
for no
em literally was scrolling through my
art tag and I was
like wait this cute this is what I asked
for and I was like hey is it okay if I
use them and they're like yeah so thank
you they're so cute and they look so
good they look so good she hates
us and now and now when I shoot a gun at
you you can respond with Pebble
boy no BL now when I say don't BL you
can BL if you have a BL
emote thank you thank you
buddy thank you for super rock rock y b
we can play together now yeah you can
play I can play we can all play we can
play
together um rock Ace thank you for super
rock rock thank you de for the new em
thank you thank you we finally have um
for be now thank you so much tble milk
milk thank thank
you they're super adorable and they look
super
good even tiny they look super
good I've always wanted a be boo
thinking cuz I I I think all the time so
huh I I'm always using the thinking
emote
H
oh oh it's nice to have my
own yeah you thank you for the super
rock rock good luck with the H SE B and
thanks for the new emote surprise yeah
thank thank you thank you for you know
providing people with so much amazing
fan
work artist
amazing um w p thank you for the super
rock rock I'm hold the new emotes and
don't kind of direct death grief to
allow them to be used um and with the we
purle emote I can use that every time I
miss the stream and show off my
suffering yes
bo
bo I see than for super rock rock really
loves the emot thank you de so happy for
you thank you thank
[Music]
you thank you for super rock rock what
you give a boy with bad breath pigment
is this a joke what's a pigment if you
have fun with this you may want to check
a
biotic factor it's up
to like pigment like the color oh is
that
oh well like the
color oh
oh not the six players halflife nerd
survival very like this with skill roles
Etc ooh a btic factor
okay
pigment nice P
[Music]
nice ah sis Lynn thank you for the super
Ro uh
Rego Rego s thank you for the super rock
rock sorry s to thank you for this super
rock rock why are we getting to the
parkour civilization Watch Lock too bad
I was already watched
it she watched it of her own
up of her own
VI we got a live reaction it's so
[Music]
funny I I did I sent her the the 2hour
video I didn't think she was I only I
told her she only needed to watch the
first 5 minutes but then she ended up
watching the entire thing I'm so I'm so
proud of her so proud he so
proud yeah I thought you I thought I
only told her you only need to watch the
first 5 minutes here's the link and then
see she got too invested just like I
thought
yes it spreads now she wants to be a
parkour God as
well uh she thank you for the super rock
rock thank you for a super rock rock and
thank you for a super rock rock
rock ah y thank you for super rock rock
S1 thank you for the super rock rock
Peter thank you for this super Rock Ro
few tips bike have storage can put bikes
in bikes but not stack items when you
start Quest it Force resets house with
first invaluable books a deagle is best
pistol but hard to find no eat
glass I will eat
glass I want to you can't stop
n looks tasty if if if not edible why
look
edible
yummy crunchy probably would make good
ASMR bomb Goblin thank you for the super
rock rock love your casting for Elder
ring H except for one person G is 100%
Iron Fist
Alexander oh yeah I guess she she would
be Alexander I guess that would work
then who's blly
I
think Callie is 100% malath yeah I could
see Callie is
Mal
uh BL is full m in a trench
Co we can
FAA is rala I could see FAA is
[Music]
rala it doesn't work quite precisely
well yeah I need to think about this I
need to
cook I need to cook
Kyle is
Marica
sure no no that works Kyla is mar and
radon yeah yeah know that oh wait
actually that's
perfect that that's
perfect
yes a Sor czy thank you for super Rock
Rocky thank you for super rock rock
thanks for the same today hoping that
this D dysfun dysfunctional I said it
correctly before earlier to the
dysfunctional family of your stay strong
together for the last day tomorrow I
like this dysfunctional family we're so
strong we're so strong yeah we all have
a rooll we're all we're doing so
good hopefully we'll carry we can carry
everybody tomorrow for the big uh finale
boom boom season 1 finale be winner
three moms
yeah me and my me and my
oh me and my three
moms hi
Windows my thank you for super rock
thank you for joining s days to die
every day having fun with your buddies
oh got some of this oh gotty some of
this like I said didn't think I would
play every day but now I have the sense
of
responsibility as like a pretty strong
person in the server um I feel like I
have responsibility to to help Carrie
and and you know and not get you know
left behind because I feel like I
should I feel like I I should
help with with things you
know I did good I did good this this for
too uh what is it the
the explosives really really helped the
explosives explosives were really really
good um for for the hor
thing and see I knew how to throw this
time I know how I figured it out I
figured it
[Music]
out
um sorry sort thank you for super rock
rock thank you for super rock rock they
was speed running the whole emo hump
thanks I guess thanks what's next yeah
emote pinch cheek emote ye emote guess I
will just find a Japan move for the time
being ask Pebbles what emote they want
now what do you want
huh what do you want Pebbles
jetpacks no jetpack
emote laughing oh yeah laughing people
would be nice we don't have a laughing
emote
yet B well the gun bble gun is kind of
meant to be a pebble Bon but I
guess like I could make a
my own pebble
BG
wiggle wee
wee Katana what even use a katana emote
for would that even be
used would that would would that nine oh
I guess nine would work what what what
would what would a katana evil be what
would what would you guys use it
for
oh emo plus Guana don't talk to me I'm
sad don't talk to me I'm
sad h
I get more of it I
see bald no bald emot we're not getting
that
no plastic
chair well we'll see we'll see if if if
I make them you guys have to use them
though so pick things that you think
will get used a lot
um
no
no no
LMA thank you for super rock
rock
H
hello do you have any planned horror
game on the list to way for you and for
to continue home home part two hope you
learn some more about OS yeah I want to
I want
to um continue home sweet home with full
uh
moku is kind of having a rough
throat right now so I don't want to plan
anything just yet cuz I want them to
have time to time to recover and
stuff but maybe we should wait until I
get over to Japan and we can do a home
sweet home off Cloud where they just sit
behind me and I play it maybe so maybe
we should wait for that maybe we should
wait when I get to the pad and so they
can physically backseat me I'm not in ja
pad right now dang
it dang
it some gaslighting
me did you get a found ticket today dang
it
um crazy thank you for super rock rock
thank you for the fun stream your family
did a lot yet you haven't even
discovered the building mechanic part of
the game the game has a lot to it for
base design and building adds hundreds
more hours of game
play yeah we haven't even we haven't
even gotone
to like there's electricity cuz we can
get solar panels and stuff like that
right and turrets and stuff we need
season 2 season two of
this
yeah H are you fan P thank you for super
rock rock D thank you for super rock
rock um Zer kitten thank you for that
super rock rock
it was funny see you locked in into
gamer mode while everyone else was
losing their
mind
T I've been using your mug for my
bedtime tea despite my cat's attempts to
eat it good luck in the finale oh
yeah if you have the B mug it is very
eable by cats cats love knocking things
over so if you have a cat protect or
protect the be boo mug from the cats cuz
you know if you leave it on that counter
the cat's going to come up to it and go
boom boom boom boom bump bum bump and
then boom it's on the floor
so if you have be boom mug beware of
cat keep it safe don't let your cat eat
it it's very eatable
[Music]
I think we're going to be well prepared
for the finale I have a lot of bullets
still even though I use so many during
the during the hoarde we just got so
many back so now I just
need maybe to get that Magnum gun H or
SMG I need handgun Parts I need handgun
parts and then um
and more explosives yeah more
explosives
H cool thank you for the super rock rock
I here again to clarify the tii tongue
twister there are two main ones about
Grandma the so one is Grandma El long
gun the yacht the yay one is Grandma
sells seashells last time I sent say so
what
oh there's two Grandma ones rock
rock okay let me find the grandma
one but see you shouldn't Des nuted me
and because then that was like uh it is
sus because of the D nuts at the D nuts
made me like
[Music]
think where even is
ah yeah
[Music]
for
okay okay okay yeah okay who whoever
typed it thank you type it again type it
again type it again y y
[Music]
Yik
y
y l y n n y
okay y
y okay now done
okay
okay basically
basically it means Grandma's eating this
fruit and her is she's drawing a lot cuz
she's eating a fruit that's what that's
what the translation is um she's eating
a fruits and she's jeweling because she
eat the
fruit
[Music]
uh
is okay well there you
go there you have happy I did the tongue
twister and S thank you for super rock
rock uh hi people we need the rock
wrestler
emote maybe wrestling matches for M
while you're at it I don't think that's
legal for me to have the actual rock is
an emote plus I do have a rock emote
there it is thank you thank you pal I
don't think I can put the actual rock as
an emote because you know how it works
but there there's my rock emote right
there love the stream keep up the good
work thank thank you
[Music]
rock AKB thank you for yellow Super Chat
that's your comment yellow Super Chat
that is indeed a yellow Super Chat thank
you thank you rock rock it is yellow and
it is a Super Chat yellow Super Chat
wonderful rock
rock are you sure it's yell yes I'm sure
I'm not color blind do not Gaslight me
into thinking it is another color of
Super Chat okay
okay I saw what happened with Nissa
no bud thank you for super rock rock
congratulations on your move to Japan
baby yeah oh at tell were you able to go
to the coffee shop and read aesthetic
I'm not there yet it's a 3ish month
process I'm not there
yet it's been like a few days
what dang it tomorrow
then she's in Japan right now no I'm not
no I'm not hello how was I I've been
streaming every single day how is that
how is that supposed to how I didn't
even AR just this makes no
sense PE recorded uhhuh the whole the
whole 7 Days to Die things was
pre-recorded we've totally all already
played
sure sure
I knew it you stream on the plane sure
you guys are pre-recorded
sure two steps
ahead man I want to talk about what's
going on the internet but I don't want
to talk about it cuz you know I want to
get in trouble but I've been seeing all
the things on the internet about the
stuff I want to talk about it so
[Music]
bad stuff yeah you you know but do not
do not do
not
anyway um yay thank you for super rock
rock
um maybe we can get a babble Pebble hug
emote it's not like we user or anything
it's not like you do that to us Pebbles
hum I don't know do you deserve me
hugging you
emote I don't know if you deserve it yet
I don't think so I don't I don't know I
don't know we deserve she hates us she
hates us
we'll see uh it depends on your behavior
and right now I don't
think B boo hello yes it's me it's bi
boo hi hi Ki
wa I'm not on line still
El I tagged you on Twitter check it out
oh okay I look I look on
Twitter oh it's
the oh I did not hit you like
[Music]
that it's helpful a lot
did you not did you not see yeah that
didn't show my screen
oops I it was a little
trick it was a little it's a little a
little wee
trick
wee that's
cute yeah on my screen on my screen we
didn't even touch right I don't think I
don't think we touched on my screen I'm
going to have to look back and see
and see
uh what it was like on my yeah you were
way past
oh I poked her a
little I just poked her
[Music]
big we can perform in the circus
yeah our biker gang we can we can do
Road shows we can do like biker Road
shows where we all like pull up and like
do tricks on our bikes yeah and we can
like do those tricks where like you you
ride next to each other and then you
stand on on your bicycle and then you
swap bikes we could we could be a we
could be a traveling family performance
biker performance thing yes let's do
that
yeah do wheelies make the bike
jump do do the thing where like you go
you go and have the bike ride up the
truck while it's
driving do a three block 360 jump on a
bike bab yeah
be a parkour P let's do more tricks
together tomorrow thank thank you thanks
for the
clip sick
trick
bro okay there
okay where was
I I mean I never I've never I want to
ride a
motorcycle and think it's pretty
cool I'm okay with bikes I don't I don't
need training
wheels I I I ride bikes without without
the training wheels so it's the it's
it's the two wheels and not the and not
the training wheel
one can you reach the padd well here's
the thing I like kids bikes more because
like full grown adult bikes like I have
to jump up to like get on where where is
like kids bikes like bikes for girls I
can just I can touch the ground with but
like for adult bikes like I have to like
kick off and balance you know because or
else it'll like lean over because yeah
bikes bikes are too too tall because
when I when I sit on the bike seat even
if I lower it the lowest it's still like
I can't reach the ground with it
so so I like I like like kids bikes
[Music]
better small
leg are there smaller bikes to traveling
yeah but I can ride I can ride uh
what is it I I can ride like um adult
bikes fine
though it's
just I feel a little bit more unstable
cuz I have to
balance because you have to keep moving
on the adult bike because if you stop
then it it it goes
like it's inconvenient cuz I have to
make the bike lean a lot to to have it
like stay and my if I if my foot wants
to touch the ground then I it has to I
have to get off of it or lean like
really really far but I still can ride I
can still I can still ride adult bikes
fine
though mom mom
have you seen the meme in your comment
section from the stream on
Twitter no I haven't looked at Twitter
since I've been streaming is there a
[Music]
meme
huh me
there's picture of NY Tad gang
uh my arm cracked nice wait can I can I
get a punch crack punch
crack no I punch crack this morning so I
I don't think I can punch crack
today punch you know I like I like
punching my arm like really hard that
like it cracked it's
fun was that a sneeze no that was a
yawn or something I don't it was a
stretch
uh Peter thank you for
the super rock rock can you try
this this is
B I have Google
translate this is B
get
some
help Al why doesn't Ty have
spaces because it's tie it's so hard to
read I impressed you're able to at
any level also this is a red Super Chat
no it's yellow
well I mean Tai isn't the only language
like
that but Tai Tai
is doesn't really have too much
punctuation I guess is is um also a
little bit difficult because it it
doesn't have punctuation so you you have
to tell the end of the sentence by like
spacing and stuff like that and context
uh may think for a super rock rock thank
you for your hard work by the way a new
flavor of family Ticky is now available
and I'm not there yet tell Japan to stop
stop wait till I'm there wait to stop
making new things until I'm there okay
stop it stop coming out with new stuff
wait just hold on for like a couple
months just hold
on
oh wait just stop hold
on wait for me it contains panu Japanese
Citrus flavored jellies it was delicious
hope they sell it until after your move
stop itan
[Music]
M wait for
me
uh well are so cute I I I was I was
talking about I was talking about
um you know the other day of wanting to
get a cat in Japan and they're like Bill
we heard we heard you might want to get
a cat ja pan if you get a if you get a
cat ja pan we take care of it we can
catch it for you we can we can we can
we'll we'll we'll take care of it
whenever
whenever whenever whenever you want to
whenever whenever you whenever you're
busy or whenever you have if you have to
travel we can take care of your cat for
you if you get a cat Jaan people
they're so cute I don't do I trust them
though what if they eat my
cat what if what if it just
hungry they keep saying cats smell
delicious
and
stuff husky M
no not husky
M husky
[Music]
M um average aan Abomination thank you
for the super rock rock
[Music]
uh I'm not in Tokyo
yet I'm not in I'm not in Japan
[Music]
yes dang
it t go
[Music]
I well than for super Rock Rock Custer
Johnson thank you for the super rock
rock hot do thank you for the super rock
rock um sour clout thank you for the
super rock rock I was AFK when it was
relevant but here's my fun tour and UB
emote don't we kind of already have
o with with like this one isn't this
isn't this kind of UB already
is now is
[Music]
that that's emo beab is that emo how
many how many how many bees are there so
many B boys
[Music]
uh rainy nja thank you for super rock
rock hi people I know it's been a while
since you played H but do you
remember can you rank the bosses you
have fought so far in order if not you
should try to tell how night L
from all right once it was a society
of uh once it was the Society of hi
Callie hello welcome where just yapping
right now welcome
welcome once it was a bugs and there was
a thing
called um the radiance and everybody
worshiped her okay and then and then uh
and and then um the hollow King came by
what's the king what's the king called
and then the king came and he made it
his society and he was like my Society
is better be you The Pale King in the
pale The Pale King came and uh he was
like hey yo what up and he was like okay
bye and he so the radio was like dang it
bye okay so the radiance got mad since
no one was worshipping her anymore so
she decided to like corrupt people's
minds through dreams and the bug started
getting corrupted in their dreams and it
was it manifested in the orange Goose
stuff um and and Pale King was like oh
God this this uh this sucks how we're
supposed to fix this so the king um and
had an idea and was like okay we're
going to like put all the goose stuff
into like one thing but this one thing
can't get corrupted or else it won't
work we're going to we're going to have
a vessel uh take all the corrupted goo
thing and seal it so it won't get leaked
right Goose stuff the corrupted Goose
stuff so um they started making they
started making a bunch of babies but
they're not normal babies they have to
be like heartless and emotionless and
like fully empty fully empty um so so
they made a bunch of bunch of bunch of
bunch of bunch of bunch of babies
mindless babies um and eventually one
got out one one became the The Chosen
One the chosen one who who had become
the empty mindless emotionless vessel
for this corrupted goo and named John
Hollow Knight yes that's John holl night
but what happened what happened was John
Hollow Knight started to care he started
to feel he started to feel for The Pale
King so oh no that's not going to work
but they sealed him up anyway they
sealed up John Hollow Knight with the
corrupted goo but it would it didn't
work because John holl had feelings and
you know how What feelings
are they're dead weight uh so feelings
suck you shouldn't have them um and then
weakness exactly feelings are weakness
um
so so the goo started to leak out again
because even though it was sealed into
the John Hollow Knight it was like ah it
leaked out because he was not perfect
and then we come along and we're the
hollow night but we're better cuz we're
fully empty and Mindless and emotionless
we're the true being of the void and
we are the the true we're built
different yeah we're build different so
the hall and I is basically our our
journey to to
unseal unseal the the stuff and face our
brother
and and then face face the dreaming
disease and
that is basically the Lord of hollow
night I mean I summarized it pretty
good and also there's bu saws
everywhere not bad a b summary
Hornet okay you can really silk song
now you can you can really you ah it was
a brief summary it was a brief
summary Hornet was born from one of the
one of the important
people
yeah she's like a half
sibling I forget what she was made for
though but a spider lady
yeah it was made to say get
good yeah all right
anyway there there's your in nutshell
um C thank you for super Rock
Ro
D4 thank you for the super rock rock be
without knowing anything about the lore
can I get a lore summary of Silent Hill
thanks do s okay there's this guy who
looks like a mix of Ethan Winters and
Leon Kennedy I think um
and
he goes to a place with
a
hill that
is
silent
and he meets a
thing
called a pyramid head I think that's
from this series and and it's pretty
scary and um it's pretty
foggy um it on the top of the hill where
it's
silent um and he explores this foggy
Silent
Hill
and meets
monsters um and
um and
[Music]
does
things on the
hill and lore
happens and he tries to survive as lore
happens you got to be silent on this
hill and um he fights yeah he fights
John
pyramid
yes is is that it is that is that is
that is that the
plot that's all I know but that's all
you need to know
right and then some people find the John
pyramid really really sexy for some
reason because I always see people like
cosplaying like sexy pyramid heads for
something for some
reason like whenever whenever like
Halloween Rolls by I always see
like Pyramid Head cosplays on my feed
but it's
like
yeah you're searching how am I supposed
to search it I don't know anything about
Silent
Hill there's it's also like not guys
cosplay Pyramid Head it's also girls
playing cosplaying his Pyramid Head but
they're pink and and uh or something
like
that oh is a nurse monster I don't
[Music]
know
anyway so yeah p Pyramid
Head is a bad guy right is bad is bad
guy but people like Pyramid Head for
some for some
reason that's all I
know well no spoilers I don't know
anything about the game yet so I don't
really want to get
spoiled go we go go we in chat I want I
don't want we no spoiling we we we we
okay thank
you
um which shark thank for the super rock
rock congrats you move to Japan people
no not yet based on how frequently you
appeared during JP's nighttime slot I'm
pretty sure you've already moved Japan
right what do you mean I'm on the
morning
slot isn't it like only wait hold on let
me get four 5 6 7 8 9 10 8 9 10 11 12 1
it's only 2 p.m. over there it's only 2
p.m. it's it's it's barely afternoon
right
now what do you mean nighttime slot oh
meain
GTA but but but GTA GTA GTA I was on
both slots though what do you mean but
but GTA GTA I was I was streaming twice
a
day I was I was a
ball B knows jst too well well
yeah well yeah because I work for hollow
live obviously I know J I have to
convert everything into
[Music]
jst you you put you give me my deadlines
in jst and I'm like
[Music]
ah I always have to I always have to be
like okay they're giving me this
deadline but it's actually the day
before that I think it is because it's
it's it's it's jst so it's always the
day before I think it's due it's always
the day before because it's j t time
[Music]
ha Ling guas thank you for super rock
rock B is in emotional Rock without
feeling yes I have no
feeling what you are seeing right now is
uh me imitating What feelings are
supposed to be like
yeah I never understood in Kingdom
Hearts this this weird thing where it's
like nobody's don't have hearts but then
why are they and their their whole like
reasoning for that for why they have
emotion and stuff is like oh they're
using their past memories to imitate
what it's like to have a heart it makes
no sense though because like then why do
why is ax always get mad whenever
whenever roxus like does anything
dramatic like he gets legit mad and he's
like oh you're faking that you're faking
you're faking
mad huh he's just role
[Music]
playing it just works yeah I I I does
make say like how does how does nobody's
not have hearts they don't really feel
like heartless heartless beings cuz they
all have like emotion and they like feel
it looks it seems like they feel like if
they're just imitating using their
memories they're
like it never made sense to
me they are good at imitating okay
also why are nobody's the one without
hearts and heartless the ones without
bodies
huh Cinema
because Harless heartless are what you
turn into uh when when your heart is in
darkness so heartless is your heart is
your physical Hearts consumed in
darkness nobody is the physical shell
without a heart so nobody's have no
heart so nobody's are heartless and
heartless are no bues cuz you don't have
[Applause]
I um when do we get back to Kingdom
Hearts again um okay anyway well all
these yapping sessions the past few days
well it always comes back to Kingdom
Hearts
somehow because you
not and
man if only if only I could one
day fall
into the sky and then fall into the
water ocean and drift cinematically
while dreaming oh that'd be so
good with with music
playing
yeah that's the dream to cinematically
fall from the sky into water and drift
while while emotional theme song plays
so Peak so
aesthetic when you walk away
[Music]
uh right out thank you for super rock
rock people l d are my favorite campfire
lore ASMR would go hard yes I need more
I need more lore in my
repertoire of
Mind video game collection lore I need
more
more so like more things to explain
[Music]
thank you for the super rock
rock
um AK B thank you for the super rock
rock B what's your opinion on the a
wrong microwave edit and have you ever
thought about being in a microwave edit
how how do you know that I know this you
guys you guys were saying no we're not
Tik Tok no we don't watch Tik Tok no we
don't but then you know what the a Wong
microwave edit
is you know what that is but then you
say no we don't watch Tik Tok
no that doesn't make
sense I think microwave edits are cool I
could see I could see people um
um be
able be able uh doing microwave edit I
like I like beat drop edits though can
you make more edits of bble like can you
make can you make like the edit like we
using the song
like and then the Beat Drops and it
goes like that one can you do can you do
that one but edit it with beo like the
one where it goes like
up and then it goes like the slots sound
effect and
[Music]
goes you know that one yeah a dub step
yeah make people edits I like people
edits
yeah the microwave edit
huh why are you talking about the wub W
make people eyes of the W of the wub
W I know what song you're talking about
thank you someone knows what song I'm
talking about based off of my weird
sound effect Clues thank you
[Music]
what's the song they use that song edit
for for a lot of Demon Slayer edits like
the one with Demon Slayer where like the
the infinity thing opens and Everyone
Falls and like ah ah but then but then
but then like zenitsu comes and boom
just is asleep but grabs a sword and
he's like locked in the locked in one
yeah that's this is all I'm talking
[Music]
about haven't I haven't watched up to
that point yet
actually anyway a w microwave edit
it's okay I guess it's not my favorite
edit but I mean I could see the appeal
why some people would like that edit I
feel like it's a lot it's it's like you
if you're not using a stand like a
rotating platform for the microwave edit
you're like some people don't need the
the rotating rotating platform and they
just rotate with their feet and I'm like
wow that's
impressive wow for some of you I must be
talking like a lot of nonsense right
now like if you if you don't understand
what I'm talking about you must be so
confused
uh SW go thank you for the super Rock BL
RC KZ thank you for super rock rock
andana thank you for super rock rock my
Lord is being a person who likes to go
to the park and look at the birds and
people tell me
oh you are so cute and pure yes I know
beo too I love games and change to my
dark side that's kenana oh you guys have
Lord too
you guys do do you guys have peor have
you like thought up your your
Pebble what is what is your Pebble well
you do have Pebble because I saw the
pebble namicon for my birthday and there
was so much Pebble lore in it so you
guys do have Pebble I read it I read the
pebble yeah the pebble
M PE I still have it
so much l yes and you have stats too
it's
cute we used to have limbs n the Pebbles
were limbs in the pebble namon I may
need
to we need to talk we need to talk
that's not that's not you you added
limbs without we need I'm going to I'm
going to take them back yeah I I to take
them back he I need to take them back
from you sorry that's not allowed you
don't have perms for
[Music]
that oh yeah I tried to take the
the
engram personality test last night the
and and and and and and
and yeah and thingy but it told me to
put in my email and and stuff and I was
like well no I'm not signing up for
anything to to get to get the uh to to
get the the results no thank you so I
don't know the results because
like it told me to put an email I was
like well no things I'm not I'm not
putting in my Emil for
that so sorry I tried to take it I
finished it but I don't know my results
because they told me you give me an
email like no thank
you make a burner that's so much work
that's so much work why is it why don't
you just get the results
use a 10minute mail what's a 10-minute
[Music]
mail is this legal
okay how do you spell it n
[Music]
n
and
[Music]
and is there one that I should be taking
specifically that that you guys
use are we going to do another
personality test right here right now
yes we
are which which which
one
which do I just do the the the big one
which is which one do the people take
the
most is it
this an a ground any a ground test one
or do I
do the one from the other one there's
there's multiple different
ones which one do I do
Pi one okay I'm picking one this one
says the most accurate
test this one says the most accurate so
I will take the most accurate test okay
I strive for
Perfection
um middle I am a little bit of a
perfectionist but some times I'll just
be like ah whatever so I'm that's kind
of in the middle I work hard to be
helpful to
others yes I would like to be helpful to
others it is important to me that other
people like me yes I want people to like
me it's important to me to achieve great
things
um yes but not to the extreme
it's not it's not to like the extreme
extreme but I do want to achieve great
things um I make more significant
contributions than the average person
well I don't
know I I like I don't I like to think
that I make contributions but I don't I
wouldn't say that I make like way more
significant contributions than the
average person like I don't want to I
don't want I want
to like I
but
but uh okay
fine what not all the way I feel my
emotions very deeply accurate I have a
sense that other people will truly will
never truly understand me accurate
because people think I'm an ENFP and not
an infp
so
accurate I deep think I deep think
I
deep I think deeply about things
accurate I am prepared for any disaster
ah not
really uh it is important to me to avoid
pain and suffering at all times is that
important like my own pain and
suffering ah
un neutral it's not like it's not I
don't I don't like avoid it at all cost
like my own pain suffering sometimes you
just have to
suffer yeah if pain helps you carry
development
so yeah
next I seek out experiences that I know
will make me feel happy or excited yes I
see the positive in every situation I
think so I'm not afraid to tell someone
when I think they are wrong I'm a little
afraid I let other people make the
decisions um half the time I'm
very
flexible so I will make the decisions if
decisions need to be made but if someone
else needs to be making the decisions
I will let them so it's the middle it's
the middle I'm
flexible I appreciate having rules that
people are expected to follow eh they're
there but
like they're
there uh I'm concerned about security
more than anything else not really
um I think about a lot what will happen
in the future or sometimes but
like more than more than every I think
about anything else no
but I do think about the future
sometimes so I guess I'll put like a
little bit I don't fit in with ordinary
people I would agree to
this there is
rarely a good
reason for changing how things are done
no if it doesn't work I always finish my
chores last I do finish my chores but
last minute so I I'm going to put that
as middle because like you
know I'm always trying that to be a
better person I
agree I cheack carefully for mistakes
and errors I am not careful
now I like to be around people who I can
help sure I'm around help I like helping
people um I like to feel that I'm an
important person in my social
groups I like to feel as in I feel like
I'm important or I want to feel like I'm
important what is this asking
me I want to feel like I'm
important well I guess I want people to
care that I exist but I don't have to be
the most important
person I just want I just want people to
care that I exist I
guess it is important to me to be
successful I think so I like being
successful um the organizations I belong
to would not function well without
me I I
think a h i would
function fine if I wasn't
there but I like to think
that you know I make it a little bit
better you
[Music]
know I'm I'm going to neutral with this
I'm going to I'm going to go neutral
with this cuz I feel like I can RB
something positive to
it but everybody's strong
so we're here cuz of you so a thank you
yeah I'm going to I often feel overtaken
by
emotion H Dem of
emotions I've always felt different from
other
people this this seems a little like uh
to doesn't it like I feel so different
from other people I'm not like other
people I'm so oh I'm so different
yes I like to analyze things from every
angle
um do I
do do do I like to think I do like to
think about
stuff I'll do a little bit a little bit
uh I always have a plan for what I would
do if things go wrong not
really I avoid situations that bring up
negative feelings yeah I se excitement
yeah I'm good at seeing the bright side
of things when others complain yeah I
don't hesitate to call people out when
they are behaving
badly yes to an
extent like a little bit yes I'm
I'm I don't like trouble
but if they are if they are behaving
badly to people I care about then
no no you know I don't like conflict but
at the same time if it's people I care
about and people are behaving badly to
people I care about that
no I go along with other people want
yes to an extent yet
I'm
flexible I'm like I'm easy call I think
in terms of
like impression I guess so I I think
more flexible is is better word for it
yeah
um people should follow the rules
instead of doing what they feel like
doing
neutral I think you should follow the
rules to an
extent
but I seek out relationships that offer
me some type of protection what does
that
mean
like don't you seek out like
relationships with other people to
to like for or to like
people you want some sort of safety in
that
a relationships that make you feel
safe I don't I I'm kind of neutral to
this it's not something that I actively
think about I
guess I do this all the time well I I
make friends because I like the person
not because I want a mom to protect me
the mom mom thing is just like a cute
little cute thing but it's not cuz I
want to feel safe it's cuz I like the
person and want to be friends with
though I can clearly visualize what can
happen in the future I mean I can I'm I
have a strong imagination so I can
clearly visualize a lot of things
including the future
average people find me a bit weird
yes or else I probably wouldn't be here
so
yeah I like to do things as I've always
done though I'm not really a
routine person too much I am consistent
when I need to be but
like I'm more
spontaneous
versus
routine I am I am again
flexible I persist until a task is done
extremely accurate this is the most
accurate one I persist until task is
on I spend time to discover and correct
my faults and weaknesses uh I'm not
spending time to discover my weaknesses
but if I discover one I'll try to
correct it I guess but I'm not spending
time to be like oh what do I do badly
I hold myself to high standards I think
so I think I do I'm a natural caretaker
I think I do I want people to admire me
h i mean a little bit but like who
doesn't
but like in like a inspirational kind of
way not a
like I'm so much better than you sort of
way I want to achieve a lot in my life I
think I do if I'm honest I feel like I'm
a bit better than other
[Music]
people I don't want to think I'm better
than anybody
if I don't I don't I don't think I'm
better than any but I'm Different
everybody's different but I don't want
to say I'm like better than anybody else
so I'm going to I
know I'm just going to neutral that
one I feel a sense of grief for what I
have
lost um I am Fort enough to not
have you know lost too much
so
yeah uh I'm an unusual sort of person
sure I take time to understand things
more deeply than most people do I like
to
think emotion oh I I like think I'm
empathetic I I
guess
so I think that's
accurate a lot a lot of these questions
makes me feel bad like I'm thinking like
oh compared to other people I'm so weird
oh compared to other people I'm so I'm
so more than other people I don't like
that
[Music]
it makes you honest with
yourself it's important to me to be
prepared for any emergency I think it's
important to be prepared but am I
actively thinking about being prepared
for any emergency not
really I distract myself from any sad
feelings that arise I'm pretty good at
distraction yeah I often make change is
in my life when things get boring
yes I tend to be more optimistic than
most people I think
yes I don't like the people comparisons
but I think I I am quite an optimist so
like have to be honest about that
um tell people what I think even if it's
hard to here I
hesitate because I care about what
people like feel too much I don't want
people getting upset
so I will hold back
sometimes um rather follow the group
than push for what I want neutral
because
sometimes again it's about
flexibility I'm flexible
so sometimes I'll push for what I want
but I'm flexible as in I'm perfectly
happy with
what the group pushes for too I guess
but I will push for what I want as
well so neutral cuz I'm both feel more
comfortable in organizations with a
clear hierarchy not
[Music]
really uh and that's something I was I
was surprised with in in Hollow live was
like wow everybody treats each other
pretty
casually including staff and stuff so
I like I like that about here is it's
all it's pretty it's it's pretty it's
more
like I guess casual than I coming in I
was afraid of it being I
guess take measures to protect myself
and my loved ones from
harm uh
again I'm not at actively thinking about
that I make plans for many years into
the future no not
really I am unusually unique person I
like to think I am
unique I just like trying new methods
and prestiges no I like doing weird
stuff focus on my responsibilities and
my duties yes I have a sense of
responsibility look at seven days to die
um I feel a duty to keep playing so I
can help
Carrie
um read books to help me be more
productive or better at what I do you
mean watch YouTube tutorials
I is new
toal I don't really I don't
really look at a lot of self-improvement
media not
really
um a lot of pressure on myself to do
things right
um a little bit but if I if I fail at
things like I realize my myself that I'm
not really afraid to be bad at
things like if I'm bad at a game during
stream I don't really care you know I'm
not really afraid to be bad at anything
so
yeah I take initiative to help other
people and make their lives easier I
like to think that I help other
people put an effort to make a good
impression other
people I'd like to think I give with a
little bit of a good impression or like
to make an effort to like be good
set ambitious goals for myself I do have
some ambitious goals for
myself but I also struggle with being
too because I am flexible and because
because
um because I I am too easily
satisfied so I have to say amb this is
go for myself or else I would be too
satisfied
because yeah I I am too okay with
things I'm too okay with like how things
are and stuff or like even if something
is even if something is unfair to me if
it is explained if like someone tries to
explain it and I'm like Oh that's oh yes
that's fine I guess so yes I am too
satisfied easily okay with things so I
must set goals to myself or else I will
be too okay with the current status
quo I'm an important member of my social
groups
[Music]
um I don't like
this I am a member of my social group
I
don't
uh I would like to say that
like you know everybody's important is
an important member
of there there's the social group
but this is stealth a
steem okay I'm a little important there
we go I'm I'm I'm a little
important I can describe my emotions
with lots of depth and detailed accurate
I often feel like an outsider a little
bit I find my mind to be a very
interesting place ew it is so
interesting
okay I am always aware what go wrong in
a situation oh a lot of these are like a
lot of these questions are are like
oh what happens if things go wrong is
that is that somebody's personality type
like the person type of person will be
like careful of
like what if or something
anxiety I have many ways of aving
situations that get me down uh I
mean neutral I guess I'm always up for
Adventure sure I believe that things
usually work out for the best yeah I
stand up for what I believe in even if
it upsets other people when I have to
yes if it's like something within my
beliefs that I will not waver in then
yes I will stand up for it um I'll often
let people take the lead neutral to this
it depends on the
situation if there are people who want
to lead I will let them lead if their
leader needs to be happening I will lead
depends on the
situation
um I just like people who disrupt things
by breaking the rules eh that's
interesting as long as it doesn't hurt
anybody is interesting make alliances
with people who can help me stay safe
and secure I'm not thinking about that
when I make alliances with people I just
People for People I'm often looking
ahead towards what is coming next um
it's in my mind the future but the
present is just as important I think
because if you're always thinking of the
future then how are you enjoying the
time you have right now
uh I have different interests than most
people
um yes if most people are normies
traditional way of doing things is the
best way
now I think tradition is good and we
should keep tradition in but if it's if
the traditional way is bad or it could
be improved Planet go kind of neutal
with that is balance have a
balance um responsible and reliable
person I think I am reliable and
responsible yeah I have a lot of plans
on how I can improve myself I'm not I'm
not actively thinking like how do I
improve myself today but like if I see
an instance of when I can improve myself
I will so
neutral I make sure that I'm I'm pretty
happy with how I am
now I I'm I'm
pretty happy with how I am as a person
so like
I make sure even the smallest details
are
correct I'm not that
careful I'm a little I'm I careful but
not careful at the same time I enjoy
caring for others and their needs yes I
like helping
people uh I want to be a person that
others can look up to I think so
at least a little bit I push myself to
succeed I think so I make important
contributions to my community I think so
a little
bit I rarely have strong emotions super
inaccurate um I feel like I TR never
belong in social
groups
um neutral
I want to learn as much as I can about
how the world works I like
learning it's important for me to
understand what can go wrong in a
situation again I'm not really actively
thinking about what can go
wrong yeah it depends on the the people
I guess that question so I'm neutral
with that takes steps to ensure I don't
feel sad or
lonely steps to ensure I I mean
what do you mean by step to ensure also
we're almost
done uh I prepare no I don't really
prepare for it trying new things keep
life interesting yeah I'm an upy person
yeah I am usually the one to take a
stand when others
won't um
I will if no one will but to be honest I
will hesitate because I don't like
confrontation and I don't like people
being mad at me I will if no one else
will but I will hesitate so I won't go
all the way um I got to be honest with
myself I got to be I got to be honest
with myself yeah
um other people have stronger opinions
than I do I think so I think I think
other people do have stronger opinions
than I do because
huh I have strong opinions but I'm also
flexible so other people probably have
more rigid opinions than me uh um
everyone has a role to play in society
and a duty to do their
best well you don't have to do your best
you can do whatever you
want sometimes it's hard to do your best
all the
time
so you know I I'm neutral to that I
guess I'm concerned with protecting what
I have I think I want to protect what I
have cuz I'm really happy with what I
have
but concerned about
it I have a good sense of what my future
holds eh I don't know what the future
can
hold is is out there is is woohoo things
change in any moment so I don't think I
have a good sense of what my future
holds I'm an average person with
ordinary likes and dislikes
nah I try new ways of doing things just
to see if they will work sure yeah I
have a great deal of willpower I think I
have a good sent of willpower it's that
stubbornness self-improvement is a major
interest of mine I do think oh this one
you don't need email
maybe oh what is this
can I no answer this no I don't want to
answer any of these I don't want these
things
to hold on
calculating
[Music]
calculating what you I have to unlock my
full
report I did this so I did this so
long I did this I took this test so hard
why what what is
oh it says seven it says I'm a seven
what does that mean my high my biggest
ones are 74 and
two no it it says unlock my full report
but it all it says a little preview
about your type
and
and it says it
says in in the pie chart
seven sens are defined by their desire
to experience everything good and
pleasurable that the world has to offer
while avoiding pain boredom and
limitations all sens appear enthusiastic
and fun loving deep down there a fear of
getting stuck in negative
emotions
ah instead they disconnect from their
deeper feelings instead focusing on
their imagination and zest for life to
keep them moving forward and Gathering
new pleasurable experiences oh yeah I
see
that oh yeah yeah I see
that
I did that tell you about me that was
fun I like personality
TP my biggest ones are 7
[Music]
two
uh my smallest one is six
my saw this one is faked I
believe okay it's okay like in the order
of biggest to smallest it's like
seven and then two four and
then after two and four the next biggest
ones are
three five and nine and then the next
one is eight and then the smallest one
is
six I don't know what that
means I for those of you who who know
personality test I'm not paying P one L
why
why why pay dang
it
no can I so can anybody tell me what my
what this what's my personality type
from this land
just take 16 well I've taken 16
personalities already I'm infp if you
take 16
personalities
okay
well is there any supers left I got
distracted with personality stuff
yeah just a tiny tiny tiny
tangent
um py Clips thank you for the super Rock
Ro d one thank you for the super rock
rock please give us limbs no h demon
Chef thank you for the super rock rock
Justin Reinhardt thank you for the super
Rock Bock your personal T are in says
your personal is cute we weren't even
testing for that but you're just so
beeping adorable that even the test fell
in love with you oh cute thank thank you
cute yes
hey thank you for the super rock rock I
come from the future and suggest you to
never start a personality quiz without
checking if you need to pay for the
results D it
D
no first the email and then you got a
pay date it's just a scam it's all a
scam I don't need to know about myself
it's interesting but whatever I don't
need a I don't need a website to tell me
about me I know about me already
dang it it's
[Music]
just so what are your guys's and the GRS
what are your guys's um personality
numbers what do the numbers mean for you
what's your number
huh 9
4 what's the w
mean what's the w
mean 4 6
8 7 W2 what's the w
mean your second largest one it means
Wing oh which side you lean
to so
so either 7 W6 or 7 W8 let me
look yeah I probably 7 W8 then because
because six was my lowest
one maybe I don't know I don't know what
this means
is it it is it does it always have to be
the number you're next to or is it the
one what are the doers
mean I don't
no my next biggest number is either two
or four
so so it's seven and then my next one is
like my next biggest one is either two
or four apparently from the from the
chart I'm going to have to research this
later I don't know well I hope you
learned a little bit about be to
maybe you don't know what the numbers
mean but maybe you learned a little bit
about me from me actually taking the
test
[Music]
so that's enough distraction
for the
day we got completely T it was kind of
fun to to take test though I like taking
test sumary evil you I knew that
though
um AK be thank for a super rock rock b i
deep thinky of what it would be like if
we didn't deep
thingly dang it
stop making fun of me I'm leaving now H
bye
okay dang it um see you tomorrow for the
finale of season 1 of 70s die bye-bye be
bo later thanks
for taking a personality test with me T
seven
we um
be later bye-bye
[Music]