[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
can't move it
uh
are you guys ready for a little surprise
or a big surprise
yeah okay
sit down for this
you have to sit down for this
sit down
[Music]
are you sitting
put on the seat belt
put it on
safety first put on the freaking seat
belt
[Music]
okay okay
yay
[Laughter]
welcome to my office
at kfb
hey
look look at all those details
look look look i know you need to you
need a minute don't tell you need a
minute you need i need a minute too oh
my god do i have some wait how about the
whole life
stick as usual here and should we show
you quickly no okay actually i don't
have so much time i have a strict time
schedule
uh that i have to follow we'll talk
about the office a little bit later but
i just want to um get you guys all
seated in here
let's turn on some music
yes
do you hear that music
that nostalgic music
one year anniversary
yeah oh you saw the casper hole
yay one year one year one year
one year what
oh my god yeah i have a frog i have a
frog
it's spinning spin
yes i want to give a shout out first
first of all to eden exile for uh doing
this for me is a anniversary gift
just a gift yes
and he made it so quickly
he was like yo do you want an office for
your anniversary as a gift and i was
like uh
yes hello oh my god for sure oh you
don't hear it okay uh
now you hear it
now you do hear it
now you should hear it
you do right yeah eden eden is the same
person who made the kitchen the kfp
kitchen and all kinds of other extras
for me
thank you it's so cool
i feel so cozy in here we'll talk about
the details and all that later though as
i said we have so many things to do guys
so many
uh i am planning uh my stream has been
scheduled for three hours with a strict
schedule so please stay with me what
we'll do today is we are getting two
special special guests
two
uh kind of loud okay giovanni
[Music]
and the fine finally i'll reveal some
secret secret
kfp recipes
or similar things
and
then i will be singing some things for
you
a little mini mini mini mini live
then i may or may not read a letter to
you
then at the end we'll watch the debut
stream
in the third hour
yes
special guest
[\h__\h]
[Music]
office party
oh my god
yes yes three hours oh so the last thing
that we'll do is watch the debut stream
yeah oh my god this is such a
exciting
exciting day uh and i've been over the
past few weeks uh very very busy kind of
stressed out but finally this day has
come
and uh i want to say also not only my
solo anniversary stream is exciting but
also
the collaboration that we're doing
later for me it's basically still today
uh for me it's 2 a.m
um so two hours after midnight right now
it's 5 p.m here but so in like a couple
of hours there's the collaboration on
amelia's channel
and that one is
going to blow you guys away because we
prepared something crazy and i i um
spent the like the last night setting it
up
and
so look forward to that
yes okay well
she's just a show we get started i'm
kind of nervous i'm pretty nervous
again
[Music]
okay the first guest
i'm sorry but
uh the first guest speaks the glorious
language of the glorious nippon land
nihongo
and it's the first time uh
we will talk to one another
so forgive me if we will not speak
english for a little while but it will
only be a short call so
um don't mind us
uh look forward to the translated clips
i suppose
i'm so nervous
[Music]
checking if if this person is ready
love it
oh my god i'm so nervous let's turn off
the bgm
turn on the desktop audio
it seems to be daijoubu
okay
wait i've never talked to them before oh
my god okay our special first guest
is none other than
who is my artist my papa
as you all should know and also the
artist of blackrock shooter steins gate
and so on
uh so an absolute legend i'm i'm nervous
like
can't you see that ah
yes
[Music]
foreign
okay
[Music]
know
[Laughter]
[Music]
a
um
[Music]
oh
okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
is
um
[Music]
oh
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
what's up
[Music]
oh my god
you guys need to watch a translated clip
of that
i pressured him i pressured him on
providing like giving me the
uh
permission to take off my belt and
become a phoenix and he was like
but there's no guarantee that you'll
actually become a phoenix though and i'm
like ah
why are you trying to tell me
yeah an interesting experience weird
experience never never like i i uh kept
up on me we have
written before of course discussing
things and all that but uh never
actually talked like this
i've heard his voice before on a
different stream where he was a guest
but this is like the second time i hear
his voice and the first time i hear it
directly
uh directed at me oh my god and he was
definitely nervous
but funny
oh man
his hesitations are
really funny so
and i don't know if you know this but in
japanese we kind of teased something
and and i would like to show you
that so let's switch our scene a little
bit
[Music]
here we are still in my office
uh
and with a screen
wait now i didn't show you the actual
the screen can actually like wait a
second
let's see
[Music]
there it is
i can make this spring calm down yay
so
i am
i know that my audience
especially the artists in my audience
are very eager
to see
a reference sheet of takanashikiyada
because it's been a year and we still
haven't shown it and like in the
beginning it was like i think there was
no actual character sheet
and then eventually hooked papa made one
but it was like a weird time and he was
like i don't know when when i when will
i reveal that
there is no good timing
and i was like okay
um
how about
under one year it's a frog
he's like almost
almost getting out of the water don't
get out of the water you'll die for frog
frog
so anyway i've come to you with not only
my character sheet but even more
extremely surprising and exciting things
so please take a look at the screen does
everyone have their eyes on the screen
yes yes yes look
it is time for the character shade the
moment you've all been waiting for
because no one knows what my back looks
like
i will show you in
three
two
one
[Music]
make it bigger okay even though the
screen is there but for your sake and
screenshotting's sake i'll make it
bigger for you
there it is
yes i have the little tiny wings on my
back that are part of the uniform and i
have a bow in the back yeah
yes
look look look at it closely
[Music]
beautiful isn't it
respectfully
[Laughter]
are you happy now
you want to get a bit more of a close-up
here there you go
uh he actually made my shield in 3d
himself
as you can see here that that is
actually a 3d i think he did that
because it's easier to uh draw me after
that
because the shield is yeah
pretty cool isn't it
yeah
that is my character sheet you're
welcome
you're welcome but that is not all
madame
so
are you guys interested
in seeing
how kiara was created
now this is a little bit for wall
breaking
but i want you guys to see it because
it's funny
[Music]
this is really really really
exclusive
yes proto type kiara drafts
of
the phoenix
i have a bunch of them
oh my god this is so special
i don't know if i can show it
no i do i do i did get them from hook
papa so
of course i can show it but that
makes me nervous
phoenix
being born prototype of me
you want to see it
[Music]
all right all right around let me show
you tatan
[Laughter]
i used to have
shorts
and
some
kind of belt
on top of me let's make it bigger that's
the screen
and my hairstyle was different my my my
feathers were kind of part of my hair
and not like you know
but this was like different ideas
what is that
[Music]
so i actually really like those uh the
hair ideas of a and b and the b is uh
getting closer to my current one
but yeah the shorts actually i i think i
remember the shorts
i might i might go crazy i might be
going crazy right now i don't remember
the the plastic belt that goes through
my whole body i don't remember that part
i didn't see that
but i remember uh i think i remember
destroying
yeah really cool isn't it oh
and my my hair color changed
a little bit too like it uh the one in
the middle
is the closest but the left one and the
right one are a bit more like yellow
type orange
but it already had this
uh the top where it didn't really change
much at all i think
and uh the hat
yeah
today i'm not wearing my white hat
because i'm in the office i'm not
cooking
but yeah so that's number one
and then after that came chat
this
[Music]
i don't know what that is
i don't know why that is on there don't
ask me
so here uh it's the same hairstyles but
a few different variations of the
uniform and i like that mini skirt from
the
right one
but i do think it's good that the the
shirt
uh isn't there anymore
because we do like to see a little bit
of a belly button don't we
and he did keep those um
the socks from number b
he did take that he did uh bring that
one along so it's a nice combination i
do like the stripe on the uniform on the
left one the middle the white stripes i
don't like that
and you know what i also really like the
feather on the top of the head that
stands up next to the next to the beret
it's pretty cool too
also my shoes were a different color
than they are today they're like a neon
yellow in that one
but they changed they're now like bluish
mostly
anyway
so that changed into
[Music]
i don't i don't know what he's
trying to do there
let's just ignore the right side
he was uh drawing a pet that that could
be with me probably i know it's a
similar hairstyle but that's not
supposed to be me that's supposed to be
maybe a pet
to go along with me
so here a few more variations of a skirt
mostly changes here but he seems to have
at this point decided and settled on the
on the hairstyle
because it's not changing here so this
is where uh he probably was like hmm
maybe maybe a tight skirt would be
better
not not shorts for whatever reason
i like both
so but at this point it was a it was a
tight skirt but it had a white collar
like my sleeve it was interesting
he's getting there he's getting there
definitely
this is really cool um i think
uh i think the next one is the one that
i actually saw for the first time
oh
yeah
uh
so at this point he settled
on the hair
and on the fact that it should be a
tight skirt
but playing around with the colors of
the freaking
socks look at the right one i think he's
trying to give me some
chicken legs or something cause they're
yellow
freaking unbelievable
i need to call him again and confront
him with this this is this
[Laughter]
color variations that's right sounds
nice well um also if you look closely on
the right one he's oopsie playing around
with the eye color as well like a little
bit more of a bluish one but
mostly
the eye color didn't change
and
yeah the uniform the the left the one on
the left is like the closest to what i
am today
and i think the left one is what i saw
uh
and the first time
what the first thing where did it go oh
well next one then
got it
i lost it where is it
where did it go
where did the last one go okay
our friend we never won a copy of it on
screen
um
number
this one
oh that's huge oh my god
[Music]
there
well you guys see this don't you
huh
transform
fit to screen it doesn't work
ah what oh well yeah well anyway this is
the first thing i saw and the belt here
is different
the belt
[Music]
i'm not sure what that was that's like a
a flame and some stars and like i don't
know an apple or a
heart or something like that
oh and awesome oh my god
nah nah this this isn't even the first
one i just thought that was one step
before that i think because i don't
remember having that um
what's it called
on the collar on the collar
the
yeah the pin the little pin
[Music]
a shashlik
shashlik
the shashlik pin
i don't remember that in the past that
was not there
but he changed the shape of the cooking
hat thingy
yeah
and still those shoes but uh they
changed after that they're still in a
very rough state at that point so i
guess he wasn't sure
during this time what they should look
like
so
[Music]
that is not all guys
i still have more
mother
and the next one is very special and i
actually i didn't
know about this
uh possibility
in the beginning
i didn't know about it at all
this is the last thing i will show you
and share with you
guys
[Music]
my obs
is like oh dear
i put on studio
mode and throw that on screen
in a way that is not too big
okay nice
okay
are you ready for this
[Music]
i could have been short-haired
wow
was thinking of making me short-haired
this was pretty
late
late uh game
already because the uniform there is no
more pin the hat is already the latest
one
and all that it already is all in place
but he was thinking about different
hairstyles
and let's look at it a little bit bigger
so this is this is me
then
this one
let's go let's go from here
so you see me
there's two different types of short
hair here
[Music]
i do like the middle one to be honest
but i think it's good that i ended up
with longer hair because the
the the feathers they work much better
with long hair i think personally
[Music]
not i like my long and fluffy hair you
know
i like it
yeah long hair is best but maybe in the
future
i wouldn't mind cutting my hair
um but a little bit longer than this one
and that's a bit too short for my
personal taste like it doesn't quite
suit me so well i think maybe the middle
one but a little bit longer like up to
the end of the feathers or like where my
neck
uh
on the on the bottom
that's that's the length that i could
get in with
like amelia length
so big big big thank you to papa for
allowing me to share these
concepts and prototypes of me with my
audience i think this is really really
really special i was i was so excited to
show you because it's like
[Music]
it's an insight into
what could have been but i think the way
it ended up
really like matches well and and uh
[Music]
i think like the shorts would have been
nice would have been nice indeed the the
blue shorts so maybe even
shorts in the same color as my top maybe
like a mixture of it
um so i don't like that they are
extremely tight though
so
yeah summer version short hair oh
maybe maybe next year maybe next year
maybe next summer um
thank you for that that is the first
segment
uh of the stream
done
so let's go back to the normal
office
[Music]
i'm back
now
uh oh oh my god i forgot something i
forgot something that i wanted to do in
the beginning
uh i received another present
that i will share with you right now one
second
[Music]
it is
something
for the members
hmm
one second
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
hey memphis
please
refresh your browser
refresh your browser for some new emotes
especially
one drooling emote and one party chicken
emote yay
for from christina manzanita thank you
i love the drooling one
thank you
that's such a lovely present i hope you
all like them and we'll use them as this
one especially today but maybe also
during karaoke streams or
um all kinds of all kinds of
celebrations maybe if we reach a new
milestone
like 1.2 1.25 million for example is the
next milestone
and if you haven't subscribed yet please
subscribe so i can reach that milestone
yeah thank you they are unlocked now so
you are welcome to use them thank you
thank you
that's so cool
i was thinking uh
i mentioned that in the minecraft stream
i think
that i would love to have a drooling
emote at some point
and then christina manzanita drew it
and gave it to me
for my anniversary yay thank you thank
you
so now i want to talk a little bit about
this
uh
new layout
but i'm looking for something to point
with
where was that whole live
pen light that i used the last time
anything anything i can use
oh i got cucumbers
[Music]
don't ask me whatever it's just
cucumbers okay okay so let's start that
um
let's start here my uniforms
this is my working uniform so
course i have more than one
and then here in the foreground there's
a tree with oranges oranges because i
love oranges
a little casper hole over here
floor
that was created after
my w
our dear friend casper you like you like
uh
cucumber
nah you don't like veggies he's not
coming out for our cucumbers
unfortunately
and we have some menu ideas
of course all of those are vegan no
chicken in there but chicken burrito
vegan yes
approved
so cute totally vegan
totally this is a fake chicken
pineapple and everything definitely
and mangoes as well
uh
chicken what this is too small chicken
chicken bread something like that
chicken lasagna no
no no no taco burger talk to ina about
the taco supply
and a vegan chicken salad yes salad is
real food it is it is it is a love salad
mmm chicken salad really good crispy
crispy chicken on uh fried chicken on
salad mmm
yes vegan of course and vegan chicken
pasta
approved approved
now we have some books here you you guys
are a lot loud welcome to zoom in to see
what those books say
then we have a best boss monk and we
have some images some pictures from
great memorable collaborations we have
my potential nameplate we have a lot of
denied applications
i'll go wait use your room release for
oh my logo in the back by the way kfc
will go
some plushies here we gotta have some
plushies in here you know i like the
cute stuff and here we have some of my
weapons some of them were used in my
yakuza streams as well we have a whole
talk poster but it's cut off because you
never know who the next guest is
we have my singles and my covers which
are apparently exactly free by free oh
interesting i didn't even realize that
and then we have all the whole talk
uh recordings here
wow it's already been so many
oh
that's that's interesting yeah we can
put them into these pieces of television
now here's your chat and uh
yeah some videos i'll put some more in
here uh when i have more time but i was
on the time time crunch oh and by the
way
i don't know that that frog kiara was so
freaking cute i had to like put her here
as my pet
yeah she is now
enjoying
a great having a great time in that bowl
yeah she's happy she's spinning
it's too late
i'm done she sent me a pen light to use
but it's too late i used the cucumber
now i'm already finished
yeah
so
do you like the new office guys
up until now we didn't have one and i
was like at one point i want to have an
office and at one point i want to have a
kitchen and eating excel is like leave
it to me leave it to me
[Music]
yeah
it's really cool he said he still wants
to add some things later on
um
maybe maybe something in the background
behind the windows so i'm looking
forward to that there's still many
possibilities this is not even the final
form of my office but i'm really excited
to have an office finally yeah now we
can do
a lot of things here like the super chat
reading we can be here or we can be in
the kitchen the kitchen is still also
one of my favorite places to be
yeah
eh orange peach of course there is no
ren's picture are you blind
it's over there here next to the
peculiar picture that's that's sunday
that's an energy
of course why would i not have an orange
picture here i have to i love negativity
yeah
[Music]
well there's a lot of work here to do as
you see there i have a lot of
applications in front of me
and i will have to work on after the
stream but for now
i want to focus on my time on you guys
let me check
uh whether or not my next guest
is ready are
you
ready
baby
because i have another special guest
um
if you guys missed it if you came in
later huge papa was the first guest if
you missed it he had to be there in the
beginning because he sleeps quite early
and he said because he's old i didn't
say that but he sleeps very early he
normally
sleeps earlier than this that's why i
couldn't move the stream it had to
happen happen in the beginning
um
so if you missed it then please check it
in the icard there was some tasty
interactions
yeah okay next guest is ready in one
minute
who do you guys think it could be
[Music]
i'm
extremely nervous about this next guest
okay it's interesting how you guys are
uh torn between mamaloni and mama tori
which have very similar names but are
two completely different people both
very important to me though
um
why
oh gemma oh you would love to hear genma
wouldn't you have gemma's mind gemma
belongs to me you guys have been trying
to take her away from me but i will not
let you
same thing with my mom mom though you
guys wanted to take away my mom from me
but my mom is my mom okay
oh kelly no no no no no
no no okay
next guest is ready
[Music]
i will mute my music
oh dear
diamond
[Applause]
[Music]
you help me
um it's my
mother
my
real live mother who has been playing
minecraft with me recently
mama tony
[Music]
okay mama please
be careful okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
no no no i know what you are
oh would you like to uh
introduce yourself don't say your name
don't say your name dog
my name is
i get use of it
well i'm mamatory i'm calling
from another planet also
and um
i want first of all
to thank your fantastic fanbase
okay for being so loyal and loving to
you
yeah despite you are such a
raging bird sometimes
and um thanks to them i think uh that
you've become a real full-time warrior
yeah but i i didn't i didn't watch the
end fight um
last night because uh after
one minute in
i stopped because my nerves no
i had to i had to pass that same same
yeah yeah yeah i understood
so yeah
um you've grown a lot
oh oh yes i have yes yes i agree
yeah you see i i i i i started out when
i was uh in in japan but uh now i'm back
in the glorious land of australia
yeah and uh yeah i think uh through
for this long time
many moves and many struggles technical
struggles and all that i have prevailed
and here i am yeah yeah i think this is
what uh this is what you are
you go to all the downs and ups and this
shapes you and um yeah
it made a good person out of you also i
think this year has shown
what a brilliant entertainer you are
even the worst events like uh when they
deleted your channel
yeah it was horrifying
but it was only for a few hours so yeah
but you made the most out of it
it was hilarious
yeah every debut
yeah
i have to draw my head if i have one but
you know
i was actually really surprised that um
you were watching my streams like and
and even if you were to watch my streams
i didn't think you would watch that much
but you've been watching literally all
of my minecraft streams and others as
well so yeah yeah
yeah
i agree very well when um
i i think it was your brother it wasn't
it was not it wasn't you it was your
brother i i didn't because i didn't tell
you right away right i think i told you
one month in one month in yeah yeah it
was one month he told me um
slowly speak slowly
he told me out of the blue
that you are now become uh had become a
youtuber
and i said yeah i sat there and how the
hell did he know before me telling him i
know i don't know who wants to sell all
this maybe because i've read it because
i think he uses reddit and we were on
reddit a lot on the top page yeah yeah
that was it that was yeah my sister saw
it too before i told her
yeah i said there and i thought
what the [\h__\h] is youtuber
[Laughter]
and he showed me the channel and i
watched one stream i don't know what it
was i think something mario related
and i sat there and i heard you and i
thought
what the hell is this this is my
daughter
why were you surprised i look like i
always you gave birth to me
yeah yeah you swear like uh like a
pirate and uh you you you said things
uh pooh that let even me blush oh come
on you swear more than i do
you
do but
most of all for me your development can
be seen your gaming development can be
seen in your minecraft oh yeah
yeah i watched the first one a few days
ago out of curiosity and i saw that you
uh started to play that game in third
person yeah and i thought
oh man
yeah because like to me it was natural
because i just prefer i always played
games that are in in third person not in
first person so i thought this was
normal but everyone was like turn it off
god kiana this is horrible
it was horrible
i nearly bite the desk
yeah so
i enjoy watching your stream not only
because you are my daughter of course
but because they are really entertaining
i never thought of that because i never
for me i never could imagine that i have
fun watching you playing zelda i i
didn't think you would also have so much
fun watching my streams for hours and
hours
yeah it's because
your reactions and your tangents and
all those things also
sometimes i leave the stream in the
background and wash the dishes and so on
it's like a podcast sometimes
but yeah yeah and
it's really funny when you're playing
especially if things don't work out like
plans
and they never do
yeah and i i'm always amazed what a kind
of luck you have in gaming
uh you know
especially minecraft other things i
cannot
judge but especially minecraft
the way you got your elytra it was
stunning
yeah yeah yeah my mom actually also uh
watches
sometimes like follows a little bit what
the other halloween members do in
minecraft so i think my mom is aware of
how long it took inna for example
or do you
remember how i got my first trident
without trying
that was
bla blatantly insane
i never have seen that i thought you
tried you you must be cheating
it's not possible
yeah but uh
before i forget
i want to say you have such a
extra ordinary crew you know your holo
myth family
all of them they are so great you know
for me it feels that's your second
family
somehow yeah
that's true
yeah yeah
and today is our one year anniversary
yeah
i hope
you have fun with being boss of such a
large fast food operation for many years
and of course i hope that i can support
you where i can a few eggs
when i get my
own employees yeah yeah i'm looking
forward to the deliveries
or maybe i can support you in playing
diablo with you and yeah
i know i have to carry you around it's
no problem at all as long as you
yeah do do you think
i am i will i will but i i think uh my
my the time when i played diablo on
stream uh the the closed alpha i think i
wasn't so bad i'd watch that no no no no
you did good you did good i i i wouldn't
have chosen this class but
you know i'm a little bit different
it's about
nice fries good visuals you know
and i hope some someday in the
brilliant future that is uh undoubtfully
for you in in in us inside uh we can
play uh
some sort of cooperative
shooter not shooter maybe some action
rpg i
yeah i read this moment ago uh
some new
uh game camera came out death loop it's
from the akane studios they
developed prey and
disordered i pretty i'm pretty sure you
will like that and
perhaps we can have a look at that step
by step mommy
yeah
you you
you know you you never recognize it but
uh since you play minecraft you play in
this game you play first person
and
the one point that is lacking is your
reaction and your panic models
guys i want to note here uh it is maybe
a little bit noticeable maybe you've
noticed hints of my mom's tangents she's
actually very proud just like me for
going on tangents
yeah i think i got that from my mom my
mom talks a lot but this is not even
this is not even close to it normally
normally she talks and talks and talks
like a waterfall like i do but
yeah
yeah when you got a talent to talk you
got to make something with it and yep
yep got to use your talents
excuse my coughing i have a cold
actually oh yeah oh yeah my mom is a bit
sick so i mean i think that was all you
you wanted to say probably
yeah
um
and you know
yes i can say a lot of things about you
oh
okay yeah
a lot of worries
and so on but i know you have to
uh
you have to follow a a certain schedule
today and so
yeah
it's okay it's okay uh i can i can move
some things around but but it's probably
better to keep it somewhat short but it
was really cool to talk to you with uh
in front of everyone i think they got
well they were everyone's really happy
to have heard your voice wonderful once
yes oh but stop it one thing i i i want
to point out
i'm really your mother
so stop pondering about
is he some sort of actor or what i'm
your mother
i'm her mother
she is she is i i know like for some
people it just sounds really crazy that
our whole family including my mother is
uh you know really really they we all
just like playing games and stuff and
and we've done it for many many years
and yeah now now my mom in the past i
guess actually you said that you're not
so much into minecraft anymore the past
few weeks months because you're sick of
it but generally yeah my mom just plays
a lot of games so it is what it is it's
not it's not such a
weird thing i mean
actually okay never mind when i was
younger i mean the other families around
me they didn't have gamer moms but i
think it's still not such a thing that
is unbelievable and it is what it is and
and thanks to that i i got into this
culture and and here i am
no when when we uh when you were younger
you and your brother
uh you used
to in school
um
when you went to school uh
you used to point that out you and your
brother to your friends that uh your
whole family is like a gaming family and
so on they all were to totally annuals
about that because
yeah jealous about that because they
hadn't
those sorts of things but
you know for me
it was just entertaining
it was entertainment it's uh
there may be people who spend the
evening in front of the tv or playing
cards or
don't know knitting or
no
yeah i don't know and we choose to play
and we choose to play together and uh
yeah it was fun and it um
formed a certain pound
around our family fun you know we can we
can i can talk with your brother or with
your elder sister or even with you about
games and it's nothing strange it's
nothing cringy or something like that
it's totally normal
yeah normally if we meet
we would sit
together and talk about games at some
point
endlessly
so you you told the story from the
vacation in italy where we played uh uh
uh magic the yeah yeah but but back then
i don't think i
uh had a
pc yet
i think it was maybe a bit after that
yeah yeah but this was also a thing we
did uh all together as a family
yeah and
you weren't you were so good at it and i
was just fooling around
i thought i was good but my boyfriend
and told me uh showed me how bad i
really was i was good because i had the
money to buy me the best cards for my
collection
you know remember
your deck was scary i didn't like it i
always had like a white or blue deck and
and i didn't want to look at your cards
because they're scary yeah he was scary
but
i was shown later on that i was a uh
yeah
not
oh my god mommy you already started
something just by saying the word
boyfriend
people are like going crazy anyway i
think we're going on tangents again but
um i think we should probably end it
here
thank you mommy for calling it
what chickens
give all your chickens kisses from me
course i always i give them kisses every
day
i'm pretty sure
okay can we can we get the auf
wiedersehen from my mommy at the end of
course oh
[Music]
thank you
oh my god
don't leave guys
she may have said of it as in but this
is not the end of the stream
yeah yeah well she's uh that's my mom
she speaks english pretty well has a
little bit of an accent a yeah german
german-ish accent but i think you all
understood her well
oh my god i was nervous during that ah
i mean of course my real name is
takanasi kiana of course it is but we
you know
makes me do this show all her life she's
called me something else for some reason
in her head in her head my name is
something else i don't know why i'm too
crazy crazy my name is tanka nasi kiana
so that made me nervous but it all went
well thank god
oh dear eh did you understand her well
very good english yeah
really honestly i
um i never thought that she would watch
my streams that much i told my family
one month in i'm not sure what my
reasoning was i think i wanted to
um
have like something to show
so that they understand what it is and i
wanted i like in the beginning i thought
it wouldn't be successful you know so
i didn't want to like show
them something that would be like kind
of embarrassing to me because it's not
not successful so i wanted to show it
after i had proof of
you know the fact that this this is
something
and has um
well
yeah a base a good base and it makes
sense and
yeah this is what i'm doing now yeah
understandable yeah yeah yeah yeah
but they kind of seemed to have found
out before me telling them
both my brother and my reddit and my
reddit both my brother and my sister uh
use reddit i haven't used it before
whole live i actually
uh only use it to check the whole i've
uh read it if i ever look at it but uh
yeah i didn't know and then apparently
um
live and told live english
were on the front page a lot
so that's how my my sister definitely
saw me
on there a few times even though she
didn't even follow the whole life
separated
yeah you use it the most in hell move
yeah i mean recently i haven't been
checking it that often because i've been
really really really really really
really really really really really busy
but every now and then i still check it
out yeah yeah yeah and i even comment on
the posts every now and then so
yeah that was my mom and uh
you see how nervous i was just now
that's the reason why i'm not putting
her on voice chat during minecraft
streams
so but at least now you've heard it
because you guys were really curious i
guess and i thought it would be sweet to
get here in here to congratulate me or
whatever give me a little comment about
my activities and yeah um i think in the
future
whenever we have my mom on my stream
if it's a longer stream it will still
i i still don't want to have her on the
voice chat because it's just too
dangerous you gotta understand me there
and forgive me there and but yeah um
at least you can always look back you
can make it you can try to make it or i
can try to make a sound board out of her
i sound bored of my mom
where i'm like
you know
push these buttons
it could be like [\h__\h] or like
a kick at the key or whatever oh
maybe i should make that
then people won't come into the streams
and be like yo this is the collab with
your mom i don't hear you mom where is
your mom where is your mom where is your
monk
and it's safe it would be safe oh think
about that all right all right all right
all right um before we continue let's
have a little break uh where i will sing
my original songs to you and then we'll
go back and read a letter and went to
debbie's stream shall we do that
you wanna hear
me sing yes yes yes yes yes let's
celebrate let's party let's get out of
this freaking office for a moment
and enjoy ourselves
hey
i got a new microphone
as an anniversary gift
thank you for making that for me
thank you and everyone else who's been
using the hashtag kianaversary
thank you for posting
uh all kinds of fan arts and other gifts
uh for me for my anniversary to
celebrate it together with me i really
appreciate it
yay and now
a little rendition
of my original songs
because in this one year i have released
three songs
and and they all mean a lot to me a lot
of work went into all of them and
they're very very precious to me
so i think i have to sing them
we will start out with
[Music]
is see if the audio is okay
foreign
[Music]
is
me
[Music]
i've been trying to find my destiny
but they keep pushing and pulling me
astray
if i go wrong what awaits me in the dark
could you tell me please
[Music]
dance and in the next lecture i promise
i will find you
hey
[Music]
my throat died there somewhere at the
end
[Music]
was released
somewhat soon after my debut
on thanksgiving at least for the
american thanksgiving
and uh
i
cannot announce details but let me tell
you for the one year anniversary of
hinotori i have something extremely
exciting and special planned
currently in the works
and will be
shown to you
when
the one year anniversary of hinotoni is
coming which is in october or wait
november when uh when's thanksgiving
i don't celebrate thanksgiving so i'm
actually not sure when was it again
october oh so next month let's go
november oh what the [\h__\h]
can we do it sooner can we do it sooner
god damn it i
[Music]
and with that we move on to the second
song of my original songs which is high
challenger with heart challenger
i wanted to
well with history i wanted to show my
cool side because i felt like
because i like idol music and all that
kind of stuff um when it came to
hinotori i wanted to go a different
direction i wanted to go into a cool
direction but for heart challenge i want
to go to go to
my my normal interest so like what i
would normally do something that is
typically me something that just
embodies me and my spirit and my energy
and therefore heart challenger turned
into a very cute and cheerful song
and it is about it is about love
and it is about valentine's day because
after releasing a song for thanksgiving
i thought it would be a nice idea to
release the next one on valentine's day
yeah so let's sing hi challenger
are you ready
this is when the whole stream heart
sound gel arc started
let's go
[Music]
oh
um
[Music]
is
um
[Music]
oh
is
[Music]
foreign
is
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
there's no one else in this world that i
would trade for you
[Music]
um
okay
[Music]
oh
yeah thank you thank you
that was high challenger my second
singer released on
valentine's day with
an amazing music video i'm really proud
of it
yay
[Music]
yes next one is spock's
my first single dad was released on
another special day i keep on releasing
these songs on special days special
occasions the next one was released on
my birthday and for sparks because
people were asking
for
something english rather than japanese
even though i personally just always
felt more
weirdly comfortable
singing japanese i did try
myself in some new waters with spikes
and also with a different producer
because sparks was
produced by and
made by
a kira
and the other two songs hinodori and
heart challenger were both made by gojo
kai
so it's a completely different style
and it was very very
um
interesting for me and exciting
and you guys are still very hyped up
about the song whenever whenever we
mention sparks people are like strange
so thank you guys so much for all the
support on my original music yeah i will
try my best to even though there's times
where it is quite frustrating and
um
yeah
uh
unfortunate things happening i i still
love making music i still love singing a
lot so i
don't want to give up
and eventually well we'll just
do more and more music shall we
so
please listen to
sparks
lying down on the floor
[Music]
don't know don't know what to do the
storm
losing is way
just take a chance and dance in the rain
cause you got the key never throw it
away don't forget don't forget what i
said
get out of your head life is only once
you make it you're gonna be okay
so go ahead and do it do it if you want
let's get to it everybody's gonna know
your name
cause sparks like
[Music]
so don't be afraid just your heart keep
your head and look and keep up keep
going
[Music]
you heard what i said get out of your
head life is only what you make it
you're gonna be okay yeah yeah so take a
step and move it move it unless you try
you won't get through it everybody's
gonna know kiana
[Music]
[Applause]
so don't be afraid just your heart keep
your head and again
you alive
[Music]
[Applause]
so
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
let's go
[Music]
yes
that were my free original songs thank
you for listening hopefully there will
be more in the future let me drink some
iced tea um
chickens in the back are vibing
one is sleeping apparently my my singing
is so
soothing
[Laughter]
[Music]
and back turn off the
echo no more reverb
now
let's turn on btm
oops double there we go
oh wait do we hear that wait you
probably don't
jump down here okay
[Music]
cool
the celebration is not over yet
we still are going to watch my daddy
stream together even though i would like
to skip on that
we're still doing it
but before that
before that
i want to
read a letter for you actually i forgot
to um
prepare a music for that hmm
uh how about
how about
my dad
[Music]
i think i saw something today
was it a hinotari hinotori piano cover
it was really new though
not
not that one
could be this one
[Music]
that's pretty nice but actually
surprisingly
even in piano
kino tony doesn't get very emotional
[Laughter]
audio stock audio stock should we go on
any stock
let's search for
an emotional song on audio stock
together quickly shall we do that
it was fun last time
emotional
when do i look up
come on yourself audio style give me
give me your bestest what is this
[Music]
i'm gonna cry if i play that
okay let's go with that
i chose you
better make all of us cry
audio stuff without the audio stock i'm
downloading it without the other stuff i
have a subscription so
rachel put that in my vlc let's go i
have a letter i know
what's going
on
okay it's quite a long one
uh
so i think i'll just
i'll just go with it are you ready
are you ready for it
i removed the microphone sorry it might
make weird sounds
that's what i thought okay this is nice
let's get cozy
[Music]
okay well
today
today is
as unbelievable
as it may sound
okay get it together
my one year anniversary
my one year anniversary in her life
a bit more
dense
okay come on come on just ignore the
music
a bit more than a year ago i was pretty
much
on the ground okay my letter actually
starts consent so it fits
i was watching piccolo every day and
thanks to that
i was at least able to make it for the
day
whole live english auditions suddenly
appeared and i realized
it might be worth a try
driven by the thought of being able to
use my skills and my talents for this
and maybe getting another chance for
success
i instantly filled out my audition
and back then i wasn't very aware of
what was going to come and what to
expect
i didn't think i would have such a big
and loving audience to support me i also
didn't think it would be so tough at the
same time
we had
many problems in the beginning
i lived in japan back then
for completely different purposes
because of lack of money i didn't have
the perfect setup or even a decent one a
bad computer
no mixer a microphone really bad
internet
thin walls and also
thin skin
and honestly i thought of myself
as someone strong originally
because of what i've been through until
now
i am and always have been a very
sensitive and emotional kind of person
but i thought i was at least used to
that dark side of publicity
unfortunately
it was very overwhelming and many
factors combined together
ended up in a very rough
couple of first months
you guys however
watched me endure it
and you stayed
and believed in me
and no matter how often i had technical
issues
or cried and doubted myself
you guys stayed
and i am by far not a perfect phoenix
but i really want to do my best
i want to keep on improving
as i think in this one year i already
have improved a lot
it takes some time to get used to all of
this you know
but i think
i found my groove
especially in the last few months
um
moving from japan to austria in this one
year
was one big change and challenge besides
joining
whole life
and then within austria i moved another
time a while ago
it's been stressful but i want to thank
my manager genma
the most for helping me with the move
from japan to austria
and my friends in austria for helping me
settle in here
again
speaking of denmark
being my manager must be frustrating
sometimes because i'm very blunt
on my streams especially
but we have been getting along so well
all this time
and i can't imagine what i would have
done without such a great manager to
support me through all of this
especially at the time in japan when i
moved apartment but had no internet
you were there to save my butt
you worked so hard not only for me but
also for the other girls you manage
and i want to say it clearly now because
maybe you need to hear it too
you are amazing and doing an insanely
great job
i could not ask for any other manager
ever and i hope i will not have to
change to a different one
i will do my best from now on
not only for kfb but also for you
[Music]
so there are many things that i
accomplished this year
we released three original songs
some cover songs too
we played many great games had a lot of
fun together
we dominated the fast food industry with
the best chain restaurant on earth kfb
we collab with many cool senpais you
know what [\h__\h]
and had really dope sponsorships and
collaborations with companies
we appeared in conventions in europe and
north america
released really neat merchandise did
many hull talks to spread the word and
sang many songs in karaoke but also
many that i wanted to accomplish but
couldn't yet
the sea thing may have helped holo ian
to get a great boost in the beginning
because people stayed at home
but it made other things way more
difficult
there i say if it wasn't for that we
already may have 3d by now
we would have come together maybe
as five somewhere and travel together
maybe gone to disneyland or something
maybe we could have done concerts and
stuff
been together on the first year
anniversary
in person but
that means
that there's still things to look
forward to in the future
things to accomplish
reasons to support and stay
so please
continue supporting me and the others in
our endeavors microphone what are you
what are you doing sorry
[Music]
[Applause]
i'm trying to do a speech here
okay so please
continue supporting me and the others in
our endeavors
i want to enjoy this beautiful scenery
these happy memories
a while longer
because
all of this has been a huge blessing
really
i am extremely grateful for the
opportunities that have been given to me
here
without kfp and whole life
i would have given up on my dreams
completely
i would have lost motivation and
inspiration
but
you guys drive me
i feel like i have so much to give and
so much to work hard for
and i have never been so productive in
my whole life as i have been here in her
life
you
bring out my full potential
thank you for giving me a chance
a dream
and a life
i will cherish it forever
thank you
yes
that was
oh dear
yes now it's time to watch the debut
[Laughter]
[Music]
i love you guys
and i think you guys know that
you are very important to me
so let's move on over and embarrass
ourselves myself
are you guys ready for
um
watching the debut together
i've been holding off on watching this
because i
don't like my debut stream at all
and wait a second i actually
asked my viewers
to prepare a bingo
sheet for it
and now of course
i can't
find it anymore
wait a second uh art of ashes bingo
yes okay
i got it
oh but that one is like mostly for
what is it
[Music]
not only for the deputy stream but
generally for the whole
[Music]
whole stream i think
but we'll use it anyway
just for fun so here's a bingo sheet
maybe i don't know take a screenshot or
something
this one is by emotion nah not motion uh
no it is motion motino mango motion oh
okay
so did you take a screenshot guys i mean
i can leave it here but it's gonna be
small
very small
maybe let me cut up this part
and then actually i guess we can even
we could even cut off bingo but people
are going to be confused oh well
okay this this is readable right
this is readable
okay
he had a fan club
wait what do we have on here idol
meeting mario hate i don't think there's
gonna be mario late
kiana downplaying her goals he had a pro
shaded cover management
can't break mid reaction oh we already
had that kiana is proud of herself i am
proud of myself gotta close her old self
cute uh-huh talk about how big the kfc
has gotten since then
piano confused why we like the old mix
mike's like so much
kiana gets nostalgic he had a fan club
uh-huh can i know this is someone in the
derby youtube chat
ah
i see what you mean cringe is an old
microphone compares old kiana japanese
and current canada japanese oh
kiana pawns in the video to go in the
tangent
canyon laughing at something past canada
said yeah that will happen comparing her
debut with the whole council then should
i be reading this beforehand just like
um i can stop myself from doing all
these things
jump scared by piccolo talking in chat
reaction oh dear i shouldn't have read
this
insults past canada making
repeats the noise that of canada did
crying
kelly mentioned mentioning how she
doesn't watch
i did watch her today and japan tangent
japan japan gent
all right you guys uh fill this out for
me
let's go
um
wait a second
[Music]
let's go it's the old loading screen
but recently we have uh
re-adapted the old loading music
because it is so nostalgic
is this loud enough maybe after the
loading
uh music we should judge because who
knows how loud it's gonna be when i talk
it's a nice music
not an original though
i have nostalgia i i did my best to draw
this
uh back in the day before the debut i
drew that
little me
i was like i want it to be like a game
and then kelly helped me move it make it
make it movable
she helped me animate it
i went over to her place
and then she uh
put it together
yeah
pretty cute how long is this loading
spring on me should we just skip it
makes no sense okay there we go now we
have the
typical intro video
where it starts like a comic and it's
like nope nothing's happening actually
we are pretty comical
maybe we are the first ring not the
artwork thing afterwards the mythical
thing
oh
where the powers of death's joy
the depths
jack
i like this music
it's too quiet isn't it
sanity
[Music]
what does that even mean chicken
what do you mean
rude
one chill guy for the investigation
gotta love ame
and all are invited to witness the myth
you as well guys
this moment was so ah
what it gave me shivers
give me uh
give me give me give me give me a
phoenix
phoenix skin
every time
oh my old transition the rise of kiara
the phoenix cali is uh once upon a time
voiceover when there were no humans yet
on earth and sightings of mythical
creatures were nothing
so bad
there was a young phoenix with feathers
burning like the golden sun
that is phoenix's name me which makes no
sense because i
said
i didn't come out of it thousands of
years
kiara would travel over the world
go on adventures like
fighting giants visiting the moon
becoming an idol and many other things
however
every couple of hundred years kiana's
lifespan would come to an end i think
this is pretty cool
she would be reborn in another dimension
discovering completely new worlds
nowadays there are no phoenixes left on
this earth and in most other dimensions
kiana started feeling lonely and decided
to take human form for her next life and
do what humans do what do you think
decided she would come to this world and
conquer it in a different new way but
you're right constantly it's that day oh
wait a day fix it for me kiara the
phoenix is reborn
yeah it looks cute see i was because
kelly debuted before me i was trying to
you know make a transition by having her
read my
introduction
and also at the same time not revealing
my voice right away oh god it's
happening all right it's happening
[Music]
that's pretty cute
yes yes make them wait yes it's a good
thing though
gotta make them wait
oh i hear microphone noises
already
you good
i was so nervous obviously
too loud too loud
[Music]
i was trying to get my [\h__\h] together
okay
oh i was so nervous holy [\h__\h]
i'm so nervous
i really want hi everyone i am
[Music]
yes also known as
xbox 360 mic shut up oh this is where i
realized i still had the reverb on
i didn't have a mixer so i had to do it
through obs like a filter
not very good quality
you okay
well i mean i would say the echo makes
me more majestic yes it does
[Music]
um
oh my god
first of all um
i'm very happy that all of you came here
today to see me
[Music]
japanese finally
revived i just uh you know i finally
revived the death just happened and
obviously it killed me she slayed me
with her
marvelous wraps
i died
but hey
here i am
[Music]
you're not going to die yeah
thank you let me explain uh
i will of course conduct this dream in
english but
i was mad and i was supposed to be man
in japanese and since today there will
be many many japanese people watching as
well please uh forgive me i'll be
self-dubbing myself i don't need any
translators no need to apologize flex
said japanese yes
[Music]
it is
you don't have to translate me i'm i'll
be translating myself i don't need you
there it is you hear that you probably
didn't hear it all right but i have
these weird echoes coming from somewhere
i don't know how
i don't know
it's really spooky comment in english or
japanese
and i'll be happy
also
and i think you see it down there next
to the bird there is a hashtag whole
life english plavie english and whole
life myth to tweet about today's stream
i would be very happy yeah no today you
use hashtag
weird things i don't know how to
pronounce that word
er
wow so smooth man so smooth
so did you like the book
yeah
great is it like the story
what is all those weird echoes so weird
story of my life
[Music]
should be louder ah thank you yeah i'll
be talking more about how that that was
made in a little bit
cute
this one year difference doesn't make
much of a difference when you're phoenix
the introduction of the majestic phoenix
that is chiara
and this was just the beginning of the
stream
i just wanted to get it behind me
nice self-made layout
i i tried my best with amelia's help to
put something together
calm down calm down it's okay okay i'm
still [\h__\h] nervous oh yeah
once again the country and it was so so
smooth it came out of nowhere
as if it's not a big deal to say that
any of them
is
written
how is the chat reacting after he said
that small are they reacting lol
f-bomb
well yeah small bird and they're not
reacting much to it i'm not really she
swore hard maybe
a few small reactions but most of them i
think didn't even notice because it's so
natural
don't mess with me okay i might be small
i might be playing now
but nobody knows
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah don't mess with
me
i'm gonna put you in the usual room
[Music]
uh i never like celebrated a birthday
until now
but
joining her life i was told i should
make
things get a birthday cause then i get
lots of presents and i love presents
so since i have my i have
when i was born first so i went with
july 6th national fried chicken day my
favorite day i'm so surprised like back
then i thought i was like
already super energetic and loud
without watching this i don't feel like
um
i speak so much i feel like i always was
pretty loud expecting uh presents that
are fusabashi but one thing that
definitely is true is that
back then i was still living in this
tiny apartment with really thin walls
and it was like 10 p.m i think when i
debuted at 10 p.m in japanese standard
time
and i have returned i'm glad to be a bit
quiet
i definitely did try to be a bit more
quiet during this video so that my
neighbors wouldn't hear me
because they definitely heard me
whenever i was speaking i heard them too
i will never die no matter how many
times you kill me callie
i i will stay alive forever since i love
you forever
[Music]
we all want someone like that
did you notice that and i'm a baby
my positioning of the microphone is kind
of like unstable right now
damn things yes i am not chicken
stop calling me chicken
and now
don't call me chicken i'm a phoenix
obviously and they still don't know
there's such a cute chicken out there
i've never seen a cute chicken before no
no no i'm also not a turkey or a rooster
i mean i've definitely seen cute
chickens before but i'm the phoenix man
she ain't one
she's not a chicken
[Music]
oh
yeah it's pretty amazing
proud to have him
i'm actually like i'm proud to be his
daughter like oh my god i still am
very proud he is
the creator of various
amazing characters
he's in the chat but no i think he's
sleeping
he's already like
2 2 a.m or so
over there
[Music]
amazing creator of many famous works
like black rock shooter steins gate fate
and many more basically everything he
touches
becomes a masterpiece so true
this is not as as i thought it would be
yeah the echo is just weird but
that's a technical issue that's not
really me
has seen at least one of his works
i see this
actually um i think
it might be destiny that we met
because uh for many pretty cute right
yeah i've been uh
it was not that bad it was a decent w i
think on the left side the black shirt
picture as a um
like a
fabric wall scroll
oh yeah i don't connect it okay
i know connected by a fabric one
[Music]
i've been alive forever so i obviously i
know all of this thing with you thank
you yeah i thought it was solid too the
lives when black boxer the first
it would have been nice this
[Music]
is
in the mirror did you guys see yourself
in the comments i don't know about you
guys but i look like
i look like 3d like look at that look at
that
your chin is amazing it is
like
fluffy yeah oh my god look at my look at
my mouth
oh oh yeah come downside uh-huh
it's like 3d in there you see the mouse
perspective
it's pretty cool
[Music]
foreign
genius tweet today i was like thinking
about you know the debuts today i was
like what if
what if a human a normal youtuber
like a really normal youtuber
does it thank
[Laughter]
with slides and showing off their the
movements and their hairstyles and their
expressions and be like
so this is my angry expression
this is my sad expression
that was my personal
bdm that is
here right now but i love it
yeah i watched the fifth generation
debut oh yeah
and some of them had music made by
minaris
and they sounded so good so i was like i
need something like that too
i
but he made two and he was like which
one do you like better and i chose one
but he then ended up giving me both my
brain bless me naughty son
japanese
bird brain is big brains
so i asked him to
make something that sounds like it would
be in a fast food restaurant it also
sounds
like some other btms from certain
streamers that i really
is so it should be something poppy and
fun but also good for like listening to
it for hours like 10 hour loops you know
they gotta be on youtube somewhere yeah
i can totally listen to those songs for
hours even today
then loving intro and the japanese float
better than yeah
it was better
because i lived in japan at that moment
speaking it way more often
[Music]
is
i think this goes back and then these go
good job good job
we start from top and then we go to
bottom
okay yes
superb superb oh funny
what's up
superb
what's up what's up super boob
i like
[Music]
just kidding i'm not wearing it on
purpose
so that you can tell the difference
between the old kiana and the new and
the current piano
[Music]
i'm not as cool as kylie's mic drop
can never be as cool scary stuff oh yeah
wait the fast food i forgot that's
the most obvious thing i love fast food
okay
every day it's healthy you should eat it
too every day
yeah you should it's healthy
there's salad in there after all right
old
right
it's really healthy i mean there's salad
exactly
that's what i'm saying
i mean you couldn't even say i only want
the salad and tomato is often in there
too
yeah
chicken you gotta eat meat i mean unless
your vegetarian and all that but
generally it's good for the bunny
i keep looking at the comments waiting
for
a certain someone to comment oh she's
coming oh she's coming
i shouldn't look
[Music]
yeah i still don't that has not changed
i just needed some time to get into the
groove yeah
do you guys know anything besides
one-sided but it's really also a big
difference because of the microphone it
really is well it's okay i love you all
back if you love me i'll love you back
so
they will love you i don't know if i
will love you but
yeah you can't call it dinner
my hobbies are
singing drawing eating fighting
i don't think that needs more
much more explanation
[Music]
a lot of you guys are hearing it's nice
i speak english but not perfect
oh
yeah you might need a german translation
where i how you will never know you have
to learn the microphone is a little bit
of thought fun at fault of that i think
though because i will not teach you i
don't have time for that
watch
definitely she teaches it sounds like
i'm still here you hear them my favorite
things
is
[Music]
you know what i love uh one of the
things i love most about the cora senpai
is her voice when she just starts to
stream when she just woke up ah
[Music]
okay
he did say to me today then he started
watching around after the first gen
oh
yeah i was really freaking out that was
genuine
oh
that was me about to cry for stopping
myself from crying
it's so weird like back then i just
joined so i had like no
no communication with her
i was still seeing her from the point of
view of the fans so it was so special
now it's been in here so i see her as a
calling but
[Music]
my queen bunny my queen bunny
princess bunny
i love you
it was so surreal to be in the same
company company is here
wow
[Music]
stop fangirling move on move on move on
let's get in even more into detail
um
my interest there it is tails off you
don't need to reach before me to stay at
the top okay you don't need to read
before me
yeah i'm part of the kids that's now
true
i don't like play the usual games that
be chippers usually
do i guess like i don't really like art
pizza i didn't want to discipline people
but it tells off serious i don't know
you're serious mm-hmm peaches are so
much fun ah good night
it's not really all pretty i guess but
yeah super mario games and zelda series
and some more
uh
i did play a final fantasy 14 before but
not right now
[Music]
what
i was really against playing shooting
games and stuff
uh you might be interested in like
shooting games and stuff but i
i
i'm not good at them i don't like them
i'm sorry so i'll be playing rpg games
and like fun games mostly let's go
i ignite oh my god
basically i like this game last time so
uh
i want to support this girl because like
arc knights just started the
contingency contract again
[Music]
it's my favorite
anime um
oh what a great girl
she's gonna be my oh let's
i have to say um like i love all of
these
i think most of you don't know kanagi
i really recommend it it's pretty old
but like if he wants it yet because
that's sorry i bought it on my list of
good anime did you watch it yet
yeah
nope
you know i it's so good you should watch
it yeah
crazy trying that's it it's pretty short
just one season i think yay unbelievable
unbelievable
all ready
i need to hurry up
yeah
favorite music i do listen to english
music as well like idiom pop like super
basic stuff i'm basic
but i wanted to write down like japanese
styles stuff that i listen to i
completely stopped listening to music
though it's so sad i used to listen to
music constantly everything about me is
perfect but now i'm just happy to have
silence around me
so weird i don't know if it's because
i'm so busy or if i just lost interest
in music it's so weird
ski i love how the project it's like a i
don't know agency that has like a lot of
uh i mean not not not none at all but
very rarely like most of them already
like god graduated bye bye and even if
then i want to watch netflix not listen
to music
because it feels like
i at least wouldn't want to listen to
music only
it would have to be while doing
something on the side
whenever i don't stream
i mostly just
quickly make a thumbnail
set up the next stream and then jump
into bed
and watch netflix it's just no time i
actually i really like it so that's why
i don't really know the latest trends
you know
i changed mine i keep on singing
the same songs
i really like it same
i'm surprised people can relate
[Music]
nostalgic
and like like for example
of course
oh yeah there you have another
connection with my papa
[Music]
all ready
make the perfect fast food restaurant
because there's like uh
like no matter to which fast food
restaurant i go to
like oh yeah she was afraid of the
second one cam is proud of herself calls
her also cute
so there's always like something missing
what the other restaurant
the
fries are
sauces
i wanna make it perfect
will you invest iris voice again
only two more girls left
[Music]
well free d p what's the other one
that's missing i made jungle proud oh
yeah thank you i didn't stand on the
same stage on my journey
yeah okay those two will be everything
that i want
i know
[Music]
i did i did i changed my whole setup i
have a new pc new microphone you mix up
everything
i use a different program as well to
stream
everything's fresh oh yeah if i get 3d i
think i'll go down looking forward to
halloween
concerts or doing like special
collections it might be oh i want to do
like rings closer than you think is
shut up kiana
so i gotta have big dreams man
i'm just trolling you guys
conventions for example for conventions
um i would like to like i'm just
trolling you guys
for anyways
if i could like voice the character
for maybe for an english stuff i guess
maybe not maybe they don't need me in
japan because
literally
is it coming back
i'm moving again there we go
sorry i'm not listening to you
i'm listening again now okay sorry i was
talking over you oh yeah i want to come
up with whole live japanese especially
of course bacon
done
yeah
of course but also many others because i
i really like a lot of the members um i
just didn't want to uh
ah
what come on what what you what huh huh
what my boobs move differently
i'll get you compare
yeah them move better now
[Music]
and i really like
so i don't even know how bingo works
you need like five don't yeah but do
they have to be in one room
i think yeah
yeah we'll see what happens
is
[Music]
how many i would love to make yeah five
in a row can be diagonal oh i can do
that i think i can
[Music]
the same stage as my japanese want to
talk about stages yeah repeat the noise
people in front of us
come on speak faster this part is boring
[Music]
nothing cringy and when i realized
originally i mean that's a cringe way
more i really like singing i'm not i'm
really not a good singer i've realized
that you got to have the question
but i really enjoy singing
and i hope others would enjoy
hearing these things too
[Music]
oh you
so i want to sing black shooter
[Applause]
[Music]
my papa has a surprise but there's like
you know
things
oh yay
i wanna have people cosplay me and get
lots of fan art chickens
you
uh creating beautiful pictures of me
they looked majestic oh my god chet are
you okay you look really good you can
make me really happy anthony
yes next capture this beauty try try it
oh chat broke it really did i mean i see
you guys moving but not on this on the
screen there it is
[Music]
i was uh giving the choices so emoji has
already been decided it's been my fate i
know i know that it's just
it's not that i am a chicken i sell
chicken i own chicken i hate that
chicken but i don't i'm not a chicken i
am not a chicken
there was just no phoenix emoji what was
i supposed to do
true
it's not cannibalism
i can eat chicken as much as i want
because i'm not a chicken
okay for fannie we have we need your
opinion
please help me i was thinking should we
do the same thing it's none
um
i didn't have much space on the slide so
i could only write two
so do you want to be chickens or fan
club attention span
well i'll forever have i'm so done
you can call it whatever
skip skip skip
[Music]
a combination of fan and phoenix
why did i not offer that in english
because it will be mixing
okay
it will be mixed so has it not worked as
in well hearts it is those three letters
but it will be it works better japanese
yeah our fan club okay
oh yeah yeah hashtag kiara fan club no
no no it's not that anymore we're
changing it
[Music]
which one we have to hurry but there was
a confusion there because on the on this
screen it was art but i ended up making
an art of ashes so people kept on
posting it on the wrong tab
and now people also often post it on art
of ashes listen
so i miss i miss some fan arts every
once in a while because they're posted
in the wrong wrong hashtags
not a chicken
looking
[Music]
hi
i am
[Music]
you can just
i'll write them on twitter later
and stream
yeah kfb i thought it was maybe too
short so maybe rise of kiara would be
better honestly
for stream tackles i broke it like
people if
maybe i knew it all along the title of
the new tales-off game
[Music]
my bro
oh yeah that's oh yeah okay
you like short things i guess guys
you're making me fall asleep
for both then
on the kfb
exhausting couple of weeks man
[Music]
we're gonna um awake until
like five a.m today because the collab
is at two a.m for me i don't really know
gotta be energetic until then
staying awake no problem staying
energetic hmm
okay okay okay trash can is speaking
true okay uh you can use kfb or kia ribo
you know it's gonna
[Music]
had yeah
but i might not have time there's things
to set up please use those stacks you
can already use them right now and
please now
[Music]
i shot my current we can do it
not the
[Music]
hello at this point i show people my
sword and my shield already but this is
this is going to be the first time where
i show people
my buy my
chicken accessory
[Music]
yeah captain to have something special
to show on my stream
this is
normal
huh
if you um
i want you to see my beautiful eyes
i can't
i can do a little bit happier
i can do that too
hmm
[Music]
[Laughter]
okay
why why
why must i always
why would you just suffer
i just want somebody to love me
[Music]
why don't you want to baby
this is when everyone
calls me chicken
huh
i wait what are you calling me
and i can't change
hmm
you don't have any respect for phoenix
this is when i see a bucket of
chicken in front of me
[Laughter]
best expression ever
but back then i wasn't able to do it
online this mouthful those eyes no okay
it's always like that
okay
or also known as
when the dentist tells you to open your
mouth even wider even though you already
have it open to the max ah is always
open as it can get doctor
huh
[Music]
okay
now let me show you my full body i have
a really sexy buddy
small and small small burpee
i'm chill
sorry microphone sorry
chill microphone i jumped around the
microphone didn't you're a loot wasn't
stabling if you think that's slow then
you're good well we all loot we all
lived together we're all looting days
together
[Music]
what is it
today
would you like
i can also feel like
i refuse
deny no thank you no no
no
isn't that good i can do it on both but
that maybe is weird
i can fly
i can't believe i can fly
i don't know
i reject you on both sides whatever that
pose is on both sides
[Music]
from the beginning
oh my god
we have no time oh my god yeah we don't
have any time
[Music]
okay one second i'll show you something
show us
so heavy
i'm not gonna change now though i'm so
happy
i'm not gonna do that
is
[Music]
so cute
i mean it's not like i want to show you
uh
my hawaii
my skirt or anything
is
[Music]
doesn't allow me to take it off i don't
know why
you said prohibited
because
i'm not allowed to use it because i'll
turn into phoenix again and in this
world it's probably not very recommended
yo those fives look so soft
those are some nice fives man
[Music]
yes
i am
are you looking at the belt where do you
think i am of course i am
i hope you are looking at the belt
where is ladle again huh can you imagine
this in 3d
okay
i thought
if only
[Laughter]
[Music]
i shall show you now
as promised
my transformation anyway
ima
i already showed like a lot of stuff on
twitter but there's still one thing i
didn't show you yes
that's a weird ass echo though are
thank you guys for all the super chats
really i'm gonna be doing a super chat
reading on tuesday i think
so i'll be reading those for hours and
hours and hours and hours
okay
yes i think i'm ready which reminds me
are you ready
yeah
show me are you ready
yes people are really looking forward to
this but then
it was not a phoenix final four and it
was also not um
a kamen rider or something
that was funny though
i got some good reactions for that one
transformed
[Music]
but it's all i can show you at the
moment it looks so cute when i stand
it looks delicious right
look at that hourglass perfect body
beautiful
don't you wanna i mean i wanna run my
finger along those
waists
[Laughter]
and i shall quickly but you can yeah i
can
[Music]
yes
you don't have time friends i'll smile
we don't have time
um
oh i'm so small
[Music]
don't cut your head off don't do it
okay
you're not married to henry
you ain't married to henry since today
is a
debut
a
marathon
i
have to me comes
and i can tell you
only a few things about her
she
has a secret skill secrets girl which is
art and she shows that off all the time
now
cookie she kept it secret beforehand
you will know later that was such a
great moment when she revealed her eyes
and everyone was like
i love that really
they're really soft
it's really nice i really enjoy
listening to her very accurate
description i would say
helpful and kind pure ancient helpful
too she helped out
and she helped me out with me i was not
lying to you
for me
[Music]
then
before i go to the ending oh the
suffering about my future streams the
suffering first of all
it will be collapse dream
why didn't we do it like this
it will
[Music]
everyone will be there it's our first
collab so you all have to come it will
be lots of fun
back then i didn't do a weekly schedule
it will be on amelia's channel i mean i
did but i didn't like i planned it out
but i didn't
publicize it
[Music]
pure suffering
oh my god i was so dead at that point
i saw that there's like a chicken
costume there and i never played fall
guys before i don't know how fast you
can get it but i want it
i never got it
[Music]
it will be uh two hours after the debut
or like one hour probably after the
debut ends i guess
now
er also one last thing i wanted to say
about my streams in the future i will no
i can't get it anymore unless they bring
old outfits back at some point a bit
less japanese
maybe they don't japanese
because i don't like talking with people
getting in my way way too much
but with me
i don't really want to do it yeah the
sniping
goes too far with fall guys it's just
not if i speak a
not funny well i just don't really want
to like comment and we when we played on
amazon streams people like all of them
away from me it's like you guys are so
obedient
[Music]
i
would like to um
oh do you hear the echo i gotta been in
trouble for
doing here i'm doing like two minutes
over time
five minutes over time
i'm not done because back then it was
still like
don't overlap with hello live japan
girls but no like i mean not not the
other way around because i think it was
our debuts and uh whole life japan was
like
on purpose not streaming over us but
nowadays that rule is gone
because i mean whole life japan is so
many members they can't
all always i prepared you know
stop streaming just because someone's
debuting
i put a lot of uh thought into choosing
because it has like
my emotions but i think like feelings
if it's within like whole life japan
i think they would still like follow if
it was a debut that's like really
special if it's on the first anniversary
then
yeah not so much but if it's a debut
then i think they would still not stream
over it i think for debuts it's a little
bit more special
here we go i was so nervous
to sing
cover shade
no no no
that was not a cover shade no
ah
[Music]
today
[Applause]
[Music]
da
um
[Music]
[Applause]
wait we can fix that let me face it
let's do a duet if you want to hear me
singing that alone then go to the debut
stream later on but once again you're
sure
we can totally fix that you should know
about
where did you start there
good but
please listen
now i shouldn't when i say now it
shouldn't be offset anymore
shiny smiley story
[Music]
a
let's go
[Music]
is
um
[Music]
yes
a
[Music]
hey
is
[Music]
um
is
[Music]
a
[Applause]
amazing
[Music]
you're a good
singer i have to end the stream quickly
everyone
thank you so much
for coming today i was really nervous
and i was really worried but i'm so
happy to
meet you all and
i hope that from now on we can be good
friends and you will invest in my fast
food business
[Music]
didn't want to leave it was too exciting
why
[Laughter]
wanted to be funny at the end
oh damn it's over
[Music]
holy mackerel name
yep
that's
it that's nostalgic too
oh man
that was just like during the
debut times though
well
well stop it on me
[Music]
small
okay
yes oh that was not as cringe as i
thought it would be i mean
my voice being very different feels a
bit uncomfortable
uh the microphone being
not properly set up feels uncomfortable
too but besides that i think like
um it was freaking solid
it was uh
i did everything properly introduced
myself properly sang a song properly
showed my body properly
it was the ideal
ideal debut stream yeah i would say so i
have a little problem with it i was set
i did a good job back then i'm doing a
good job now positivity let's go
but yeah we've come so far i've already
read my letter to you guys but
we've really come for i've i've come far
and as all thanks to you guys and i know
that
um back then
a lot of people who watched my debut
stream
uh didn't like me
oh
some people simply didn't like the fact
that i spoke a little bit more japanese
than others in my debut stream
just to you know that was simply because
of me wanting to get the message across
to everyone
and some people just didn't like me
because of my voice some people just
didn't like me because of my looks
but
yeah a lot of you guys
either liked all of that or you
liked some of it and decided to support
me because of who i am
and so others others didn't like me in
the beginning maybe but like me a little
bit now
a little bit so i'm really grateful for
the chance that you guys all of you have
given me
and i mean i did change a lot so i
understand if you maybe didn't like me
back then but let me know that that's
okay
how you like me now peach sorry
yeah um
it is
it is a crazy how one year went by so
quickly
when you stream every freaking day
time just goes by
insanely fast
and i just realized i had
my balcony door open the whole time i
think
and they probably heard me singing
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
let's go
let's go i mean it's different room but
still let's go
awkward
[Music]
now there's some cranes yeah there we
have it yeah
yeah
let's just hope that through those walls
in between there was not much to hear
[Laughter]
i'm suffering more right now than i did
while watching this
oh well
well well well one year as i said has
gone by so fast and i hope that the next
year will not go by this quickly but it
just does when you
are so productive every day is yeah you
can't help it
um but i still hope that we at least can
accomplish many things in the following
year and i hope that you guys will
continue to
watch my streams and i know that people
go back to work and go back to school
and know that therefore a lot of people
may have stopped watching me so actively
as they did before that's okay because
life life happens life is important
there are priorities in life
but the people who are here now
and the people who will join us in the
future
and maybe some people in the past who
will come back
i hope i can make you guys proud and
entertain you guys with my streams
yes that's what i want to do and i want
to give you guys back for all the things
that you keep on giving me currently
i
felt
very very
worthless
before
whole life and there were times where
i felt the same
even during whole life
but the past few months i really have to
say
i feel like things have been going
really well
and
i
i really
enjoy every moment
of doing this
except maybe
yesterday
but besides that
[Laughter]
ah yeah look forward
to the future please
there's
as we have already established there is
many more things that need to be done
we need to do 3d right
yeah
other
[Music]
um
well
i
just said to the japanese bros i hope
they also will continue watching me even
though i stopped
uh i i kind of like speak way less
japanese than i did before um
but but i wanna i wanna you know maybe
do another japanese only stream sometime
and and well i do do a lot of collapse
of japanese senpai's and next week i'm
planning one night senpai senpai
look forward to that
so
chickens
all over the world
thank you from the bottom of my
cocolow for
continuously supporting me
and believing in me
i
will now leave and prepare for the
coming up collaboration stream on
amelia's channel don't miss it it might
be
really bad for european time zones just
like mine
but yeah in that case you gotta watch
your archives so just promise me to
watch the archives if you can't watch it
live otherwise watch it live uh it's
probably gonna be scuff but it's also
gonna be really really exciting and fun
so yeah
um
with some announcements as well yeah
yeah oh yeah because there's no
merchandise have you noticed yeah and no
solo merchandise but who knows
what else there might be and what kind
of announcements we have for you okay
okay
so
thank you i'll see you on
tuesday
i think and i'll uh
probably
make the stream from yesterday public
again after editing it i think yeah and
yeah i should see you on tuesday i think
i'll take monday off
because it's been crazy
tuesday in it
it's true saying that
[Music]
thank you i can't say thank you enough
i don't know i want to thank you guys
more i want to thank you guys more
because it's like
unbelievable
unbelievable it's unbelievable
it's really
all of this is so insane
i
and
i've just been so blessed you know it's
such a blessing like what the [\h__\h]
ah
but i'm gonna leave
i have to prepare okay okay okay we can
probably oh well we'll probably have a
lot more to talk about during the super
chat reading when i go through all of
these super chats
yeah
yeah let's keep let's keep the rest for
the super chat reading
it's probably going to be a 12 hour
super chat reading
[Music]
thank you for the insane support guys
absolutely insane
i'm so happy to have you all here thank
you
and
in german we say
auf wiedersehen
see you
in your number two
bye-bye
um
[Music]
do
so
[Music]
do
oh
[Music]
you