DET [
Music] [
Music]
[Music]
DET [Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] A [Music] [Music] [Music]
DETDET [
Music]
DET [
Music] [
Music]
N
[Music]
DET
[  MUSIC]
[MUSIC]
DET
[
MUSIC]
[MUSIC] [MUSIC] [MUSIC] [MUSIC]
DET [
MUSIC] [MUSIC] DET [MUSIC] [MUSIC]
N [
MUSIC] [
MUSIC] [MUSIC]
[MUSIC]
DETDET
[  [Music] [
Music] [Music]
Ah
[Music]
BM ready
Good morning
[Music]
Hello-Welcometo
[Applause]
I you
forsee
[Music]
EL
likeThankyouGUfor
andouwith
TE  Chimchimchim gather together
[clap]
Okeoffu
have
[music]
[clap]
Ne
[music]
Netagaba te ta
gamba te
NEXT
TE
Team
[music]
Howareyouhowisyour
prarforthisfortoday
EVENTPR
muchyouguysGUPOSyou
guysWin
toNo
[music]
andWhatisyourteamnamehave
TE
think
teyyou
Good ganbatte
[music]
isTeamname
IYouEnjoy
[music]
todaybethewinners
Ganbatte
[music] tethan papa [music
] ki mochimochi
mochimochikochikochi
Who is the sky team
? Hey, let me introduce myself. Hey, let me introduce myself. I've
learned how to take care of myself.
Sorry, what is that team name?
Yes, it's me. I hope you'll enjoy today. I'm going to have fun. Yeah, here, here.
Okay.  So,
how is the team's preparation? Ah, it's already perfect, isn't it? You
can do that picture, ah, good luck,
Tan,
Llama
, oh, you're already good, right? You're good, aren't you? You're good, aren't you? You'll win, this,
yeah, and, um,  The clothes and costumes are
so cute. I think this is an
Indonesian uniform.  It
suits you so well
[Music] You're
cute, do your best, Sora, please
do your best. I'll do my best with Iepasi, yes, I'll do my best, I'll do my best,
eh, next? Hello,
meow,
hello, hello
[Music]
A little more here, here,
here, here
[Music]
[Applause]
okok
Inside
notHJPOkOk
[Music]
OkEN
H
[Music]
TEganbatteJP TEganbatte te [
Laughter]
Halo
[Music]
goooooo
herbal
asmenykarHARGsendi
UNSARA
[Music]
so
guyskitakurang
satuiITUkita
treasureHsothefirst
GAME will be treasure hunts There will be
around SPOT [MUSIC] so yeah have around for
also also There is also
around the are that you
Find treasure around Bob In Shilka In
Tess It might even be in Hopper
Good luck
[MUSIC] [MUSIC]
[MUSIC]
OKONE
OneTimetimeforHthe
trewillbe
10  It's
only 10 minutes, I
think. [Music] [Applause] [Music] Stand up, senpai, senpai, seriously
...  Do your best, where should I press
this button? Thank you for your hard work, M.
[Music]
cont no
let
goshx
shx
ABUbuis
wait a minute here
[Music]
te onlyup
Oh, I wonder what that is, I don't know
[Music]
know
Good luck
[laughter]
[music]
Oh,
no ...  [
Music]
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music] I'm
laughing
but it's not that. [Laughter] I think it was there but it wasn't that.
So, this is really
funny.  The
focus is
on this red flower, I think I got it right,
but, well
, good luck, this is it,
but it's not this, what
are humans, wait a minute,
look
[Music]
There it is, it was
n't this button. There must be another button around here.
Where is it? It looks like
there's a Silka box. It
looks like there's one. If it was Silka, it would be easy to understand. Hey
, let's
turn around a bit.
[Music]
Yeah, it won't open, but I already have the emeralds, so that
's it. [Music] Ah, I don't know. It doesn't look like there'll be any gaps.
[Music] Oh,
this requires teamwork. Yeah, we have to
work together, so I'm looking forward to it.
[Music]  Simultaneous
press switch
[
Music] Click wrinkle Ao [Music] NoILS IOhGodoh GOD oiru [Music] gampanggampangOhiya sudah diiludahdiambilo S [Music]
urinfinish [Music] [Music]
[Music]
AR
NIBRA
I
[Music]
FriendIlovelovei
Iwanttock
Her
knowyouguysyouguys
Find
anyar
[Music]
NothereONECloseby
It's okay It's okay It's
okay [Music] It's okay
[Music]
Yo
E
As expected How
[Music]
guys
anyYES
[Music  ]
jegjeg
[music]
[laughing]
Ptake
[music]
ATTpleas yes Okthank
youthankyouforATTWe
alreadydonethe
treasureHSowehavetogobackandtotheSIMONsay
[music]
[music] Let's
go in
pasang
DIADIA
sudah [
music]
NokokK
kerSD
[laughing]
[music  ] Amo
round
[Music]
HEverybodyareyou
guys
[Music]
AllWho
think next time, eh
And then
[Music] That
was
it, that was it, that was it
[Music]
Amo,
Naik,
it's okay, it's okay
[Music]
Okay, so we had rules.  I
feel like it, one more time, one more time
[Music]
times,
um,
[Music]
bevel
[Music],
diamond 1,
all emeralds, emeralds, emeralds, I
need emeralds, but if I keep winning, it will
continue forever, but if that question
Or maybe if you get the fourth question wrong, that's it.
[Music]
Okay, let's get ready. Let's do our best. Let's start.
Oh, I see. Yes, yes, that's right. The other
group's voices are, why are they making them now?
That group oh um where is it?
Daimon Seth's push the groove ah Simon
Seis's
guy yeah wait oh
goh yeah wait wait so my heart is beating
heart is beating okay okay like
practice so shall it start it's starting
okay level 1 yeah
[music]
Wanwa yes
buah yeah buah oh  Buan
Rampa Sorry, can you say it again?
Hey, hey, did you say Repa Repa Rempaar? Yes,
Rempaar, right, right, right, right, ah,
this, right, right,
don't say it, Bolballball
[Music]
ONE
Ohhhh
Towanpa ranpa
Jinjiranpa
ranpa No good good good 3
Ella
next next
ranpa Jinko rapa Ronpa Majdoa Karimajdoa
akariooo Owa Repare
Jinko
Ronpa Majdo Majdo is hey
Owow next next
next it's getting long this is getting long  It's
getting long so forget about it, then next, then, um,
Repa
Jinko
Ronpa
[music]
Otowa
Repa
Ronpa Maji
[music]
Next, next,
next, okay, then,
Repa
[music]
Hakankanan
Ooooh
Towan Repa Repa
Jinkan
Ronpa
Pandoa
Ki
Kanan,
hit ...
Oh, that's it. That's it. Okay,
thank you. Thank you. Thank you. But five, five, five. It's
amazing, sister. It's amazing, it's amazing. Yeah, okay. [Music] So, oh, oh, thank you, thank
you.
From the voice group chat, from the group chat,
ka
ani
ani a
[music]
nice
thethinkthinkStand
InTheforStandthan
[music]
aBlindapparentlyOK
sotherleislikeexpl
duringthepracticeso
youguyswillbewillbe
given
progressivecomm
[applause]
[music]
oneofyou
failDotime
thefirst
ONE
LtwooneletgoHowIn
Thisgame
[music]
har
OKOKyouyoutake
backokayOKNEXT
nextyouguysareright
soNextOneis
lempar
johnkTHtwoone
GoingGoingNEXT
LAMPLP32
ONE
Going
FGEHNEXTisLjoh
Ronpa Magic Door
Cali
Susto
Ah
Ah Ah
[Laughter]
GU
[Music]
[Applause
] [Laughter]
for
[Music]
Momo It's okay It's okay Stand
are you are
you will be
Easy Slowly will
give
3GO
NEXT Ok Ok
NEXT NEXT
is
johone
ONE
know NEXT NEXT
[Music  ]
NEXTNEXTNEXT I
don't remember naNEXT NEXToNEXT Ranpa Jinko Ronpawa [Music]
osisDJlanjutokeNEXT
oke NEXT jkokmajuDUKalihadap KIhadapkanan
[Music]
ONE
LP
right
TurnI
meanasTurn
Rightas Turn
[Music]
MINGmeans
thattheway
[Music]
same
are
[Music]
ront
okokokokR
like
hadseeup
RunNo
Worrycompliasguys
think
ONT
[laughing]
BlockAreyoureadyforthefirstonethefirstONEgoingtotellyouis
L3twoone
[music]
NEXT
WayMOVonMOVONTHE
SECONDONEisL
joh32
[music]
ONE
backthethd
onetwoone
HNEXT
is32
NEXTGoing
StrongGoingStrong
NEXT
lokKIThreetwoone
[music]
[laughing]
GoingStrongNextOne
is
okp
MA
kiantwoone
oGoingStrongGoing
evenStrongerNext
Onelok
[music]
hadapKI
hadapan
[music]
Mtwo
[Music]
one
[Applause]
[Music]
WOKNEXT
NEXT
KI
mul
Kone
[Music]
KukuGUforNextOne
NEXTNEXTGet
positionRPleasethan
younextONE
lkp
majuKI
paThreeTwo
[Music] [
Music]
OneLastOneLastOne
LastOne
[Music]
LASTTHE
LAST
GO
jkp
majuhadapKI
hadapanmund
Block
mer
Three
two
[Music  ]
oneOU
byidso
apparently
ARMforg
[music]
Oto
Thankyouthanyou
thank
[music]
youis
[laughing]
Ohhh Ihave
[music]
is
the
[music]
upthanOKAreyouready
CanIJustGiveYouThe
commNowYesOKsoevery
EveryTimethecommand
finyouGUGetBackto
theRBlockandPiupany
youOKthefirst
One2ONE
Easymovingonmoving
on
NEXTJThreetwo
oneNext
One
LPjoh
LP3two
[music]
oneI
NEXT
Lepajin
Pama
DU3to
[music]
one
NEXT  Lapa
J
jongkokLP
majuhadapKIThreetwo
one
[Music]
[Laughter]
back
YouNextOneNextOne
Herewego lar
Kone
[Music]
apparentknow
Do
[Applause]
[Music]
Ah - Have you
practiced yet? Yes, yes, have you practiced
yet?  Okay, great. So
please stand up there, the red block. Right
here. Okay, okay, okay. Are you
ready? Ready. Okay, it's
starting. Good luck, good luck, it's starting.
Start Ookefust
One
Repast 1go
Repa
Ren
Itoito Wait Wait Head
Think
Repa Repatori
Rere
[Music]
Next Next Next Uh Renjon
Wagoo Next Next Next
Rampa
Johnco
Romper 3
[Music]
Wagoo Next Next Next
Rampa
Johnco
Ronpa Majudo Akari 3
Towa
Go o
Yes Next Next Next Not
yet Not yet Not yet There's
still more Not yet Not yet Money is still
Okay Then next is
Um
Repa Johnco
Ronpa
Maha
Towa
Gomu Eh  Like this, like this, like
this
[music]
a
l hakirihado
canaan three towa go baron
rekaun e
from here to the right mi thing is
here kana e
what kana e tan the clippers are but the right one is too far away so it's
not skin canaan  It's
like I'm naked, like I'm going back to the clippers. Is
that how it is? Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes,
yes
[Music]
Right, it's fine, it's fine, from here to the right. Yeah, yeah, yeah, congratulations, congratulations, congratulations, you did it,
yay
. [
Music] Thank you, let's do our best. [
Music]
Da-kan-kan.
[Music]
Kan-ka, no, no, ah, here, here.
No, it's a little far away, ah, oh, oh,
oh.  Where is this?
[Music] It's
Bonk here.
[Music] It's dead. [Music]
It
's here. [Music] It's
built here.
[Music]
Well, this is...
[Music] [Music] Biara [
Music]
[Music]
Well  Let's join a group,
everyone, let's do it together. Let's
do it at the
same time. Let's
do it at the same time. Let's do it in one minute.
And then wait for one minute.
Please write it in the book. The answer is, please
write it in the book. And Builder
, the theme is here.
[Music]
If you know the answer, please don't shout.
Please don't say that, write it in a book.
[Music]
Please, look at
that person over there. Please
don't do that.
[Music]
Wait a minute,
even if you don't do that.  It's okay,
so
we both saw it. Chan
also saw
it. This one has a skull in it,
so I
saw
it.
[Music]
So what should I do? I wonder if I should change it to yes. I'm
ready.
[Music]  ] I
wonder if it's okay to keep it as it is. I don't know what to do. Please
stand there.
Who is it? Wait, wait, wait. I'll
keep it as it is. There's a second one. The
second one is new. I'll
do it now.  So I'll take a look.
Wait a minute. Let's try it out. Please
take a look.
Where is the chat?
Where is it?
For now, I guess we'll just have to wait for a new theme.  Gane
Ganakare Doni Ano
[Music]
Thema
Oh, there's nothing here.
[Music]
So you're allowed to give me hints.
[Music] That's bad. [Music] Oh,
I have
a question.
[Music] I
got it.
[Music] It's
so difficult,
so difficult, so I'm
going to make it with this and this.
[Music]
Right here, yeah, yeah, yeah.
[Music] Do your best, do your best, do your best, do your best, do
your best, if you have any questions, let me know.
Do your best.
[  [Music]
Yes, yes, yes, yes, do your best, do your best,
do your best, do your best [Music] [Music] Do your best, do your best
[Music] Hey, do your best,
do your best
[Music]
The game is
starting, it's
starting, it
's starting, do your best, it's starting, hey,
hey  Okay, it's
starting. It's just one minute. It's
starting. It's starting. Okay, okay,
okay, sweet. [laughter] kita [music] majustBel chiamaa [music] [music] Neyananyanyanyaamaruawatta
It's cute I
wrote it, write it, change it,
write it, write it, I'll check it out, okay,
thank you for this
and
thank you, okay
...  [MUSIC]
Okay, I checked, I
checked, I checked
[MUSIC]
Okay, okay, I checked
for
[MUSIC]
BUCK
Camille
Beer, next,
next, next, I'm
ready
[MUSIC]
[MUSIC]  ]
[Music]
Jijieto ne
willconfSkate
CheerswhatIwillconfiscateCheers
THANK
YOU
NOwhatthe
[Music]
fuckyouknowYouYou
SORRYSORRY
[Music]
Oh why
yo
Suisui
I
PE
[Music]
Uayapermipermi
Ganbare [
Music]
[Music]
Tengune Ore Ani
GoodThislikePIDPID
this
[music]
iest
Okayfor
forGU
[music]
me
Look at it Look at it
Oh, that's good, that's good.
[Music] That's right, that's right. You did a great job. I'm so happy. Isn't it heavy? Biddy is so good. Oh, nice, you did it. Amazing, amazing. You've got money too. [Music]
[Applause] Nexty, next, next toddler.
[  Music]
[Music]
1than
ta
[Music]
Do
your best Amaru Amaru Amaru Amaru Amaru
Do your best I don't know why this is dying
ThislikeanEG
Do your best thisalsolikean
EGThisisa3DATT
Do your best
[Music  ]
Hey, I know, I see
, I see, I see,
what is this? It
looks delicious. Okay, now.
[Music]
Cute, good luck
. Hey, this also looks like an egg. This is good. [Laughter] Good luck, everyone.
[Music]
Hey,  I'll keep watching it.
Ah, I wonder if it's done yet.
Amazing.
Eh,
yeah,
yeah, it's
incredible telepathy. Eh, yeah, it's
amazing.
Amazing, as expected, as expected, amazing, amazing, La, no no no,
yaya, good luck with the
builders,
good luck, good luck, good luck,
amazing,
knowanswer
otherthe
[Music]
good luck
[Music] yaya yaya good
luck, good luck, everyone, good luck,
lady, good luck,
yaya
[Music]
Hey, Let's go Mario
begins, begins, Amaru begins, what is this
, I don't know, I can't see it yet, Amaru, Amaru, um,
hey, I see, I see, oh, a genius, a
genius, a genius, this
is similar, this is a genius
Wow, Dore-senpai is amazing, a genius, a genius,
this is good, let's
go home,
what is this, restin, uu,
okay,
[music]
,
okay,
okay, wow, everyone looks good, good, good, okay,
maybe I don't have the talent, genius, amazing,
genius
Amazing,
oh oh,
amazing,
amazing, amazing, amazing,
amazing
Wow, good luck
[music]
Nea
Sutamstime oSW tata
[music]
Neya
a
[music]
Indonesia
run
[music]
Malaki
Indonesiagui
[music]
[Music]
Something feels
BadIfeelBadbecause
Thereisalotof
stuffhappentoPA
nashiandIhopeandI
hope
[Music]
TheyDENDENHoldHold
grchOnUS
look
[Music]
Superwiththe
timeF
in
Indonesia
What is this Godzilla? What is this? I
don't know
[Music]
Isn't
it?
[Music]
Wow wow
wow
artistic artistic
other people shouldn't see this but just this
[Music]
Okay okay oh I get it I get it amazing amazing
amazing  Amazing,
amazing, amazing, what is easy? Easy,
what is easy?
So, come ...
for WasMan
the WasManthe
[Music]
Waniwani
Pirowani Piro
nextbodyseenthe
[Music]
I
[Music] Let's
start,
Kopila I
[Music]
Nanwa I can do it, I can do it, it's okay, it
's okay, I can do it, I can do it,
K
yunakdiasINI
[Music]
[Laughter]
Amazing, amazing, amazing
[Music]
Amazing, this is  What is this?
What is this? I
don't know. It's difficult.
This is oh, this is oh, this is my.
[Laughter]
The end.
[Music]
What is this? Thatisto obvthatisto obviousDIA DIAITU SIUS ngerSSK Good, this is
good, amazing
[Music]  ]
Amazing
Yuri Nonotbutmissyou
Wa ni wa ni wa
[Music] Ni
La La
Litre again
This is Toms again
KAtams
mgu
NDIA
anj
ITUE
jegDEN
[Music]
BLZG
glesman
BU
akdasiak
Oniwaani
[Music]
Guy Yaya
Hi
[Music]
hello mitoo meet
please OK
every dehun mimu dehun o
iyai
mimu everyone miu
neasosomi OK everyone than you so for playing this game we mve to then exten GAME ARW So we have 3 minutes to play with Team every each ROUND Got FIVE emeral There
will be ROUND So Let go
to the
[Music]
US yes yes let's go
yo I think
GU
need IDE san
this bed touch please ta
Touch the bed, this is still here, where are you sleeping,
where are you sleeping, where are you, everyone,
where did you see, ah
Oh, so where did all of this
go? Where is my Ella, my senior? My legs are fine, but I'm
not good. I'm going too far, I'm going too far.
Where are you? I'm still at Wool's place.
It's on top of Wool, right?
Yeah yeah yeah yeah I'm not here, where is the
bed? It's below. So the bed is below, right? Where is
it? I'm on the second floor. I'm on the second floor. Ah, I'm here. I'm not here.
Where is the bed? It's underneath.
Yes, it's a white bed. Thank you. Yes, I
fell asleep.
[Music]
Oh, there will
be3,
there will
be
no, and this is
Battle
Blue
GoingGoing
atandforthe
CUTTERarePress
[Music]
F  Ah,
yeah, I feel like I'm falling. Is
it okay to hit someone? It's okay to hit someone. What is crouching?
Ah, this, that, so as not to fall, you have to squat like
this. It's forbidden to crouch. Oh, I'm not allowed to
[Music]
PeoplePeople
[  Music] I'm
sorry  It's
okay to hit,
but
[Music]
What color
What is it okay? What will you do? It's
okay, I'll try my best, okay?
I'll try my best, so I'll change, it's okay, I'll change
place for this round, ok, I'll change my place, thank you
Okay, good luck, thank you everyone, stubbornly, bye bye bye
Byles,
somewhere, um, up, up or down, which one is
no, up, what color is it, no,
what
color is it, if they're the same, is it the same, if they're the same,
pink, pink, this  It wasn't the color,
but is this okay? Yes, yes, yes,
oh, well, do your best, Kanade-chan, do your
best. Yes, you can hit me, okay
?
OffCanIseewhatyour
col
isokkuisYELL, uh, show me the color
[Music]
Leo,
tetete
[Music]
Well, then,
please, it's
okay even if you don't have it.
[Music]
Not grePINKYisgrepink
YELL
[Music]
and
isYGreenandPINKOUT
ONEBR
[Music]
Yeah
Disbanded at BC
[Music]
Do your best
Kanaris is cute, quite quite quite quite quite quite quite cute,
I am
quite quite quite quite Utari
ta,
fight and do your best
[Music]
Do your best for peace, do your best, do your best,
Yechimnem is
Quite quite cute
Ogo ah 5 ah 5 No,
I can't do that,
hey, it
's red, oh
oh oh, off, it's bad,
oh, it fell, who fell?
Good, no, no, no, no, no, no, it's
okay, I
did my best  It's okay
[Music] You
did your best,
it's okay, it's okay, next time, definitely next time,
[Music]
There's lots of green
Green, green, so
do your best [
Music]
[Applause]
[Music]
Next,
next, next time, do your best,
okay  Let's do our best, let's
do our best, yes, yes, good luck, yes
[music],
yes
good luck
[music]
[music],
do your best  I'll
try my best, I'll
try my best, I wonder if it's already on top
[Music] Are you
okay? Are you
okay? It's bad Are you okay? Are you okay? Are you okay? Are you holding it
? How much is Ostack?
Nice 4 stacks
[Music]
YES
Wago Ah, what is it?
Where are you? Red? Red? Where are you? Red? Where are you? I
'm fine. [
Music] But there are a lot of people.
[Applause]
Keep moving.
No, the staff who are still left are no good.
[Music] The
green is strong.
[Music]
[Applause] The
brown is slow.
BR
[Music]
Okari
Quite an enemy
[Music]
Nice Amazing
[Applause]
[Music] Your
water is strong, strong
[Music]
ELL
Hehehe,
there are emeralds  So
[Music] It looks like it'll be
fun, it's fun, it's fun,
yeah, there are a lot of emeralds, you know,
Maka and swords and stuff, I'm going home, yeah, there's a lot to
change, yeah,
do your best,
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Music  ]
[Music]
F
3 where is red where is
red
be there
[Music]
to
Who fell
[Music]
[Applause]
nanana nanana nice nice
nice nice nice
[Music]
naina no out do your best  Do your
best
[Music] You can
go to Pink
[Music]
Amazing There's
still some left Amazing No, it's okay There's a lot left
[Music]
Amazing
Amazing Good Good Good
Good
So next,
next, but in the end I managed to survive
[music]
So it's
amazing oh
[music]
Amazing
[music] I'm
strong I guess I'll go down here, down
here
[music]
So I'll choose a bed and that luggage is
here, all the luggage, the other luggage  So,
put it in here. Emerald
is fine. Emerald is using some kind of
item.
[Music] Please
wait a bit for the food to come
.
[Music]
What is that?
Tade-
chan
[Music]
Mao,
then, what kind of item do you
want? What about money? Is
30343434?
[Music]
What should I do? 30? Maybe?
Sword Sword
Ton Stone Stone Sword Sword Yeah yeah yeah Stone
Sword
is
[Music]
And I want a shield shield shield shield shield
use
Faci
to Fi
potion what potion is that
potion is
invisible potion
there is something like that right right right right 3 minutes
only but yeah yeah I'll buy it for legs
nah ok
So, um, Fightin Fightin
or Navigation, which one do you want? Which one do you want?
Navigation, Navigation, don't beat me up, I'm
not good at it, ah, I see.
[Music] I
see, then
VC, that group, BC,
I guess, I'll join, then, if it's Navigation, then,
Bo and Arrow and Shield
[Music]
Ino
[Music] Mase
Um, is the
Axe that goes in here okay
? Is it
shopping
? Opika
wouldlikeONE
SWORD
Shioha
[Music]
Well,
wait, I'll
do my best, I'm
kind of lost, easy easy, easily
confused
[Music]
Hey, it's okay, it's okay,
Navigator,
oh oh yeah yeah yeah, those who
believe, yeah,
sword and stone, I think  Axe, I guess.
Axe is stronger, so I think I
need an axe
and a potion. I think I need an axe and a potion.
But in Kana, it's like a bow and an arrow.
Arrow
shield. Well, I don't think I need a shield for the body. I
see. Then that 10 arrow is 3.
From emerald, I
want one stack, so let's go
to the yeah, one stack
might be a bit too much, yeah,
that 10 low, 10, what was it, 10
for sure, yeah, yeah, yeah, 30 arrows would
be good.  3030 Aro, then
use about 15 here,
Aro 30 Aro
, 9 Eri-senpai can also use a shield  I
might not be able to get a shield.
So I can't drink potions
then. Potions, uh, I think I'll be able to get the last one. I'll
buy a bow, an arrow and an axe first.
And then I'll probably use the money left over to buy potions. I see, maybe.  I
think I'll change it.
[Music] I
want shopping. I want
it. I'm not ready
yet ...
Just one, one by one, I think just one now,
then give me money, money, oh
, I took it,
[Music],
okay, I'll give you one stick, please,
Roro, I'll give you 30, yeah  Yeah
[music]
Oh, give me some money.
Um,
okay, I
got it. Okay, so how much money do you have left? I
have 12, so I think we could buy some potions.
Potions, I
think. Potions are a good idea. Right?  Shields and stuff.  I
think a phi phi shield
would be good. Okay, so how about a shield?
Yes, one shield please.
[Music]
Okay, so you have 5 emeralds left. If you
have 5, you can use an arrow.  I think it's okay.
Yes, do you want to make it an arrow? Yes,
10 is okay, so please give me 10.
Yes, yes, this is
it. Okay, let's go.
But do you have more than 46? I
think I bought 50, but
there's 46.
What is 46?
Maybe from here,
Ade-chan, please take that VC,
what VC, yeah
, it's okay, it's done, yeah, who's here,
yeah, the body picked it up, yeah, it's nice, the senior
picked it up, what  There are a lot of arrows
. There are a lot of arrows. Someone picked up
46. Who
is 6? Who is it?
[Music] It's
probably the one who
got the arrow. It's ...  Let's go in, okay?
All VC yeah yeah yeah, this
girl was there
Now I'll wait here, right, right outside. Yes,
sorry, thank you. This is the
team. Yes, right.
MeOverFOR
teigMETHESTILLmust
goNavigatorhelp
All
shigAll
Youallyouisdependon
fight
ifnaig
Navigatorbeideofthe
tempFightwithand
AR
have
Kill
EnemyitemsFall
Ayaya, if you defeat an enemy and the item drops, that's what you
got.  It's
okay to fight, but if the
person fighting dies, it's game
over.  If you fall down, you
can't talk, you can't talk, but
the game is over.
[Music] Can I get some food? [Music]
[Music] It's
okay to get some food.
[Music]
Satade-chan, um...  I'll make a group chat. I
guess I'll have to take it then.
[Music]
Okay, let's wait. I
can't hear you.
Wait a minute, I
muted you.  Ah,
in which tower should this body be? Maybe
we'll wait for you. Not now. Maybe not now.
Because it's only those three teams. Yes, yes,
do we like them? I see, yes, we're watching from here.  Maybe,
from here, over there, or from
here, yes, it looks like it's easier to see from here, right? Well, is it
okay from here?
Hello, um, Kanade-chan, here, here, over there,
that staff, staff only,
staff
[music],
here, yes, yes, it's here.
Wow, it's amazing
. Right now, I feel like I haven't found anyone yet. Chim
and Inaina's Ina and Anya.
And who can
fight?
Wow, I'm excited. Wow, I'm excited. Wow, wow,
and the other navigators are for
sale.  It's okay,
okay, I'm going to kill you, yeah, yeah, it's so
far away, isn't it, it's a bit far, a bit
far,
bumpy, exciting, hehehe, do your best, do your best
[music]
Everyone, wow, I see,
hey, you hit it, you hit it, oh, do your best,
do your best
So why don't you get closer
? Everyone is far away. That's right.
Oh no, it's bad. It's fallen. It's fallen. Well, it's
fallen. Please cheer me on. Wine wine. Okay. Yes.
Yes. It's fine. It's fine. It's fine. I
heard it fell.  Wow, I
can't climb that, oh, look, I'll show you around, oh,
thank you,
thank you, here
[music],
stand here, thank you, yeah, thank you, thank you, sorry, excuse me,
excuse me,
hey,
yeah, wow, Iofi, that's strong,
not this way, it's this way,
ah  Mira-senpai, wow, what dropped? That
bread, no, it wasn't your body that dropped it.
Okay, wow, it's strong, it's heading towards a strong fire, it
's going all the way, it's strong, it's going all the way, yeah, it's strong, it's
good.
[Music] It's
amazing, it's amazing.  That's nice, that's nice,
hey, someone's coming, they're fighting, yeah, I
can't see it but I can tell, I
can see it from here,
while eating dinner,
oh,
wow, do your best,
ah, what a
shame
Wow, Reine won.
Reine-senpai won.
Amazing. Senpai can fight.
Yes, yes, yes, I'll do my best. Do my best.
Do my best.
Well, shall we go to the bed? Yes, let's go. Next, we're here.
Let's go. The place is red.  I think it's good
. Is the red one this way? Maybe
this way? Yes, yes, that's right. Okay, no,
this way, maybe, this way, maybe this way. I don't know. Where is Kaade-chan
? It's here.
[Music]
Oh, where are we?  Where is it
? Can you decide?
Where is it
? Nao,
mochimochi,
Okay, then let's wait here. Ao, absolutely.
Yellow, blue, squirrel, pink.
Where is pink? Pink, pink, pink. Maybe it's not here. Where is that? Pink, huh?  There's
definitely no pink
Pink
Yellow
Blue Pink Maybe red Okay Maybe red Red Red
Okay That's good Yeah I'll do my best
Okay,
here it is Watch this [Music] Okay, I'll do my best Okay,
where are they
Everyone has to press F1 on the navigator  good
That's right, I'm going to do F1, yeah, F1, right? Wow, that's
difficult. Oh, maybe I should
n't have done that.
Fighter, ah, fighter, okay
?
Okay, okay. OK, okay.
[Music]
Lady, okay, let's
go.
Exciting, exciting, excited, Ah, F1 is fine, I
'll do my best, this is Kuni-senpai
, it's already starting, it's started, no,
maybe not yet, not yet
[music]
Still okay, is it the start, let's
go, te, ka, ka, heehee, I
can see it, I can see it,
papu papu po, who is it? I can see it, I can
see it, wow
It's scary, it's scary, I'm running away, let's
go home, see?
Oh,
I saw it, but I'm lost, it's here, oh, I'm lost,
no, it's okay, it's okay, I think it's difficult, everyone is a little strong, I think they won't come out, why, why are you
running away,
come on, why are you running away, yeah  The
shield is used. Hey, I'm
fighting. The
shield is used by smart people. [ __ ], it's
a bit clogged
. Hehe, wow, it doesn't fit at all.
Wow, it's difficult, do your best.
Oh, I hit him, I hit him, oh oh oh,
wow, I did it, yeah, I got hit, wow,
I did it, I'm
going, that's good, that's good
, hey, where can I see it,
ah, the very center,
oh oh oh  I
can see it, I
can see it, I can see it, I can see it, your eyes are here, here
, can you wait?
What is this? Oh, no
, no, oh, your
movements are
good, it's bad, it's bad, it's
strong, it
's too strong
[music]
It's no good, I ca
n't hit it at all, it's
difficult, far away  This is too much
Wow,
ha,
do your best Wow, I can't hit that spot Do your best, I can do it, OK, OK, wow, I'm
using a spot, spot, spot, spot,
but oh, is that on the right?
Is it close? It's running away, I can see it, running
away, running away, what
?  Music]
So, you can see the armor.
Ah, behind, behind, behind. Ah, I
can see it. Sorry, I hit him. It's okay, it's
okay.  I
was totally fine. Yes, I could see it. I could see it.
Good luck, I'll do my
best
. Wow, no, no, good, good, good, good, wow, I did it. Wow, I'm
shaking. I'm shaking
so much. I'm
nervous, nervous, nervous. Right, well,
I've been popular up
until now.  Maybe I'll give it to you, but I did it. I
have a lot of swords, I've
done this too.
[Music]
Then it's the finale. Yes,
the two of us will fight. That's right, that's right.
Wow, I'll do my best with 22 of them.
Yes, 22 of them.
Okay.
[Music]
Group, you're
green. Yeah
yeah
yeah. [Music] This is gray, this is gray, and this is red and over there is green. Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah. I can't really see the color over here. Well, it's far away. Yeah yeah. The navigator here is  You can't hit it,
right? Well, if it's in the middle, yeah
, maybe you can do it, I see, yeah, yeah, yeah, it's better to be as
close to the red as possible, yes, it's easier to hit,
but yeah, you have to move forward, hmm hmm  I
can't fight, so thank
you, welcome, pania pania, wow, wow, lady, lady, lady, wow, scary, scary, wow, it's okay, it's okay, I can do it, I can do it, yes, I'll do my best, do my best, I, I, who, who is my opponent? I can't see their name, certainly there's no buff
Oh, Raine, Raine, it's all over the place, where is Raine? Hey, I can't see her, Raine, where are you? I'm
still
waiting, right, right
, right, come
here, come to the center
[Music] In
the center,
there are lots of them, they're coming  It's coming It's coming
Oh oh oh yellow yeah yeah yeah Ah, it's
more purple
Ah I
can see it Wow, it's so cool Just a little bit Oh
yeah
yeah Wow, come
on, this Wow, what? I'm already in the middle too Oh, is this it?
Wow, this is bad
Ah  Riri
Rinja I'm still at Apple I see, it's
far away
[Music]
Far away Nice I
see your name Fight here
Do your best
Senpai is
too strong, I did
n't do anything, but I
did it, it's amazing, wow [Music] Pa Yusha, I
did it, Squirrel Senpai was too strong, this is strong,
ok, let's do a group voice, shall we?
Yes, yes, yes, congratulations, thank you, congratulations ...
[Music]
of
after
forforthe
Hey hey hey hey, that's no good
Thank
you
en en
forplaythe
[Music]
[Applause]
Photo
Ote
[Music]
Tet
taa item here this item yes
yes oh
Die, sleep,
sleep,
sleep, sleep, yes slip, slip,
slip,
wait for the orchestra, take a picture, it's San, we
're still here, we
still need to stream, so it's outside, right?
[Music]
After handing
them
out, I
went outside.
[Music]
Wait, wait ...
Here, here, here
[Music]
Yes, here, here,
here, maybe it's okay underneath, yes, back, Pao,
aaa, it's okay, okay
,
Piao, it's good,
Otowa, shi, ya
[Music]
Gebed ga ne
[Laughter] Let's
take one more photo.
Otowa
go
eeee
[Music]
Kiwa
Thank you, thank you, you did a great job.
Thank you very much.
Yeah,
see you later, see you later, see you later. Bye, see you
later.
Eddie?  So thank you
Nepi thank you
Ko
[Music]
[Applause]
Oh, well ...
[Music]
Hey,
okay, thank
you very much for
what
the How
[Music]
the
GU me put the
[Music]
indindonesia
F
SA me the
[Music]
GU
pleas
S
may you
know will
in
guyscoun
DownONE
[Laughter]
[Music]
[Laughter  ]
mzzcounDowncoun
Downcoundown
Ma
[Music]
GUin
[Music] [
Music]
SATU
[Music] [
Music] [
Music] Na
toang
toangtokangkangsail [Music]
KJBU
JIA [Music]
La [Music] [
Music]
[Applause]
Pa Singdar
[Music]
[Applause]
guys
[Music] I'm a
besar woman's pot of besar ...
Tapantira nya The
focus is
Tira
Pachi
Utapan
as
Soa
[Music]
[Applause]
guys
Uwaaruko
pasa
[Music]
N
Rupama
[Music]
Sari
Poko
[Music]
Ere Ma
nite  No, I thought
so,
PERmusim
SOL
[music]
PERRatMU
Rmusic
PER
key wow, amazing,
amazing,
Kankanta
[music]
Heto
Jira thank
everyone and
you
GUdid
[music]
GR is hologram o de hologram
huh wait
what no no no
no no head a little
hologram hololive
manai ro na
roro
live a
[music]
low live
ma
[music]
nafushi
hololive
life se ha
malive
e
sry so
[laughing]
[Music]
V
hitam
guysPM
What was it 5
[Music]
PM Official Channel
Yaatsu
Anpan no no no no Os bye-
bye
[Music] Popipopipo papipo [Music] Popipopipopipapapapapapipopapapapapi Pipapipapapapapipapapipa puii Pipipipipapapapa Pipapipipapapapapapapapapapapapipa Pipapipipapapapapapapipa Pipapipipapapapapapipa Pipipipipapapapapipa Pipipipipapapapipa  Beep beep ...
Beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep
[music]
BANGBANGKU
nnn
[music]