[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
hahaha
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
daddy key
hello
[Music]
Kitty
no PNG yeah no PNG I mean when I tap out
uh the game status but that's okay
that looks different your chat is
chilling up there at the top
I thought would play in um full screen
today I'm lagging a bit nah
no no I'm not
yeah well
Diablo is currently taking up 5000 MB
of my I don't know
process whatever I don't know what that
means OBS is taking up four thousand
and my face is taking up
600. it's better than before it went
down a bit
yeah
and also I lowered the quality of the
game
quite a bit I played it a little bit
yesterday it looked really beautiful
like also I made a test character
it looked really nice yesterday
um but yeah I changed some things to low
a five gigabyte of ram I guess that's a
gigabyte also my Google Chrome just to
chat alone is taking up 500 MB
I closed the
other browser but
[Music]
um
yeah apparently
there is I totally know what that means
when I say that but apparently that's
like um like a memory league but I
totally like uh hahaha
um but yeah it's okay I got it I think I
got it to work out unless it suddenly
gets worse
um
yeah
Chrome eats your RAM yeah but I mean I
could even close the chat window but
then all I see would be the small ones
up top of my OBS screen but I could do
it oh actually I want to try out because
I'm using hyper chat that should already
improve it but I do want to know how
much it will go down
it's at 450. not that we really needed
but okay let me close it here
I wonder will the game take up even more
RAM once I really play it though
wait well now now Chrome is gone
completely so
that's extra 500 MB RAM
delete us I mean I still see you but it
will be harder to catch certain comments
they'll be gone instantly I could have
you guys open on my phone if I wanted to
um
I couldn't even make it make it Jets
that uh how much have now four thousand
separated it so that you know
um
you see so now
stay still guys stay still
so like this
now
there's plenty of you on the screen
[Laughter]
I see you I see you
there should not be
anyone double I think
at once
I I would hope so but like you you maybe
show up here first and then on the very
left one and then you go to the middle
and then you go to the right one
go up up up up you climb your way up
yeah it's all right though
um
it the game seems fine I mean it's kind
of sad that I have to lower the quality
so much
I guess so much for yesterday's
conversation of I don't need to upgrade
my PC that's not true I never said I
don't need to I mean I mean no I mean I
I didn't really feel the need until now
and then here it is now I feel the needs
for it but but but so many people have
been complaining about this game taking
up too much RAM okay it's not just me
and and
it's a coincidence and how
come in you know
that was open to improving my perceived
thingy stuff
I didn't say I did not ever want to do
it yeah
um
I had a yummy breakfast today
I'm drinking yummy fresh pressed juice
orange juice
I got water
I've got a raspberry chocolate muffin
if I need a snack
I'm gonna pour some more water
okay we're going to play the open Beta
of
uh wait I want a new character the open
Beta of uh this game uh Diablo 4 which
did I get it right it comes out in June
nice wait I want to do something real
quick
okay yeah no no no no that's not what I
want
um
oh yeah six six oh sixth of June 5th of
June maybe it depends on your time zone
did you ever play Diablo Oh My Sweet
Summer child
you don't know my history with Diablo do
you
I didn't
on my channel I have already played
um
here I can show you all the instances
this was Diablo 2 resurrected stream
number one
actually I may have made some changes
after that
this this ah oh wait part four
did I just make
um did I really stream it that much I
think I just made some thumbnails ahead
of time I streamed down at least once
and then oh look at this oh wow wow wow
beautiful that was a beautiful thumbnail
I played it at least twice and then I
played at least for ice because this was
also a thumbnail
and then this yes we had a collab a
Diablo resurrected collab and you know
when I was small when I was a little
itty bitty blah blah blah blah blah
um I
tried playing it as a child and I was
always too scared and I never got a past
well
what's her name
what was her name that lady's name
and Darielle yeah
scary but sometimes I would jump into
my mom's
my mom's play
file say file and just play you know a
little bit play around where she was
um
yes uh no I don't know which character
which class we should go to but first of
all I was really pleasantly surprised
that there are like
uh similar or the same is there anyone
missing I feel like
I mean the Rogue isn't that just the
Amazon basically I don't know
but it feels like there's a that Crow is
busted early oh
[Music]
necromancer
man
so yesterday I played five minutes with
the druid
it was nice with the bunk stick that was
fun
not sure who to go for
I mean I think I do not want to be a
barbarian
even though she's cute
ah
broke so Rogue can do both close and far
combat
um
Barb is hard oh really looks so fluffy
though
it has fluffy companions
Okay so
I don't like having skeletons around me
all the time maybe I it was really good
that I didn't get Kelly's design
oh it's not my face
my face that'd be it's
hmm But so sorry I mean I feel like
Necromancer is basically just a less
boring version of the sorcerer
because it doesn't necromance
and then I feel like Necromancer is just
an upgrade to the sorcerer
hot takes
um
so sir is wicked fun
[Music]
yes it is he has more physical magic
physical as in what close combat magic
or what
sorcerer is fun
druid
yeah I was thinking of the drill too
like fireball What which one sorcerer
right
well yeah I mean fire is nice and all
but
wasn't kaella playing the sorcerer
if I'm the second Holo member playing
Diablo 4 I don't want to play the same
thing she did
yeah okay so that one's out then no no
no I saw her blasting fire it looked
cool but I can't play the same thing
even if it's just an open Beta okay so
for me it's between
necro and Druid it's Druid really
difficult
I only played five minutes not even
hmm Droid week
bad weak damn okay I'll take the cracked
one all right character creation this
makes me really happy too because you
can't choose
like you there's an actual character
creation like what
oh
she looks like uh Alice who just came
out of the asylum
oh they all maybe kind of look like they
just came out of the Asylum
um yeah customized yeah yeah yeah I will
I will
just like a starting point
should we create me
scary so scary
Wednesday oh
okay well I guess we'll try to create me
um okay done
necro is really fun oh yeah damn
yeah I thought it was um also nice that
there's like different body types I mean
you can't change the body type of a
class apparently so it's body type
locked no gender lock anymore which is
cool but no now we have body type block
um I'm not this flat we cannot create
myself
done
okay what what can we do there's is
there oh
is there a purple color
no
um no purple maybe blue is the closest
done to purple or
yeah I guess I'll do blue
monster yes very interesting man you can
see those who
what is Vans like this unless you're
like really buff and muscular
I don't have veins like this at all
unrealistic but even with really little
um
settings right now she looks quite nice
magic veins
It's pretty dope she's really pretty why
are you so pretty face variations oh
wait oh
oh
[Music]
um
she looks like she got some Botox in her
lips
that looks like more natural
that looks
also natural
that is a double chin which is also
looks good on her actually but it's like
a scary overall face impression
okay
I will what's this four one two
I guess I'll take the fourth one
Kardashian
skin tone I'm kind of yellow unlike what
Kobo said
uh wait
well I mean anime be like light as [\h__\h]
go white girl go that's pretty yellow
that looks um a bit
I mean it's like
I don't know
she doesn't really look healthy is what
a lot of people tell me too so I guess
it applies
oh one step back
and that's like the more
Rosy version but still
I don't know
no I gotta I gotta go with this I mean
we're probably never gonna see
I can't recruit Perfection oh probably
we'll never be able to really see her
this nicely up close anymore all right
okay next we have hairstyle what do you
got
I like this one
didn't we just talk about recently that
like in terms of new hairstyles in the
future for takanasi kiwawa I I was
surprised nobody has ever rocked this
before but if anyone did then it would
be Ollie or Kelly possibly
nice though even the short one looks
good on her damn oh I like this
but we're Necromancer though a bald is
kind of hot I saw it on the other
character too on the Druid why does Bob
look so good on them what the hell
um
hair oh that's already looping
I mean and nobody got banged I accept
this one thanks
well is that a ponytail oh looks like a
Viking all the fancy Vikings
on TV have that hairstyle
ponytail is nice too but
um
so then even this one
oh you know what we're necromancers I
want to be cool I'm gonna go with this
one
I'll take this one
facial hair ah
can we Zoom oh yeah
she's why is she sweating is it so hot
quality will definitely be nicer if I
had it higher but oh and OBS it doesn't
look so bad I guess you guys probably
watch it a little bit smaller than me
these are nice okay now do we have like
a orange
oh
yes girl
even with some white highlights oh wait
a second oh hot
interesting gradations I think the Druid
didn't have so many interesting
gradations but okay so Necromancer can
be fancy huh
do you hear the game begin by the way I
think it's pretty quiet right now I
should probably make it higher
I raised it a little bit
tell me if it gets too loud but like
yell at me
can't hear it okay well now maybe a bit
better
okay we should go for the copper Shimmer
Maybe
Auburn
Auburn or copper Shimmer
as if it really matters
I think I'll go with copper Shimmer cop
copper is hot
girls with copper hair hot hot what does
the other stuff look like oh ah the
blonde colors kind of all looks so [\h__\h]
but
yeah I'll go with a copper Shimmer based
agreed
yes you get it
okay next we have makeup oh let's go
girls talk
oh
oh I I I would like to have something
edgy too that's cool
that's um
[Music]
this is like
emo emo kiwawa
oh man crying all that
mascara away
oh this one gives her a nice lipstick
um
quite nice
I shall go with
I like this one
oh my God
I feel like a golf Queen
nice
so then we have markings oh yeah we want
some markings yes
oh
wow wow oh that that's like okay there's
some Demons Inside me if I have this
I need exorcism
oh God now this one is like probably
I have a lot of voices in my head
so I wrote them down on my body
because that's what my voices are
telling me to do
[Music]
um
this one is
sadistic
this one gets a bit more
neutrally
this one's nice too
this one's kinky
[Laughter]
there's nothing on the scale because
that's exactly how much the boobies
weigh
um
oh this one's kind of cool I like the
contrast looks like uh I have like this
power arm I'm gonna turn into Metroid
Prime anytime soon
oh armor I ran out of makeup for this
one and I don't have the money to run to
the drugstore for more
on this one as well
this one's the shy one
I'm not sure if I really want to do this
this one this one as well as like oh man
I I I have some bodies in my basement
okay very interesting well nice
Necromancer creepy markings yeah okay
let's go for
don't we all
yeah yeah I got some chickens in my
basement
that's where all that comes from yeah
yeah there's so many choices damn it
wait only six no six pages
damn there's so many
I'll go for this I feel like if I like
um
put my arm this arm straight to the
front and then hold
it's supported with the other arm then
then I can blast some magic out of it
you know what I mean
I'll be like
[Music]
yeah like that
[Laughter]
the arm power
okay okay oh my King's color oh
[Music]
I like this one though
yeah the light ones are kind of weird
but I guess it could be
I could get used to it too
I'll just go
with the fresh blood one
[Music]
okay ah
what's up what's Kiara but a bit more
intimidating in a like creepy or
I don't know
I'm scaring way
no
kiliara oh kiliara
okay
let's go
um I read this before I'm fine with this
one I don't know which guys prefer but
I'll go with this one
here we go
XX Kiara x x
shower time I skipped this one before so
that I could have a genuine reaction it
was never meant for humankind
it was forged as a refuge from the war
but when the High Heavens and the
burning Hells
instead
it became a new Battleground in this
eternal conflict that's me on the horse
she could have grew called the haradrim
has kept Mortals safe
but now we're swans powerful order is a
husk of what it was
and sanctuary's ancient creators have
returned to claim the hearts of
humankind
[Music]
this is the story of their downfall
Gambar Skyrim Horus cute
[Music]
quite nice even low Graphics I'll need
to watch this with high graphics though
later
[Music]
is this like a continuation of previous
Diablos or just like randomly or or like
a
just recreating the story
does it have any connection
no
after free other time periods to
continue okay
here I guess
Grandpa
look it looks hot
my horse dead now [\h__\h]
oh
horses no more but I guess that's some
food for now
a horse
unfortunately but
gotta make the most of it
scared I'm gonna look badass Necromancer
man
don't be so terrified it's not not like
I imagine you would be
breathing
all kinds of briefings here
oh no
circle's dead
oh I just thought no just one second
before the half a second before they
changed the scenes
oh
scary
I should find better shelter before I
freeze okay oh we have a nice voice
different than the drone's voice I think
so everybody every character has their
own voice actor I suppose every link
class
all right so what I already really like
and notice is that
we are
we're able to automatically collect
items when we run over them I love that
absolutely love it
do I already have a spell race skulls
and raise a skeleton from a corpse to
fight for you one of your skeletons
happen I never played Necromancer before
but that makes sense rice counting
bravely summons
wait wait once all of your skeletons
happen summon Ray skeleton briefly
summons uh
skeletal priests to empower your minions
for five seconds
um increasing the damaged by 20 and
healing them for 10 of their maximum
life
skirmisher Warriors word sword shielding
sword wielding skeletal minions
make that hat deal 40 decrease damage
okay cool
try it wow
follow me deadbeats you are in kiwawa
stream today
also there's like a little more time I
need more time
Sushi skill who's
ah
yeah that is immediately more damage
that's nice
oh hi
Coolio I like that and he's doing pretty
well
oh yeah I can summon up to five
cracked
Kraken
come with me
dead bees lurking now
wow
are they gonna also start dancing like
in Kelly's backgrounds
oh no dead people can I get one out of
you too no
what does that do is that just a failing
animation
oh wow I don't even have to do anything
oh wait salmon
why does it not come out of this one I
thought it was maximum five
oh wait what did I how many
once all of your skeletons have been
summoned I guess no maximum four
fresh of course that was fresh
it doesn't have to be a human before
it's lost but didn't I get the other
ones from uh
wait that's it
I have to kill it oh oh gotta be faster
than them okay okay
yeah I got three now okay okay
oh
spawning out of these wolves
logical problems
but the fourth maximum machines
don't question it wait was this the same
thing in um
in Diablo one and two
I mean I think they had necromancers too
right
I'm gonna raise the priest oh
[Music]
the logic
so this is the open Beta but today so
they already have online payments
everywhere
thanks in the dark
we have arrived me as a city careful
he's a wild one
yeah they do huh damn nice
he's a wild one who's a wild one
don't worry about my skeletons by the
way
I know it's scary but what's going on
here just ignore what's behind me and
tell me what's going on right here it's
just I don't worry I'm a good person
I suddenly intrude on your household
with my four skeletons just to help you
surely I'm a good person don't I look
like a good person to you with my shaped
half-shaped head huh what's it to you in
my fancy makeup also in hush
I'm sorry wondering
maybe I only see that commitment just
stumbled into town and started causing
trouble and they don't
spilling from the ruins kill us all kill
us all oh okay you want me to kill you
all
they're back you'll explain okay
imaginary
I didn't really though
there is evil staring in the ruins to
the north
that poor monk back there must have gone
inside
I say that's unfortunately okay
he's a Healer
definitely okay I talked to Banny again
I uh say it isn't safe here apparently
could you protect us from whatever is
out there
we have nowhere else to turn by the way
Kiel was like is gathering strength five
seconds I will bring it to you you guys
really scared me with the queue on
Friday thank you
yeah
it's really no issue and I wonder until
what time it is tomorrow
it was only bad on Friday apparently
yeah and Edwin Kyla was playing it last
week
what I didn't even do anything now I get
a quest complete
does someone know how long on Monday
4 P.M jst
for am jst tomorrow 4pm GMT
oh so like still half a day
after today
you okay oh wow I like this is already
the fourth di apple game but like it's
still kind of the same
I'm however so happy I couldn't be
happier that the um
inventory looks much bigger
it's separate and also uh I've been told
that items don't take up like different
amounts of slots anymore
is the most triggering thing ever to me
and oh just
oh this is gonna make this into a series
in June
I already I already want to make it into
a series damn I wonder how long the game
is
okay we can reap we can decompose we can
Hemorrhage and we can bone splinters
splinters and bones
[Music]
uh
so and do I have to spend two up here in
order to go down here
oh it's skill tree
well oh there's many things
yeah okay that's how it seems to be
let's see what are these
uh-huh
uh generate Essence four per enemy hit
sweep hit ah sweep and ethereal Scythe
in front of you dealing free damage
hitting an enemy with rape increases
your damage reduction by 15 or two
seconds what should I do guys
seven per second tear the flesh from an
enemy dealing 9 damage per second and
forming a usable corpse with the flesh
every oh 2.5 seconds okay
I can change it for free at a time
the one on the right in composers man
burst an enemy's blood dealing 7 damage
hemorrhage
has a 20 chance to form a blood orb
heal you for 15 percent
maximum life and pick up cool this is
not it's like a like a healing one
struggle much we should invest in that
too
Maybe
at my level three up to level 15 free
Skillet whoa Coolio
Fire free Bone splinters dealing six
damage each each subsequent time an
enemy is hit by the same cast of bone
splinters you gain one Essence alright
let's try that one
uh do I have more to spend no okay oh
but now I put that down there no
[Music]
I know it's here
it's already here okay it's my left
attack now
was it already
I don't know
okay Coolio I want to test it
should I talk to these people
I'm a vendor oh
what do I have I have the same
stuff except 21 armor
oh it's kind of the same
yeah okay probably no need for this now
what about the
what wasn't there uh
no
A Healer
wow cool
ah
sound the flask sound
I want to hear it again
nice it sounds just like back in the day
new stock delivered oh there's a time
for when it gets stuck
I love it
okay so we have armor and healing here
come my little skeletons I'm happy that
they don't just disappear
um like time wise
can I start to see the map
oh okay
oh
is there like more past here
is this the whole map for the whole game
or or just for like now I wonder
kind of have to go upwards I don't know
if it's left or right but I'll go this
way no
maybe it's connected
whole map just for the Bella okay
whoa
hey does that take up mana
I don't think it did
for essence
this
is an enemy is hit by the same cast of
One splinters are you you gain one
essence
generates it yeah
oh
is this uh
I can't pass
[Music]
okay this is my basic attack all right
all right all right cool
and this is
ah I already have a weak healing potion
upgradable at level 10.
wait
does that mean they're not in my
inventory they're just there
oh
[Music]
oh don't carry posters
wait how do I do this again
oh
even more room and wait do they how do I
fill them back up
if I use them all up do I do I how do I
get more
very different but I like it I mean
enemies drop them oh
the Healer also fills them up I suppose
they drop red orbs
let's try the handwrap school
[Music]
I don't have anything for my hands oh
I like games where
um every armor piece gives you like an
actual difference in look
[Music]
oh that looks really scary but it's all
right
because in many games it's like
you have only one main outfit right
or you have like I know different
outfits depending on
your class or so I don't know but it's
nice I like it when you get different
ones depending on the armor and then it
actually looks like what it looks like
on the picture
um
what trans something I've heard of that
in other games before what so you can
change the looks
you want to join my team
oh potion charges ah automatically
picked up one not at Max Capacity cool
what should I go up on
what was that
buckler
a shield I already have one
wait compare a shift
all right is it the complete same thing
oh okay I'll sell wait 12 item power 22
item power
item power as in like strength of [\h__\h]
what does that mean
it's better
right
what is item power
you can rotate it I know
[Music]
uh one has more self well one can be
sold for more okay if it's just a
money difference then I sell that one
oh it looks good
I like the the ground graphics
by the way I'm not sponsored but I'm
already really enjoying this
looks like I could fall down
she kind of drops down here that's cool
let's go guys
let's kill some more skeletons who don't
want to be our skeletons they will
regret their life choices
but then aren't alive anyway so
I guess there's not much to regret ooh
stinky
have you guys tried the open Beta
already you can just like you don't I
thought maybe you would have to buy the
game or so no
you can just
whoa
yes no time already max level yes
25 wizard oh
through it already finished play two
characters wow okay so a lot of you guys
tried is this the the orb thingy the
healing potion thingy
I think so
also I got a I got a level up I'll take
another one for now and then I'll think
about it
so much stuff try this tunic I think
that's better
oh
plus 47
sick oh
um wow I'm looking uh sick
he hit
what is this scary scary room why is it
so empty
shiny deadbeats need glow sticks no they
don't need it there I have glow sticks
in their body and like their whole spine
is basically a glow stick
you're so shiny
cute so you can't lose them also I guess
they kind of work as like a
an extra light like a flashlight
my chickens
I'm gonna make the fire go away
why did I do that twice even though I
kind of knew what was gonna happen I
guess my skeletons didn't take that much
damage wait there's one missing uh how
do I raise them again
yeah it's happening
what am I doing
don't I get a fourth one if you're not
fresh anymore
yeah he's stuck oh he is there ah
open the door yourself you don't need
Mommy to help me help you what the hell
cute oh there's a fountain over there
Striders leggings
Plus 19.
oh I don't like the color combination
here but okay
I almost forgot about him if it wasn't
about for you guys I would have just
left him behind
Slaughter down
oh everyone who is not my skeleton
shall finally be released and go to
heaven
what does that sound scary
right click is
thank God mine are so glowy otherwise I
would try to kill them too
make no mistake these are my skeletons
cute
but uh maim kill
pushed for blood yum yum yum
they can take quite a bit of damage
second of all
oh they do a lot of damage
[Music]
they're so helpful
whoa magic glow
I don't even need to do to do anything
from the milk they drink uh I'll I'll
leave the milk drinking to them I don't
like milk
I mean not not just you know
just milk
okay
get stuck
on the fence
my game did something funny for a moment
when I'm behind the fence it looked like
the shots got stuck behind it but you
know that's actually like realistic so
I'm fine with that
look is tasty
to each their own I mean I think I'm
jealous you know when you enjoy milk
which I can't I'm jealous
Tapped Out weirdly which I mean not
really I think I dragged something top
of the top of my screen
because I'm in Window mode
does Diablo ever do DLCs
question mark
oh did I Circle
oh I did
they do yes
and those DLCs do they ever add like
extra classes
hell touched corridors
very edgy oh wait I can do a level up
yeah they do oh fun okay
they should add Phoenix Class
anyway should I continue up here or
should I go down
Bloodlines blood surge
blight sever there's so many choices
bone spare ah
anyone who named Necromancer already
helped me out I don't want to think too
much go down
really
blood surge spare
oh okay let's do both what's blood surge
draw blood from enemies dealing six
damage and expel a blood Nova dealing 15
damage blood surges no damage is
increased by 10 per enemy drained
up to 50 percent
yeah unfortunately my brain is not
taking in any of that
I can test them yeah because your bones
are on the ground
I want to do the the bloody one for now
skill has been also assigned to the
action bar okay cool right click okay
I'm kind of tired again why am I so
tired I actually didn't sleep that much
because
I got two addicted to Queen's Gambit I
admit
oh what was that my blood search
I'm almost done with Queen's Gambit now
but holy [\h__\h] it's such a good show
I was like I'm just gonna watch them one
episode at most what did I do I watched
two of course I did
of course I did
so good
why am I so late to the party
why why and why uh what did I just get
the hand drips
oh no mine are better
[Music]
oh yeah yeah also yeah we had actually
time
skippity scoop
uh time was adjusted back to Summertime
and yeah so I lost one hour suddenly and
I was wondering
and then it already started that one and
I was like why is good at streaming
so early
and then suddenly it skipped from 2 am
to 3 A.M
I understand now
so yeah one last hour but it's okay
I don't know how long I'll stream but
um
I
I could put something into these tiny
rooms
my brother is coming
I told him to not
come until like on my stream is down so
it could be 11 pm could be midnight I
told him
yeah I just don't want him to join in
the middle oh
this is
that box
yeah that was easy
yeah he's um just staying at my place
for two nights
because he's got some job interviews
so tomorrow I will not scream I guess
Western Diablo again with chronulator oh
if she's interested sure of course I
also wanna if Kyla plays again in June
or whoever like we should still win a
whole party
maybe Callie will start playing as well
that would be really cool because it
didn't really happen with resurrected
um and that's okay
but this is a completely new game in
this like online focus so
would be really cool to have a group I
still don't really know how it works
[Music]
exactly but
wow holy [\h__\h] I'm so strong
and what if you play can you like go
into dungeons together
[Music]
is that a thing
what's up Kelly's PC that's comment went
way too fast sorry
yeah oh okay but what if someone chose
like the easy mode and someone chose the
difficult mode
like what's with those differences how
are they gonna work that out
it's not a problem
party leader
the scales you are skilled
you have to be the same game difficulty
scales for every person
uh-huh
okay please don't scale it to the
difficult one
but I don't know
I doubt they would play and then like a
Madness Hellbound whatever
oh God
decapitated priest oh no
are you good
oh
my God
there
is
not taking any damage
little [\h__\h] why am I taking way more
damage than they
got one
oh easy easy
[Music]
it's totally fine like my potions keep
on recharging too it's nice
let's go that's fun
dead beats let's go
um
thank you deadbeat it's just so nice to
me
thank you for always being so nice to me
okay let's see let's look at the items
that was
much easier than my my first um boss
battle in
in the Apple too
but and Dario was was it the one outside
or the one inside because I was
struggling with both but I already had
the biggest problems ever with that one
first outside
spooky boss
which is not really a real boss though
okay and Daryl is the inside one what
about the outside one black raven yeah
so I would put this on the same like
uh level not in difficulty but in
importance
as bloodraven but blood Raven
definitely more difficult than this
or I'm just better now
nah
oh plus 40. that's a good Scythe that's
exactly what I need oh but it takes up
two oh
five now
I can rape the big grass now oh but also
a dagger but I'm not a dagger kind of
person am I
yeah no I'm not I'll take the size
was more difficult right I I think so
cosplaying can we
okay I guess I can teleport out now I
just want to check if there's like some
secret stuff
used to my RPG games
this game doesn't have as much
like stuff to find
where is this
oh
you get out
huh
well that was fun
is that aren't we somewhere else now
different from where we entered
I guess that makes sense because we also
left from a different space where am I
where was I
um
not sure
I get some resources to find later
Fun Dungeon yeah I agree I enjoyed that
very much
oh this is isn't this where we entered
yeah yeah yeah what was in here by the
way oh I can't go through
come on
that's actually a realistic touch that
we come out somewhere else
was this cliff
rather not even attempt to jump
yeah I know yellow point I just want to
check you know every corner you know me
you know
me like everything I'm sorry it wasn't
always like this
I feel like
streaming games has made me to this kind
of person
because I wasn't in that corner yet
before I didn't I missed it I would have
been mad at myself if they had some cool
items
and I missed it
gold farming yeah because I will totally
need all that gold uh okay inside
do you not think I would
you are under estimating me the old
ruins are clear
your town should be safe now travels to
talks huh By the Light you are Heavens
no I'm Health Center
I'm so sorry we haven't any coin to
offer oh don't worry I grind it a lot
what do we have hot stew good company
and stay foreign
if you join us
medieval twerking
buy my fitting twerk girl
hey hey hey
I love wait they feel real
me
I was just joking
[\h__\h] I just saved y'all
what
[Music]
why
are they like people
did they use me
um
I mean they didn't joke about stew I
should have taken that seriously
last one what the [\h__\h]
no more medieval twerking
ew
that's my biggest pet peeve please don't
do that around me that's so disgusting
my coats and from my mouth is this game
over Pearl hatred a father during his
children on a pyre and a mother molded a
new age From the Ashes
drug regions don't spit yeah
I saw the week made strong a pack of
lambs feasting on wolves
it just looks exactly like the the ocean
I went to with Cali you know that photo
sorry sorry that was more important now
this look sounds like it remember that's
fan art then came a sphere of light
piercing hatred's heart and he who has
found in Chains was set free
[Laughter]
yay where's Cali
it's an awesome right
right
I'm just gonna announce on vacation
onto this kind of red
did you like I don't know
fill it with rose petal liquid
can I stop this do it am I supposed to
like do something no okay
I thought that maybe it would have to
get up by spamming attack or something
that's pedals
my mother's blood
experience
with this her glory
why why are they doing this you die
[Music]
yo this other
dead woman bodies
oh oh oh he's my friend
thanks dude y'all
Joseph
they're coming it's a whole damned
Village
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] is going on
I want a refund for my own son vacation
[Music]
you treat me like that
you'll pay
10 is for breakfast
like us
are you okay
that was all of them
not willing we have sand now beautiful
where now
oh that was it you're the madman from
the shed madman those Heretics
just like you ah to my wits and escaped
try to get inside the chapel but it was
locked
yeah I mean what manner of evil is this
petos
of blood that's interesting beautiful
they
they must have fed them to me Chihuahuas
throwing up too much these days
they kept it locked up for a reason
the key might be on that woman who is
leading them
okay this is fun
skeleton friends let's go
open the door okay key is on the woman
wait
inside what
where is she
I'm clearing my throat so much
ah
what where is
loot the chapel key from when where's
[\h__\h] her corks what
what is
blancho
where is that
open
right now
wow many EXP
I'll check in a moment we're kind of
busy now
I see so slow are you gonna for real
gonna be this slow
I'm just gonna go ahead all right
you just catch up later
only fire can cleanse the
bit of that the ones I was fed
I can barely hear him
oh
poor old guy he saves me and I'm not
giving him the time of the day
oh
nice
set the decapitated one
his new title
hey everybody
[Music]
gather for our Cult of the Lamb ritual
I'm gonna marry one of you guys now
or two or three
pretty eyes shameful
I'm our father has granted you a path to
Salvation
and yet you stray from it every
opportunity
a drink aggressive
covet
and steal
shameful really
where is that coming from
the bathroom
[Music]
what what
oh
she's from you coming to devour our
world
salvation lies not in the light
it's in you
faith has taught you to deny your
heart's desire if evil
break the chains
and discover
who you were meant to be
break the chains
and be beautiful well she sounds so nice
break off chains just like Daenerys
Targaryen
oh [\h__\h]
brainwashed
oh
money
it's me
I brought your child into this world
[Applause]
[Music]
laughs
holy [\h__\h] can I really show this on
YouTube
they have
a mother
mommy the first
go to the dry steps
and continue your preparations
and yet she comes to this tiny ass
Village yeah
you came to thank the light I had a
vision
sheesh
how did I get out here what were you
doing in Nevis I want to hear both
you collapsed inside that I thought that
Darkness had swallowed you
uh
put this cursed place to the torch what
happened to you in there
I
saw a vision hmm
a horned demon
she said the Lords of hell are coming
hmm
she wanted to
help survive
help them help
called them her children and they
welcomed her like
a mother
no
it cannot be
I must report to the cathedral kill you
are a hero of humanity there is
a man of questionable loyalty but he
knows how they forbidden he might be
useful to us
bring him to the cathedral in keovashad
Hermit and you will be in the lights
favor
okay
fine level five already damn okay
um
that was pretty nice
it is the next step uh this one
but enemies damaged by Blood surges Nova
while you are healthy then gain one
stack of overwhelming blood when you
have five seconds of overwhelming blood
your blood surge overpowers
I'm trying to use bonus damage based on
the sum of your current life and 45 life
mmm
I know what makes me do more damage
all right
I'll just invest one more
those are like additional bonuses okay
Coolio
I wanna ask one more thing
uh what were you doing here looking for
the town priest
sending tides and came to find out why
because I near the village I
I went to investigate
found the priest's body
demons [\h__\h] [\h__\h] foolishly I took
shelter in the vesque and ate their food
you know the rest yeah all right
now we have learned from our mistakes
where are we gonna go next
in this area
okay which path down here I didn't go
down here yet so I know maybe the other
path is open now
but I still want to see what's down here
too
all right it's a dead end anyway I'll
check it out
come on one hit kill
ah
I want to snooze
[Music]
let's Direction line but ah I mean ah
cool thank you
why no give me a special reward for
going to Each corner of the world eh
[Music]
excuse me
well this doesn't work so well this path
thingy because I can't go there all
right we'll go the other way
the other way surely will work right
Google Maps be like although to be
honest I never really have issues with
Google Maps I want to make fun of it but
my real problem is that my phone just
tells me I'm looking in a different
reactions reaction Direction so for a
while I'll just like go in the wrong
direction until I realize this is not
working oh
altars of Lilith are hidden all over
Sanctuary they Grant permanent wait
good
does she have altars that help you
[Music]
if if if good why it looks so evil and
it's complicated she's complicated okay
[Music]
sounds are a small chambers that can
contain a wide range of content
extra dungeon
I guess we can do it
it's called White evil
foreign
[Music]
okay time to go already
then the important question is is she
single
when Elias was here what son or just
companion or
who is he
why does he have
close relationship
with my waifu
oh
oh so much money
Rich baby
okay I shall just not get myself spoils
anymore from the chat I mean I don't
really feel like I was spoiled yet
I did a double
can I like them with all of you
and I like um we'll put
um some nice cute dresses frilly dresses
on my skeletons and maybe some bows and
I don't know some some cute lashes and
fingernails
make them feel pretty
I want them to feel pretty
did that just make me run faster
nice okay
maybe not in this game
oh
ah they don't even leave me a chance to
do anything I'm too powerful
let's see do we have something good
uh
Plus 16.
uh-huh oh what since when do I have this
choker of penance
uh four percent resistance to all
elements plus one maximum life
whoa oh that fits my bottom
same color
[Music]
nice
oh way to go
where'd you go
oh up there okay
excuse me
checking what's down here
oh
bomb camping
whoa little church nice
hope they don't report me for spawn
camping
[Music]
should we sing like a crab song
Country Roads
take me home
to the place out where I belong
Ed my mouth
Country Roads
this is not home
me not likey
disgusting
not cute
I mean
thank God I don't have a spider phobia
what's going on where are the enemies
okay we could you
climb up oh I can climb
they just teleported up there they're
keeping up
really fast
good boys
[Music]
oh nice how much money do I have now
2000 285 gold coins and we have reached
the area I think
let's try this ground
so I don't want to cover up my pretty
hell ahead
can I like
hide it while wearing it some game was
able to do that I think World of
Warcraft
I guess not
let's try this leggings
oh they're better
but I know they're red come on I just
color coordinated my outfit
I came later oh
boys why later though bite Berry
what is that harvesting herbs and ore
can be found throughout the world and
are used by artisans for variety of
functions
is there crafting
and uh can you like make potions and
weapons
[Music]
when you get to the big time
okay
[Music]
imagine a full team of necromancers no
I'll probably like if the real game
drops
I assume that Cali would do Necromancer
I mean I just I
I wouldn't even want to take that away
from her
so I would have to play something else I
don't wanna
you know
play the same thing
maybe I'll be a sorcerer then
I'll try some more things out at that
time
where am I going
nice house
is this what the hermit is
sorry I'm taking everything from your
garden okay
there's some of them still reek of
strong spirits
okay I should go inside
wind swept cabin
does Cali even play RPGs like Diablo in
a rough time
I feel like she was already interested
in Diablo 2 Resurrected
when it came out
I mean even if she doesn't play it or
regularly I don't think it could be
her thing
no one say anything it what's happening
young
freshly turned smells like gollums an
easy kill
further south than the others
they're spreading
oh is that
family of Lapras
professor as like a thing between
Professor Snape and Gollum oh oh what
nanny
well maybe he's nice
I mean that looks scary but maybe it's
just one of those scenes where someone
really looks very intimidating but it's
actually really nice
oh he's nice then at least after this
decency to join me
I'm bloody hungry he's bloody hungry
oh thank God
I knew it
it was terrifying but it had to be nice
the [\h__\h] wasn't true
thank those friendly villages
they gave you the blood of Lewis
[Music]
not just any demon
the daughter of hatred the mother of
sanctuary
she was banished ages ago
but this world is her creation
it was prophesied she would come back
that's the question
Sanctuary has always been trapped amid
the Eternal conflict
a war between Angels and Demons
but Lilith serves neither side she has
her own plans for us
am I corrupted
not sure yet
but you two share a connection
what will you do about it
use it
find out what she's after hmm
good
then we're in this together
rest while you can
then we'll start and kill the chat
if we can't stop Lilith
we'll all be damned
[Music]
hey you missed supper oh man
yeah
nice I'm relieved oh he's following me
now Lord of now
vibing yeah it's fun so far
I'm really liking it
[Music]
it's like Diablo 2 but it takes away
everything that triggered me
and adds even more good things like
character customizations
spreading
wait do I have a
okay
okay we'll hold it down yay yeah
well always look on the broadside of
life
I guess for the sake of showing a lot in
terms of progress
since it's an open beta and I'll only be
streaming it today because it's ending
tomorrow
[Music]
I guess I shouldn't
I shouldn't go for everything so for
Broly but I can't help it
oh
how many boots
plus 22. nice
also I need a shop to sell my my stuff
soon
I'm still surprisingly
uh fine
I don't know how much longer
the campaign's really short yeah how
quick can you get to level 25 I'm level
five now but like normally in games the
higher you get
the less exp you get I'm not gonna go
there just yet I want to see
I'm almost somewhere around himself okay
yo Alice I got 25 of them eight three to
four eight eight hours
[Music]
three hours really really
if you three to four hours really
six to eight the way you play 10.
okay if we hope that I could finish the
ribbon today
with Neko it's faster okay okay how
about let's explanation exploration then
less of this picking up every single
thing
damn those are some big demons
simple size it's probably not better
than mine is it
time to speed run
said the words with tier 2 for more XP
yeah but then it's more difficult
Joe linarius
I'm sure you've heard the Cathedral of
light
Angel walks Among Us
and when he learns that Lilith is here
blood will flow
they are ancient enemies
they'll drag the whole damn world into
their Feud unless we can stop it we will
stop it
I guess it's okay just ahead
even if we don't get to 25 today that is
okay
for cute puppy at lunch oh okay okay
level 20 must happen May lack of faith
in areas do
um
Doom upon all
Travelers of this
Holy Land turn your face towards its
um
I don't know and finds
don't know
[Music]
who don't I agree but I also don't
understand
I'm almost like at my gold
don't worry don't worry I'm not gonna
eat beer tonight
simple dagger more things to sell
what
Gate House
where's my destination I entered the
city
what's this about
you must perform a cleansing ritual
maybe it was gesture that some people
take comfort in it
how dare you
[Music]
through I've tried for years to get
Laura to do the ritual oh you know him
okay fine but this one stays
I'll meet you inside
yeah okay
um let's see what they do to me the holy
Cedarwood from the shrine and inscribe
it with his sin which troubles you
into the pressure
as the fire burns the wood so too will
the light burn away your sin
okay what's my sin guys
Tokyo
cute is that what you're gonna say
oh
fear anger Pride green inscribe nothing
but scribbles into them
[Music]
and I'm not gonna do that
I would say
fear
[Music]
what is that a sin
how can you be
this is really my fault
to be fearful
I did it
you must feel as though a great weight
has been lifted from you totally yes I'm
a different person now
lunar mom's ghost breed
I'm playing the game as it should be
played with love
right of passage
800xp 300 money oh I like this bridge
cool we're entering a big castle or what
oh
oh wait
all these challenges
[Music]
progress one percent
so far
[Music]
I want to go here
hello well welcome to the second stream
of Atelier rise of free you thought I
was done no I'm not let's make some
cookies in this pot
oh
ah this way I am I improve these potions
that's cool thank you Alchemist America
oh no I spoiled the next Atelier game
after ryza I'm sorry I didn't want to I
have to cut that part out of the VOD
later so
so be right on that piece of wood not on
your business something about coffee or
cowardice map
yeah it matches Little I suppose
the game told y'all
I'm off to the dry steps Pale Man from
your vision
I must know
what party plays in all this
but first I need you to retrieve
something of mine while I finish my
negotiations a merchant in the center of
the city has it just tell him I sent you
okay
what would he have said if I
have done the scribbling it would have
just reacted to that I suppose
um
the cathedral loves to go on about him
his imprisonment in hell is Valiant
Escape his glorious return here the
world he created well they never mention
I'm being tortured in hell for a few
Millennia turned you into an ass
[Music]
I can imagine
leave some moon for next time
I know I still hear him as if he's right
next to me
well wait is this city really big yeah
oh
we have an occultist
brings amulets Jewelers wardrobe
stash my stash
waypoints A Healer a blacksmith armor
vendor purveyor of Curiosities
a little side quest
and the world tear statue
let's go let's go
ah
did I do it
yeah I think I did
oh it also looks like back in the day my
skeletons names
um I will tell you my points allow you
to fast travel for really quite
Sanctuary yeah you can earn Renown by
completing various activities across the
content continent obtaining Arena will
Grand rewards on certain thresholds
well okay so um this is Frankie
and stop moving Frankie otherwise I will
forget who you are this is Frankie this
is
um
Valentine Valentino Frankie Valentino
and this is uh
Miranda
and this is
Scooby-Doo
[Music]
yep
there's one odd one in there
still the old man's finally decided to
buy it back
the chicken coin did he
I have to pay if he wants his weapon you
will need to pay
how much is it
this one lorev's pole arm
only 20. that's nothing
easy
the other stuff he sells
pretty weak and disappointing
wait ah the old man sold me this too who
said he didn't need it anymore but
I think he'd want it back all the same
no charge Noni
a Strange Amulet thank you
is that in my question okay can I sell
some stuff now
oh yeah
anything else
everything
take everything that is not better than
what I currently have
[Music]
um
wait whatever I just sold was apparently
better
it was a sword
I'm using myself
I need to be in character what's this a
book
okay beautiful
and can I like oh
oh I'm lagging
can I repair too I guess I don't need
repair right now
next stop my favorite class from Diablo
2 necromancer
Necromancer always very popular
because everybody wants to be so edgy
apologies
he also gave me this amulet
what is it
the mark of the heraldroom
an Ancient Order of Scholars and mages
sworn to protect Sanctuary from demons
these days we are few in number
there isn't who is he talking to I'm
behind you
his breath of knowledge about demons is
equal only to his hubris
sounds like he could help us
you should seek him out in skulls gland
scores but don't forget about the
cathedral they'll be expecting you and
they might prove to be useful allies too
and go to the dry steps to find out who
that Pale Man is
join me when you can just
be careful well your ties to Lilith the
Visions you see
you are the key to Chihuahua and
stopping whatever she has planned
horse cute
that's the way he mounted it
all right bye-bye sometimes
our paths my balls right now oh no
that's the helmet
whether it is by accident or Fate's hand
there is nothing we can do about it
I'm lagging lost in the storm
fed the blood of Lilith
saved by a lone Monk
different lives and incidents Drawn
Together
by what
destiny
for some greater do your best textures
come on you can do it
I did not know
but at the time I thought I had the
chance to protect Humanity from the
daughter of hatred
the wanderer's connection to her gave me
hope
imagine that
[Music]
yeah I look beautiful no matter how
little or how many FPS I am in
welcome to the better yeah before secure
pre-order
cool thank you
am I like mixed with people from
European service only
skip ads
hello wait are you okay with me if you
can't feed then
um then
[Music]
um stand under the lamp
foreign
no way no way like how do you even
choose a server you probably can't right
is there any mode
I'm too shy to chat
press e
greetings yeah say okay I don't think
that I don't think so he would have
stood under the lamp by now I don't know
say hello again if you are from kfp I
don't think so though
[Laughter]
[Music]
yay bye bye
cool
yeah but I don't no way that I always
see like everyone
that is actually there right now I hint
like wouldn't that be overloaded now or
is it really everyone who's here also my
skeletons are lagging
can I turn them off
can I turn my online mode off
so that my skeletons stopped lagging
not everyone
[Music]
that beat lagging now no no you cannot
turn it off
um
okay
uh I wonder if it gets better better if
we leave the town
it's a feature and stop lagging
Press Tea and get the skeletons fixed
what was that what is that what is that
what's that
I pressed T didn't get them fixed I made
a portal
didn't fix them at all
were you really thinking that would fix
it
hello people
I am a whole party on my own I guess I
could get rid of them for now but um
is this a side quest
type collector
yes well boson has yet to return from
delivering our tithing demands to many
stud after unsummon you could sweep the
roads and see what's taking him so long
the cathedral must receive its dues
type collecting I want to do main quest
so
I want to focus on main quest but where
is main quest right now oh here
let's go
two main quests
just don't mind my skeletons for now
okay
they're trying
everything that is in their power right
now to catch up with me
is really nice
oh now it's gone
new bgm
still violent though
oh
it's pretty
[Music]
I didn't I returned from this I thought
something was happening because they
reset me
we were born in sin
Children Of Darkness
father's light can be sought through
penitence and face
walk in the light
okay next me please
we must be ever Vigilant against sin
brother yes reverent mother
burn away wickedness but not Temptation
lead you from his holy Radiance let
righteousness sear away corruption and
sin cast out thy Darkness for only light
must remain cast out thine Darkness for
only light must remain test out fine
Darkness for only light must remain
not a company
he sent me on without him
putting faith in that old man was a
mistake what could possibly be of
Greater import
Lilith
you know I know
[Music]
we have received word from one of our
Knights the demons sighting in Yale
Valley
the description matches too closely to
reciting universe if you would travel to
your lesson and take stock of the events
there
you would have the Gratitude of the
Cathedral of light
I had thought to send Laura but again he
fails in his duty
The Roasting never ends
shall be done he's really salty what
happened between them
[Music]
I'm on a mission take the knights report
before you go hi
I take my friend mother I received a
report of a potential demon sighting
horned woman near your lesson of Mines
sounds about right performed routine
inspection nothing yet
sent him priest and escort of knights
will report in when we find something
okay let's go and hope that the
skeletons fix themselves when I go
outside otherwise I'll try to respawn
them more so
we are going here next
foreign
[Music]
should I stay here or continue again I
don't know wait I can't I need two more
should I focus on one or I should have
maybe try another one too I'm loving
energy
flush
all right A corpse at the tallest
location
good Super Chat oh sorry I can't read it
right now
focus on one okay
thank you
maybe television I already tried that
but um
what here can someone help him it was
only an Apple iPhone Apple my father
wouldn't want me to go hungry Woody dude
you're in here for an apple you're gonna
die for an apple
let this be the first step on your
journey to the light
[Music]
[\h__\h] up here what about you
say it a damned snake she keeps them on
the chain around her neck damn
her and I hope she Burns for what I've
had to watch
okay that one I'm not sure what happened
hello oh my God there's like people
running around
that's so cool
okay it didn't fix them how do I
unsummon them
foreign
[Music]
how do I get rid of them
that way
wrong way
the one I chose is the wrong one
what do you mean oh there's another one
tarnish Blaster and this one's an
unforeseen
ah this Quest cannot be progressed in
this version of the game okay let's go
this way sorry
uh shift plus C really
[Music]
well
can't
the green icon near the mono
ah I don't think I can get rid of them
he and I come over tonight
press any upgrade
and raise one additional oh
I should do this anyway
hello
oh hi hi
[Music]
okay so I upgraded them now can
apparently do five
the last one we'll get rid of them
okay this one also got rid of them
what's your name Cal gorins
fancy name
I'm die thank you forever sorry that
[\h__\h] you'll be right back
don't worry you know how this works
don't you oh
aren't you used to it
Eastern plain
or another side quest I think I'm gonna
ignore all the side quests now but if I
play in June
I'll do them properly
I need someone to help me
more more skeletons
okay free now
hello cute little foxy
ice Fox snow fox
and just so that I can get
as far as possible before the better
ends
she says while going a different path
than she actually should because she
cannot resist oh but this one works too
every path leads to
where Rome
what does that sound
am I going the right way really
that's weird now I have to go up here
a room okay okay
while I'm so wise
and why is Wawa once said
who said that anyway
claimed that all roads lead to Rome if
you go by that logic then all roads also
lead to Berlin probably
some dude
a Roman some Roman which one it's
important also the discussions are fixed
look I just noticed
nice
they were a little bit overwhelmed by
them
other people they saw
what
Rome Rome built all the oh they built
all the roads okay I guess then they can
take the credits
all right we're partying five now or
actually six I guess
one two three four five yeah one two
three four five six seven You're Gonna
Make Me Feel Like eleven
you'll be Overkill
nice music playing again
Diablo osts are pretty nice
we like it you know what I also kind of
want to play again eventually for
nostalgic
full of Warcraft it's been a while but
the thing is with World of Warcraft
since this is an actual MMORPG
kind of drags
more than like this type of game
any kind of MMORPG
takes a lot of time and maybe it's not
so interesting for the viewers as it is
for those streamers
[Music]
it's really just you know
that's silver ore
it's better than it was before well I
would want to play the classic
nice
scary
what's that who is you
who is that
is that another online player what is it
an NPC yeah he doesn't have a name
though sorry did I just like take all of
your
uh enemies
random dude okay okay Hunter MPC
that's cool
I have random NPCs there
okay we reached another little village
thingy yeah
level seven plus what level am I
six I'm not ready for this yet
but honestly Necromancer level six is
basically other classes level 10.
I would say
what do you need
prava sent me I'm looking for Vigo
you and that nuisance of a child both
girls been nagging us about that demon
woman all week
into her claims he should be at the
moment Quest level is one yeah
it's like missing there last week
along with the girl's mother and another
woman
watch yourself out there no worries
I am a grown-ass woman with five grown
ass skeletons
um no one can stop us
except a game crash
yesterday my game
[Music]
um
when I first opened it
it kind of froze
and I had to restart when I was in the
character selection
but besides that so far I've had no
problem
I mean
I had on maximum quality I had no lag
when I was not streaming
um
but for the sake of streaming I have to
lower it anyway I got some cool books
oh Nike kind of cold
but okay
[Music]
can I go shopping
um
you'd rather bring your legs
this check event gives you a small
chance to obtain a Batman oh
gotcha
in exchange for murmuring Opals almost
can be found by community events
throughout the center of him
[Music]
foreign
ER
gotcha
yeah I'm lagging a little but I think
it's acceptable
you guys should be looking mostly at the
game screen anyway
[Music]
um all right let me check the blacksmith
Savage will break them down into
crafting materials as well as unlock
their appearance
oh
should I not be selling everything
[Music]
I want to repair actually
I'm gonna need to repair or something
oh
no actually no anything breaks the forge
is hot
we're fashion short Salvage instead of
selling
[Music]
stare at me
okay well hmm
kind of too late now maybe when I
actually play the game in June
for now I'll just sell everything ah
Waypoint ah
a
thank you
I would have just skipped that look at
all these tickets
today the deadbeats are working for me
and the chickens are having a day off
isn't that nice look there's so many in
the Quito
oh you can fish and probably only NPCs
drop the fish are biting today
I hope it's for your your tummy's sake
as well
any lowlands 7 plus
but this is all just too easy
well tell me guys if you need help
foreign
[Music]
upgrade it again okay
until it's Max I guess
who's this
murmuring Mill
I shouldn't be going here I think but
foreign
[Music]
oh wait so is this system by any chance
like you
um
you Salvage like some armor
and then you can give a different armor
the looks of that armor that you just
salvaged
or or is that not possible because I
feel like that was possible in other
games
that's it oh
but in order to do that do I have to
salvage both of the items or just the
one who which looks I want to have
now this transfer Coolio oh why so dark
cute
okay I don't like it
that's the one I want oh no no no
then honestly I don't feel so bad about
not uh doing that with the first
few things I had because um
the top I'm wearing now is kind of cute
though
fun I like that system it makes no sense
but I like it
what 15 monsters and then what
I'm really like having a field day
it's too easy
I was struggling way more in Diablo 2.
oh thank you for the orange
don't worry don't worry
you guys have to get a day off because
you were like working so hard for me
strangers
gonna thank me for coming here Orlando
rats
Julie Julie Julie
ew you Infested by rats and you complain
about Strangers Like Me
get rid of the Rats first
um
I was sent
oh yeah
oh
God you know what I saw
kind of she had horns like a beast
Strode right past where you stand
[Music]
been there with her but you let my
mother through sir shouldn't you be
responsible for her safety
we have soldiers stationed inside you
should be worried about them too
maybe you can help me hmm
gladly
but why do I still need to talk to him
she did why did I just ignore her woman
I just I just passed her when she asked
me to help her that can't be
my mother taught me that name
you speak of the daughter of hatred
mentioned me
she wasn't angry was she
has more than your job at stake here
it's over with
feel my side weapon it's basically just
decoration right
did you guys told me the other day
Cyprus a really [\h__\h] weapons
I guess I'm using Magic
also a time anyway
[Music]
the damn hoist is stuck oh
got to go on foot
okay
I feel so strong man it's mine now
now she gave it to me
Paula alert what what
the whole stream every stream I do I
guess in some way is a spoiler alert
I got two buddies with me now
we're at coach party now
getting a little bit crowded
nice War
so can I craft something with this label
what was that
oh Chad was swallowing
ah
yeah that's all right it's not didn't
feel like a big spoiler it's okay I mean
it's not okay but it's okay
um
for upgrading aha
upgrading my gear
that's cool why my deadbeat's not
helping me pick up the money
you could do that
oh quite simply the Knight and the
magpie isn't that food
it go back round up the knights and
leave my mother in her and care for as
long as that will take
no
I'm going on are you sure your mom is
with Lila maybe it's just a cost
the fan
well we'll see I guess
the death beats were down what is that
what is that
sorry guys got distracted I'm on here
I'm here
the enemies are like dead so fast that I
don't even get to
speak
dude my NPCs have HP because I don't see
any bars on them
wealthy one because I'm a coward
I mean I did write down that my sin is
fear so
I am admitting it and I am standing by
that
walking simulator
maybe highlighters maybe in June I'll
I'll do the other one okay so there's
basically there was like that
choice and difficulty and then there was
another one with like before
four difficulties and if I know prava
doesn't tell us anything no one goes in
nothing comes out that's all
and two of them you had to unlock I
guess by playing the other ones first
I just went for the most simple ones I'm
I'm sorry
normally I get you guys to convince me a
lot of the time to play something more
difficult
than what the game has to offer
easiest one no no you guys won't let me
go with that
I guess it just means you guys believe
in me
[Music]
now we can go here locked
locked I can squeeze through to the
other side
hold on
There She Goes Down
enemies
to go
fights coming to us this is nothing
is that it no more
but the Druid has uh animal friends
right
even though you guys said through it is
bad but it's nice to have some minions
at least
I kind of I'm really interested to throw
it out
of a druided too sure
do I need some Buffs maybe is that a
thing they might do
when people give them feedback that like
one class is totally overpowered
Jordan is constantly out of Mana
it's not bad it's just harder
why would your mother
leave you like that I love it oh okay
cool potentially okay okay we gotta tell
them
through it please
because I want to play Druid can you
only have those two bones or can you
have any any animal like the ones that I
the animals on the field like the Bears
and stuff
or
or does it depend on what type of skill
on
it I doubt you can have chickens depends
on the skill
hmm I mean the wolves are cool though
oopsie
[Music]
Plastics and although although wait
maybe I'll keep those they have some
more interesting
oh
some more interesting extra bus
chicken familias yeah we were hoping for
Cult of the Lamb to add those two and
they kind of hinted at it but up until
this day they never really did today
I mean maybe they're still working on it
but I'm done
what the hell were you
read them they did
recently
yeah it's too late now they should have
followed that when they first developed
the game and the chicken should have
been like uh
Main
well well well
bounced by that to the enemies
there were literally no boobs oh yeah
yeah that was the thing
there was no other burps either
I like how I've been like
it's so unnecessary for me
uh potions
dead end
that I have been constantly just playing
with one hand with the mouse and just
chilling like this is really comfortable
to play
wait
maybe when it gets a bit more
challenging then I might need my second
hand but so far
my other hand is just chilling
[Laughter]
an opening
oh go
I'm flexing now
I have a skill point no
upgrade that ooh it's spooky
what's up
tunnels closed
we're trapped without the Hoist
even easier with corpse explosion oh
okay
next time I get a skill point we have to
think about what to do oh oh wow
[Music]
looks really cool even with low Graphics
oh my God
statue
oh okay the way I saw her
Lilith
we need to find my mother
um
I'm not gonna jump down there
I think
this way
[Music]
they're faster than me
I like this green
glowy stuff
fall damage I don't think so because I
can't even fall down if I wanted to I
can only safely climb down the Hoist hmm
all right
whoa
yes
explain
wiggle
what's up
we need reinforce yeah I heard good
things about controller
controller controls
what was that
but
you know Diablo classic way I guess is
to play with Mass
for the Nostalgia
oh
look up
oh the escort
they're all dead no this one's alive
event
help him
over there
oh yeah maybe if you I guess you can
play it on PlayStation 5 too right
oh it's a cross play like um what's the
word where you start on PC and you can
then continue on PlayStation 5
seamlessly
oh
Bank
God oh
that's amazing
so you could then just continue to play
on your TV if you wanted to
vehicle
it was
you sent
she wasn't human
a demon like the statue hmm claims your
mother to sanctuary
The Other Woman Vernard where is she
for her life
um spiriter letter deeper in
[\h__\h] girl no no this is lost she's gone
you must please
you all did nothing
compared oh yes
the Army the father
voice acting
do this for
oh he is dead yep now he is maybe I can
raise him
your mother told me make him join dead
people drink Good Fortune
do you think I trusted her
she bribed you with it didn't she
you weren't supposed to let her through
at all
but it's not too late she can still be
saved you think so
not anymore
[Laughter]
abandon that's how he was speaking
yeah it really just it's already been
two and a half hours it feels like I
only played for one hour
it's up to us now time goes by fast yeah
up to us now
search for Lilith and Bernard with
narelle
okay
fine of me
wow no this can't be too far for real
am I already gonna meet my orshi I'm not
ready for that yet
oh my God I feel like I'm in the end
game
it's a good game if you lose track of
time yeah I think so too
[Music]
what is this oh
I don't think we should touch it
no I don't think we should interact but
the game is telling me to
you hold on grams of Lillard
daughter of hatred
oh I have
what do you seek is that her mommy you
hungry
hunger dragged your
suit of it
no I I taught her how to survive
is that
there future of you whole life festivals
I
I everything I've read me against you
and hologram you've read so much
yet know so little
will you accept my offer
I I don't know
will you let me try
I want to try foolish Ambitions your
mother's
alive
she came this way with Lilith
how can you be sure
oh
sometimes oh only I was seeing them
I saw them
what
the hell
Lilith's petals the blood was
put that to rest
hmm put kiwawa to waste so time with
wine while we need energy drink
I want no Health Energy drink
wow always so tired
I want more challenge
I want to be challenged I'm gonna check
my inventory oh a ring mine is litany
ring a rare ring lightning resistance
fire resistance maximum Essence damage
to close enemies critical structures wow
Chihuahua so lucky again
[Music]
the lips are a way to escape the Eternal
conflict she tells me inside of the
seduction of the angel in Arias all this
time he was just as fallible as any man
[Music]
yeah yeah and then Bang
Moorings from my possession my precious
so anyway I started blasting
I wonder how big this dungeon is looks
pretty big from here
wow actually reminds me a little bit of
this one area in tunic
remember
foreign
[Music]
five attack speed extra
okay Arium is real is it is
the mines yeah yeah yeah yeah
it was so good
good
I feel like in the future that will be
one of the very very few games that I
will have the desire to play a second
time because normally I don't do that
but with tunic I want to do that
all my life I've sought the origin of
humankind it was always her from the
union of Angels and Demons came the
first generation of humanity they were
powerful
movers of mountains shakers of sea
such a great game yeah
the truth
that I speak
oh that's why I work
foreign
yeah the AOE damage is just so
overpowered
oh man I wouldn't mind like why can I
not open this door I wouldn't mind
eventually like
playing something close combats too
because in these kind of games oh
I often just
go for
uh distance combat because I just I'm a
little [\h__\h]
Black Lake
cool
Neko can go close too
I mean yeah I do go like in the middle
of these enemy groups very often
so I guess like both the combination she
was so proud in the telling of this part
Lily said inarias bore a son together
Rahman
he is wise Beyond years the first one
Tangled the power of necromancy she says
his lit hair lies deeper in dot dot
a cradle
burp is cat oh what you mean
why is both chicken and
p-u-s-s-y
uh another word to describe someone who
is scared or fearful or a coward
and why are both so related to me
what a weird coincidence hmm
all right let's listen to this
so cute
and why you was bad
yes
do you have faith in me
I want to
good for now
all you need now
she's got it we are going to tail like
LaPlace
the first necromancer
the other thing is that laplos doesn't
have
the key sounds like they're searching
for Lilith's son
rothma
what are you thinking rap Plus
mom I think so
he may not even know herself
but all signs point forward
oh I used my left hand unbelievable I
probably you know didn't even really
need to
where are we I wanna go left too but
progress baby
ah we already said someone in Fire
Emblem is left with us man she has many
mummies
should I eventually upgrade my bones or
should I just replaced it with something
else
and as we speak
answer my question please
so I can decide what to do
um
this one wouldn't this probably
um replace it
corpse explosion
where is that
where is it
wait sound here maybe
bone prison bone missed corpse explosion
now there it is
detonated corpse dealing 49 damage to
surrounding enemies
bone sphere is a classic Network skill
from the Apple II okay so this one's
online too
now I have to use my left hand in order
to use that
uh I'll chill a little bit more
it costs no Mana
I don't see it at all
where are the bodies
it worked
oh yes do I have to aim
the red blobs on the floor no no there
was just so much going on let me test it
again when I get the opportunity
I mean that that seemed like something
was happening there I just can't see the
body because it explodes explodes too
fast
no way
can I spam it
rudimentary wand
ER
you can spam it over the corpses ah you
need a corpse first
ah I thought I was just like I don't
know
taking them out of my back pocket
create some corpses first
wow fun
now I understand
okay I will have fun with that
yeah well basically I'm also just
spawning bone splinters out of nowhere
it's not like I need a corpse to spawn
that so you guys trying to correct my
logic but I'm just using game logic guys
it's very crispy
I went in a circle again
some nice Buffs too
okay music is kind of freaking me out
nope see wrong one
can we go right then
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
foolish demons
okay
if one of my skeletons ever happens to
die please let me know because I
probably won't know this
is
if I had known that
open Beta was happening this weekend if
I had known earlier I would have
scheduled this whole weekend for it does
let us know we're coming
oh
thank you
these are all so weak I think I can even
take on Lilith right now I'm
confidential fear
do you still remember the names uh
Miranda
you miss your daughter
Skippy Boop my magpie
she's scared right now
she must be
go
for stay you got the two I forgot it's
time to choose
Scooby-Doo
I trained her well she's a good kid
Valentino and Frankie okay she'll be all
right she
Valentino and Frankie my child
I like those names to reach rathma we
will need to
hit requires a ritual
shoe
you wish calm and soft spoken
good
it's like a you're ready for lesson one
low voice phone alert
what did you see this time
I don't need sparing tell me all the
family plans to teach me a ritual
one that needs blood
receptive
we have to reach them the fifth one is
um
[Music]
see
German four five
his name is from
[Laughter]
incredible
using the same strategy of how I give
you guys employee numbers random numbers
the enemies are getting fancier and
fancier
okay they look very
threatening but they really aren't
Halloween
upgrade clubs exposure generates mana on
YouTube
[Music]
oh my God that's
too powerful
[Applause]
as if I needed any more power than this
even stronger than he aura
so many
strong Chihuahua alter egos
so I heard
you guys told me
the Apple four from your guys's
perception at least
strong and it is more difficult
than
the apple tree but easier than me
foreign
correct
what about Diablo one I never played
Diablo one
is there a door here
level two is insane
yeah I know I'm playing on super easy I
know I know but still
one is way harder one is a horror game
one is literally hell oh perfect that's
what it's supposed to be
but when I played Diablo 2 I'm pretty
sure
I just it was there even any difficulty
to choose from
because I don't remember changing
anything but I
can't imagine myself going for something
really difficult
the able to is the hardest
yeah but one was horrific and hard
not at the start right
um
no difficulty same kinds of magic as
before
thank God there's difficulty settings
here the door is sealed
please do something Demon's approach we
need to get through I think I can dispel
it
multitasking
oh
my God
y'all if you don't have minions though
this could get kind of chaotic
kills
some achievements
and it don't stop coming and they don't
if they stopped coming what
why'd you stop coming coming
[Laughter]
more please more
um
They're All Dead
cost of knowledge
storming the gates oh
more EXP
I'm almost out of 10. Where'd I go
I don't know where to go I'm going up
shouldn't I be going down
Osama level nine
why am I going up
yeah I'll go down this is maybe some
extra
for people who want to do extra homework
and back to where I was what in the
beginning
no way
a little too loud during battles
I will follow you to the ends of
sanctuary mother
wait can I change that
uh
effects
a little bit lower
um no you know what I even more
should be good
nice atmosphere
a healing well that's the first one I
see in here
oh don't need it though
are we gonna have a fight oh I am
hi
bring your knee and tete reunion of
mommy and daughter
or
could it be
too late time
Beyond this lake lies the necropolis of
the first born
a trove of magic and knowledge
I open the way for this
but
could not pass through with her I
I
lack the vine element you see stop but I
can find it I'm so close
look at what Lilith has done to you
you're writing in your own blood my
little Magpie Magpie she awakened me
she showed me things
can't even put into words
once I finished you will understand I
don't care what she showed you please
let's just gets out of here
oh
I see yes clever Magpie
trying to Lead Me Away turning into a
Golem creature
that's a little bird Oh I thought it was
a pie this is my discovery not yours
[Music]
well you must stop it immune look at the
gifts she's given me what
what
why are they flying away stay here
there
[\h__\h]
oh at least this is a little bit more
challenging beautiful no
you won't take what's mine
yeah that's a good power maybe I should
talk to Lilith a little bit
where am I ah why am I so slow
foreign
I'm not ready
whoa wait that is us I did not expect
that
[\h__\h]
oh my God what the [\h__\h] is going on
I'm out of potions
20 seconds Focus
do I still have five of my uh skeletons
I think so okay okay we're good we're
good with a little bit of a panic mode
there but
we're good now
[Applause]
no that was one moment that was really
dangerous
Phantom
I had to well
could have been longer
koala after every fight in this game
should have been longer should have been
more difficult
but also fun you because it's easy
protecting me
I don't want to hate
I'm trying
I really am
we're going to make Lilith pay for what
she's done
so we need blessed blood
campaign
get that blessing beg if you need to
whatever it takes
okay my mother started this damn ritual
I'm going to finish it Revenge meets me
in the Mr Woods
why there
The Horizon hit a vault there
finding it with her life's work
Ed for that
maybe it will help with the ritual
if not
at least I can bury her where she'd want
I need time I'm sorry just leave me
um
okay
if you're fine alone here all right oh I
got something
but it's a dagger mother's knife but I
mean I guess I could use it if I wanted
to
but I wanna die
I want to stay in character can I use it
I thought you know
I should just be using the things that
fit my class
raise the mama skeleton I have five
already
I can use this
um
stronger
post song
then
Shield was that the only one I have
oh wait I can hold a skull on the second
hand too huh
this one does some damage
[Music]
yeah
I'll take the
Shield
where's the exit
uh
no idea
is it here because you guys were saying
I was going back when I was going this
way
oh
oh all right
noise
oh the Wolves died
poor wolves hey I'm not lying this time
hello
hi guys
wow
where I went to Wako where is here
life's guidance
it's time to go to church again I guess
it's Sunday after all
a Raiders again hello
playing open Beta what's wrong with them
they're all crying in front of the
church
let's see
Maybe
this is where Quest continues yes yes
see that the kitchen is ready for the
model service
hello kiwawa here you've returned of
course I have
I need a holy blessing to continue
chasing Lilith
we want to hear of this
he's away at corvallar
Pick Your Blessing there oh everything
is unfolding as inarios foretold soon we
will be free to escape sanctuary and
return to the heavens where he belongs
foreign already
where is that
this one
pretty far
okay
pretty
[Music]
wow it's so emotional
does this always play when you're here
can you check shift seat
again
what for
should we do something here
I've created a sacrifice yourself I
don't want to sacrifice myself
you can upgrade my potions
[Music]
true
I forgot
let me go to a merchant
you can change skeleton types
oh I'm happy with the ones I have now
but let me take a look in a moment
should ever go in the wrong way
[Music]
oh that sounds interesting what are
curious Jesus sounds curious
there's more
wait are these mine no
who are no skeletons
to whom do you belong
I'm a vendor okay so
um
I don't care about the trans Morgan
thingy now
next time next time good deal father
please
okay
any repairing could do 100 hundred
hundred wow why does it not go down
that's another thing they changed Diablo
all that done
and Diablo 2 you had to
repair everything so often
I never get hit
ah you lose 10 if you die
that's the only time
I definitely got hit a few times
especially just now in that boss fight
potions
can I push it and fine hard mode hard
mode
I need more of a challenge not while I'm
in town
and this each time you critic you
critically strike your skirmishes
Warriors next
attack critically strikes oh and Deals
50 percent bonus Critical Strike damage
no I don't want the skirmishes
[Applause]
does this mean I'm down to four again
now or
[Music]
if I do that
I can only pick one I thought it was an
upgrade okay okay
[Music]
I'll find them again
should I continue upgrading that
all right let's follow this beautiful
icy path wow
they'll come back don't worry
and let me just find some what the [\h__\h]
[Applause]
yeah food just poop is gone for now
sealed Exorcist gosh did he not delete
his card what is this
what is it
why are there more people joining
what a question I don't know about yet
fun further turn yeah maybe if I'm like
gonna
critical situation again I could
you know maybe get some more help
whoa
that's a lot of cash
you have a spirit wait what you have a
spirit animal from the end oh what I'm
like filling that thing up with the dead
spirits
come on give me more
[Music]
seems to be
the the item itself seems to be the
giver of the side quest
basically uh-huh
all right what is that
oh what
[Applause]
I that didn't really fill up though
oh Sony
do I have to do something
you have to be in the blue area ah
oopsie
oh are you okay
probably not
foreign
[Music]
until June
I will get an upgrade so that I can play
this in high quality but maybe they'll
also fix something
[Music]
you guys were saying
it might be partially their fault
not my fault
they should
yeah I mean upgrading my PC
they'll probably optimize it it's better
after all okay
yeah but I feel I'm okay with uh
I'm okay with upgrading my push you
I just don't know what I should get
ah
well hopefully not the one that's
apparently Diablo is able to completely
make boom
go explode
there's some graphic cards apparently
that it just doesn't
it's not able to handle at all
it's crazy
yeah I think I know
I know plenty
I have many
I guess nerdy friends in the in a good
way
I am not saying you know I don't well
it's really getting laggy I'm I don't
think that
it's a negative thing by the way my
Diablo is up to eight thousand
MB RAM
OBS is down to one thousand so I feel
like it was higher before
good job obs
yeah is that normal
it's very very very big
[Applause]
what's it I just run into
no problem for the Wawa
how much RAM you got I don't know
genuinely do not know
what I'm not hating on Earth
[Music]
you know they're cool they're helpful
would you call me a nerd though am I
nerd
maybe in some way
I mean being nerdy
doesn't always have to be about
computers right
yes I'm one an idol nerd see yeah that's
the thing it's just like
it can be an otaku of like anything
though I feel like the word otaku can be
used in a more widered sense than
nerd but
um
[Applause]
similar enough
[Music]
fun
a two PC setup
I don't know about that that's like too
too high level for me
try myself come on ketchup
oh there's something there
hi help the health one executed
did I
lose one
skeleton
oh [\h__\h]
oh it's so far okay
it looked like I only had three
I don't know what to talk about guys
I can't think of any topics today
can you guys think of a topic
friend of mine went up to a
Mountain yesterday
and there were people still skiing I
thought season season for skiing was
over waffle
cat stories
[Music]
my cats
I've been doing the usual thing although
hey you know I just switched foof again
and Chunky Monkey threw up in the
morning for only a little bit but it's
your business I'm worried Reverend
mother prava expects me
yeah
that that reminds me of something
you know the robot toilet that I have
for my cats
let me tell you about that in a moment
there's a problem
you were good soldiers
worked hard
drink hard too already reached my
destination
Brothers
sisters
I hope you find peace in these Flames we
go long time no see
Vega
what are you doing here
so you lived
do they sleep in it no thank God no
humans bribe
it's looking bad
my ass is on the line might not have a
job when she's done with me
hey
you're here for her right let's go
together
maybe she'll go easy on me if you're
there
okay
pledged a lie allegiance to Skynet haha
no okay it's not that crazy
and I'll tell you when we're walking
around outside again
I really like those City designs too
this OST is nice too
oh
there you go
good luck main question
um
hi have the new Watch Commander replace
the forces we lost at the mine this
feels very game of throney you've
returned
Vigo here tells me you were braver than
he oh please no not at all ah yes yes I
totally was I need a divine blessing
to chase Lilith first
you will be made worthy of
uh a holy war cannot be won with
faithless troops
make no mistake
this war is Holy
Lilith has brought the Eternal conflict
to sanctuary
and Denarius will deliver us as writ in
Prophecy
until then we have our parts to play
make a pilgrimage to the alabaster
Monastery cleanse your spirit
then we may discuss a blessing
may as well make myself useful
come by the ruins south of Europe
me you talking to me
for the man by shampoo
Quest complete
all right we go
here
pilgrimage
complete the pilgrimage to the Shrine of
the pen what penny tent
okay
on my way
ah gifts
so I noticed
that there's like a like a gray plastic
um soft soft type of plastic inside
toilet that you can wash too but
um it's like it's all the way inside
where the
uh cat sand is supposed to be on top of
and then at the entrance as well where
the cats jump through but my cats and I
think other cats do this too
they have this
um
um this thing they do when they're done
at the top of their thing in the toilet
they like scratch
something
and in this case there's something that
I guess looks very scratchable to them
hell is like that gray plastic on the
entrance and they've been apparently I
guess I think it's mostly chunkers
though
scratching it so much that it's like
pretty much ripped down and it's like
falling apart
and I don't know if I can replace it but
yeah I can't stop her from doing it
either because then I would have to like
also I mean she's just trying to clean
her paws it's not really like she's
scratching like a scratching pole for
fun and she's doing it for cleaning her
paws which I mean that that she should
do
yeah I think she must have been added
while I was gone for the month but she's
still doing it now I don't think she was
doing it in the beginning like this
vigorously
yeah I have to check if there's maybe a
replacement or I don't know
because the toilet was expensive I
didn't pay for it but it was expensive
so maybe maybe there's like a
replacement for just the
plastic stuff there's a shrine
I'm not mad
I'm told it it's on your sin
weighs you down Body and Soul Beats the
hell out of you it'll cleanse you
prepare you to stand before the father
just cat mommy fingers don't have many
regrets friend
this kind of thing is a lot deadlier for
some than others
watch out all right
I'll find you at the end
okay
you're not coming with me again
I'm not ready not by a long shot
even if I could survive confidence
there's no telling what would happen in
the end
you though you have a solid chance hmm
I suppose you chose the wrong class in
the beginning should have chosen
necromancer
but it'll clean you up for anarius
rare honor for an outsider
if you can call it that
okay because uh what which way what
here
on my way
I like those icy areas
no
kind of sad I didn't go skiing this year
because last year I bought all that
skiing equipment
and then even right after I bought it I
brought it to skiing vacation but then I
didn't use it because we figured out
that as a beginner you should be using
really short skis and the people at the
store didn't tell me that
when they were giving me advice on which
ones to choose
and then I didn't use them at all back
then but I thought maybe next time when
I get better
well I still didn't get better but I
could have at least used like the other
parts of the equipment
um
oh well at least I'm fully grown so I
don't think I'll grow out of it I will
only grow
into it by skill
but I really I should have gone skiing
if you put so much money into skiing
equipment you really gotta go skiing
but I thought it was too late already
but the the timing was missed
hard creature of Darkness foreign
lift your sins breathe deep the cold air
the path to Redemption lies before you
if you have the faith
walk it
I mean yeah the biggest problem was that
I was just
uh two whole more than two whole months
of this winter I was not even in Austria
so
Idol of the faithful what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h]
scary
[Music]
why is it so bloody around my eyes
night time this is night time why is it
so red
get out there and go again when you can
I know it is definitely too late uh at
some point throughout the year
then you gotta wait until next year
okay I gotta make sure that next year
I prepare myself for skiing vacation
and also prepare myself for breaking a
body part
as I get so close every time
it's a miracle that I didn't break
anything while skiing yet
the other girl's ski well Callie does I
guess
what the [\h__\h]
[Applause]
we're poisoned oh no
[Music]
I don't know about the other girls I
actually never heard them
talk about skiing
I'm guessing no
maybe somebody knows more than me
just sprayed my shoulder this time
I hope it gets better soon
ah
look at that much better now
California
for the agony of the flesh he's the
first cleansing of the Soul it's snow in
the mouth faith stronger
oh no please don't rely on me for
teaching anybody how to ski
I wish I could I want to have that
Austrian Pride I want to make austrians
proud but
oof
feel the string
I just put it there to listen and then I
put it to the next place I guess it is a
pilgrimage
makes sense now
ah Aussie winter
that's true you guys have winter
in the summer
but do you guys get snow I don't think
you guys get snow
hey
what could I teach I think the only
teach this thing like the teacher's
language is but nothing physical
mostly rain
they're important for real
I don't think they would import it I'm
sure they can just make it themselves
like a fake snow are there fake snow
places to ski at
in Australia because even here sometimes
people use fake snow like for skiing
tournaments and so on they use fake snow
often as far as I know
I taught me if how to dance I guess
it wasn't very good at it though
I feel how small you are
Embrace humility snow cannons accept
your place in worship to the father it's
everywhere for he has shown us the way
oh it's definitely a thing
so take it again
uh am I doing this right
huh
uh zombies
oh I feel sorry for them
they didn't even see that coming
when in doubt right click
foreign
together
yeah I mean I mean there were definitely
moments where they lost the attention
span but don't we all have
very little attention span like just
uh
it's because we were all raised
I don't I died
for the first time
I was sad I was partially on me
accidentally tapping out
that was so unnecessary where's the
checkpoint
[\h__\h]
not so far
this way
don't forget spacebar oh I'm not ready
yet
wait so do I still have that Idol thing
I think I do
I'm getting out leveled by the area
that's what level am I
but I'm blind where's my level
[Music]
I saw it before now I don't see it I
love it
hey I'm not that out leveled
it's not that bad
I need some enemies though
there we go ah even when they're not
fresh anymore I can still raise them
that's great
all right oh
what the [\h__\h] people this is
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
those dudes are really powerful
because they were protecting the last
altar
damn
you find your faith
feel how it fills the void within you
remember you are nothing without faith
hold fast to the light
and remember
okay
now are we done bring the idol
oh another one we're not done
that was not it
I asked for tougher floods yeah
kill free enemies of critical strikes oh
love critical Strokes
it's like they just dropped dead bodies
from the sky
they're dead the moment they
fall down you're not even sure if that
was
fall damage or if that wasn't me
foreign
that must be the last one
a vehicle was here too
okay
playing cards doesn't make me a sinner
with that bribe could soldiers died on
the count of what I did
is that the kind of man I am
and I'll always be
you know I'm behind him damn it
praying why he's not working
sorry for disturbing
you made it that makes one of us at
least you heard from Bravo I will soon
but enough about that
you're about to meet father in narius
himself
stiff drink
AKA ice cream
all right I wanna check down there
there's like a treasure chest
I saw that
I know you probably meant alcohol
just saying
this sounds just like a frozen drink so
probably ice cream
oh
wow I like this feature
we had that already inside the
they live
whatever that was
hell
Alabaster Peak 12 plus well [\h__\h]
I have a point by the way
hmm
I couldn't prove my scale to Warriors
but 15 percent
[Music]
I wonder should I do that or should I
continue with the
a corpse explosion
small points are massive
do it okay
skeleton Warrior mastery
yeah we need their help
it's getting tougher
a little bit
sometimes
uh I can change him for Defenders yeah I
feel like I'm being defended just by
them being aggressive though
it's kind of hard to see in here
before him and remember you are small
wonderfully small
many many stairs
and more stairs but this place is really
cool is there like descriptions
oh yeah cast down from the heavens but
prophes prophecy prophesied to return
our father inarias will Ascend to the
heavens and on his wings we will be
redeemed
you're here too something oh
cool the falling sickness claimed her
childhood but the father gave her new
life the Reverend mother prava is but
one of his many blessings
the paintings are really nice
the father points the way to the light
but the order of the knights penitent
was founded to carve out our path to it
all right
seems I have arrived portal of that
radiance
oh
cutscene
no I left my skeletons behind this is
not good
oh
um
forgive this intrusion but tell me what
you
and that cannot be done without your
blessing
if I've learned anything during my time
here
it is that what we're looking for
about rarely the same thing
I once thought I could find an end to
this war but there
are the resolution
everything I've done has pulled me
further from home from the place I need
to be
this world we made was born from The
Impossible and yet like its creators it
rots from the inside
I
I don't
Lilith has entered the ancient city with
your blessing I can pursue her
weak and this world has been wasted on
the Crusades
this audience has concluded what
but I have yet to be blessed
dude
what that took over law
well
said no
what's the problem with him
yeah
am I not worthy
dude was used to say I did all of that
for what
all those stairs for what
Not Gonna Worship that guy anymore
no blessing for me
damn it's okay as long as I have kfp
blessing
it's random Angel guy blessings
so
what what oopsie wrong thing again
and
I'm going here right
lights protection could I teleport there
was been there before
how does the teleporting work how do I
know where I'm teleporting
oh
wait what
where
thank you
click the blue icons
oh
only here because I didn't find any way
points here why did I not find any
waypoints there
not so many
a lot of walking huh
and we're definitely more waypoints in
Diablo 2.
oh well
oh what the hell it's locked
I won the whispering key where do I get
it looks so fancy the treasure chest I
have to remember that one
can you buy the key or
is that something you find didn't find
any that air area
buy the key at the ah curiosity
merchandise God damn it
should have gone to that Merchant
I was even curious about it
[Music]
I need more time
I can buy the Patel
now I'm already so far
I already forgot where it was I need
more time
do the enemies respawn
the ones where I already
I need more time killed them
ah
thank you
I need more time
yeah
sorry for
hurrying you stressing you out
stay a while and listen
blessed are those who bask in the light
let our faith be our armor I need more
time sorry I only got parcels
funny
10 out of 10.
ah you've returned come
out of the cove
I mean actually I lied I do have some
time
and parsley though both
kinds of stuff I've got all the good
stuff
leave it to me if you need some spice in
your life
yet you stand before me unscathed
I know his ways that is approval enough
for me in the name of the light I bless
you or May the light flow through you
and keep you in your blessings
our victory
prophesy
I need someone else's
in the Heaven's eyes creating Humanity
was a sin
they cast him down now he seeks
Redemption and the chance to go home
has prophesied slaying Lilith is their
chance
when he ascends
so shall we all
oh does that erase Humanity
are we sure we want to do that from the
father's voice
in my ears a spear of light piercing
hatred's heart
first lilies then the Primes
he will Deliver Us
from the Eternal conflict
that's a scam
what will become a Vigo Vigo and I had a
good conversation when he returned
he will do his Penance trust that he is
in good hands
I will only trust
when I see him again
but okay
what is next
what what's next
game tell me
this
do I look for a name right now
we're done here maybe
cool
okay
and but at least I should teleport over
here
let's go
it's kind of far
I hope she's still alive because we left
her behind in that
hell hole
okay uh ah okay she's gonna search for
her in that area
um
should I I should sell
actually better
if I get it back is it very expensive
no I think I bought it back for the same
price
wait no but I got all the Buffs that's
actually not worth it
sorry I'm very indecisive
about the gloves
um
two percent lucky hit chance but no
willpower no attack speed
ah
I'll keep my gloves a little bit longer
also oh maybe I need to be
repaired now
yes this time there was actually
necessary
let's go
black jaw
oh
sorry your return follow a little bit
close ones you looked on oh that's fine
lag lag
maybe we'll get better
all right
where is she
I am the am the storm's fury made
manifest
oh that kills them
yes
wait I want to read that but I want to
make use of this magic too
oh okay it's gone already a hood
now let me take a look at that what's
that
faded plate plaque most of the
inscription has been lost to time a few
barely legible words read greet death
open arms
ah yeah they're just describing
how Cali greeted me when I came back to
Japan
so Titi how do they know
chess
okay when I play this game again in June
then I know to always have
one of those
keys on me
Kitty
I know right why is she not here where's
she
around
real cool
hello
came here already so this way maybe
thank you for the pinky
behold the troops that lie within
there is something strange going on here
oh narelle must be nearby
darken is she in the dark and hold why
is she in the dark in full
Winding Way oh if I was a cave but it
doesn't really look like a cave from
here
should have followed me after all
always follow wow wow guys
you have to hold each other's feathery
hands okay
not lose your partner but also always
follow the Wawa
again
the three peoples
and trees or what and and
and no one's hurting them
I should get them to be on my side
they're so powerful
supposedly
oh God this is a maze
but it should be this way
that's planning
okay wait let me look uh do I need this
oh yeah the helmet yes
oh it's like it looks something you
would get
from a dentist 30 years ago
for fixing your jaw some really old
school braces
okay
Plus 20.
poison resistance nah I'm still keeping
mine
she rocks it she does she actually looks
good in it
I don't know
40 years ago Rose no not roasted
I mean I wouldn't even know
30 years ago koala was Phoenix in
different timelines
left
or here here I don't know I'll go here
gotta follow my intuition
so much for my intuition
we cooked
did you
Kiana ever have braces no
never
had a dentist even tell me
I need them even though I find that
interesting
I feel like maybe they would have been
beneficial but oh well
sorry little Panic moment they didn't I
was stuck
oh sword
stick oh oh new clubs
um
oh another dead end what the [\h__\h]
it was it this way
we're that way
I'll go left down
chihuahua has teeth
yes I know it looks like maybe I don't
but I do
maybe it was a like a question of
money though because even with European
Insurance like normal dentist visits are
fine but I'm not sure if braces are
covered maybe they're not
I want to say sorry about it like
because yesterday Twitter showed me or
today this morning could have showed me
you know one of your one of my chickens
um comments on Twitter and I realized I
mean maybe it wasn't so serious
after all but I feel kind of bad
apparently my my comment
about how the cost of doctor in Japan
was kind of expensive from the point of
view of a European
is kind of painful
from the point of view of an American
I'm sorry and it's kind of true
unfortunate
when I reach all my American or what if
you live in a place where it's just
expensive I don't know what other places
are crazy expensive I wish you all
all the health and luck in the world
and hope that you don't get into a
situation like that
in order to not get into a situation
where you need to go to go to the doctor
you should get a shield like this to
protect you
from everything
yeah I think I think it wasn't
um that serious from
I do agree like
unless it must sting a little bit when
you
live in fear of having an accident
because then you are [\h__\h]
absolutely [\h__\h]
Canada pretty lucky
is that only America
what
yeah oh oh damn
hands that's a scope that's a skirt
ah the other one I'm currently wearing
is also called Pants
it's always on pants there
oh no okay there's pants underneath huh
I'm at a dead end again what the [\h__\h]
ah
is it that way
[Music]
yeah this is why you guys you guys gotta
take your health more seriously than me
if you're from America
cannot afford
to
not be careful with it protection trying
faith is a shield against Darkness you
are invulnerable wow
well we killed everything here
all right I'm completely on the wrong
side
let's go here
what the hell
why every path I chose was a dead end
huge maze I love from Finland hello oh
my God that reminds me my flight back
did I tell you after my first uh one
month trip recently the one that was in
January
uh did I tell you about you know the
flight problem where they told me uh
sorry your flight has been canceled and
there is no other option
so I had to contact them and then
basically pull it out of their ass
to give them to have them give me
another option let's just cancel my
flight
because the flag was still going
but they sent me a cancellation email
just because they changed airplane and
the premium economy class wasn't
available anymore
because of the change of airplanes and
then you know I went through all the
trouble
we had to leave one day later with a
different airplane same Airlines same
route same time everything's same
but this time they had premium economy
oh dear
oh that's scary
so that was the the pre-story that I
think I told you before
stuck
eaten by the huratrim
the portal will lead you through this
crude trap
okay
scary
um
what should I do next
thanks Milo senpai
it makes everything's more stronger more
Mastery good okay
oh I have one more
um I guess I'll just bring in one more
eh
all right let's go for the fire portal
really I'm saying there's no enemies
here at all
do we really
sucks
I saved you in the mountains I've lost
your horse
would have frozen to death if not for me
ah you good wolf oh it's very
seriously but I want you to
oh but
that by following the whole Rod trim
tell me more about that
their paths always ends in Fire and
death
open please seen enough
open the door okay
you yeah
you come with me red you're sure I'm not
gonna get hurt here
it looks like I would
why are you telling
me they will come when the horadram
stumble
don't be there when they do
portal will lead you lead you to that
little girl you're looking for
you're not gonna explain these other
humans
that are obviously suffering here
what is this place
old imprisoned Diablo the Lord Of Terror
beneath the
SE and then they built this town nearby
foreign
I like the world the way it was
without Lilith the little game of
rebellion will only lead to chaos
you've already seen visions of the
damage she can do
yes I know you have fed her blood do you
feel it changing you perhaps not yet but
as long as Lilith walks in your world it
is only a matter of time
okay interesting wolf and NPC
I shall take my leaf
back in the garage resolutions still
looking for narel though what the [\h__\h]
didn't get me any closer
or did it well I did it
all right so basically
surprised the same thing happened again
with my flight
no well oh she's there there you are
the exact same thing but this time they
I think last time they sent me for real
legit the wrong email because it was
wrong my flight wasn't canceled this
time they just sent me an email that
said uh your flight class original class
it's not available anymore because we
changed airplane so the thing that
actually was happening
this time they got it right
they must have sent me an automated
wrong email the first time weirdly
enough but again again in the email
there's like no offer of like here how
about this flight instead nothing
nothing I had to do all that myself
again
um
yeah
so then
same thing happened so now I don't I
really don't want to use this Airline
anymore because it happens every time I
think I've lost my way the same thing
happened to my mother and me earlier on
the trail to the Vault ends here so it
should be somewhere around in these
Woods
why does it happen all the time
same thing
but I just didn't really didn't really
have many options this time in terms of
Airline I mean they're where but they
didn't make much more sense
I think by the next time I go to Japan
there should be more options again
slowly but surely they're coming back
and every time I go to Japan
there's like a different
like cheapest airline that's currently
offers the cheapest
flights and routes to Japan
that's why I tried like so many
different things with the airlines so
far
worse one was Turkish Allen
oh
the first one was Turkish Airlines
but not only Turkish Airlines but also
the customer service from the airport
in Istanbul
that was the one with the bomb in my
plane
now many confused chicken Zilla chat who
don't know the story because I guess I
never thought did I ever tell it
properly
what what what
oh she must be joking haha funny funny
kiwawa you don't joke about that kind of
stuff yeah because it's not a joke
there you go
sounds also it is a really old story it
happened before Holo
I did I did tell before
I can tell you again there seems to be a
lot of people who don't know what's
going on
[Music]
fly to Japan
then
uh Kiwa of Life of Turkish Airlines for
first time
Chihuahua mixed up in Istanbul
where are we going oh wait what
why tell me to go where I just came from
the president use it for the
unbelievable collab
yeah I was thinking about it but I
thought maybe they would have heard
about it already from uh
from uh like clip Maybe
wait ah this way
see oopsie the past is different now
sorry the statue was the source of an
illusion
oh nice item Maybe
oh
it looks stupid though
anyway so make stop and Istanbul and my
stop was already supposed to be pretty
long I don't remember exactly anymore
but
until Easter I think it was a flight of
maybe
six seven hours or so and then from
there it would be like another eight
hours or so and then in between the
waiting time in Istanbul
was already gonna be many hours I don't
remember let's say it would have been 10
hours okay maybe more like six seven the
horrific fall felt really long
so I was really tired
but we finally boarded our plane until
here everything's cool
I bought my plane and this was the first
time I flew premium economy because they
just started
um at this time they just started adding
premium economy to some airlines that
was like still very fresh at that point
and I was so happy because
after a million economy flights to Japan
I just couldn't take it anymore and that
premium economy at Turkish Airlines was
pretty good it was very comfortable the
food was good too
with more coming soon not what I
expected
but let's not give up three hours was it
only three hours to Istanbul all we need
is one book one late bill I think it was
more like before I crossed the Black
Lake
just Lilith
um
anyway but yeah I guess uh my layover
was just really long
what's of the passage over there
yeah that's cool
Are You Gonna Come
You're Gonna Come
come
is she coming
maybe I'm looking for a key
word
you guys are back shooting my story nice
okay I appreciate it because it's been
so long since I told the story I don't
remember
am I looking for a key
it's a nice mirror here
access ah I got the book Lessa versus an
incantations
okay
Sonic
until yesterday I thought it was hedge I
don't think it's written in horror code
not Hedgehog the same symbol on the door
I have an idea
my brain always auto-corrected
not relatable
[Music]
Sonic the hedge dog
hmm
let's keep on
going and brought a book on his visit
the writing is ancient the squirrel from
the
Laura from nappy place but if I'm to
fight by his side one day I need to
study everything love is wise but his
cautious I'll proved myself to him yet
some lore here and there
many of the notes Here deal in
mathematics and Astronaut is astronomy
astronomy astronomy
each page is lined with commentary on
star charts and prophecies
hey wait for me Hey listen
uh
and I'm trying to find
an opening to tell you the rest of my
story but she keeps on talking to me
well
let's see
it's the same seal as before astronomy
would be easy enough to break it again
but why would someone use it here
one way to find out
of course we can't let anything stop
opposite of Lilith
I'll open the door and if we split up
we'll work faster that way
only if you stay on this side of the
door
fine
what am I looking for
don't you know a book a scroll or
anything that will help us cross the
Black Lake
okay
Chuck
thanks oh
this
what is this place
cookie
okay I think there's some time to talk
now oh hello
oh so yeah I I got into the plane I sat
down into my premium economy seat got
myself comfortable I was very tired
though because it was actually sleepy
time
but soon after the takeoff they served
they started serving some food but in
this case they were serving it not all
at once they were serving it like one by
one seemingly so they started with some
star top
some appetizer or whatever and they took
it away after I ate it and then just
nothing came after that I waited on the
waiters
and they were just not following up and
eventually
I don't know I think they if I remember
correctly they may have even
turned off the lights in the cabin
ET
but I got really tired so I just fell
asleep waiting for the food hoping that
they would just wake me up when the rest
of the food would come
um
because it was supposed to be you know
like dinner time but they only brought
the appetizer and I knew that wasn't all
of it that couldn't be all of it
that was weird but I didn't think much
of it I just fell asleep too tired
eventually
I wake up
and it's just like the whole plane is
quiet
and kind of dark but I I had like a
middle uh
um
what do you call that seat it's like you
know there's it goes like probably two
or three on the left window side and
then in the middle
next to the
corridor
there's like four more seats and then on
the right side there's like two or three
more that was in the middle part but I
looked outside the window and I saw
uh that I don't know it looks like we
were descending
but we just took off and this was
supposed to be a little bit of a longer
aisle Stadium but like middle middle
aisle seat
was supposed to be a longer flight
so
it's kind of weird and normally if we
were really already landing and I just
slept through the whole thing but it
really didn't feel like it but then they
would tell us oh we are not ascending
please buckle your seat belts etc etc
this and that thank you for traveling
with us
no nothing of that like no comment
nothing
they just started descending
so obviously something was off
[Music]
what is that
what is that portal guys
because it seems like we have to go
straight up is this
like a safe Point portal
review well they were definitely trying
to hide something or not making us
get too excited for later okay already
Boston
don't fight in progress
what
I cannot
you cannot join a boss income but now I
can
come on
hey
what is this
oh there you are
oh my God
I'm scared I'm scared she seems uh
Herald of Lilith she seems a bit more
challenging than others
become
ow there's no bodies that can explode
unfortunately
is that a bug
out
what an annoying what
so much faster and dude for real
oh I think just
[Music]
blasting me around
oh okay we're already halfway
no problem
oh what the [\h__\h]
where's she
um
audio Yeah is this an audio bug because
it seems
not fitting
that's the game the fight started bug oh
oh [\h__\h]
okay hello I need more essence
[Music]
why was it so buggy
seems like the music should not be like
that
I had no issues with the stream oh okay
what about the what about the game
inspect the spell book well the game
recognizes that I killed the boss
it seemed kind of
hmm anti-climactic why was a demon
guarding that book
I should take this back to narrow
oh
good job thank you what
hmm something to fix for them some work
for them nice
so I go leave now bring a pausing
Spellbook to narelle through here
oh
yeah
okay wait we'll talk tonight around I
hope you had more luck tell you more
I found this interesting
this Ledger was written by the haradrim
this is chronicling spells and theories
created by rathma the first necromancer
that's not what we're looking for
um no
second door but it can still work there
must be a spell in this book we can use
to bring my mother back oh she knows the
ritual to cross the Black Lake okay what
well I am
coincidentally a necromancer it's all we
have my mother will help us through what
a coincidence me to be down there
should have done that right away
from the get-go
meet you down there okay
you're invested in the story okay okay
so yeah okay I look outside I see we're
kind of like descending nobody's saying
anything it's just quiet I think all the
others are also mostly asleep
and then
we land and I look outside and it's dark
outside it was already dark when we took
off but like it looked like really night
time and I see an airport outside
but kind of a dead airport because
Istanbul airport doesn't operate 24 7
it's like
oh oh we have a long path to walk
huh
doesn't operate 24 7. it was closed at
the time it was like past midnight I
don't know how late
yeah but uh after a really short time
for some reason we came back
and still we landed but still no comment
like that's the weirdest thing if you
fly
if you have flown before you know that
this is not normal when you're about to
land they tell you all kinds of things
save and tell you information about the
weather or before that even they tell
you oh we're gonna stop our
our uh past duty-free sales now
so I see the airport and this one people
start to wake up and the plane and get
confused
but still no comment
what the [\h__\h]
still no comment and then we are being
asked
to the board the plane to leave
still no comments we walked by
the um oh my god it feels so laggy right
now we walk by the
um cabin attendance and leave the plane
and they just say goodbye
we're all confused and they say please
just go inside there
into the clothes
empty airport like they opened up one
room
one room with
uh one single
Security check walkthrough thingy
and maybe two airport staff maybe at
most
but this is a big ass airplane this is
like how many I don't know how many
people they fit in those 300 it felt
like a lot of people
hmm
so they make us go in there
and ask us to go through
all of the
um
Security check again let's just tell the
actually just the
hand luggage stuff
but it's just one single I lack the
requirements okay that they prepared
because the airport is closed and they
have no staff and you know
just one so I was I was traveling alone
and I was feeling like really like
concerned at this point and I'm like
what the [\h__\h] I need to
I need to get to
Japan
actually it was only supposed to be like
a week
of vacation at that time
yeah
so
flying back and losing some time was
gonna be no problem
I mean seconds
good stuff that I'm getting here
[Music]
so I stand in line with a million of
people I was pretty far in the back one
by one they check everyone's luggage and
scan their bodies
and then finally it's my part my time
and I I after I'm done
I asked the airports security staff guy
who's standing there like what's going
on and he's like you don't know
at this point like me waiting in line
there already took an hour
and I was [\h__\h] tired and confused
oh Pine Hill
More Strangers in the camp
and behind me there were still a lot
more people so it was far from over but
I was done and I walked through and I
asked this guy what's going on he's like
hey you don't know and then he says
um there's a suspicion of
the t word
the t-e-r you know word
uh like
in your fight I guess
and I'm like what
uh oh oh oh oh okay
okay
so after we're done we were just like
told to wait in that one room
and I started like you know eventually
after a long time because it was just
like everybody was confused we wanted to
exchange information so I started to
talk to some strangers like one Japanese
uh dude who was like good with English
some other foreigners who were traveling
together oh no terbites
yeah we started talking eventually
before like they would actually explain
to us what's actually happening
you know where we first found
information
we spent in that first room we spent
like three four hours
in the middle of the night eventually
the airport even opened up during that
time it became morning and then while we
were there raining exchanging of
information
uh a news article went up
that said something about our flight
with something like a b-o-mb may have
been in there
and I was like oh good to know
yeah so we're getting hungry and then
eventually after three three or four
hours they finally bring us some
sandwiches everybody is like the
hundreds of people from the airplane are
jumping at the sandwiches like oh I want
I need I need
but we thought okay I mean we're
probably gonna board another plane soon
right right right so we weren't too
concerned but then eventually
they uh they tell us okay everybody
um sorry for the wait please follow us
this was some Turkish Airline stuff they
tell us to follow them
and they'll bring us outside the airport
to a hotel because we have to take a
different airplane and we'll just you
know they will take care of it
we just have to go to hotel room for a
while no exact time yet but we'll be
able to take a shower and maybe take a
nap Etc
so these hundreds of people follow them
through the airport then to the
immigration
like Gates exit thingy
and
I get there too
and then I am being stopped
and I am not able to
live because they asked me for
well some of the local currency in order
to get a Visa but I'm like but my flight
was basically delayed because bomb and
they told me to go with them I just I'm
just going to the hotel that's at the
airport and they're like well you need
to give us money
and meanwhile you know they're just
leaving the other people are just
leaving the Turkish Airline staff Etc
which was maybe one or two people
leaving me behind and I'm like you know
everybody's like
it's like normal flight passengers
everybody's mixed we're not not like one
compact group anymore so then I'm like
[\h__\h] and I get stressed out and I I go
and try to find an ATM but I think my
card wasn't working at that point
because overseas
and my card was just like not active for
some reason at that point
so I couldn't get any money
and I was [\h__\h]
hmm
yeah I was panicking I was much younger
than now too
so that was I was like what the [\h__\h] do
I do and then I tried to I think there
was some kind of like internet cafe
thingy or so so I tried to contact my
accommodation
tell them I'm I guess I'm not coming
and and then my accommodation is like
yeah I'm sick anyway so you can't come
anyway and I'm like uh great
um great this is exactly what I need
right now thank you
hmm
anyway So eventually
oh it probably would have been fine in
yours I don't know but the problem is I
didn't have any cash with me and I
couldn't take any money out of the ATM
yeah
anyway so
um now from here starts to 24 hours of
Doom because to just put the story kind
of shorter
uh
I was just stuck in the airport
without knowing when the next flight
would be they did not give us
information no matter how often me and
some other that people that I eventually
found who also couldn't go through to
the hotel and also were stuck in the
airport from the same flight I found
some of them we were going to the
Turkish Airlines customer uh service
support table desk thingy uh several
times and we're asking them begging them
to give us something to give us maybe
launch access because we're like there
forever
um we've nowhere to go and no help and
no accommodation and no no information
nothing no food either
that was my biggest problem I guess
um
and they just ignored us like it was
like a you know customer support desk
with like maybe free staff and two of
them were like maybe talking to other
random customers and the one that we
went up to in a group of like 10 people
they just like stood in front of us and
ignored us and then turned around and
went behind the counter behind the the
wall
you know they were just like walking
away from us and we asked the other ones
they also ignored us
the ironic thing is that at that time
they were
um they were advertising themselves as
European Europe's
uh number one what was it
customer service Airline or something
like that something like that something
similar
and there was none of that visible
they probably paid for that title
um that was [\h__\h] it was a freaking
joke
yeah so we were really frustrated
thankfully they were like
um a lot of people in that group that
were stuck with me that were way more
adult than I was and they were fighting
for justice and I don't know we were
just together for the whole time we
couldn't even get some launch access no
we had to sleep on
um the loud in the loud Hall on the cold
hard ground and the cold hard seats of
the of the airport
um when we could but I was like going
mentally insane felt like I was going
insane
and yeah the whole time which is the
boards wouldn't update telling us our
new flight it just wouldn't update so
for a long time we didn't know but we
spent 24 hours there on the airport
finally when we boarded though our new
flight we were really happy and all that
but we decided that our group we would
get together and then demand something
to make up for this [\h__\h]
um once we entered the airplane the
staff they still didn't apologize for
any inconvenience
they didn't give a [\h__\h]
ironic thing is that once we arrived in
Japan
um Ahoy Japanese
customer service
a Japanese
uh Turkish Airlines employee from that
was like at the Japanese airport came
into our airplane when we landed finally
and
um uh said
like explained that there they are sorry
and they gave all of us a printed letter
it was them though
and yeah we got the letter but we were
like well this is not enough so we went
up to the Turkish Airlines support
customer support whatever uh counter at
the Narita Airport
hoping that they would maybe like help
us with some compensation
but nothing and at this point we were so
exhausted
we were in this whole
thing for ages for like 30 hours I don't
know so we kind of just gave up
eventually
God's clear information for by Turkish
Airlines what happened but what we did
find out is later in the news so
basically
uh
soon after the flight
took off
um a cabin attendant opened to one of
the doors of the toilet
the toilets yeah and then inside was
like written in red the name of some
bomb
like a
like a I don't know
professional chemical name that I
wouldn't know that I wouldn't understand
like two numbers and two letters I don't
know yeah and they took that as a you
know as a fret
and but after checking all the luggage
um
after checking our hand like I also
ended up checking all the big luggages
oh yeah C4 that was it
turns out there was even
a bomb in there but not one that would
have gone off
like a fake one or so I don't know
maybe just to scare
for fun I don't understand I still don't
really know
but I did read that
there was something in there in fact but
it wasn't like really endangering us but
you know you obviously have to react but
it seems to have been a prank and then I
read some more information that this was
actually at that time happening a couple
of times
um
[Music]
it happened several times back then was
maybe the same person the same people
doing a series of
pranks
um wasn't the only occasion where
this happened
with a Turkish Airlines flight
so
yeah
never got any
questions out of that short already
short seven day trip I lost a whole day
which is a lot if it's just seven days
if it's like two weeks okay whatever but
seven days man I'll explain on the way
yeah
oh she'll explain on the way I could
have just walked all the time I was just
waiting because I thought you were gonna
she was gonna drop a lore bomb or so
yeah
well thank God nothing happened of
course
but what a
surreal weird experience
uh it was just like
I was so pissed because
they didn't help us at all they didn't
provide anything
I think eventually after a lot of like
pushing for it they
I'm stuck oh never mind they did after
many many hours give us some food coupon
for
one meal at the airport
in 24 hours
funny
yeah customer service local
yeah harassment's description of the
ritual was difficult to understand
and the notes weren't much better
I know how to talk
like nice okay
no it was just really frustrating and we
were all so exhausted that um
our minds were breaking
really bad
sorry for the thing here's a Snickers
bar
and since then I mean I I'm sure that
it's been many years that maybe they
made improvements on across
plastic possibly that wouldn't happen
again but just out of pure
salt and
me being pissed off
not wanting to support something like
that I decided to never fly with them
again
so Turkish Airlines perms lost forever I
don't give a [\h__\h]
spite yes bite
um
you feel it
let's hurry
like I'm I don't want to blame the whole
company and all that but if you can't
compensate
and take care of your passengers like
that and don't give a [\h__\h] about them
sorry you look others can still use it I
don't care but I'm not gonna fly with
them anymore they don't deserve my money
thank you
oh it's working
what mother please can you hear me
why they told my pie
I guess I can save you from this mother
I promise stop
[Music]
I can't be saved from my own mistakes
this bar that is only a husk
my spirit must pass on
and you must let me go
mother know if you love her let her go I
need you oh she's turning into a monster
oh my god without me no okay but I can
help you one last time before I go
you
you have the divine blessing
sorry your blood is the necessary key
[Music]
whoa
wow again
it feels kind of often in the slots
but
what's up with her back to life she may
have only come back to life as a
skeleton and who knew who would know if
she could even talk because my skeletons
don't seem to be able to talk maybe
that's the difference
oh sorry
the way is open
we have to go let's go
[Music]
let's go through this is even still here
in so long I'm afraid she's won this one
besides
I have to
sure stay back again and let me do all
the work it's not over yet
not for you
now this was off to rosma
find him learn why
I'll be back at the Vault okay all right
at least if you're gone maybe you'll be
using up a little bit less Ram
necropause of the firstborn
well that's a cool path
hey we just skipped it I know
so I want to walk over it
oh man
all right
cool
she got her mommy back for a little bit
you what the [\h__\h]
what the [\h__\h] you
don't know how that will
work out is she just gonna die you are
the last visitor to my Sanctum
though you come too late
just as Lilith did before you
for it was my father
inarias who arrived here first
it unfolded as my Visions foretold
how we
hurtle towards the prophecy's end
oh
interesting
[Music]
why did they die I wasn't in reach
is it the last
taco
all alone against the Thundering
Revenant my God
but wait there's more
oh level 13.
so I got all of those upgrades
what's next
I saw shattered images of the end of
sanctuary
the scales of a great
serpent carried these visions
and so I went to visit him
Maya and the Serpent's thoughts met
and the fragmented future
was mended together
I put it down in order
and the prophecy was born maybe another
skill
dispersed into a blood Miss bloody
missed becoming immune for three seconds
your movement speed is reduced and I
don't want that
50 for a life that surrounds the target
area for six seconds
Ironwood Maiden
Chris the target area enemies afflicted
by Iron Maiden take 13 damage each time
they deal direct damage lessons
that's like dot damage right
I don't know about that
because
oh there's more
skeleton Mages
up the irons warrants
Iron Maiden
one top one is good the bone thingy
what
one
what which one
what about this one A specter of your
charges forward and attacks with its
Scythe for 85 damage and then returns
you on attacks again
kind of sounds fun
Alicia concentrated the light that deals
for the damage and leaves behind a
defiled area dealing 108 damage over 6
seconds
what
oh no
at the right of
Iron Maiden just
there's nothing there's nothing on the
right side
I know it's a rap band
do the branch for corpse explosion
well I'll give it one
I'll give it one because I cannot decide
yeah all right yeah I I kind of I don't
know I thought we were gonna maybe
replace bone splinters soonish anyway
but I guess no not so far
so far not
if if it's worth it then I need to
destroy the tumors to go
to go humorous
if it's worth it then I would
upgrade it
can't
I can't replace it
oh am I stuck with that one as my base
attack
ah well then
okay
and I'll focus on that next because I do
use it a lot
obviously
[Music]
oh there's a chest there about it
destroy another tumor
anyway I hope you guys enjoyed the
beautiful story
of my travels
but
how much I travel
how many planes I've boarded
that is the only really
weird dramatic annoying
thing that happened to me
I would say at least
one that's really it stuck with me in my
mind
what this means I'm just like I'm
unfazed by anything else
cannot
annoy me lying to me is just
so
I know
so used to it
understand the nature of such a thing
I know anarius would be driven to
interfere
believing that it was about him
savior
piercing hatred's heart and Hell
thanks for the lore go next
I skipped all of that
but since we got low hair I think I'm
the on the right path
oh well
another beautiful statue of future wife
funny how you almost became
yes true I almost became a
cabin attendant
I would have if I wouldn't have been so
honest
sorry
oh raping side
let's go more in character I love it
[Music]
I'll keep the shadow resistance for now
I'm a reaper now
deadbeat's reaping now
finish folio
getting the perfect
weapon for a necromancer AKA
Reaper
uh
look I can't I can't go here can I
maybe another tumor in the way what
about this stuff ooh
ew ew ew ew
huh
hola
I am
circling back
I'm circling back to the area that I was
worried that I missed
amazing
Angelic Memorial
oh
when I
[Music]
nah no need to switch to that
oh hi so I locked
locked to hell
it was only a matter of time before
norius would discover what I'd done
and come demanding the key
who the reaper now Kelly real quiet now
okay my inventory is getting really full
what the hell
so I'm gonna start picking up items that
don't look important after all
the money
and the items are not gonna be worth it
afterwards
no need to worry
you you what's this
ew
I'll put back now it's all right
Resident Evil 4 right oh she married she
got it
she did it
she got to play the thing first Persona
now resident oh assistant a lucky one
good for her wearing my Square sheets
games the holy blood in your face should
be boiling
is that a remake the new one that she
played nothing you do will change the
future I don't really know much about
Resident Evil I
part of it
it is wider Beyond Comprehension of
ungrateful spawns like yourself
am I done with your banter
I'm glad
is it good
not playing planning to playing but this
is good
oh geez from 2005. oh wow
where I belong
I wish it would be true father
rave reviews oh damn
it's just in your head
oh
look at this View
Ashley from the Remake looks like me oh
I have to look it up
like me really is she pretty she better
be pretty
excuse me
I won't say it I won't say it because
when I say this gives me something
something about you guys just
probably think
everything gives her something something
vibes
you know what I mean though
can you guess cute oh Ashley cute
yeah
oh yes I meant Lord of the Rings I
cannot
is it are we bugging again
[Music]
have a similar strategy but who the [\h__\h]
are you
what's happening
I'm gonna die
okay okay
[Music]
I can still make it I can still make get
inside okay okay okay now I get it I
thought I couldn't get inside thank you
for protecting me
[Applause]
here I'm alone without the skeletons and
I'll show you even without them I'm
strong
I will win this no matter what
Gokey Wawa
hi hi
no need
oh it could have possibly been shooting
this whole time
yikes
drop me some more please
otherwise I die
where are the drops
laughs
foreign
[Music]
persevering even through the toughest
moments where it looks like All Is Lost
once again she did it
once again
what's this oh beautiful
[Music]
hell to the hill
it is inventory a little bit
first legendary
huh
what this all looks legendary to me
Oh you mean enemy or what
orange weapon
what
that's yellow
where's the orange
oh wait this one ah legendary dagger I
wanna decide this is weaker than what I
have
oh well
hey color blindfold
kneeling in front of me what a helmet
are we giving a hug
oh
oh no we opened
he's empty his hollow
hello there is someone
oh my God
I have done all that was asked
the brain is gone now
punishment
no a stronger man would have refused
venard's Prime
[Music]
is she safe yes
She is safe
[Music]
no coincidence
I came here to help
[Music]
I don't even give this to her for me I
should never have taken it
[Music]
he's so dark repented
do you think I was
no no no
not too late
the light has come to carry you home
see it friend
yes
I see it now
they
have come
[Music]
at least you died
in a sick ass armor
you let that
ruining what I just said but okay let's
contradict ourselves
[Music]
man
that's so sad the way he died but he
tried to protect and help me
thanks beagle you are a good man
I appreciate it I will
under the watchful eyes of the Great
Serpent in my Sanctum
if you are chosen as you say grab his
skeletons come
that's kind of deep let me try that I
need my skeletons They're All Dead
was really cool yeah
oh it's not his I think because his body
is here
what was that was that the boss's body I
I didn't look so closely
that's all I can get
who was that from
that's from the boss no way cool that's
a cool skeleton to have
yeah let's let's rest in peace
we're still going at it now why let me
get some
let me get some
before we go there
did I backtrack will I get another
chance for skeletons
no need okay I guess she probably won't
even be there we probably won't fight
her because shouldn't that be the last
boss rathma
eh just cinematics okay okay no more
fight hopefully
oh my God
whoa
like a movie
yeah that's so big but wait where's she
she's so tiny
to stand beside me in this new world
that I would have saved your place
just the same
and now
all that you might have been
has been stolen from me
Stone
hey
[Music]
is it enough
it unlocks our path to the Future
made possible because of the price you
paid
your sacrifice
will not have been in vain
[Music]
that's so good
blessed prayer beats what blessed
prayer up prayer not player
I just switched it up to a orange one
you can't offer me another different one
now
I was putting on my skeletons if I could
speak with narelle where she
don't have to walk do I
what
I think I have to walk I can team
peoples
oh ah that's food now okay that's good
then I mean she can gladly have it but
wouldn't that be in the quest Adams then
ah but we got here
I should go here if anything
[Music]
good night
good night hole
if you go to sleep
did I just make a big mistake
oh wait I can at least sell some stuff
here uh
um
[Music]
I want to sell that but I won't be
playing after today I'll take it
he's like
um
that's not even ask her if she's sure
what else you want
give me all the money almost 30 000.
make it all good deal boys special item
that cannot be replaced
[Music]
um
it's not a quest item though
slight discomfort keeps on going
what else you want
um
[Music]
it's okay to sell it okay
this looks so nice I don't want to sell
this stuff
uh this can go
yeah everything can go
[Music]
there's also special item but not Quest
Adam
bye bye why was so laggy yeah that's how
it is I don't need to use my stash it's
okay
I am just want to hear what narrow has
to say
and then
that might be the end of it for today
I can't I can't uh keep my brother
waiting for too long
oh yeah I think the shop makes me like
more
um I was all right though wasn't it at
least I didn't like completely crash
Frozen
just saying but last time you guys were
like feeling so sorry and so bad for him
he's freezing outside
first of all that was like the deal
and second of all
he even after that when I said you can
come back now ended up staying outside
for one more hour
voluntarily
wanted you to have this
um
he was a good man
oh chip just buried her mom
is she even there
did you meet her already gone by the
time I arrived
more I can see that Lilith took a key to
hell off rathma's body
then it was
all in vain
the only one who got what they wanted
[Music]
he came seeking the horadron of Legend
hope thank you Kevin yeah collapse
that's for sure but her part in things
was intrusive I feel like I'll find one
or two to collab with me at the time
though
for anyone
inarias proved to be just as under
unreliable as I'd feared his
self-obsession had driven him to murder
his son act one done did I manage to
clear one out what's behind perfect
Lilith had taken a key to hell
where would she use it
it only depends on ourselves to find out
another advertisement Why I'm not done
right you could play longer right or is
is this all of the story but you can
still up your level
interesting you can play more but
stories then ah oh well then I mean no
need to get to level 25 I did like the
important stuff I did all of the
story for now but wow
you could explore
all of this oh yeah there's areas for
level 20 for 35 where you could go I
guess in theory but sounds dangerous 36
40.
oh wow wow
yeah
oh it's closed off ah okay but it seems
like you could go like here maybe
shows you a quest that you just can't
progress so I feel like you could go
there
Maybe
we should launch wouldn't be so far
honestly June feels extremely close to
me
it's already the end of March yo
level 20 for the doggo uh too bad we're
pretty far from that
not really manageable
now
how do you save by the way in the game
is there like Auto safe
I would like to save at least before
closing
how did you light the Necromancer it was
amazing it was really easy it was
comfortable it was fun
all the safe
okay
yeah I had a good time
but as I said I mean if it wasn't for
Cali I might play it but it seems like
such a popular choice and I should just
try something else
because I feel like if Cali plays she'll
go for the Necromancer I want to try
something else but I really hope that
they buffed The Druids by then because
the Druid speaks the most to me
I did play also drew it back in the day
in World of Warcraft for a while
didn't get far but you know it's one of
the things that I'm interested in
they won't they then maybe well don't
say they won't they might
they might
the words are cool yeah they're so cool
plenty playable
really don't listen to metal players
we'll see we'll see a little buff would
surely be nice
Necromancer seems a little bit
overpowered
Shaman was fun
yeah
oh your old man was a druid and World of
Warcraft hey
well uh
I welcome somebody oh dear I can't stop
fighting
I'm gonna go and make some food now and
tomorrow is my day off
um I'll make a schedule when I wake up
but there will be at least two Fire
Emblem streams and more Metroid Prime I
think I was playing Medford Prime on
like Tuesday maybe
on the weekends I am blem
so something like that we'll see we'll
see I have to think a little bit about
what else
thanks for the stream thank you for
watching
I hope you guys enjoyed it
um the better the open Beta is so
playable so you guys can play it
yourself still if you want to
give it a try
leave a game I guess
yeah I'm glad it worked out thank you
guys for telling me about it I didn't
even know
next time feel free to tell me earlier
remind me earlier oh
that reminds me
the eShop is closing right today is the
day before it closes
oh
[Music]
touring my beloved
torn was tauren was the the one who will
never will be
slow motion low FPS
was amazing
Paula bought so much stuff on stream
ah
I don't know if I'll buy anything at all
[Music]
it's not even know what I don't know if
you can
I feel like
I had big issues trying to use the eShop
before when I tried to buy uh
when I tried to buy
um
the what the Zelda game that we played
yeah I don't remember
I'll give it a try
but I feel like I had troubles with it
wait let me
quickly go here
[Music]
that didn't happen in a while I wanna
see
really quickly
I tried closing ah
I'm trying to close the gate but it's
like uh
freezing my computer I don't know what's
happening right now
are you guys hearing me hello
let me open my my Google my YouTube
you see the comments
wait wait wait
okay game close
chat let me open you again one second
YouTube slow
uh uh hi hi
sorry game Crash almost a PC crash
almost
okay I don't think I'll be reading super
strong
let me see let my if my brother wrote To
Me
it's just waiting
yeah he's just waiting
stay a while and listen
I guess
I guess we can read some so stay a while
and listen if you wanna
nice mic it's cute red blue made it
maybe the ones from this stream nah I
shouldn't skip so much that's weird
you won't buy games eh I don't know
does it count as another game finished I
mean better finished I would say more or
less sure
but not really the whole game finished
[Music]
kind of like oh I'm not lagging on my
side are you sure
I'm gonna sleep now good night
I'm not ending yet
you've got two hours two hours until the
shop closes for real for real
but like there might be a problem even
if I get to like like you know use the
eShop you know how recently my card has
been declined by the switch eShop for
example
and other things
I wonder
that would happen now
browse for some games
huh thank you I'm glad you can watch
this dream
better hurry time to try
yeah
Nintendo does not take care credit cards
how did I
how did I play last time
at Wii U
someone remember how I paid for it
uh Wind Waker
Bishop card PayPal
ah no way doesn't it work like you load
up your account
on like a browser on your PC or so with
PayPal
give your account some money
I don't is that not how it works
did I use cars gift cards
foreign
yeah no I think I loaded it up on the
browser though because I don't know if I
could do it properly on the Wii U
H
it's so annoying
what games okay
somebody surely sent me a list before
right of games that would be interesting
to me
send me that again I'll look for it now
and see if anything's worth it to me
going through that trouble
they've turned off the right buying from
the eShop
so how would I buy it
I did
I wanna buy it
Twilight Princess would be nice but I
feel like I could just buy a physical
copy of that
I'll surely find one
if you don't you'll have to buy physical
trial princess over 100 plus or over and
finally I'll find something
um you could buy for the website can I
wait what's it called this is the same
as the normal Nintendo website are they
connected
it goes crazy expensive for real
[Music]
it will likely come out on switch
now come see that happen
still connected for now okay so how does
this work though my Nintendo store I
thought it wasn't like
wasn't it like separate though
I thought it looks separate
just can't add funds from the issue
if I can't add funds then I probably
can't buy anything
ah you add the funds on your own okay
but that's what you mean yeah yeah
that's the same thing I did last time
because it was already not possible that
back then I think
yeah
guys can't you just like borrow me your
Wii U physical Twilight Princess copy
let's have one just borrow it to me
please uh I see the list
[Music]
video games travel princess Paper Mario
not interested Nintendo Land
not interesting I think
nah not interested Kirby and the Rainbow
Curse
thank you
cute but not interested no need
it's a banger but
I wasn't like planning on getting it I
mean it looks cute but like
I don't I don't feel like I need it
Wii games
that will need a Wii remote Super Mario
Galaxy 2.
so is there no
um
other console
for Super Mario Galaxy 2.
I mean it's a Wii game right but Wii U
and Wayne
not yet well you know I haven't been
trying to play all the Mario because I
can play them just
one Metroid Prime Trilogy
well that's something interesting now
but
I play I'm playing it on switch right
now
so where's the difference to that
I guess it's not the trilogy but
the only ways to play two and three now
um I don't know nothing here is really
urging me
it's annoying this is completely on
Nintendo though that they closed the
shop and now
it's just annoying to go through all
that hassle
[Music]
I would buy what you want to stream
yeah I agree that's what I'm like
thinking about when I look at this stuff
I would like to stream Twilight Princess
eventually but Chad has been telling you
for a year I know
I know but
I waited until the last day but I don't
care stupid
until last time because in the first
place it was never that like interesting
anyway
for me to get that any of that
[Music]
the ball around someone or you know if I
really really need some I think you know
even Twilight Princess
maybe I will get a remaster you know
um switch yourself and until
that comes I'm busy with all the games
anyway because first I'm gonna play
um in May gonna play the new one
breath of the wild too
and then later I'm gonna play uh I have
other games I can play first
um
oh
come here
lazy because you are crazy I'm just
gonna borrow Paul moose Wii U
if I need to play one game so urgently
for one reason that I'm here and I just
really have to I have to for some reason
I'll just like fly over to pomu and
sleep at her place for two weeks while
streaming that one game
I'll take it
brilliant problem solved Felix says
but so far nothing here is like
screaming to me that I need it right now
and also not anytime soon I'm so sorry
you guys were trying to get me to do
this for a year I'm sorry
hmm
sounds like a good deal oh everybody's
happy okay
hmm
[Music]
let's get toilet prison no I'm just
gonna
yeah
one second
we have this
website
where they sell like used things
let me check
Twilight Princess
we
um
wow
maybe not right now
no it's not eBay
sold sold sold sold why everything's
sold man
my friend says
oh
42 Euro
what is this shop though
[Music]
seven percent off
cool
oh it's a game code
oh and it sends digitally no wait it's
out of stock
[Music]
what about Amazon
Twilight Princess HD limited edition
and I buy
Ultra cup
uh
oh yeah well I mean
Nintendo this is one of your best games
why you make it
untouchable
no way they will re-release it they have
to
move
five
[Music]
I think my Wii U was not even charged
can I do it all on the PC
I don't think I can even turn on my
can I do it on the PC
like everything the whole process
okay walk me through it
walk me through it all
and that
food baby
thank you where's the potato
first turn on the PC it's on
no you need to download the game well
yeah I mean that's later
can I not download it anymore after I
bought it later
let's do step by step let's buy it first
movie okay
moving
[Music]
a little [\h__\h]
not only right away uh-huh
okay yeah sure okay
oh browser's open
skip skip
where do I go what do I do
[Music]
ah
Nintendo store
why does it have to be UK Twilight
Princess
I'll miss this you're just saying that
now because you want me to visit promo
okay is this gonna buy it here
uh what I never bought something like
this before on the on their website how
does this work
can I even buy it I can't buy it here oh
wait my tattoo
what's my password maybe that
okay
oh guys guys it's happening
but okay I
um won't work with my card probably
let's first try the card I guess
probably turned me down
[Music]
purchasing
you probably want me to uh
it's done
I did it
it says thank you the download will
start automatically
um
when you activate automatic stuff for
downloads on your console
I I think I did it
uh
cool
that was easy wait let me go back I want
to read the
with some information there
download
okay but the other games
what's that I is the DS Virtual Console
work do I have to like how do I buy
those games
same way
say
Phantom oh but I'm not I don't think I
would stream that
privately no
I don't know how that works it doesn't
show up when I look it up
okay
okay I don't need that I don't need
those two
I just did Twilight Princess I got it
now so what I will do is I will try to
charge my Wii U now and download it
right away just in case because some of
you guys were saying I have to download
it also right away
just in case
what game what's happening I just
um I was pressured for one year I was
tortured and pressured to use the
Nintendo eShop against my will to buy
The Legend of Zelda Twilight Princess
and now in the last one and a half hours
they have pressured me so hard that I
was sweating bullets they've pushed me
to a corner and I had to do it I had
given I used my money 50 bucks they took
it away from me they ripped it off of me
just like my pride and everything
I have nothing but a hollow shell of
Phoenix nothing is left inside of me I
had no choice
okay
so okay I will go now because I I have
to figure out this view thingy
um I might schedule some Super Chat
rating for next weekend because I'm
behind
um
[Music]
one year you told me every day you're
like Chihuahua Kiowa in
364 days the store is closing
you have to go buy the games now you
have no time left
and then it's 250 days oh keep all this
only
all of the games now or never and it
continued like that
it's just we have uh as burbs okay we
have a tendency to be dramatic don't we
just find Common Grounds on that huh
a bunch of Nintendo salesman oh
is that what you guys are are you
working for Nintendo
extra lie are you working for Nintendo
and yet you waited till today yeah
yeah really urgent until today
you definitely are dramatic
what
oh no she found out Nintendo ninjas
online
yep yep
I'm sorry to apologize into buying
something you didn't want
to add
to refund me if in
in 24 months Nintendo releases a
remaster a remake or whatever uh or just
a really thingy relocation whatever you
call it for it for the switch or the
next upcoming console if that happens
yeah I'll be like
um
um so what did you put me through for
what a whole year
I'm just I'm just kidding you guys okay
it's kidding you
it's okay thank you for reminding me
endlessly
until the last moment thank you
but that's really the only game where I
feel like I need it
emotional damage
but really you didn't have to remind me
like six months ago
I wasn't gonna get anything at that time
foreign
you know come now and clean the
apartment a little bit because
yeah
no I want I've been watching nothing of
that guy I don't know that thing just
stuck to me from watching some meme
where that was used
just like that one voice clip was used
emotional damage
I literally don't know who that is
some popular
meme Lord right
it's not that
today is
anyway I had fun guys thanks for the
banter
uh
shall disappear
and shame
she'll crumble
like apple pie
okay
tomorrow sleepy day
and build Furniture day
and installing Sims one day but I won't
play it the upcoming week right away and
I think I think I'll wait um
yeah when I'm done with Fire Emblem I'm
Metro prom
[Music]
adventure guys for a fun time thank you
soon
yeah Sims one I've been wanting to play
it for a while and I I bought all the
physical copies again
played on stream
okay
[Music]
see you soon bye bye
hasta yasumi
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]