[Music]
oh
help me
i am
[Music]
have you seen her
before
[Music]
good good i said i need to coupon before
i turn into a can of tuna
[Music]
hello
hello hello
hello hello hello
sorry for the wait guys uh welcome to
mario party
with us
um
super mario party so maybe superstar
yeah it's new
it's a
new mario party with old games and uh i
welcome these beautiful ladies tonight
with to play it with me
hello
did you hear it now bloop was looking
for you
what
oh you didn't hear me
ignore bloop at all costs
and nice to have you gua hi ame
hello
and we have from whole council mummy
my
boyfriend yes uh i think we are
actually
not even that hungover how's everyone
feeling
i'm over here
a little bit
yeah i'm sleepy oh no
i am sleepy i slept like seven hours
after this yeah
[Music]
did everybody just go to bed after i
think i tried
i had caffeine so it took me another two
hours to actually fall
after
[Music]
how's the audience did you guys get some
sleep chat i hope you did oh yeah
good morning
bright sunshine
let's get freaking started mario party
don't tire yourself that's freaking
party we already tired ourselves out
too late
was that toad speaking to us
he said that um
can someone like this
someone read this with toad voice
oh
if you want to play with someone else
press b to end your current session
wow uncanny i'm sorry if that's loud
that was incredible got it
wait
i like this one after
i think we can just rejoin really easy
yeah wait we have not in game though
yeah because the room id will show a
thing oh yeah but it's only for it's
friends only so
ah
let's step back to the start screen what
the what oh no yeah
we go pretty much it's the online start
screen because i think it's like a
little world thing
[Music]
okay room is open
look at my mario party car
the mario party card my favorite game
nintendo gamecube mario party 5 yes yes
uh favorite board i wasn't stacked
but favorite minions you see those i
love the one where you move bowser's
face
i love that one
good one okay only am i missing
um
no card
i think i pressed b by x and so it sent
me back to this yes it happened the
lovely start screen no problem
the permission
what's your favorite uh mario party chat
and girls
do you have one oh
oh there's one on gamecube
yeah there's two on gamecube i think two
four and five i think
yeah one of those
i meant
don't tie yourself out oh it's more like
toad i don't know what it sounds like
i think that's more feminine
which one do you like
oh no more mario party games i like
mario party hey
for the nintendo wii and then i also
like mario party diaz is pretty good oh
yeah there's this video of this person
playing with a bunch of their friends
and they enabled like really crispy
audio while they all played mario party
ds and they did the candle blowing out
game maybe that was the gamecube i don't
know but it was really funny i should
find it and show you guys who won that
hurried
read it read it away my maple
me i don't know what they sound like
just make it up
imperfect to decide the superstar is
about to begin
cute
i'm getting excited
do you know how to play no you don't
make or explain i don't but but don't
don't
oh
okay well we should explain how to play
mario party oh you can play no no i have
an idea i have an idea don't worry about
me okay i'll figure it out why is daisy
because she looks like me sorry i'm
using the cutie
i'm using the cutie to charm you girls
why are you for almond guys donkey kong
yoshi for mommy i like them i'm glad you
like donkey kong
oh cute fruit
okay five maps difficulty one difficult
two difficult degrees
our birthday cake sounds cool yeah i
wanna do this one yeah
it looks big yeah
it looks kind of lame
[Applause]
which one doesn't look lame to you
this one
what do you want there's no doubles too
spaceland and then end it with
horrorland or so perhaps how about that
how about that perhaps i'll do spaceline
okay venture into the galaxy but beware
of runaway spaceships and bowser beams
oh [\h__\h] all right
all right now bowser's beans
uh 15 turns
45 minutes okay sounds good let's do uh
two uh two games then i recommend 15
turns if you're playing on spaceland
okay bonus stars bundle stars can really
turn the tide of a game i wonder which
ones you'll get
[Music]
classic disney strategy sets set
features rich mini game and eventful
bonus
bonus star stars what
oh classical bonus star stars
which which mode is let's do classic i
guess because we're playing this game
for nostalgia reasons
and minigame help you see instructions
and controls before starting them in the
game yeah i think we need that to get
the best trees
yeah
handicap uh everyone will start with no
sides okay no star stars
oh lastly pick a minigame pack each pack
holds a different selection of mini
games
can we go
[Music]
yeah or we could do it all cause i don't
have ever anything true okay okay okay i
love my gamecube yeah
mario party
skill
uh totally existed skill
[Applause]
mummy please read
oh what voice was amelia i'm not so
luxin huh
i don't remember the last time we played
mario party to be honest i don't know
what happened when are you reading this
[Laughter]
we made it this is space land
yeah
is it the vine sauce that played it with
the microphone
[Music]
what
what i'm sorry i'm just gonna ignore me
i still try to find that candle video
it's so funny that you guys would like
it sorry sorry
and the ds
oh wait
who is it just my voice um who may read
this
oh
a brave superstar vanquished an evil
king and restored peace to the galaxy
i don't know
the galaxy i like that
galaxy another one gomez oh oh my
goodness
[Music]
the people of this galaxy need a savior
that's us
will you step up and become the
superstar that the people need
motivated right now he does okay
excellent i can see you're just the
person for the child
oh yeah we are good good eyes
oh my god there's so much i didn't take
it
but now
with banana we're here i've got some
business to take care of i'll see you
later thank god
okay bye-bye
from here oh thank goodness
you got it
i guess it's up to me to be a guy
oh it's your first time playing
is it no i mean yeah are you gonna
explain everything no surprise we don't
want to know anything
okay we'll decide to turn order okay
it looks vibrant
oh wow oh she's backing oh nice is that
good or bad
thank god that's good that's first
she used up all her look in the first
row guys let's go
yoshi's second
donkey kong third
you gotta press
a i think you got to press a gura
oh all right say
thank you pop all right
it says i'm first though oh you guys are
first too now the territory has decided
here's some coins to get you all started
oh yeah
it all hurts
[Music]
where's the first four kings jar dokka
tell that
towards
[Laughter]
wow
[Music]
let's get started
everyone give it your best shout out
there good luck and have fun yeah we
will thank y'all
oh my why is yoshi okay
yeah that's right
why are we always taking a look at the
floor
okay okay oh cute you pull out of my uh
um
okay oh stickers oh nice
oh wow
let's go
we're the wario stickers whoa
what
wow that's cute
so yes i i truly don't know what i'm
doing but i'll pull out a map too
yeah
she said that she doesn't have much
experience in it's been a very long time
oh yeah we have any questions
dang it
that's okay solid
uh dices huh is there only i hope one
dice i like that
if you get the option maybe
oh you have to go this way all right
that
hey hold up sorry with the the darker
mask it's like a gas mask why is he
wearing a gas mask that's scary oh what
is your eyes oh my god
oh yeah
wait what the hell i didn't realize that
kanata simple was playing with us
huh
i don't know what that means
okay
congrats
yes
oh speed oh item space desu
give me something good
what is this
game time oh no yeah is it a minigame it
says this is focus pick an item start
because i can't get the key
i don't know what i even want i don't
even know what i want here's the one
well then i'll tell you
i'm keeping an eye on it the key is the
one on the top right top right really i
mean i don't i don't even know what i
want but i'll i'll take it then i'll
take it
what's that
what's that florida justin star no
i don't know
magic doorway to this
skeleton key open the gate oh it's a
gate
thank you amen
you're welcome
oh four player mini game all vicious
everyone
what's it gonna be bouncing trash like
my friend knight right oh is this the
magic mansion one
oh it's not
i'm so good at that one
the chain chomp come as close as
possible and stop it with a flashlight
whoever stops is close ah i see
ourselves oh
this is like a game i played recently oh
we'll get it as close as possible
yeah and then press a to flash the light
edit
are you like that you can test it out
right now i think
oh wow oh i was watching yoshi i give
him yoshi
yeah that's too early obviously
i am ready whatever you want until you
gotta press start if you're ready
i mean plus or minus yeah
okay okay
okay
easy enough
hey wait the first time you switch
it hasn't been wrong all the time or did
it change back to this stupid oh yeah i
saw that before when you were playing
with good uh
it happened before right
yeah it's like default for a minute i'll
change it a little bit in a moment
oh i think actually i think good i got
this one i know a good idea may look
really close oh nice oh
nice fixing thumbnail
oh no my browser where's your guys's
switches mine's on my desk it keeps
making me look like i'm in a nap
oh because you're playing they're like
playing handheld sort of and for me the
thumbnail is superstars oh well
i usually do that but i decided not
today
what are these stickers
i can choose a sticker yes
what do they do yeah it shows that
you're motivated
snippet patrol
what's the sniffing
it took five coins from you
oh i don't know
oh no taking your money
right the police
oh they're going to jail it's the pogo
i know are they coming closer
oh what am i doing cute
go yoshi go yoshi
[Music]
oh what's this
oh
oh can you go in there now oh no oh oh
she's taking no money uh-huh all right
ah you're lucky then
[Music]
at least say that you're passing through
make a hole
monkey coming through
yes go go don't waste so much time what
is this
kuba bank uh
oh you have to
will i ever get it back though
yeah you probably like when you come
back they're like your canal deposit
you're really maybe it has an interest
rate who knows that would be nice anyone
who lands in this space gets all the
coins we're holding
[Music]
where does it say how many more steps i
have two ah in the middle
okay
i'm getting closer
[Music]
for play minigame again
oh
oh my well i didn't that didn't enter my
brain
how many ah how many ball bombs in that
country how do you how do you oh i
oh god
yeah
oh oh but they're also going to be
exploding oh
i see and said ivf of sexy
oh god it's so many
i'm ready
i can't count that fast what the hell
are you guys actually counting it like
properly
i was oh
that was a really good impression thank
you
okay it's like i get it
when do we start
okay
no no i don't know
[Music]
so you can just copy the guy next to you
right yeah oh wait did we remove it
yeah yeah we've beat with beans
but i see are we all right
[Music]
it should be hidden from the others
i feel like i shouldn't let us see each
other's yeah
that is true indeed yeah
oh well
don't get used to this easiness
ah real time
oh it's a square
the spaceship is a squeeze oh yeah
what was that
yes oh
i hope it's a barrel one again
oh i was too good at that one
they knew it
oh
oh oh is that good
it doesn't even stop when you break it
just look bad
[Laughter]
what's wrong with the baby bowser
he's ugly
oh callie is with us in spirits
on your right left wheel oh what's this
i have to jump oh cool that's cute
yoshi okay
get the key how do you
how do you do that next moment
jump
got it it looks good double wait
that's pretty good yeah
if you're like really far away from the
star and you want to get there faster
use the double dice
i'm kind of close to the star but can i
even buy it is it 20 coins
yeah i was gonna say i thought it maybe
it's 30 or something oh [\h__\h] oh god
what do you think the first star is like
10 or so i don't know saying it's 20. oh
nice
funny okay please please give me good
roll
i need one two three four land on the
bowser yeah don't roll it too nice
[Music]
please be cheap
oh you definitely have one
[Laughter]
that's what it says
yeah just keeping it warm for me thanks
kiara you're welcome
oh next up
goodbye bye bye
oh hello i should have went that way oh
you can oh
when you reach the middle can you decide
which way to go yeah i think so yeah oh
[Music]
you are broke yeah
i'm gonna come back again bye-bye oh
lucky lucky
uh
[Music]
does that make me faster plus five oh
that's pretty good yeah yeah mini game
girl mini game
oh full play again come on give us some
versus cool i like this music
i have a pair of sounds okay yeah
what's that
sounds dangerous
it does
oh i think i know this one
yay
oh god oh no
i'm like i'm switching to my pro
controller okay uh i'm on the pro
controller too and i'm still falling
down every five meters oh sh
am i gonna beat to that in the mario
movie hell here i am whoa
[Music]
okay okay i'll see this
this is a good one i like this one
intense music oh god
i feel like it just randomly accelerated
act too hard
[Music]
which way am i supposed to go does this
matter
i'm just i am just a jack guy
good question
i wonder
there's a timer oh my god what oh
that's stressing yeah i got it already
[Music]
oh
i'm a gamer
yeah
what was easier the obstacle course in
minecraft or that's that path now
i'm in um
probably the path just now
really
yeah
i can use my double dies what if i get
two oh
oh
i'd cry
it's not holy
okay
can you read that for me omelette
you can use the item you just got do you
want to give it a try
yeah
do it
is there a strategy
uh
be lucky
yeah
time it no don't have it close your eyes
when you do it close my eyes yeah i
don't trust you
that's what i do
yeah is there no strategy no unless i
mean maybe i don't know
mario party oh your heart me
ranked mario party nice
nice
we just want a bigger number than two
here
no
please
it's a grand slam
give him that money
he's got a gun he's pointing a gun
wait a minute i shouldn't be the other
way
are you pointing a gun at him
he's the bank person uh you wanted the
money
how did i go this way i wish to go oh i
see okay well that could have been bad
give me the eyes
yes
first get those stars
suddenly here become competitive
because i have a chance
awakening that's the spirit
let's go
next eye location
goodbye
make it a close one oh hello oh okay
that okay interesting
oh
thank you tell that
in theory
could women just go left
[Music]
is the spaceship gonna explode if it
goes down to zero
is the game over there
when are you okay mo
nice and you walk
thank you
treat yourself before you wreck you
screwed up i tempe oh i get a goody bag
[Music]
it's early christmas
i want a participation gift
participation
[Music]
i'm racking up the lucky did i have
bonus stars in this game
oh yeah i think we turned it on yeah
yeah
all right i'm racking up the lucky
spaces with my buddy
okay is that i met with a
i'm mask that money from everyone
yeah
[Music]
sorry
oh
everyone versus them
okay i was wendy's squared away
good luck you guys
let's destroy ami
what is this
oh what is this
copyright to chase down the solo player
okay
[Music]
when the ground pounder becomes the
ground pounded
yeah good luck guys
okay good luck okay
easy easy easy easy
[Applause]
[Laughter]
oh
no my minigame is
of course it is it's not even at all
they should have made it bigger they
should have made the map bigger
i kind of see that it doesn't seem very
fair
i'm gonna need to win right now
i'm gonna use a star
now the comeback i've learned you can do
the same
in the second half it'll happen
dang it
yoshi's really cute but wiggles oh no
uh oh the money
[Music]
not the money
uh
okay so it's one way what does the power
plug mean i wonder do you want to use an
item
open a gate
steal item from the opponent of your
choice interesting
roll the dice and you're saying it was
to a regular roll then yes it had
scratchy
yes
oh yeah
three
oh
you at least have enough money to buy
something yeah well you have a lot more
oh one more
oh
actually the key is not even worth
that much you should get the custom dice
block you can decide how far you go with
the custom dice block
yeah custom how about you ah you're
working on items oh i was gonna say
though i think i don't have enough space
for anything because i got a lucky bag
let me try though let me try uh
uh
um
let me see if it lets me though oh i can
it does nice
random opponent okay okay oh now you can
get it and get rid of it
here's an item to discard
bye
ah
i'll put a mushroom
useless mm-hmm that takes milkshake away
i'll be right back
uh i should have bought an oreo shake
when i was outside oh
oh so good well
do i want this
eight eight eight but i don't have i
don't have enough money even if i get
closer oh well let's unlock it and then
maybe in the next mini game i can make
some more money
huh
i truly enjoyed the time we shared i'll
miss the way the inside of your pocket
smells
ew
what
yeah go go move why is she not moving ah
okay
oh is it open for other people now to
the gate
i can name you
what for free
oh
uh i would have had to pay 50 coins
before a star but i can steal money for
free let's go that's good i needed money
anyway
so this is where it begins
exactly lots of money in the bank of
shark oh i'm coming for your money go up
okay
i think you have to press away because
oh yeah okay no don't
know
you can apparently smash him away
no that's garbage you can't really
[Laughter]
you cannot
money
attack 12 coins that's enough to buy the
next star perhaps is it or is it 30
coins now
it goes up what is that
oh i need to go there then
free
why was that me oh
i think it is
we can get money a lot of money
[Applause]
that's so nostalgic
i don't understand john you just have to
go around
because the coins will uh be in your
inventory later on oops
knocked me off easy
because you're so short oh sorry
all right i'm ready
wait why are coins going through you do
you only collect coins sometimes
yeah no i don't think so
i think that's the point maybe
this is the only time in my whole life
that i'll ever be on this treadmill
because i'm trying to there's
[Laughter]
i might think about it in the game
i don't think it's 3v
yes
oh i thought it was like if you get
coins you just oh
huh maybe we split them i thought i was
gone and that's pretty unfair i'm not
going to lie with me
i'll cherish them forever it's to the
left
yes laters oh no no wait how many he's
coming are you getting it no yeah
[Applause]
yes you want to start an hour or start
yes bring the star to me today
you know you want the monkey you gotta
press
you know
oh it's my oh sorry every time when you
uh triggered it then you gotta press it
pretty fly
oh yeah it is
oh
okay
oh that's way far where am i
yeah i didn't see you with me
am i not there anymore oh there you are
there i am wow
15 that's not that much
a little farther
[Music]
you can do it
get that second star
i will go and make your bird senpai
proud oh
an item
i don't have that many coins
can get something cheap maybe the double
dice
then you still have 20 coins for the for
the star if you write
i will get the double
give me that
let me be your financial consultant
looking pretty good for mma oh you what
wait we're at that patrol we'll chase
down speed runners for just five points
what does that mean speed runners
what did they do
look outside i don't know what that
means wait that means that they're gonna
chase down fonda mummy do they do you
want them to chase down fauna yeah and
then bring her to me
give it a try
excellent
but i don't have that much money i'm
kind of scared
but
you're still gonna land on on some
a field maybe that will give you money
as well
i don't even know what does this even do
i kind of wanted to i want to know what
it does so yeah
maybe people that run by um
there you go you never lose that much
let's go conquidong
um
did you just say conkey
yes did you say that
i did
let's use this
uh
uh oh so you only take monkey items wait
what is this
steal an item
oh
oh what do you have a mushroom or a
double dice
take your mushroom yay
give me your mushroom
what is mushroom i just found something
in the towel that cracked me up
here to share i'm not
thanks
racking up those bonus oh
what's going on
okay i'll buy that's treasure free ina
the most expensive thing please thank
you
[Music]
shopping yes yes
well wrote whatever you want um
[Music]
it's funny how everyone knows that one
can pick the color and then hopefully
you don't get messed up and uh
accident yeah it's just orangey gonna be
lucky
why do i gotta be the
last out of out of us for to push
let's pick the cali color
don't screw me now
he's pretty
and here comes the comedian
oh 50 50 chance yeah please no
oh yeah okay
oh good thing it's a practice round yeah
oh it keeps going into somebody else
well that makes sense otherwise there'll
only be one left
okay
okay ready oh romeo are you ready
[Music]
i guess the pressure builds like it
won't explode right off the bat
ah
got it
maybe oh yeah maybe each thingy has a
certain amount of pressure
oh
nice
bowser is happy with that
don't fail me now green
oh
i failed me
it failed
oh it goes again oh okay oh now it's
just three of us
nice bowser
oh
green
please
oh wow
no silence
[Music]
here we go
come on baby
in this case it must be yellow
i know it for sure
[Applause]
i guess it was
[Laughter]
the winner
oh i still got three coins okay
i am
oh four
hole tony needs to step up their game
roommate come on come on get serious now
you need another coin dump game like
that when we play the 1v3
yeah maybe maybe
maybe they take a bit of time
maybe it means only if you use like
double dices then you're considered a
speeder or something like that
well they come after me if i use it
hopefully not
cursed
oh
no that can be useful too if you like
one step oh no actually never mind you
don't need to land on it exactly
you huh win the lottery then yeah how
much money if i get to the store
oh
okay hey
what does this mean
oh you can use it on others i have
enough money yeah
you get all of it ah
give me it
nice are you gonna give me it
what you gonna do with that money dude
it comes out of his what
nothing
i can't
wait
i wasn't paying attention
oh
for science you should maybe use that
speed uh less room
no
okay
oh i'm gonna try this one right now
oh perfect
oh
oh awesome
sorry mommy
this is okay
this is fine
well
i'll just go normally
then well red looks good on me that's
why i did that
oh look away oh i like poco and goku
that one's fun
oh that's creepy
choose the direction to look by the time
the music stops team's eye look at the
right different direction oh
okay
hey what what
what
wait does it have to be synced up is
this like a look
move head do we have to hear the audio
for this
ah
i don't
you're not moving don't look the side
that kiara looks is pretty much what
we're trying to do oh do the opposite to
the up uh look a different direction
than solo side don't get tricked
[Music]
but i need to win against everyone all
three of you need to fail for me to win
or what
oh
i'm being tricked
this one's a little confusing
i am being tricked oh this time
all right
yoshi
i win against one of you at least once
all like all of you at least once okay
okay
oh i can look straight too oh okay what
oh okay so mummy if you stay looking
straight that means we have a chance to
win so if either of us go left to right
then we should be fine right like i go
left and then it goes center and then it
goes right on top of those strategies
what the hell
i just want i just won't move
oh you got you so scary
is that it i just don't move
well you don't want you want a mind game
kiara whatever dude
stick to your directions good as on the
right i'm on the left
i got it one down
i like how yo she looks at donkey kong
like you [\h__\h] up
i did
[Laughter]
i don't think this is going to work out
well she could get all of us can she
then we're all out
i don't know
oh
[Music]
would you maybe mind coming here with me
for a moment
give us the big money
[Music]
i will hurt you
please
are you are you a masochist
what's that
nah i could never show you the things no
no no no no no never never never
my good bird my cute little owl
[Music]
21 i might want to show you the usual
room though the usual room yes yes a
good place for verbs to learn what they
did wrong and how they do better
okay
browser
all right oh what items do i have
mushroom
sure
[Music]
dude
oh
[Music]
he's cool it's kirby bgm right now
apparently yeah
mommy i didn't recognize that
[Music]
i think i'll can i get that uh golden
pipe is he gone
is that freaking toad gone lunch break
yes
oh yes worth it
now everyone's gonna buy that is that
ever gonna be out of stock
all of us are passing that dude
sure chase them go go go go go this guy
didn't even help us in the last there's
like that stone guy that came did he do
anything
i guess he wouldn't push us all the way
to the start was that it
yeah i think so
[Music]
but that also changed
back to the
to that spot
i think that was it does good or nice
switch
everyone's coins are oh
this is good this is good
dude needs to
get less than 20 coins okay okay we have
this
will be given to daisy for landing on
the space thank you
okay that's not much though
now decide how many coins to wager waker
wager wager you actually get the
decision or is it a i guess
how do i nice ah
20. okay
that's pretty good all right
oh no
i think mumma needs coins
and then cash out to me
80 coins
to pew
oh no
bill
fire away
it won't count if it hits their cannon
what
okay
i seem to only be able to hit moomae i'm
so sorry
bye
when does this thing stop hold on
oh my god this is
difficult i cannot
oh
mamey
sent by respect
i don't know what i'm doing i shot alma
in the butt it's gone
oh that's not right
[Laughter]
okay let's do this
i think we understand let's do the real
thing
oh
oh sorry
that's it
oh no
[Music]
am i shooting it like inside
you have to hit the player yeah yeah not
the cannon
oh that's kind of
it's
[Music]
i don't care
oh
yeah but i got some good shots i'm proud
tiata is back
oh 16 and 56. holy crap
i no longer feel wow
we're still getting another minigame
because it's the end of the okay yes we
are wow nice
[Music]
jump rope i think i know that game
snowball summit
winter time
wait make a snowball oh you do that push
snowball what
what what
[Music]
wait is the goal to have the biggest
ball or to push the others off with the
ball push people okay push people oh it
is all right
launch it launch it
[Music]
kiara's in control
dang it why didn't you push it off
movement why did you push it off i just
want it
okay
you can push it
oh you can do that
how'd you do that
hello
[Music]
[Laughter]
come on don't let your junior destroy
you
it says dominance what's the big one oh
it's a big one oh god oh my god break
after a certain amount of time maybe oh
focus
[Music]
the gamer neurons they're activated now
we both get 10 coins
you gotta do what you gotta do
yes
name of the game
yeah
[Music]
are you gonna get the golden pipe
yeah
understandable have a nice day
i would have done that too
oh no
no
they're useless anyway
it's usually kind of useless yeah
the juicy use what
what juicy connie i thought you said the
juicy kind of useless doesn't say what
does that mean no i said
i said they're kind of useless
oh
i go
nice
if everyone gets that golden pipe where
i'll just set the same amount of stars
again
i'll take it
unless someone loses their pot because
someone steals it or something before
they can use it
oh yeah that's annoying
you need an item for this event yes
it doesn't matter oh
what
what not again
okay no one ever called me stuff control
ever again that was me i'm sorry i'm
never gonna call it again stupid it's so
stupid
we're never getting sure let's use it oh
unless yeah lunch time
wait do you get into this i'm gonna
start closing you guys
you directly go but maybe i'll send it
to you guys so this could be useful for
you
everybody wins you consider it huh
[Music]
i'm a superstar
okay
i get the star star
yeah give it here
pink shroom
thanks
look at that
it looks like the smile on those dog
treats
i know what you're talking about
donkey kong not the bacon strips you're
like you're like the cheeto man
oh cheetos
[Music]
that is pretty far
all right good thing we have some a
golden applause so we can keep it moving
yeah
see where do i want to go
wait does it tell you
how many moves do i have left
very lucky this is rigged
okay
this is mine
i would like to still kill us yes
indeed hello to that long time no see
give me that beautiful golden star star
thank you thank you thank you very much
what a peaceful harmony
harmonic game harmonious
that's the one
thank you thank you i'm listening wow
beautiful oh
whoa
[Music]
okay wasn't she up there before
definitely
okay get back go get her
go get her chase her we're like stalkers
grab star so that's talkers what
[Music]
what
oh we always know her location and we
always go after her
creepy we're simply starting something
oh perfect i don't even know which one i
want i don't really care
oh i kind of like that that's a good one
i didn't care much for the key anymore
oh that one that's good it is cute good
good good
hey okay
me liking me
girl i said see you later girl
around the ring i love that one that's
so nostalgic
oh this is how i move are you into this
wait
hold a oh hold
wow what an elegant ice skater donkey
kong is
[Music]
okay i was button mashing
how do i get it
so cute we need a penguin uh
if we get a penguin in whole life that
would also count as a whole torii i want
it that would be something oh cute
look at them
oh no relay flashbacks from the sports
festival come here mummy
hell yeah baby
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] keep wiggling me
goofs me up
yeah me too that that one yeah
i try to turn like in
as you would in perspective i guess but
it's like it doesn't it doesn't count as
nice
how do you push me
sorry
that's okay
well in a previous life i used to be a
professional ice skater so that's not a
surprise to me
oh i don't don't believe it anyway i'm
scared of ice feeding
yeah it is kind of scary yeah i get
scared of falling
i never ice skater before i'm going ouch
never yeah almond never i'm taking you
ice skating if we ever meet in rl
that's the plan is they haven't gone
either basketball yes is it not so
common where you are or is it just you
never had a job
i guess i've just never done it yet yeah
that's not what i meant to say
that's what i meant to say
i wanna go sledding
like really fast one time one time i
built a hill when sledding and i knocked
myself out because i landed on the
ground too hard because i got too much
air
oh
yeah
i want to do that um
okay
wait did you get that one with the pipe
or did you walk there on your own i
missed it
um i got it with the bible oh
okay bye bye
[Music]
we should set the thing off in the
middle i want to see what happens
oh yeah
sure okay
stupid sticker thing it pops up all the
time it's probably because i move around
my
thing
[Music]
yoshi i love
this thingy how
yes
[Music]
stars stonks rising
so that must be like why why am i
selling so much of these now what's
going on
i demand
maybe yeah should raise the price i
never thought about that it was done by
kiara
i want it they raised the price on other
ones don't they the gold one yeah
maybe that's the difficulty setting like
if it's high difficulty then the price
changes on the star
[Music]
perhaps that makes sense
hi the next star is
[Music]
the danger
oh
who has the most that's the least
actually
yeah
like if i'm gonna so she can't so she
can't
take a star from somebody
yes oh no yesterday
tell me what to do okay
i don't know
oh i like bossy mummy
[Music]
that sucks but she's so cute
no but cuteness is not everything
but that little yoshi butt how can you
say no it's so cute okay you gotta mash
it until it's really far back and then
mash
[Music]
now it's up to you when you want to
press b
did i press b yeah yeah
nice oh
triple
[Music]
um
what no i don't see anything anyone
leaving the room
what i did a random
a 50 for one star
steal money for free
oh
let me take a moment to read oh so
there's
it's so cute when he reads there's just
i love it i pulled the actual map out no
way he's he's already squatting too
like he's on the toilet
[Music]
i think it just gives you a star it
doesn't actually steal oh you can choose
i still left it up to rayon yeah no come
on
no
what the heck
can i stop this one
[Music]
um you will all have to feel my wrath
now you chose to still be randomized
yeah
it has to be randomized
no it doesn't hurt oh
wait does this one count one two three
[Music]
i'm officially taking star donation
stuff
please i want to give me something good
lucky
the cost of your next star is cut in
half oh
i love how excited he looks when he gets
something he's like
wow
[Music]
doko i won't have to go
he looks like a tourist at disneyland
and then uh there's no way i'm gonna
reach it
pirates of the caribbean
i mean is that really gonna help me in
that situation
um oh did you check where everybody look
i think it's randomized
with me
oh
you can't say that
oh no what
what
oh well
no that's okay that's okay nice
hi
that's some sad time don't make me pain
i'm sorry
everyone just takes everything from me
what am i left with nothing
oh wait what
i don't know
no he cares about that
bonus oh is this my ex
is this yeah
oh okay just a bonus i'm getting mario
party this is this is what was always
supposed to happen messy memory oh mummy
let's go
memories that's your nickname isn't it
oh no try to return let's get it right
to the original slot when you're done
shut ah
what oh god i was i wasn't i was reading
i can't pay attention all right i got
this
oh god i didn't see it all i was reading
you can just copy the person in front of
us yeah but how would you know that they
know what they're doing
they could oh it could be sabotage
wait what oh how'd you hide it ah when
you don't shut your curtains to stop
others from cheating yeah yeah yeah oh
no idea man
[Music]
how do you put something oh hey give
everyone a different screen
to
copy
from i don't remember the color order of
this yeah i don't remember i'm not
giving time either
go go remember
i was paying attention that time dang it
now to the real one
no idea
literally just forgot everything short
time memory why do you do this why do
you do this to me
[Music]
no i can't move my thingy that fast oh
no hey
[Music]
not oh
humans uh where used to be um monkeys
yes yes because monkey smite and big
brain monkey
sometimes banana banana
it's the final
[Music]
that's i mean that's a recent change
that we had i should have been higher
but okay it's rng's fault
it will still change oh wait
who will win let's hear the prediction
from one of what pretty good
i don't is so you know nothing
who is this i don't trust him
for sure well thank you for believing in
me but i think you're wrong
eh are you gonna help me at least come
on now daisy help me then if you think
i'll win
i've protested what are these overseas
minicoins
i want a star not coins
uh-huh
we're supposed to give you six
okay
[Music]
don't give up
sound
why are you so weird there's something
so comedic about this just nothing on
the map but the person reading
let's go butchen
right
what does this do
you can decide
oh she's thinking about it no
we don't like him
we don't want him
i think i'm going to land on the
exclamation point maybe
we want
so wait does this activate the
exclamation point
no now
the last time i felt like it went way
further every time well every time we
did do it it went further and we didn't
it did not
[Music]
mashed potatoes sounds so good right now
like oh my goodness
why did you bring the mashed potatoes so
i love mashed potato
instant mashed potatoes uh if you want
those are pretty
i good
to start
it's just the last round right uh five
more points
five more this is oh yeah one of the
five yeah
please oh or like uh you guys have the
what are they called croquettes
that sounds different
but i like to i like the japanese kuroke
much more than the ones
[Music]
um
did you go the right way or the wrong
way
me
oh it still works
[Music]
[Applause]
[Laughter]
give me
[Music]
i'm going to pursue my dream of
collecting stars
can it be close to me come on pity star
please open the bottle
where am i where am i i think i'm
already past that point
[Music]
oh man
what happens
that's what i liked about the one on the
wii i like the one we drove around with
the koopas
that map was nice which one is called
it was like monopoly almost it was nice
interesting spicy you have to buy hotels
and you get like a five star oh
yeah that was good
added more to map other than block
mushroom
that doesn't matter
oh no don't say that
hey roll don't be lucky let me at least
get lucky
oh
all right it's okay
as the one who
um put this collab together i'm okay
with losing
monty's revenge
this is funny
oh the mall
okay
but don't let a monk team whack your
head the player who stays out longest
when huh hey what i don't where am i oh
oh you pull this off my eyes
what oh i see oh we are the mouse only
the monty hall whack your head you're
the player who stays the longest um we
are the wacky ones
[Music]
bunk the ball camera
wow that's quite a different perspective
you are the the the mole
oh
monty's okay make sense now
am i doing okay
where am i
she knows how to evacuate
[Music]
gotta stay close closer to life
um
yeah yeah yeah
oh no
all right moment let's see what this
does i
um
are you going to use those three sizes
maybe
i can use it right but the fragrances
the maximum you're going to get is i get
30 and you're 37 away from the star hmm
there's something what but i don't know
what happens to me hmm
give it a try
what's gonna happen to me
ah
[Music]
wait what
is this what the check was saying rp
and me
is this what what did he say about the
coin being one
not always am i right
oh you guys are saying
all of my
[\h__\h] coins
how could you do this to me
now and to me i was already on rock
bottom and you pushed me underground my
man
well mario party once again proves that
it ends friendships uh sayonara everyone
return to a lonely wolf
one two three four five
let me see
[Music]
no i was screaming did you not hear him
he's screaming really
oh
cream i um i have never been on the
right side of the freaking board
never
never well
you saw three turns
[Music]
wait one two three four
what
is the perspective weird yeah
very strange i have not hit a single one
all right i don't understand i'm ready
time to destroy it
okay i think you have to stand under the
shadow so pay attention to the shadow
completely under the shadow that's i
thought
i am not sure
i'm not even doing it
[Applause]
okay nothing less expected from the
ground pounder of whole live
uh shortest round a world record speed
run for that one
i'm so salty
no
it's the bonus stars too though
so
rage quit coming soon
hello
content inviting my time
my turn uh 22 to the next store
let me
so where am i uh
to the next store
is anyone else closer to it
now i don't know where it is i'm like a
million miles away
oh i see
[Music]
okay i could walk a million miles
it's a thousand i think though
the dice
what
oh
[\h__\h] mommy
oh wow nice
it's wrong dang it
oh
you're you're two away from the star
apparently
oh wait
oh yeah i am
[Music]
if you push random i'm going to there's
one person in the lead
one person with a star in the lead yes
me may think i don't know
homemade way to come back
[Music]
i just wanted to taste muscle
four stars movements
unbelievable
[Laughter]
i wouldn't have the money to pay for one
of those hours it's pretty crazy that
that happened
i don't have money
wait i don't have money i don't have
money though oh that's okay uh-oh oh
wait wait a second
you could only move like one space
forward if you wanted to get more luck
like right a chance to get more coins
yeah
are you aware of the senpai tax that for
one senate you pay one star
are you aware of that
and i s do i still have to pay yes
i thought i paid a lot already no no no
no
you could pay it to me
it's never candy right
oh
i could give you one i would
sure i'm a man
the mechanics of this game don't allow
that uh-huh
as far as i'm aware
can i get on the
can i get past the car
oh no money
well
oh
that's at least interesting
i can move it away from whoever's close
to it at least sabotage a little bit
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
but don't give me
where is this hammer oh i see i think oh
ouch
oh you can't stop wrapping
up
[Music]
okay
so everybody wins in this one right
because we just got unless you fall off
the gym
can you push people got it
downtown
i
see you
[Music]
the bonus star for the mini game she's
going to get all this
wow
i'm trying to remember which ones
there's a lucky space and then an
unlucky space
i mean maybe it's different in this game
i don't know i think i've seen anybody
land on a red space
me true i landed definitely
twice at least
[Laughter]
oh
don't worry i'm leaving it up to chance
no actually no
no
i'm sorry today we just got to even out
there
don't
[Music]
don't be scared of those
spooky ghosts
let's try to do the boulevard
you should have brought your vacuum
cleaner that you built in ttrpg
[Music]
oh
i can't even bet that much money
i might even
hope it's not too much
yeah
28 yeah
chomps noise is this like red light
green light
it is kind of hidden so you don't get
noticed
[Music]
one more one leg release to hide okay oh
oh i win because i can't do anything
never mind
i don't understand i think when the
bubble pops you gotta stop
stopped early
you gotta think of them
i stopped really early
all right
yeah you can't wait until the bubble
pops you gotta you just have to stop
randomly yeah when you think you're
scared
don't want to risk it no more there you
go
nice oh
the ping is working wonders
oh that's so bad
[Laughter]
slowly but surely
oh everyone stopped quite early
i'm gonna play my party alone after this
against npcs
against easy npc nah oh no
[Music]
that's what i like to say everybody gets
their coins back or what now we fight to
the death
[Music]
that was always like
five minutes yeah
[Music]
i wanna marry your sheen
is yoshi a dinosaur
one
yes
he is right something like a dinosaur
oh please say yoshi well he is oh please
dragon he's hurt he's like a turtle
it's cute no yoshi they say it's you
listen he's a pokemon okay
how do i win this
all right turn this turn right you play
the 15th turn i think you play the 15th
yes yes
we do we do all right well
i'll swoop in for that pinky kong you
know
oh
because i don't think anybody's going to
pass the boo again
well there's there's bigger fish to go
after for that one then
give me
[Music]
we met
away she goes
come to me
okay i think it's close to you
no i think i already passed
yeah i didn't far away
uh
oh no no however i can
please if i move it can it please move
right next to me please please please
please please because yeah that's
bubbling
but i wouldn't be able to take it even
if it move would move there right i
wouldn't be able to take it
yeah
okay try it anyway
could i have been one before that
and
okay at least i can be less salty
i guess it's the same
about the same man
all right
does anybody have a warped
wow
a lucky doll
oh look at that oh yeah
do i want to i mean it's too late now
for all of this
unless next turn i get to the boohoo one
but i wouldn't have enough coins to
steal a star
just money
but i will land on the lucky one if i
don't okay well why not use up my items
okay
before it's over
go go go go go daisy
go daisy
yes
oh okay it looks like candy what's
flowers
uh
i feel
[Music]
[Laughter]
what is this so i try to hit the moving
target avoid getting hit okay
is there an npc among us
among us okay all right pull the arrow
so i'm trying to not hit the purple one
try avoid oh avoid get what oh
oh
i went into that
oh this isn't
well maybe it's not impossible all right
sure let's try it
because there's not much space to move
anyway
oh the purple ones are just a challenge
for you guys i guess so
boink
boing
boing and this one's
that one's not fair though because you
were sandwiched in between them pc
boards so you couldn't really move
watson
all around me are familiar
oh
and i find it kind of funny
i find it kind of sad
dreams in which i'm dying are the best i
ever had
[Music]
yes
[Applause]
oh you choose the wager mummy doesn't
have much to lose here
[Music]
yeah it's gonna be like a 1v1
drag the say suburb into hell do it
dummy ah
come on mummy you can do it
stickers
stick
oh i love this oh fun
that's not a good sign navigator
seriously can you fall off the edge and
make your way to the goal
no but you don't know where the goal is
right
now you gotta guess i gotta have a late
start
well just practice
it's always at a random place i guess
for this game
or is it
where is it specific oh nice
where could it be
[Music]
i don't know where it is
uh-oh what's in season i don't know
okay look gold is always problems
okay there's only one ah
yeah yeah oh go go go go go
oh goodness oh god
oh
so far it's the same movements
it's coming down to
leg
oh [\h__\h]
oh smile
oh they're mirroring each other
it's not always the smartest choice
to go the way that your senpai does
real cool high
the stakes still go the same way
oh now we got some changes
oh no
interesting
guys
i uh track of where you girls are oh i
think am is very close now no yeah i
don't think it's oh oh now we're in the
same spot again
now come on
it's a huge internet
[Music]
[Laughter]
photo finish
oh the ping
what does the cursed dice do
i can roll only a number between one and
three oh
but according to chat you can let
someone else rule that apparently but
i'm not sure it's it doesn't really
state it in the description but
apparently it does
use it on someone else
number
five nice slam it onto kiara have i not
suffered enough chat
oh nice
very last turn we got so many
a game of good sportsmanship it is
movement
get out of here
let us have a
timely
of course i was just here to play with
my friend it's serious guys oh nice
i love them
what goes both ways oh
maybe towards the end a little
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah it was a nice try i forgot the time
she didn't see you coming
my two coins
[Music]
oh i owe the money
how did they find me
oppa
do i have anything
no
bunch of nothing
uh okay
is this the final turn
this is the final countdown
yeah she got it
i see a huge imbalance on this uh
score with everyone uh-huh a huge
imbalance how did that happen
oh my goodness rng
or skill
maybe
where is the next one
goodbye
[Music]
oh yeah
okay
that's near
i don't know if that's near anybody it's
near
me
i'm not gonna be going there anymore
[Music]
please press a yeah
okay
[Music]
hey girl
yeah wait i can choose how many oh
you can get it
it says seven can you check your map
seven
away
oh am i at least getting wait wait ah
yeah am i at least getting one more star
really
are the gods being kind of
celebrated get it girl
just make sure you put right here
where's the seven
keep going
maybe i could even go for eight
so that may happen
why the hell not just max it out huh
oh i should have gotten 10 i guess
whatever doesn't matter
let's go
just saying one person has the most
coins at the moment
actually we all have a lot of questions
yeah you all got about like a close
amount
it's hard being number one
smack him you got those big hands how
come you can't smack him
guac plus it goes right through us
okay only eight
okay that's fine thank you yeah for that
little puppy
look at that store it's left isn't it
okay
it's right there
is it okay that i take it
yeah maybe i really wish
surprise is actually 50 coins no
final star
finally at the very end
nice thank you until that i appreciate
the pity start
[Laughter]
unless the last mini game gives us a lot
of coins
that's brilliant
that will decide it all
oh
if i would have gotten 10 i would have
landed on the bowser field
oh no no under
the next one nine would have been the
bowser field and 10 would have been the
red field i calculated that totally
noise paracel plummeting
bumper balls
again
oh [\h__\h]
wow
okay
all right
those look like balls from that one
movie what movie
uh
boy
tale
[Applause]
oh i'm on a tomatillo
mario party game with us like this is
like you i think it's maybe actually i
don't want to say that yeah
yeah yeah hey somebody recreated this
but with uh us
exactly
what happened oh god oh god don't hear
me
[Music]
no
uh
45 minutes approximately right i think
you're gonna get two hours
it's been two hours oh mario party
let me get away
i think you're rich
it's my smile
mini game
[Music]
oh
[Laughter]
are made out of salt yeah the winner bee
i'm a wonder
i'm not sure
think oh thank you [\h__\h] oh she's dead
hey come here
oh my gosh she has her
[Music]
oh yeah
to the story
wasn't this supposed to take 45 minutes
it's not like yeah yeah that's what i
was saying but it took us two hours
oh she's a second place a nice moment
ah
wow shut up
a for effort
a
foreign bad
enjoying it
wow
yeah
shut up toad
[\h__\h] you're the luckiest of all come on
kiara i'm not lucky obviously look at
the results
about the bonding
seven incredible
well um i was saying in the beginning
that we should play too but my saltiness
uh
made me not want to play no no just
kidding but also it took us much longer
than i would i thought it would
yeah yeah
yeah yeah if we would play another one
it would have to be a super short one oh
well just uh let's just play this again
some someday but uh yeah there's always
next time yeah but without without any
of us just let's just watch someone else
play it
again i want to play this again sometime
it's my first time of course i don't
want it going to be at the left it's a
good collab game too
especially with all all the mini games
that they have in this one there's so
many yeah
yeah sure fun yeah a good choice kiara
so thank you girls for joining in and
thank you to the chat for uh sweating
together with us and and also yeah thank
you um to all the girls in here for like
making this on this super uh
you know uh
tough day with the sports festival and
thank you for squeezing it in today
um yeah i hope y'all had some fun
[Music]
like i mean it's it's a game that makes
it very salty if you the last one but
uh
i think look at this i love mario party
i don't know do i like this one i think
i like this one more than the the other
um switch mario party i don't know it
just has a more familiar like minigame
yeah stuff so i think the newest
the switch the other switch mario party
i feel like it's just like a bit too
much
i don't know you get what i mean chat
i think this is this has more charm to
it because of the old game and the old
system and stuff
is this just the old games or is the no
i know what they were going to do is dlc
for the uh the other mario party
oh
as far as i know it's like nintendo 64
gamecube etc
maps that are all revamped and like real
new graphics i i saw this video that
compared to graphics and it looks much
much nicer
beautiful beautiful
thank you
[Music]
anything
important or so
uh
i did it for you
[Music]
all right chad i'll see you i haven't
had something really okay tell me tell
me what's up girl i said
i said i had fun ah
very important
i'm happy to hear that mommy our one and
only council i hope you felt uh i don't
know like you you belonged here i hope
so yeah my boob
i felt my place even though i was a bit
angry at you please that's a good thing
please don't please don't mean yeah um
please don't be intimidated by your
birth mom okay uh-huh
i'm sure there's some clips we could
play back that might uh contradict that
you ever had in your generation go eat
bails go
okay i'll go do that yeah do that
all right and i'll i'll read the super
chatters and stuff tomorrow after little
nightmares that's what we'll be playing
tomorrow okay thank you guys for
watching
[Music]
do
so
[Music]
do
you