[Music]
so
king king
[Music]
this is a 3dw
yay isn't this amazing
whoa whoa a hand oh my god hand reveal
i'm wearing gloves because of reasons
and don't worry today nothing will go
wrong
everything will go right and
my my manager is here just in case but
she won't be talking
she will actually you know i i i asked
her
if she wants to be here for you know
security reasons
um even though i know nothing will go
wrong
so it's not really necessary but the
good thing that comes with that is she
can help me
she can um take uh
my chocolate to the microwave because
it's downstairs
so that i don't have to move it would be
dangerous for me to move right now right
so it's very good very good no no no
flags no flags
there will be an announcement um
somewhere in between
not at the very end because we gotta
freeze our chocolate and at some point i
know what i'm making
and we gotta freeze it at some point and
and then while we're waiting for the
chocolate to be frozen
hopefully that doesn't take too long
that's when i will be making my
announcement
obviously the announcement is my 3dw
which uh
yeah hello i am debuting as 3d now
this was unexpected what why
um i have i i
have really fancy gloves don't you agree
you're pretty close
i bought a lot of new stuff for uh this
because i've never made this before
now let me tell you um i understand many
of my viewers were very confused
uh as to like
how am i making chocolate and why am i
making chocolate uh
i'm not making chocolate from scratch we
will be using
lynch chocolate i bought some other
chocolate too but i i had to go for
for the european chocolate you know it's
the bestest
um so uh in japan
on valentine's day it's not how it is
overseas it's not like
um you know uh
you guys are going crazy over a freaking
hand oh my god this is
it's making me very nervous too actually
this is super special my heart is going
doki doki doki doki toki
what i was saying is let me bonk you
with this
box just kidding okay this is too
exciting um
i was saying that um
yeah the valentine's day i mean in most
countries it's probably
like um you know
um the the guys
giving their girlfriends or their
fiances or whatever
flowers and chocolate right and the
chocolate is all usually i mean i've
never seen anything else
store bought and which is i mean that's
also nice i like receiving flowers i
like receiving uh chocolate
hasn't happened much in my life but
still it's nice to you know receive
chocolate from your mom
and flowers from your best friend yeah
yeah
yeah that's the valentine's day
experience that you want to have yep
um chicken wing fingers what
but in japan it's a little bit different
in japan
and the girls uh make chocolate
by melting chocolate and then making
like pralines or something out of it and
decorating it and
it's not that hard but you know it's
about you know
handmade making something by hand makes
it so much more
personal and some some make cookies some
maple leans
some make brownies even but most girls
make pralines
and um i'll be making something like
that too really something easy because i
never made it before
so and then they give it usually to
their crushes or to
or to friends there's also tomochoko if
you don't have a if you don't have a
crush
then you give it to your friend oopsie
um
so we all know who i'm making chocolate
for
also i i will it's probably going to be
a lot so not only cali will receive my
chocolate but also i'll be giving some
to
manchester so she can test it and you
know
maybe she will die from it well that's
uh that's going to be sad
i don't want that to happen um
she'll be testing it if it's poisonous
or not
she will not be talking but she can nod
at me and tell me if she's still alive
and she tests my chocolate
but it will be fine how can swiss lint
chocolate be
uh poisonous you know i would have to
mix in some crazy stuff
with that said i have some other
ingredients um
so i was thinking maybe i'll put oh i'll
mix in some blueberry
a dried this is dried blueberries maybe
i can
cut them small and then we can add them
in there and i also have uh
here this is a show it into the camera
like a real youtuber
nama kurumi this is a walnuts walnut i'm
not a huge walnut fan
but i'll um i'll cut them small and then
we'll put those in
some good nuts and i also got some
some almonds sliced almonds i'll be
cutting those smaller too
and we'll put those in there too i love
almonds
and this is uh also fun this is
a biscuit chip uh caramel
um i think it's gonna be a bit crunchy
here an asmr let's go nuts
so this is uh our ingredients we got we
got lots of nuts we got some
some healthy dried fruit we got
obviously the
the best chocolate uh one of the best
chocolates that exists on earth
lint chocolate and oh yeah we
would forget the most important part
corn flakes
yes i'm making a very easy type of a
crunchy chocolate
it will be yummy believe me um and this
chocolate
uh without making uh thankfully it
doesn't need any
baking and we're just um
going to be uh melting the chocolate so
should we get started guys this is so
exciting oh my gosh
it's almost as though it was a 3d ww
[Music]
okay let's freaking go i'll show you how
how much of a cook i am
actually uh my i think my hat is very uh
fitting isn't it
um my cooking hat is very fitting today
finally
finally it makes sense does that reflect
no
i mean it does but no you can't see my
can't see my beautiful face
unfortunately unfortunately
throw my trash on my bed
[Laughter]
sexy hats well hell yeah oh yeah look at
my sexy hands everything about me is
sexy obviously
i i was actually before the stream i i
realized
uh i said to a manager son wait
don't you think there's like people who
have a glove fetish aren't we just
helping them at this point
oh no
i hope you guys don't have a glove
fetish
this paper really uh scares me it's
reflecting so much oh my god
it's like emitting so much light
open up the chocolate yummy yummy yeah
smells good this is a perfect
quality milk chocolate oh yeah it's kind
of weird to touch it with gloves but
it's a hand model do you guys think i
could
have a career as a hat model
okay manager son please get me some hand
modeling jobs
please give me hand modeling glove
modeling glove modeling uh
jobs oh hell yeah i mean it's winter
right now don't you guys want to sell
your gloves
okay there we go we got the chocolate
guys we got the chocolate
oh step one open the chocolate
we're going good oh my oh my god it's
gonna be fun to clean up my desk
afterwards
okay see knife and
i will now cut the chocolate and i will
put them
into the bowl hello bold this is a bowl
ah i'm not much of a cook guys you know
usually you guys cook for me
so that's that oh but i think i can make
some chocolate that shouldn't be too
hard the chocolate is quite hard
[Music]
why am i doing it like this actually
just
you know do it like you guys there we go
i'm i'm doing it so that you guys can
see it well
uh i'm just gonna break it with my hands
yeah
who needs a knife when you got hands
sexy hands you know
sexy glove pads oh yeah ugh ew my gloves
are getting all chocolatey maybe that
wasn't too smart
oh well we're rolling with it now we're
rolling with it
oh yeah chocolate gloves
do i have a second pair of gloves
probably not
this is 200 gram chocolate
i'm gonna apparently according to the
recipe there's gonna be a lot of
pralines coming out of that like 40 or
something
probably oh god no my hands
okay you don't see it because it's black
ah do you see that super chocolatey
yay should i lick my gloves you know
need latix gloves now you mean rubber
gloves nah
i wanted to go for these fancy elegant
gloves
i don't want rubber gloves feel
we're going with this okay number two
oh yeah break me you guys uh are you
excited
are you excited for the announcement i
think a lot of people are just here
because they want me
uh to have an accident on camera but you
should be here for the announcement
all right
oh yeah what do you guys think of this
what do you think the announcement is
huh
obviously it can't be my 3d debut
because i i have it right now that's
what i'm doing right now
[Music]
oh my god the chat is going so crazy
fast today
holy crap you guys need to chill
meena doki doki star now
i see some good answers in there
oh i see i said let's see where you're
coming from hey we're done with the
chocolate
okay who wants to eat the rest
i'm gonna put that in there
okay
[Music]
the chocolate is ready to be microwaved
bye bye see you later so next step my
dear friends manager is going
downstairs to microwave my chocolate
good to have an assistant next step
we're gonna take this uh
a ziploc bag and we're going to do the
following
we're going to throw in a [\h__\h] ton of
cornflakes
i wonder how much
[Music]
maybe all of it i don't know nah is that
enough
probably probably what do you guys think
i don't have anything to measure i don't
have a scale because i didn't want to
just buy a scale for one time and then
throw it away
hey i just stay there for god's sake
stay there okay let's go there
okay that's a that's a good chunk of
sexy cornflakes i should probably not
uh bonk it too hard uh but we're gonna
be bonking a lot now
wait uh actually we gotta put in
[Music]
i'll cut those and just add them in
later
okay oh i heard that i heard a microwave
teeth
okay corn flakes i have this
this thing here i'm gonna try my best
to i mean in the video they bunked it
but i'm scared that something will drop
that the camera will drop so
i'll try to just massage it nicely oh
that actually works
did you hear that oh yeah
oh yeah oh
my god that's that's how you know that
your
your um bones are uh
cracking nicely when you hear that sound
oh
oh yeah we got that asmr with the camera
that knife is kind of in the way
[Music]
i wonder how how small it should be
and the camera is wiggling a little bit
but don't worry until it's attached
very nicely
now let me move it a little bit
quite nice there's still some bigger
chunks in there
the usual sounds from the usual room
you think this is how it sounds in the
usual room oh no let me tell you it's
way more terrifying
[Music]
are you guys scared
i'm a bit nervous here oh my god i'm a
bit scared that's something good
this is such a thrilling stream oh my
god
especially the first time when you do
sell latest but if this goes well then
we might do it more often oh i have
received the chocolate
oh look at that melted
nicely
kanji nice okay
we'll get to that in a second
i think the crunchy
we have received the the right amount of
uh
crunchiness let's put that to the side
and then quickly
uh cut some almonds and some
walnuts where we have speech
we are speed okay how many do we want
not to not too many i don't know
how many
maybe i don't know
i don't want too many because we gotta
we have we're adding a lot of things in
here
it's i added uh i'm adding way more
things than the recipe wanted me to add
rta chocolate any percent
i actually i wanted to do this like
slower but
i don't know maybe it's me being so
nervous that's making me work
much faster this is supposed to be like
a long stream
okay okay no problem okay here we go oh
that's nice that feels nice to
to cut that oops and oh they're going
everywhere oh my god oh my god
okay oh yeah let me let me taste one
[Music]
yeah that's an almond pretty sure that's
an almond
oh cutting the big chunky
walnuts it's a bit difficult because
they're
so big thanks ah
did you eat it was it good i'm sorry for
everyone who has a nut allergy
well i'm sorry but you um you just can't
say no to me
you cannot say no cannot deny me
of the ah experience worth it
i would say
you see my my professional cooking
skills my professional cutting skills
this is
do i look like a cook yet i'm being very
careful
very careful
stress making you work faster yeah thank
you for the super chat i couldn't read
it and read all of it because it just
went by so quickly
thank you for the super chats thank you
the knot is killing me and not just
trying to
kill me from inside water water water
hydrate yourself guys you guys seem very
thirsty because of my sexy gloves
okay i have survived you cannot
get me down that easily you stupid nuts
i'm a phoenix
is such a nice asmr but you guys do you
guys hear the
the nut crunch no you probably only hear
it while i'm talking because other ones
won't activate the microphone that is
such a nice sound do you hear it
when i'm talking here
you hear it nope yes
you can listen more closely
okay the chocolate doesn't like
just uh uh
uh what's it what's the opposite of
melting
probably fine it's a good chocolate soup
right now um why first guys we'll just
put it into the
we'll just put it into the uh
microwave again oh
very uneven sizes here
we gotta be more concentrated but we
have a lot of time we have a lot of time
i'm very nervous about the announcement
actually
did you guys watch the collab that we
just did on inna's channel that was fun
too
did you watch it heart solidified mel
okay that's it that's the word that i
was looking for thank you reveal
but not quite close enough
you know i wish that for this for this
stream particular
i wish that and i had gloves
like you know in my in my
design so that i could you know wear
appropriate gloves
that would be funny
i think the only whole live english
member who has gloves is
you know right that's it doesn't she
have like
like half gloves yeah she has gloves
maybe she could do a cooking stream like
that and wear her own gloves
that would just make so much sense
okay i think now there's still some big
walnut
chunks in there i want to get rid of
those
okay i'm so nervous that it's kind of
making me feel sick
what if i throw up all over my nuts
oh my god i'm feeling also pretty hot
damn
yes well you guys are absolutely insane
my why are you hoping that i would [\h__\h]
oh you guys are insane
you need to check up on your hobbies
guys
professionals can probably do this much
faster than me
my hand is exhausted my arm is exhausted
i got like zero muscles apparently in my
arms
there's some big almonds over there
but here making or making it all by
myself i could have already bought
crushed
nuts when i'm doing it myself because
you know self-made handmade
is best
do you want to buy the chocolates that
i'm making guys would you would you
would you would you pay for them
would you buy them if i if i would sell
them
yes you're gonna be expensive though
it's gonna be quite expensive let me
tell you that
kiana made pralines don't come that
cheap
by the way uh
uh do you guys notice something about
on which hand i'm holding the knife
the dad actually does anyone actually
realize that
oh the chat is way too fast yet yeah
there you go
well i guess it's kind of now kiana
[Applause]
announcement i would like to announce
that i am left-handed
that's why i am a creative type of
person
da vinci you know kiana da vinci
jimmy
is it
[Music]
it
sorry i wanted to read someone in the
chat but the comment
actually after reading it it seemed like
a very lewd comment so i'll take it back
[Laughter]
the lootest artist in town
okay i think this is now what do you
guys say are you guys
some professional cooks would you say
that this is
the right size i think it's quite nice
i'm going through one more time
what are you saying this is too big i
still see some big chunks
damn it it just won't get smaller
does it look good
i mean having some bigger chunks might
be good because like they they crunch
more
that's gucci that's gucci
okay my hands are exhausted anyway so
we'll just go with that
and we'll also add in these biscuits and
yeah
chocolate the chocolate is being nice
okay okay
it's so hot too
yummy okay so we're going to put in
the corn flakes first
one second done
is this for cali yeah
yes yes who else would it be for
oh oh oh yeah
oh that's a lot that's a lot
maybe that's too much i'll leave some
inside
and also
yeah i definitely have to vacuum clean
this whole area later okay
throw in those nuts hell yeah
that's a lot of nuts maybe we need more
chocolate i still have more chocolate
but it's just not from uh
lint worst case we can mix it if it's
not enough chocolate
oh this is this is
this is making me so nervous and um
exhausted oh my god let's mix it
okay all of this has to be covered in
chocolate
let's see if we can make that happen
um oh yeah oh yeah it might be enough
chocolate we just gotta mix it a long
time
would you guys would you guys help me
before mixing
come on help me mix mix mix mix
mix mix mix mix mix mix
oh that's actually yeah it looks looks
uh pretty
good covering it up nicely but it has to
be fully covered
mix mix needs more chocolate
you sure no
would like maybe like having like one
bar of dark chocolate could have been
nice
mix mix mix
thanks guys for the help
oh
oh it smells so much like lint mixed
milk chocolate
smells good one second let me do it on
my on my lap for a minute
it's easier oh [\h__\h]
because i'm trying to reach out very far
with my arm so that you guys can see it
on camera but that's a bit
exhausting
a date for valentine's day by the way
i know
do you have a date guys or like a crush
that you want to
say i love you too
anyone you want to propose to
or do a kokuhaku
no no what what about me
you can just say i love you to me
say i love you i'll say i love you back
that's that's a special experience
oh it's it's really nicely covered now
but i still want to add the the
blueberry
yeah okay one second
that's that let me get
a few blueberries
there we go here we have some
blueberries we got to get some vitamins
in here
oh there we you guys like blueberries
i wanted to put in dried strawberries
but they didn't have any so i'm doing
blueberries they only had like
dried a lot of dried nuts and they had a
lot of
dried pineapple and dried mango
but no tried strawberries
okay how many more
blueberries topped here blueberry i love
blueberries that looks nutty
don't worry i'm getting into i'm adding
some fruit so it won't be fully
nuts it's corn flakes almonds
walnuts and blueberries isn't that a
nice combination okay here we go let's
cut it actually i want to taste
i never ate a dried blueberry before let
me
hmm oh that's pretty good
yummy i usually i never eat any
dried fruits i prefer them to be like
fresh whilst they stick to the knife
damn it
oh yummy wow
definitely tastes different than when
you eat them fresh
they all stick damn it
notice me kiara i have noticed you
toronto what
why would i taste better than a
tarantula
yeah i i i cannot okay i cannot actually
confirm that because i don't speak from
my own con
experience i have never eaten a
tarantula
but i would assume that this tastes
better
i wonder if uh hata ma senpai is gonna
do a
chocolate making stream as well
i can only imagine her doing chocolate
coated
tarantula legs and i i don't know if um
anyone wants to eat that
i can i can see it happening oh my god
i'm gonna call it now
that's exactly what she'll be doing
either like
a tarantulas or scorpion bodies covered
in
chocolate and then she'll be like please
accept my love
i i would uh say um yeah but
you might you can you can eat the
chocolate yourself i have a chocolate
allergy
sorry about that well if i say that she
might just offer me a whole tarantula
oh damn it's probably also not the way
to go
is that small enough i can't really tell
that one is big one by one eliminating
the big ones
oh my god the chat is way too fast what
the hell
holy [\h__\h] you guys are insane what's
going on
mama is making chocolate for kelly
yes sister sisters
your popular girl only because i'm
making chocolate and everyone wants to
see me uh
fail okay i'll throw those in
it's not manny but you know we don't
want to overdo it uh oh
okay okay okay beautiful
such a mess this table is such a mess
now
okay mixing again we got some
blueberries in there now nice oh
this is gonna be great especially
since it's made with lynch chocolate so
i might want to eat them myself too
marshall i'm gonna mix it nicely
eh mix mix will it be edible of course
it will
oh my god
mix mix i also need like some kind of
you know chiata cooking song
you guys are uh welcome to make a kiara
cooking song
kiana cooking song contest starting
today
ending in uh one hour let's go let's
freaking go
the prize will be
a praline i will send it to you
just kidding i will not i will never
because
uh probably not
it's probably gonna melt and uh
not gonna taste really good until it
arrives i'm sorry guys
you have to imagine it imagine but
you could make it yourself you could you
could actually just
buy lint chocolate at the store and buy
nuts and and all that
and then just you know what is that big
chunk in there
but make the same chocolate as me and
then just
act as if i made it for you obviously
that's not never going to be true but
i'll i'll eat it anyways how i'm not i'm
not yeah imagination use your
imagination guys
this is a chunk it's so huge what the
hell
is that chunk
i need to destroy the chunk
oh that's a huge walnut where did that
one come from it's just a huge
huge and chocolate covered walnut oh my
god wait i'm i'm cutting something on
the side
sorry my body is like making rick poses
because it's uh
it's just you know my body is just
feeling a bit weird today okay you're
back in there go
get back in there grab it
okay
so i hope there's no more huge chunks in
there
i guess we are ready for the next step
so much chocolate okay next step
next step oh wait i forgot the caramel
biscuits
i forgot the caramel biscuits
[Music]
caramel biscuits i think they're appears
like
oh wow that's a strong caramel uh
[Music]
smell i can't speak english anymore and
only for
i think a few months it's very strong
my gloves are a mess
do you guys like caramel
there's too much stuff in that no
next time next time
okay am i mixing it well enough
oh god okay okay
okay okay okay
mix
okay that's good enough oh my god what a
mess help me
now okay so
next stop let's go
i am going to
uh put
some cooking uh uh baking pap
paper are you a chef yes look at my hat
obviously
[Music]
manager's emotions i don't know she
looks uh
excited about eating this chocolate leaf
manager son can you please open that
tape because i can't
excel why are you doubting she's she's
super excited to eat this
it can't be that disgusting it will be
very good
[Music]
i got a scissors
okay okay nice
my table is huge but even like satsugani
when i'm cooking on this table then i'm
lacking a little bit of space
okay okay we got that nice people
and next step this one look at this
isn't this cute there's so many spoons
they're spooning each other it's like
spoon
infinity spoon inception spoon
separation
i will use the biggest one i think
yeah actually
let me take a look i got these uh for
later we're gonna package them
uh i got these little uh cup copies
and how to open them
these little cup stores should be a size
that fits in well there's only like
a million in there
oh muzuki
oh my god
oopsie this is very difficult with
gloves let me tell you that
[Music]
oh
okay so uh then actually that might be
way too big that's too big so maybe we
go for
[Music]
yeah maybe that one and the 10 i don't
know what the 10 cents for 10 grand or
who knows uh nodding
okay and we take let me take a spoon
of this mixture
made by the best cooks on earth kiana
wait no we don't put this right in there
we do that later we put it on the paper
first
i just wait i forgot to put the oil or
whatever i guess it doesn't matter
probably don't need the oil i was going
to put some oil
on the spoon first because the recipe
said so but
it probably doesn't matter okay just
stay there okay and now we just do this
it should be that easy yeah
it's that easy it even stays intact it
doesn't even move
it's like a little bowl shape oh yeah
you need the oil why i'm not baking it
guys
i don't need the oil looks fine it's
gonna be sticky but i'm not baking i'm
just freezing it this is no bake
no bake brilliance no need for that
no no i don't need the oil it worked it
worked
super well let me get more we're gonna
make a lot of these
i'm gonna have a lot
i don't like the way that fills up here
it needs to
be more
[Music]
okay
there
why did the first one go so well wait
you should just stay in there just chill
chill my friend okay
oh oh yeah probably fine
probably fine that looks delicious
i'm glad you say that thank you
it it just works tm
okay that one has a lot of nice
blueberries in hmm
[Music]
next doll
it doesn't come out oh there we go maybe
i should have put the oil in there
stay the way you are oh that one doesn't
look so pretty
[Laughter]
no need for oil you gotta put the oil
wait you think that's gonna help nah
i don't need the oil put the one why
would i do that no
unnecessary also i don't know how long
is oil even good once you open
the bottle once because it's probably
gonna
it's probably good for a long time right
but
um when did i actually it's not that
long ago that i bought that one
how long do you guys say
i put the oil no
a long time six months only six months i
would have fought longer
but don't worry this one is uh still
fine
it's more than six so definitely
oh no this is horrible
hold on manage yourself brought me some
oil in the bowl
uh butter chaton also wants me to use
oil i don't know why you all insist on
me using oil
okay i'll dip it into the oil pool
mmm oil yummy yummy dripping that oil
[Music]
well let's see if that goes better
[Laughter]
sasuka okay
okay we're using by the way we're using
sunflower oil
because i i i'm like a sunflower
wouldn't you agree
i'm a cute little sunflower sunflower
maybe i should have started from the
right side because i'm left-handed
oopsie
i can turn it around though
you guys don't see it well but that one
looks very sad uh
probably didn't put enough stuff in
there oh well it's okay
i hope they don't taste too oily though
okay i'm going from that side now oh no
it's falling apart yup
okay whatever you're just a failure i
hope you're happy with being a failure
it's a depressed depressed berlin yeah
this is taking a long time i think we'll
only do like one
one plate and uh then the rest i'll just
do off stream
because this is making me very very
nervous i'll just
you know oh oh my god i dropped what did
i drop the spoon
i will i will make one plate
we'll put it into the freezer can you
get my announcement
and um uh
i'm focusing focusing to make the
perfect brilliant look at that battling
i have the the autofocus off so yeah
that's how it looks
unfortunately okay
let's go perfect praline come on
looks like crap
okay it looks like crab
damn it it's the thought that counts
it's not only the thought but also the
taste is the the the the looks of it
it's not important it's not important
how it looks like
right yeah you guys will eat this anyway
right
go another one
i mean this is my first time ever making
pralines like this so you're gonna give
me a break
that one looks okay why did why was the
first one so perfect
and everything after that it's just a
red rover
share i kind of i guess that reminds me
of that a little bit
but isn't that isn't that the one with
the coconut
it's not like uh the white perliers with
coconuts
i don't like that one that much i like
jojo do you guys know jyota
you know no manager son doesn't know
jyoto oh my god
what johto is so good
some people in
[Music]
look it up it's so yummy i think the
company behind it is also very
very very very very very well
i think is that how you say it you see
that ferrero
very hard to say that
it's so yummy it's so addictive it's
like a little uh
it's a round round pralines with like
nuts covered in some nuts some specific
nuts and an inside
some like nutty cream
uh anyway let's stop that
i just really would recommend jotto to
you guys
oh god this is all please come on get
your [\h__\h] together
oh that's all right
they were never supposed to have a round
shape anyway no
now it was never supposed to be like
that
i've got some more oil here
not too much
get rid of it again use spoon carrot to
make it what
do you think i should refine it with a
spoon
but maybe we'll see well we'll first
place it all there and then we'll try to
but i'm just scared to break it even
more you know
because i feel like they're very um
fragile
my my pralines are just like my heart
they like to listen to panic at the
disco you know my pralines
you know now that my manager is here i i
wonder what she thinks about every time
when i sing something
mega design is giving me advice for
words uh for your word document writing
it down telling me to compact it more
i mean you mean to like crash it more
into the into the spoon
now who do i see let me try
what that
praise the manager i mean
that's for me you spot allah
wow
like that
i think many jason seems happy
but now it's feeling so comfy in the
spoon it doesn't want to come out
come on come on
it's the birth of a new praline there's
a boy or a girl
awesome i want to say it's beautiful but
it's decent i want to see it from the
other side
does it look good from that it's rounder
than the other ones i've made
here yeah
thank you megazon manager son is not
only here to prevent me from
accidents also here to help me with my
cooking
if you can call this cooking
okay okay i'm gonna follow the advice
you guys don't see it right now but i'm
i'm gonna uh fill up the spoon
nicely and then
you know crunch crunch
ouch that hurt
making these weird body movements don't
mind me
okay okay looking good
okay push
add the chocolate pat it softly
and gently oops and then drop some
chocolate always of course
okay are you guys ready one more come on
dunk that chocolate ew
come on come on don't be shy
yeah that's okay
[Laughter]
why not why not no that one is a little
bit smaller again for some reason why
okay let's make four more
four more i got a nice
big fat spoon filled up with uh this
mixture
yeah that's a lot hmm that's a big one
a lot of blueberries in there as well as
for the blueberry lovers out there
i got a spoon for the blueberry lovers
i hope callie likes okay i didn't ask
her if she likes blueberries but she
pretty much likes everything
i was quite surprised she not everything
i guess
not everything but she was able to eat
like almost anything that they served us
in the
come out come on oh that's that's gonna
be a nice one
[Music]
got some spikes there just gonna
um push that down that's an
okay looking one i don't know about this
one though that one is really bad
from my angle from your from your angle
everyone
it looks a bit better i'm sure she will
love it
you think so jack payne salmon milk yeah
yeah salmon milk now it wasn't sound it
wasn't salmon
i don't know which which fish's milk
that was supposed to be but
it was a fish milk yeah that they wanted
to offer
us whatever that means
nope still bad what i mean
okay okay oh that that one is filled
nicely
maybe maybe it should have been like
maybe the nuts should have been all a
bit smaller
maybe that's what's like not really
helping
okay chill chat no no no no no stop
talking about the milk
stop stop
oh that looks very sad
it's okay it's okay you're fine you're
beautiful everyone is beautiful
actually i think this will actually be
yummy don't worry it'll be yummy
oh my yummy
[Music]
don't start it then
it's not my fault i'm just going on some
tangents where did that come from anyway
from uh if
rather or not callie can eat blueberries
so i was just you know i was just trying
to tell you guys that cali can't eat a
lot of things
and i was i wasn't even talking about uh
she couldn't
eat that one i was surprised now that
she was able to eat uh natto
did you guys know what natto is before
we talked about it yesterday
because uh it's like
very a very controversial food
yeah i mean i have to say i didn't try
it but i know that i won't like it
i i say that about a lot of things
there's a lot of foods that i have never
tried and they say i don't like them
because i just know i wouldn't like them
i know that's harry
i'm gonna a lot of you are gonna be mad
and be like you should always try them
though
who knows maybe you'll like them nah i
know myself
i know but it looks and by the smell of
it that i will not like it
i just know my body very well
same dough really is is there anyone who
can relate to that
being a very picky eater who just
refuses to eat certain foods just
because of the looks
kelly just has no fear um she does give
a lot of things a try that she has never
tried before which i guess i guess i
should
i should learn from her but i did i did
give sashimi a try
and i didn't die from it but one thing
though um
that i ate before but that she refused
like she didn't even want to try it was
um
raw raw horse meat
i tried that before i didn't
like it very much but it is kind of like
a
in japan they uh it's like a very
expensive type of
i i i can you can you call it delicacy
generally i just
didn't really want to eat a horse but um
yeah
uh that was that what's it called again
in japan
the bar is for horse and
sashi is i guess like the sachi from
sashimi
what does that mean though
yeah if you guys are ever in japan maybe
you can try it but i just don't really
like raw stuff in general like raw
raw fish or raw meat
like if i get a steak or something you
guys are gonna be
shocked by it by how how cooked
i want my meat to be you guys would be
shocked i think a lot of you
want your steak to be really really rare
but that's just not my thing you know
i want the meat to be meat not just
some bleeding red
i don't know something oh god does that
look okay
last one guys yeah well done
yeah it worst case like sometimes when i
go
um i i went with some friends to a steak
restaurant before
in australia and uh they really like
steak very
rare but they all went for like rare
stuff
and and i didn't want to you know it was
kind of embarrassing
like just like how it feels embarrassing
to me to be the only one in the room who
doesn't order alcohol
um so i went for medium
but deep in my heart i wanted it
to be well done
so yeah i just did it for for my
audience
my friends i didn't want them to think
like oh my god you
because chris what's with these people
who wants their steak to be like super
red and then when someone orders a weld
on steak they're like
ew how could you do that to your meat
eww way too dramatic come on
don't be so strict gosh
we are we're done with that i think that
can go to the freezer
[Music]
okay
let me try to clean myself up a little
bit of
tissues okay
okay we are actually you know what i'm
gonna turn um off the camera for a
little bit because
you know what time it is guys do you
guys know that the chocolate will come
back and we'll package it
it will we will package package it
package it we will um
you know put it in in those little cups
and then we will put it in like a nice
box and all that
so it will come back the camera will
come back but for now please excuse me
while i turn off the camera
for a little bit because it is
and let me take out my disgusting gloves
for a moment
it is announcement time
announcement time it has been done i
know it's been done
exciting so exciting so
today is not valentine's day but
i'm i'm making valentine's day chocolate
uh pretty early now
why why why could that be why am i
making
early valentine's chocolate
[Music]
why why have i been saying that i have
prepared something for valentine's day
i've said that like two times or so let
me drink some water
before before we think about it
[Music]
leaving soon well that's too but that's
not the announcement i think that
i've been saying that for a while now um
well well well well
well well wow
where to start where should i start
[Music]
maybe there is no start maybe there's
just the ending maybe it's just one
sentence
deep okay take some deep breaths with me
guys
breathe in
breathe out
thank you for the membership i've got
the super chats guys thank you thank you
thank you
let's go
[Music]
um
on february 14th
february
[Music]
in one week from now oh wow
and do you
do you guys want to listen to it do you
guys want to listen
once again just as a as with hirotoni
of course i've prepared a little preview
for you guys
of course i if you want
if you want if you really want i can i
can let you
listen to it a little bit
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
okay let me tell you one thing this song
is very different from hirotori it is
also made by the same person
and i've i've worked together uh with
gojo-san very closely this time
and with the lyricist and everyone to
get
um a very specific type of song and i
told them exactly
what um i want the lyrics to be about
and what
what instruments i want to be played
now i think you will probably hear it in
this little preview
what what's what specific instrument is
playing a big role in it
let's go three two
[Music]
one
um
[Music]
me
yay
[Applause]
did you like it guys did you like it
it's a very yeah i don't play the
it is it's mostly this song has much
less
english in it than he
[Music]
but but i will give you guys a
translation of it when it comes out
it is coming out in exactly one week
from now
uh with with a with um
a music video that
is also going to be very special and i
asked someone very
very talented to make the music video
it's going to be amazing i don't want to
i think i'm not going to spoil it who's
making the
music video but uh let me show you
as you saw here uh i think you can
recognize the art
the promotional art and the video art is
both
by mama looney mama
she's making the video art and the
the cover art this is the cover art but
actually the actual cover let me show
you
the actual cover uh one second
this is just a promotional art to be
honest
this is so huge
wait transform
actually it's so cute it's me in the
maid uniform
it's a maid outfit
look correct
and uh the logo the the heart challenger
logo
is uh once again made by spirit snare
who also
helped uh me with the hinotori logo i
commissioned
him once again and yeah i
for this one and i am very much focusing
on the story the whole song the whole
lyrics the whole video will be a whole
story like from beginning to the end
it will follow a storyline so the art as
well is that there's a lot
there's so many different uh art pieces
uh in this
song in this video so that's super
exciting because i
uh it's like um for for every little uh
line there's another piece of ice so
it's a lot of work that mabaloni
uh was putting into that that's why she
wasn't uploading so much
as per you as as she usually does
recently
the lyrics no i didn't write them uh but
i
like i wrote a whole story and i sent it
to the
to my maloney and to the lyricist and to
the composer gojo-san
and i told them this is what i want the
story to be i told them exactly what's
happening
yeah it's like a whole situation
so yeah um very very specific stuff
um do you guys want to listen to the
preview again
i want to listen to it again guys i'm
going to vibe together with you guys
because i feel like the
the first time you you listen to it you
you don't quite get the gist of it yet
you got to listen to it one more time
so uh let's just listen to it again
it's the chorus by the way that is only
the chorus
but did you hear the trumpets guys
did you hear the trumpets that's why i
yesterday i posted trumpets but also i
think like one month ago or so i also
posted trumpets because that was when i
think the time when i first
heard the rough version of the song
maybe
i think that's when i first posted the
trumpets and everyone was like why is
she posting trumpets
actually yeah the trump is actually also
something that i requested i told um
i i in this song i was way more involved
than in hinotoni and i told gojo-san
that i want trumpets in the song and i
want i wanted to be a song like this
so yeah one more time
[Music]
one more time
um
[Music]
oh
did you hear that at the very end like
when it was fading out there was a
pom-pom
i put in some some you know some pom-pom
wow yeah
and some like cheering voices and stuff
yay did you hear the trumpets aren't
they amazing
this song is so puffy and and poppy and
cute
and colorful and happy and it's a it's a
it's a song about valentine's day and
like um um
you know telling telling someone
that you like them it's actually it's
actually a song about
confession
yeah if you will if you guys listen to
the full version soon
then i think you will um yeah really get
the theme and and feel it and understand
yeah isn't it cute i was really hoping
for it to be uh
much much different from hinator i love
hinotoni and it's very cool very dope
but i really wanted to have a
i wanted her challenger to have a really
different feeling
what a cute song huh it's definitely not
about cali no
no no actually
[Music]
i will say more about that when when we
will release the full song
uh it would be so can you it would be so
exciting can you imagine
if i would ever like um perform this on
stage it will be so like energetic and
everyone will be like so hyped up if i
if i would perform this
like with a choreography and then dance
along
like a really cute happy energetic
choreography
the video i'm gonna still keep secret
who's making the video
oh but trust me it's going to be amazing
i got like a i got like a i got like a
little tiny
a preview uh yes
yesterday yeah yesterday um
and i got so excited it was just 10
seconds but it
already looked so amazing yeah
no it's not cali it's not kelly kelly is
not making the video no no no
she doesn't have time for that kelly
doesn't have time
no no no i didn't want to i didn't want
to stress her out with another request
of mine so
uh i i commissioned someone whose work i
really enjoyed
um actually let's show the
promotional art yeah i suffered so
nicely here
do you like it kiara with the twin tails
and with the maid outfit
got the made kachusa
what was the proper pronunciation of
katjusha in english
is it cute twin tails 10 out of 10.
[Music]
it gives me a little bit of a trying too
hard
vibe like that's that's not the usual me
obviously
i'm not that cute usually but um i
wanted i wanted to
try that uh hairstyle
headdress is the translation oh is that
is that not eagle is it is that not
english actually kachusel is that
actually like russian or something
is there a trumpet solo uh solo
not exactly but in the like there's a
several parts where the
trumpet is the main instrument going
really crazy um
but there's also another guitar solo and
stuff uh
because that's just we can't do a song
without a guitar solo no no no no no
spanish it's spanish katusa is spanish
oh funny in japanese they use that word
to describe that a headdress that mate
dress
or like not even that one just such as
generally any any kind of
head dress um
a lot of different languages have that
word huh apparently
it's also a russian name hey
anyway that's uh kind of off topic but
yeah um
about the release this time we're not
releasing it with a voice pack
uh no voice pack this time so that means
we're not selling it on booth this time
it will be released
on youtube with a music video and
hopefully at the same time it will also
be released on spotify
amazon music apple music itunes etc all
those kind of places
hopefully at the same time last time we
had quite some delay
uh but uh uh we're trying to not have
that delay this time
and karaoke version yeah that's
something i've been thinking about i do
have a karaoke version but i'm not sure
if
i'm gonna make it public i don't know
because last time we had like the
karaoke version uh sold um as like an
extra for the voice pack
for uh if you purchase it on booth
yeah but this time i don't know i
honestly i don't i don't know um
maybe i guess like some people release
their singles
with the karaoke so i guess we could
release the song on spotify with the
karaoke
maybe not i don't know if
well i don't know maybe maybe it will
not be released at all and
it will be super like uh but then
there's no coverage that's also maybe a
bit sad because there's some people
covered hinotori
and that was that was pretty pretty fun
to listen to
yeah i'll think about it maybe i'll just
upload it on youtube randomly
maybe who knows we'll see or maybe maybe
membership only content
oh yeah yeah okay shrugged in a positive
way
i think manager likes the idea of uh
having it as
manager only manager only membership
only content
yeah yeah in some way oh we gotta get it
out there in some way
but anyway i'm just super excited to
release another song
yeah uh it's been a little while the
last one we released in november
he noted it was november thanksgiving
yeah
and i've released hinatori for
thanksgiving you see
i like to release my songs on specific
days
maybe i oh wait when's easter maybe we
gotta release a song for easter then
wait when is easter is it in april or
wait
when is easter april let's see if we can
make it up today
i will try speed make a song rta now
that next song will be uh
actually easter ah fourth of april
wait
yes wait kelly's birthday is on easter
yeah kelly's birthday is on easter that
means
four four four what
that's interesting that's interesting
yeah well okay we're probably not going
to release anything for issa but it
would be kind of cute because you know
easter chickens it could be like a
family
theme song for kfp
easter is no death day well that just
makes sense
that makes a lot of sense
[Music]
oh
um
[Music]
oh
sorry i have to admit i'm i'm addicted
to my own song
i'm so addicted it's so much fun
yesterday yesterday actually i will i
i uh received the final version
yesterday and
since then i've been listening it to to
it so much time
i still even after listening to it 50
times
i'm still not sick of it so that's a
good sign
it's such a fun song it's so much fun
actually before the or
no after after the collab we just had
with the other girls
i gave them a little listen as well only
to the sample only to the
um the chorus only version i didn't hear
the full version yet that's gonna be a
surprise but
yeah hey i'm just so excited
so excited it's so addicting very catchy
you think so
you think so i hope it's classy for you
guys not only for me
oh congratulations for the released song
thank you it's not released yet
it will be released on 14th uh actually
um
with 14 february that's only really for
japan and
it will be for like it will be for for
american countries and so on american
countries
for america canada etc it will be for
like um
the 13th of february so like the night
before valentine's day
depending on the time zone
release now now i'm addicted too well
i'm sorry i'm sorry
14th february is my birthday what wait i
forgot to turn my bjm back on oh dear
there we go here's this here's some btm
valentine
american country they said it again i
said it again what is it for this
what's going on yes the american
countries
in the american countries it will be uh
the night before valentine's day
can i send that to my crush yeah
actually
yeah you could uh confess your love to
people with that song
yeah it's the perfect it's actually good
that really that's for
american countries it's uh released uh
the night before valentine's day because
that means
for the whole valentine's day 24 hours
you can blast the song out of your
stereos
and just listen to nothing else all day
all day valentine's
song heart challenger by takadashikiyada
hype flirt yes do a flirt
i'ma send it to you
i see you're gonna send me my own song
to
confess to me now that's that's a
big brain move there
smart smite smite
okay guys uh we are going back to
uh cooking soon um
i wonder how how
solidified the chocolate is by now
it hasn't been that long but maybe
managers are just gonna check it out
and see how how
so i'm really trying hard to not say
hard because wait i said
i said i said it twice because you guys
like
you guys are stupid so i'm trying to say
solidified
let's see if the choco is solidified
i'm so excited for the song oh my god
i'm so excited to release a song in time
for valentine's day
um
valentine's chocolate is also gonna be
made right now
oh apparently the chocolate is all right
now oh
oh it does look very solidified okay let
me put my
gloves gloves back on and uh come back
to you guys
we're gonna turn the camera back on in a
moment
going back to the cooking okay yeah that
was fast wow i got a really strong uh
looks actually looks good i got a strong
uh
freezer
manager son are you scared to eat my
chocolate
her reaction
that's rude
it's okay actually i gave my jason also
some chocolates from hokkaido from the
trip
so she probably she probably prefers
those
and not the ones that i made with these
gloves
i think she's probably just worried
about the gloves having touched
everything die double
don't tell kelly that all right
so oh
nice and nice nice nice and nice okay
we're going
we're going into the packaging arc
uh one second guys i'll turn it back
on right away
then let me get rid of that actually let
me move it
let me move it we can get rid of those
speech bubble now
which one is the speech bubble this one
and this one okay
let's make it a bit smaller
what it did like change size with lee
no it's okay okay
[Music]
packaging arc let's go
oops okay
okay okay
there we go way back
and so you see this you probably don't
see much of a difference on the
on the webcam but i see a big difference
it looks very solidified
actually looking pretty good now
let me open this stuff
um
this is the box that we will be putting
the chocolates in
and i will i will test it too i will
test it too
there you go gloves time yay
here are my here my hands here there you
go did you miss my hands
did you miss them oh how does this work
i'm first gonna put those in here okay
okay oh yes it's very solid
maybe a bit too big for uh i mean i
guess i could turn them around
that's the wrong side uh
maybe i should have made them even
smaller but my mama i'll force them in
there
they're just too big for my paper
it's okay it's okay they don't have to
fit perfectly look at that
it's so dark um
it's so dark here but you get the gist
of it
okay so they will all uh how many do
how many oh wait oh wait this comes with
the paper oh
these look bigger okay then um four four
uh
four thingies okay
that's a pretty nice okay let me put
them in here
come on make yourself comfortable
oh yeah yeah yeah it's fitting nicely
okay one more
oh it's turning around no
okay oh this one is very small oh
nice
[Music]
another one
there's gonna be a lot of leftovers guys
cute container right
see this is much more special than the
store bought chocolate
although i mean depending on the taste i
prefer stove store-bought chocolate
anyway but it's
it's the thought that comes damn it
this is very hard to do with the gloves
get in there come on
another one which one should we pick
[Music]
this one
oh
okay turn around
so we put another paper on top let me
show you guys here
and then we close it now pull it into
the fridge until
i give it to callie all right now we put
this on top
there we go
there we go it's a little heart
this is valentine's day chocolate for
cali completed but we didn't test it yet
we didn't eat it yet
okay well um my name's
sanyo welcome to um i'll give you i'll
hand you one a small one
yummy i'm gonna eat this one okay taste
test
three two one
also made a very happy face it's very
crunchy oh
[Music]
damn good oh
hmm
it's so crunchy
i think mine didn't have um blueberry in
it so
it means another one
maybe it did it just didn't stand out
that much
i need one more ah oh
the blueberry is also um
quite quite fitting i'm glad to put that
in there let me see
hmm
[Music]
surprisingly good don't you know what
them yeah i put them
and put four together for a miniature
sun
um but without my gloves
um so let me turn it off a moment
give us a sign she's fine
she's fine don't worry about her
i'll make another box i have another box
it's a it's a blue one
it's the same box as the one for kelly
but this one is blue
and also i also got a bag i got a cute
bag as well
[Music]
so let me make one for manager son
jenna's okay yes yes yes everyone's
asking gemma are you okay denmark okay
jim wait okay i guess you guys are just
um
you know talking about the things that
me and me and kelly talked about
yesterday
where i said that if people ask
eh how you are you know that this is
it just shows me their appreciation
and how much they you know like me
should have done it like that
okay so and this one this one i'm i'm
trying to package uh
more nicely because jen jenna is
watching oh that's much easier i found a
way easier way to put them in there
should have done that from the start
we appreciate genma and you thank you
that's sweet
miniature what are you talking about
she's very much alive and very very
happy
very very happy that
i made such a yummy chocolate
i mean what what what what should be
going wrong
everything is going right this is
exactly how it's supposed to taste
you can't do much wrong here honestly
it's just a bunch of corn flakes
mixed with chocolate and uh
and some some blueberries and some
walnuts and some almonds
[Music]
i made another box guys i made another
box
looking nice
are you guys jealous
i will i will send every single one of
you some chocolate too just wait
just uh wait until the post postman
arrives
you gotta be patient
people never go
ah there we go here we go
[Music]
asha i will present uh
you guys uh this one more time i'm
probably gonna take a photo later as
[Music]
well
pain oh you're sad because of what i
said oh
guys don't worry it will arrive it will
wrap you
but even even more important than the
chocolate
it's my song i know the camera is not on
right now i don't know
you you'll all get a present from me on
valentine's day
which is my song
hearts challenger coming on valentine's
day what else could you want
that's all i could ever wish for
there we go okay so now
let me try one second
[Music]
there's too much stuff on my table guys
help me
okay
you see the back well it's kind of dark
in here
um
one second let me light it up
there you go
[Music]
here's my my my phone light doing some
professional
lightning work hey
hey beautiful
i bought those uh i bought some bags
that we can put the chocolate into
everything's perfect what a perfect
valentine's day gift
a bit too early one week early but good
enough
actually wait i realized oh
i just realized that ah
we wanted to do the shrek watch along
next week but kelly
said that she's too busy next week so
it's gonna be the week after valentine's
day
i guess i have to visit her anyway even
though we're not collabing next week
to give her the chocolate before
valentine's day
because otherwise it might go bad i
think for a few days it should be fun
but uh more than a week i don't trust it
no has to be eaten as soon as possible
too busy for shrek yeah apparently uh
she says she says she loves drag so much
but then she's too busy for shrek
unbelievable unbelievable
how could you ever be too busy for shrek
right right
just kidding
i also i also have to give her the the
play button because i
i got her youtube play button so i'm
gonna bring that to her as well
oh you see how messy the table is right
now oh dear
let me turn this off because we're done
with the chocolate
and let me make this bigger again
[Music]
add got some chocolate for me
and some chocolate for manager and some
chocolate for most importantly
cali yay
thank you guys for watching i hope that
was really uh fun for you guys it was
very exciting for me it was
something really really new something
very um
fresh never tried this before we could
do this more often i was thinking maybe
i can show you guys how to make uh
australian pancakes
yeah because i can bring i have a
portable um
what do you call it portable hot plate
not what you call it i don't know but i
can i can cook
upstairs properly with a with a frying
pan
it will be also very uh chaotic but
but i think now that we have
successfully done this without any
accidents
no accidents yeah then i think um
i have i have uh the permission to do
more of these streams
i'm a professional after all of course
why would there be any antioxidants
yeah next time maybe with um maybe i
could cover my
my my black gloves with uh some plastic
uh you know those those thin plastic
clubs not not the rubber ones but
like really thin uh see-through plastic
clubs
something like that australian pancakes
yes
tarantulas no no no no i mean australian
pancakes not australian pancakes
australian pancakes
good job thank you thank you
no gloves next time marry dude
i'm sorry that's not possible that is
not possible
always gloves yes yes
um i think um we should read some super
chats
and so the manager sound i guess can
actually
leave because i'll be reading super
chats and oh don't forget your chocolate
finish yourself
i gave myself some other gifts as well
so she's just she
she's obviously most happy about the
self-made chocolate obviously
she'll be leaving in a little bit and
i'll be moving to my super chats
oh man i can't wait to clean up my desk
after this stream
oh yes such a mess here i don't know
what to do with all the
all the leftover uh not a solidified
chocolate cornflake mixture that just
should just
spoon it all out there and eat it while
i'm streaming
probably that's gonna make me throw up
pretty sure
yep
i think we're gonna stay on this screen
for the super jet reading today because
i want this uh
this beautiful promotional image to be
there
and it's all valentine's day themed i
like it i think we can stay here what do
you guys think
i think we should stay here
all right but let me move myself in
front of it
there we go there we go
actually i should probably make a tweet
before
we start uh because now that now that
the information is
out there i do want to
write a tweet really quickly would you
guys stay with me while i'm tweeting
what
how should you write this um
[Music]
new single announcement
okay
what do we write um
february 14th valentine's day
on february 14th valentine's day i'm
releasing my second single
[Music]
art challenger all right i
guess that's not caps it's just normal
art
challenger
[Music]
yeah um eh
mm-hmm let me put the
car in the promotional on the cover
let's put the
club nah that's a promotional one
all right
what else should i write er
please wait while potential sweets
important announcement thank you
it's a very happy
energetic song
that's perfect
[Music]
to gain
confidence for your ellen
heinz day confession
look forward to it yeah
and then add some trumpets trumpet
emojis
gotta love the trumpets i freaking love
them so much
preview did you listen to
the preview in my stream
asking because i want the people who
didn't listen to it to go back to my
stream and then watch the archive
how could you not have listened to it
right now though
obviously like even if it's in the
middle of the night he should have he
should have woken up
just for this
wait i'm missing uh there he says two
two letters too many
damn it did you listen to the preview in
my stream here is a very happy energetic
song that's perfect to gain
confidence for your valentine's day
confession
how do i make this shorter
look forward how do i say uh
[Music]
how do i make this shorter damage it's
too much text ah
instead of february for teams i should
say uh on valentine's day
i'm releasing my second single
chin
okay now i added some japanese so now
we're missing
we have too many letters again just add
post
a trumpet emoji what you mean i should
add a reply with trumpet emojis
no they gotta be in there
okay let's just just get rid of the
happy now it's just an energetic song
not a happy song
it's a very energetic song it's perfect
to gain confidence for your valentine's
day confession
look forward to it did you listen to the
privy in my stream okay
that's okay
okay you all are welcome to retweet it
guys please
please retweet share a favor with
it give it a heart you know
but don't forget to keep some of those
of that uh
hyping energy until later when the
actual song the full
full version comes out
wake up can you canada tweet go go go go
go go
retweet retweet retweet trumpet trumpet
trumpet trumpets
maybe maybe i should uh change my my
oshimaku
to a trumpet for one week in order to
promote the song
my oshimak from today on will be a
trumpet
yesterday
[Music]
so excited let me let me uh pin that to
my profile
okey dokey honestly i don't think we can
read all super chats today either
but i'll try to uh once again catch up a
little bit
super chat uh we have the
i'll read the ones from the animal
crossing stream
and
let's see how far we can get you know
pop out
chat put it there
thanks for the fun stream camera you're
welcome everyone who wants to stay for
the super chat reading you're welcome to
stay
my my viewers do say that my super chat
reading is the main part of my streams
i wouldn't say that's today because i
think today was
the main part of the stream was
definitely the chocolate making and the
announcement that was a lot of fun
new song new song high pine pipe
but here comes the super chat time which
is also very important
okay scrolling down my friends
scrolling down
[Music]
it's such a happy
i feel like this is very addicting
especially once you've heard the full
version i think you guys will be very
addicted to it
although i mean maybe some of you guys
maybe for some of you guys this is not
exactly the
the normal genre that you listen to but
but you will have to listen to this one
i'm sorry thank you for the membership
boba tron
thank you okay
okay it's renting here in my country
attention it why
yesterday it was also kiara trending in
like two or three countries
i have no idea why is that really about
me i don't think so
weird listen our usual room seems fair
exactly
as a trumpet player i approve what david
aragon
you are a trumpet player what
what oh spirit snare is also in the chat
hey yeah spirit's there
spencer made the heart challenger logo
thank you
thanks for being here i mean obviously
i'm sure you wanted to hear the
announcement
and hear the song
i gotta give big ups to uh mamaloni and
spirit snare
because they they made this art and the
logo
like without like any
any sample of the song i sent it to
mamaloni
later on the sample once it was done but
she started working on all the video art
just with my like explanation of what i
wanted but she had no idea what the song
sounds like so
she only had like a like a explanation
with
words yeah that's it
but that was enough because i gave a
good explanation
okay so let's get started with the super
test i'm gonna uh let me put the
thumbnail
on screen of the suit of the one that
i'm reading now
we didn't do that last time but we'll do
it now
okay animal crossing super chat
let's go
yeah big ups to everyone involved
exactly oh
i'm so happy for this song
thank you sure thank you for the red
super chat hobo line what the hell thank
you
mom for 10 attention this is the first
round i've sent
oh wait this is a wrap again pretended
angel this is the first red absent i
have no regrets it was 100 well spent
for all the pure gold content you give
us kfb gents calling you 24 kiarats
would make the most sense
[Laughter]
oh you're calling me a diamond
well that's cute by the way welcome back
my queen hope you had fun you deserved
it thank you javelin thank you so much
you are spitting bars damn really smooth
24 carat is gold no diamond oh
oh oh yeah i don't know i i
am yeah
never mind i knew that i knew that
i knew that stupid irish is testing you
guys
24 carat means pure no additives well
then couldn't you use the same thing for
diamonds as well then though
it's a measurement these guys don't know
what they're talking about
oh wait oh wait what what
yeah diamond two oh see there you go
there you go okay it could be diamonds
too okay nice
it is for diamonds too lol oh well there
you go
there you go i i knew what i was talking
about all along
patrick chen duncan pudding donkey
shooting
welcome back lady kiana i hope your
brief takamori respite was wonderful and
relaxing
now shall we get back to expanding the
kfp empire into the animal crossing
world and crushing the jfp rebels
yes hooray let's do it
yes yes yes sounds very very like a very
good idea take his monkey
oh there's a difference between c and k
in carrot
oh yes why
i wonder
that's that's interesting you heard your
let's take down the rebels take him down
take him down don't
don't you ever forgive the rebels
carrots wait am i pronouncing it
in german we say karate i think
does it sound like carrot for you guys
i'm saying carrot okay i guess it sounds
it sounds the same open cut you're
pronouncing it right okay then it's just
uh it's not my fault then
24 carrots yummy that's very healthy
thai sedakisun ceiling fan function mr
khan's big sunglasses
super chat thank you
welcome back to angel thank you i feel
very welcomed
thank you so much thank you for waiting
for me ethel
thank you soon moto account name thank
you
and thank you for the pinky tom
tornadoes thank you
brian hitchney oh wait sorry i i i i
should i should have read the pinky
chiana back 30 seconds and started
calling us idiots
did i i i apologize
for i'm sorry i didn't i didn't mean it
that way
sorry yes you did sorry
well it must have had a reason he must
have had a good reason
he's into that though yeah it seems so
he likes it
and brian hitchco
[Music]
thank you for oh thank you for that
super
good to chat you back from your
honeymoon despite the both of you
on vacation you also try to stream and
provide top quality
money moments so here's an akka spot to
show my appreciation glory to takamuri
thank you
[Music]
thank you that's very sweet of you thank
you i did try hard to give you guys some
content even though
uh it was very scuffed but i'm glad you
guys appreciated it thank you so much
did anyone remember to refill the food
balls in the usual room
wait there are food fowls i didn't know
yeah thank you d love thank you
[Music]
i'm glad that everyone is welcoming
welcoming me back
everyone is here i see all the all the
usual names
there aren't yeah that's what i thought
hey father sorry attention i'm late oh
my god new single yes you are late
yes i'm putting out a new single on
valentine's day
for some of you guys this will be the
night before valentine's day
and because the the video will come out
the music video will come out on
japanese standard time
uh 14 february
11 a.m
and i'll be doing a countdown stream
that leads up to that
i'm not sure yet what to do because we
made chocolate today
so what do we do for the for the
countdown stream
for that i don't know i'm not sure
uh we'll do something we will do
something maybe
[Music]
maybe a countdown but i'm planning
karaoke
on a different day next week i don't
know i need to figure out something
what if you're 800k by then well i don't
know what
what what what is that supposed to
change
i guess uh i guess yeah next week will
be um
new song celebration and 800k
celebration
we might just combine it yeah
we just add it together
we want to celebrate with you i want to
celebrate with you guys yeah
let's do the work together of course i'm
going to be celebrating with you guys
how about a third hat oh and that's
something we have to talk about with
papa
look at papa
wawa world's one million celebration
when oh
not plenty of like a full-on celebration
for that but i was quite happy yesterday
and
mitchie mitchell retweeted my tweet
where i wrote that we got
a 1 million i'm so happy i'm so excited
which like he also uh retweeted it back
when i first released the cover
and now he retweeted it again when i was
celebrating one million michy m really
tomorrow cover next
i definitely want to cover more michy m
songs i have a bun my eyes on a bunch of
them
michi m is a god yes i love frilly
tomorrow
i love all of the mitsub songs oh my god
they're so great
[Music]
okay it suits your voice you think so
really
thank you thank you
songs are great yes yes yes yes
yes that little sample of singer really
gave me them konosuba opening vibes
wait i don't i don't know what that
opening sounds like thank you for the
membership welcome
fatty snake
it suits your voice and style very much
vowel world you mean
thank you did we get to see the pralines
yeah
i i was making them on stream and showed
the finished version as well and i even
packaged them
i saw i saw funny now we're talking
about vocalized producers i saw a funny
tweet the other day
um from a certain uh
vocalized producer that made me giggle
someone called kira which is funny
because it almost sounds like chiada
and he speaks german just like me he
wrote something like um
sorry that was so funny i have to share
it he wrote uh
and he got criticism for um
like gumi he's using gumi as a singer
in his vocalized song then he got
criticism that it sounds too much like
like a robot or two to auto-tune or
something and he was like
well sorry well i'm gonna tell goomy to
sing better in the story in the studio
next time but
how how okay i i i don't think i got
the joke across quite well but i think
some people you get it
it's so funny because like gummy is a
freaking
vocaloid of course it's gonna sound
auto-tuned of course it
that was so funny oh my god i had to
share that that was just funny
funny thank you and el canel
thank you for the rest of the tai chi
thank you gumi best vocaloid i do i do
really love kumi's voice yeah
it might just be my favorite uh as well
out of all the vocaloid uh voices
gummy still has like one of the more
human sounding voices out of the bunch
yeah compared to the other ones so
it's like it can't get much better than
that
you got it the first time or i don't
write all right i thought you guys
didn't get it
thank you tai chi wow welcome back thank
you i'm glad to be back thank you for
waiting for me taiti
thank you for the support and the
generous donation
i've resisted giving a super chat for
this long but after hearing your song i
finally given in the new one
you liked it that much thank you i'm
glad to hear that thank you
you will like the full version even more
trust me
the trumpets are just so addicting
the one with the red twin red pinkish
twin towels
i might be wrong but i i did uh watch
another vocaloid back in the day a lot
of vocaloid songs
yeah it was said all right
it was cute very cute
[Music]
is it correct
just this little tiny bit sometimes
sometimes i gotta sing a little bit
nostalgia yeah
wait wait now that you say nostalgia
that reminds me of uh
it wasn't there a song that was uh
called
was it like nostalgic
and uh i always wondered why why they
wrote it wrong
yeah that's it is that actually a word
now
and there was a vocaloid song called
nostalgic right no styles
that is nostalgic but what does that
mean what does nostal logic mean
is that a word ah okay so it is a
combination of nostalgic and logic
ah i always thought that they just had a
typo in the title and then they just
went with it
i see that makes sense it's a
combination of words huh okay
i haven't confused me a lot back in the
day
ah
[Music]
it's only been a couple of days but we
really did miss you kiana you truly make
our days brighter for every one of you
streamed
yeah it really hasn't been that long but
i understand that i missed you guys too
but don't worry it's all back to normal
now it's all back to nola but
we might get some uh
some bigger bricks when i move depending
on how
how well the moving goes
and if it doesn't go that well then you
might have to
be a bit patient guys and and wait a bit
for me until i'm back
[Music]
that's fine we understand thank you but
i i don't i don't want it to be like
that
i want it to go well
i'll always wait for you thank you it's
so good thank you
you guys are so sweet we'll wait for our
attention thank you
you understand danjo thank you you guys
are so sweet
thank you never leaving yeah you will
you can't anyway
even if you tried
you you guys are stuck with me forever
until i leave muda thank
thank you welcome back my queen viva la
chiara glory to kfc
hell yeah i'm glad you you keep on
chanting
those important important chants never
forget
hashtag vogue hashtag yolk
as well yeah we really miss you mama
tanjo can't wait to hear all about the
trip
we'll we will be will we be getting a
new little brother or sister chickens
[Music]
no no no no no no
unfortunately not yet we're not we're
not ready for that need to give
up the time will come
maybe one day maybe maybe
it's a bit early for that yeah first
marriage magic
ball one after another don't crush it
did you did your wife get to see your
final form
so what do you mean with my final w with
that we definitely saw each other's
final form
i tried not to look actually i guess i
didn't really look
exactly at her final form but like at
the corner of my eye i might have seen
her final form
and let me tell you it's quite final
royal aidan
thank you for the red super chat
uh not a common writer scammed
bamboozled unsubbed
[Music]
um
jasper for sending me yours
jasper i miss you wait one second
oh welcome back baby
hopefully you've enjoyed your honeymoon
by the
jasper italian boy
daniel my village oh yeah oh oh the don
who's the dawn hmm
i i will probably need eventually a bit
more donations
yeah i'll come to you guys and collect
the taxes
when i visit your uh villages then i'll
collect your taxes
for the people who don't understand
jasper let me explain
i have a mouse i have had a mouse in my
ceiling i haven't seen or heard
uh casper for a long time but we games
we gave the mouse a name
the name's mouse and mouse's name is
casper
and uh so there were
some this casper was sending some super
chats every once in a while
and eventually this jasper dude showed
up which is also a mouse
but it seems to be an italian mouse
uh some kind of relative uh from casper
i guess
yeah yeah and uh jasper sends super
chats as well sometimes so i like to
read them with an italian accent as much
as i can
wasn't casper in a vacation
yeah casper is so
so casper just moved i think he really
just moved
i'm sure he's not dead he just realized
he can't get into my
pancake mix anymore so he's uh
he got himself a new house to terrorize
let me drink some more water my throat
is feeling rough
no don't be so negative guys
he's alive he's strong
don't underestimate uh casper
typhon you say you're not allowed to but
you transform every other week to not be
late to holotalk
ah
i still hear the screams of the people
on that train
typhon you have a point there
i guess so but i'm just gonna
act as if that didn't happen
[Music]
consider the following you wanted to
marry kelly and she rejected you
you also wanted to marry chad and only
some of them rejected you
ergo you and chad is the more official
club book
hashtag kiana x chat otp hashtag
takamori
is platonic don't say that
[Music]
the chat is not otp and it's not i need
some
we're not we're not like that you guys i
offered it to you guys but most of you
said no
so that's that um it has to be either
all of them or none of them
heretic takamori otp
heretic true
we know you'd reject us in the end
nine nine nine nine nine
wait guys was it
was there a moment when i spoke a little
bit german with gouda was it during the
stream or was it after or before the
stream when you guys didn't hear it
today
because that the german just reminded me
of it that i need to give uh
it was during it okay okay i need to
give a good a german lesson
following up on the japanese lesson we
need to teach her some german
it's good that she already knows like
some small basics
what was the announcement oh it's
literally right here next to me
that is the announcement
deutsche 101 for sharks uh deutsche
lines eins
back five
wow how insulting
you're going to recall roll her again
now in german yes i would like to do
that yes
via sentence
[Music]
i will do it trust me it was his
birthday yesterday
what it was his birthday yesterday
my man my man had his birthday
for real
happy birthday to you happy birthday
to you happy birthday to rick
i play happy birthday to
you happy birthday to you
happy birthday to you rick astley
yeah happy birthday happy birthday
[Music]
happy birthday happy birthday
good to know thanks for telling me how
could i miss his birthday he's such an
important
person in my life how could i miss it
unbelievable
this question has been asked before but
i've been curious peeking in on your ac
streams do you have a villager or two of
the whole lot
you'd be most excited to move in to see
moving in
hey actually no not really except i
guess the one that i had before in my
first uh
and the first time i played on my first
island and mira
i think her name was mira
she's a bunny
and i i would actually be very happy if
i would get her back
because i miss her
she's cute i have her ow please tell me
when she's
hoping to move out tell me please
please let her move out and come to me i
have mirror on my island
give her to me please
but otherwise aya and phoebe i want
phoebe because she
looks like a phoenix yeah
we gotta get phoebe over
but yeah wait she was supposed to be
wait was she
she is supposed to be a phoenix right
yeah
pretty sure i seem for benedict well at
least someone does
oh jasper just wait let me read that one
right now
he can't see himself at the moment
[Music]
he says he's fine now though
who would have known and it's that easy
to poison casper
she should have given him nuts all along
damn a mousepad
oh my
casper is allergic to nuts apparently
you would think that
mouse love mice i love nuts
i guess i was wrong excessive food thank
you
you sent him to the hospital excuse me
what was i supposed to do
these pralines needed some nuts
[Music]
as i'm not known for wise decisions do
you and probably a few of your employees
wants to visit my island it's a very
fairly rural one but at least you can
perhaps steal some ideas from my island
oh you even sent me a code sorry i guess
it's way too late for that now um
i'm gonna be visiting islands eventually
so please wait
wait did you maybe originally sent some
emojis with that and then
it just didn't get shown in the super
chat i wonder
i wonder i don't have my
rejected uh rejected um
thingy over right now what if we move
over here
let me reject you real quick there you
[Music]
go
[Laughter]
whoopsie that plate automatically
once i opened that
blessed i bless your ears with my new
song
surprise
well um account name i hope that's what
you were
hoping for for the rejection
thank you shane thank you for the red
super chat
thank you for the support i don't know
how i deserve all that support from you
but thank you so much
mrs thank you soon
thank you for the red super chat i don't
know what to say with this red super
chat
wow what a deep
deep message to go with a red super chat
piano rejects you by blowing out your
ears
never know when another kfb jump scare
is going to kick in
i'm sorry sorry guys
anyway excessive food thank you for the
support thank you so much
it means a lot to me thank you even even
if you don't know what to say
i think you're trying to say that you
like my content and that you
that you enjoy it and that it makes your
day
and you you hope you can watch many more
streams in the future you know that's
all those things that you could have
written in the super chat but you chose
not to
anyway thank you
um let me
let me just stop get something from my
throat
it hurts as usual
i was later missed the announcement and
probably now i got to hit it for you ah
should i do you want to hear it
completely yeah i will i will play it
for you
i will play it for you okay since you
missed it let me let me
let you listen in on the preview
[Music]
[Applause]
happy guys remember the lyrics already
i hope you did
did you remember the lyrics of the song
already you should be able to sing it by
now
yet okay you better loop it uh after the
stream is over
[Music]
i know
while watching my stream over and over
and over and over and over again ian
lyrics japanese phoenix singing
wow now this time i'll actually
translate the lyrics for you guys so
that there will be an
official uh translation there is some
fan made translations for hinotoni if
you guys haven't seen it yet
and you really want to know what the
song actually means
there i i saw one or two good
translations
but this time i'll write it myself
yes yes because it's quite easy for
hinotoni the problem was just that
um hinotori uses so many difficult
and japanese words very difficult ones
like
really really like i don't know fantasy
terms or something like that
but for uh this song we're using baby
language
that anyone can understand we had too
many lyrics exactly
maybe i'll do a cover oh please do i
don't know i don't know yet
if i will release the karaoke version
but if i will then you're welcome to
cover it
so there will be subtitles um yeah i
uh i think that's possible
baby japanese that even cali can
understand did you have to roast her
like that huh
oh yes it is it is very important that
cali understands the meaning of the song
it's very important downstairs i'm
looking for the top down question
tiger donkey shouldn't thank you for the
red super chat again
insert deeply moving message that causes
kiana to well up with tears as she reads
it
[Music]
i'm totally crying wow what an emotional
message
thank you so much stilov
thank you for the support i know you
could do it if you wanted to
i know you can write an emotional deep
message
i know you can you're just gonna try
hey cake also thank you for the red
super chat yeah
no hair no new joke and you like that
magical
[Music]
room irresistible round round fight to
power
that lava floor yeah definitely doesn't
look very comfortable
bruno l thank you
when they came to clean the room in the
morning did you have to tell them to
come back later
ah actually we did uh um
we did indeed not make use of the room
cleaning uh
because they wanted to come super early
when we were trying to take a nap
it was like we woke up for the breakfast
quite early
then we went to the breakfast and then
they asked us if they can come clean the
room but we were planning on taking
another nap
after the breakfast and i asked them if
they can do it afterwards like after 12
and they said
no they they that that hotel
wanted to do everything so early thank
you for the membership
thank you that song slaps i should
re-watch guna nagan
oh yes i love guru nagaland it's one of
my favorite animes
i love that anime so much
that's too early right i know so many
hotels who do like
room cleaning at least until like three
o'clock or four o'clock
sometimes even until 8 p.m
yeah but but i feel like the the
japanese ryokans
they just um are very active in the
early hours
our dinner was also very early our our
first dinner was at like 6
30 p.m and the second dinner was uh was
at
seven 7 30 pm
isn't that early like normally i mean i
eat dinner very late just because my
sleep schedule is [\h__\h]
but that's normal for me yeah
looks like normal hours yeah that's
early that's super early
i would eat dinner if my sleep schedule
wouldn't be [\h__\h] even then
i would eat dinner maybe at like 9 p.m
or something
at the earliest 8 p.m for me 8 p.m
sounds like a good dinner time
you are the one who are weird huh i mean
i did eat dinner
at midnight or
one am last night
i know
when do you guys eat dinner usually
you're stopping by to leave a like have
a great stream well thank you
oh you're not staying it's
6 p.m what
do you guys not get hungry before you go
to sleep then
how can you eat dinner so early six
seven
what a highest
seems reasonable to me
oh thank you for renewing your
membership
eat before sleep get fat easily yeah i
mean i've heard that but
it doesn't really apply to me so i don't
care i just eat uh whenever i want
pretty late often after midnight often
right before i go to sleep
[Music]
7 nine pm gosh
nine pm seems okay
maybe those flames burn all the calories
oh
yep that sounds about right thank you
for the membership
steve welcome hey chad
is she german no i'm not german
but i speak german it's my first
language
my mother town but i'm not german
i am australian
thank you for the membership thank you
and looking for the top function
our nine thousand duncan excessive boots
thank you
looking for the top function whereberry
thank you guys
bank induction got too fat when you were
gone
gotta throw out that money huh it feels
too heavy huh
thank you very much thank you for your
generosity
[Music]
struggling suffering from having too
much money huh
thank you so much for being so kind and
so generous
tell me duncan thank you for the
membership miso thank you for hatching
best time to eat dinner is when you're
hungry exactly
i just eat whenever i'm hungry and
unfortunately that is often quite late
oh goodnight daycare monkey
i'm reading a lot of names in the chat
today huh
i'm trying to be a bit more personal
with you guys
but don't get used to it
how do you say phoenix in german phonics
you write it um with ph but the oe
turns into an earth and it's like an o
with two dots on top
yay second single yay
isn't it coming out of lurking to say
hello
hey yeah thank you
yes yes yes i think that's how you ride
it i mean i've actually
i don't know actually i don't know
now that i see it written out i'm not
sure about it is it correct
it should be correct
we cover you kiara ah
is that a meme now because someone
typoed that when they even
told me if they love me it's correct
okay
there we go i hope you too
i call you too my friends
my chickens ready daddy son kashan
captain jelly thank you for the red
super chat once again you seem to be
donating
for the cause of other people who cannot
represent super chats very kind of you
this time revolving at aenon revolving
adam patton
p-a-c-n oh
marketing intern have been sponsored for
super chat by nerf and the new cafe
two-ton bucket with new spicy cali
dipping sauce at any participating
location
hmm spicy cali dipping sauce huh
yummy if it's like uh
the karai type of spicy
you know that why why is there english
language is amazing but why is
spicy can mean two different things it
can mean that it's like hot spicy
and it can mean that it's just like
spicy spicy i wish it would be more
clear
i can have spicy pie spices spicy spicy
but hot spice is something i cannot eat
spicy is usually hot spicy
heart is hot spicy spicy but hearts can
also mean different things and hot can
be
hot spicy or spicy hot but also can just
mean hot hot like river the weather is
hot
it's so confusing
english language confusing
[Music]
please be more clear change this please
my german speaking bodies understand
okay we change it now yeah you better
i'ma change it real quick hold up oh
yeah we changed change the duden
thank you captain jelly for your support
thank you soon
well next is thank you inside questions
looking for the top thank you to flame x
thank you for the for the red super chat
wow buying 100
of kfp stock because i like this bird
kfp to the moon
now i'm very happy for your generous
donation but
you cannot buy a hundred dollar
kfp stock if you're only super chatting
99.99
you're missing one cent please come back
with one cent thank you
i will wait for you thank you
thank you believe me
investing in kfp stocks will be worth it
that's just one cent yeah but it's
important you can't make a purchase if
the
if the amount that you're paying is not
correct it just doesn't work guys
it just doesn't work that way
[Music]
interacting with you and seeing you
happy and fun having fun you bring a lot
of joy to my day along with everyone in
kfp
thank you you guys bring a lot of joy to
me too
thank you
it would be so bad if one cent super
chat existed as an option super chat
ratings will be weeks long
yeah that is true although
yeah there's also a lot of one dollar
donations which is totally fine but yeah
that also
i think it takes a lot of time sometimes
when when i sneeze
everyone sends these tiny super jets
it's totally fine though i i i am happy
to take my time to thank every single
one of you
flame take 50 bucks but you're missing
another cent again
flame sorry for missing a cent
take 50 bucks a set but that's 49.99
incorrect let me let me move over one
second
deny there we go back here
i don't have to stamp over here
thank you though thank you shane i
appreciate it thank you
ocd kicking in
need some purpose though they do you
know yeah that's not that
that that's not
not quite correct we want to be correct
now
overpaid and spilled the night
it always two cents now yeah see it adds
up
it adds up eventually you keep on you
can't just say it
no no that's okay just because it's one
cent because they will add up eventually
and then one day it will be hundred
dollars
ocd kicker we're kicking in shut up
shut up shut up
math 100
chocobos for kfp deliveries oh that
would be cute
but we were talking to ina about
possibly
making use of her delivery service
because apparently she can
travel through fridges
if i understand correctly
so that's quite useful definitely we'll
save uh
on that deliver delivery time yeah you
know
it's kind of hinting that she can that
taco eats delivers by traveling through
fridges it's like a portal or something
yeah teleportation
very very interesting
[Music]
i didn't ask about the details but i
will ask when we uh
uh whip up a contract you know
i'll cover the two cents that's two
dollars not two cents
that's too much take it back take it
back does this make up for two cents no
that's also like i don't know but
actually i don't know
maybe that does make up for it because
that's uh what is it
uh uh is that
what's it what is that i don't know i
don't even know what that currency is he
attempts to have twenty dollars that
those are so much goddammit
i guess you cannot donate two cents huh
then i don't know i don't even know oh
wait i guess that's a
5.02 sly thank you that's that way
we can work with that
oh wait a second that's not 20 that's
it's 1969 what the hell
tonight
[Applause]
you guys gotta be more careful with your
financials gotta be more correct
is that if this is how you pay your
taxes then
you're gonna be in jail one day
they're not gonna forgive you for even i
actually i don't know would they forgive
you for one cent
i don't know how strict are they i
wonder
yeah stop my pain donkey [\h__\h] oh you
changed your name you changed your name
and a double red super chat wow
thank you oh my god
now that you're finally back i'd like to
give you my heart as a presence
okay then please accept my love oh yeah
we had that i did read that before
didn't i
thank you thank you so much thank you
for changing your name now it's way
easier to read for me because now it's
the america stop again
now it's a whole word thank you
looking for the top don't question my
financial decisions don't worry you got
you're not missing any sense so i don't
question anything
i don't question it are super chat's tax
deductible
i don't know mama you should maybe ask
your tax office
tell them you're trying to give money to
a phoenix
to a super cute phoenix and they will
understand i'm sure
anyway thank you so much for the
generous donation yummy dukulas
thank you that's very very kind of you
very kind thank you for welcoming
me back so kindly so so openly so warm
thank you i'm glad that you're always
there thank you
moto account i'm also thank you for red
super chat wow
thank you friend
are you pulling a fuji on me
that's okay i guess
i guess that's okay
i want to marry kelly what should i give
her
you cannot marry kelly believe me
she's mine now stop
stop trying to threaten me that's so
disrespectful
unbelievable you guys are just a
challenging life at this point
just being very very very risky living
on
on on the edge and ice my friend
oh yeah what's up thank you for another
red super chat
is yours your wallet feeling better now
is your bank account feeling better
after all these super chats thank you so
much for the support
thank you with all my heart
oh
oh a name i cannot read i haven't had
that in a while one second
let me send that over to google
translate
[Music]
there's a free app called a cnh guide
you can find out all the fishbox and diy
on it and it also can tell you what kind
of fish or bug you can guess very useful
i know there's lots of guys out there
i don't do my thing
and just you know move along slowly
dan can i marry you what gift would you
like nah
i'm taking what the hell if i'm marrying
kelly i'm saying i'm not only saying you
cannot
marry callie i'm also saying you can't
marry me
it's one plus one equals two
mate thank you my australian buddy
welcome back my queen kindly greets the
broke gang i'm sponsoring them with this
super chat glory to kfp rival
ah broken
wow i think i already reacted to this
when you first sent it
but anyway broken what up
this super chat is for you this kiss is
for you
thank you for the support bro gang as
well
no matter if you can super chat if you
can't send super jets or not it doesn't
matter i'm just happy if you guys are in
my stream
watching my streams and uh following my
twitter
subscribing to my youtube you know all
that kind of stuff that you can do for
free
that's a lot of support and i really
appreciate it
also if you want to help the algorithm
even if you were
live at a stream you can always comment
and give the archive some thumbs
afterwards once it's archived because
that helps the algorithm
you rush go
oh thank you cd thank you for thinking
of the bro gang
very kind of here
official 18
[Music]
wow thank you
i pay back have to defend the honor of
owls oh yeah
i remember that super chat
very nice of you to cover for blabbers
but he has to fight his own battles you
know
but for now i'll uh i'll take it but
next time he has to fight his own battle
that's for sure he cannot always
hide behind you
thank you thank you for the support i
love owls
please post more owl videos trevor
on your twitter please and tweet them at
me i want more
i told you before and i have barely
received any owl videos
i will write a strongly verdict
complaint
to you if you don't send me more owl
videos i want more
what's so hard to understand when i say
i want more owl videos
all right all right okay you better get
going go
you must i mean if you have an owl you
must have like a whole like
folder with millions of videos
so why are you not sending them to me
have i not been clear enough
am i speaking french or something
huh show me more owls
imagine me with a gun you know that gun
meme
show me more of your owl it's a falcon
owl but sure what does that even mean
like what what what is that
excuse for what that's not an excuse for
not having more owl
videos
he's busy he your owl is busy
where is he i want to see more of him
he's busy he's a freaking owl he has
jobs too he's a freaking owl
okay okay but i still want you must have
you must have more contents to show me
are you just renting your owl or what i
understand
is that not actually your owl have you
been lying to me
actually you're also not quite role
playing very well because i thought you
were supposed to be
out and now you you're talking in first
person
as if you're not the owl you gotta step
up your rpg game my friend
thus exposed
are you the owl or not
oh are you just a mere human
we're playing game games shut up yeah
god
shut up don't make fun of me
i am but i take care of him too oh so
you're an owl taking care of an owl
uh-huh
i say i see i see
but who takes care of you then if owls
need an
owl to be taken care of and who takes
care of you
is there an owl taking care of you
all those questions
you me i guess so okay
alception but i'm i'm not an
owl but i'm a phoenix i guess i could
yeah i guess i adopted you so
um yeah i guess i'm already taking care
of like
almost 800 000 chickens so
i can take care of one owl that's okay
all right though all right though i'll
do it
okay actually i really i really would
like to
do it because i owls are so cute so
fluffy
i love all the birds birds are so fluffy
and adorable
i cannot turn down a bird boob
forever burb love unstoppable
also owls don't else actually
am i going crazy have i heard that alice
eat mice
they have a small beak though how do
they do that yes they do right
oh they do oh you answered with we do
very smart
they do or maybe you can eat some
casper is gone so maybe you can eat
jasper
do you like italian mice do owls eat
italian mice or is that actually that
could be very tasty you know a mouse
with like
tomato sauce and some parmesan
cheese on top of it
[Music]
[Applause]
they swallow mice hole
oh my god mice are universal so it
doesn't matter where they come
that's nice oh how nice how open
you are
oh my god this is going crazy
67 thank you for red super chat your
haiku
sucks oh are you i
are you um quoting me
i i did probably say that about you
didn't i several times saying that
haiku sucks well i'm sorry sorry i'm not
sorry
thank you for the rest of the chat
though yeah maybe you can give it
another try
maybe you can give a hiker another try
sometime
i i will listen to it i will open my
eyes
and my ears and my heart and listen to
another shitty haiku of yours
[Music]
sadly this is going to be my last big
super chat for a while i've got to save
up for upcoming taxes
love you and uh the entire kfb fam wait
what does it mean why do we have to save
up for taxes is that supposed to be some
kind of hint to something
what do you mean you have to save up for
taxes
i don't understand that but okay we pay
for oh
[Music]
boom i guess that's just how it works
out
u.s taxes are weird
complicated uh adult things i understand
well thank you nancy kiba
thank you anyway i it will be fine
always your own financials your real
life goes first please take care
and and and yeah good luck with that
thank you thank you
thank you
[Music]
i'd like to report that i just sent a
letter to you oh
hope it will arrive before you leave
japan i hope so soon
oh my god i'm looking forward to that
thank you
betta licks thank you looking for the
top tank shin kitty turtle
[Music]
67 another red super chat do you love
wow wow are you okay
deal off last canada catchphrase
what color are your plants but in
japanese
i only say that during holo talk tell
but you are not incorrect
thank you thank you thank you for the
support they love you
always so supportive oh my god please
take care of yourself please make sure
to
get yourself some some presents as well
please thank you for the support though
it's amazing i don't know what to say
honestly it's
overwhelming thank you
with all my heart thank you so much for
always supporting
[Music]
chat from mama luna who did once again
let me tell you she did this cover art
and she's uh she did the the the music
video art as well
both the cover and the music video art
she had a lot of work from me
and but it turned out absolutely amazing
she's such a talented artist
and she's such a fast worker
she's so cool
um
[Music]
don't worry if you need to ease back
into longer streams hopefully you gained
confidence that you won't fall behind
even if you don't stream for a few days
credit cards are good if you pay them
off on time
oh wait you have to pay
credit cards off actually i don't
understand how credit cards work
don't let them top note you with
interest i see
i i don't understand these words but i
will keep them in mind
for the time when i why is everyone
laughing
you get a grace period to pay them
without interest i don't understand
i understand that because the lady who
was talking us into buying a credit card
and getting a credit card she said that
one for one year there's no fees it's
free
but yeah what happens after that i don't
understand okay you sweet summer child
it's probably but what if i have money
and i'm not what if i don't need to
borrow money
i don't understand
someone needs to like explain these
really basic things to me you use it
like a virtual wallet
yeah so like paypal
but but paypal just takes money from my
bank account there's a credit card not
like can i is it not just like i put
money on my credit card and then i can
use it and i can i could like
use more than that money but i would
have to pay back eventually
is that not how it just works
that sounds like how it works yeah
correct well that's fine
it's alone yeah but i just hey
that doesn't sound like so dramatic
it's pre-loaded every month you have to
pay what you
charge on the card but that's what's the
problem with that you guys are
you guys are is it that's just
uh i don't see a problem with that
that doesn't sound too difficult
interest hurts
oh sometimes up to three percent what
you run the risk of overspending yeah i
guess so
ah i see well
i i will have to get one eventually
though because for so many things you
need a credit card
and they don't take anything else and
that always like pisses me off because
it's really bothersome and then often i
have to ask
friends if they want to like help me out
i tell them
i always tell them that well i i have
the money but i just said you don't have
a credit card can i please like follow
your credit card
but that is like usually
usually
[Music]
they feel very uneasy about me using
their credit card
and i mean i guess that's understandable
but
get a debit card well my bank account
card is the debit card
but still that it's like a debit card it
was like
it should work like a credit card and
sometimes it does work like a credit
card but then on certain web
websites they don't accept it anyway
they only accept credit cards
so annoying
anyway continuing yeah i gotta thank you
for the red super chat
i appreciate it i'm glad i'm back i'm
glad you're there as well
glad you didn't uh run off for something
soon
thank you hope your vacation was fun and
relaxing thank you it was
captain jenny another red super chat
thank you
give county the new kfp two-ton chicken
bucket with 11 herbs of spices in our
new spicy reaper dipping sauce i'm sure
she'll love it
sponsored by sam paul uma katie uma
flickering light bulbs
i read that before i think
if you fall into credit card debt you
have us to sin for you
well how how um
reassuring that is thank you guys
one day there will be a stream from me
stream title and broke and i'll just be
like
i got myself a credit card but now i'm
like five thousand dollars in the miners
what do i do
nah it's not gonna happen never never
never never never
that i don't i don't know i would have
to buy a space shuttle
to make that happen
don't worry i don't the thing is that
i said this to cali too many times
it's very weird like even after it's
been almost like half a year
and uh my mindset
of uh spending money
barely has changed like i still i still
try to
like when i'm like when i look at like
clothes and stuff and i'm like oh that
won't
that would be cute i kind of want it if
it has a ridiculous price then i i feel
even if i can easily pay for it now
i feel like i don't want to pay for it
because it's it just has a ridiculous
price
and i also feel very uncomfortable with
using ubereats too much because it's
just way too expensive
though the delivery is just so freaking
expensive and i just
i just don't want to pay for it it's a
good mentality
[Music]
yeah if you want to save money but yeah
at least now in the supermarket i don't
look
uh i don't actively look for the
cheapest
food anymore i used to like if there's
like five different kinds of
bananas i would buy the cheapest banana
if there's five different kinds of uh
waters i would buy the cheapest water
and all that
um but at least now i don't do that
anymore i just buy
whatever looks the most delicious to me
so yeah
that's good we don't have to save on on
that
and like i used to like for example i
really wanted to eat more fruit
and fruit is healthy right but i i was
barely able to buy fruit because
especially in japan fruit is so
freaking expensive
yeah apples are so
expensive you guys have no idea like one
apple is like five dollars
it's [\h__\h] insane but now i can
get as much fruit as i want so that's
nice
okay uh well it depends there are indeed
apples that cost five dollars but
um i guess you could get maybe two
apples for five dollars if
yeah yeah i guess that seems um
they also sell apples for more than that
but
most apples i guess would be like the
price of uh
[Music]
two or three apples for five dollars
um something like that maybe yeah that's
way too much right
where i'm from you can get a bag of
apples for five dollars
whole bag it's like 10 or 15 or 20
apples
for the price of five dollars
where i'm from
here as well same in italy
i don't understand why it's not like
apples are so hard to
to um farm
or raise i don't know how this how to
say i i can't
i don't think it's such a hard thing
like also
don't they grow like in any season
pretty much
[Music]
um
japan local products are very expensive
but in my country as well like it's
local
it's local apples it's still extremely
cheap
um
i have my own lemon tree in my backyard
lemon lemon tree
lemon
lemon tree
yeah no you guys think i'm i'm i'm not
confused about the fact that lemon's
growing trees
i just wrecked uh i just remembered the
lemon tree the song from fool's garden
i wonder how i wonder why yesterday you
told me about the blue blue sky
and all that i can see it's just another
lemon tree
i remember like when i was in junior
high school for some reason we sang that
song in class several times like the
teacher would make us sing that song i
don't know why
and i loved it because i love the song
i don't know why yeah
and you know it's a german-speaking
country
but they made us sing that song
i feel like the probably our teachers
just wanted us to
have some fun and the only song that
they could come up with was
lemon tree it is a great song yeah yeah
that is true
okay i'm gonna listen to it actually let
me let me add that to my
uh boomer karaoke playlist
how old is that song though that's at
least like 10 years ago at least like 12
years ago or so
maybe in the next puma karaoke we will
sing that
hmm
[Music]
can you say that one time of course i
say it every stream
do you love thank you
thank you patrick and looking for the
top function
that's all this animal crossing super
chats and
i will i will end it here because
i don't know my throat hurts so much
every time i start reading super chats
before it's fine like if i just stream
normally and play a game for five hours
i'm fine but the super chat i don't know
why they are so straining on my voice
maybe it's because i'm
really constantly talking with
almost no break and really trying to be
very cheerful for every super chat i
read
i definitely try to speak uh in a
specific tone when i'm reading the super
chats because i want you guys to
you know feel appreciated that's why i
try to always be like
that's extremely straining on my voice
but i don't want to do it any other way
it might be the
repetition i know what you mean but yeah
maybe maybe that as well
it is insanely straining
[Music]
maybe you know sometimes i i envy
like for example kelly who says a name
and then makes a
uses her instruments if i would do that
too
it would be much easier for me to go
through my super chats but no
we said thank you soon we will never
change that
hmm what if i
speak last during my stream i could save
my voice for super chat that it doesn't
work like that honestly it doesn't work
like that it's magical like when i
stream
like any game or whatever karaoke even
karaoke where i sing the whole time
for like five hours it doesn't strain my
voice at all but the moment i start
reading super chats
i don't know what it is i think it's the
tone of my voice
and uh the way i pronounce uh danke
shoot
and all the names and all that
it's just really uh cool
hurts pre-record the duncan we did that
before but that just feels
it doesn't feel personal enough you know
i don't like that and we did it before
but
uh i don't know it was funny because we
did it one time but
um using a less straining verse i don't
know that's
somehow that's not possible i can't i
just can't
uh thank you
nah
[Music]
next time um i'll probably do a super
chat only reading stream
tomorrow i will rest my voice today i'll
be back tomorrow
um and yeah
that's it guys for today i hope you guys
are super excited about the new song
they want to listen to it again let's
just do it one more time
[Music]
three two one
um
[Music]
ah what a freaking banger
i'm so addicted guys i wish you guys
already had the full version
you would you would also be as addicted
as me oh my god it's so addicting
i love that as an ending
i feel like that's more like an opening
song opening anime
for like a really cute anime like i
don't know an anime about some school
girls
i don't know something like chaon or or
what is that i didn't watch that one but
what's that one called hibike
or oi um i don't know i don't know what
that one's called but
any any like music related anime or like
uh school related girl anime
would be perfect for this song
[Music]
okay
can vibe you feel it really that was not
on purpose but um
basically i just told him i told
gojo-san who made the song i told him i
want a cute song it's very poppy very
happy
and with uh trumpets
in any case trumpets are very important
i don't know i really insisted on
getting those trumpets this is
i love trumpets right now
kazoo's next yeah who knows what the
instrument of choice will be for the
next song whenever that comes out but
yeah
anyway guys i hope you had fun today at
this very very special valentine's day a
chocolate cooking stream i had a i had a
lot of fun
i was very nervous very anxious but it
did go well so
thank god we can do it again maybe i
think i think
i will i will be able to get permission
to do it again someday
[Music]
i will make my schedule and upload it
in a few hours probably my schedule for
the next week
which will also show you once again when
my song is going to be released
and uh yeah there will be a members only
stream as well next
week uh we're gonna watch a movie i
think or
maybe we're watching too many movies
maybe we should do something else
i will just write member stream and we
will decide later i guess
yeah so yeah
also i'll be doing an unarchived karaoke
and we will be combining the 800k
celebration with
the countdown to the song
challenge
[Music]
songs again it's been a while
uh what same time as usual what what
what what
kiara okay google
again not exactly i mean there might be
some old songs there might be some newer
songs we will see
i didn't decide yet are the chocolates
frozen
why are you why are you spamming that
comment what's so important
i i froze some of them and they're
packaged now
ready to be eaten anytime one last time
cover
yeah i wanna sing that one
last time i need to be
the one that takes you home
oh yeah god i appreciate ariana i love
your song
so much i know i know i'm such an such
an edgy teenager
such a mainstream edgy teenager
all right so see you guys soon and
don't forget to hype up the release of
the song
i'm so excited for it i hope
[Music]
thank you guys it was nice making some
chocolate with you guys
oh and then you make me say alf
vida scene
[Music]
okay
foreign
it does it does sound good as an ending
song too yeah
bye
[Music]
do
you