[Music]
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
dee
[Music]
voodoo
uhtee
[Music]
Ugh
Beginners n
ana
Yeah,
yeah Erotic tee Hey everyone,
live 6th generation Secret Eraser Horrocks  I
have gone with high -priced female executive high -priced clothes,
oh, oh, oh
, I'm a
little sick, but I will do my best
I think
I'd like to go to the 8 d group.The
d group that I'm in is
really strong, and the b group is
full of people who are just as strong.I
don't know if I'll be able to reach the strong range, but I've been
practicing so far to go to the 4th cup.  I wonder if I've been doing my best.I
want to do my best.However,
today's
resolution is to practice my own running.
As I was thinking about my own running, I
thought, ``A'' and ``Emo''? I think I should try to focus on my own running without thinking too much about other people.And
now that Sakamata, who I have been practicing with, has entered my strong range.
I definitely want to go with you.
Yes, I
can't really see everyone's comments during the tournament, but
no matter what the outcome is, I would be happy if I
could hear your kind words
from my seniors.
This time, the 3 thumbnails are of
my senior.The thumbnails are of my mother, who is full of those feelings.She
calmed down from Sakamata and didn't give up.Ah,
okay, let's do our best.Sakamata is
also rooting for us.Let's do our best.Yeah,
okay,
okay.
Today, even without looking at the comments, there
may not be much chatter or anything
like that.What I'm saying here is turning the steering wheel early and
drifting early.  It's
not like I'm pointing at something like, ``Don't wear your jumper.'' I don't know what to say, but
I'm trying to keep my fingers
crossed. Yes, I'm going to keep
concentrating. Everyone was working really hard.  But,
as expected, the
boom was involved, so I couldn't get into the range to hit it,
and
of course, as a result of that effort, I was able to demonstrate my ability,
and I was in the G group because I was doing a lot of research with Tame-senpai and others.
I don't really know what's going to happen because that strong race is going on and on.First of all, I want to enjoy myself and calm down and run my own way.I'm nervous.The
volume balance is okay.The balance of Yin and Yang.
Is it okay?
Yeah Yasi, I wonder if it's a job. ok ok Thank you. I'm
really nervous.
But when I was looking at Sakamata, I thought, ``
Sakamata really suits Sakamata's running style.''  That's
what I thought, and
I was also practicing with Hana-chan's buggy, but it turned out
that fava beans are super easy to use.Hey, I
'll show you what the results will be this time.I
thought I'd like to practice with fava beans.In the future, I wonder
if it'll be like that.  Anohana-chan, believe in the buggy, A
-chan, we're in the buggy,
Anohana-chan, I've been practicing, so I
believe in the buggy, A-chan, and I want us to win.
Yeah.  I guess
Miyo is
worried about her beauty. It
was a fortune telling, but
people who involve that kind of thing are a little judgmental. I've
heard some crazy things, so I
want to continue believing in things as they are.
One thing is
true, Ma'am.  I
say it's beautiful, but my head keeps going back and forth, so I
think I'll try to run as I am.
Yeah, I'm not feeling well,
so I might be a little shaky today.  I'm not sure,
but I'll do my best while drinking water.
Pen
[Music]
Okay, yeah
2 I
was there.
Whoa
2 Is it going to be
projected and moved?
Wait, I've
prepared it. I've
prepared it. I've prepared it.
Alright, alright,
yeah
[Music] I'll
prepare it and make an appeal here as well,
etc.
ok ok
[Music]
Get them to concentrate. Concentrate.
This is the result of the chu-chu. Yeah,
yup.
Alright, alright, I wonder if it'll
go well.
OK Let's start.
Well then, everyone, please do your best. [Music] Sweets, sweets,
Canyon, I guess. I've
been practicing, so I'd like to wear a cami with a sanctuary. Yes,
please.
Web 0 b Bag.
Ha, Taki-senpai is Bailey.  I'm going to choose the parts. Yeah,
after all, there's no senior in between, it's the ocean, right? They
say there's a water buff.  That
's it, that's no
good this time. Good night. I
lost it, so it's not full. Day Mom. But on the other hand, let's put luck on our side and do our best. Let's go. Concentrate on the start. It's here. Yes, it's okay. Calm down and calm down.
No, no, I can't get the item.  I'm here.
[Music]
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, I still have Alma
[Music] It's okay, it's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's still there
[Music] It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
[Applause]
[Music]
[Music] I
knew I was running safely. I
want to see it.
Mom, but, but, but, well, well, well, I
can't help it. Yeah, it's okay, it's okay. There's a lot of
luck involved here, so I've
been practicing.  All you have to do is give it out. It's
okay. I came in 7th place, so it's still okay. It's okay.
[Music] Hmm. Yeah.
Cool! Men's start [Music] It's tough because you can't even get the opponent, but Blue means you can't get any coins either, so let's aim for the inside course. Yeah, I can't use even the people, so it's okay. I'm in 9th place and eu is fine. Target is okay tonight.
[Music]
Job,
put your shell close together and say, "
Hanatare bag,"
please. I want to take
more pictures. I got a lot of points.  I
have a banana in a state, banana,
it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay, I want to take you Even if you don't answer Pa, it's okay.  [
Music]
[Music]
e 4 e
[Music] It
's okay, it's okay ko I
want to make a quick decision and press on. I
'll introduce you to Daisho University. It's
okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay, I'll share it.
Okay, okay, ok,
ok, it's dangerous, it's
ok, but go ahead. It's okay, it's still okay. You can
go, you can go.
Sakamata will be cheering you on.
[Music] I
think it's Sweets Canyon. Let's
concentrate and
aim for the top.
[Music] It's
okay, it's okay. Just run your own way.  It's okay.
Calm down.
[Music]
Just came out. Mute City. Yeah, I practiced. It's
okay.
Edited.
[Music] That
's not it.
[Applause] I
want to aim for points. I'll take the coins.  I
'll take care of the management. All right, all right. Items etc. [Music] Subaru Tari Guide I'll be lost soon. [Music] It's okay, it's okay. [Music] Come on and calm down. The other person should have been repatriated, so I
won't call. I'll
keep calm here. Oh,
take a picture.  If you don't have it, this will hurt. It's so
bad. This will hurt.
It's okay
le
[Music]
That's right.
[Music] It's
squeak.
There was no singing voice, but that's okay.
Princess, it's okay, it's
okay.
[Music]  I
didn't have a turning [Music] I did
n't seem to have it [
Music] OK OK OK Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah Ah, but 22 OK OK OK OK OK.  Please
support me and
let's take a photo together.
Hey, next is the battle. I
want to get out next.
[Music] I want to go. I'm so
nervous that my voice is so loud.  I'm so
nervous that I'm crying,
but I'm okay, I'm okay, I'm calm, I'm calm, I'm okay.
Even women don't make mistakes.
[Music] I'm
here. I've
practiced a lot, but I'm
scared of shortcuts. Don't
take shortcuts. Let's take a picture of stability.  Take it and
keep up
with me. As long as you run, you'll be fine.
Stop the drift early.
[Music]
No, I'm going inside.
He's alive.
Now I'm going outside.
[Music] It
's okay, it's finally okay, it's
okay.
[Music] It's a lie that I just
threw out. [
Music] It's okay. [Music] There's
no opera. You don't have to run. You don't have to rush. [Music] It's okay as long
as you don't get Acela.
[Music]
[Applause]
ok It's inner circle and you can't dodge it.
Princess Suka. That's a nice dodge.
[Music]
It's okay, it's okay
archi pe
Store knowledge ok
ana
Yeah
yeah Yeah
Machi Nakase is aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah  It's
okay
, hey, thank you, Chloe,
oh, thank you, I'm going to today's number. Yeah, I'm
going without skipping 8. Yeah,
drink some water,
calm down, Saeyoung
. Yeah,
follow me. As long as you calm down, you'll be fine.  We
also practiced at Cape Dolphin
Yeah, it's okay
[Music]
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's
okay, it's okay, I just lived
here, it's okay.  It's
tough not being able to catch the accidental ingestion, but I'm
losing track of it, and I
can't catch the police officer.
No, I
tend to throw away items.
This is another employee
[Music] It's okay, it's
okay.
Paula is 5
[Music]
Yes, the job is okay.
Take it and avoid it properly.
Hey, Coin Coin is dangerous.
No, it's dangerous here. It's okay, it's
okay,
it's okay
. Yeah, yeah, yeah,
what's this? It's not yet sold out. Nikoto is
ok. I
want to save this for last.
Please
[Music] I
want to decide on a shortcut with this
yeah Isn't that right?
It's Daito Daito
yeah e re
No, I won't give up until the very end, it's okay, it's okay It's tough
not having an official seal
[Music]
[Music] I've
decided on
that, right?
[Music]
[Music] I ca
n't help it if I eat, I can't help it, this is the last one, I
know it's unsettling. I
can still go on, it's okay, I still have a chance of winning. The
next one is the last. The next
one is the last one. I can
go on the train. Yeah, it's
still ahead.
If you buy this, you'll
be strong Hmm, okay, I've been practicing
Thank you black Good luck,
I
[Music] It's
okay, I've practiced here as well As long as I
start drifting early, I'll be fine here
[Music]
Bowser,
see Bowser raise his arm
That's it,
let's do our best,
failure  Don't do it.Nice star, lots
of cars, lots of people.It's
important to get the item.I want to get the item.I
want to get the coin.I want to
turn the steering wheel early.I
can
do it.I can land very well.Read the
next one.It's
okay, it's okay.Let's
start with the hard part, okay, okay.  It's
okay. [Music] Don't raise your arms. It's okay. It's still okay. It's okay. I want to take three cucumbers. [Music] It's okay. You can go.  I
'll keep an eye on you from a corner I don't know.
[Music]
Well, it's dangerous here. It's okay.
[Music] Let's
follow the people with the pack.
[Music]
No, this is the workshop train or I'll see you again on the
4th. That's
all right.
Yasaka pulled the flower again.
[Music]
It's okay. It's in a good place.
The coins are there.
Go to the love hotel.
There aren't any big rocks, but I
want to get two.
e 4 e
[Music]
[Applause  ]
OK OK,
oh
, oh, oh, my mother, oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Okay, thank you everyone for your support.It
was a disappointing result, but I'm
sure Sakamata will support me as well.Also,
I want to practice hard for next year.Haha,
thank you everyone.
30,000 yen Let's watch Sakamata's strength together at this Aisin
Thank you for your hard work. See you
at 24 o'clock. See you soon.
Timer
[Music]
Acti Track
N
r
[Music]
N
LOL
[Music]
N