thank you
[Music]
foreign
in another world
[Music]
a girl was studying at an Academy of
magic
foreign
[Music]
ation spell
oh come on
you should all know this by now
pavolia Rainey yes
[Music]
amazing work Miss Renee amazing Rainey
teach me
how did you become so good Rainey oh
it's just a lot of studying can you
share us your routine sure every day I
wake up at 5am I take a shower do some
exercises and make a cup of tea
then I go through just four or five
spellable volumes before class oh no
that's kind of hard it's not that bad
once you get used to it I bet you're
gonna score perfectly on the potions
exam today potions exam
oh no
[Music]
how could I forget
ah it's marked as Pancake Day why did I
remember pancake gaming not the potion
exam I guess four hours of sleep is
catching up to me
whatever
do my best
[Music]
I spit right through all six Alchemy and
potion brewing books I had
I can do this and you may all begin a
bit of this and a bit of that wait
Miss Renee is your potion quite all
right yes teacher it should be I added
in unicorn hair
and a dash of cinnamon a bass of
cinnamon no that's a portal potion Renee
my memory get jumbled everyone get to
the back of the classroom
why did I try to speed read the entire
companion
right now
huh
where am I
watch strange buildings
[Music]
I sense it
Magic
[Music]
who are you
a zombie
[Music]
[Applause]
give me
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
everybody
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
foreign
soon
[Music]
foreign
Mother Day
[Music]
thank you
wow whose 3D showcases is who's
this you guys are right attention please
I'm for fully Arena from whole life ID
generation too
attention please welcome
to rain is very very special tea party
oh before we start please do tweet with
this hashtag this hashtag but only rainy
3D my child please tweet because I would
like to hear your consoles and opinion
about the live so what are you waiting
for
right now or later if you want
[Laughter]
[Music]
original song
yay but
oh no
what am I gonna do I gotta clean but
before that let me
show you guys
this model I just think I look
no you don't see anything camera camera
camera camera
okay yeah
yeah
[Music]
nice ride oh rain is back oh my God for
real
[Music]
except me in my very clean room
yay clean Doom okay oh but for real
though uh what am I gonna do the 3D
showcase the private Tea Party
today but my room is still a messy
just now I've got some guests coming too
what do I do what do I do
I guess I gotta guess I'm cleaning huh
oh well
ah
oh I don't want to do this but wait just
wait a little bit okay
so that
it is
wait wait wait
it's uh
oh and this one this one's like the
heaviest
but it's okay we're putting this aside
so the camera it won't be
I did a lot of cleaning right yeah
and because uh you know I'm feeling a
little bit thirstiness
so now
I'm gonna drink a little bit
less drink
[Music]
oh
hey
oh my God yeah yeah maybe yeah yeah I
think okay
yeah okay
I think I think that was perfect
all right everybody for you welcome to
Arena tea party and it's time to come by
cheers for the tea
okay and now uh because we already done
with the tea I'm now energized we can
clean more
[Music]
excuse me
and it's time to clean let me get the
broom
ta-da I have the broom
oh where is the gummy oh my God okay
oh
go
sh okay
okay go
go we got it
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
and then we we want to go me
oh
that was so tiring
ah and then ah but that's not done not
done yet because uh
I have a Magic Tree to show you
[Music]
it's the hataki magic is the commotion
Magic
ready to cleanse your soul yes
time to clean
um
[Music]
well you know what look at this
beautiful cityscape too
you guys like this place so much right
but this is not all you know because I
still have the bedroom to clean
let's
soji the bedroom okay
okay
oh dang I'm here
this is this room might be familiar for
you guys of course
and in here
we have the spicy spicy spicy spicy
and the hat and my spare clothes spicy
so we can't show the contents of this
one in this stream okay
[Music]
I'm gonna clean that and there's um this
two we got the fishing rod fishing rod
and we can clean this too soon
[Music]
many many many things fishing
fishing and then we go to this very very
special place to my PC
and oh this is my my dust mat with a
specially drawn by animal fisa
and love me love me also look it's hello
little desk man would you buy this I
think this is very nice but too bad it's
exclusive for me and me only for now
whoo
okay
oh
okay I think uh that's enough cleaning
right let's just take a little break ah
ah I'm satisfied and I think no it's
time for someone to visit
okay
say it with me three two one
many many
look at these star tongues OMG
I've just cleaned this room
oh my god well let's pick up one okay
many many
Tata yeah
yeah
look at this
katang was lost but he is here he comes
to my my 3D
dishes
OMG
many many times I'm falling oh my God so
yeah well oh
please
I want to um I need to clean this room
I like it that you're uh any I like it
that you're falling down but
I need to soji okay
so we can uh we can move on to the guest
segment right I've got a lot of special
guests today actually yeah
thank you oh thank you we'll play again
later
and uh where is the special guest I
wonder Maya
oh
looks like somebody's already here oh
let's set the room up so we're ready for
them okay
[Music]
change
oh
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
can I use
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
good night
[Music]
foreign
baby
[Music]
foreign
only one dance lesson together where
there was no teacher so I took the
yakumet the position of the teacher and
when Reyna was on the floor taking a
break
studio for two hours
this floor
what do you think about the sound well I
mean it should it should be wood do we
hear it
we knock knock
it's mystery flooring but it's 10. bird
approved I think to you every floor is
10 out of 10. it is sometimes it's cool
enough to lie down yeah
do some cute poses okay okay I want to
do this
screenshot time use winner birthday
hashtag it's somewhere up there yeah
it's up there
um
secret agent secret agent so huh
nice
so when you still have some stuff to do
right yes
yeah
it's available to dance with you me too
let's do more soon
and next song is
love me love me
[Music]
all right
cheers
[Music]
see you
tonight
[Music]
give me
more
[Music]
[Applause]
tonight
[Music]
wow hello everybody
oh right I've got more people who want
to celebrate with me today
and they should be calling anytime soon
hello can you hear me hello
[Music]
I get the dog hello
why how
huh
oh yeah
wow
[Music]
thank you so much
[Applause]
[Music]
At Your Service
okay
[Music]
um
oh my God
yes yes what
um
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
foreign
bye-bye
[Music]
foreign
but it looks like we got even more gas
who do you think is gonna show up next
they're my senpais
uh Japanese mode um
[Music]
good afternoon
Japanese
only mess yes yes Japanese is only the
only because it was pretty okay it's a
Japanese only
yeah okay guys
[Music]
bye
greetings
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
beautiful
animals
it's good cleaning is good right okay
thank you okay
um
hello hello
[Laughter]
number one lady
thank you okay okay let's go thank you
so much
[Music]
[Applause]
that was Senpai at Silverado Senpai from
Hollow live dippy my simple
I'm so happy many many people coming
Emma and then some girls from the Ian
Branch are also here
[Music]
hello
I need to hide this
is
somewhere secret yeah
okay whatever if that's what you want to
call it yes that's right please
introduce yourself
English
[Music]
I'm Maury
kill everybody from Whole Life English
yeah let's go who's next and I'm Iris
Iris it's Iris
for coming today
is I'm accepting requests from you for
you know your screenshot time I'll do
any posts
anything anything
all right I'll go first I'll go ahead
and make it easy rip the Band-Aid off
show us your panties
what's next
I want to see a close-up of your ribs
and rocky pie at the same time
how do you not have those I was like
gills
man what the hell oh my girls any more
requests I got something to show you too
actually after this
lie down first it's dangerous
I don't know
cameraman was not really not really all
cued in on the memo there
we broadcast sorry sorry
I gotta show you something do you know
who this is okay
and I wanna
um you know say a little bit something
this tatang can grow big you know Tata
is small right but like your chest
[Laughter]
oh no with this team
something you can
drink
[Applause]
you want to uh maybe for example uh grow
bigger and stronger like have a bigger
heart or something maybe yeah you guys
can call me and order this tea for me
everybody join the royalty so if you you
know if the tofu has a little problem or
something
yeah I don't specifically need anything
like that but yeah I'm just saying I'm
not I'm not mentioning anything go
bigger everywhere everywhere of course
if you take a bath with it then maybe
you like it every single day then maybe
I only take a lot of tea yes yes I'm
still like my mom telling me to drink
milk every day of my childhood life
exactly it's better okay even better
uh where do I put this yeah sign me up
I don't know what I want to grow but it
sounds cool we need stuff like that in
our lives oh God
you know
okay
for coming
to the car
congratulations on your 3DS
amazing you look great you look awesome
beautiful girl beautiful keep doing your
best yeah thank you bye
-bye
[Music]
hey
I don't know yeah so um just call me
guys if you need that yeah anyways
um that was great I'm so happy that so
many people can't see me but I'm not
dancing yet there's still more
I'm going to sing someplace else maybe
I wanna sing in a place where I can sing
as much as I like and then so let's eat
it
[Music]
foreign
my daddy name
[Music]
anywhere go away
in the shower
[Music]
foreign
birthday dinner
[Music]
hold on
can you walk away
[Music]
oh my God
so that boys
[Music]
thank you foreign
do you know
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
she said
foreign
[Music]
attention please are you somebody
looking for a new experience or are you
by any chance a miraculous we just can't
wait for when I'm going to be
implementing a certain feature
or are you simply wanting to get a head
start with flexing using super amazing
Badges and cute emojis
well you're in luck my name is William
Rainey and I'm going to be here
explaining briefly what is going on with
the volume ratings membership that is me
by the way
at the royalty are super Advanced
magical technology grants you badge
flexing rights which you can constantly
show off every time you're here with us
we also make sure to provide you with
utmost care and sense of belonging by
granting you a one-of-a-kind experience
with cute emojis at just the right price
you'll be able to join our exclusive
Royalty Parties which also means
membership exclusive streams in which we
can have various talks play games
together and do other miscellaneous
member involvements like what you might
ask
only one way to find out
and lastly safety isn't guaranteed
development training in which we aim to
build a community of people who like
Living Dangerously
welcome everybody with open arms to join
the royalty
[Music]
[Applause]
again
[Music]
[Applause]
take me
[Music]
trust me
yes
[Music]
anymore
foreign
[Music]
thank you so much for today everybody
but
uh so yeah that was illusion and how did
you like the
video
nice Oh and before I end things I have
an announcements
foreign
just for you well look at that the front
part the front part there's an
illustration
and look at the sides look at this
sleeve design has Solomon against
perfect for the Maracas who want to have
a tonjok identity pew pew pew pew
you the size of the hoodie is one size
fits all so you don't have to worry
about size and the material is cut
to me
and the goods will not be on sale
immediately it will be on sale in the
hollow 3D collaboration on July 29th
Godzilla is
and I also have a very big announcement
to share so
then thank you
[Music]
is
and don't forget to tweet with the
hashtag tweet povolia radio 3D go
console waiting waiting please do it
because
for watching Pavilion rain is pretty
showcase
[Music]
foreign