[Music]
we s sale like 5 hours ago
and I still can't get a decent nap I
feel like
garbage Senpai you think the waves would
gently rock you to sleep yeah or make
you violently sick I'm sure we'll all
get some time to relax once we've made
it to the shore right you can nap later
look at how beautiful the ocean is from
here lots of wildlife swimming around
here too I'm watching you tacos you
better behave oh that's right wait I
wonder if we'll get to see some crazy
Wildlife out here can someone rub in my
sunscreen I get the feeling I'm going to
burn so bad out here I get the feeling
I'm going to burn too and two a crispy
chicken all right I'm going to do you
you do me narissa
sunlight yuck can we go home
a Callie said bye it's okay things might
be rough now but it'll be worth it once
we all get to spend some time together
on the island yeah come on Senai stand
up already you'll feel better if you
walk around a little bit mukan there's
no need to rush her she really doesn't
look too good H sometimes a situation
calls for a little tough love
but we don't really know where anything
is how about you new person if you could
help out our s by we'd really appreciate
it there's also a couple things we need
to prepare before
landing how did you get the job anyway
it seems a little s
suspicious are you guys sure we didn't
accidentally let a fan on the boat they
seem harmless enough especially helping
cie out like that I'm sure they're fine
now if you don't mind grabbing some
waters for all of us oh what's going on
up here death is
dying I'm fine hey you you're here to
take care of all of us right keep us in
line can you uh bring me a trash can did
you guys see there's a huge rock over
there a rock out in the middle of the
ocean that seems a little odd and not to
mention dangerous we passing
ships yeah but it looks like such a nice
rock all covered in Moss and stuff wait
a minute are you sure that's a rockby
wood yeah that sounds a little more like
an island
we finally made
it now it's vacation time girls hope
you're ready to be forced to relax
whether you like it or not
[Music]
no that's not right I'm pretty sure we
were supposed to turn right a few trees
ago but ah this is hopeless I have no
idea where we're going none of us are
any better at directions than you Iris
just try to pick the direction that
seems the most beachy you mean like
follow a trail of sand or something all
of the trails are made of sand I could
see what the trees have to say maybe
they know the way but fauna trees have
never had to travel anywhere before why
would they know the way they don't have
LS it's okay trees she doesn't mean that
I wasn't insulting them it's too bad mum
had civilization duties to attend to
she'd probably make an amazing Navigator
oh at this rate there's no way we're
going to make it to the beach coming
here ahead of time might not have been
the best idea but the retreat was your
idea be I know hle my ideas are perfect
all the time sarcasm I don't know why
you're getting mad at me go off on the
trees they're the reason we're lost the
trees did nothing wrong I won't stand
for this slander wait you guys is that
Justice
what are they doing
[Music]
here Senpai is that you guys what on
Earth are you doing here you all look a
little lost I guess we are supervisors
huh we were we were not
lost yeah you guys know where the beach
is we're supposed to be meeting the
others there ooh did you guys come to
the forest for retreat or something we
totally had the same idea Justice wanted
to do a grip Retreat as well before
meeting with everyone but Mama Mia what
a surprise we stumble up on you all
great minds think alike after all and
you guys definitely saved us from a
situation we spent one night camping and
then 2 days wandering the woods
completely lost well we're certainly
happy to see our promised
Senpai but I do wish it was Advent we
found here come on Liz why not get your
mind off at work for just a week we'll
get to see them soon enough but we did
call a treaty for just this vacation so
oh M I just remembered the ship should
be talking right now should we go meet
everyone wait so you guys know where the
beach is oh thank God we're saved Right
This Way Lady
let's go give our Senpai a grand welcome
shall
we land ho ladies and what an
extravagant
Resort wow yo really went all out
choosing a high-end place for us to stay
huh get me off this boat right now
somebody better get the bucket don't
worry don't worry about it we'll all be
relaxing on the beach soon anyway oh
look over there is that promise and
Justice already on the island wait
Justice is already waiting for us does
that mean time for us to make a hasty
Retreat huh already but the vacation
only just started Nissa you didn't
forget right you know that we're kind of
on the Run hey Liz Gigi Cecilia what
long time no see she's going to blow it
cover it you guys are very obvious but
that's okay I think they're supposed to
have some kind of packed in place for
this trip or something wouldn't be a
very fun trip if Justice was just
chasing you guys the whole time true
that we're just here for a good time you
know
oh so this is where we're supposed to be
staying can't believe we missed it yep
only took us 2 days Starving in the Ws
not my fault she's right it's everyone's
fault we suck at directions for the
record the trees were telling us the
right direction you guys chose not to
listen hey who's that with you guys
coming off the boat I don't think I've
seen that person before ah this is our
manager kind of they're like a very
specific manager just for this vacation
it's a bit of a long story but we heard
they y's choice to watch over us for the
vacation or they could be a really
really creepy snowway fan who just came
to spy on us oh God everybody running
hide it's a lie she's messing with you
they're cool I promise highly
recommended Yo's Choice All That Jazz
oh okay cool yippee I guess we are all
just a little Dan maybe from all the
work we have been doing we seriously
need to relax don't have to tell us
twice we're ready for the best vacation
ever things have been rough lately so
let's just try to keep things relaxing
and fun also everyone's swimsuits are so
cute and cool you don't look so bad you
see how cool s can beat
you h b damn
everyone really kept in shape
huh it's true enough that 2 days
wandering the Wilderness without food or
water couldn't keep Perfection from
making a fashion statement wait 2 Days
in the wilderness are you guys really
okay
[Music]
Sun babing under an umbrella some people
have really sensitive skin Oh Shi do you
want to join us at the beach nope the
Sun and I are enemies but only on
certain days I'll go with you three
maybe we can look for some sea wildlife
Splendid we'll make our way over there
now then race you guys
there I'll take you on your
majesty hey wait for us you two there's
plenty of time to race when we get there
hey sori if the beach is a noo for you
what about a spot trip
oh sounds relaxing and the opposite of
bad for my skin yeah that's a group I'm
going with I think crony needs a spot
trip every hour of the day to be honest
jto come me in I haven't gotten any
chance to relax since a you think we can
convince Yago to slide us some cash for
relax time you got death with you he'll
be persuaded oh we're down for going to
the spa if you guys are yeah the trip
here was pretty rough after all and I
feel all stiff not
possible it's fully booked no room for
anyone else wait a minute how are you so
sure hi cuz I looked it up before we got
here and low and behold only room for
four people at a time sad face if you
guys still want somewhere to relax
though I actually know the perfect spot
a of course F and I would know all the
relaxing spots on the
island is it another Spa sadly no more
Spa on this island but how about a
secret and in the forest yippee I know
where we're going let's hit it
ladies also I'm totally going to catch a
f there and make Li super
proud huh good luck with that it's okay
M let's just let her dream guess that
leaves us for anything you guys feel up
for today games games as in like beach
sports games
gaming gaming I think people wants a
little competition I've played a few
Sports out of curiosity before I'm down
all righty then beach volleyball anyone
oh hak you're going
down why specifically me why not
specifically you bails hackers first of
all I don't know who that is isn't that
your name rat second of all cool Q be do
it's on save it for the court ladies we
still need to get warmed up
[Music]