[Music]
me
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
oh
[Music]
me
oh
[Music]
um
me
uh
[Music]
me
[Applause]
[Music]
hello
oopsie that always happens yeah i always
just um turn off the
the game capture card but yeah
the rest i'll just leave on
[Music]
yeah no problem
smoothie
what is it
okay my voice maybe is a little bit um
husky right now not necessarily because
of
some serious reason but maybe it's just
because
i actually i woke up once at 9 30
but then
uh after
like an hour or so
i forced myself to go back to sleep
again because i knew i needed some
energy afterwards and then
yeah i slept all the way until the
stream hallelujah finally finally
finally
yeah i mean there was one one hour of
being awake in between but still
like your father
father
and i have i have vitamin snacks
prepared aka um
[Music]
come on quinoa you can do it what's it
called again
um
[Music]
what's it called
what is this
what is this what i'm looking at
uh
um
[Laughter]
no not gummies
no fruit no no i have fruit
fruit in front of me but what was it
again
okay i think
i think yeah the humidifier is on thank
you
i mean i think it's on i turned it on it
kind of stopped again but i think it's
gonna
uh start again anytime soon
there's some kind of uh fruit with the
small
many many small
round green things
uh
come on i know the word
i had no sense i don't put scent in it
no no
grapes yes grapes
grapes uh i have with me and i have a
savory snack as well
yeah like a salami
bar
a bar of salami
so i prepared
more or less i also have chocolate here
in case i want chocolate yeah
i am prepared i forgot the word grape
yeah well
it happens and i kind of just woke up
kind of
and no not a beefy i don't like beefiest
no this one is called
land diego
yeah
also different from the last time i ate
one of these but
yeah cause i saw
who was it was it dominic
who like analyzes what i eat on my
streams
and tweets it out and i uh yeah last
time um
last time you posted something
uh about my salami snack no that's where
bear
oh sorry whoever
i was whoever the last time you posted
something about my salami snack that was
wrong that was not the right salami
snack
how dare you assume that that was the
salami that i was eating
they're close enough though close enough
yeah yeah you always try to explain to
the others what german snacks i'm eating
i'll show
everybody we're gonna play wind waker
one hour earlier than usual because
kiwawa is early sleeper now meow
nanda yo
let me just check if they have uh
kibbles i think they do what's that
[Music]
okay
uh chunkers
i don't know man what a problem is
jonkers was just um
at the top of
like a a wall climbing thing that i
built for them at the top
and then standing up kind of and meowing
at the ceiling
aggressively
[Music]
she probably was like i want to go even
higher
i don't know what her problem was man
yeah okay
she saw some ghosts or something i
thought it was the food but no she was
just i don't know meowing at nothing
oh guys thank you for listening to
fevernight by the way it's already like
almost at 200k thank you so much let's
go let's go let's go let's go let's make
a record okay i mean even if we don't
make a record that's okay because i made
a record by making music right
um
[Music]
is it even called record in english in
that sense
is it yeah okay well then then my uh no
not a vanilla
then my joke worked
okay so we have one shard
but apparently we're gonna be doing a
little bit less of chart collecting and
a little bit more of
where the [\h__\h] am i
oh
is this the beginning of the dungeon
where is my girl then why do i get
warped to the beginning of the dungeon
and my girl is like somewhere in the
middle of the dungeon
oh yeah she's she's on b1 and i'm on at
one f
wait then how do i
oh with my floaty thing
uh wait is there music wait a second
i don't hear anything
hello
oh
i will fix this
i
will try
to fix you
oh no probably i just have to restart it
yep probably
the music very subtle yeah but i have it
all
at the top and
don't hear anything
well you guys hear something i think but
[Music]
no sound
to myself i hear nothing
[Music]
okay i heard that
wow
uh let me do
the
these settings i got the sound capture
output
i think
meow some
sometimes when i connect something
it just i don't know changes wait wow
i don't hear it
wow
i don't hear anything
why can't i not hear this
you hear drums
[\h__\h]
[Music]
it was very faint uh yeah but i don't
even hear the faintness
uh
well i think you all think previously
when i just restarted the
game capture it worked but no it didn't
what if i
put this
house
on
huh
[Music]
the part of the game no no no no like i
legit hear nothing even when i like open
the menu
i'll like do something on
huh
oh yeah wait it's coming out of my
oh
it's coming out of the speakers out of
my way
eh why why is that coming why is it
coming out of my speakers out of my way
huh
coming out of the speakers of my way
i just maybe reconnect
oopsie
oh yeah
[Music]
restart the wii
put output
no there's no there is no audio cable
it's just
people
what data were you installing okay you
know what let's restart this uh
power
okay
set your audio output
now the headphones are connected to my
uh to my pc though i'm not connecting it
to the wii u though i don't know what
what the [\h__\h]
i'm dead
and i still
still hear
it from the
mom
[Laughter]
[Music]
um
yes i'm playing it on wii u
as much as i'd like to play it on
gamecube the wii u version is
better
uh
now my makeup
let me go to the
how long are you loading huh
faster okay can i go now
well
i can't go
do you hear this sound
really faintly what does it even come
out of
hello
i'm posting the home button a million
times finally okay let me try to do some
settings but i guess i'll hide the
screen
[Music]
it's not controller settings just
settings jericho
um
yeah i don't really that's just rumbling
and
and display settings right in normal
settings
oh
where are the normal settings because
when i go here
it's just
these settings
on these settings
in the main menu out of the game uh
i have to close it again
okay
yeah these aren't the other dudes
this is uh who the way you originally
belong to
[Music]
um
we're into settings
[Laughter]
system settings let's go
[Music]
the miiverse
compared to snapping me i don't know
anything that is uh unnecessarily
manduksai it will not be done
ah
set date and time
tv
remote
gamepad
where's audio
configure automatic powertown set system
language
transfer
where's audio
[Music]
i feel like we've been looking for audio
before
how does someone know where audio is and
yeah about black it out
tv and tv audio output you're amazing
tv
[Music]
uh
tv
make sure your tv is switched on before
you configure these settings
but why did anything reset anyway what
was it supposed to be because it's
stereo now
isn't it supposed to be stereo
or is it supposed to be mono
we changed this before i remember
we shouldn't have reset at all right
stereo okay
[Music]
it is stereo
ah
[Music]
let
me
reconnect the cables of the you know to
elgato
one
and
two
maybe turn this [\h__\h] off again
where must we have these problems
i shall reconnect
reconnector
you
okay and now
um
[Music]
now
ristato
[Music]
i'm supposed to hear it from my pc but
oh
stupid
i still hear it from
mom did
i still
still oh now i hear double i hear it
from the i think this is how it always
was i hear it now through my headphones
and through the
wii u speakers but whatever
that's that's the surround sound yeah
yeah
okay
wow
[Music]
okay sorry about that
maybe move the speakers oh
[Music]
oh yeah i can mute it on the
thingy without muting the actual sound
nice too
[Music]
why is it still on system settings here
i see a different screen on my capture
card
hello
[Music]
and the activate activate there we
go so time to rescue
burp girl
let's go
oh [\h__\h]
that was input lag hundred percent trust
me
oh
trust me
input like this
yo and i'm holding the sword and not the
hammer because the hammer takes up so
much space on the screen
but we have another new item on the
thumbnail
thank you guys for making them i still
have a bomb to use and the shield so i
guess
we might be fine until the very end
oh um
can i not just run straight over there
of course i can
i can even kill you on the way
[Music]
right away
nice nice nice nice nice
money money money
makes me
funny
no
in a rich man's world
money money makes me funny
that's not the lyrics
sounds like double sound eh you guys
hearing double
you should i don't ah yes you might be
yeah yeah now that you say it i checked
okay
now it shouldn't be double tell me if
it's like too loud or too quiet later
it must be funny
uh must be
must be funny is it really bad
wow look at that it's so sparkly
wow amazing
i just since i beat this game but it's
awesome to see again because it was a
blast
understandable yes where are we
here almost there i almost down where a
burp girl is
please leave me alone please leave me
alone freaks
is that the sun that burned my aussie
yes kill it
kill it
for its sins
you must destroy the sun
one thing we can do by playing zelda
games is
i guess destroy the moon somehow
by having them oh hi having the moon uh
uh
come crashing down on earth
yeah i do want to play more zelda games
so wait i came
actually where did i want to go
i remember
leaving a woman and having her at the
beginning no no no no this no this is
actually where we ended yeah i was
supposed to burn everything here oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
oh my god i'm so sorry how much hp does
she have or does she have endless hp
um could you like come here
[\h__\h] how much is
[Music]
yeah get the others while you're on it
yeah was this i am supposed to do it no
[Music]
okay it's okay
she's invincible
really all the leave i forgot
she's invincible no come on
oh thank you
i can climb up there
nice
that was very dramatic excuse
me and if she can't die then that makes
things easier yeah no need to protect
her i guess i thought i had to keep her
um
out away from the harm oh so anyway
since you're standing right there
i guess let's try to
okay uh let's try to
yesterday i was like already
no wait
i will be here
she will go to there
i think
yesterday my brain
juice was already empty
yeah i think she goes into the big beam
and i go here because uh then i can move
freely
i know i know
right
so i'll just shoot it no somewhere in
the middle would be good
and then
ah
here maybe
oh it hits the ground
and it could work anyway
so
but i didn't have my sword out right
okay
oh oh oh
[Music]
i'm so mad i'm gonna make this mistake a
lot
[Music]
you know what you can do this from here
what the [\h__\h]
hey why not
wait
why was i like i even need his help
i can do these on my own i cannot but
this one i can't do on my own okay
okay
the last one i can't
now
sort out
i was about to call her again by
accident and then
[Music]
there we go
okay oh
special door wait let me get to
okay
how the light goes once into the ground
and then up here is questionable but
thank you for your help
can you
stop
come on okay
let's go girl
also what's over there ah okay that's
where the light comes from
[Music]
thank you for renewing your membership
let's go
i need to do a membership next
membership membership stream next week
but to be honest
i might even uh stream from
the hotel room a little bit
because i'm bringing my whole equipment
this time
last time
last last time i used um
their
microphone and
i think
no mixer
and
i don't know i didn't it was really
really confusing
because
i think i had no audio feedback in my
ears
and
yeah so i wasn't sure how was the
balance and i had to rely on the the
audio team's
um
opinion
on how they
thought
it sounded if it sounded okay but i
don't know like i felt like oh it must
be peeking or whatever
um yeah and if you're used to
working with uh feedback in your ear
every single day then not having it oh
hello
is
yeah
really
uncomfortable
hello can you not
[Music]
pretty strong enemy coming
hammer it's time my time it's time to um
um wait not so fast
[Music]
[\h__\h] hell man
oh wait i didn't need to hammer it
that's right i could just hit it on my
phone
[Music]
old people be like dislocating their hip
like that
i'm sorry
come here
and this is me dislocating my my head
like that
okay there we go
[Music]
ah
i almost missed it oh wait there's a
music thingy here i didn't realize until
now so yeah i was saying um last year
last year at dokomi the
you know i kind of left all the audio
stuff up to them because i thought you
know people perform on stage there so
they must have like the right equipment
and all that but you know there's also
the thing that i wasn't exactly on stage
i was like somewhere backstage so
um
it was a little bit a little bit
actually it was very difficult to figure
it out like on the
on the day
can i do this
on the day before the concert
in the late evening
like before dinner actually dinner was
already going on
and then
[Music]
yeah wait i think i remember it was like
uh we were going to dinner with the
organizers and i
was like hoping to still
check out the venue and
like prepare i guess
um but then
right after choosing our courses
they told us that the staff is going to
leave
now
so if i want to do any testing i need to
do it right now so even though we
already chose um
our dinner
i had to
run out with genma
and uh
and we went to the venue for like a
while
[Music]
i know it even before that i think even
before dinner we were testing out things
but then
i had to test out more i think
that was a lot of testing hours of
testing because things weren't quite
going that well
[Music]
beautiful beautiful beautiful
yeah yeah yeah
uh it ended up somewhat okay but it was
still very concerning to me during the
live concert i didn't know what it
sounded like
because that's like i asked genma to go
there and listen if she thinks it sounds
okay there but you know the problem is
like i can't
i'm behind the scenes i can't go to the
stage and listen to myself singing there
which really annoyed me
oh would you look at that
oh i don't have a basket but
so this year i want to make sure that i
feel comfortable
singing and therefore
i'm bringing all of my equipment i'm
bringing
my mixer and my microphone
yeah the microphone i used
there last year was weird
uh wait do i want to go for a hair i
just wanted to activate it right it's
like a shortcut
come here don't fall down girl
stop following me
come on
yeah and i'm bringing my laptop again
last year we did use my gaming laptop i
think but i also asked them for an extra
monitor
where would i be going am i going down
wait
wait no no you will fly down just don't
jump down okay
couldn't i also
just fly down as well
yeah i could just fall off with her oh
uh yeah anyway
do it flip
ow hey
now we get her
[Music]
she suddenly stopped flying okay uh back
so are we going down there
come with me
are you reading chat backstage yeah i
had um
i think gemma put up like an ipad or
something where i could read the twitch
chat
yeah yeah yeah yeah so i'll have the
twitch chat up again
um
and they also gave me a little bit of a
camera feed
from the audience
the thing is i could not really hear you
guys um i could see you guys and
when i saw you were cheering i just
hoped that you were indeed cheering with
your voices
yeah i couldn't really hear much
again because of the audio feedback
not much audio feedback of my voice and
not much from the audience
yeah so
a bit musukashi
what do we have here
[Music]
all right let's figure this out
i guess first of all we move these
things
um
we need a light beam first
mazda
light beam
[Music]
snake
light beam
give me a moment i'll figure it out i
need to make something go boom there's a
hole up there
secret chest what about
here
huh
[Music]
bro
uh but i think i need medley for that
the button
please don't tell me it's time limited
[Music]
okay
let me eat there
oh but she can just stay up there i
guess until i'm done with my business
yeah okay okay okay
you stay
now we have light
let's there be light oh and i have to
make it this one light source go all
around the room
then
oh it can't go back
okay nice okay i stand there
and i reflect it
ah no
i reflected to here and then there's
something behind there i guess
i i will need her oh okay but wait oh
first
first i will try to do it myself
i don't want your help stupid girl
i can do it on my own
[Music]
okay yeah that's what i thought that
there should be another mirror behind
there
they have a nice design it's like a
crab
like a scorpion
whoopsie
hey that's a scorpion
hey hi
yeah i'm an independent woman
so heavy
oh oh and there's a scorpion sign here
wait does everything have a difference
does everything have a different uh sign
here i just noticed a scorpion i don't
know about the others
okay
put it in its place
uh i think uh wait these chests
were they activated by light or just by
something else i don't remember i yeah
light
[Music]
that was relatively easy
50 rupees let's go
okay
getting rich in wind waker
uh
oh yeah
[Music]
it's reflecting there
is
kind of useless
can i move it back and
no
it's stuck
isn't that useless
i don't hear him everyone needs to go
here okay okay okay okay okay okay so
ah okay i see now i need i need her
i need her now
now she's reflected into that corner and
then i reflected at the wall
oh from here
go up oh
can't climb okay
and then we reflect it
down here that's
absolutely perfect placement
is this a bit it okay it just disappears
like
but it's still it's still there in
theory okay
uh
pull up that
[\h__\h] out and then let's go let's make it
burn
[Music]
do you guys know what i just said
you know and if you speak german but do
you also know it if you don't speak
german
yay
and i will prove it to you
if you don't believe it now i'll prove
it to you soon
what does that mean i don't know
i will show you my beauty um
on stage at dokomi
maybe or maybe it means something else
maybe maybe you're gonna overthink what
i just said
and think it means something that it
doesn't mean
don't overthink it
snow white reference
that's the german way of saying it
and in german we say sprinkling piglets
i can barely think at all same
that's an m
the shape of an m or w wario or mario
let's go
i'll i'll take a bite into my grapes
um
gosh it's so bright
turn off the light
so obviously there's a platform here for
a reason ah for later
or can i do it now already does it need
to be at the same time again i forgot
yes
let's see um
we can turn on one eye already maybe
oh [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
i forgot sick
[Applause]
[Music]
molding
[\h__\h] you gamepad
[Laughter]
kill me please
this is so much easier when medley does
it because i can keep her in place
no i can't do i can't do this [\h__\h]
[\h__\h]
i can't do it
buddy
do i need to complete the other side
first anyway really
i can keep mine in place no i cannot
not with a drifting joystick not that i
know
[Music]
it works but uh what if she leaves
in any case
we have some light here let's reflect it
i saw a meme i think it was on reddit
with uh
good eyes
uh reflect song
jacket illustration
and
and then it said
it's morbid time or something
it's as if that was planned because
that's like the perfect
perfect joke man
oh i can just uh stand like this nice
and good as morbius apparently whatever
that means i don't i need to watch this
movie that you guys are all freaking out
about it's inevitable now it's
inevitable
i cannot escape from it
you guys are using it too
no don't but no you guys are you guys
are using it i need to i need to keep up
with the younglings you know i need to
stay hip
don't actually watch it
is it a bad movie
okay now let me uh
you uh get the chest
huh long no not necessarily but maybe i
don't know but i'm i didn't watch along
right wait let me do this one on the
side as well
let me guess there's an enemy behind
that
enemy enemy
could
let me open up this one first
why is that the boss key in there
it must be i think that's the last no
wait there's one more chest
yeah uh the basket's probably in the
chest behind that big door
okay okay
oh wait there's nothing more and more
there's more oh wait there's more shut
up
i can't i can't activate that one i
think
yeah i can't china i'm getting bad
the connection is so
blah
i don't want to fight all three of you
at the same time
now
i don't wanna
come at me
do it
swing your hammer oh
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
there he goes there he goes
i'm stupid for this
[Music]
i missed the timing why do i insist on
using the hammer i wondered
yeah
that was a hormone
[Music]
okay we need to open up the other ones
there
nice spin
yeah it's in the thumbnail good reason
for me to use it
we'll get this one
uh-huh surprise surprise who would have
thought come here
i want to do like a jumper test
[Music]
your lower body has been
what was what's a good word
has-been
[Music]
tell me a good word teach me english
chad teach me
you always want to feel smarter than me
anyway teach me
smashed no that's too boring and and
i never know to say that word
shattered
decimated
obliterated and i like that word
warped now it has not been morphed
[Music]
i think if i understood correctly then
the word morphing means
changing
[Music]
your
outer visuals or maybe even the inside
transforming basically
so no this is not the correct usage of
it okay even i know that
yeah okay that was easy peasy
smash
warp means anything no i don't believe
that
i don't believe it
okay so we got a chest from then
[Music]
is there was a shard a shard behind us
then it would be a different treasure
chart right
[Music]
i wonder what that is
um
oh she's back at the beginning
okay
yeah and the other side isn't that
active anymore okay well that's fine i
need you and now anyway
[Music]
so
she is going to
go to where i stand right now i guess
and then
michelle
and then send it to
the mirror over there
ah no wait i can't uh she'll send it to
go up go up
no no not that a i want you to fly
[\h__\h] no not that eh
why is it the same button
um
[Music]
i'll i'll get it
wait to that mirror
[Music]
which mirror do you want me to move that
one is already in place
and then that one goes over there that's
perfect that's perfect
perfect it's already in place
but i would like to destroy the wall
over there
can i do that from here
oh come back
today let's go i
yes and then we can do it together
oh oh wait there's one more
another mirror
i needed another mirror i thought i was
done here
oh shut up
connection very unstable today
two more
[Music]
oh because
i can't have her continue standing up
here because i need her to go over to
the other side so i do need something to
reflect it for me
yeah now i get it
[Music]
yup yup
okay
oh
anyone tells me that i'm done now
is there money in here
[Music]
so much green
okay so now i guess um
oh we can have her stand on one platform
oh i'll have her stand on the other one
this one
[Music]
okay
and i will stand up here
and then we'll make it light up
uh please please please be
please be easy
no
is there no way for me to make it stop
oh no
oh no i'm morbid
no i can't i can't stop it like meddling
but madly i'm stopping it by like
tapping out of her
no this is not controls this is joystick
with tilt controls it would be easier
but i can't move the shield
with tilt controls
unless there's some settings that i can
change but
i did it
salty huh
don't be so salty
you got into the meet and greet didn't
ya
don't be so salty
and
come on
you stay out there that's better
hello
nice to meet you sir you're guarding the
basket
uh-oh you have some friends oh no um
was it this
no oh no no no no
wait that doesn't work on them
i hate these mobs
ow thank you for that [\h__\h] packing i
guess
okay okay okay okay we're good
okay now now what about you
[Music]
[Applause]
obliterating the guardian of the bus
here just like that
i want my reward
[Music]
i got his belt
okay ooh what could possibly be in here
[Music]
a basket
hey they stole it from my phone now
[Music]
let's go it's boss time
i should have ten nights not quests
right now
um i guess i can check
um
what bag are they
here
i have 12.
i have 12 actually what do you get for
them
where is she in the beginning of the
room probably
new attack oh
okay then maybe after this dungeon we'll
go to orca
why does it say i have zero keys i do
have the boss key i guess that doesn't
show up under the normal keys
uh boss door
i need to climb but she can fly
i need to climb though
don't you fall
uh
trying to go up but he only goes
sideways what
now there we go
there are a small craze yeah i guess so
okay and then
[Music]
nice
you chickens wish you could fly like
that right
man that's sad
so sand
bar store
loco next
[Music]
uh wait girl
hey there
all of them
[Music]
i missed the door
go back okay
wrong way okay good good
come with me come with me
your little sword is so cute wow are you
making fun of me have a little respect
r-e-s-p-c-t r-e-s-p-e-c-t
da da da da da da
what a small door
i mean it's understandable that i missed
that one right
it's so hard to
see what happens
it happens okay
only two really
okay i have
i have a fairy and a soup
and perhaps do i need you in this battle
i hope not because that makes me panic
um
let's go
oh uh
uh
what is this sound
oh no not these they look like tinkle
like a ghost version of tingle
oh and they become one big one and then
they split the word
but they panic when they're in the light
so i need to turn on the light or
something
[Music]
wow
um okay i'm really bad with this enemy
[\h__\h]
i don't know
oh there's light here
okay
[Music]
oh nice oh he's so bad that i don't have
troubles
aiming at him
oh that works i i feel like i need to
get on top of him though
how
[Music]
oh i pick him up oh and i throw him
where ah at the spikes at the spikes
with the spikes
yes okay okay i figured it out kfc no
need to no need to panic
i'm gonna go get ya
and he keeps on getting smaller i
suppose
[Music]
maybe not the best idea oh yeah okay
okay
where's the light here here oh [\h__\h] okay
[Music]
there we go
and then um
don't wait i know pick him up pick him
up hook him up
and rally like a bowling ball
and attack his small
insides
[Music]
there we go
maybe there's oh four or five more
the yontai
[Music]
i want this
[Laughter]
okay i gotta say it's a funny boss oh
[\h__\h]
okay i'll stop
[Music]
oh
oh oh no no no no too close you're too
close you're too close you're too close
where's the light over there
run run run run okay i'll [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay
uh where are you
i got him i got him
[Music]
picking up older already in the right
direction and there we go
[Music]
please don't let me do it another time
yes okay
[Music]
welcome
can i get this though
i really want it
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
ah
chaotic boss isn't there oh [\h__\h]
oh
okay
[Music]
wow like a pro
and last one
last pin standing
is you
can you change color weren't you purple
before
you want that
[Applause]
string
it's a good boss
i like it it's not that easy
when you're trying to pick up items
[Music]
yesterday
i saw that there were already like two
reviews of my
new single up
and um
in a certain review i feel like this is
not the first time
the reviewer named my previous
singles once again and called heart
challenger
uh i think love challenger which is i
guess close enough later on he said it
correctly though
i think before didn't he say love
conqueror and now he said love
challenger he's he's getting closer he's
getting closer yeah yeah
but i wonder did he do that on purpose
this time and why are there three beams
of light
huh i'll take the heart container first
he's learning yeah step by step heart
container well now he might think it's
hard container no no it's hard
challenger
and why aren't there three beams of
blind
it's confusing me also
don't we want medley to be
here badly
it tell you
eh we can't open
admit medley
heart clapping
oh is she coming now
there she is ah
i was so considerate i was gonna go get
her
are we gonna play music again oh
she's got the toothpick and she got the
weirdly shaped guitar
[Music]
become
dora
[Music]
beautiful and they're loading up maya
they're charging my master sword
[Music]
is it getting bigger
i thought it would change its shape but
no it just gets bigger
i guess it got bigger it's almost bigger
as him
oh no it didn't change shape ah can i
get an update on my sword please
oh the prayers of the earth states have
restored the monster swords foreign
there is but one last step before it
becomes the true master sword once again
[Music]
the power to repel evil who's talking is
not yet fully awakened i think
dad is talking to me
to complete the awakening of the master
sword
you must go to the wind temple for one
more prayer
all right
yeah the dungeon was um
cool
it wasn't
as bad as you know normal escort
missions
because
it was not so much about protecting her
more than using her which
i hope you guys will never say about a
girlfriend of yours
please protect your girlfriends and
don't use her
step into the light behind you and
return to the surface your next duty is
to find the sage of the wind temple
i remember
i will remain here and continue to pray
you must hurry
oh wait oh she was talking oh
she wasn't moving her beak
[Music]
about prince comani please watch over
him for me
oh
wait you stay here forever
only for that until i'm done with my
other temple
they dropped money when you hit them
money craps
okay um
wow it's so calm
look at those sparkling stars
manny connie
yeah i didn't know you could hit the
crab saver
all right uh
the other one i guess let's go no we
wanted to go first to my home island
which was it outside island
no
no it was
i really prefer the german
name outside island right
okay it's right over there so no problem
we'll go get to something for our belts
that we have collected
um
definitely
i am home yay
once again
i'm really glad we can go
home
like any time
i feel like in a lot of games once you
leave home you're not really going back
but it's nice how the game makes you go
back home every now and then and you can
even greet your grandma
when you're worried about her that's
really sweet
[Music]
dropping me nothing wow
all right
do i need to wait until morning time
let's see
[Music]
how are you awake okay
oh we have not met for some time do you
wish to fight me again
no that's not really what i'm here for
hmm
that's all you can do for me
[Music]
here i show you
well why that is a night crest
how many of those you have
tonight suppose the time has come for me
to speak to you about the night's quest
the nightcrest it is a symbol of a
courageous night but not just anyone can
gather them no it takes a soul who
possesses not only power but wisdom and
courage as well
[Music]
yes i already beat the temple it wasn't
so bad i'm glad i didn't force myself to
do it the day before yesterday i was
already so dead inside just like in my
thumbnail
any courageous soul who gave us 10 of
these quests can learn a powerful new
sword technique actually i thought today
would be very painful that's why i made
the thumpnail look like that but so far
it's been okay
both my brother and i dreamt of learning
this technique in your youth we worked
so hard to collect the crests but it
took many long years and adventures
beyond count before we even approached
finding ten of them and we both grew old
it appears you have enough minds to
learn that technique now perhaps just
perhaps you could master it
very good chihuahua hit by words
[Music]
to build a power and then release it
come at me do it okay
uh wait
yeah okay you mean holding it up okay
first and then coming at you
oh
[Music]
wow
that will be very useful with a lot of
enemies
hold b to build up your power and then
release her to perform a whirling attack
with your blade
remember it consumes magic power ah
wait thank you oh you did it oh
you have monster to hurricanes me
[Music]
at last you have made a long-haired
dream come true
oh the joyful tears they won't stop
if all my tears had tried up long ago
there is nothing left for me to teach
you
i'm certain now that you will save your
sister aryl and bring her hope to outset
ah
wait what if i collect even more belts
is it uh
useless now
is there any more meaning
does he not know oh that i already
rescued ariel
kind of
there can be salt now oh okay
yeah sister is on the way but apparently
their big ass boat is way slower than my
small boat is that
logical in the real world
aren't bigger boats like able to
be faster than smaller boats
[Music]
because i'm thinking of how airplanes
are faster than seaplanes usually
because they're bigger they can i don't
know make more speed
i like big boats and i cannot lie
depends on the engine
well they probably don't have an engine
their ship is a normal ass ship and my
my boat is a god boat so i guess
i guess mine's more powerful
now i guess so
um
we are going oh wait i can teleport um
which one this one uh
this one
was it this one the name i don't know it
doesn't really tell me anything but okay
it was correct we're going here
rainfall island
windfall island
is it the city
if it's a city we can spend some money
on the auction maybe which is happening
at night right so that's perfect
oh yeah
do you want to go to the auction
before it turns daytime
i don't know what there is for me
to get but
oh it's one of the girls that were
captured
right
hiccup go away what
oh she's trying to steal something cause
she's poor right
wait which one was auction this one
auction only has maps now oh
[Music]
really
try following her okay i will follow her
i'm really uh you can get one more
bottle
really
ah this sidequest gives me a bottle okay
let's try to follow her from like here
is this okay
maybe too close don't hide there
here
talk to her first i have to trigger her
first okay okay okay
a bottle i mean we haven't really used
ours that much we don't really use the
fairies and the soup that much but um i
guess um oh there he goes
i guess why not
how stealthy do i have to be oh
oh she didn't notice me really
it seems like i don't really have to be
that stealthy
okay
i like this
funny
oh [\h__\h] she went so far
can't be be quiet
yeah she didn't even wait
oh she's going to elvis
oh oh she's going up
wait
you must wait she's so fast
[Laughter]
okay we have to redo it
ah she was going so fast man i was
stressing out
i can i still do it again in the same
night
nah she's not here
ah
do i need to
waste some time
um
mission failed
but this is only at night i suppose it's
only at night time
[Music]
oh go inside she comes back oh oh there
she is during daytime
hey you come on use your hand you can't
just stand there like that you're in my
way can't you move
oops that one too that won't do it all
already i'm back to my old habits and
terribly sorry i really am um
welcome to you sir this way to win falls
outdoor shop chock full of fun and happy
products
okay she's helping out with uh his shop
now
i guess
trying to be nice but she's still at
heart
a burglar
[Music]
yeah she has a job
hmm but she still steals
all right let's trigger her
oh there she goes
mother
it's okay you can go
you can go
huh
[Music]
i made a cat noise
meow
well honestly i didn't move what the
[\h__\h]
we're going tonight is it
very smooth yeah
link becomes cat girl
okay this is where she already goes
around the corner
then i have to wait
here
where is she
okay okay
[Music]
where the [\h__\h] is she meow
not here
i'm not here meow meow meow
meow
oh
oh now i'm supposed to catch her
right
ah got you
you're trying to open the say of all
your little [\h__\h]
you you startled me
what do you want
my heart is racing you scared me
wait are you
the kind of crap goes around the night
scaring people that's just plain mean
just who do you think you are anyway
an alley of justice
a what an an alley of justice
i i'm not a thief i swear i haven't
stolen anything no yet please let me go
it was just an impulse that's all just a
bad idea
well why don't you say anything because
he's linked he just the the the fact
that he told you
uh an answer in the first place is a
miracle
does this mean you're mad at me
could you at least listen to the
circumstances in my life that led up to
this moment please you owe me that much
okay
okay explain yourself
look who i hit you
[Music]
which one should we go for
be nice
okay
[Music]
i was once the racist little debut tent
in this town did you know that
but one day a monster spirit came and
took me away to a terrible place called
the forsaken fortress where i was locked
up and held captive oh it was awful my
father spent every last rupee oh that's
how they became uh
poor
in his coffers in an attempt to get me
rescued
that's right every last bit of our
family for jungkoon
that was when my life of poverty began
now every day from morning until night
i'm busy working for the open-air shop
so as you can see at least i'm trying to
settle into my poor lifestyle
doesn't that just target your
heartstrings
what do you say about the tragic events
in my pitiable
uh
she's trying to get my pity
it's kind of funny it
it's not funny it's it is indeed
terrible but you're trying to
make it an excuse i don't know about
that
and to make matters worse for some
reason i still can't figure out that
slob maggie who was the poorest girl in
town suddenly got filthy rich
maggie of all people
did they
take all the money that they spent
for rescuing her i don't know
it makes me so mad that i want to do
something terrible you understand my
plight
okay so you're
just really angry at the fact that your
life turned around like that and you
think it's unfair that someone else got
rich
in exchange hmm
well i guess i get it you know
can you let me go
uh
[Music]
no no
[Applause]
well why not
because i like you
no because i'm honest
it's true i know i'm quibbling over
nothing but being so poor awakens a
person's very soul
well it's time i quit making silly
excuses for myself
thank you so much oh
thanks to you i didn't have to sink down
to the level of a common thief oh
i will never do anything like that again
ah what an amazing feeling this is real
is she acting
bubble bubble
i've let all of my worries out of my
heart
wow i actually feel refreshed
let me at least thank you please take
this
oh that's the end of the quest oh i
thought i maybe have to sort something
out with the rich girl
oh
now look at me like that i didn't steal
it i washed up it washed up on the shore
so i picked it up don't taste me like
that
it's a tiny bottle made of crystal clear
glass it's so beautiful
i wish my soul could be that beautiful
oh what am i saying when you live in
poverty you can say the cheesiest things
without blinking an eye
so um i guess i should go soon my father
will start worrying
goodbye little alley of justice
and good luck to you
bye thanks for tonight oh
cute
okay so hopefully she really will not
steal anymore because
the fact that she gave me the bottle now
gives me the feeling that
she
really changed her mind about it
okay
cute
happy ending
all this time we're pretending so much
[Music]
these are um normal arrows though right
10 30 and the base but i don't have
space for the baits anyway
[Music]
oh wait a second how do i reflect light
during the day time to go
here in that chest
can i is that something i can already do
i wonder
or does it not
show up with the daylight
can i do this lighthouse puzzle
oh i need to light up the lighthouse i
want to do that can we do that
um
i suppose during the daytime right
i can do it okay let's light the light
has
wow oh wait but lighthouse
oh it does need to be nighttime yeah i
was just thinking like lighting it up
during the daytime
[Music]
oh okay
i thought i had to reflect the sun or so
but okay
so do we do that it's already like lit
up
but not like that i guess
what do we do how do we do it
when you sell bones
do i have to enter from the back
not that one that's not the lighthouse
but it's tall
oh lighthouse
the thing at the very top
oh that thing
oh the thing that's turning
[Laughter]
correct and i've done it
okay
okay okay
i thought that was it thank you me too
we totally told him mm-hmm just inside
here ah
at least they're doing like two mini um
two cyclists
you finished up your school year let's
go
i saw you were also
debuting as a veto book
i um keep on getting
these things from i think dakuma's likes
okay do we have to talk to this dude
first
[Music]
um
welcome
10 rupees per game for kiss you want to
play what
yeah
i guess
[Music]
welcome tutor fleet i'm so great at
miranda wansky look shop for the soul
protectors of this island
so now shows that schools of deadly
giants
[Music]
to seek out and think all of these
foolishly hidden enemies
but beforehand you have only 24
cannonballs that you could buy yeah
so destroy symbol running squid balls
you must score four direct hits on the
large three on the medium and soon so
small
four large free medium too small uh-huh
oh
god i i read this out really
passionately but i understood nothing
uh ate a fire may you aim to be true
that is all that is also
[Music]
eh
is there a right way to do this or just
luck
and
i want to get the squid right
should i make more boom where there was
already a kaboom
okay
[Music]
um
free
splash
[Music]
okay we got one that was a big one right
because it needed four that's good okay
[Music]
now i just need to find a small one all
right the smaller one will be more
difficult
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
i can't make it
yeah what do we get from this
[Music]
okay we got the big one already without
um
wasting anything
okay that's that's a good start
oh
[\h__\h]
i'm cheating i must be cheating
oh i got the i got the small one
i got the small one
what's going on yo
he got it he comes in well then we have
a lot of yuyu a lot of
um
a lot of bumps to waste
[Music]
yo
i deserve some grapes for that um
[Music]
so
excited and passionate once he gets into
his role playing
oh yeah yeah
please take this
piece of what
oh so worth it let's go i think i have
two hard pieces now
[Music]
15 that's a new record of course it is
oh
[Music]
maybe there's more hard pieces in trash
you know what i kind of want to go
looking for treasure charts
uh
so guys okay but first that's the
lighthouse
i'm having fun doing some side stuff now
we already did one big thing the temple
um
we might focus on side stuff
for the rest of the
uh day uh
can i talk to you
i why not you should do it
you know this wig might look like a
windmill but it's actually a
wind-powered ferris wheel it is used to
harness the wind's power to spin in
quite a nifty manner but we rarely get a
favorable window around here anymore so
it doesn't budge
pretty sure if it's not broken or
anything though oh here we go
so if the wind blew in the night right
direction again we just have to hit the
power switch out back to get it moving
whoa that's a pretty incredible wind
we've got blowing right now but the
funny thing about this very real is that
fact that it doesn't matter how strong
the breeze is it still won't budge
unless someone presses the power switch
i don't know why they didn't just make
it work like a regular old windmill that
would have been way better
okay i need to press a button that's it
there's the button outside he said
back of the villain go up the leather do
you have to go down
shut up gamepad
so cute i like the idea though of a
ferris wheel being a windmill or the
windmill being a ferris whale
uh around the back so i have to go down
i think so
shut up
ah the letter is here
[\h__\h]
it is a cute idea yeah i wonder if
that's actually like possible
i mean i guess anything is possible but
did anyone ever make that in real life
okay i did that so
what now
is that it
that's not much of a puzzle
what now
go on it oh okay
uh
going for the inside
now we're at it okay
i haven't been on the ferris wheel in a
while but i like ferris wheels
but they're too short they should like
stay longer oh
i think i have an idea for an activity
for
when
[Music]
when cali comes over
i think i have an idea
what's ferris wheel in germany again
yeah maybe like a dinner in a ferris
wheel how about that
maybe
oh yeah
cause i've seen it before
[Music]
oh
oh it's quite expensive
you can even have breakfast up there
candlelight dinner
oh
i want to do that i i always wanted to
do that like eating the ferris whale
i always wanted to do that
[Music]
but it's normally something you would do
as a couple i guess
uh oh
i have to fly maybe yep
[Music]
i guess you guys had the same thoughts
at the same time kiwa cute again songs
that i'm not no
i'm not that particularly cute today
i can just jump in really
oh i forgot about the wind no that's not
the problem the wind is not the problem
oh
i can indeed really just jump in
oh look at him stylishly standing there
you could also just sit down but okay if
this is what you how you want to do it
then that's up to you
and here we are at the top
okay uh
oh
wielder oh the flaming arrow when you
appear the lighthouse signal shall
return to light the seas at night uh-huh
i shoot my arrow somewhere
what is this platform for for going back
inside and where do i shoot it into
we shoot it at the
at the chest
oh my head hurts uh
no i need to be at the top and then
shoot inside there maybe
okay wait we have to do one one round i
guess
maybe if i'm doing this correctly
uh
please wait
you know what i mean that that elevator
music
please play that now
[Music]
i don't know how it goes anymore
i'm almost there almost there
uh
hello
yeah this one i want to shoot it in
there i know i know
[\h__\h]
[Music]
i don't even have to reflect it to go
there uh-huh
we have solved it
[Music]
i'm on the roof baby
i'm on the roof
yep
[Music]
yep okay
i wonder what it is
can i even climb there
or do i need my boat
let's see
oh [\h__\h] i need my boat
oh i could have maybe uh flown over
i think i have to
oh my god i almost
i almost died there
okay then we need some wind going on
here
[Music]
this one we barely use anymore because
we got the red um
thingy so quickly so early on
oh
yeah that's about right
yes
[Music]
so close
come on
[Music]
this this this is it
i okay okay okay
what is it a hot container maybe a piece
yes
two more
two
well i more had like two until now
two more
where do i get two more
tomorrow
recently dad um
that tomorrow meme has been going around
even though inna saying that is already
a while ago
i want to do treasure chests
i want to find treasures auction house
really is there another hot headpiece i
think i already got that one
everybody's trying to recreate it now i
don't know why
even though you know said it
quite some time ago
ah
okay um
treasures
okay um damn there's so many treasure
charts
i don't know where the [\h__\h] that is
how would i know where that is
ah
i don't know we should we should first
um get all the
undiscovered
maps i guess
um not the maps the fishies shall we do
that are you guys up for some boring
work
we need to get it done guys
[\h__\h] why do i keep on jumping out
okay
let's go
sorry this might be boring but let's do
it so that we can
then we can do some
side step i don't know maybe next time
we'll do more important stuff but today
well i guess we'll do sad stuff
fish
fish okay so this one over here i um
i'm supposedly i supposedly didn't find
yet there's a fish somewhere
fish
please
oh and the treasure but just normal
treasure i see the peas
fish fish i'm coming for you
oh
guys if if a meat is like a steak uh
i think it's beef if it says that
best to eat before this date can i still
um prepare it one day later
when you think
because yesterday when i ended it was
already midnight and i was tired so i
didn't
i didn't make it i didn't cook anymore
eh
it said in german for alchemists
and it's like vacuum packed
it should be fine right yeah wonder is
fine okay then i'm cooking it today i'm
looking forward to it because it looks
yummy i'm making um some kind of
schnitzel with some kind of yummy
salad with radishes
[Music]
visual inspection of the color important
i don't know
[Music]
best buy just means
no it's
it's not best
buy i think it's
eat until
yeah i guess so but next week um i don't
think we have the same recipes probably
because i
i didn't make it in time to choose them
unless you also automatically had them
chosen
best before is whenever you can't sell
it afterwards the date is no i don't
think it was best before like there's a
difference between
uh
yeah eat until
and best before
oh i'll check it yeah if it smells
weirdly but how is it supposed to smell
anyway
hmm
crescent moon
what what's about the crescent moon
[Music]
[\h__\h]
uh
um
one day is okay yeah i bought so till
one day shouldn't be too bad
one day
not stinky passage okay
okay next piece please
it's okay okay
i think so too
oh [\h__\h]
sharkies
and a lot of whirlwinds here
what is this place well it looks like
tingle island or something cause the
face
is that single island
ow
[Music]
[Applause]
okay here eat this [\h__\h]
eat it
eat my feet i'm not beating them up
i'm gonna be listening while driving
home i will go thank you
oh you smell fry
yes please give me the chest and the
charge to charge or whatever
yeah yeah chicken with chicken i know
like there's salmonella so i want to be
more careful but
it's beef so
i think it's beef yeah is it beef or is
it pork it might be pork i'm not sure
anymore
i think it's pork
anyone who doesn't have a deep wallet
won't be reading any maps that's for
sure sorry i also never read what you
say
sorry
and my humidifier the air that comes out
of there smells weird man
it smells weird
probably because the old water
it wasn't much left but
[Music]
yeah there's enough water but
i put fresh water inside today but i
guess maybe there was some old water in
or it's the filter or something what is
this place
[Music]
what's up
what should we play what do you want to
play what can i hear to play
next time bring me one of my favorites
so shark charger i haven't seen you
please sir please bring me one please
come visit me at the tingle tower again
my wonderful fairy magic is happening eh
what kind of chart you want do you want
to see
jingle charts
a [\h__\h] helmet
nice technique
okay i'm not really here for you anyway
tingle
turning around it's daytime
good morning
well big curve big curve
we're gonna check out
the
north
east
oh we're looking at the sunrise together
how romantic
[Music]
romantic and inspiring
what do you mean
[Music]
down
what is this
what is that huh
that's the grappling hook was a hook
shot
same thing
[Music]
there's an actual hookshot
there's nothing oh okay there's a peach
meow meow yeah my cat's meow junkers me
out and then me out back at her every
night the people gather in the hall of
love to amuse themselves by spending
other auctions okay
actually may be erased
[Music]
um extra fast i already have that
i'm sorry this advice is so useless
oh my god
[Music]
have i been in there before in that
fairy fountain no no because there's a
stone there
[Music]
oh yeah
i haven't been in here yet
how did that stone get here anyway
explain that to me
is
[Music]
young awaker of the winds
allow me to aid you in your quest
[Music]
oh more bums okay i don't really use my
bombs that much but okay
the fairies in this fountain shall use
your wariness when you grow fatigued
from your battles come here to be
refreshed
okay
oh we can catch another fairy if we want
[Music]
i think you're happy to be with me don't
aren't you
don't lie to me
[Music]
yeah
i'm gonna capture you one way or another
cool move there's no escape
okay next up um
[Music]
one above i'm going one north
oh what could we talk about uh
[Music]
what could we talk about
i'm sure there's some things um
oh today's sunday
i'm making my new schedule and i guess
i'm making it with the june art i guess
because there's not many maydays left so
i guess i'm making it with a june art
um um [\h__\h]
wait
ah
oh [\h__\h]
wait let me let me go a little bit
further then turn around
because then it's easier
when i see where it is and then go
straight at it
escape
[Music]
what kind of treasure thank you hovie
thank you
oh
i'm so
thanks for renewing your membership a
piece of [\h__\h] heart
a piece of [\h__\h] [\h__\h] let's go one
more one more
uh but um i need uh also what is this
island
what is this island this is a yoshi egg
what is this
it seems like i don't give a [\h__\h] about
the bombs here
that's the island oh
is there a hole
there's a hole
how do i become small again
like this
wow
fancy it's like an igloo
but different
hs thank you
oh
where are we
i'm trying to shoot
are they not to be shot
yep i wanted to shoot them
them yoshi eggs is that how they grow
wow the fairy dust
or the
fireflies
is this a maze
the 10 million fireflies you would not
believe your eyes
[Music]
everything is never as it seems
i see that what is that for
wait what
what is it for
i can't look around
[Music]
what about the other paths
i'm curious
[Music]
oh
okay
special chest right here
container
[Music]
i want it that hard because like you
know having just
two out of four or three on the floor
man that's ocd inducing
should i get something if i get rid of
all the grass here
oh this is the accept
i think it might be
[Music]
oh no it's not
another chest
wow
obliterate it
come on
[Music]
i guess there's just some money in here
or
yeah okay
nice move thank you thank you
thank you
oh
this is a nice island man comes with
nice items and nice money
now we can go up now i'm ready
okay hey is that the exit then
i suppose so
[Music]
thank you for the membership message
so stop and how do i
can i stand on top of it
yes okay okay
[Music]
stop moving
and then oh wait
i'm gonna turn around and then go up
oh
go up
i won't let me ah cause i'm on the other
side uh
okay
uh
last one
be careful don't fall down
[Music]
oh there's another chest
dangerous
that's weird the chest that's so hard to
reach up here
only has the money
maybe it's trying to mislead you or
something
that this is the best you can get in
here and then you don't even look for
the hot container but i don't know i
feel like the hard container you also
can't really miss
but i feel like the hard container
should be up here
okay
all right i think this way was the exit
what do you mean there's more down below
oh i already found everything right i
found the most important thing so
game designer
chihuahua
one more rock
[Music]
uh
this one
how did i miss this one
oh [\h__\h]
but it's just money or a treasure chest
oh joy no crime mm-hmm
what is this
[Music]
oh wait
it's time to leave
now we found everything
okay
i need those for a shot oh the joy
pendants oh
oh oh [\h__\h] uh well
i heard nothing
weird
i look at those dudes again
okay
i'm back to
map collecting did i talk to the fish
oh [\h__\h]
okay
[Music]
um
i got distracted i didn't talk to the
fish
also what is that
hello
ah there he is
[Music]
yeah
what you got to say
[Music]
i feel like we're really on an adventure
this music does so much for me
oh cute it looks like a animal paw do i
have a trench ah the treasure that would
be here i would have already found
choo choo
not talking about the sound you make
when you kiss someone i'm talking about
choo choos
there are no slimy ones so like puddles
of goo that turn into blobs of jelly
stand up and start jumping at you like
crazy when you come near them well any
case there's lots of them on that island
over there so if you see any i'd avoid
them they can get nasty
now that i think about it every once in
a while i see the potion bureau who
lives in windfall island come here now
why would he do that for i to get the
little thingies
[Music]
i don't make use of that potion brewer
though
uh
wrong direction
[Music]
ah the weather is terrible once again
but we don't care cause ooh
we have places to go and places to be
we're also really close to the other
temple i guess we could
go in
i guess
let me just get the two
or all of the charts in the top row
because i'm missing four
let me get those and then we can enter
the temple i guess
i might as well um while we're here i
guess
i see the fish
oh there's a lot of
uh lot of pots around here
[Music]
the next temple isn't doesn't scored
heavy but it is confusing
so i don't need the girl anymore
but who's going to be the god of that
temple
ah
this game is 20 years old wow
20 oh i think it aged very well
oh crescent
shaped i think it aged well
best worst temple oh no
oh no you'd be best careful sailing
these waters uh on nights when the moon
is full
if you like pure self-raising horror fry
then maybe you can handle it and that's
all the info i've got to offer
now you all do
well thankfully it's not full moon right
now i think
and what is there
anyway wait is that a sword
i know it's a person
i bought your sword
on this chest what do you say
[Music]
no
spikes flying around me
help
a treasure
okay
oh that's okay i guess all there is
let's get the
chart from
one to each
one
[Music]
one next doors
stream favorite night yeah you can get
about you can forget about the sparks
for a while oh that was another thing um
the other review of favorite night that
i watched um was like a a guy with a
british accent and he was like
uh
talking about my previous songs as well
and he would like um say them by name
you know heart challenger hinotoli and
streamspikes and i was like did i hear
that correctly
he kept on saying
sparks as stream sparks almost as if
like
i i don't think he was doing it as a
joke i feel like he
got so brainwashed by the stream sparks
meme
oh [\h__\h]
no that was close
dad
he even really thinks that the title is
stream sparks
or
or he just
automatically keeps on saying it without
realizing it
yeah you would be like oh yeah i have
previous songs hinatory hi challenger
and stream spikes
ah there's the
fish funny
yeah it's a reflex now
no but the thing is like he said that he
doesn't really watch my streams
so it's surprising that he uh
picked up on that one though
but i understand if you hear that meme
so often you might really think
the title is stream sparks
[Music]
[Applause]
what do we have
aha many weird small towers of islands
treasure child 33 might be here
[Music]
um but i didn't see a beam of light
um
let me look at this is this does this
look like treasure chest food for free
are the treasure chest like
um always
um in the right what to say
are they turned around or are they
always in the right direction
a big octo
uh could i meet the octo
[\h__\h]
[Laughter]
avoid fishing
am i am i missing or am i hitting i
think i'm hitting
and there we go
kill him
kill them all
they do take quite a lot of hits you
what do they drop
they drop nothing
now what about these birds
oh oh
what if i kill them
[Applause]
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
i should shoot them with my arrows i
guess
[Music]
bird fights bird bites they're burning
up on me
well they will pay for that
oh they're fast
oh come back
[Music]
oh they're so far
might actually be easier if they're
coming at me
that was fast
let me get them
[Music]
when you're on the ocean it's so hard to
pick up items up there
okay [\h__\h] them
it's not like i needed those feathers oh
hello are you showing me where the octo
is
where is it where is it where is it
where is it
i need to follow them right
[Music]
we'll just suddenly show up
why can't they go straight
up
here
[Music]
well there's nothing
a ring of them
oh this is not enough
i don't like looking for these things
man
what if we go up here
[Music]
yeah
infiltrating the system
i think there is an enemy up here
and he doesn't know what's coming for
him oh there's no one huh
[Music]
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
yeah well that was easy
okay
there's another one
don't tell me there's three of them and
there's free chests
[Music]
it almost fell off
there it goes okay
there's more
but wait there's more another one
nice
that was the last one
i think no
golden feather oh the ones i was
supposed to get
down there
making up for the loss of it
you're so far away come closer
[Music]
there we go
and that's the last one
and then also
10 or 15 of those for heartbeats oh who
do i give it to because i think i have
enough maybe let me see
oh
i have eight uh
maybe i'll get another one
here
[Music]
birdman on dragon roost ah
makes sense a treasure chart
another one
okay
[Music]
where's my boat there
let's continue
um did i find
the
no i don't think i did
what did i
oh so that's a circle that's a circle
[Music]
right
maybe is that what octal is
yes okay uh how how
wait i should do it with
[\h__\h]
okay go go go go it's been a while
it's been a while
oh
i go all the way around even though i
just selected the ones in the front
oh yeah they were getting so close
bombs take out each eye and one hit oh
[Music]
i don't know it's harder to aim
hey am i hitting him though
ah how can i am
can't i can
focus on them
oh okay okay
okay okay
well then it's easier
oh okay let's walk in the park
oh my god there's so many
[Music]
on the back side oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
the frame rate was kind of weird
um
fire no more firing necessary thanks
birds for telling me
no no no oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
i'll try here i guess
what do you oh pancaking what does that
mean
is that like button smashing a different
word for it
[Music]
all right let's go what
oh my god
all right let's go here we go
okay did that so did i find the fish
here let me see on the map it would say
if i did find it then the fish is on
the map screen right
if i didn't find it it wouldn't be there
i think
how many joy pendants oh
i
have 18
yeah i have the map okay
and this one i have two
i might need to do treasure hunting in
my free time i don't know
[Music]
need 20 okay
to beat the game oh because that there
is one shard that you can only get with
the joy pen and so they are really
important
okay well
let's go what the [\h__\h] is that oh
let's go into
the next temple
ah and this wind doesn't bother me
because i have
the bootsies
[Laughter]
let me
play some elevator music again and eat
grapes
[Music]
do you need a bump but it will fly away
what if we just explode together
i'm fine with this
i it didn't work
what
happened
hammertown
don't forget about the heaven
okay we can get out of the boots now
i think or we might need them more often
maybe that's the theme of this dungeon
ah
voila
that sign
isn't that the base
um
[Music]
wow
i learned a new melody wind god's ariel
the wind's gone
it's pretty
[Music]
the cookie tribe i know i appeared to
you as a child but the eyes can often
deceive i am the most esteemed stage
i had been praying here so that the
power to repel evil would continue to be
contained within the blade of the master
sword
it looks like he's from
uh ocarina of time
when i was attacked by the evil
ganondorf and this is what happened to
you me
to return the power to your blade don't
you
oh
listen to this version of the
ost
[Music]
ah
i love it so much
[Music]
in that case look for the one who has
the same instrument
oh one of the small
plant people
then i hold and teach him the song you
just i was wondering like who is the
other one that we need to bring oh
the small one
once you do i'm certain the holder of
the instrument will feel the blood of
the sages awaken within his veins
not one way can you hold was used long
ago to conduct on sages when we played
our song to call upon the gods
in those days there was always the king
who conducted florence but please tell
the king that i was still playing even
in the next and in the next level i
promise i will play music too
oh where the [\h__\h] is here
uh what's the island called
where do i go
forest haven
all right
then there we shall go
[Music]
is it close
forest
[Music]
and we okay
get some maps here too
swoosh there we go gotta run boss i'll
be boss but thank you for watching until
now though thank you
oh there it is
oh i see music
i see music
is he right there
oh i hear it now
it's in the water
[Music]
this
[Applause]
[Music]
how do i get behind the waterfall
okay wonderful in the video game
surprising
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
it sounds cute
[Music]
okay
uh
someone said swing into it
[Music]
okay
guess i gotta go pretty low
[Music]
uh
okay
i don't think i can go lower yeah
okay and swing
yeah that would have taken me a lot ah
long time to
notice on my own i think um thanks for
that and they're back of course they're
back
spam
farm them
their items if you need them
[Music]
why you just ran out immediately not my
fault
[Applause]
hello
[Music]
okay
by the way tomorrow i have another
recording for an official program
uh another one
and then i have one
right after dookumi as well
[Music]
can you like go faster
yeah a lot of them but they're all
japanese so sumimasen
i'm sorry
there's because you know official
programs there are no none of the whole
life english channel
would be nice if they at some point
start doing them too but i guess like
they have their hands full
of other stuff maybe one day
maybe one day we can have
such official programs too
it would be nice
[Music]
i haven't seen you in quite some time
have i
i'm surprised you were able to find me
here
you were wondering why i'm all the way
down here
i'm practicing a new song for next
year's ceremony and i need privacy
it isn't any fun if everyone knows in
advance what song i'll play
what you can hear my song outside
really
i thought the sound of the waterfall
would run it out
perhaps i just play a little more softly
when i practice from now on
no no no no no we must uh do something
else more important also notice the
sound is correctly
[Music]
i can't wait to hear it please conduct
oh he's so cute i love him
kawaii majida
oh by the way it was the last song
apparently according to my
wii u pad thingy
there's no more space for any other
melodies so that was the last one
[Music]
i like dad
now he'll be inspired
that's it something like this
strange why does it feel like i already
know this song
[Music]
i can imagine hobbits dancing to this
this sounds like a song they would have
in like the beginning of a hobbit movie
at a festival where everyone's eating
and they're gonna let fireworks go off
yeah
and they drink ale and [\h__\h] and they're
like oh that girl she has nice bubba i
want to marry her
who's
applauding that's the flooring is it us
it must be caffeine
[Music]
i didn't know you were a fan of the
hobbit and the lord of the rings too
this sacred song that you've conducted
has awakened me i know myself now i am
the sage of the wind temple
[Music]
it is my faith to return the power to
repel evil to your mouth
and to ease the regrets of my ancestors
okiewawa please you must take me with
you to the wind temple table temple
let's go see
hmm
oh he's sitting i was like where is he
are you standing there between the horns
[Music]
oh my baby i love them
cute
i want that as a plushie
i want this as a blessing
or figure i don't know i don't collect
figures but
that would be one
i wanted maybe oh wouldn't it be nice if
there's like because they make these
sounds um wouldn't be nice to have like
a wind uh what do you call them
those things that make the wind noises
in the shape of this
a chime yes
a wind chime
that would be nice
oh sure okay we have to
go
up
[Music]
my colleges exist yeah but i wanna i
want a wind chime
[Music]
good idea for valkyr yeah maybe
i'm holding my macabre right now really
oh
cute
[Music]
oh that's cute
no link has his own wind chime on his
boat cute
[Music]
time for the worst dungeon oh no
it's a good dungeon it's not that bad
just a confusing
it's the best one okay seems like
opinions are splitting on that one oh
was that a fish no that's a fish
fish
[Music]
let me get that
okay i'm ready
or this one i don't have the map for
this one yet
take this
most people hate the water temple on ot
because of it being confusing the one
example of oot i don't remember
[Music]
it's been a while i want to play oot on
stream but then
people say you know there's you can play
on the switch right but people say it's
a shitty port
and like shitty in
meaning that it's really really shitty
that you can barely play it they fixed
it was fixed
can i play it on switch now
they patched it when
isn't ideal but it got improved they're
working on fixing that they patched it
oh let's go i want to play ocarina of
time
weeks ago okay
ah
it's playable
i don't play okay in all time i never
played that without my brother
as well
oh i want to play it i want to ride on
the horsey
oh but i'm so scared of the spiders
what's what are they called again
[Music]
nonsense
um
can we like
mod them so that they look cuter
and not so scary
have you played any zelda but yeah i
mean there were times where i played it
by myself for a little bit but
i would never play for the whole game
and always get help from my brother
[Music]
zelda games are you thinking you want to
get into the cave small fry the one
that's protected by the crazy winter oh
no he already took care of them
dude i already took care of the wind
yeah yeah yeah yeah
thanks dale
so outdated
oh well now we're getting a sequence
yeah very spooky
oh discovering that role is your duty
i'm certain that by cooperating the two
of you can overcome the dangers and
pitfalls of this temple sorry i'm not
doing the voice anymore i gotta save my
voice
um
i thought today even though we're doing
some side stuff i feel like still we're
very fast and productive
[Music]
hmm
the nut please is it not
he looks more like a root
to me like a tree's root
[Music]
oh i had to wait for him
the way he runs i love him
oh you know that would also be cute to
have like a toy like this one you know
the ones that run after you like charge
them
and then they run like but they always
suck those toys always are terrible
but that would fit so well with the
style how he's running
[Music]
is it okay now
yeah it would always fall down i'm sure
of it
[Music]
it doesn't really look like you're
playing as buddy you don't even have
strings on your face
me and i hmm
don't know
okay
he plays in his heart okay
he's so cute with the waddle well
oh
i love you yeah let's go
i'll follow you until the end of time
ocarina of time
i'll follow you until the ocarina of
time
let's go baby do i have to call you too
ah come on come on baby
can i carry you too
i love him
i love him we're all the credits no
wrong game
i may have set a title but not the right
title
um
can i control him too
do i need my bootsies
what did that do
[Music]
more escorting
take him up now
i don't need him right now
[Music]
don't set my baby tree on fire
okay take them off
okay not a hugo i see
um
[Music]
but where do i go from here
well first of all let me kill you
dodged perfectly
i already understand why you say it's
confusing already
okay let's let's do the easy things
first taking care of the enemies
wow
[Music]
okay it is a one hit with a hammer
but it is magical with the sword
[Music]
[Applause]
okay let's put a bump here
yeah
explore with my car
uh he can probably plant himself in here
huh
um
[Music]
why is there no shortcut
for this one
oh
does that stay there
he plants tracer
uh is lincoln the way or can only one be
planted at a time
is lincoln the way
[Music]
oh okay now i know the melody by heart
imagine he was like not really not even
on it
okay we have some cute trees oh in the
chest okay
if the trees are like the thing for this
dungeon though like i wonder what can we
even do with them
besides planting them
wow 100 let's go i'm almost at 2000
and uh i guess like
i can
see where this takes us
do i need to ah i think i understand
[Music]
why
it pushes me down though
i need to go over there to push the
button ah i can fly with
him
don't worry guys i figured it out
and then
link can
then lane can fly over
with the buoying void
button
is he even having enough to activate
that no way
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
put them on
take them up and fly is that high enough
well
yeah i'm getting any
why did he not hold on to it
yeah when you turn off the ac
i can go a little bit higher there we go
is that better
okay
okay come with me buddy
it's so cute
[Music]
so cute
those i need to shoot at the butt right
[\h__\h]
what can i do
boomerang
and i always turn around
oh oh i don't have to shoot their butt
up the front is fine okay ah no i shoot
them in the front and then i hit their
butt that's what it was
i figured it out i remember
all good
[Music]
okay
it's safe now friend it is safe
so
we'll have him
stand
[Music]
here all right then the other one goes
up
so i stand on that one to the mother
hi
oh oh it opened up the back
oh
[Music]
we'll have him plan some stuff first
that's annoying right wait
what's really necessary to have it be
the same button like there's so many
buttons to choose from
[Music]
and it even shows me a
as a prompt but it still makes me fly
sometimes
i have to lock on no time
but it also works without the locker
honestly i should have just used two
different buttons
it's not like i don't have enough
buttons to use with
my ma what was her name marac what
was it
and the door opened up well that's
fairly easy so far
i thought there was more to it
fair criticism thank you i agree
okay i suppose
first we make makkah fly
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you
ten members membership let's go
[Music]
there we go
another train we're building so many
trees
why is he so goddamn cute
jacob had a big a button it makes sense
hello if you look at the controller oh
yeah i guess so
i know i had a big button but still i
feel like they should have had two
different ones
is there something down there you can
fall down and get back up apparently but
why would i want to do that
follow our proofs
there we go
[Music]
i mean that was inevitable who would
have expected that
is he at the beginning of the dungeon
now
wait where does he go
so
he young
keep going okay
[Music]
sad
don't worry i'll save you
i'll just make the area safe for you
come here
uh sorry i'm too slow
oh you're not going past that point okay
i'm so bad at this
oh god now two of them
he ate it he ate it
[Music]
okay
okay getting back those wasted bumps
all right took care of them
okay
um
can i even
because i have to go there from a
different side what are those
i guess we'll have to go for here
bubble bubble
we could make a
cow carrot lore video about the baby
because like even though it's like a
viewer i feel like it's kind of
like many people probably don't
understand the history
it would be kind of weird to make it
but
somehow i also feel like it makes sense
[Music]
even with context it doesn't make sense
of course it does
no
it looks like it could be bombed
wow
i guess i can go back on
yo
uh how do i fight these again
just normal hitting
uh
yeah
okay
okay okay okay no need to be scared
no need to be scared
[Music]
oh what kind of hits you know
that's all this okay i went
to open up this gate i guess oh [\h__\h]
um
now we go up
one thing i like about the whole thing
with the wee
pad is that with other games when you
have to switch something out in your
inventory to your like shortcut
inventory
it takes a lot of time
changing it around it's annoying i hate
it
but
in this case oh
it's not even open
in this case
i can just look down it takes not even a
second
oopsie
to move it on the wee pad so i don't
like that yeah because i don't like to
go into the menu and switch it out like
that
[Music]
yeah for the diaz tell us it was
probably similar
ah
would you look at that
huh
what's up
no [\h__\h] way
believe that but okay
did not miss
[Music]
absolutely rigged but okay
sometimes they just have to make the
game a bit difficult a bit more
difficult for me because i'm just that
good
ah that opens it up oh
i want it down or do i want it up
oh wait does that switch it in
oh so the hole is on the other side then
um
[Music]
where is the hole
we'll see the holes
there's no hole oh wait what am i
talking about the hole is here what am i
talking about i guess oh
i guess i'll open it up
for now it doesn't matter
oh julie the nuns
[Music]
um
[Applause]
does it make sense to play it alone here
[Music]
yeah i thought so okay
thank you very much oh i see a button
does this pull me down or does it
let me go up
time to test it out
oh it makes me go up okay
very good that's what i wanted whoa
[Music]
anything else down there no
hello
[Applause]
oh
can i fly up again
[\h__\h]
where am i
oh man
i'm confused i can't go up here
where can i go up
sit
uh
messed up back here
back to the start
um
that wasn't my fault
just listen to fever night what a banger
i'm glad you like it
[Music]
it's been a while since my
last music but yeah finally
kiwa come back
you know what confuses me and
in k-pop because they don't have this in
j-pop in k-pop the groups always do
like a comeback can someone explain that
to me
because they call it comeback but then
it's often
not even that long ago since the last
song they made
don't get it
[Music]
like is that even a comeback at that
point yeah you're just continuously
making music
they just call it a comeback whenever
they release a single yeah
they never stopped coming back but then
they also never really left though did
they because for me that would mean that
they haven't been active for a while
also outside of their music production
like they may have not even produced any
other content they haven't been on
social media whatever
yeah maybe this is marketing but then
it's not special anymore if everyone
just keeps on coming back
oh
why marketing thing west and pop artists
do it all the time
[Music]
i don't really but but for western
artists like the famous ones at least i
feel like it makes sense because they
take more time releasing songs while i
feel like the k-pop artists most of them
they really said they release new songs
pretty often in my opinion
but like let's say for
for example ariana grande or rihanna or
lady gaga they take their damn sweet
time producing new songs at this point
probably because they don't need it
anymore they already have so much money
[Music]
okay
uh
nice
yes we need to go to that side
should we go over there
they perform on tv broadcast
oh no
i see a fire
inside the mountain
[Music]
so confusing because i keep
if at least there was like one shortcut
or so
one time falling down is like going back
to the very beginning that's kind of
rough in here
yeah well that generally makes sense but
i feel like the word comeback has been
misused in
music production
in this time
[Music]
all right one more time
let's try to make it quick
oh god i'm running out of magic
love it
oh
what if i don't have enough to fly back
[Music]
it's not
much oh god but they will do why do i
always run into those
[Music]
can't grab me
okay
i want my body back
he's been gone for so long
we'll not see kai's
can you guys remind me after the stream
on a tweet
people asking you guys for these kind of
things
to write a very important email can you
guys do that for me
after the stream
please thank you
uh
oh
[Music]
we're in this room but
we thought we would
end up on his side
honey
does that stay open i think that sound
means it stays open
mambo number five
i don't know what that is
yeah people reminded me about about the
humidifier yeah yeah
okay so now we're going down
[Music]
i don't like this
let's go
these look like chocolate waffles
i don't know if i really wanted
to jump
but now
how about we just go to that door down i
know that has a key and i don't have a
key where do we go
uh
to the very bottom
[Music]
and save some magic oh god
where are you
[Music]
okay here we are at the very bottom
maybe that's what was supposed to happen
anyway
there's a door i can enter oh wait wait
they dropped that too
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
i got both of them in the end because
the other one was so close
yeah
oh they do
i have
i have 11 of those now 11.
okay
[Music]
farm them by using a grapple hook oh
because they keep on regrowing it
what the [\h__\h]
eh
what is this room
not cool
what
this is making me really nervous
ah
this is making me really nervous please
stop
uh
huh
oh no i need to move it over there
oh no
there's no hole there right there's no
hole
oh no there is there is there is
oh no behind the spike
i think
i know right where that the
tile is like oh
it's a bit hard to see you lift that
camera around
a bit it's very hard but okay i'm gonna
trust
the tiles
please turn it on
can i jump from here
almost
see someone make it stop
i hate it
hallelujah but it's still going on
finally okay the first key what is it
stopped what is this though what is this
platform
nothing
okay after getting the key it finally
stopped
do they have these traps in the unit
i uh i said before that the yojo room is
actually
individually personalized
so whatever
you feel the least comfortable with is
in your usual room
so yeah the image that i show of the
usual room is just a sample
oh [\h__\h] it's dark
mid boss
uh huh
quite a big room for mcbuzz oh yeah
what's so funny
oh that that's very funny that is very
funny uh huh
no problem
i didn't have to sort out
[Music]
you still alive
oh he's boxing now no he's getting his
sword
i cornered him
we're on fire but that's okay
sometimes you have to make sacrifices
okay
[Music]
what are you doing here
instead
maybe maybe huh
[Music]
like collecting farming items
when will we come down
can i shoot them
you should be able
[Music]
i would like you to come down sir very
kindly i ask you
[Music]
yeah okay i got some hits i got some
hits
[Music]
but i still need to take care of the
other enemies apparently okay
nice yes
[Music]
being disturbed by another enemy doll
that's not so fair
okay
these are fun to fight actually
[Music]
go
oh
[Music]
it's getting more quiet now
that was a nice meatball it's actually a
little bit challenging normally the mint
bosses are kind of [\h__\h]
in this game at least
just being honest here
and a good opportunity
um to farm items if you wanted to
oh there's the hook shot that you guys
were talking about i thought it was like
an optional extra item
no no
[Music]
ah that's maybe what those ah those
those round
thingies were for on the wall so i
can uh hold on to them i suppose
time to rescue my car
oh
okay i think i want to eat my salami
snack now
need something
savory yummy
you guys have some snacks too
[Music]
what's your snack of the day guys
don't forget to eat something healthy
too every once in a while not beefy no
no
i don't like beefy i tried it before but
the the the bread and salami balance i
don't like it it's too much bread
no snacks
eating ramen ooh like real proper ramen
or instant ramen
[Music]
okay i just need one
they're connected
okay oh
wow
hmm
these are okay huggers
maybe a bit better with bread actually
definitely life in america
avocados movie
i guess
so many items to choose from
um that's how you get up here
it doesn't give you a sign that you have
selected it hmm
all right
[Music]
it's weird i just took a bite from the
savory snack and now i suddenly want
chocolate
can't decide
oh so now
what what what happens if i use these on
them
[Music]
interesting
can i do it while focusing too
[Music]
okay this is how we can bet get back up
not a huddle
and then we need him to make some trees
here
let's get back up i guess have we done
everything we needed here
no
yes we've been into both rooms
oh
can i reach
no
[Music]
you want to come here
okay didn't drop anything nice that's
good because i don't want to go after
him
um
here
above me
[Music]
oh
how do i i guess i can fly over
but maybe i'm gonna fly from a little
bit higher
that one must either be
huh
a key
or
i
okay
so
a little bit move the trigger just a
little bit
and uh
now up here
maybe i can't go there i need to fly to
the item instead
i can try
all right
yes yes oh my god everything looks like
chocolate the floor looks like chocolate
waffles and this looks like some kitkat
this looks like many many kitkats next
to each other
okay now i really need chocolate i have
lint chocolate
with like it's it's milk chocolate and
orange like mixed which is one of my
favorite or my
favorite lint chocolate
the milk one with the orange
slight taste of orange in there
yes
yes i am
in german we like to say
that's actually cute because i am a cat
right now nascar means snacking cat
yeah
we like to say that to people who like
to snack i guess
snacking cat snack cat basically
auf wiedersehen
[Music]
you guys need to try this chocolate
not only this one this one has like a
creamy inside
but then there's also a different
version of it
where it's just um
really thin plates of chocolate
[Music]
oh man
i'm snacking a lot
on fruit on on salami and on chocolate i
i would say at least i have a good
balance going
come on so far that's too far eh
how do i get up
that's too far
ah
this thing here
and we would want to go up to this one i
guess
now
can we reach this one
no nos
choc it's not salami chocolate ew
that's disgusting
[Music]
this is just like you know
before
when
we were flying around and once you fall
down you have to start from the very
beginning this one is also like that oh
it seems like this dungeon has a lot of
that
that's pretty annoying
if i fall down here one more time i'm
gonna go
insane
[Music]
okay okay okay
on such tiny platforms fighting with
enemies is really
a challenge
quite the challenge is this where my car
is
oh see it doesn't always show maka
no you're here and no
the stone that blocks sandra seems
extremely heavy oh
i can lift that [\h__\h] are you kidding me
[Music]
no sasugani
that is a little bit too much for me to
lift
who gets that kind of id oh because
there's a sign on it
ah
okay with the sign i can understand
excuse me how do you not get damage from
this
i got you
hi
baby
why is there no celebration about our
our reunion huh
where is the celebration where is the
happiness where is the excitement
where are the tears
where are we going to go
over there
if i jump off he's going to fly right
ah to you
let's look at the map
i don't know which way i should go
i just see a monster there
no room
you know what leave him here yeah i fly
let's go here
oh that's not enough
i thought i was falling
oh yeah we wanted to plant trees at the
at the very bottom i guess i guess do we
not need to do anything up here right
now
stunning
can we not fly together
let me what if i
uh drop him to the bottom
[Music]
oh god
sorry about that buddy did it hurt when
you fell from the sky because you're my
angel
um
baby
[Music]
let's go
let's go let's plant some trees for the
world to become a better place or i
don't know
stop lying
let there be trees
[Music]
no i don't throw it like trash
now if we fall down it's not such a big
problem anymore
no
um [\h__\h] oh no
is there a time where
it stops
um
i know there's like a room
somewhere here
on this side
let's go
oh
no you're so stupidly
is so annoying
uh
what is that thing by the way the spiky
it moves
[Music]
okay i'm i'm getting i'm getting i'm
getting mad
i need to go back to the top i think
i think
but that thing
those things are moving
i wonder like what do i do with them
but why do i not want to
ah
because i take
i just avoid them okay
um i'm just gonna
i'm just going to
jump and then fly
go to the top yes
okay i guess we're going to the very top
because there's a chest here that was
totally on purpose
[Music]
oh
panic buttons
yeah but i can only jump into it when
i'm jumping off a surface and that's
kind of annoying can you open the stupid
chest
[Music]
no that's not an item that helps me not
at all if only i could fly like a
butterfly
with those pendants but no
oh [\h__\h] you
it just focuses on nothing even though
the enemy is so close i don't get it
i don't understand i will never
understand also what happens if i do
this
okay
now why would i want that one
oh my god i want to go for the door
below
so
um
[Music]
is
run away
[Music]
it's always fun when kiwawa plays
a zelda game it's always fun to panic it
just feels good doesn't it do we want my
friend to come up here
uh
no
[Music]
maybe
let him come up here
now let it let go
i was pressing
when you're falling can i not fly again
okay i'll just fly later so that the
wind stops earlier i don't
know huh
oh god
okay okay
[Music]
is it really so painful
oh my god
okay
i'm staring but he doesn't really go
anywhere
can you do it can you do it can you do
it can you do it
just took a little [\h__\h]
let's go
[Music]
oh my god
come with me
well maybe let me try to get some
magic here
no
really
sad
i don't know what that was
that was only the second third hardest
way to do it no [\h__\h] way i want to
see a video of someone doing that
normally
show me
[Music]
wow
[\h__\h] sake
[Music]
i'm having a good time though i don't
know about you guys
are you having
a decent time
oh what happens if i slice him up
do i want to go down
oh no it's that thing again okay i'll go
first without you because i don't want
you to
fall into the netherlands again
when i say neverland i mean with with a
v
now we have a th
okay
now i think it's safe to come
wind let there be wind oh let me kill
this one too
not the netherlands
the netherlands of t8 are beautiful
though the netherlands of v not so much
okay
they're both into salad
i love salad
i guess you can follow me too but don't
fall down
oh there's more
ah this is the room i was already in
before why are we in here ah cause we
need to play the music together
sorry i was watching i was waiting for
that to happen
let's play some music
are you ready to play music dude
come on come on
let's make some music
[Music]
[Applause]
what
game is rigged
[Music]
left right
no
[Music]
what a bop
um
good job buddy
good job
oh [\h__\h]
well i guess i'm eating it
are you safe you stay outside
[Music]
um
[Applause]
let's go
[Music]
it's a dance buddy
i am
[Music]
that's that was fun
i was kind of cheesing it though
that's the cheese way to do it
[Music]
that's a special chest what is that
doesn't look like bosque
[Music]
treasure chest always had spikes
am i confusing something right now
you're late welcome though thank you
didn't it always have spikes
eh
spikes is a new item hmm
[Music]
we're already that far for the dungeon
i'm happy because i want to
get be done with it
the item one is that when i'm thinking
of oh okay
i feel like you know because the the
boss can leave leads you to a dangerous
dangerous bus
so the treasure chest for the bus key
would also look more dangerous with
spikes you know what i mean
doesn't that feel more fitting
i need the buddy to come to us
[Music]
i agree right it makes sense ryan oh
thank you wow i am just so
that's genius wait what
um
uh wind
i'm here
i'll pick you up
mommy i'm scared come pick me up okay
okay okay
chris i forgot your name again ma buck
mug
[Laughter]
skittle ah we're in this room again
did i just fly without you first
um
can you join me later or
where am i even going here
just to the end of the room am i not
going like
am i going right
my car there ain't no time for ipad no
more electronics you're becoming a god
okay you don't use electronics if you're
god
[Music]
can i use the hookshot on that do too
um i mean i wouldn't say i missed but
yeah
didn't work though
oh hi thanks for coming so close to me
i appreciate it uh
uh why i don't use arrows because
they're usually like a pain in the ass
to
aim
unless i have a little bit more time but
he moves around and shoots fire at me so
i feel like i don't
i don't really have much time to set
the position
okay i guess we're going that way
i don't even need to go for the middle i
can just fly from here
it was on the wrong button again
okay
i'm
i am not triggered
i'm not triggered
i was i always missed the buttons
because i keep on switching it around i
should always put it on
the same button
but
at this point we have so many items
it's always gonna be confusing
okay let's go
at least the enemy is gone now so
afterwards my car can fly safely
on his own
you must almost miss the button again oh
there's another one
[Music]
why do i have to deal with these [\h__\h]
again
hmm the other one is so far i can't
reach
oh no not that one
i meant uh boomerang
[\h__\h]
god
stop
[Applause]
okay
[Music]
yeah everyone beats fire
oh hook shots here
i hope this wasn't for nothing
[Music]
um
wait am i too far now to make him react
to my ballad of gales
i hope not he's in the same room
command melody
oh
[Music]
look at this little boy he's gonna be a
freaking god can you imagine
oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h] push it
this is why you don't underestimate
people who look weaker or smaller than
you
or children for that matter
who's absolutely killing it
[Applause]
[Laughter]
[Music]
it reloads thankfully
we're good
wait let me get into this wind
please blow
am i in the wind i'm not in the wind
is this really
the only way to like do this it takes so
much freaking time and
once you're on the ground you're kind of
[\h__\h] especially as length
can't believe it
it looks like yo
keep my shell baby let's go
that's how i remember doing it
walk on the ground and then fly up with
him
why are we
here
but the boss is in b1 so below us
where the freak is the boss door i
didn't see it yet
i see it i see the map but
i think
the map is confusing me a little bit
because it doesn't show in which rooms
you can go down to b1
i mean we can go down to b1 here
obviously but then
i need to sneeze
what if i call
fruit deer
how about this door
where does that lead me
here
that's not it
i'm confused
maybe there
okay
maybe try out there
yeah i know i don't know where those
trees are anymore
well go here
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] was that sound oh i heard
it oh
boy
and this one oh i got all the different
ones nice
is this supposed to be a mid bus
it's not a midfield spin on these guys
too really
it's got the conga line ooh it's an item
that's probably a treasure chest i'm
calling it
a trap
i mean the treasure map
duh this strategy i'm calling it is a
treasure chest but it has a small tea
[Music]
okay
i take it back
that's what i meant all along i'm just a
bit confused but i got the spirit
uh
what uh
i don't know what to do
see brain juice already is saying
goodbye sayonara
i don't know where i planted those trees
[Music]
oh but i need to
ah that room i didn't go for that room
yet
but i guess that one
i have to push the buttons or
some other button
maybe that's for later
left one floor down
left
[Music]
you guys did say this one was a little
bit complicated
not only complicated that's not even my
biggest issue with this dungeon okay
[Music]
here
ah freeze
thank you
who said that
down and left who said that you're an
angel you're my angel
now i want the other thing
this one
that works yay let's go
finally a new way to fight these
bastards
let's shoot this bastard too
with my arrows
[Music]
[Applause]
i don't know why i don't know why i'm so
making it so difficult sometimes okay
why are you still alive
oh more enemies let's
go uh
where are you
finally
what
he summoned that skull thing again
oh no no no no no no this one
[Music]
a little bit ahead of him
there we go
okay oh oh there's a fancy ball there
but wait if i'm not in the same room
then i can't call my my car
over right [\h__\h] i don't want to leave
the room because then i have to fight
the enemies again
right
now your name
oh [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay
shut the trees
[Music]
they have a face and a nose
a [\h__\h] up sick
[Music]
my aim is godly
aim for the nose aim for the nose this
is this is the fault of the
motion controls
okay here we have another door okay so i
guess i don't need my car
oh dear
i'm getting pro with this now
[Music]
[\h__\h]
wait a second wait a second
i need my cardo
in this room
because otherwise i can't get up there
i need him
[Music]
oh but the mob is gone he's gone
i like that name that will be his new
nickname
[Music]
hey what do you mean
that's not my [\h__\h] name [\h__\h]
oh
where where am i
where am i
where is my master
uh
up there maybe
i think i think one higher right
[Music]
no he wasn't here
uh
but here
no
but then down in the left maybe
yes
master
i missed you
i missed you too buddy macaroni i'm
getting hungry i want to eat you
never gonna eat you uh
that's a lie i know we both know it
hey i'm finally gonna
fly with me no you're telling me the
thing that i already know okay
uh
well then let's do it again
one more time
[Music]
need some cheese
yeah but no i guess today we're not
making macaroni we're making schnitzel
some kind of schnitzel but not the
classic way
but i'm looking forward
hey hey [\h__\h] you said you you had the
same recipe did you already make this
one are you making it still
was it good if you already made it was
it good i have one more recipe though
i've i haven't really been cooking
these recipes much this week
[Music]
okay
did you leave the guy who had the same
recipes
and normally you eat it with lingonberry
jam but in this recipe they don't add it
but i might just add it on my own very
good really okay
but yeah i might add lingonberry jam
sometimes i feel like like they're
really
missing um sauce needs more sauce or
needs
sauce in the first place oh wait i need
you come with me
hello
it's okay calm down pilava
you don't have to go down he can come up
here
oh [\h__\h]
helicopter this is crony
this is how crony flies around
[Music]
this is how it feels
to be a helicopter
okay okay i need to take care of two
more
uh
no all of them
three more
[Music]
was there originally four
look i killed more than one i'm so
confused
[Music]
um
oh yeah so this is why i need our body
but
i wonder if i can do some more ground
work oh oh he's coming closer
oh [\h__\h]
wait
good night
if you're going to bed
try not aiming we mean not aiming
it's okay i can do it
[Music]
become
holy [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] sometimes i have these
these
flashes in my brain
but it's expanding
it's like that good connection that we
made
oh my god
it's all connected
put on the tinfoil hat yeah it's coming
to good use again
hello no please no
no no no no
[Music]
does it does he stay there but he
doesn't get attacked again okay are you
attacking me now
okay
rescue macaroni
genius
ah okay
hey
okay one last tree please i feel like
we're getting closer to the end here
now he's still here he didn't respawn
but i'm not going up there without link
no no no no that one is dangerous
and i don't want to know where makkah
ends up at this time
[Music]
in makkah rony jail again no thank you
oh but wait
i have i need him
was there another sign that i can
hold on to
does he have to go up first
[Music]
usa
well that's that's very a dangerous game
that
okay let's try to stay away
i'll make a noise
solo mission let's go
[Music]
all right
let's go good job
not getting caught here by the hand the
dangerous hand oh this opens up
yes
i didn't realize we were going to come
out here but that's beautiful perfect oh
now the door is open
follow me
oh
do we go
up to that door hmm
what exactly
ah that one that one opened no
no wait what
i need i need to go to b1
which one
hundred under the fan
yeah okay okay
okay
to the very bottom right
he followed me
i think he followed me did he
dangerous dangerous i was about to
become
a lynx movie
which
because he's green is supposedly very
very very healthy
but i don't recommend it
blink smoothie
wait for the wind
bye-bye
[Music]
oh there's another button here does it
stop the machine
[Music]
but hey that only did uh one-fourth of a
heart damage you would imagine it to be
more than that oh
i don't know what that's for but i have
a door over there and no key for it so
we're going through that one
maybe it's just a way to get back up
like this
uh hello
um
he joined me that's not so good stop
stop following me
how do you make him stop following me
again
okay okay i guess you're just gonna
watch
[Music]
it's time it's hammer time
you can't [\h__\h] around here
oh but at least um macaroni probably
also has endless
health
[Music]
or get off of me
these masses of enemies wait is someone
spawning them again though or
hey let me let me
take care of the fire guy because he
[\h__\h] annoys me
where is he
[Music]
i hear you
i got him
got him once
[Music]
let me take care of him first where is
he where is he
[Music]
okay now
what we're gonna do is this
[Music]
hey really
finally finally
i have the upper hand again
[Music]
smash your hips
you look um desperate what are you
looking for your glasses
you're looking for your glasses i i i it
seems like i need glasses could i
because i just can't seem to hit you
[Music]
okay
love molding
[\h__\h] you
why you're still alive
[Music]
okay that took
a little bit too long
just a little bit okay but worth it hi
enjoyed the show
i hope you did
so i was working really hard there okay
um
is the other hook shot thingy obsolete
now
no i guess not maybe not
my car oh if only you were strong enough
to carry me
i'm flying up there that would save us a
lot of time
huh
i need to go down first to go up again
still useful to swing
i guess so
[Music]
and
down
[Music]
yes my child
i'm wearing the iron boots in this
family
[Music]
hi
oh
what is this
i still have not seen the box door but
we're getting very close i smell it
i smell the stinky boss
getting closer
[Music]
you can take that and those [\h__\h] i
always keep on getting more bumps here
when you're so mad you explode with
anger after turning in circles while
relatable
out
oh oh oh oh oh oh
[Music]
anime boston as well by the way wasn't
there like this convention where fauna
uh
whales know what that's crony and then
ollie and rainey were
going to be appearing at are they doing
it today as well
yeah yeah they also did a meet and greet
right
nice soup
okay that was yesterday
among others yeah there's like chrome
season isn't full
what's the word brothel
uh
cause there's so many conventions now
documents next week let's go
is there something down there that i
need to activate
or is this just
coming back up when i fell down
um i suppose i need to fly over there
with my car alone
full swing yeah full swing
no even a meet and greet yeah then
there's
more and more meet and greets happening
quivrala did the first meet and greet in
whole live english because
not because the convention asked me to
do it or the company asked me to review
it but because i said i wanted to do it
pioneer in whole live english let's go
[Music]
sounds like a dolphin sounds so strong
um why does it take so long
[Music]
[\h__\h] you
come here
[Music]
not this time buddy
okay
it's safe now
is the box difficult than this one do
you guys know
wait that's so cute
[Music]
oh he could fly like what is he scared
of
more wind yeah
i'll be fine not difficult for me of
course not yeah
okay i reckon we have to use
uh no not that the boots
maybe
and then um
i stopped each one of them with one
because there's three of these things
and three cubes
so we create a path
for ourselves
oh
no i would never never do such a thing
even though that sounds awfully familiar
to me
yeah my car is cute
i kind of wanted to be stopped like on
the very right side so let me
move it a little bit to the left
can i do this no i don't go up why is so
annoying
yes yes yes yes perfect that's beautiful
look at that yo
nina how far have you
gotten with practicing my new song
already huh
don't worry no pressure just kidding i'm
just kidding
oh [\h__\h] you think
okay one more
is that gonna hurt me
she did what
what did she do
learned a song
she didn't
did she do it already i was late what
did i do
what did i do
killing the boss or are you
eating the thing yeah i guess i did
didn't i
looking respectfully on the music yeah
also i don't know if you saw it but mama
donnie um posted like a i guess kind of
like a
was there a gap a celebrationary
piece of art
um
for the release of favorite night i
didn't know she was throwing that but it
looks so good with me on that yoga ball
uh can this fall down
oh i need to
ah
[Applause]
i need to make a bridge and then
well
[Music]
so true
okay let's see um
you know if we can do this now
yeah yeah i don't need to stop the last
one i got this you can just run through
running although i guess running is not
really enough to thank you for the
membership bring you well
like
uh bring one of them over now
can i do it
maybe if i was on
one side uh
[Music]
i should have moved it to one side ah
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay um
what are we gonna do uh move one of the
cubes no i need them i need to move one
of them to the very
side
of like one side
block the first one i was also thinking
of that maybe that's possible blocking
them with one block i guess so let me
try to
do that
right here
um can i do one more
yes okay
maybe that works oh it should work
a box
yeah
we'll have to do it
that's okay
but like
still
going through that is still
looking very tough
i need to give myself more time here
uh although i guess you can kind of like
out
walk around the corner
oh well i can go up but
i will move one of them
to one side
well maybe the other side
the right one that one goes faster
but now in theory there's more time to
walk through because it needs more time
to get to one side
well
yeah well
bird voice
we're forcing
making this harder
oh yeah this is the stuff
wait
um
okay
i see i see
um but um
mom
i i see though i see
now it's perfect
now we wait and
no
don't go up i want you to push it
i guess that side works
let me move it a bit closer so we have
some space and
here we go wow that took a long time
but finally
we can pass now buddy wait maybe without
boots first
actually big brain sometimes
[Music]
took me some time but thank you
but everything you do in this room takes
your time because you can only walk that
fast
smartest i've ever seen oh come on now
you're making fun of me
oh my god is the boss door behind here
yes it is oh my god
finally we've made it
[Music]
left right
hmm
[Music]
the crowd is going crazy
there it is
i'm scared
but there's no need to be scared
i have two fairies and one soup
is overkill
oh [\h__\h]
boy
get the boing off of me thanks for the
hearts that was actually
why do i keep on throwing it now
hope that works
um
yep
don't don't even ask me i it's okay
hello fairies it's been uh
almost oh four and a half hours wasn't
it just three hours
half an hour ago
okay then for four and a half hours of
zelda
you must say
it's okay it's understandable to have
some problems at this point can't wait
for document the ramen associated
convention yes i mean i'm not gonna eat
sushi but
uh indeed i need to actually check like
how are we going like to eat somewhere
with with gemma and co
i need to ask that i wanted to ask that
thank you for reminding me
[Music]
all right there are plans for
oh
[Music]
okay
tell jenna we love and appreciate her
she's very very busy at the moment yeah
the boss is very cool really
bring japanese food nah
i'm not asking her to bring japanese
food um
i asked her to bring something else for
me
this time
um
magic test cutter
all right
i should probably change the item
best song in game oh yeah you guys said
the music was good
um
sand um
i see
probably some kind of um what are they
called
moldova
yeah
beach episode
and the sandblams
yeah it's called the
holdover right small thieves now
oh [\h__\h]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
oh [\h__\h]
it feels dangerous
right now
oh okay it goes into the sand let's see
anger alert okay what do we do do i need
to put on the
iron boots sometimes when it like
drags me in
oh i see
oh yeah let's go
yes
[Music]
i make it louder actually
oh god oh god oh god oh god
scary [\h__\h] scary
what was that
[Music]
[Applause]
disgusting
[Music]
enjoy the meat jam while i'm panicking
please oh my god
[Music]
oh my god that was close
what am i supposed to focus on
oh
i got him i got him
is that one of his livestorms
[Music]
making some good damage here
now he has three of these [\h__\h] worms
out here okay no problem i can deal with
it
give me the heart
[Music]
yes yes okay one more down i think
there's one more around there that one's
coming at me
[Music]
okay
the small ones are gone where's the big
one where is it
[Applause]
it sucked me in literally
it's okay
that's okay
[Music]
[Applause]
i'm so sorry that it looks really
painful
a little bit repetitive here
i wish they weren't so repetitive
did you have to come out there out of
all places
[Music]
okay
thanks for the hearts
i should probably take care of the
smaller ones first
[Music]
part
i'm letting it happen a little bit too
often
all right
done
oh no phase two okay are you gonna fly
around now
wait no it's dead no it's dead
you know it could really act like a face
too
that's too much to
[Music]
i thought we ask
battle in the sky now i wouldn't mind
that
raise the difficulty a little bit
it's no hell didn't break but no not
only now during the
game
um
[Music]
another boss on first try as expected
you guys
you guys are so sweet you treat me like
a real gay mom i love it
uh where's where's my boy macaroni i
guess he's gonna join me in the moment
first tricho
yay he's so happy
we're gonna get a nice cut scene now
yay
play it i believe in you
i'll be your master
let's go
[Music]
what are you playing
different songs
[Music]
wow wow
yeah he eventually
lined up with us
the light activated
it's a golden stone now
the master sword has returned this place
once again houses the power to repel you
the soil of the one true hero is revived
at last
and my ancestors are most satisfied
[Music]
i shall continue praying to the gods
here
pilar please step into the light and
return above ground
[Music]
may the wings of fortune be at your back
i don't want to say goodbye to you
oh miss you i guess i can always come by
and say hello
maybe
no
but i feel like
with him it makes more sense i feel like
because
i don't know i feel like um
the burp girl she had like a family and
a love interest kind of
so leaving all of that behind and and
also she was more like a human being so
it felt like she had a
life ahead of her
i mean okay one might say there was
always like the fate the destiny for her
to become that god anyway but still like
it felt like she was
leaving uh
somewhat human life behind and then my
car
yeah i mean he might have had a family
too but did he have a love interest and
i don't know did he have
i don't know i feel like it's a bit
different it feels it feels
like she was leaving behind more
and and put into a role
um that
feels like
very very very big for her
well my car is like a forest spirit
thingy anyway originally so
i don't know that fits better um
yeah
you know what i mean
that's not racist
and so anyway wait is the ship talking i
say
[Music]
um yeah um hello i see i see
i see so the forsaken fortress has
already
like a molting snake that casts off its
dead skin
that place is so empty and quiet one can
almost hear the echo dead leaves fall
into the cold cracked ground
why what ails you don't dot that dot me
oh i hate that
the monsters are gone from the world
doesn't that make you a little happy
sauce
very suspicious
chihuahua i have traveling news
ghana has not shown himself about the
seas since value unleashes fire fear
theory wrath upon him and what's worse
there is not a creature staring in his
base of operations in this world the
forsaken fortress
i cannot imagine how it is possible and
yet i cannot shake this foreboding
feeling that i have about the princess
zelda
huawei you must search for all this
rifles charts so that we can head back
to hyrule without delay
however
there will be delay because i will now
end it here
and um we will read super tests because
i have a lot to catch up on you're
welcome to stay
uh
[Music]
yes
and because i reckon we're probably
gonna be reading for at least two hours
i don't want it to get too late again
because i need to cook and i need to
still sleep fairly early because
tomorrow i have an early recording
[Music]
okay
almost had it
[Music]
yeah so thank you for watching today for
helping me out oh my cat came by
no it was not a ritual to call you my
dear cat potato cat
oh
uh one second please
i will switch to the office in a moment
[Music]
yeah i will try to squeeze in a wind
waker stream on wednesday because that's
the only day that makes sense in my
opinion when like a wednesday
and not quite the weekend but yeah
[Music]
uh and yeah you'll you'll see a schedule
for the coming week very soon
um
but there will be many streams next week
because of dokomi
[Music]
okay let's go to the office
me
[Music]
big cat cute cat i'm bigger than these
cats i guess i always was
[Music]
okay
oh but i guess i should go to an idol
meeting
[Music]
we should listen to the wind waker asked
when we read super chats again now let
me turn the switch off at the switch the
wii u off for once properly
oh no the music is gone what will i do
without the music
rachel
okay i'll turn on some bgm for you guys
to enjoy
how about
fever night
okay and i'll just uh
quickly
well it's an idol meeting so we can
write some just comfortably
oh my god free cats on my gun
really i'm dancing okay i need to go
a beerbee don't leave okay
[Music]
i brought junkers
chunky
[Music]
oh she's so warm her tummy is so soft
wow all right baby
my baby
dream favorite night
are you so sweet you're so sweet
why are you so sweet
i love you
oh
wait let me put on the headphones
okay
that's better
chunky wonky chunky wonky donkey wonky
chunky wonky chocky wonky donkey wonky
donkey wonky
wonky
hi
her big round eyes
staring at me
she's like mommy let me go i don't want
to be held like a baby
[Music]
it's not my fault you're just too cute i
can't handle it
so
i need to read the ones from yesterday i
suppose
from the stream
oh honey
the night is calling don't need a steady
simple melody
you make it all
original take me away luck is just the
two of us
but please bring my cats too
i can't live without them
[Music]
i want like a
long chill remix of this actually i've
already seen people remixing the song
um
[Music]
favorite knight remix anna
have you guys seen it too
um
[Music]
i can't find it
on youtube
no one person uploaded one
on youtube that's for sure
oh
when i look for favorite remix camera i
can't find it
somewhere on twitter yeah there's a sega
a sega remix
which i feel like would actually be good
for
the
loading screen for a while
because when it's like
you know sega
ish styled and i feel like it fits the
pixel
um image
um
it should be an arts of ashes
you know what's that what else is an art
of ashes lots of cute art from kiwa oh
what is this oh i haven't seen this one
yet
yo
a cute this is a shorthand version oh
look at this
oh
wow
isn't this outfit such a blessing thank
you seven years ates for blessing us
with high cut body suits and colored
tights underneath this one is from
tanooki draws i will retweet that
let's go
it's actually a high ponytail but i
guess it looks like a short uh bob cut
to some people which is cute too or
maybe it was on purpose meow
meow
meow so chockers is meowing at me in the
distance chunky
oh cute cosplay photos oh my god
cute kiwawa wearing a mask
cute that's not what i was looking for
though oh what is oh
a korean artist drew oh wow the boing
boings
me and lena on the beach
wow
wow holy [\h__\h] that was badonkadonks
oh nice ocean a nice sky
looks pretty
okay that one gets a retweet as well
that's also not what i was looking for
maybe twitter decides what i'm looking
for
for me
oh
sean also did one ooh
looking good
yeah i like that outfit
i hear this i found it
aha
there it is
[Music]
it's a sega genesis arrangements
that's the second verse
so emotional while i'm singing the
second verse
break down
oh honey
the night is gone and don't need a
steady self on my body
[Music]
do you feel the music
baby underneath
[Music]
let this new sound take over me
intoxicating means i keep playing
wow
[Music]
lately i'm dancing alone
so robotics so emotionless
but then i see you
i crash the
dance floor so now honey follow me i
need a frilling red hot melody oh
something to keep me up all night
don't look away now it's just the two of
us i'm ready
do you feel the music baby
[Music]
i don't need no drinks tonight give me
that feed get me dancing singing harmony
again
[Music]
[Applause]
i don't need no drinks tonight give me
that for you give me something feel it
rush through me baby
can we dance until the day like crazy
about this and i'm making a view
nice
[Music]
i love it
it's so good hey would you mind if we
use this as my
starting
uh loading screen for a while would you
mind would you mind i'll put credits in
the description then
if you're okay with it i really like it
go right ahead
it's really good and this way i can
promote fibonite a bit without using the
same original
instrumental all the time i like this it
fits the pixel loading screen
yeah he did it so fast like soon after
the release he already had a preview up
on
on twitter
yo you guys need to
go to the link and give it a like okay
i'll put the link now in the chat
thank you so much so fast
so speedy
oh
diamond city lights illuminate what's
inside
[Music]
tonight
they have a remix of that too
damn it's anyone i love that song too
much i love it so much
oh there's a
you did a hilltoy
did i listen to this one ever before
[Music]
hmm
i think i probably did
[Music]
maybe not on stream but
me oh wait but that was i maybe not have
listened to it before because he
literally made it last month
then i probably didn't listen to it
before
oh
this was
put on youtube in april
i don't know
oh but wait nine and eleven months ago
he no tony by takana but the beats are
in the wrong order what
[Music]
listen
it's somehow cool
wow
[Music]
foreign
japanese anymore
[Music]
i like the instrumental here
without the singing it actually sounds
like that could be
a song
[Music]
me
oh i like that
[Music]
i love that melody that you know it
gives you random melodies by mixing it
up like that that's funny
it's really funny
i kind of want to hear the the guitar
solo
[Music]
why does it sound so intact like as if
this was just the normal guitar solo
[Music]
it's so funny i like it
what is the difference between this
takana shikara hinotori remix and the
other one
uh i don't mean the
mhm super mario 64 slider but i turned
it into hinotoy
oh my god
can i play this because in theory we're
playing uh
we're playing a nintendo game
and when i played super mario 64 it was
fine too
in favor it should be fun i want to hear
this
[Music]
why does he have so many funny remixes
little banger it's like we're going to
rodeo while singing
[Music]
my great wild west oh my god where is
[Laughter]
[Music]
here's a link by the way
this is a treasure girl
[Music]
oh my god
that you always knew was a remix instead
this is the real one could be possibly
holy [\h__\h]
oh
no okay this one i cannot play
well that was unexpected
that's probably okay
that one second
that's a really interesting channel that
you got there
mashup identity voices is an original
song that does
what
what what what what
i need to look more into this
d
m c a n n
sorry your channel was so interesting i
couldn't stop myself
i want to know what this club penguin
remix is
[Laughter]
oh
okay okay um actually i wanted to make
some tea um so
you guys
listen to this again without my singing
and i'll make some tea okay
brb i wanna read super jets comfortably
so i'm gonna make tea
peace
[Music]
[Applause]
moving so high
[Music]
[Applause]
okay
come back
[Music]
do
okay
the moment i put on the headphones i
hear a banger oh my god what could it be
what could it be
you cannot
yeah it came in the perfect part where
the wrap happens so
perfect
timing
okay i have a big big big cup extra big
cup
um of tea
now it's too hot to drink right now
because obviously i'm a cat i'm a kitty
cat
hmm
i should put the music video back in the
background at some point but
for now
for now it's gonna stay like this
at least for today
i love the video you mean the music
video or fever night
oh you mean the kitkat video
oh that one
but fifa night two right
so we wanted to listen to as good as
fibonite is we wanted to listen to
uh
wind waker ost
um
the full soundtrack no i think i want to
listen to a specific song
but which one
would be good for
maybe this one the great sea theme is
that the one we listened to last time
yes yes because i see it's already at 40
minutes
[Music]
am i the only one who just loves this
ost so much i can't stop like vibing to
it
ah
oh no oh no oh no
i need to control myself
foreign
[Music]
oh my god
it's just so good
i can't help it
what do i do
help me please
so stop
listening
and vibing to
this pop all of it
so much
what was i going to do
oh yeah i was going to open my super
chat window
[Music]
just can't get anything
done when this music plays
the spanish polio does not only refer to
a chicken but to the hatchlings of the
birds themselves so there can be pollos
oppo
chicken or hawk yeah but where the [\h__\h]
is the phoenix
[Laughter]
where is the phoenix in that
[Music]
oh thank you welcome
lpnt you good
[Music]
okay i'm scrolling by the way fever
night after talk
super chat dose
[Music]
i can do it i can do it i'm feeling way
more energetic today in case you haven't
noticed
i think it might be because i really
slept um more and until guillory
right before the stream
[Music]
but then the problem is i basically did
nothing with my day besides streaming
after i end this
i'm going to make dinner and then i'm
going to sleep
[Music]
yeah
i don't know how i feel about that
[Music]
that's the problem with long streams you
end the stream and then it's like
the whole day is over what did i do
what did i do
[Music]
but okay
at this point
um
i want the time to go by faster
partially anyway
wow so pretty
because
it's a stressful time right now just
once although i do need more time i feel
like i need more time i don't know and
in one way i wanted to go by faster and
the other way i don't want it to go by
faster because it's more stressful
so we're reading these subjects
[Music]
uh
okay here we go
[Music]
motion thank you thanks for the pinky
and enjoy it was so good the mv and the
song worked together so well and all
ended up so great i've had heart
challenges my favorite thing from you
for so long and but this might give it a
tough competition oh excited to hear
live without me thank you okay
i love heart challenger but there's not
many people who say that that's their
favorite of mine so motion that makes me
happy thank you it's probably not the
first time you told me that though
um
but interesting i see
people night might be your new number
one huh
oh that's good that means that
i'm improving myself maybe or i'm just
making banger of the banger and you
don't know
which one you like it more
[Music]
but don't
don't forget your love for heart
challenger okay
favorite challenger oh
mash up doco
[Music]
what would a fever
challenger mashup sound like
[Music]
i can't i can't think about it now
because i'm listening to this great
theme
theme sim sifin
mr casper thank you soon thank you
oh my burns are
yeah just um shedding at this point
and they're not red they're just like i
mean i'm partially like
a reddish tan
[Music]
mate fever knight is pretty good i was
surprised i liked it more than i thought
i would nice working come nice work
coming out with such a unique song also
look obligatory stream night fever and
all that
thank you
yeah unique song indeed hopefully that
will
stand out a bit and make more people
listen to it hopefully
we need to spread it spread spread the
awareness
you meant fever night oh night people
well okay that one is understandable
because there's like
a lot of different uh night fever songs
but
yeah that might have
been occupying your brain your double
sonic fan sub count nice i'm sure he's
very happy about that
nice
it is an interesting channel
[Music]
new
why does every song of yours have this
more the more you listen to it the
better it gets effect a lot of kiwa will
especially love the combination of the
hype music but very slow in dreaming
lyrics
it's hard to explain but it's very
really pleasant to listen to
i had some people
share that
like a similar opinion
with me that this song is
kind of like a
what was the word
not slow but
a more chill song
interesting i didn't think of it that
way
but i guess that's good
[Music]
a chill song you know apparently
i didn't see it that way
but some people take it that way perfect
for night driving
yeah okay i can see that
yeah
unfortunately i don't drive
sim 5 is what i listen to when i want to
relax
i guess that works yeah
i feel like it's more
a chillable song
if you listen to the instrumental rabbit
and the lyrics uh the lyric
version
because then it's a bit more calm
well thank you thank you
in the game of criticism
[Music]
thank you for two pinkies mate
love the song is pleasing to listen to
chill by the song but
i could listen to when just laying back
or cruising
kudos in expanding your repertoire great
mv kudos to everyone thank you
thank you thank you thank you thank you
yes yes
um
it seems like
you know also with the upcoming song
my repertoire is getting more and more
variety and that's good
i'm gonna be hyped when performing all
of my songs in one stream
hopefully for my birthday yeah
thank you very much gd i appreciate it
i'm glad you like my
songs of course and this new one too
because i was so nervous about releasing
it but
you guys
took it so well
thank you
what you said next one wasn't a new
genre no
no i feel like
[Music]
in genre
it's
a little bit similar to
sparks maybe
but
not quite but i'm not gonna
elaborate on that because let's keep
this one a bit more uh secret
[Music]
it's definitely an english song though
i'll tell you that so then i'll have
free
english songs and two japanese songs
[Music]
um
i'm so excited for it already because
the the song is really above
i
had to listen to it several times during
my vacation because i just kept on
wanting to listen to it again
can i drink my tea already
please
[Music]
yeah dada was there when i first
listened to it
hot hot
[Music]
hot hot hot hot no you
are you saying i'm hot
daddy delta thank you for two pinkies as
well
has done it again you jumped into a
completely new genre to her life and
passed the test with flying colors yay
what it perfectly perfectly encapsulates
those 80s feels it's as if i've turned
on the radio in gta vice city oh
astrophysics also did a great job with
accompanying your cute voice and oh my
god mama only is killing me with all
these outfits and just how cute you look
in them such a stellar work from
everyone involved can't wait for the
next song thank you
yeah she did a great job but i knew i
knew it from the start
anything that she does anything she
draws she could draw me in a potato
sack and it would look hot
anyway
yeah she could draw me in a trash bag
and it would still look hot too
no matter what she does
[Music]
like a challenge
yeah i really trust her
i'm so glad to have her
be
so supportive and be a fan of mine i
really really appreciate
her existence
[Music]
is
do you mean the one where i'm basically
naked yes i saw it
looks good but i guess that was a little
bit too much to retweet um
[Music]
tyson thank you for the red super chat
mwah four songs for genres for absolute
knockouts truly showing off the
powerhouse that you are you never fail
to live up to the hype of this i love
everything about this song so much it
was totally worth the wait as always
can't wait to see what's coming next
thank you
i can't wait either i'm
currently relatively motivated about
making music
um but yeah after the upcoming one i
think
there will not be some like much music
except for some covers maybe for a while
because i need to start planning if i
really want to
make that album then i really need to
get
into it and that will probably be a big
commitment and yeah
take a lot of time
and money
yeah need to
um but yeah one thing i'm looking
forward to is like
asking many different
producers to
write songs for me
so we can get
so many different flavors
in one
palette
[Music]
that's gonna be nice
yeah
and hopefully if if we put out an album
i do want it to
be physical at least maybe as like a
collector's
bonus or something
[Music]
yeah maybe we can have a digital but
then
some people can order it
physically if they want
i don't know
i'll think about that
eurovision
yeah i'm kind of
i want to do it but the thing is with
your vision um
the
like it depends on the country
um
how they choose the their artists and i
think for austria it's like some kind of
[Music]
tv company
i think the orf
television station
i think they're choosing them
and
yeah i i personally like for me
it's not like i want to participate
because i want to win
um i just think it would be an amazing
opportunity to
um
to promote myself and to promote whole
life
and to just leave an impression and
become a topic
um
i i think
you guys say it's tough and all that but
um i think especially the people who are
european and watch eurovision song
contest
would understand that it's not such a
crazy thought to have me in eurasian
song contest because
uh austria and also the other countries
have put up really
weird
candidates before and that's actually
what you want to do in eurovision con
song contest put up a candidate that
stands out because they're weird or
crazy or have just have something
interesting
about them
yeah just like um previously austria had
um
what was his name again i forgot
conchita wurst oh yeah have you heard of
conchita west
the lady with the beard singing rise
like a phoenix
isn't that a coincidence but you know
stuff like that stands out
and considerably won that year
and as i said i don't really need to win
i don't
need to win if you think about the
amount of viewers that eurovision song
contest has i feel like it's worth it
just participating
so many people are going to look up
who i am
out of interest
and it might come of course it might
come with some
a good amount of normal people who are
like what the [\h__\h] is this
that's so weird that sucks i don't want
to see that
but that's just what comes with i don't
know 80 million viewers
per
year
and
for a handful of those people we'll also
get a handful of people who are um like
oh wait that's cool what is that
beethoven interesting
hmm
yeah
and um yeah well i'll i i will i've
already like
mentioned it to genma and
we'll discuss it again i hope after my
birthday
when i'm a little bit
less busy
the elise can easily beat us in it
what germany
like austria this year didn't even make
it into the finals
they lost in the preliminary
sadly
but you need to leave an impression in
eurovision song contest
leave an
impression with your song or with your
looks or
i don't know with your performance
and then you have a good chance
i think you should go for it i think so
too
like it's really just about
participating
for us i think it will be a milestone
for
the v to being community
[Music]
and um
a huge huge huge step for me
that i need like i feel like
i need something big
to get any further like i feel like i've
reached a point where
no matter what i do and this is this is
okay i'm just being realistic i'm just
stating things the way they are no
matter what i do things don't really
[Music]
grow
and
get bigger that much anymore
no matter if i really release a banging
song
no matter if i
make amazing collaborations that
everybody enjoys
no matter if i have an insane
performance at lincoln wish concert
it's just there is no growth
no
um
big growth i mean it's not going back
either but also there's not really a
growth
so i need something big you know and
that would just be an amazing
opportunity
yeah i mean it's not only me
in home life i think
it's just the big boom from last year
it's kind of
over where it slowed down by a lot
but i feel like it hits me
especially
[Music]
and i try really hard but
i don't see
much growth at least you guys are
staying and i beg you please stay
i don't wanna beg but please stay with
me
[Music]
um i'll continue working hard
and hopefully we can make this
eurovision thing happen and we'll all
all be so proud okay i'll be proud you
guys will be proud whole life will be
proud to be represented like that and
yeah
let's try and if it doesn't work then it
doesn't work we'll find a different
big thing for us hopefully
another thing that would be cool is like
um
you know how kpop
has been like
showing up in like big american talk
shows and so on
now i'm not necessarily saying that who
needs me to visit we had a talk show but
i mean showing up in like normal tv a
bit more would be nice because in
japanese tv
they have japanese youtubers showing up
here and there nowadays in friday mostly
but
um
yeah
we need that exposure you know
even if as i said even if there's a lot
of
normies who will be like you
don't like this
nerdy [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] them
it's an opportunity
bbc breakfast oh yeah see stuff like
that i don't know even like a german tv
i feel like
german tv would be happy to have me on
the show
because
it's a really interesting and new thing
to have right
and then that way i can get some more
european views too
um european viewers
that we don't have yet need to be made
aware that there is this thing called v
tubing now
[Music]
that's the point of whole live meat
expand outlands
no
i would say the point of whole life meat
is that the fans who are already fans
can meet us
german teammate would love you
and they would also make fun of me as
well um
i remember uh
i remember there were like um
tv shows was it may really have been a
german one but i'm sure that it also
happened with
other
like english programs or so where they
would
um follow around for example
like cosplayers and then interview them
and make like a
report about them
but then
and they wouldn't know about it until
afterwards
once it airs
once it aired you notice that they have
like a bad intention somehow because
they they twisted in and edited in a way
that they completely made fun
of the whole culture
[Music]
yeah i'm not sure if it was really
cosplay or just conventions or if it was
something completely different but some
kind of like niche culture
yeah it was picked up by some tv station
and then
they complied and and and worked with
them and then afterwards
uh they were [\h__\h] over
i don't remember well anymore but
yeah rtl there's a german tv
[Laughter]
station i guess we're losing them now
but um
they do that quite often
[Music]
well that's okay i don't mind losing
them
i prefer um posible
[Music]
oh where were we we used to read super
chats well we went on a tangent there
didn't we
[Music]
did it
i guess
anyway uh
where were we
here travertine thanks for the pinky
yeah that was such a trippy trip sent me
back to my childhood when i'd see 80s
music on tube tvs
it's a crazy blend that grows on you too
for me with every watch it gets better
and better hopefully the cassette tape
can hold up all the replays
ah yeah yeah yeah that's
something uh we need to worry about onyo
onyo the poor cassette tape
[Music]
so apologies
uh
[Music]
someone in japanese said that
well
younglings aren't watching tv that much
anymore though and i said yeah that's
true i also don't watch tv anymore
but
still there must be someone
that we can reach there
there must be some kind of audience that
hasn't been reached yet
there is definitely some kind of
potential audience there
[Music]
no
the boomers i'm sure i'm sure there's
some boomers out there
who can find an interest in this
anyway thank you trevor
please keep on replaying until you break
the tape
darkhood thanks for the pinky your
singing is always fabulous buzz the envy
creation outfit art were also terrific
song is bopping very 80s really
can't wait to see you and dance to it
someday now we have two great creations
to come from the 80s chicken mcnuggets
and fever night
she can make nuggets
wait what chicken nuggets came come from
the 80s
i was like for a moment i was like are
you referring to a song of mine but no
what nuggets come from
wait the mcdonald's nuggets or any
nuggets
oh my god and now i really want to eat
[Music]
damn it
where are the nuggets
[Music]
oh
some comment just reminded me of
something
[Music]
hmm
no not the email but
well
wow
i want to kind of like record
um
at least
uh some songs of my performance but like
not record the screen but record
like what's going on
inside the venue
uh
but with a proper camera
and
[Music]
i guess i guess one of the staff can do
it but i don't really have a camera
i need to
ask someone
[\h__\h] there's a big chunk of cat catter
in my teeth and it's gone don't worry
it's gone
not really the audience
more like something else
need a camera
[Music]
small cuboid small camera would have
been nice to have a document
like smaller amount
no i didn't drink it no no no no
[Music]
yokomi staff can do it no well i wanted
to be looking a bit more professional if
you give a camera to a random person
chances are that they're not going to do
a great job at filming
what's going on
um
now think about it hopefully i don't
forget
i'm missing thanks for the pinky uh
thank you for feeding ikea i landed all
the vibes that i was expecting it to
have so emotional classic and reminding
me of that great age as it feels right
out of the 80s always loving
experimenting with genres nicely done
thank you miffin that's so sweet i'm
happy to hear that
thank you
please continue listening to it dark
coat oh another pinky
can't make the aftertalk due to spending
time with papa but baby i'll meet you
underneath the strobe light with other
timkens
we'll come alive and move our feet to
something something awesome song yoshi
thank you
it's um
a little bit embarrassing for me
when people
call me baby i know that like in english
in like relationships
people call each other that and it
sounds
kind of hot when they do it but i feel
very embarrassed when someone calls me
down
thank you though
i felt a little bit flattered there
baby
i love you baby
[Music]
[Laughter]
cute
[Music]
why the [\h__\h] are you doing this to me
there is no better way to celebrate
second friday then with
a new banger oh g song this one is so
sick and hot it actually has
um has a fever i love 875 flaps from it
mama only art is just
can't wait to add it to my spotify
playlist thank you yeah by now
it should be out in every country in the
music services so feel free to do that
everybody if you have some kind of music
service thingy app on your phone or on
your pc
please try to find my song and and
listen to it there okay thank you
silly follow thank you thank you
jacob47l thanks for the red super chat
it's amazing i was excited but when the
beat moved from the teaser to the whole
thing has completely blown away the
music video is far more detailed than i
expected and really neat the song has
been a really neat shift in style from
you now back to listening to it thank
you yes something fresh so you guys
feel refreshing as well
gotta keep you guys on your toes
thank you for listening to it thank you
for supporting it thank you
already on my playlist thank you
cruz danke soon drowsy cat thank you
soon for two pinkies i'll be honest this
song snatched my heart it was wonderful
song that really suited kiana's voice
and tone nice and brilliantly done i
love you my wonderful and proud i see
and i've always wanted to say is getting
to know tension is one of the greatest
lucks of my life
lastly i think the profession of this
envy is crazy fantastic thank you to
everyone who made the song and music
video awesome
thank you for your sweet words thank you
thank you i'm glad you like everything
about it so much
oh
then hopefully you won't get sick of it
so soon
please continue listening to it as you
can thank you for your love and your
support
i am a tea
the question for the pinky i'm usually
more into new wave than synthwave
but people knight is making me
reconsider
it's a really fun song and i can't wait
to see the choreography thank you
choreography is already
uh
almost
done not that i have had time to learn
it yet but uh it's almost done
so we're getting there it's looking
currently it's looking very um
feminine
with a lot of hand movements which i'm
not sure if they're gonna translate so
well in 3d uh when i
do it
i hope so like this is a worry that i
have for all of my choreos
um whether or not they're gonna work
well
when dancing in a 3d model buddy
but we'll have to test it out because i
can't test it out now we'll have to wait
and see and just rely on it
[Music]
um
i need to write something to genma
before i forget it because i'm worried
about it so many things planning for
my birthday um
um
[Music]
okay
no it's not about the email there's so
many other things yo not everything's
about the email
and the father thanks for the right to
attack mom feels like i have a fever i
can't stop looping it i love it
thanks daniel you're dancing so nice
mama only my god again yes ma maloney is
god
god lonely
i agree thank you
i'm glad you like it
well it's called fever night so
unfortunately i can't help you it's a
normal effect it's supposed to be like
that
thank you
[Music]
for it
so
[Music]
the firebird does it again baby all
right for the national anthem of
sobriety
and pour me another shirley temple
because this beat is gonna keep me on my
feet all night
what's that officer why no i haven't
been drinking just got music running
through my veins well tanaka
[Music]
wow
wow you're feeling it aren't you
damn he's so into it
i respect that i appreciate that thank
you tanaka
and yeah shirley temple was that without
alcohol
sounds like a
alcoholic drink but it's not right i
think i had it before
i think
[Music]
oh it is wet
it's not alcoholic okay there we go
i need to remember that
order something that sounds
a little bit more
sophisticated
than ordering like a coca-cola because i
don't know what else to order in the
menu because everything's alcoholic
besides some soft drinks
[Music]
your choice of words i dig it
it better be non-alcoholic not a whole
doll that makes sense
no hito
no hito is called nohito because no
alcohol in it
you think thanks for the red super chat
wow again i'm not able to join so early
super chat yes uh fifa night is another
bangle for sure 75 is a good try and you
showed you're perfect for this too thank
you for taking us back to the 80s love
to see you trying anything new keep
going always support your creativity
thank you that's very sweet of you
yeah i hope to
put out some more different songs here
and there although there's obviously
like the genre that i enjoy the most
right now
so
some of the album songs will be
in the same genre but i'll try to
sprinkle in
some different ones as well
hopefully
[Music]
and when it's an album i also feel like
i can do a
a slow quiet balance song as well
and i'm sure you guys are gonna like
that yeah
oh and what's the vod hello you waited
for the right moment to send that huh
right got now thank you for the red
super chat actually a rainbow thank you
congrats on the new song 10 to the
vocals the instrumental the envy
everything is amazing thanks for your
efforts thank you as well
generous a beautiful rainbow
oh my god
thank you so much it's so kind of you
thank you
way too way too generous thank you ryan
god now you're the best
thank you
[Music]
looking for the groove thank you
diesel
for the pinky
congrats and thank you for the new song
symphony was a surprising for sure
uh
but a surprise for sure but a welcome
one thank you i'm glad you think so
and hey it's uh the producer is someone
from your country
isn't that funny
[Music]
hmm
already got an answer to my question
low-key
uh
all right crispy duncan naked chicken
duncan solar punk dreamer thank you for
the rest of the chat piano plus
synthwave is like it's like a dream come
true i love everything about this combo
thank you for this and all your other
great content that gives us so many fine
hours of entertainment thank you as well
i don't see your name that often in the
super chats at least so nice to see you
thank you very much for being part of
kfp i appreciate it
glad you're enjoying the song
makes your dreams come true yay
oh it's just funny because your name is
solar punk dreamer i made your solar
punk dreams come true
spider thanks for pinky
the new song is absolutely stunning so
thank you i'm not as stunning as you
um
[Music]
thank you
mr ratchet two four two four thank you
for the red super chat
[Music]
i really enjoy
really enjoying your new song yeah it's
an absolute banger can't stick around
for the stream today but i hope you have
a great day and a great stream thank you
i wish you a wonderful day as well even
though that super chat was from
yesterday i wish you a great day today
and hopefully
you're catching up with my stream soon
yeah
got some catching up to do
thank you
for the red super chat my favor it's
rising uncontrollably the song is hot
hot
i agree
i agree i'm sorry guys you need to
do something about your fevers i'm sorry
for creating such a banger such a hot
banger
but
sometimes a favor
is
[Music]
just what you need
a favor on the dance floor
let's go
[Music]
oh my god my chickens are on fire oh no
someone get the fire department oh
that's me
[Music]
oh
okay okay okay okay okay
okay
[Music]
my birthday is making me so [\h__\h]
nervous
[Music]
oh my god okay okay um
but there's something big coming if it
works out then it's something big that
you guys are gonna cry about literally
[Music]
thank you for the pinky favorite knight
was an instant favorite for me i love
his move a vocal style in this song oh
yeah thank you thanks for noticing it's
honestly unreal how catchy it is was an
unexpected genre but you nailed it first
try you never failed to surprise me and
i love that about you i love you wait
that's not what you said
but
it has a cushy that is very embarrassing
i said
i love you even though you didn't really
say i love you oh no
but that's what you mean in reality
right
you just didn't say it directly but in
reality you feel it that way right
thank you so much
[Music]
thank you you're glad to talk to me too
oh
first time
that means you saw me in one of the
american clans last last year
oh
oh and now you're going to document all
the way oh my god
thank you
thank you so much oh my god
you guys are crazy now we don't meet you
thanks for the pinky congratulations on
your fourth original song kiana i can't
stop watching the fever night and being
surrounded aesthetic as heck hell yeah
especially the taxi
you and your team did totally nail the
vibe the art the envy to beat your voice
it's the whole packet
ah i love you you're so sweet thank you
navida mini also is that
is that profile picture the one
where i'm
kind of naked
why are you using that
oh you're the one who commissioned it
[Music]
i guess it's yours
don't look don't look
[Music]
don't look please
oh dear
it's art
[Music]
your name was spicy chicken taco before
why did you change it to pablo
oh am i going crazy
number eight 890.
for the pinky
uh
it's artistic yeah no no it's definitely
um tasteful
it's not like straight up like you know
lewd
yeah
i would say so
because it wasn't delicious enough
apparently oh
ah anyway yeah this song has everything
i love fluffy hair 80s art style mama
lonely art synth and your amazing vocals
this is such an amazing song and i
cannot stop listening to it you have an
amazing range with the type of music you
make thank you i also like your fan art
by the way thank you so much
looking really cute there thank you for
your sweet support always
[Music]
a silly fellow thanks for the pinky
absolutely amazing i've always liked
yours i've always liked sinclair and now
i just love it oh and you're singing
mamaloni's art and astrophysics music it
all brings us another masterpiece fever
night is really catchy and already stuck
in my head
my superchat isn't in wrong color oh
oh oh no
no it's
well thank you so we follow
hey it is a perfect combination yes yes
indeed a masterpiece thank you so much
i'm glad you like it makes me very
happy thank you
another pinkie another
it's not the second one
love the variety of styles and genres
you do with your originals and hope you
continue to do so in the future stream
fifa night you know what you are
deserving kiss now
stream paper night yes indeed
unknown thanks for the pinkie thank you
for this masterpiece potential words
can't describe how much i love it you're
singing it's so beautiful everything
about it is just perfect i've been
looting it since premiere and i don't
think i will ever stop stream favorite
guy forever
well you can stop when the new song
comes out but for now you're welcome to
stream it forever
thank you unknown
thank you
[Music]
thank you soon
keeps getting better every time i listen
to it yeah that's good to hear
i think a lot of people are experiencing
it the same way
but i think that's relatively normal
with songs
like the first time you listen to it
it's the first time so there's like so
much to
register in your brain
um i think it's pretty normal to like it
more at least in the second lesson
and then you get really hooked on it
i mean it happens a lot yeah thank you
and mrs ticky thank you for the red
super chat
thanks for adding another great song to
my driving to from work playlist
as someone who is not a biased person
who listens to set
i can't read it oh my god
as someone who is not a biased person
who listens to synthwave on the regular
this song might end up being my personal
favorite from you oh the outfits in the
mbr are also chef's kids perfection
thank you yes they are
[Music]
when i was looking up like inspiration
and outfits from the 70s and 80s
yeah it was uh
pretty cool to see all these different
fashion
styles
and i'm glad we were able to squeeze so
many different
outfits into one music video thanks to
mama looney being so
productive
and helpful
thank you image ziggy
glad you enjoyed even as a sinful
newcomer
have another cult thank you for writing
the chat fun so potential spies stay
picked
why would they not stay thick
was there something i said
[Music]
are you funding my fines
oh yeah yeah
don't worry they'll stay thick
i think i can't really like
when even if i try to lose weight which
i never really do
then
[Music]
it just doesn't work i always stay like
about the same weight
i don't even have a scale but i know
just by looking
there's never really any big changes in
the past couple
ten years
[Music]
that's good yeah
i know like a lot of girls like stress
out so much about their weight so i'm
pretty lucky when it comes to that
it's better to monitor your weight
yeah but i don't really need to because
i can look at myself and i know oh i i
have a healthy weight
so no need to worry about it
once i have a really really really
really really big
beer belly then maybe i should monitor
it but that's not gonna happen because
no beer drinking no no
ah
a certified doctor that reminds me emma
did some kind of doctor and stream oh my
god
dad must have made her fans go crazy
playing doctor
[Music]
spicy
she cured more of it really
[Music]
really she probably was so sick of them
saying it all the time that she was like
i gotta cure them
in a role play
so that they shut the [\h__\h] up
she's so cute she thinks of these
original small stream ideas and i like
that a lot
[Music]
she plays like she's sick of it but she
feeds into it too oh definitely
[Music]
i'm so happy that you made such a cool
song i like it so much the music is
probably my favorite instrumental so far
love the genre your voice fits so well
and the video is just amazing my maloney
really delivered yes it's like
oh my god can you imagine her working
like for pizza delivery she would be
amazing
because she just delivers like a god
my pizza would be there in one minute
and you know what she would give me like
five extra pizzas
for free
[Music]
pinky
uh
congratulations on a new song at kfp
once again we are proud with a banger at
first i thought it would be a chill song
but as with sparks
i fully got this song after some
loops uh-huh by the way see you next
week at dokomi let's live up the stage
let's go you're gonna be there too
looking forward to having all of you
there let's fill up the hall completely
i think last year there were regulations
um to keep some space in between the
seats and they didn't let in so many
people but i hope this this year i want
to see a full
a full haul
[Music]
i want to be i want to see people
sitting on each other's laps
[Music]
chickens
about you
kfb jim kings you need to really try to
be early i don't know if you saw the
schedule
but i'm like after the opening i think
i'm like the first act
it's kind of weird
um kind of wanted to be the last one but
i don't know but apparently we're going
first
um so you know you have to consider the
fact that you need to
stand in line to get in
and then
yeah immediately make your way to the
hall so ah that's
[Music]
i really hope you all can make it
inside
yeah it's pretty early
[Music]
that's actually pretty wearing for me
that
all of the kfc make it in i have a
feeling that a lot of
randoms which is that's cool too you
know having new people watching me but
no one everyone can't fit to make it in
for sure you know especially the ones
who came from so far
[Music]
so
yeah just to be safe
line up as early as you can
no i don't know how early
people will start lining up in front of
the venue
i don't know how it is normally because
i'm not the type of person to line up in
front of a convention before it even
starts usually except if it's comic
market
or tokyo game show
i hope you guys won't make it in
[Music]
now wake up berlin
line up early
and then even if you ended up being so
early and then inside there's maybe not
so much of a trouble getting into the
halls and you can still
spend some time
um
i guess going to the to a booth actually
i think i'm am i not also in the opening
show or something
like in some
panel before my performance i don't even
know for sure
where is that afterwards
um
11 am yeah i think my concert is at 11
00 am
[Music]
and uh
the panel is much later oh okay
i wish it was the other way around to be
honest less stressful
[Music]
but i guess the later it gets you always
have this
um
chance that maybe there's a lot of
people just staying in the hall in the
venue inside the
the stage
um
the whole time throughout the whole
program just because they're
i don't know too lazy to go see
something else so they just stay for the
whole program and that's all they do in
the convention so they just take up
those seats for the whole day
so if we're in the beginning then
maybe that's less of a problem i don't
know
yeah go early everybody
worst case if you don't make it into the
hall you can still like stand outside
the hall and then watch it on twitch
i know it's not the ideal way to do it
but it's one way to do it
the worst case
scenario
[Music]
yeah at least you won't be like
completely deprived of seeing the
performance
and i think currently with the autograph
cards
um what we're gonna do is
and i want you guys to spread this to
the meet and greet applicants if they're
not here and if you know somebody who
applied
um
i will sign
a card
probably also with the name yeah most
likely also with the name of the
applicant for every single applicant
and
it will be
able you guys will be able to collect it
either at the meet and greet if you're
part of the meet and greet or
maybe
um at either the whole life booth or the
fan booth
i don't know yet which one and uh when i
say fanbooth then dominique probably
doesn't even know about me thinking
about that but i'm just thinking um um
one of the booths will surely comply
and then basically what you can do is if
you're an applicant then you know that
you applied so you know now that you're
supposed to get a card so uh you can
walk up to the booth and you'll be like
hello this is my name where's my card
and then whoever has the cards will go
through all of the cards which will be
you many cards
and then give you your card okay
[Music]
yes
that's how we're gonna do it now you
might not
know oh yeah right you might not know
which name
i will write on it because there's like
you guys signed up with like a twitter
handle a youtube handle
and your real name and all of that
i need to decide one thing so you guys
know which name to say at the
at the booth huh
should i
the real names have a higher chance to
overlap with others the real names
maybe i should write the
twitter or youtube
names
yeah like a nickname
[Music]
don't use my real name okay yeah
username some people only had twitter
um
accounts in the application and some
only had youtube accounts
so in that case i will choose either of
them but if there's both then
i will go for your youtube name
how about that
but for example if your name if your
youtube name is
deal guinness emmanuel cruz
then i will only write probably probably
deal guinness or the old guinness
emanuel
if it's that long or if it's lord evil
kfp winemaker then i will only write
lord evoke okay
okay
just so you know i will maybe
write this on twitter as well
but i think
this way
you the applicants should be able to get
their card safely
[Music]
oh yeah they might want to show the
picture online that's true yeah okay
okay
[Music]
ah okay
and where was i
um
here
i want more i want more repertoire to
choose from
for concerts and all that
yeah
that's why i'm also pushing to get more
songs out
cause now for my birthday life i'm also
gonna sing some
non-originals
i wanna be able to one day have a one
hour concert with only original
so random collusion thank you for the
support we'll get there
yahoo
we love listening to you sing in any
language but still 5's so good i love
this thank you
it was fun singing the song live
yesterday
yeah
definitely
a fun song to sing but i keep on singing
the
harmonies the more you guys will listen
to the song the more you will notice a
difference i think the first time i sang
it yesterday i think for a lot of your
guys's ears it was so fresh so i didn't
notice but
i've been singing singing the harmonies
a lot
[Music]
but it's so natural it's blending in
nicely
[Music]
thank you for the red super chat
congratulations to the great new
original song it's been so long i really
love the sound and vibe and your voice
really fits well of filament
thank you
[Music]
i'm glad you're enjoying it it's indeed
been very long
i hope
we don't have such a long break between
releases anymore
um but
i gotta work hard yeah please continue
supporting me
feel and leave and dank online questions
[Music]
my flaming lesbianism jackasheen
interesting
[Music]
on the new song here i absolutely love
it hope it doesn't discourage you from
making japanese songs because i love
those two thank you
for singles i might continue making
english songs but maybe for an album
song
i can
dip into japanese songs again personally
[Music]
i'm glad you're open to it thank you
because i also really still enjoy
singing japanese a lot
and i do want to make some more of those
typical idol songs and i feel like they
just sound better in japanese um
[Music]
thank you guys thank you
because the idol songs are just so hype
when performing they're just so easy to
vibe too
so
i need to make more
hmm
korean name
[Music]
can i request a bullet happy birthday to
rs rskfb onion and his super chat is
somewhere out there oh no i just see you
molly's super dead oh that's so sweet of
you naveed
oh no
rs
arrest my man oh my girl
happy birthday birthday
oh he had to go oh no
give him the time stamp
happy birthday to you
happy birthday to you happy birthday
dear rss
happy birthday to you
thank you
i'm sorry that i
skipped this give it up to you
sorry
um
[Music]
oh
what is his profile picture is that jojo
or what
this tech
bought by thick zero thank you
thank you
skye thanks for the pinky i love your
new song this style fit you so well and
get the chance of meeting great let's go
skye oh exciting
yay
i'm so happy because you come so far
from so far away i'm really glad that
you're part of the meet and greet
good for you
that makes the trip worth it right
oh god
says donkey shooting great victory one
five one zero donkey shooting scratch
super snake mario thank you for the red
super chat i can i love fever knight
it's such a banger song speaking of
songs one of your songs really helped me
while i was at work again this time i
was having a busy day at work and i was
stressing me out but then i found myself
singing heart challenge and felt better
oh come on
that's so sweet don't you mean love
conqueror though
i think you got the name wrong
no no no thank you very much i'm so
happy you randomly just
find yourself singing my songs it's an
honor
very sweet
i feel flattered thank you
[Music]
martin belgium thank you soon
cyrux thank you for the rest of the chat
one second let me finish my tea because
it's getting cold
uh
[Music]
oh my god there's still so much in there
it's already cold
dominic no wait sorry facebook writes a
picture the new song is great uh listen
to it while driving home from work and
it's just so good definitely my new
favorite song amazing work once again
tanto
a new favorite song
wow thank you
that's great to hear oh
thank you
thank you thank you thank you i'm glad
you like it so much
and um
yeah
thank you for supporting my music
yeah that fish and siri
i think you'll probably also be
uh dokomi right
so look forward to hearing your new
favorite song live on stage there
thank you
dominique
i'm done with that
yeah and it's not even 10 p.m
i think we can read the ones from today
as well
yo
let's go
oh
god so i look so [\h__\h] scary
i i showed this in the pre-chat but
there was a
this version too
which is not so scary
um
but i felt like you know
want to make my thumbnails look
interesting
oh my god
a terrifying state of takanawa
it's just me being tired
oh my god they're asleep for a week yeah
well
this is what happens when you have a
healthy sleep schedule you look like
this
terrifying
that's why you shouldn't have a half
received schedule just kidding
mr cat speaks
thank you for two pinkies plus you
mentioned possibly having three days
three weeks in june due to having lots
to do
now i wanna do minimum four though
i don't want to speak for the other
chimpkins but i support this
we love your content but we love you
more do what you're gonna do to make it
to birthday
well apparently i'm gonna work with some
kid now boss may have a job title to add
to my name anything you like bus no
preferences a job title
[Music]
um
how about um
babysitter
can't be babysitter for all the small
chimpkins you because you seem to be
really good at taking care of people
i don't think we have a babysitter yet
for the babies yeah the chicks
the chicks
the chicks and kfb
exeter
no i'm the accident because i sit on
them at all times
but the ones that just hatched
they're running around like crazy we
need someone who babysits them
child care services let's go
[Music]
i don't want to be sat on well it's okay
you're not an egg currently
oh that was fast you changed it so fast
[Music]
wow
nice looking good looks so official
[Music]
nice
speed
and thank you for the topic is a kiss
for you
congratulations on your new job and
i think
uh yeah well i mean i said that i will
be using the time to learn
choreographies but it might also be
an opportunity for me to recharge
partially as well during a very
stressful time
um
yeah recharge a little bit and
have more to tangent on later on perhaps
well
[Music]
yeah
i'll try to not go on the four streams
though
so
well originally we recently had a lot of
five stream weeks
that will go down
to four maybe maybe after talking me
perhaps but but actually you know
documents
week might also not have so many streams
it might start
coming from next week and i'm
breaking my heart but i need to learn
those choreos
if i uh end up like having them all down
early then
we can go back to normal streaming
as soon as that happens yeah
or as soon as i'm done with the
recording
[Music]
thank you guys but i'll try my best and
then show you a great result at the
end
and you guys will be very proud of
kiwawa
hopefully
putting pressure on myself
yeah
thanks vortex
just keep liking for two
pinkies oh no
i was initially sad about not getting
into the meet and greet this year can't
deny those selfish feelings but seeing
you push yourself and almost unhealthy
degree to get as many as possible in
this year
and still give to those who didn't get
in was just so heartwarming to see i see
so many tweets of character who got in
and are getting the same
and are getting to experience the same
wonderful feeling i got to experience
last year i'm no longer sad and just
feel a lot of love for you and kfp now
thank you cara for being you oh
[Music]
oh
thank you yeah it breaks my heart then i
can't like
take the time to see every single one of
you
but unfortunately time is limited
yeah i already am doing
way more than
originally
the staff and the management intended
for me to do
so
yeah
i'm trying my best and yeah
hopefully um i can make up for it for
the ones who didn't get in with
the signed cards um
yeah
thank you swarovski please hope you're
gonna enjoy the convention i think you
will
thank you for two pinkies my aussie i
found you again for a second time
i'm so so so so sorry because i promised
you i wouldn't be there this time what
do you mean you will be there
even if it's not for the meet and greet
you'll be at the doko me right i tried
my best but no luck tokum is the only
con i can go cause of reason i told you
before so i promise all my life i try
again next year they said third time as
a child but with a little bit of
feelings like this become true yeah
third time is a charm i won't give up i
will be revived chicken by the time next
door can be happened so i bet my phoenix
luck increases too oh yeah it could be
it's your happy time and good memories
best birth thank you but yeah you're
still gonna go to dokomi so you'll see
the concert you get a free autograph
card
so and you can watch the panel you can
go to the booth and meet with kf people
so
i think you'll make the most out of it
anyway and it will be a great experience
anyway
oh
so don't
don't um what's the word
lasting company hanging
thank you
tai chi thank you
oh dear a double rainbow
it's more like a thick rainbow because
it's not like
you repeated the rainbow
but you're putting everything twice one
after another
two reds two pinkies and so on
that's that's a fake rainbow
damn
mate
[Music]
oh it's oh it's savage it's you
when i come back i will probably be
forgotten from you but i will always
remember kiara and cheer up
and challenge my dream
and we'll be back with a smile see you
some future day savage kfc software
spencer pepper's doing what happened
with the pepper
oh eh what what what happened oh wait i
write you out this one first hello kitty
i came to preach that because i missed
my kfp family a long time maybe it will
be two or three years before i get back
for kfb
that's a long time
will i be there until i came back as a
racer not an agent so busy days but it
was nice to listen to the fever night
while driving at 9.
well
it's your freedom you're allowed to
go and do other things even though it
makes me a bit sad
but you um
should at least please
continue following me on twitter so you
get some updates so if something really
big happens
you should
okay
you don't have to watch my streams
actively but maybe just you know keep an
eye
on what's going on huh
please
and have fun drift doing
yeah fever night is a good sound to
listen to on the road so
listen to it while drifting away from me
so sad
i already said goodbye like weeks ago
now you're here saying goodbye again you
want to break my heart twice
good luck i hope to see you again
thank you for
holy [\h__\h] the huge rainbow thank you
[Music]
no more normal comes only
onion
[Music]
is
thank you for the red super chat hey
thank you congratulations on your new
song sorry i'm a bit late but i'm here
just want to say that i really love the
80s vibe and especially the tight body
suit design that was just blessed yes
also i'm so glad i can watch your life
to fall asleep in the oven again
oh no please don't fall asleep or you
will have the same thing happen to your
body that happened to my
parmesan chicken yesterday
you'll end up being completely burnt we
don't want that
be careful don't fall asleep
no no no no sleeping in the oven
okay
jeez i thought i
told you guys that when you were little
chicks
[Music]
exactly
thank you felix
[Music]
scratch cut me out and cushion not
applicable duncan pilot evergreen
what you got married with n a
what does that mean
just want to say got married with n a
thanks to you
right
is this like did you actually get
married with with someone
oh just got married to violet thank you
but you guys are just joking right
[Music]
you guys are joking right
of course it's not that's not
necessarily and of course because like
sometimes people
meet on the internet and then ben
i mean i mean
bam
[Laughter]
[\h__\h] i mean like bam surprise
[Music]
thank you
cake thank you the red super chat nice
to see you again
hi how's it going
you enjoying the new song
hmm
so quiet again cake
and blink twice if it's your new
favorite song
[Music]
thank you
oh employee number
the one you have at the back of your
name already looks like an employee
number
we should use that one
one five one zero
what's your number now
the koala universe sanchez thank you you
also want one
five
four
your father would be another five no
it's five five five four
[Music]
oh my god i'm i'm ready to refresh
and see what else came in since the last
time
oh my god um
ah
not so much nice how about dan kashin
sirik donkey shin wiki chillin swings on
the pinkie i'm in love with fibonacci
and how you always try new genres i
totally dig that it is aesthetic mama
luna's outfits are the icing on the cake
and you look so sultry
proud of you as always buzz p.s i have
her out of you from lone alpha minutes
as my sales background oh yeah her remix
artworks are also so good i love them
yeah
thank you thank you very much
[Music]
i
can totally relate to you
yeah
especially the lone alpha one yeah cause
that one is like so girly and pretty and
cute
i have to
agree with you
kamiloni yes
paper lonely
thank you thank you thank you thank
you duncan may believe 2501
looking for the top down question
thank you
it may believe 2501 thanks to the pinkie
pie or not makes me feel like i should
be watching an old ova
from the 80s on the vhs at midnight with
somebody's munching on pocky chips and
drinking soda
hopefully um
what's it called again
[Music]
[\h__\h] what was it again
that japanese soda that they drink at
festivals
uh the one with the ball that you pop
[Music]
i forgot
lemonade yes you should be drinking
lemonade
i think yeah i'm gonna have something
very nostalgic and retro wish about it
too
it definitely has been around for a long
time and it's something you can always
find in like retro old nostalgic sweet
shops in japan
[Music]
um
if you guys haven't had lemonade before
and you're going to dokomi you can
probably get it um either at dokomi or
in the
restaurants in the city
and in the supermarkets in the city
i've seen it yeah when we went for the
asian supermarkets
in that main street
there was definitely ramona being sold
there
probably not only in
not only darium there might be an
asian shop
in your
region that sells it
[Music]
at your local supermarket
that's something we don't have in our
local supermarkets
there's a bella that isn't for the pinky
fever that has got to be one of my
favorites i've been replaying it since
its release i'm a fan of the 80s music
in style so this might take my number
one spot looking forward to more music
from you thank you
wow
another one that says it's their
favorite and it's so nice to hear really
thank you
please enjoy it as much as you can
and maybe share it with your friends
[Music]
yeah i'll be saying details on how to
get to the live stretch at 11 am for
tokuma 2 including my description wow
yeah you guys if you're going to do me
you really got you really should uh
listen to dominic
he's been there many times you know what
he's talk what he's talking about and he
seems to be organizing the fan booth so
yeah
the booth cat is alluding to
d35 stay tuned oh yeah i want to see it
thank you
my tanker
looks like i've missed my chance to try
to participate in the middle green once
again oh no
oh yeah you've probably been like so
isolated from the real world um didn't
know document what's happening or that
you participated especially since i
could have went there this time really
oh no keeping up with caffeine news is
so hard sadly now next time for sure
oh no but wait when are you out of that
service again are you still here
when are you out of that service and
have more freedom
i miss my chance to
oh man
[Music]
yeah dominic's isn't it kind of
suspicious that he has a name where if
you realign the letters you basically
get dokomi
kind of sucks if you ask me you sign for
five years oh [\h__\h] and you need someone
to alert you
if something in europe happens
in the next
couple years you need someone to alert
you
so that you don't miss it
someone to send you like i don't know
an email or a private message and be
like yo yo yo yo yo
you better sign up for this buddy
yeah that's so sad five years oh my god
yeah spam spam valiant please
needs to get his chance to send him a
pigeon
oh man
anyone get in contact with dominic to
get in contact with me did you hear that
dominique get in contact with [\h__\h]
apparently you're needed
[Music]
i can't be newsletter
there's already something like that
don't know
i'm done basically smoothie wait
dominique
i'm basically done
smoother
[Music]
wrestle free thanks for the pinky it's
payday again oh yeah it's the end of the
month oh my god that means it's also
payday for me soon
probably tomorrow though
i'm going to try my best to get my fat
together into three minutes
we mean three minutes
three minutes
are you typing another super chat right
now but
[Music]
get that bread you know
oh you mean to me to greet out
gosh
i didn't realize oh you're coming to the
meet and greet
let's go
you donate in great british pounds which
means
you're from that
land of the british people which means
you maybe have a british accent you know
i have a thing for british absence
oh my god i'm gonna talk to someone with
a british accent oh my god oh my god oh
my god oh my god
i might i might get too nervous to talk
to you yeah
british mate
uh you know what i'll i'll talk back to
you you're like you don't have a british
accent are you sure about that
if you talk to me in a british accent i
will talk back to you in a british
accent during the meet up great
or whatever that is
whatever that accent is
pudding pudding has a british accent
okay
pudding let me hear that
i want to hear it then you better prove
it to me
scottish yeah i'll talk scottish you
talk british to me
[Music]
oh man
but anyway wrestle free
your name
there's the number three in your name so
i think getting your thought together in
three minutes
you can do it you're destined for it the
number three it's your number
maybe take some notes
if you're nervous hmm
and if you're completely blank don't
worry i'll help you out
kakun dankusu
[Music]
thank you
mr
my grandfather's 10 plus year old
printer
oh does it need to be printed out on
paper
look at me please uh
please how old school
can it not be on your phone or something
with a qr code
no way if that's true i need to i need
to scold them
first of all environment okay
second of all that's so old
can't be unbelievable okay remember that
guys
it needs to be printed out
i'm going go to your local coffee shop
i have a printer i can print it for you
guys just kidding
i'm so happy because i have a print and
i know how to make it work hi scooby i'm
done i'm done she's sitting there on the
ground she's like literally waiting for
me
i love my kids so much they're either
they're either like outside somewhere in
the living room waiting for me and they
enter the room when i'm done or
sometimes when smoothie gets really
impatient she will just walk into the
room around the end
of my streams somehow she knows it
and then just wait and stare at me
good fox
after this prime time kitchen yeah
oh let's be happy it wasn't with the
facts because i for the life of me
i am not able to send faxes at my old
workplace
i would sometimes need to do it and
i just couldn't get it right and then i
would always just give up and and leave
it for the next
shift um
and i think the next chip usually just
probably threw it away and
sweep swooped it under the floor
under the rug
who the [\h__\h] uses facts man
cool who uses that
unbelievable
dominican
and now we're done thank you guys i'm
gonna go um
cuddle with my cats and then cook
something
well when i take a deep breath
i have a painful experience what the
[\h__\h]
i think that could yeah it's food food i
hope it doesn't take too long i actually
have to you know fry the schnitzel
in oil and i'm like uh i want to use so
much oil so i'm thinking maybe i should
try to use my
um
my air fryer for the first time but like
i'm worried about it because it's the
first time i don't want to mess it up
[Music]
how do you use an air fryer
i'm scared cause like in the recipe they
don't use an airfryer
i wish i could like turn on
airfryer recipes and then they add them
to the
recipe
like consider that
[Music]
a tiny bit of oil where do i put it
though i don't have a spraying bottle
can i just like um
wipe the
the box with it
[Music]
and then i put the schnitzel in there
oh well even it even came with a 100
recipe book
i'm sure there's like instructions but
i'm nervous anyway that i'll [\h__\h] it up
[Music]
have you guys ever fried the schnitzel
an airfryer or something similar like a
schnitzel
[Music]
you put the oil on the schnitzel
um
just like sprinkle it on it
okay
so not i don't i don't
i don't wipe the box with the oil
[Music]
the inside
well maybe i'll check out the video
ah but men looks like
i'm scared of [\h__\h] it up and i don't
want to unpack it's
it's still in the in the original box
[Music]
um well i'll think about it
sprinkle the oil on the schnitzel and
put it in offline
okay
how do i know how much
maybe it's in the instructions
i was gonna ask how do i know how how
how hot i should
make it
flip it over halfway through
[Music]
don't let your dreams be dreams okay
oh it hurts
okay i'm gonna go now
pain pain pain kiwawa
why does it hurt to breathe in
i'm doing better than yesterday though
okay everybody thank you so much for
today
uh
schedule
coming
tonight or tomorrow because yeah
actually you know what i'm not streaming
tomorrow so there might not be a
schedule until tomorrow
mommy is coming by
okay
bye-bye and then germany said nothing
oh my god the talk of my week is coming
yummy
oh my god let's go
bye-bye
wow
[Music]
do