[Music]
a
he
[Music]
n
h
[Music]
n
he
[Music]
great start
takwa stiff and with
buttons s where does the chat go where
does it go normally I forgot maybe here
and I go left side I think or do I
okay do I look gay I hope I do like at
least funky I want to at least look
funky uh strong
[Laughter]
start just very European oh
FL what what was it flaming no
flambo is wasn't that also kind of a
term what what's flam what's what is a
flamb flamas flam
flambo how do you write that
flamboyant it sounds very French like um
like burning
bananas but it does mean extra vaget
extra vaganza
extra extra
extravagant
extravagant EXT EXT you know in German
we have the same word extravagant
extravagant extravagant extravagant
thank you for pronouncing it in two
different
ways
extravagant
no h guys welcome to the stream I uh the
stream wasn't danger that I might not
stream cuz I'm not feeling my best
today uh but it's getting better I think
like my the left side like the cheek my
left cheek the inside of it was
feeling weird a little bit painful and
and and just generally I'm feeling
tired I was trying to sleep more and I
was getting like so cuddly and muddly
with my cats but I still didn't uh get
to sleep uh
my my desired
amount but I had a breakfast again not
this this is the third day in the rad
that I made a non-sweet breakfast oh my
God oh my God oh no they didn't keep me
this smovie didn't keep me up that much
though no not so bad
um and oh this time the salad I made was
even with carrots like shredded carrots
I made a shredded carrot with lettuce
and tomato salad and uh two Sunnys side
up eggs and with the sausages I love the
sausages yeah that's what I made and
then I was going to eat the rest of the
cake that I bought yesterday but I
didn't have time for it so now the cake
is in front of me and ready to be eaten
at any
time maybe
now maybe no one bite one bite now that
I'm looking at it how can I
possibly
Mama
Mia Cake it's just a simple like creamy
creamy strawberry jelly
cake like creamy on the bottom jelly on
the top almost dropped it
almost
M that's the good that's what I
need in my
system
what my second breakfast I'm such a
hobbit and maybe a third bite maybe a
third bite maybe the whole
cake maybe I'll eat the whole cake it's
not even the whole cake anymore cuz I
bought two pieces yesterday and then and
then yesterday I finished one piece and
I was like
M maybe a little bit more so I ate 1/4
of the second cake
too
[Laughter]
M mhm mhm all 1,000 episodes yeah
y
MH that's what I was working on these
days
mhm when I say I'm busy what I really
meant is I was secretly marathoning one
piece 1,000 episodes
yeah that's what I was doing sorry I
didn't tell you it was secret cuz I
didn't want you guys to find the one
piece before I
did you know kind of gredy I
know why is this so
good sugar I would think I would hope I
would assume that having these like
non-sweet breakfast recently is giving
me more energy I think it would
generally apply like yesterday and the
day before I think it I I felt generally
more
energetic so I might do it more
often until I get sick of it soon
TM of preparing it too
M but I love making salads for breakfast
or anytime really I just love salads and
thanks I have to actually give credit to
hellofresh I I've tried so many um
different recipes with hell fresh so far
like holy I could make five books
out of the recipes that I've
accumulated but I don't really know them
by heart you know but one thing that I
learned to know by heart thanks to
hellofresh is salad
dressings
yes so I can do them without looking
them up and I just throw some stuff
together and it turns out
good it's such a simple thing that I
always used to struggle with like salad
dressings or I'm just going to buy
one but you
know every time I would buy a salad
dressing that's not like you know the
tiny tiny one salad packages but like
bigger
bottles I would like use it once or
twice and then I won't use it for a
while cuz like I ran out of salad and
and I don't know I just don't get to use
it anymore and then it gets it go goes
bad so it's just better to just just
just you know throw it to throw it
yourself together with you know vinegar
and oil that's like it never goes bad
you always have it standing around you
always have something so you know that's
so much
easier and then sometimes I like to put
in some honey um and maybe even honey
mustard so honey
mustard dressing wow
amazing really changes with the type of
honey and mustard you use
though even then there's some
variety yeah I'm the salad con
coniss
my fridge is a graveyard for salad
dressings and it was the same for
me we have to stop
that we have to stop
it do it you know do it do it inspired
by
me make your own Sal
dressings
m m okay I'm almost done with the
cake this is giving me joy so I'll be
doing better at
GTA
so
good
okay okay so then we shall get
started how do I start up this game
again press play is that enough
was there something more to
[Music]
it wa it's really slow updating Rockstar
Games launcher oh
no did you hear
that the blad B Ballad of the Gay
WWA why is it so
slow Rockstar Games launcher slow it
really annoys me when you get things
through through Steam and then it still
leads you to some other launcher
that you have to suffer
through like dude then why put it on
Steam in the first
place why
it
right bower skate is also one of
those culprits but okay we shall forgive
bers g bubble
G
okay Buble Buble Buble Buble Buble
Buble
bam yeah yeah we know that too well G
Tony why is my mouse so slow when I'm in
that
window Don't Stop the Music I know you
guys were listening to it for like seven
minutes
sorry okay let me move the chat
closer
wait I think this is the best outfit I
could possibly take out of my life Tod
wardrobe for this occasion isn't it what
was I wearing last time and why was it
not this probably because I didn't have
the swimsuit yet what does it say chop
operator
certificate we can does it say crash or
crush doesn't matter uh a crash
course in in context of like stuff like
helicopters is really concerning like
why you crashing it
or in in what way were you crashing it
you know that's that's
important okay how's this game work I
feel like I haven't played for 5
years
my what are we doing ah okay I really
don't remember it but it seems like we
have last time I I I was doing a mission
and I failed it once and since we
already played for so long I was like
it I'm done for today
right and that was maybe the
tea
Tony I don't know I'm going
there um how do I this is how okay no
police Insight I got a bike as if I'm
still in the biker DLC but I just felt
like it you
know oh who whoa whoa whoa
who
oh no I'm late did I miss anything
honestly no you're so like sometimes
when you guys are late you come with the
exact perfect time because I literally
didn't do anything until now besides
eating a cake
and talking about salad
dressings is the sound too quiet too
loud let me
[Music]
know also you missed seven minutes of
gay W
intro a little quiet that they I thought
so turn it up a tiny bit just a tiny
bit let me me know if you want
more better now love the intro right so
good y why is my I feel like my controls
are
inverted in some weird
way why are the curves so big on this
bike no they're probably not inverted
but still oh do I need oh wait I
probably should get armor before I go
anywhere holy
just and because I just remembered it
because I
saw this hot
hot chai
to you like the thumbnail than thank you
it was the the funkiest thing I could
find I wanted something colorful cuz
like the the other ones what was the
other DLC called the biker
DLC I was going for like the
intimidating
monochrome oh there's actually one close
by nice uh gray
one but sasani for Gay Tony I need
something more FL
flamboyant
am I right oh hello Tony I'm on my way
to you hey Tom what's happening boss
you've been hanging out with people
behind my back I've been trying to make
us some money yeah you have anything to
do with a little boting accident that
went down it's all over the news I don't
I genely don't remember but probably
yeah freeding to people smug oh Tony's
mad at me I heard there was
I'm sh with you arm smug well there
you go why are you with me what
I what I do I you you
idiot Lis don't turn into a
freedom fighter we don't have a luxury
of that right now and stop going solo on
me not now I wasn't involved of course
not but if I had been it would have been
for us for the business sure you be
careful l so unnecessary why why why you
pranking
me no
all right we'll get some armor but
that's all we need I
hope and I don't I don't even want to
check
like just a prank
bro
Jordan okay now we go to
Tony who is very close it says he's
available what do you
mean what does that mean am I reading
too much into it maybe available just
means he's available yeah but like does
it did it always say available for
quests like
[Music]
this single he's available for a
relationship with
me AKA this character in the game not me
cuz you know he he he's gay so I
wouldn't really make him happy I
think all right we made
it is this really the quest that we last
time the mission that we last time
failed bang bang he shot me down oh
Watch Out Boy Che you
up she comes she's a
man here she comes Watch Out Boy she CH
you up oh here she comes here's a
man oh oh yeah I remember watching this
let's watch it again though where's Tony
what's wrong with hi EV you're looking
cut hi EV like a
drink stra I'd ravage you right now EV
there's Stony he sent me him here who
cares about neurotic he's back on drugs
he's looking old he refuses to get any
work done ands the man's a wck then
break up with him for the last time
off out of all of our oh these two are
dating uhuh somebody's got sister
underwe on
by pretty low all was
that for a Coke Boo and steroid junkie
you a particular okay I'm just
going to admit that now would you shut
the up before I shut you up now
where's Tony where is Tony De me where
is Tony no where is
Tony still ah hey Tony get up
still come on get up man let's
go piss off I want to die okay man if
that's how you want it come
on water boarding let's
go what are you
doing better I guess come on he's a he
he's got a hangover and that's how you
wake up people with hangovers couldn't
be me can't
relate can't relate you said we had
something to take care of I ain't having
you screw up does that really work
office put you back in prison all those
years ago you're a degenerate what about
me you guys can't just leave me here
yeah good
point off EV ouch ouch
before I get
back let's go come on
God how why would you do that like even
for yourself
like certainly hurts yourself too oh
wait wait wait wait what something
forgot what the the the explosives oh
yeah the explosiv yo what's wrong with
you man you want a nightclub not a
terrorist
nuts he going to kill us yeah
he's gone crazy and you're running
around with some bombs okay what kind of
drugs are you want I hope they strong I
told him I take care of his Union
problems for him it's uh it's the only
way out either that or they kill me I
wish You' talk to me about this first
man okay blowing up any yeah I
guess he went for the nose what do you
care about the you got your your
head in the clouds B shot you're nothing
and soon you're going to be a dead
nothing yeah no doubt boss now where
you're going think I got guy digging up
Frankfurt Avenue for Liberty electric
okay what else the the the transport
workers guy is driving an outou of
service subway train through take the
whole thing out a subway train Jesus
Christ please tell me that's it the head
of the LTA is out of Fran International
and his private jet and you'll probably
blow yourself up as soon as you walk out
the door I'm surprised we have to do all
of this again not just part of it I
thought the checkpoints were pretty nice
in this game try and stop me huh
[Laughter]
okay are you asked for
it h not if no because I reload okay
okay
okay I I think the first were really
simple no I had a really lucky like last
millisecond throw for the sub Subway one
right like I arrived and I threw it
without aiming in the last second and I
managed to do it should I go with a car
or with the bike H this car looks
nice would a car be maybe a bike would
be easier
actually
car
safer blue one faster and controls
better
[Music]
okay it oh it does look e wait it almost
looks like an Aston
Martin from the front I don't it does
remind me a little bit of the ones that
I was looking
[Laughter]
at I'm extending my car
repertoire my car knowledge
repertoire if nobody's submitting a
privately owned Aston Martin to
my car review then I'm going to be so
disappointed like what the
can't afford Aston Martin then
don't don't don't even
try just kidding just sold mine sorry W
oh oh man what are you buying next a
My Tho s s bombs on the base of the
crane a yeah um this one I did on foot
cuz you can activate them when you're
like like on your own whenever you want
right
so just one no oh no he said several
never
mind the base actually is maybe more
like down here is he oh he's
mad okay let's go let's go let's go I
don't know if he realizes what I'm doing
the guy like he got mad yeah
but oh here she
comes she's a
[Music]
man n n I'm so not impressed because we
watched this
before oh wow where did that go into the
Earth or into that uh underground system
nice it will surely be comfortable in
there
mhm is that like uh what what what band
I think you guys mentioned it in in the
chat I only heard that like randomly in
random places before but
Raiders what welcome it's not for M time
yet right for
raid it's not for rating time Hall and
Oats see I've never heard of the that
band name
before guys I'm having um some
pretty scandalous thoughts right
now
I
[Music]
am I'm
thinking why am I not playing GTA the
right way that you should be playing it
like with
[Laughter]
cheats like I I know we talked about it
before like generally I just don't feel
like when I stream a game like this I
got something for you
I I I I feel like you know I should be
legit how do I redo this will there
be another
train fell down I don't think that one
stuck on
it oh
man new train please or do I have to
follow this one
ah but well I was saying you
know for GTA GTA might be one of the few
games where yes I know I lost it well I
feel like it's
acceptable how do I open the phone
again win
hey
what what the the is wrong
with that
the biker
King what the hell they all look the
same too now I need new
armor unbelievable well not for the
train for the train I'll just go like
this that's so
lame okay I was
saying I was saying for GTA I feel like
it would be
more the
classic fitting way of playing the game
and I would then have an faster faster
time with it maybe treat
away like I would not do this with any
other game unless I you know with AOE
where I for one part of the stream
without counting it as you know a proper
run doing just a cheat run a specific
cheat run yeah you know we did that
that's fun it's only okay to cheat in
GTA
oh a sh
fck
no please let me do it again oh nice car
[Music]
why was I so good at this last time o
nice car and now I'm struggling so hard
with
it I wish there was a cheat for getting
your armor filled back up I would be
using that all the time I would even
maybe say that's the only cheat I'm
using and be happy with that that would
be plenty of help for me keeping my
armor up at all times oh there
is
cuz I'm just so annoyed at constantly
going back just to buy one piece
of armor between each
Mission can I do
it I
won't it's not because like it's not
like a you know skill issue it's just
that it's annoying that I have to do it
every single time you
know
yeah oh wow okay especially yeah when
like there's a
retry the is wrong with you
people for retries it's just even more
so oh we shall do it we shall do
it after this and you guys have to teach
me how to do cheats again cuz I don't
even I don't even know how to cheat in
this game hell oh look at these
nice
[Music]
cars will you do San Andreas uh I
actually noticed on my steam library
that it seems like a long time ago I did
buy like
everything that's like
available on Steam I have I have GTA 3
and San
Andreas come on please
yes yes one extra throw it in for good
measure on the
ground can I blow it up can I blow it up
can I blow it
up may I it's going to tell me when it
wants me to blow it up right or I'll
just do it
now but the other one told
me you won't enjoy those to be honest
well I honestly also don't know H not
anytime soon if if I feel like playing
one then it will
be in a long long long time
later long time
later the last one is difficult cuz I am
too stupid to figure it out okay how do
you cheat how do I do the cheat first of
all like is there a cheat window that I
have to open like in
Sims
to I have a time limit to reach the
airport too oh dear
no use your
phone really why do nobody ever crash
my do I have to put a
number oh you call specific numbers for
cheats oh that's
cool
Is that real
48 wait how do
I 4
8 two that better not be a real number
and you were just giving it to me so
that I call you
later oh it seems
real I imagine it's giving me a real
number right here right
now oh
call me later
W cheat activated let's
go cheat da cheat da cheat DA has
anybody ever come up with that cuz I
feel genius right now for coming up with
cheat
da GDA I'm a real GTA gameer now let's
go
this is the correct way of playing
GTA nice my health and my armor
fixed but it's such a long
number 482
5551 hey I remember that
even
the true GTA experience right I would
say
so who here she
comes ah
I already need a new car
[Music]
probably they don't open up for
me oh it save streets time to spawn a
tank if if I fail this Mission too many
times maybe I will maybe I will maybe I
well make it easy for
myself 100
helicopters well what I do with 100
helicopters if I can only get into
one I have a
airb
ah and I can't even I don't even know
how it
continues oh here she
[Music]
comes a
m I have arrived uh what are we throwing
it on
again also what was the what was the
like recommended method of getting
in um walk can't war of a
car the plane okay aren't there like
more than one
planes just driving fast
okay uh
where's this hot shot at what are
you doing sorry please don't be mad
thank you I missed
uh this one
smaller
you got a nice
plane and they're all on the
ground yes okay I don't know if I really
got one on there oh yeah by my stars are
going to be really bad now uh okay
uh blowing up the plane wasn't even
that biggest problem I think getting out
of here and then losing the stars is the
real problem but I automatically quickly
lose a couple Stars right when
I
ooh uh-oh the thing is like they close
everything
off they close everything off
though is it already closed
off here is fine oh it's fine it's fine
it's fine it's fine I think last time
they closed off a bunch
oh my tires I got to switch
cars do it now or never get out get out
get out get
out um muscle car or this one this one
looks fine a faster oh
quick oh he has to do all the no
let's go let's go let's go let's
go oh the
helicopters but it
am I like I'm not uh Invincible right
with the
cheat uh
no okay
good yeah I can see it now definitely
took some damage there all right all
right all right um oh Circle kind of
small right now
interesting
uh get in why is this car so
slow and why is the circle so
small wait I only have two stars now
right so that's the thing yeah when you
get out of the
airport your circle and your stars get
really small small to smaller small to
smaller
danger small SM danger
noodle whatever that means no no no no
no no no no no go
away I'm I'm taking a different path
now we oh my
God nice
landing more more danger
sticks danger
tree I I was not I was not very
committed to if I was going left or
right around the
tree okay
duno I'm getting out of the car cuz it's
not looking so good I did it
yay first
try why was I struggling so much last
time player damage zero yeah oh I guess
cuz armor yeah okay I guess that
count uh thank you uh thank
you thank you I did
it yay he was over complicating it oh
nice car nice Aston
Martin K me out really necessary were
you going to let me take care of this
explosive or were you going to
insist on blowing yourself up I got us
into this mess exactly man you're
getting us out of it too you should know
that Evans walked out on me we're over
yeah I heard that before T if it's real
this time it's a good thing he's
dragging you down man he's a
parasite you need to concentrate on
getting your own life together see you
soon all right
yay
Tony Little P
Tony let's go to my
homie there is the Tony oh he's so far
should take a
taxi
to
as
Martin you should also visit your mom my
mom I have a mom in the game
what or or oh are we talking about your
mom
H should I visit your mom jokes on new I
visited her last night oh
oh
oh ouch I'm I want to I want to how do
you how do you call taxi again
e uh
Q
I'm holding e nothing's
happening what's going on maybe ah there
was no nothing considerably close by so
it doesn't work
uhhuh there we
go
nice you didn't even say hi to you while
I was there yeah cuz you were not
my you weren't like my my my my
goal of
course I want to make it
subtle hey L want to make you feel
uncomfortable inside no he's not here
yet uh did you talk to him whoy about me
what about you about me working here man
I can't do it no more I ain't queer and
it's doing my my head in bro you work
for a guy whose nickname since 1985 is
Gay Tony why do you give a I want
to be married man you know I want to
have a nice life I want to pick fce and
Aly I want to raise kids play ball you
know well that's wonderful that's lovely
bro I don't know what to tell you man
des's the man of masoner okay this is
the job we got for you if you don't like
it off I guess if you do shut the
up and stop being a don't be
like that man you know me I'm an artist
I've got songs in me funny hole in his
chin I I I you're the door man
bro not the Cabaret what's wrong with
you you're real T man and you used to be
cool hey still cool asck L come on let's
go pretty quiet oh
fantastic what is wrong with you people
don't you know a good time when you see
one Jesus when even the Queens don't
want to get wrecked you know this city
is turning into a suburb right L
that's exactly what the guy wants a
suburb sweetheart in the back Tony can I
have a work
no
no God please no can you take us out to
Gracie's house on babage Drive B babage
like
cabbage
wait
H hey babe how are you hey yo Gracie
what's up do not flirt with me what the
is it with Louise I mean he'll try
to bang anything with a but it's
Mr limp dick when I'm around I don't
know maybe it's your Charming turn of
phrase or your demure almost nlike
matter what is up with that Louise sorry
Gracie you're a't my type so can you let
me be a limp dick in peace having a
is your type Lou tell me what's
wrong with me there ain't nothing wrong
with you if you're like really loudet
Louise you hey hey look I stopped
dealing with monster brats after Danny
lupella tried to get her daddy to cut my
balls off call me an but that
was it for me you're coming from the
I got into after my night of
indiscretion with Royo oh tried to claim
I spiked his drink Roy aomo he ain't a
very good one I never would have guessed
it yeah well they don't wear a label one
a very good one look at this
behind the wheel thank you thank you my
pleasure is starting to rub off on the
employees look Gordon what are we doing
out of Grace's house we're paying a
visit now come on now that you mention
it there is another issue that
nebish the celebanator oh my God I just
love that guy's blog well that guy's
blog don't love us what happened he's
talking like it's going out of
fashion so what he thinks he's the only
guy with a mouth on the internet
this is something we don't need right
now no one comes to our party what do he
doing what does he say are we going to
kill him first of all Su us a long way
off and second we shouldn't be having no
party in the Caraway with our financial
situation this guy could sink us listen
to him Lou the cator is real influential
relax bro send them a basket it'll be
cool it's a fruit basket he got
left off a list somewhere so it's our
livelihoods at stake yo all right I'll
check him out what's his site I'll send
you a link you drop us off and go
through it now but that means Louise
won't be able to see the inside of my
place oh well in that case I'll
definitely do it now another time
oh yeah sure B some other time I do not
care about the inside of your
place so go leave my car call me when
youve email I'll keep the car of course
although that's a nice cute pinky car w
cute cute cute I like the color very
pretty see
you see you Lou okay
bye-bye remember the car steal it
okay I I feel it's kind of familiar yeah
yeah
yeah yeah it yeah it is wait is that is
that the what you waiting for go Che
that it's not the I can't take it no it
won't let me
is that the car that yeah I abducted
someone with oh my God
[Laughter]
oh maybe I in order to steal the car I
have to steal a girl too maybe it's a
full
package doesn't work
[Music]
without
internet
cafe why are we using the internet cafe
when I have internet on my phone
internet on
phone I'm doing a meme guys did you get
[Music]
it I don't well maybe I maybe maybe I
should make it work what are we doing
against
cator here you been
cated what the
this looks like Sims looks like a
Sims
advertisement Sims 2
advertisement fruit bow party for two
Tony Queen and his rent boy princess
Louie Lopez are ated again apart from
being the least convincing non couple
since two men spit roasted an albino
cheetah in last venturus Queenie and
Queener inist on telling half the few
desperate schlubs who bother to try to
go to the now irrelevant masonet to take
a hike get over yourselves hello
sweeties no one is interested in coming
in there to watch you LA dance each
other
anyway should have read it like that the
whole the whole thing uh what was I
supposed to do leave a
comment don't
submit oh is this my
reply hey Mr celebr inator we're big
fans of you site at the club so it's
kind of confusing when we read this
spiteful I'm sure you don't want to
offend us so give us a call and we'll
try to work it out is this supposed to
sound threatening doesn't sound quite so
threatening but okay hopefully it does
the
trick oh that's it Gay Tony block this
car damage already 50% s n thanks oh
what what's happening I was going
to call
someone do it again do it again do it
again do it again do it again my
car truly one of the missions of all
time so true are we going to go golfing
again oh my
god oh no it's Club
management oopsie I I scrolled in the
game and it made me
bigger
confusing
okay nail her nail
salon
h
m
subtle very
[Music]
subtle I should go
taxi there's a taxi there's a taxi
there's a taxi Mr taxi taxi tax
me uhoh uh does he understand yes okay
hey
I'm not taking good out to that na no no
we'll do our nails in Japanese nail
salon
oh it's about to fall in wait
here I want chocol hey I'm all good baby
how you doing
ID hey desie hey what's up man what's up
man D in uh a while
ago night please after
you she got so much Botox in her face
she couldn't even say anything like
Hello thank you how are you oh hey you
okay I'm good I'm
good
e you like
that didn't warn
me
um why did you not want me D me
you not want
me n need the
I need the
[Music]
I feel you're late Dirty Man
something up dirty what's going on I
need to take a shower right
now it put salt in my eyes expl as we go
[Music]
quick
gentlemen my name is Tony Prince
yourselves great
Bulgarian tell me where are the women
well they're
everywhere TV Starlet that one there is
model and that one there I don't know
but I believe just sign on with the
derrier campaign how much the I
mean no no no no no it wasn't
gay that's my real
complaint uh can I buy you a gentleman a
drink Cindy Cindy come here take care of
Mr buer in here it's good to meet you
please come back enjoy your night my
rightand man Luis will take care of
you thank you
so oh she's cute so how's it going
gentlemen
must make for funny times at B
hysterical hysterical where does the C
come from in this place I don't know
about that man I just make sure
people don't get killed MH how very
boring I prefer one day two you should
come back on a busier night then
normally it's Walk to Walk corpses by
midnight you I right tet not so much hey
gentleman thank you uh L we got to go
it's his Club so that's an
issue Jesus russan Rich than their
Church buy this place end all our
troubles yeah nothing like Russian
gangsters to bring a sense of peace and
stability to a
problem
M oh Jesus what did I do wrong take us
to Bahama Mamas Bahama Mamas ooh
mommy's from
bahami sounds like
fun now Mama's is more Rocko style than
our place tell me he's going to start
hanging out with all that bridge and
tunnel crowd rather than us don't we
wish no sadly he just wants you to talk
to a lady in there yo T I ain't heard in
old lady foro they just want you to hit
on her she's an old friend of yours
Monique from the derrier store in suffk
Monique after to that thing with
her roommate I don't think that's going
to fly what they want me hitting on
girls for they want you to get at her
boyfriend he owns the place but he's inv
venturist now so I'm some jigo
now perfect I never seen you complain
about chasing women before well welcome
welcome to the stream I was waiting for
the dialogue to end so I can drive into
this do what you do best partner you
ain't coming you think having a passed
old Queen on your arm is some kind of
afrod looks dop try and forget it's a
job the day has finally gone see you've
become my pimp and I finally lost my
self-respect later
bro uh y'all are lucky you didn't arrive
uh 3 minutes
ago and I hope I would hope that you
know even when fuku sends all the bow
bows over that they're not actually
watching because imagine me ruining for
sayess with the scene that just happened
imagine
that I'm just going to assume they're
generally not watching they redirect but
they're not
watching that is safe to assume I
thing they a Sayo well yeah who really
is Sayo is that you Monique oh God do I
have to like actually like do the dance
game again cuz like I failed so hard
last time no
no instructions uh okay W in time to the
music okay f for more uh left shift to
start Dan that's
it
just that's
it that's all I got to
do uh what but what what is this about
the about the left Mouse button and
the right Mouse button they didn't
explain that one
[Music]
oh all right at least it's going better
than last
time yeah I didn't even click the mouse
buttons like what are they supposed to
do oh yeah he's slapping a bot too in
the
ribm I feel
we ah I can continue the ribon maybe
with the mouse button
butons hey
[Music]
he yeah maybe that's what they want me
to
do prepare to sensor
again
no I'm not sure if it's better to press
it oh wait I'm supposed to
hold
I don't I I I will never understand that
but we're doing it it's
working okay I Really they really have
to sensor they can't do it out here in
the
open this is fine this is still
fine they can't do
two Maxi scenes in the
row can
they
can
I um wait uh let me find uh
something
um
here this
WWA is going to protect you it's going
to protect your
smiles but not mine I guess mine will
not be
protected hey wait what what was there
to sensor that is it because I
accidentally I clicked into the window I
just skipped
it she's dead on the
ground the I I skip all the good
scenes ah
a I forgot the
number all this over a
lady I think this is the
number what
happened
sh you make a
goodg you too sir beautiful
Target one
more hey who else wants to get shot get
out of the club all
right I'm going
to oh I didn't even get the
civilians hey what the who what
what what who's shooting what I'm done
hi what what what what what where are
[Music]
they well maybe we'll see
[Laughter]
those ah maybe we can see the scene
after all that was uh so
sudden
oh
o
o was from left
side it's saved on the oh no I bet thaty
was plan
fck why can't I not just type it in
normally no scene for
us how many times you want to get me
into Rocco okay I shall be careful
uh maybe different
weapon yeah Grenade
yeah it's the sniper right this this is
the one good
Target get down oh sorry oh God did I
give her a head
shot
uh that Bloods do be getting
bigger
well it is what it is it is what it is
everybody
uh dance outside I don't know dance
wherever you want don't don't do it here
I don't
recommend
nice I have this situation under
control o o o dog run I'm sure there's
like another uh score for not hurting
civilians
right well that score already I lost
it are these
civilians they don't I don't
know wait I probably could have seen it
on the
map they probably wouldn't be hiding if
if they were not
civilians sorry sorry sorry about
[Music]
that should first ask
later whatever they were they're now
dead something up there oh
okay guys leave the club you
[Music]
idiots leave the club how addicted can
you be to
this is why I don't go
party what is this
camera just let me out of this
place who wants
trouble
uhoh oh I don't have the Stars yet so
maybe it's not on
[Music]
me oh oh you broke my
arm
okay give me the mission complete thing
please I'm waiting I'm
[Music]
waiting
yay ooh player damage 4% check ooh
groove on
hey just didn't get the good guy I'm
guessing that was um related to not
hurting
um civilians
oh
GG oh
Tony L you got Rocko there with 2 is he
there what's got into you why are you so
moody Lis you should talk to someone
yeah I get moody after I'm nearly killed
Tony that's happening I out right now
Monique's boyfriend wasn't
adventurist the whole club got
shot to okay see why you're was not
the best outcome soon you're keeping us
afat here L get some rest he
says
I the the wicked never rest I will not
rest oh My Dead Body
literally I think that's probably
Callie's life modotto I will not
rest Only Over My Dead
Body that's when she'll
rest what does it even mean no rest for
the wicked what's that even supposed to
mean I'm being M I'm being moled OH
police car didn't notice
thanks
guys you know want to know what my
recent binge watch goto YouTube channel
is Cody Cole you know Cody Cole with c
and then a k Cody with c and Cole with
okay my God I laugh so hard at his humor
it's cracking me up so
funny M basically he's a react YouTuber
but he reacts to all these like cut and
Jubilee
videos and like his his comments are so
freaking he points out the best
things so funny I can't stop he's a
great musician oh yeah he keeps on
Advertising it but I'm not planning on
listening to his
music not even oh look who it is house
party I mean my heart is being oh God no
don't do that this is good blow we don't
support this on my channel straight edge
all the way Father tell him you've been
selling me c that they look so up
mean that I mean tell them tell them I'm
okay you know tell them I'm on the up
yeah tell them if he needs a good fake
tan or some hair gel rockco can hook him
up oh off Louis try it bro I'll
happily do more time for you oh L you
always got to act so tough just have a
line and chill out like me you
people L is always such a we're meant to
be having fun here having fun I am
where's my phone Coke is kind of
Speedy Rock where's Tony he went out you
better not be spiking me with speed rock
or I will be so angry where did he go
who what is wrong with you man you are
ruining my bus L Tony where's Tony he is
over there oh yeah he passed out again
how did I not see him mess L
holding you back he holds everyone back
no he doesn't get up come on get up get
up you has been no good 1980s throwback
relapse junky F wrong with you Tony get
up baby ladies and gentlemen more
shots hey hey hey what guys what's
what's going on you tell me boss what's
going on H why'd you call why are adults
such a lost cause thing wake up you
junky you think adults wouldn't be as
right that thing okay absolutely
hopeless as teenagers are but look at
this look at the absolute state of these
adults Jes man I feel like
AEL it wasn't fun here we go oh no no no
no no no no not again not again no no no
no no hold on guys I want to come God
off Evan this is work it's not
working out whatever
so anyway anyway anyway Sharon I
think I'm GNA sell my car oh my God that
is so fun oh my God what tell it to me
for free absolutely
nothing my
God I hate
humans just makes me hate
humans limos I know I had a big
night when it's one of these stupid
things waiting I'll go with the driver
Lou I need a bit of Peace take Evan for
me thanks a lot
though run walk run walk hook please
driver what exactly are we doing man
listen Lise no offense but I don't know
how much I'm allowed to tell you what
you mean Evan tell me everything you
know that gets me really I mean how
much information are you privy to you're
just the driver after all yeah
I'm enough to know that you're a piece
of who's using Tony and you're only
going to be hanging around for 2 to 3
months before Tony moves on to another
chunk I'm pry to the fact that the Coke
in your nose and the roids in your veins
are going to send you worse out of
control real soon I'm also privy to the
fact that you're going to be some fat
trailer park Queen back in the midwest
before you hit 30 now tell me what the
we doing right now that attitude's
not going to get you anywhere sweetie
you better stay something nice to me
tell me what's happening if you
say something nice I'll think about it
you can get Tony up like no one
else can Evan that nice enough a sweet
thank you Louise Tony is more fun when
I'm around what do you want to know what
are we doing going to the docks in is
we're buying diamonds million again
diamonds or diamonds only get that kind
of cash bro you don't know everything do
you Louise yeah I know that money can't
be his unless he borrowed it where's it
from how the should I know I'm the
look not the accountant oh yeah I forgot
you just sort the money you don't know
where it comes from the money could be
Bros could be gra great driving
guys wow what the is that dude so
serious don't worry for once Tony 10%
off the agree amount what is he trying
to escape
from today baby even better bro
even
better I we're getting
diamonds I feel like I've been here
before been there done
that
been there done that it's like a dja
Vu maybe
it's where have I done this before maybe
it's the same thing but from a different
POV I don't even know anymore like what
have I done in which part of GTA
4 cuz like there was the main game then
there was one DLC and this is the other
DLC like what did I do when where and
what with who
stream POV and then you'll surely get a
clearer view of what the hell is going
on but only if you stream takanasi
Kara's first original album point of
view this is
it it'll change your
life diamond
[Music]
sign bright like a
diamond hey what's going on right which
which one is Mr Tony that would be me
all you got what we're looking for you
got the money sure right here M then
then I'll get the ice he looks like a
how you feel about this bro like a
butcher or something okay it serves me
right for leaving the party with you
losers shut up idiot don't we co let's
just get this over with my head is
killing me my life has been reduced to
this so no Louis we are a long
way from cool but for right now let's
just see what the chef has to say for us
that's what I think I
agree yeah all right this is
them these are great they're great but
uh 2 million you had your head in the
oven Mr Tony I have what they tell you
perfect clarity beautiful clity well cut
and we got to check it got to make sure
it's for real for gorgeous just like you
come oh my God get out of here this is
too much
IGN
bikers you're a
chef yeah that's that's why it felt so
so
familiar the money we aged just give us
the ice what did we do Tony can I hold
them thank you
thanks oh we out of here come
on just Escape
okay use sticky boms to take out the
biker poor
bikers what is this shitty ass
view
things wait who am I why why am I not
driving it oh
okay okay I'm not even driving that's
why the view is so shitty
okay oh dear oh dear e too
[Music]
close Okay difficult to find a the
balance cuz they're mostly on the ground
also my ears I can't
hear nice
okay I am enjoying this wait I'm dying
wait I'm dying wait I'm dying did some
of the explosion get me they're on
our
left uhoh uh I don't have time to cheat
please tell me it's
over I think it's over I think it's over
don't you dare crash cuz I'm not putting
my seat belt
on okay get us out of here they're right
behind us oh wait I have a certain
amount
only only 10 left no
what they they shot me from the
front it's unlimited really oh really is
it always
let's Frost the cake
again I underestimated that although how
much what must have gotten like a big
head shot
somewhere got to do this without armor
now unless I can cheat quickly I don't
think so
though is that my person no
right
I thought you'd be an explosive expert
by now get
him they they shoot so
well
your hey look how much damage I've
already
taken throw a bomb
L throw a bomb L I say tribe kill them
all Louise they say look at that man
those bikers are in there as
well
nice okay bike is driving on its
own got to got to look at the map and
sometimes turn around and shoot the ones
that are in front of me rather than the
ones that are behind me huh cuz
otherwise we'll give them too much
chance of driving past me and then
that's if these bikers don't kill us
you're driving in that moment they'll
shoot me even
more they're coming from behind don't
worry about
it hey oh my God no my what the my
HP
though blow to wait there
uh the cops are blocking the road
helping us
do we blow up the
cops that might have hurt myself though
are we good we
good what the is that
sendings that shit's crazy that's messed
up nah I can't even I can't blow it up
how much do you want me to blow you up
okay oh my God
how do I throw this at the
helicopter I don't know if I can throw
that
far wait wait wait
wait to today
uh
yeah did that do it
no yeah that did the trick holy
I am so
surviving this guy doesn't is so
resilient oh I did it
okay
W chill ah
sh bro what are we going to
do just C down I'm driving now po C we
got to lose these am I driving and and
shooting uh wait where am I going lose
the cops okay no more shooting just
losing
you are not good at cornering me Mr
cop the normal people are better at that
somehow okay survive survive don't die
here is the end of the
circle got to
make
three a two I one in
the
the I'll be on the next plane to Los
Santos if you ask me answering his phone
I'll check his bleeder he's not going to
update some social networking site when
a couple a dozen AR ra bikers are trying
to kill him bro no one's that V not even
him 10 man 89 bleeded less than 10
minutes ago I can't believe it man
what's it say cornered by bikers ug ug
ug Too Young To Die we got him
Jesus poor bastard I know poor Evan
he was a rotten human being why like so
much that got himself killed and I
Diamond stolen on might head because he
needed to tell the internet about his
problem I can speak ill of him as much
as I want that's the stupidest
thing I ever heard all right it was a
weird move I'll give you that but he's
dead killed by social networking cheated
on me stolen from me and put his plastic
surgery on the business credit card but
I like the guy and I'm kind of sad okay
well I didn't like him he's dead and
he's still pissing me off we just lost 2
million on those diamonds damn that's a
lot of money your boyfriend just been
killed got to get it
back you really think kin's dead I'm
sure of it he bleeded yeah it's
somewhere in my phone but I don't know
I'm where really in a now got no
more car just typing it in again the
is going to go wrong next stay cool
and don't get too up on those
spills all that Charlie any new
hey Evan ripped you off and he
didn't get away with it look at it like
that I'll come see you soon sure
whatever so long
stranger So Long Farewell hope he
doesn't
goodbye I go to party every single night
ooh bomb accuracy all right play oh
that's because I cheated before the the
mission was over for real ha
well I'm just that op
okay wait what's the next mission I
guess I got to wait for a
call should I should I stay in this
limo I've never been in a limousine I
think in my whole life have I have I I
don't think
so have you guys been in a limousine
before I'm stuck
oh should I go to the
m oh oh oh for real for real that's what
you mean with visiting my mom
okay oh it does say mom's house okay yes
once no prom no no prom for the waa yeah
that's one one kind of sad thing cuz
like
oh
um I did get some kind of
like the uh uh you know like certificate
after finishing that like
school but there was no prom yeah we
don't I don't know I think normally in
in other schools maybe there are proms
in
Austria but even then I don't know if
it's really like an American typical
prom no one asked you to prom yet yeah
no I don't think I've ever been asked to
prom because there was no
prom yeah
boss I'm just wondering when you think
you're going to do a don't make it so
clear do that Lopez magic I try to put
some time in soon man make me St so
clear look after
things dad can I take you to prom want
to go to prom with
me let's go
[Music]
to
should we do a prom stream in in like
VR get a prom
world and then I get a cute
[Music]
dress then we can do some awkward
dancing and we can drink some Punch or
whatever I guess what else do you do
have a
prom the prom queen and king thing
righta this is Mr Santos what's going on
hey I guess I didn't recogniz mom not
having any pictures of you up on the
walls I guess she doesn't have any of
now you mentioning I guess mug shots
don't sit along too well with graduation
shots who the are you well it's
it's complicated Mr Santos is a
businessman it's not that complicated
when you think about it you see your
mother here has been making that classic
American mistake classic American M
living beyond her means hey bro be
polite when you talk about my mother man
I'm being very polite see I like her
she's a good woman if I ain't like her I
would have burned this building down by
now iom me you know you could have came
to me for money but what would you do to
get it yeah I wouldn't borrow for a
piece of like this hey be careful
kid I could have you killed oh I'm real
scared of you huh how do
you sleep at night man long shocking to
old women hey he she called me okay it's
business we run a service she knew the
rules she should have read the small PR
you know you really are a piece of
I'm a businessman and trust me it could
get a lot worse my friend business Cal
down you your mother told me about you
maybe you can help me pay all loone
shark that way this building doesn't
have to come to unfortunate end
unfortunate end like blowing it up or
setting it on fire let's go as always
nice to see you miss Lopez be careful
you from you you ought not to judge
me Luis Lopez you're with the
wrong
mama going to you up is that him no
need for transport we're going somewhere
close
oh I really want to shoot him or plant
the sticky bomb on
him you're going to start fighting for
money again sorry bro but I don't do
that no more I saw you go a few years
back could have been something if you
didn't care so much about that pretty
face of yours D thanks but that ain't
the reason I quit you ain't quit no more
my thinking is you were bad enough for
no one to notice when you take a dime
you beat the first two guys I set you up
with then you fall on the third bro
bro I so didn't think I'd be coming
back here again man there's probably
even some guys on the scene that still
remember me they ain't all up
right now right I wonder if I can for
you
guys no right that was the
problem the voices are not separate
do
it it just said follow him I don't think
you're supposed to kill him
yet
I got to follow the instructions
guys what if I get used to winning then
your mama better get used to me coming
around and not being my usual okay you
made me do it you made me do
it what
now all so now I have to redo it now we
have to follow him
again stupid
chickens okay can we go
faster so anyway guys uh yeah um good
news I bought you out of retirement
you're uh how's it going opportunity to
kick your ass no such luck pretty boy I
got you set up tomorrow is AE day then
I'm going to bet against you and you're
going to let the third guy take you out
let's go I'm excited for AOE
want to play more
AOE I was waiting for D bro I spent
some time in this place just like you
must spent time communities and churches
want to play
Skirmish and squir in the
squirmish squirmish squirmy squirmish
squirmy
skirmishes swey gamer training time hell
yeah I'm going to make people
squirm in the
skirmishes learn to count I know how to
counter elephants Now list man you
out of a promis career that is burnt
into my brain thank you get too proud
now that was my one takeaway hey put
that weapon
[Music]
away what remember how
deal usually unarmed in Toe to
Toe freaking Fight
Club use the crowd to hold opponents
what what do you ah do you mean through
the
fence bets are canceled if you step off
the mat and contenders lose their entry
fee do I have to do
this get your bets down place your bets
place your you can come back and it's
like a mini
game that's who I got to
fight no
way I forgot I forgot how to fight is
this is this how yeah oh hey I'm winning
what him up right now that's
what I'm doing what why was he so weak R
for an alternative punch Q to kick I
didn't even need
that next ding ding ding ding
muscles
alternative
fudge
wi hey in your face let me smack your
smack hey everybody who whoa whoa whoa
be careful now you don't want to get in
trouble with me yeah I've got all of kfb
behind my
back that's what I'm talking about you
should have stay quit little get your
health to below half and take a dive
what why would I do that
what you want me to lose
no wait it won't let
me how do I take a dive what does that
[Music]
mean what how to
dive it said let it let him hit you to
dive oh
lost hey man I don't
understand nice to see a man like you
swallow his pride for his mama just stay
the away from okay you got your
money we done listen to me I was there
for your mama when you weren what mean I
you must lost some brain cells in that
fight why did they want me to lose I'm
out I'm taking it I thought it was a
fighting move like jumping on something
and then whoosh like you dive into a
pool but it seems like it's fine this
way I just lose a lot of money or
what
hey I won money
though was a rigged
match yeah I was supposed to lose eho I
took a dive in that fight for you mommy
you don't know that goty any more money
what do you mean you took i di f mean
you lost you claim to
be you can't even win a fight for your
mama I lost a fight for you Mommy I
didn't ask you to lose no fight I did
not ask for losers in my family you know
what forg about it man so that they win
a lot okay yeah yeah see you soon some
rigging going on behind the scenes they
were
betting for me or so so that when I lose
they get a lot of
money and no the other way one I don't
know you know what I mean you
know what's happening you you know
what's going
on
hey oh
n yo what the is wrong with you man
what you mean homie you can't be sitting
here man watching him any fo policeman
on his second day on the job will know
the other guy with the man you
wonder back inside you is this a
side quest nice to see you Mr big shot
real nice to see you Captain
downtown come up here to talk down to
his old friends yeah I just scar about
you guys I don't have a choice man they
told me to take a d got a single digit
IQ hey I was just following instructions
of course I could do what you did run
the away go a man or some
yo I ain't no man bro okay I'm
working the best clubs in the city I
ain't go nowhere I'm 10 minutes away on
the train 10 minutes what's up h
w it's another country down there 10
minutes I give you 10
minutes you ran away yo whatever man
whatever
whatever what the hell you want a job
bro get you a job man I don't care
whatever yeah yeah for sure man I want a
job sucking some agent Playboy I
want that job real bad sign me the
up you're sh your dick bro you would
know Enrique would you get the to
shut up please I'm sorry man I just miss
you maybe I expressed myself coarsely
but we was like family oh yeah Lo we We
are family man but family doesn't mean
we have to live up here slinging dope to
a bunch of suburban punks from Alden man
complain about how life could be we on
the doorstep man Liberty City we
could run the world man oh and
you running the world or you running
errands for some ass muner yo Tony all
right man he's like the daddy I never
had sugar daddy he whatever man
My Lou
boys
mise you look tired hey Mommy I've been
working you know I do know that's the
problem when you're going back to
school I hear you going back to school
Armando doing an NBA Mrs
L hey let's go mom I got to go okay but
here take this gra out Louise take your
life more seriously baby please don't be
like your father look at your brother
look at your sister they're doing so
well Mommy I know but what do you expect
I got to hang out with morons like these
two
okay let's go POS Mor like us my brother
you mean like us woman has been
abandoned by her children okay I know
you think we small I know you think we
ain't but that's why I hit you up
man why because we got something real
coming down yeah the last time we had
something real coming down I did two
years look I'm not going to insult your
intelligence by telling you is
going to be different now but it is it
is that
closeup to make it to emphasize
it it
is what it is bro trust me bro for real
bro I mean it
bro bu is going down in East hook bro
wait one second over
thereo
get in the
car get get in the car Shinji get in the
car wait how do I get the the short tato
is it ah there it
is I'm serious about this man you need
to get out of this place make something
of yourselves easy for you to say d Wan
I don't get your problem with the
neighborhood the heights ain't all bad
bro oh yeah sure it ain't man how many
kids from our class stuck around up here
none that did anything them punks Oscar
Willie and alanso did and look where
they at Dam you had some good times
here don't forget about that you
remember the summer of 99 yeah I do that
was up here in 99 and we started
getting into that BPI University Toto
remember that nothing quite like college
girls even got him some didn't he yo
that the glasses right off a no I sure
did yo hey everybody got to grow up
someday not if you live next to a
college you do them stay the
same age your whole life true bro
thought you was man I know how them
Gomez boys anyway Luis hey you know I
don't see them dumb no more 5
think you do 5 asking us about you and
them all the time you see lisis Lopez up
here with the Gomez boys you see Mr Luis
Fernando Lopez associated with Willie
Valero it's like they obsessed yeah man
you get bagged with a couple of punks
it's like you associated with them for
the rest of your life 5's dumb
useless bro I wonder the crime's out of
control in this I know what the
they talking about reason trying to
listen speaking a crime bro the
shit's good enough for us to start
seriously stepping on and making
some real profit product then profit
then P that's not what that stands
for sure it does r can you remind me why
I'm coming along on a dope
deal I don't touch that no more man
I got a legitimate source of income this
I'm doing on purpose guys just having a
FAL me with the got to smooth out some
detail really help if we had a
respectable Punk like you along yo this
is just for appearances right you sure
yo sure I'm sure just for appearances we
shaking hands with the man is
all bro okay okay it's so wobbly
you guys you should know that I want a
new car this car is I want to
return this one it's too wobbly he gay g
g g g g nightmare
inducing you bro
W may as well be prepared for some
take hold of this Auto shotty and these
pineapple pineapple yo nice really
makes don't get me in trouble with the
police Lo the cops before the deal goes
ahead I'm going to try what happened did
you see that are you seeing that
Bros are you seeing that
he fell off the bike and time
stopped the moment he fell
off okay let me let me just relax here
please please please please please
pleas that was so close that was so
close I don't know if you saw on the map
but
damn oh
hi Apple
hi I'm wait to be in the heat so sick
it'sing can't you dancing to my be you
going be my yeah now you see me see me
baby I need just give me give me no my
hesitation don't pay twice cuz you're
mine the war son on me I want to go why
can't I not just turn turn around
here cuz it's not legal I
suppose I watch some funny traffic
videos uh like yesterday or the day
before absolute more runs I watched one
where I have one guy was like driving on
the highway like this and missed his
exit so what he did he just like turns
around thankfully it was a relatively
um empty Highway it just did literally
this
this like how how I understand that
missing your exit like adds a lot of
time but like how can
anybody have the like audacity to do
that in real life oh my
god that is just so yeah I think he's
playing GTA for
real or some other driving simulator
where it doesn't
matter oh my God and then there was a
like um there was like a a like a normal
street and two rows were like the same
direction so they were cars here and
there were cars here right and then
there's a there's a
crossing and um one side was like
completely opening up for an ambulance
but the car that was very very very much
in the front
t uh that like was the only one who
wasn't like opening up up and going to
the other side for the ambulance and the
ambulance was like it's a huge
ambulance actually firefighter truck
standing right behind him going we we we
really loudly and I don't know what the
is wrong with him like he must have
not heard but like what how do you not
hear it like it's right behind you and
like even if you have some uh what's
probably illegal too noise cancelling
headphones on your head I feel like you
would hear that and see that in your in
your rear Vision whatever
thingy like what the
hell and like in front of him there was
no one so all he would have had to do is
like go a little bit to the side either
left or right and then the ambulance
would have gone through huh man I was a
couple of Clips like that it was just
fascinating how people are so
dumb
awareness minus
12y what's up
man what's good chilling bro got to be
on purpose I don't know
likeo you're killing people by doing
that so this is lope I feel like he must
have just not noticed for some reason
maybe they were drunk or on
drugs our connection bro package in town
you know I got that raw baby you already
know probably not really like con
yo what the that yo you
you shut me up you were
follow right yo we wasn't were you baby
was going onzy going I didn't do I
was just telling a story
amateurs I'm out of here
man a driver must have been high or
something it's just not normal like even
if you not nice to humanity you wouldn't
just stand there
uh okay I got a nice
gun I
think actually it's slow I don't like it
is a
shotgun some clicking bro I should have
pck it can I
[Music]
sque anything else these guys going from
your pH
conversation and nice
B That's What I Call take a
dive I hope they don't pick up the GR He
Knows My Name that guy knows how to
run
this you ain't going back
inside I
get oh oh I hear helicopter oh no
reinforcements wait where are they
they're supposed to be here I guess
they're all down
[Music]
here much for the Redemption can't I
shoot the
helicopter I don't even see
it oh here where is that my helicopter
am I supposed to ride
that
[Applause]
okay
yo fibo even got any evidence on this
here I don't know what they did before
but I guess they go
now nice clean up
W thank you
kfp you're so supportive I love
you it's going oh oh
oh
uh-oh let's get out of here
Annihilator scary
you got to get behind that and deal with
those Bo On The
Roof oh thankk you on the roof on the
roof on the roof on the
roof no more goof on the
roof I did I took him out
outo what else do you want
taking cover is a word that Takara does
not know even though she's part of a
company called cover
H
[Music]
H she does not seem to
understand no fear better this may take
a minute that CH back get out of here
how the we going to get rid of this
thing check the news fan now there might
be something in there got you bro the
new let's
go bro let's
go there we go beautiful
fireworks the end of a summer is
announced the best with a beautiful
firework in Japan you know
yeah okay what now boys feel like I need
some kind of reaction here or like
what's
up you're going to you want to go into
the car wait there's a there is a yeah
okay we're going to use the
car tactical response unit wait get in
get in I
can't do I have to take a different
car these are all shitty
cars
H okay this car works
that package of
yours suddenly
traffic you got to be careful with them
phones man people are on to that
that Dingo is a ma but that means
they can pretty much read a th now and
get away with it just leave the
crime I qualify you to teach Street Life
101 oh yeah I ain't lecturing I'm just
looking out for New York like what you
do them clubs of yours looks hug
Massacre wow be back there again uh 2
minutes later tax hey who want a
taxi
well make your money now that you
mention I do with some dick sucking
lessons I hear you nailed your Technique
on the last bit of State eh we were just
close friends whatever anyone told you
was man
he's a good
guy we on NF someone misses their
cmate you both of you yeah I don't
see why you guys are giving me you
was the ones who asked me to come along
on this thing while you driving in the
middle you look pretty was going to
up will did up and I
nearly got killed so I think I in the
right to be hurt for a second oh Lu got
his panties in a Twist speak your peace
bro look as you say wow wow but I do run
a business well you run Tony do you
where's the money then you're going to
listen to me or what you're never going
to get anywh you guys there's enough out
there to do that work for you high level
and never talk on the
phone that's all well and good bro but
selling in our issue is getting hold of
product what are you talking about man
there product all over the city just
take it off steal that
they ain't exactly going to call up
5 are they could be right
bro P to overse there ain't nothing else
coming in for us we might just have to
start ripping people off you going to
help us made I don't know I could do do
with the money but you boys is clowns L
back on board bro I know it holy
move okay perfect driver thank you uh I
still don't have a license IRL and it's
probably found in this
way nah I I will get one
eventually when the time is
right and then then I will be a menace
to society as I always wanted to be and
make my GTA dreams come true I'll make a
reality we live in a
society you have a license no I don't I
just said I don't only in
GTA my license in GTA is
real but it's only in
GTA but there it's real
within the boundaries of
GTA it's real to
me oh right shut up for
sake you know there's cities that have a
a doot
ban more cities need the like the big
cities they all should have a do D ban
you can't just do D for Fun For No Good
Reason M New York definitely needs it
holy if this is how it is probably
worse than reality but me and going to
need to do some serious work if we going
to maintain on these streets we
could use someone we could trust you
know I said I wouldn't get involved in
that no more most cities also don't let
BS Drive see you I am more than just a
bird
oh
head shot 16 that was not enough
for
you 16 e your results can of be
okay I just used one small small
Cheeto just one small small
Cheeto
a I don't care I don't care what you say
this is the right way to play GTA no
arguments the what are these this
is the underground battle thingy and
this what is the drug wars
one not that I want to be involved in
that what the I shoulde you for
stressing me out no kiaha on the lead
the
boards I will never never be on any
leaderboards
man me when I say this I have to the
other side you spin to the other
side what Brazil what
Japan what do you
mean have you heard the news Evans
definitely dead hey we expected this
don't don't freak out it was an
my guess is he was intending to steal
them diamonds when the bikers got him
Okay evan was a conceited dick a lowi a
a truck pedler and a seat he
treated me like dirt that's the kind of
guy I like you should start going back
to the shrink bro screw you anyway that
doesn't solve the diamond issue brocco
saying we owe him his share of the they
want to punch me guys this ain't good
man oh no they're running away oh you've
been in wor before oop I'm counting on
your leadership you believe those
stories wow I never took you for an
idiot I just pretended to know what I
was doing I'm a schmuck who got lucky
we really are
screwed
okay why are you driving right in the
cars uh can't you see my dear chicken
you tell him I don't care I have to go
there a billion dollars this gu place a
billion dollar buy anyway today doesn't
even buy a million dollars I want to go
on the bike arcade you tell him Yousef
Amir is speaking those look like fun
that name does mean something in this
town H one second hello excuse me hello
golden phone hello who is this papa papa
papa how are you yes papa yeah it's a
present it's a gift oh no you didn't pay
for it I did well I didn't pay for it so
you
didn't Papa it's it's it's it's
complicated I miss you papa I
do yes I'm close to closing the deal the
biggest tower you're going to be so
proud of me well 10 million is maybe a
little bit too much to spend in a month
but it was necessary but papa no no
that's not fair no no no no that Papa
they're not prostitutes they're loose
women Papa Pap hello
Papa hey it's you my friend how you
doing how you doing what's up Papa
trouble with your old man no it's my
father okay yeah that's the old man be
tough man he's a very conservative man
he doesn't understand what I'm doing
here thinks my life is one long party a
reckless orgy of sex drugs and spending
[Music]
really he's deluded I I work my fingers
to the Bone to the Bone you know last
week I got exhausted test driving sexy
cars had to fly to Vice City and bang
for 2 weeks just to recover I'm
a workaholic Man Poor God what alcoholic
homie yeah evidently now I have to meet
Ahmed and his brother to take a business
meeting and I I love those guys they're
like family but oh God is going to
exhaust me how was that these guys
they're always going on about how rich
they are L money here the money there
you know what that reminds me of
something they're very um what's the
word um
tacky no taste I mean I love those guys
but seriously come on okay well I I
guess I'll see you later then no no no
no no no no no no hey you're coming with
me baby you need to hang around you got
to act like we're friends we are
friends baby make out that we got
going down going down my
niggaas anyway let's go let's bounce
baby when I say bounce I don't mean
bouncing literally I just mean I know
what it means it's a ter from the street
meaning you have to walk yeah okay okay
I mean I guess get like it's
understandable he explains it to me cuz
I didn't understand diving
either
is that egg yolk or is it supposed to be
golden cuz I think I'll have to
disappoint you will with you I'm
giving you this special auto shotgun
with explosive shells thank you let's
hope I don't have to use it the
make sure it's all cool and safe
enough yo what's up tell those
at rdam there's ain't going to be the
tallest tower for long your's in to baby
and your about to
be yeah I'm coming man the yeah the
thing that reminded me of like rich
person complaining about rich people
being so rich reminded me of why you are
so agit like a YouTube short that I
watched yesterday in a moment I don't
have a good feeling about this is not
we in observation checking out
two floor mansion in
Soul which is like must be super
expensive talking like while she's
making food talking
about uh her rich friends like in the
way that like oh my God
like they're so rich and then look at me
like oh you know do we have the same
YouTube algorithm it's coming from what
I'm watching I think what I watch is
recommended to you guys but um like she
grew up really really rich too but like
doesn't realize it like honestly
so toned deaf and then people people did
already like uh call her out for it in
the comments hundreds hundreds thousands
of them and then she was like ah sorry
guys I didn't realize I guess I I have a
wrong image of you know no I didn't
realize I was so
privileged
mhm yeah but she was trying to make such
a deep statement about I don't even I
don't even really remember
anymore but she definitely was far from
being
broke and then talking about how good
rich people have it not struggling in
their life meanwhile she has her own
huge ass twostory apartment in
Soul and like all kinds of other
privileged
the
irony let's see what's going
down wait what uh what exactly what am I
doing there we
go
Louis my man where's Yousef what's going
on bro what do you mean what's going on
chill
homeboy look at the real
estate free real estate yo what's wrong
with you man yo what's going on he know
he knows we're in the what
do I know I thought it's ch man
tell me what I just walked into sh me
please what are you do I'm sorry
St uh CH
what man this town is full of
[Music]
degenerates
okay immediately oh uh What uh wait wait
wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
wait wait I need the right weapon for
this there it
goes
bye-bye where's the rest of them where's
the rest of
them he dropped the vest nice he's NY
NY let's go
up I need everybody to get
down ear this dropped really tato
because I was like really caught off
guard there we go wow these helicopters
are like way more easy to take
down than you would
think okay F to mount I will Mount the
ladder
oh helicopter back
hey why so
resilient you why you were dead I'm
you go away now go away now another
[Music]
vest
please everyone get on the ground and
try to remain
[Music]
calm
okay oh hi didn't see you there oh wait
wait wait was that
bad well I just saw somebody and I
thought shoot
everybody ah ahed ahed
I thought you
know all trer happy I
guess this this shotgun it sounds like
the most explosive thing ever I guess I
did say something about explosive shells
I don't like it though
also I think the the helicopter I took
it down oh what what was that jump I
think I took it down cuz I heard a big
Kaboom use shotgun I don't want a best
gun nah oh what's with the helicopter
Revival how how does he survive and
recover from all those head shots and
those explosions you telling me that's a
different helicopter like where is it
suddenly coming
from helicopter second electric
bugaloo you prefer mid-range I prefer
bigger range than the shotgun I just
don't like also like how slow it
is slow and loud and just confusing me
you know giving me confusing mixed VI
it's not that slow you just need to hold
down oh
well I want to work with what I already
know you
know feels more
familiar and safe this time I will not
shoot you but you the way you're
climbing up there looks so funny to
me back
up a oh goodbye
goodbye Oh by bye
bye
to my
a okay okay I was my aim was so bad cuz
like I I I I just didn't have a grip on
on the mouse for a
[Music]
moment can I not get up this stair thank
you any more
helicopters a long long way down
what these
know what show this shortest shortest
air
airway would you guys be able to climb
up a building like this you crazy
n the hell no we just wanted
youf out of the picture
no I wouldn't
not that fast that's that's that's for
certain I think he's dead
already don't land on
me and I don't stop coming and they
don't stop coming four stars now woo
pretty the stars in the sky the
constellation is telling me that I'm
being followed by the
police what a weird constellation that
is
is do a flip okay we're up here I have a
parachute parachute I know how to
parachute sh about you believe me
normally I would like to do it with
someone else oh man if that's okay I
could
have killed him before too I didn't do
nothing to you uh in freefile P press
left Mouse button to
activate
Okay what the kind of mission is
this
it's
like I'm I'm
playing I'm playing um bre of the
wild where are we
going where am I
escaping this indicates your height
above sea level okay where where what
where
way uh it's not that
easy I'm already Landing I didn't get
very
far get up come out my
boy oh my stars are gone just by Landing
okay okay no
problem what was the supposed okay I get
it but I want to see what was the ne
necessary
it and soon oh whatever do you mean dude
took a dive down to sea level bro
set you up with the news so
they could take your business I cannot
believe it
unbelievable unbelievably
believable money ain't enough I have a
deep sadness in me L will you join me
please for an orgy of champagne C wom
watermelons and and whatever else the
may have to offer we must forget them
you're going to have to do the
forgetting by yourself man I got a lot
of other business to deal with I'll see
you around man okay that sounds like a a
great way of getting over but oh my
what what can I like Parachute from all
these places base jumping
wow now
hold
uh wait no it was uh
here hey do I need to buy a parachute or
just do I just get it like up there once
I'm at the
top that's cool but I don't think I'll
do it
again can I use
this thank you take me
to Gold this is it thanks man don't
don't get me in trouble with the police
now
Mama
Mia don't drive so
weirdly caught with your pants down uh
do I need to censor
again we're getting air money we're
getting air
[Music]
money and again let's go hey bro
yo uh this is uh J
as jelle I think you want to
moderate to use of the word bro it's not
cool all right listen are we
going to do or what I'm on the
clock man chill baby get into it feel it
let's
go that
package what's wrong with you man maybe
put some of that package more on your
butt cuz your butt is so flat man I'm
going biggest building in this
town the front looks like a
diaper biggest
my name will go down in
history yeah I don't doubt that man what
you
want well why am I dealing with this
that we can get some real Hardware
bit like the chopper but better partner
better I don't think I could handle
anymore that
partner I'm talking something seriously
intense how
about a
mother
news tank
give it up bro come on come on hey what
you need a new stank for man what are
you crime fighting
now I want it come on baby you and me
doing our tank thing just rolling like
some Desert Storm oh Chinese
person byebye you
ridiculous man hey man m is it money is
that money you want here here have it
but come on let's go get this thing
come on come on baby get up come on
let's go again to the left and get air
money come on
baby what are you doing
here dignity not found uh this is my
business associate and Mr uh Le Mr Lewis
Ya Allah he is the greatest remember my
name at this point this is his wife J
this oh careful yes and uh
you know we just having a little
creative meeting and things were a bit
crazy and uh I somehow lost my pants
oopsy TOS but you know Papa I tell you
you are looking you're looking very well
in
fact I knew how
drugs
hookers oh guys
hello
hello I think we're back you can't miss
this we're back okay good this is
important like we're finally somebody is
finally telling that bastard what's up
that he he he can't he can't just be
this little bag of you have to
witness it and no
pants I think I don't need to read
it well Papa you know these people they
mean nothing to me in fact they're just
going go get out you Mr Lewis take your
wife Mrs Lewis and may I say Madame this
is not a very uh appropriate way for a
married woman to dress I told times
father this is this is way to dress do
they listen to me no never and you by
the way I'll text you in about one
minute about the tank okay new tank sh
go and leave right now and don't you
dare come back
without knocking first these people are
disgrace Papa but I tell you moving
swiftly on you will be very proud of my
plans I want to show you for the
Imperial Amir Towers I tell you
papa
magisterial doesn't do justice to
it uh well at least we get the car it
seems Yousef Lis I think I can give old
Papa the slip me me in Star Junction
really I'm coming D just hold on see you
soon my friend what the is going
on the star Junction can I take this car
yeah nice my car
now my golden egg yolk
car pineapple car I guess you could see
it that way
too follow me to the was it start
Junction or something like that what
what the hell are we doing we're getting
a news
tank all right what else do you want the
Eiffel Tower as well like what
what else can I get you P it on the
list there it is ah okay I see why they
call it
that who tank no's tank
oh oh nice
helicopter I going to own this squad get
out of my
way I'm just going to land here because
I like
it oh my
God go wait
[Music]
helicopter uh uh
um
well you fly man I'm getting uh how I
forgot like
this yeah
okay they're air liting the tank across
town let's intercept the I
remember that us meeting some bankers in
the exchange luckily for us this stuff
is too serious for Yousef to be invited
it thinks I'm waiting for put him in the
lobby they're
man they think they can your life I'm
old and ugly enough to just go up if we
need to get higher than these buildings
taking care of yourself B I don't know
about that bro maybe you're all right I
don't have the means if only he gave me
a few billion I could really call my own
then maybe I would grow up I feel the
same way
bro
what he would grow up if he would get a
few billion what US dollars what
yeah not asking for
much come on give it to
him that's that's nothing come on Papa
become your own son's Sugar
Daddy might be better because then he is
going to stop being a the tunt
you must have one it's an air cran bro
do me a favor will you just buy
one okay no
feel
perhaps okay now don't worry man I got
these controls again I shoot he fly okay
okay
okay oh he's got the nose
tank uh shoot the
bolts what bolts bolts wait BS this one
this here don't we should we get lower
before it can we really drop it from
this
height how how fast do the bullets fly
also this is not really where I'm
supposed to shoot huh the bolts like
here
ah
what I'm getting f
way oh wait I can zoom I can
zoom oh is this is are we in the water I
don't want to drop it in the water do I
let probably probably on the yeah we're
on the what just just shoot the Rope
then Mama
Mia Mama Mia get everything but the last
one I don't know it's pretty
good is the Rope okay too oh don't know
it said bolt the bolt
oh they're moving so
much how did how is that missing you can
literally
see you can literally
see
oh
man what
the
what how give me a bigger hit this is
bug this must be
bugged this must be
bugged
give me a bigger hit box like
what no
way not am I shooting the wrong
thing cuz so far I was always shooting
like the the attachments and it worked
what what the
I was I'm trying my best to be very
aimful maybe I should try to not
aim what
the do you got the final don't you're
kidding me right like I hit that
a million times
wait
uh my God
ridiculous R I got
scammed oh nice landing nice
landing
attack this so cute look at this small
baby I have to wa I have to have to
escape with
this you got it yeah bro the cops are
all over me good thing you're in a
tank it's just a new stank
bro who gives a
play it's going to be difficult it's
going to be difficult
[Music]
um uh
uh I'm kind of slow you know I don't
know how I'm supposed to escape
know can I shoot only into the
front it doesn't seem like I can
aim okay that that feels it was like it
was frontal
okay oh sorry that's civilians I don't
know why I did that I'm so
sorry how am I going
to escape what if I kill everything
that's in front of me
wait
[Music]
then
well it shoots everywhere
what is that oh I CH the where I'm
looking looking
at in that moment okay okay okay okay
but do I really want to get in more
trouble well actually I did go just down
to three stars
interesting
oh
[Music]
H who oh what happened what the
happened extending
my contact
Circle I I don't know it's going to take
a while oh no there's the end but
there's another cop car
there
don't extend
it
no got to go a little bit
further the game said to fight them
until they stop following you
well I don't think they'll ever
stop oh wow news tank
strong they're not in my vision right
now
oh oh oh
oh over
theic hello seems like seems like OBS
has troubl accepting the truth as
well
maybe take a lesson from these cops who
are slowly but surely accepting the
truth that they can't get to me
as we're losing these beautiful
stars and I'm out the
circle he no it how did they see
me how did they save
me there was literally nothing close
by
lose the cops I'm trying but it's like
oh it's only one star now maybe I should
stop fighting them
now just drive I feel like shouldn't I
be getting more stars the more cops I
kill guess not not in this case this is
an exception it
seems oh
I think I'm good w e the
show I like this
vehicle let's submit it to my car
reveiew
oh
[Music]
y
I made
it so what's the logic behind that did I
just kill every every cop that was
available so that's why they stopped
or did they understand that they have no
chance against my news
tank they gave up normally they wouldn't
give up though don't just give
up I think they should all be be fired
for giving up but I guess doesn't matter
cuz they're dead so can't fire them
should we deliver uh your fired notice
to their
graves just to make it
official I say
yes
[Music]
y
love that song so good one of the best
anime openings ever youf bro where you
at man all of the Z openings were so
good back when I pick this thing up
okay man thanks for everything bro
you're a Diamond don't mention
it you're welcome I
guess what do you want
now the sharp I didn't get the
Sharpshooter
bonus why
not
it's cute and sexy when kiia is causing
Mayhem in a teal bikini thank you for
stating it so
clearly
facts very blunt shooting when Post in
car if
ah take the take the pictures now and
then submit them when I say submit them
but uh yeah I need to I'm actually kind
of waiting for thumbnail material cuz I
want to post it with the
like please submit your photos under
this hashtag so that there's a picture
to look
at so kind of waiting for
chy D bro what's happening I've
organized that face to face with our
good friend this cban there he is oh sh
we're going to show him a good time yeah
I thought we could persuade him that
we're not such bad guys after all he's
meeting us at the Hort on the west river
we're taking him out on a tour of the
city I wouldn't missed this see you
there
oh
wowow oh today I'm kind of bored man but
at least I'm feeling
better so I can play for a while if I
don't die from boredom sorry
guys we going to take a
[Music]
care one of those days can take it's
kind of rare though I normally I don't
get
doing my streams
but
no I can't get any closer than this so I
have to drop you off right here yeah on
yeah perfect how am I supposed to get
out
huh do have to dat stupid even he's
getting
out no his own car backstabbed
him his own very own car killed him is
he going to get back up
is he dead for
[Music]
real
she I I think in a in a crime
investigation they will see that the
Last Passenger was me and this kind of
looks like I did it I I I don't even
know how to defend myself even though I
know it wasn't me such a situation I
feel like I might be corest into saying
I'm
[Music]
guilty what the am I supposed to do
was an accident watch the VOD
yeah just watch the VOD watch V
get in Lou don't worry then you
understand I got you or shoot confusing
let's go first on the agenda is a trip
over happiness Island get us some
altitude who's the dude in in
there who's the
dude as high as possible okay Louise
meet our new friend the celebanator the
celebanator
like name or do I got to call you the
was it this is a gay I wear in public
I'd preferred if you called me the
celebanator okay it's a lovely
helicopter you've got here Tony I'd love
to say this was mine but I'm just was
barring it off a rich friend of mine Mr
Yousef Amir he let us use it because
it's such a special occasion that's is a
very grownup gesture of yours they
thought it' be just Tit for Tat from
here on in what you mean TI for Tat you
just started insulting us on your
website we ain't done through you
I'm not naive Lis the DAR launch masonet
fth birthday he left me off the list it
was a deliberate snob what you talking
about man we never even met you I was on
the scene Louis it I H see me why
is he what kind of accent is that
supposed to Beal War so I
brought it oh yeah you want the lud
man having a website don't
make you the SC not now Lou we're trying
to charm him Irish so it's time be asked
what's it going to take to give me box
French excellent black Mill is a
language I know only too well a mixed of
everything the problem is that you think
you're operating in a box you the vogs
are just as important sounds kind of
like how I sound when I want to sound
Scottish
British K and British show me anything I
blogged every inch of this town are we
going to push him out I don't think you
ever seen Liberty City like this oh
Are we going to are you going to
drop him just scare him don't droping
who the big man now huh I think you're
slipping oh they're bye-bye
birdie he's ass but you got to save
him
wow freaking wait oh that's not going to
be enough uh sorry emotional roller
coaster got be confused we got to do
this again it
seems I I don't think I can save it I
don't think I'm fast
enough and I can't open my parachute
twice but he's still falling
hey might land in the water good for him
good for
him where is he uh I still see him there
he is okay he uh I think he hit the the
the stones on the shore which is not
very
comfortable
uh I I I I I got nervous and I quickly
opened the parachute not realizing that
I would be falling way slower
so redo
please guess I got to land first before
it offers me a
[Laughter]
redo all right what's this island oh
it's the Liberty
Island um
ow I think I broke my
ankle sorry Tony oh you managed to
arrest his terminal velocity there a big
celebrity somewhere he ain't going to be
blocking no more is that an optional
ending looking for was it I don't know
what the carer is going to think went on
but we better lay low let's talk soon
you're going to offer me to redo it
right yeah
okay please don't make me do the
helicopter flying
again
okay good it no okay I still have to do
it is it all of it wait no the
phone Louise have you met our Charming
new friend The Not So Nice this uh we've
met all right really bro cuz I don't
remember it this okay it's the last one
I'll take the controls not so bad then
really show me anything I'll fall
vlogged every inch
there's a lot of time to fall so I don't
need to be nervous about City like this
opening my parachute too
late slap slap I'm sorry I just hurt you
how you liking your talk
yeah roast some
more yeah him up now drop
him do it l some P Bro you're too
heavy no don't make him feel conscious
self-conscious about his
weight it's just like tears of the
Kingdom
a
uh I'm saving you look how he's holding
on to
me can I land over there getting a
second chance at life you're a
miracle back what a romance
what a beautiful romantic moment here
want to let go be my guest be my guest
help
me there you
go I hope we broke at least his hips
man oh
e someone might post a picture of that
online sh
himself
[Music]
well plock
this interesting
Mission yeah that was
that
now let's forget this incident hopefully
we get better press from now on oh Tony
he's alive don't worry this time he's
alive how'd you boys get on after you
left me okay D he's an annoying little
but I think we saw eye to eye by
the end of it he ain't going to be
giving us no smack talk no more that's
excellent news we should smoo these
citizen journalists more often it will
be my pleasure so guys if you ever
talk me on the internet you know I just
took inspiration from this I feel very
inspired just saying I'm feeling very
inspired that's all I'm saying I'm just
like wow a third eye has opened up on my
forehead and I see all of
you don't talk
me where the are the
taxes not
taxes no
taxi there the
taxi which save the
haters
hello to today today today is one of
those
days where
OBS keeps on disconnecting huh wait you
you did I not disconnect for you guys
you only heard the sound cuz it did say
OBS disconnecting obs
reconnecting only for one second okay
today is a weird
day just one of those days why are there
so many limos here but no taxes like
what kind of what why are limos driving
around here where are these people going
these rich
people okay I'm going to take this car
cuz I don't see anything else that's
good sorry I guess it's kind of a taxi a
limo is kind of a taxi next time son I
put a no no no no no no no no no no
no I'm going to lay you out
no I'm going to enter from this side ay
Get Out of now I'll drive
[Music]
byebye see you at
saon what so on
I don't know just a Nutty
convention the old rasle
Basel now it's about the time okay okay
now uh now there's a taxi sure of
course
typical now that I have my
limousine
I'm going to drive backwards
now
uhhuh aren't you impressed by my
skills I'm stuck oh no they killed
another truth
Seeker oh sorry for disturbing your
home sorry I didn't want to Bonk into it
like that okay I I
I I am
now cancelling my
plans I do not want to go backwards
anymore
sorry the contrarian in me has changed
her mind oh
money I wonder is there something to
talk
about uh I'm supposed to have a meeting
with my tax lady tomorrow that I knew
was going to happen
but I didn't prepare all the things so
I'm asking her to change the date it was
it was also like these meetings
genuinely make me feel so
anxious like I feel so g n nerve
wrecked she didn't reply me yet wait
maybe maybe she didn't
know
no she didn't reply me yet I don't know
man yo D there ain't been a disaster has
there nothing like that I'm just
thinking you could put in some hours
after masonet make sure we're running
things to your exacting standards I know
you can handle it bro no I already rote
her a couple hours ago before the stream
started she ghosting me
maybe
well I said I even I even I didn't even
lie I I was thinking like I could make
up some like need to bring my cats
to the Ved or something like that but I
was just honest and I just said whatever
sorry can we move it cuz like I I I I I
didn't get to do like all these things
that you wanted me to
do I'm an honest honest person oh my God
is OBS cutting up it's not OBS this time
it's honestly not
OBS do you hear me are we back that
wasn't OBS that was YouTube if
anything I was saying uh I need to
sneeze I think uh I was
saying I Could Have
Lied I Could Have Lied and and be like
oh sorry can we move appointment cuz I
need to bring my cat to the vet or
something but I didn't I didn't I just
said honestly please I need more time to
prepare the things I didn't get to do
it didn't even make any
excuses got it my car just being honest
thanks for the membership
G
I can people call me dangerous you're
deading
bro you are her boss not the other way
around well well I I do think I I have
some like how to say credit for her
messing up
[Music]
recently and coming back to me like way
too late and like she also said like oh
sorry we were
like we didn't get to do this until now
sorry so it's late please pay it anyway
like
okay I would like to get out of this car
thank
you back at the mson
[Music]
net yo hey man hey man thr the inside uh
yeah but can I speak to you for a minute
no not really no it'll just take a
minute man I really need you to speak to
Tony I did and you can't move to Mason
it no no no no man not that not that
guess what I'm going to be oh that was
hercul serly so so so are you insane man
what else matters the production company
here man belongs to one of the guys they
are going to make a show about me me I
mean they were going to make one about
this Puerto Rican guy in Bohan but he
disappeared now they're going to make a
show about me uhhuh SP standing here in
the exact same
it's very stressful man but it's not it
all think about it Drama Action sex I
don't see any of that right now they're
all going to shoot it Through The Eyes
of of a tough guy the POV of a tough guy
I'm sure and it sounds all like
fantastic entertainment now if you'll
excuse me I got to get back down to
earth okay if you excuse me also hey he
he hey did I say next you said that was
next man Hey listen man get back in said
I was de you know what well you said I
was what's up D oh getting rich here
look at this place so many Rich happy
Queens spending their hard earned money
huh man what went wrong my day gay guys
used to be lonely needy and lost what's
this song they're all in relationships
learning how to
cook man therapy's got a lot to answer
for huh where's all the self-loathing
gone
H
Ben
there is a lot of people and where the
is graci she's supposed to meet me
here her man we got to go
make ourselves Rich because after all
the night trade is not what it used to
be I fit right in don't
I those diamonds I heard my bikini at
the liberoni I could be a bartender here
I thought we could go down there put in
a low ball bit and take them for
ourselves huh nice so let's go ah
exactly
okay yeah maybe uh maybe I should handle
this one on my own okay you just sit
tight he for SC I'll give you a shout
when I get back SM small PE drug man I
know I know I'm not on drugs just high
on live
right he's tripping yeah on
himself why's the music on
my favorite dude Luis what's up oh yeah
Yousef I can't chat right now you mind
if I borrow you Chopper which one man I
got a fleet special one the one with all
that military the you mind if I
borrow them for the next AOE tournament
too you love what I've done Fleet of
Choppers over at my P on the west river
thanks
bro could come in
handy ah here again I was just so close
okay if it's that
close then let's go on our
own yeah what elephant's going to do
against my Choppers
they're their noses they're ter ain't
going to reach me up
there try me what am I
doing directions confusing
me the oh my my God oh my God look at
that car oh my God look at that car oh
my God look at that
car load
elephants yeah okay combination got how
to combine T and elephants throw the
elephants
that sounds funny ain't no one going to
expect a golden Chopper to shoot them to
it's yellow it's not
golden but okay cope cope
harder oh
[Music]
wrong let's
go rumbling of my helicopters is next
not the rambling of some elephants
no and for celebration I'm going to eat
the Benjamin blooman cake with the
elephant on top remember that
one hell yeah it's all I'll be eating
for two
days all right that was supposed to land
uh uh I don't think that's happening I
don't think
so
uh wait oh I can do it keyboard
controls
Jo calm your nerves calm your
fingers how how smooth do I have to Land
wait wait where am
I
wait I'm not actually there is this not
the liberoni what the
wait wait wait wait I thought I was
on the right
spot oh the building next
St OBS don't be such a
what's wrong today what's
happening
yeah Windows the window sounds like just
me telling OBS is going
down at least I survived I made
it I made it out of the helicopter you
you didn't see the moment did you so
sad it didn't look very smooth but it
works you missed it
no I did a flip out of the
helicopter let's see the stuff gentlemen
Mory come over here whoa whoa whoa whoa
since we're a little let's see some
money of course no problem I was
there there it is beautiful huh I was
here un bills no history no need to
launder good Nico show them the
stuff get in there
Mory
I feel like I had an understanding
before of how money laundering works
but I forgot already great how do you la
their money just asking for a friend
rest do your want to die
do something stupid okay you just
get the man come on it's
complicated need some
soap
you guys saying it with free words is
like not really doing it for
me I got to watch YouTube video
explaining it YouTube tutorial on money
laundering wa wait listen if you get me
out of here I promise I'll split this
with you can you do me a favor and I'll
take this too personally what
oh gee
we stoling from us first bro true true
true top 10 way to L of money and how
to oh
[Music]
man uh fle oh in the chopper again oh
than God I actually when I landed I
almost like like it was still moving
like slippering slip slippery
sliding I thought it was going to fall
off with without
me that was
easy
oops that was too
easy that's all I needed to do H without
killing anyone
lame It Go pretty good bro I guess I
landed it perfectly in that spot all
right I'll try and so up yeah great try
and do that for
me okay now I just got to escape all
these others all the other
helicopters man in the weird helicopter
on their
ass uh destroy
destroy okay uh how do I how the do
I shoot again in this thing
with like how do I turn I have to look
at
them uh o
o I know it's not appul
[Applause]
shits how do I
aim if I were you take
some well this is so confusing I think
we I don't want to switch to the
controller like it's lying around
somewhere man I don't want
to
how this
impossible
what wait let's get some distance turn
around fully and
then wait for
him
this is so difficult with a
keyboard come
on oh
[Applause]
no
[Music]
ah so close and yet so far I I do think
I need
some the
controller that was
[Music]
good need to get higher oh God I need to
get higher I need to get way
higher oh
no now I'm too high I I hate
this you air I hate you the
sun the
clouds I'm so stubborn I have to do this
with the
[Applause]
keyboard yeah please tell me that was
the only one I had to do oh uhoh
uh-oh sending them in
here I think that means I could fly a
real helicopter now oh God there's
[Music]
more he just flew into
me okay gain some height what is this
camera oh my God I don't know I don't e
did I lose a like a part of my
helicopter because I'm not flying
normally
anymore
um okay finally right
[Applause]
direction
great
how does the minigun work
[Applause]
again oh my God I can't believe I did it
holy
that was
close no there is no minigun right click
isn't
working okay get up yeah get up keep
taking missiles uh why am I looking up
why is my helicopter looking
up sabotaging
me one of them has to hit one of them
has to
hit no learn the guy in the golden
Cher I got him wow I did all that with
the key
Mouse you can't even the thing is you
have to switch between the the d-pad and
d-pad no not d-pad what's it called the
numbers the the numbers only side of the
keyboard and the mouse cuz you shoot
with the left Mouse button and then you
use W ASD and
4568 for
controlling but W ASD alone is not going
to do the trick so you can't just have W
SD and the mouse button you have to yeah
you have to use the numpad and then you
have to switch your right hand from pad
when you like fix your position and then
quickly go to the mouse and hope that
the position doesn't change too much you
know it's like he helicopter's still
moving kind of kind of
unstable yeah it's really
difficult but I insist on doing it with
the keyboard
ha now we just got to
land I don't know if I can do it if I
fail because of the landing I'm going to
morb I wish I could go
slower am I landing on this big ceiling
or just there where I picked it up I
guess just
there
Elegance
please we're flying a golden helicopter
we want to fly it like we're
royalty
okay
I can't believe I did that first try
even riding in style I learned the
ancient art of understatement from
you try to hold on to him this time
thanks yeah sure right next to the
emergency a a freaking miror
yeah m is the keyboard the
I completed the
Trinity it just gave an achievement for
completing the Trinity of the ballot of
the gay to I'm not
done it's not the end of the
DLC as far as I
know that's
weird L hey bro thanks for letting the
same Miss with the three characters ah
that's what I do sneak up
on them hide in the sand
then po I'm a cobra I'm a cobra in the
sky flying with my Cobra Wings I'm the
executive flying Cobra when I stick my
tongue in you you know you've been
poisoned I'm glad there could be of
resistance anyway well exactly thanks I
appreciate
it I hate him he's so obnoxious holy
holy
[Music]
definitely in the top five of most
annoying
obnoxious uh GTA characters
congratulations should I go to Mory I
haven't been on that side of the island
for a
[Music]
while okay I need a
taxi My Ride My
Ride now you got to let
me drive for free right free ride right
right got it thank you very much yo I
mean
that okay Mory it's been a while let's
do our nails together all right it's
nail polish
time I forgot about this
guy I bought all of
them
hey Lou come on in hang on one
second check
mate well you're so
cool little thicko never went to college
that's not how you League school I got
into
two come on let's get out of
here that's not how you shoot the
gun good night all good
night maybe a different kind of
gun get us to the Hort near Fish Market
South Fish
Market go to Hort oh
Lord so I got a proposition for
you it'll be little Louise if I wanted
this car is driving F money so still my
man Tony you owe me bro making me
hang out with this jackass now listen to
me I got a wait I ain't having no
monster measuring contest bro I keep
telling you I ain't into that creepy
no but Jack Hammer would crush the
out of you n no no no no I'm
talking a fair calculated risk what's on
the line then you terrifyingly insecure
well how about everything Tony
owes me and I promise to get out of your
life if you win and it sounds too good
to be bro why did we go over to this
island again just ignored
him Bud for life nothing eh Heavenly
Beast or lifetime of being torted by
some hellish imp is tough
calculated risk what are you going to do
okay so what we betting on it's a race
you all around the city
only
for Choppers boats cars and everything
no not a race of Choppers win part of
our lives in theory yes but that ain't
going to happen dog cuz I never lost a
nothing in my old life I mean as long as
I don't have to shoot I think I'm
fine but the switch between everything
is just
stressful yeah you all right win
but you won't you just got to help me
with one more thing and all your
contractual obligations are
released uh uh GPS you good
there there was no way for me to go left
but
okay all
[Music]
right roll out the red no roll out the
blue carpet for wearing the blue because
R blue the royalty
blue royalty wait oh my god I didn't
even say that on purpose like that just
now I was just going to say cuz blue is
quite the Royal color color you
know
wow join
the
royalty how much is this royalty can I
compare it to any other T's in my get
off the road you B in my stream in my
next review stream of price range never
thought was going to be this easy
[Music]
yo them little legs of yours they going
to carry you too
fast is this the start of the
race
commonality
peasanty I would say a compared with
peasanty you have all been provided
parachutes boats and cars you will be
airlifted to the start where you will
race from one vehicle to the next the
first person to make it to the Finish I
don't think I'm first trying this winner
are you ready so the chopper part is
just jumping out of this why
wouldn't I be ready three two one
go oh my
God okay better fly like this for a long
time because the parachute makes me
slow do I have to go to the m no that's
just the the another guy or what get in
the get in the
boat the other guy definitely had his
parachute out early where the are
the boats anywhere I don't see them
where are the
boats uh can I spawn a
boat ow doesn't have to be a
specific
boat run run run run run run run run
run I landed so shitty is this a
problem
there's no boats on this
Pier
H
I was supposed to land here after
all vehicle
yeah yeah I saw the em and I was
like should I land there was the M even
stand for like before what let's swim
I'm still first out of four apparently
currently e
what don't count down on me like
this
no okay I have learned my lesson wait I
can't open the phone while I'm there's a
boat can I just get on your boat so I I
can please
please no I just want to open my
phone no no no no no if I don't open it
fast enough doesn't it like cancel my
redo
option cuz I did that before I was
trying to open the phone but I can't do
it in the
water wait wait wait wait wait
wait please be there please be
there oh thank
God I can't indeed
redo the race again this you're going to
get your ass handed to you you hey
we going to give a head start to those
on the four
feet where I'm supposed to
go okay this time I'll do it right it's
time for
sure please look at the map this time I
was looking at the map but I wasn't sure
if that's really or if I can take any
boat you know I thought that was more
freedom to it
here we go here we go also it's really
like confusing like you think you in one
place and then you're not really
there
there there are the boots those are
the boots can I choose which one I
[Music]
want see what yeah
okay
I want the orange
one what are these
people get in the boat
Lou that one's
orange
go okay we're certainly first right
now it goes go go go go
uh oh
oh no the water is so
wobbly no him no oh
God okay I it's it's pretty vague pretty
[Music]
forgiving
but I feel like I I can still make many
mistakes while he's probably just going
smoothly sailing
smoothly for all of this making no
mistakes he's always at the same speed
[Music]
too
y I'm pretty good so far pretty good
control I should have taking one of the
smaller boats maybe the big one feels
hard to
maneuver hold space for
really I have uh cuz it's a
break I think yeah we need it
[Music]
now
okay okay go go
faster I just go off the gas to be
honest in these
moments it
works
o nice ruins wow pretty does nobody want
to clean up those
[Music]
chips oh they're kind of stuck somewhere
there
okay thank god
wow I've got some good distance
now no money for cleanup is that really
like a thing in New York big ship rcks
it it could be kind of a tourist
attraction to be
honest don't have money to clean it up I
feel like as a tourist if there's like a
big famous shipwreck
[Music]
somewhere I feel like I would I might
want to see it if there's history to it
too no that's just in game oh okay
h
too bad by the way one of the things
that I bought uh that weren't in the
test because I just wanted to try it I
found it in my
searches um I bought an
orthopedic uh star
shaped pillow and I'm going to test it
out I already used it last
night the reviews were
absolutely wow overwhelming ly positive
everybody's saying like how lifechanging
it is I don't know if it can help me cuz
I don't think my problems
are that
simply fixed cuz then I I wouldn't have
them for so long I
[Music]
think this place looks really
familiar but yeah I'll try it out I'll
give it a try
it was kind of
comfy but yeah okay I'm taking the egg
Yol car of
course I got a good
start close the what
[Music]
the what what what the what what
the I can't control this car did
somebody Rak it
what it's what what the okay I hope
it's better on the actual Road oh my
God oh my God
Co must have been the sand man
sand okay I've got this I've got
this I'm very good at this kind of stuff
I'm good at driving I've had plenty of
practice yes yes yes yes yes
hey is that pink what is the pink dot
the other person what
no am I first no I'm second where is the
other
[Music]
person Mor is behind me though do I only
have to win against Mor or
[Music]
everybody good good good clean empty
road why does it sound like I hear an
alarm
only win against more I'm not
sure wait on first I don't know where I
passed the
guy but I
did it's more
friend don't
[Music]
care hey he must be close when I hear
him so quick
bar Finishing
Line I did
it
h ouch man that's got to be an expensive
race for you man someone must
have sabotaged me or something oh
no I wanted oh you saying it to him you
think Tony's cash means to me I got
other Investments yeah good for you tiny
so we got to see each other again I told
you one more job I got some cars to
procure and you're going to help me come
by brucees and we'll hit it yeah all
right bro I gave my
word it's always rigged when you
lose ah I was thinking about maybe
Landing in the
boat a I should have done that I wasn't
sure if I could land so like nicely h
mon but yeah have you guys tried
Orthopedic pillows like I tried uh like
different memory foam
pillows they didn't help but this one's
star shaped so that you can it's like
ideal for many different
positions they had so many good reviews
like everybody's like oh after one day I
was like okay after 3 days I I already
noticed significant differences and
after two weeks I feel healed so stuff
like that it's like
okay sounds freaking
promising my sister did she loves hers
wa star pillow for Idol
only nothing super special about getting
the right height and stiffness help
helped a bit yeah yeah the right height
I think my my old
one probably like a tach too
[Music]
high but I don't know it's difficult why
why do I I feel like when I was younger
it didn't matter so much sleep with any
pillow now if I don't find like a
literally Tailor Made For Me
pillow I'm dying from pain is this
age
why but who knows I don't really think
it's only on you I got here as soon as I
could bro oh man Louise Gracie but it
could help gra a little bit gra they got
Gracie she's gone Evan's dead Gracie
Evan who's got Gracie I I don't
know what are you talking about bro
where is she I some guy's at war with
her father I guess I don't know hey
Gracie's pretty tough she's a princess
she's a tough princess they hurt
her yeah they'll have you me and my
family to deal with you never liked her
you never did you never liked anyone
that's not true I like her no you didn't
true she's my favorite goore oh makes
you so good huh it wasn't for me you'd
be selling dime bags in the street
corner I made you yeah and she and EV
made you into a junkie okay I mean she's
not a bad person okay she's not a murder
and greedy psychopath like me she's so
hard you know if you can get past the
accent okay but she made you into a
useless old Queen to whack out on
blowing bills to notice his business is
going to oh here we go huh here we
go huh oh I see it your eyes
travel in Paradise this is it this is
the moment to put me down this the
moment where The Apprentice takes over
huh oh man you think I'm done you're not
so tough Luis and you're not so
smart you dumb junkie yeah you
Lis come on Tony chill out more no
you're right you're right you're not the
one with the problem I
am Noony what the are you doing no
I'm holding your back I see that now I
see that now oh you are the close thing
I ever had to holding me back from
playing other games I'm sorry L I love
you goodbye no hey come on man idiot
goodbye I love you sh he's
really going to do it is wrong with
you dumb prick huh get up get up so I
can kill you myself was a toy gun I'm
sorry just to I just couldn't take
it
anymore come on get up get up you old
bastard huh come on let's go find Gracie
okay okay
Jesus Christ oh
Louise Jesus
Christ Jesus Christ
D their Chopper it's at the Hort on top
of the entrance of the booth tunnel why
are we not using this
car all right what's Chopper oh my God
why is there so much Chopper action at
this part of the game ch do you think
we're doing on this outing we're looking
for Gracie you got any ideas where we
might start doing that it's a big city
though I may be semi suicidal but I'm
not completely stupid Louis you ain't
even semi suicidal D you're just over
dramatic I wouldn't be surprised if that
g was just a movie
problem sh recently for me to carry
something maybe before going you should
have
clean before you
pointst next time disengage
self-indulgent cry for help you mean
okay I need your help Lis You're All
I've got left now was one of well done
you win jackass okay bro where are we
looking for this girl there's some low
lives and Dukes who might be involved
losers even by current mob standard
which is saying something you from Dukes
ain't you I try to forget about that mob
don't Ro play so we head over there and
do what land on the roof and ask them
where they got gracing we've just got to
follow them see if they make us anywhere
interesting okay bro let's hope for the
best who knows what they could have done
don't shame King could be at the bottom
of Shame him could ding of
a he lik that danger
feeling over goles you're right that
could be the smart P her old man said
something interesting to me by the way
oh yeah what'd he say that he's blaming
us for this whole thing either we get
her back or we're dead that's definitely
you I'm a Fu did he get that in his head
I barely know it's the diamonds Lou
rockos had a word with him
quo I just got b a photo of from
the kid girl not look good hey who knows
sh L next season anyways look at the r
side at least she's
alive wow wow that is a nightm god a
problem cuz uh you would enjoy being
King shamed King shaming is your king
and then you excuse all the king shaming
of the world because you say you like it
well that's a
problem what truly a myth speaker
moment come on hurry up
man place cheing
out
Heights so expected kidnapper is near I
always push that in meido
park not that I really know where it is
I wonder if you live in New York this
about saving our own assets then this
game is like are you happy now easier
Strangely I am you don't even need the
GPS your hom it's become a lot clearer
great how we going to get out of this to
what all this piling down on top of
us how are we going to get up have we
got a plan I don't know we could play
the loty start a little Ponzi scheme buy
some cheap diamonds and try to sell them
on a profit oh wait we tried that and
it's not going so well we still need it
I'm from New York and it's so confusing
might get us out of our problem oh yeah
I've already beened off got K because of
I'm serious Lou most of the girls H it
seems really like how come you can't
manage to find a rich one easily overse
I wish I had your principal genius at
least you'll have a nice message on your
gravestone mine will just say seems
really tiny to me playing GTA my
impression of sorry I'm stressed all
right Universal
Studios oh that's Meo Park wait this
exists
in in in in New York not one to one yeah
but it feels
tiny it's way smaller
e
really I think that's their car Lou the
red one let's follow
uh cap lock well where's he going I
don't know where he's going you idiot
that's why we're following okay all
right can we follow with the car oh wait
one second my keyboard is going Japanese
I think my keyboard is turning
Japanese I can see he's going west where
West there lot of West of could be could
head all the way over to Al he might not
be going west at all be head over
Bridge Fu I just be heading down the
block for a slice of five okay okay
I take point if you see him stopping let
me know you'll see him stopping too bro
you ain't going to sleep on me are you
just forc myself where is he you ain't
got your pills no idea where the target
is
she gxi and you know how I feel about
flyow a guy out of Chopper you go for a
riding one you should have shared your
anti-anxiety pills with
the no amount of pill oh the red car
okay it's not on my map huh don't
with the baby that's what my my my
helicopter is really wobbly right now
man Cho in line we can start an
Outsourcing company we
be enough exactly what we need to be
stop try me suspiciously Lou he'll get
wise to us wise what are we in some gums
now I'm driving as unsuspicious as you
can when your boss only out
helicopter course flying Wise It's
because you're a tight ass you being
anti-semitic now nice call me a f oh
yeah very
clever go up go up go go go go go go is
heading west well now he's heading east
we won't lose him man we're cool come on
you dumb Dukes take us to her do
got stop
the enough we can Will him to go there
my helicop when you stop the just need
fixing you forever it's all good see how
beautiful I can fly with it wow look at
those straight lines unbelievable
actually where these guys from other
than Dukes I mean they're an Irish
operation headed by this Maniac called
Gerald mccre I've got it under control
you're going right now you
you it's
over we landed so nicely though on such
a such a small
narrow path
I hope got to give me credit for that
just kidna the Moss's daughter he's got
every reason to believe some of the most
unpleasant cats on the E seab are about
to knock down his door and rip his he
Ain parid and he's
stupid we have been forgiven see us
isn't he the first thing of parid I'll
make no more mistakes even after a half
nost full of blow I'm
heing at too much momentum in the
beginning
in this at any this time I'm flying the
bridge don't doubt the imagin of a man
on the Bri W he might suspect we're
chasing let's hope he STS panicking and
does something stupid I know he's going
to go left so maybe I'll
go if he thinks he's now there nothing
in comparison let the death of a boss's
girl the heat would be on us as well Lou
it won't let me so let's hope he where's
that red piece of Lou we're losing
him no I know where he's going I'm I'm
meta
gaming okay I'll stop meta
gaming see him I see him talk keep on
talking stop driving suspiciously L get
wise to us get wise what are we in some
gum so I cannot predict where he goes I
have to follow him your BOS only fued
out for a weak in helicopter course if
he's getting Wise It's because you're a
tight ass you being anti-semitic now
okay it's this place you call me a all
right all right he's going to make a
curve and hopefully I'll be up high
enough too so oh no ah this is the
different place this curve is also a
t oh and another to the park for he on
to us just going for a drive come on you
dumb Dukes let me let me let him
drive a little bit in front of me cuz
like this camera is me
up what the
that spiritual when you stopped
dating the yoga instructor there are
things that stick with you forever the
fact that he could get his ankles around
his ears this Caple camera that image is
going to stick with me jeez don't lose
him Lou where is he no
idea I mean I kind of do thank God I
know where he's
going uh he should be somewhere
here wait the camera should he be
on the left side or did he do another
turn
didn't he go here I'm pretty sure
he went that
way he did he did but he was too
far
what what I could be anywhere now poor
yeah shut
up just let me do it
again
man I feel like we've already done so
many missions to today and it's only
been 4 hours almost 3 hours 40
minutes half of the time I was eating
cake I think that's their car Lou the
red one let's follow it you're probably
bored to death of hearing me go on I'll
put on some there's only
eight I didn't think it was realistic
that I could finish the game like what
didn't I already do like 10 Missions at
least
today I did 12 health and there's nine
left H then that would be a good moment
to decide do I want to add another like
pretty much same amount of
time or do I want to cut it off feel
like it would be a short stream if I cut
it off now I thought I thought if I do
short one it might be 5 hours or
so h
doing the whole
[Music]
thing yeah I can imagine some of the
final missions being pretty
hard you could read I was going to say
like what super chats do you mean I
don't have any super chats left to read
you mean predict the future and read
super chats for next
week
yeah no I actually don't have anything
to
read I can't see the car I guess I
got to start reading books
now I was thinking like when I take that
vacation where I'm off the internet is
thinking about where where is
he did I miss to the turn again
going back to the park for to us just
going for a there is on you dumb duk's
take us to her I was going to maybe
read like either Game of Thrones or
Wheel of Time I thought you got over
that sh when you sto dating the yoga
instructor there like he could get his
ankles around a lot of mon where is he
gone where the has he gone did he
go straight
or
right I don't know I'm going to go
straight okay
that's what I thought it what do you
mean I he's still somewhere
there it's hard to catch up I was
staying
close well I heard that um Wheel of Time
is is an easier
read Game of Thrones uses very very
difficult
words
did he actually go right got to stay
closer this time but when I'm too close
the camera is absolute let's just
listen to the
radio oh did he give up on talking to me
cuz they know I'm already doing this
Mission like five
times
nice
that wasn't the same turn where I
crashed no that turn was different I
mean I I thought it was straight and
then came the
turn right it's not right in that like
Parky
area hey I'm trying to do cap lock but
it doesn't do anything anymore I feel
like I'm I'm locked on to it caps
lock what the is this iing
surveilling but if I go too close to the
car and there like how am I supposed to
dodge all these
things especially when he does a sudden
turn that I don't know
about well it's kind of
chill
I'm chill I'm
chilling just kind of stay slightly
above building level but then there's
some that are suddenly so tall
though I could take part in a freaking
going back to the park
keyboard helicopter flying competion
take us
Championship enough he might just hear
you him to go there I thought you got
over that spiritual okay let's look
close where is he going straight
right my memory he
went a lot of that image is going to
stick with me Jesus I can't go too low
here cuz of the turn there an Irish
operation headed by this m he fast he's
doing time in Al State
I could be the same
oned did he myos daughter when they got
all the bank's money how the do I
know I guess greed is a powerful
motivator I there is great what is it
not that car we rig his ball to the
battery by the time he smells them
cooking at this is a great bit of
improvisation L but I think oh my God
professionals people in
government look he's going through the
booth tunnel what going in there team
what tunnel want you to kill us where's
the tunnel where he comes out what
tunnel boof tunnel where am I here what
tunnel I don't see
him straight left pick this Chopper
up okay boss
F wait wait is
that what I don't know where it
is
I oh
I'll just yeah I'll just go where the
camera seems to be leading me look there
he is he's coming out of the tunnel on
the you know how they got Gracie
something to do with that pink piece of
car how long is this they think the
guy pretended he wanted to buy it you
should have got suspicious to Second
anyone expressed
interest want I can see you driving a
pink car T why because people call me
gay Tony exactly that's why think I've
got massive sculptures in my
apartment as well gay guys love that
you cliche loving there was
that one marble thing you bought that
was Art yeah giant B Phoenix shape art
at least you made a profit I heard
Phoenix
shap had to double check the subtitles
there oh he's going in the parking lot
what's going on so can I land here or
what she could be in the trunk of a
car in there she could be in the trunk
of the red piece of sh were follow they
would have checked that let's see if she
comes out oh from the top
okay no no no no he's there just lead us
back
tock not what I
expected oh God this is so long is there
checkpoints when I fail
now y y y y
yeah oh he's stopping he's
stopping he's stopping stopping that
must be where they're keeping gra SE
it's somewhere at least what street is
that I don't know alate well bro but I
think the big one's Sacramento call it
in let's get this bird on
the to the helipad
okay okay the camera is normal
again that
helps
God bus you should know that club
promoters are the first to master all
new forms of communication always find a
new way of profitting if we pull this
off we'll profit we'll get to keep our
spinal cords great I like my spinal cord
it would be a shame to lose
it
wait wait slowly steady Ready
Steady
I landed just like I did every other
time does it really
matter no you're not me no no not the
whole thing right no no
way I I landed this it's calmly as I
could it doesn't matter why why do we
care about one helicopter I I'll bring
you another
one oh okay oh okay okay it's it's a
checkpoint it's a checkpoint what is
this view what the
oh my
God what a pain in the ass mission
take us back to Gracie
[Music]
now oh was the other
way all right he stops
here what was that car park maneuver he
sto that must be don't make easy
somewhere at least which street is that
I don't know alate well BR but I think
the big one's Sacramento call it in
let's head back to the helipad all
right a normalize my camera thank
you okay I sent them the location so
that's it what do you mean we did our
bit and Sal that was not fair me
providing they find her and get her back
sa at least it's not from the beginning
is the money we owe them and the fact
that we've got his baby girl kidnapped
in the first place but we didn't get a
kidnapped
you're right that told me it
was my fault so many times that I'm
starting to believe it you need some
rest calm down calm down wor I'm taking
a spa day the first opportunity I
get no it's not broken
wow
uh uh okay calm down calm down calm
down that was not considered a landing
apparently but now look at this look at
this look at this
okay I landed I landed the beas
if see you
soon I did it we'll take it was almost
exploding oh man what a pain in the ass
please stop the helicopter missions no
more please 0% helicopter damage um
that's not what it looked like to me but
okay
okay that was definitely helicopter
damage I mean
look what's going on here do we need
some witnesses here come on keep it
moving people there's nothing to see
here you have the gun literally in his
body
that seems like a little
bit too much
honestly oh I don't like to pick up an
unknown caller
numbersa burrito burito how'd you get my
number I don't want to talk to
you too bad Mex this line opened up just
as soon as Tony took those points you
know Ro your guinea ass is lower down
this country's ethnic food chain than
mine so don't condescend me oh I
got Senora sensitive here hey look I
respect you so I'm gonna talk straight a
second Tony's pissed a lot of people off
you need to control them Tony's going to
calm down as soon as you stop sending us
on suicide missions oh look at my
position serious Mula you think the
higher powers are going to stop
expecting envelopes from me because of
the homo's midlife crisis doctor's notes
don't cut it with these people be
reasonable then Rock China baham mamas
those bombs that's some out of
control man no Tony's some out of
control think about what he has got
you into but if you think about it too
long def of getting out of it not really
bro goodbye
byebye
vamos ooh rocka's on my list
now a new friend
perhaps
yay m
let me
think I think I should probably stop
it's already half past 8:00 p.m. if I do
all right so the missions were probably
going to go to
[Music]
midnight probably should stop it here
then we can comfortably finish it next
time yeah save at home oh is it because
I'm in am I in the mission right now
where is my
home where is my
home
oh where's my
home that's my
home no no no no
here let's watch some
TV do they have anything
new
otherwise someone is I don't
know son of a oh great
view let
me I'm trying to skip but won't let me
skip
uh did I break the
button
enter no it's not Japanese
keyboard okay I guess we got to watch it
I think it glitched because we were
driving into something
maybe en enjoy the sides I've enjoyed
the sides Plenty when I was driving on
my
own it's fine yeah calming taxi drive at
the end let's go you so
monage try Japanese
[Music]
keyboard or am my English one oops sorry
I broke the
window no nothing changes road rage is
just a media
invention no road rage is very
real it's unnecessary but it's very
real
uh I don't know when a Noir detective
monologue would go
like I know sorry guys
I I I was I was probably really boring
today sorry about that I just really
didn't really feel like you know just
didn't feel it I don't I don't think I
really felt
it
ah and I don't know it's kind of
dull right
now was a great stream really thank you
at least we got quite some progress
done also I was trying to not talk too
much over the dialogue but that you know
it just here's here's the proof it gets
kind of boring cuz they just blah blah
blah
blah nice piloting yeah I'm going to get
my pilot license before I get my car
driving ding license how about baby and
a jar peanut
butter you me and a jar of peanut
butter this ride will take forever it
wasn't even that far actually the
destination that I
chose I'm tired I want to
[Music]
sleep oh
there's less for me to miss that is true
I guess tomorrow AOE I think I'm going
to be more excited
again yeah going to learn all the
micromanaging
[Music]
micros I tramed I tramed about uh the
idol again you know that
Idol that I that that Sarah Gutenberg
met dreamed about her that I met
her and we talked
about we talked about the the problem
that we're having where like we just
kind of like stopped talking about the
thing that we wanted to
do and she was like explaining herself
so realistic like
wow she was making reasons up I was
making reasons up and and and then we
were like okay from now on new project
let's go let's let's let's be
communicative let's have
communication it was a
vision I don't know it's it's just like
it ended so awkwardly with like I think
I asked her for like an email address or
something like that so that uh jenma
could contact
her um and then then it just stopped cuz
I never got a reply and now it's been
like months
oh it's been like two or three months I
don't know feels like I should have I
should have at least like followed up
like like 3 days later or so and be like
hey this masan but like a month later I
feel like she's also feeling awkward
about
it what no that was my dream my dream
was like meeting her and like
you
know clearing up the
issue I don't know our leaders need to
admit that they get Road raage just like
us that's why they have
lios like I don't even want to do that
song cover anymore I feel like it's too
late but I may have a different
proposition I may have a different
proposition
H but then how do I say hey like forget
that idea
like how do I say
that just
like yeah it's
just hey buddy get this crap moving will
you no like I'm man you guys don't
understand understand the awkwardness
cuz you're not in the
position of
me don't get
it so awkward you know how much courage
it took me to get to this point in the
first
place complete the taxi right without
skipping from one Island to
another
oh man New York traffic I'm
going to sue the whole city taxi
drivers in New York
[Music]
all can I walk over to my bedroom
please I'm losing it now I'm losing it
Jenny I am losing it
Kimmy my
God
I'm joining in on the road
[Music]
rage I could take the blame so she would
feel less like it's on her hey so sorry
I've been super busy hell but like after
free mops that that's like taking a big
blame that isn't even
there how did I not no n I don't know I
think about it m
think about it I I'm thinking about
it but yeah this is how it ends today
I'm so sad we have no super chats to
read what is this
world this doesn't feel right like did
we slip into a different dimension this
is the wrong one isn't
it
haven't haven't had a moment like this
in a long time where I I don't have to
read anything cuz there is
[Music]
nothing you can't even send any
yeah we lost all
purpose
well
does this count not really but it's a
good exchange thank you for the green
super
chats
oh there are members super chats but we
said we're going to read them during
member
streams oh I got a I got a reply oh
thank
God oh than God she said yes no problem
oh that sounds really friendly I'm
happy
okay now it's now now it's next week I
really have to sort my out man
really have to sort it out guys have you
ever like tried to get a a a bill from
from booking.com how does it work like
cuz like I I saw like I had to get the
bill from booking.com for something and
uh I don't know how like cuz when I go
to the reservation the copy the the
build that I can access it says it's a
copy and it doesn't uh this one does not
work for
tax uh uh write
offs the first
email I think I checked that
too where's guys I'll call them
maybe no no no this one was prepaid for
booking.com so you know I worked in
hotels so I know this cuz so many times
booking
guests would be like can you give us the
bill and I'm like no you have to ask
booking.com this doesn't go through us
we can't give you the
bill and the truth is because like we
could give you a bill but it will say a
different price than the booking.com
bill because like part of it goes to
booking.com you
know and yeah so our bill would look
different than what you get from booking
outcom and you the customer would then
find out how much extra you paid just by
going through
booking.com
and booking.com doesn't want you to see
that so you have to go for
booking.com
yeah makes sense right
yeah so
okay okay okay okay
sneaky
hate third party reservations they can
be annoying I don't the ones that I
don't like like booking a combo whatever
is fine but the ones that are really
annoying uh was like voucher uh travel
agency voucher reservations but that
stuff was annoying I think
no should show you your invoices on your
account page I I guess I'll check again
but I feel like I already like looked
and then it said like it's there was
like a
transparent uh copy written all over the
the bill so it's not the original and
then underneath it said this one's not
Val valid for tax write offs I'm like
okay what the
okay I should go I guess cuz like
there's nothing so what where's what
what you know imagine the GIF GIF where
it's a guy in a suit with his hair in a
in a tied up and he's just like standing
there like looking around
like is that John
Travolta and Pulp Fiction uhhuh that's
me right now
like kind of like this but not quiet my
hands are not quiet like this
oh what is
uh
um
oh oh uh
[Music]
um all
right bye and
[Music]
enjy