[Music]
yay welcome back Eden welcome to Eden
Eternal K I got new oh my good gosh so
pretty wait have you found this sh well
yeah yeah I've been I've been hiding
away though where are you don't hide
from I don't know I wonder I wonder
where I am look at all these P oh my
God thank you for the gifts you guys
have been sending by the way I collected
them all are all the
gifts I look so cute I got a pop star
[Music]
outfit and some other Stu trying to find
you amongst the frogs and the random R I
think I got some things double too I
think I got the the Scythe double and
the key the flame key I got double I'll
give it away oh maybe that's pretty cool
yeah I think was some doubles too no
doubles wait how do I know which one I
find right
there how how does one oh here's ad I
have added you without your permission
without our
permission without the permission wait
where's G I'm in the Middle where are
you oh I see you you're the
you're the one you're the one with the
Grumpy Cat what oh my so cute I am
sister Shori you must repent for your
sins where did you go I can't tell you
anymore there's too many invite your
party show me your cat I am now in your
party yay I you were absolved from your
sins and I can't seem to activate any
skills here I am absolved of my sins
you're
absolved you're Absol I'm absolved
Abed three time I'm absolved of my
[Music]
sins are you looking at the kitty cat
yeah all my attention is on the kitty
cat I'm lost again where's the beautiful
kitty cat oh I see it it's right
here it is so cute the
face it's
grumpy grumpy kitty so maybe you guys
have noticed that we're now not just
gigy and Wawa anymore but no she already
called wind of us playing Eden Eternal
and you like it too I hear yeah I do
like it this is how I met some of like
my early friends oh oh my God and only
one remained don't over I'm going to sue
you okay sorry so Shion also took it
took took the the job upon herself to be
our healer right yes I will heal you
from your sins yay there are no sins I
am pure as it gets oh my god there a
phoenix Mount above
us
you how expensive was
that oh my God that's a big
Mount oh my God I want not
that that is a large large Mount that's
oh wow that's pretty cool you know
sometimes people send me like tweets
every once in a while there's like a
phoenix sighting in the sky some have
you seen one of those before I don't
know what what is it fireworks or just
some cloud formations or whatever with
the sun setting and then they're like oh
my God I saw you oh my God you were seen
in like Mexico oh my God you were seen
here and
there no no no no no that's I don't
think I've seen it I want to see no
really I want to see a phoenix
sighting maybe maybe I'll fly you want
to see a phoenix sting I'll fly over to
you
yay can you can you like do delivery too
when you go over yeah can you drop off
some food while you're
here I would love some food if you could
drop some
the fire some kfp some chicken nuggets
yeah that would be
good okay so today we're going to grind
a little bit more but shielding is a
little bit uh below our level so I don't
know you you're going to like join us on
our off your XP except like the dungeon
depending if let me go through we can do
the your main story Quest so we have to
walk story Quest I
they want me to do the ancient Water
waste but I have to do that solo which
was like not a requirement but it says
solo but when we're in a party and we
join solo as well we're actually in
there together oh really oh that's
pretty that's pretty helpful very
convenient very misleading very nice
well I got to go to the ancient
waterways I think that's like in the
swamp which I have forgotten where cuz I
can no longer
teleport oh yeah they take it away from
you I know they want you to pay $1 for
it or something I know oh my
God $1 per
one uh teleportation or for all
teleportations for all of them I'm not
sure oh well that's I mean
acceptable okay one request wait I'm
coming for a week oh
okay still cheap enough and one request
uh guys don't right click follow me
you'll always be like in my screen
covering up a lot of so try to follow me
manually okay and give me some
space okay not not you girls I mean the
the
kfp
oh there's a lot of them I met a kfp of
yours earlier they like ring off stream
I it's probably cuz they added you and
they where you
[Music]
were they they're observing our actions
how do we get
inventory how what in the swamp what's
the swamp region called uh I don't I
don't remember hold up where's the
portal I do not remember anything from
here I don't remember I think it's
around yeah around the corner outside
yeah uh you riding a huge bunny yeah I
think Rainbow Forest that sounds like a
place that would have have a marsh in it
rainbow rainbow full Forest okay yeah
I'm on my way and I got to go find the
tassos channel tassos channel okay
Channel that's like at the top right of
the map just just right click the wait
do you have the quest now I have the
quest yeah okay yeah just let let it
lead you automatically I got to defeat
Juan and Angela okay
I I'm warping to you once I get to it
for war no I have to go walk to the air
balloon and find my way
over I'm sorry to hear that I know why
don't I use my
legs wait I lost you oh it's just at the
top right um from the Rainbow Forest or
rainbow rainbow fall Forest oh there so
I just need you guys there yeah the
tassel J it
exists going in a
circle okay I think where am I I'm
there uh are you hitting the outside
mobs
first oh I'm at the uh complete right
you're kind of close though complete if
you press M and then look for my big
giant blue ball then you should be able
to find me you're big
giant blue ball I see it you're giant
blue ball you got a blue ball the
biggest ball yeah I only have one can I
CR here you must be doing well
in
November oh no I'm doing horrible
it's yes the big ball keeps growing and
growing I know it's going to keep
growing until the end of
it oh I like your alpaca it's all
Halloween yeah thank you I love
yeah it's so cute I collect I guess you
just wait for the gister now I'm on my
way I got lost cuz there's a mountain
can't believe there's a mountain let me
look at you let me look at Sho am want
to look at you I wish I could look at
you too but there's this guy in
the what did I tell you guys about
taking keeping some distance okay wow
wow you're so you're like a Christmas
angel
actually and what I'm a popar the angel
you would put a top the tree just like
SP on top of it I love the bunny the
bunny thing is that oh you paint with it
it was gift to me oh not no not that
bunny bun the bunny is so large The
Bunny The the bunny paintbrush right
actually was first released too now my
account is gone though and I also have
hey how long did you play back in the
day um I assume maybe like a year
from like when it started like the
release oh no I I don't know about the
release part but I remember I remember
like certain events and like Ro
bosses like they have Halloween bosses
and everyone has to get together to kill
it and it takes a really really long
time nice so we're all experienced in
this game to an extent to some extent
yeah nice all right uh do you need to
get into the dungeon
know uh is GJ here I'm here she's also
on you're just so short I can't find you
she her she's crying
me so
short I assume I assume I go here and
solo and then you guys are good yeah
yeah yeah yeah do we just walk in all
right oh there I I am in the solo
experience oh hey work I didn't know
that yeah was large both of you guys
same color Wings all right good luck I
We'll Kill Them All For You I already
forgot what my buttons are for shielding
let's go thank you oh c I keep
accidentally typing in
chat let's let shielding leech off of a
our
exp pulling everything level oh she's
pulling it all again oh no she is one of
those people I'm pulling all of them T
she's not even t maybe maybe not even a
tank I know but she is killer she's got
some
AOE I
know what a typical MMO
move the
Healer we should let her die shoting no
no so that she will learn her
lesson I don't know I feel like you do
do they give charms I feel like they
might give safety charms don't touch it
don't touch it oh thank you thank you at
least someone has my
back don't worry I'm killing it so it
can't touch you in the future in in the
future thank in the future I'm looking
out for your future
interest oh thank you can you also pay
for my college tuition then I can
try but you can't go very far okay I'll
miss you too much you have to stay
within the state oh I have to I have to
travel remotely I see yeah yeah you have
to commute from home or I won't pay for
your your college [\h__\h] wow what a what
a typical parrot you have to stay
home are you getting
goodp oh I have no idea honestly am I
getting good XP someone keep an eye on
my my
percentage I'm still getting I don't
need that I know wish you could pass
instead of greeting yeah cuz it feels so
greedy yeah you can pass you just to the
X
oh yeah but like I don't need the axe
cuz I'm doing certain things oh to my
inventory oh we're done wow that was
fast good
job nice I got to talk to
S Sid
s SI I I be like a son of a well son of
in a [\h__\h] son in son
in no what is he doing in
there how do I get to S actually oh
there you go I have the left
cck I will
follow wait where did you
go oh I'm I'm outside I'm about to head
to h s look my big ass bunny yeah
there's so many shiny people but the
bunny definitely helps yeah it's oh my
God it has a cute little animation that
hops such a large cute bunny I know it
also takes large poops all right I'm
heading to did you get that like did you
did you buy that or did somebody give it
to you oh no no I me spend on an
[Laughter]
MMO no it was it was gifted to me
although I did spend like once here
probably I was trying to get a
masquerade
outfit recently or in the past no no no
it was like in the past I don't know
they have it at the moment wait where
did you go there is really pretty I lost
you oh press um press um I'm heading
back to town really quick oh she went so
far already oh I'm hopping away I don't
know why your your bunny disappeared
from our view yeah right it's a
camouflage bunny I was following the
Bunny and the bunny left us and now I
don't know where I'm going but it's with
you and
spirit I'm trying to find your blue
ball just just press them it's in town
oh you got there so fast
oh I'm sorry it just so fast probably
fast did you find siib I did yeah it's a
frog dude oh after that I don't know
what quest I have like what what quest I
should do I can go to gos mountains are
you guys there in
like are we I think so I remember being
gos
Mountain oh yeah gos Mountain was one
before Beluga
mhm okay well I I got to go ahead there
now if you don't mind unless you want to
do your Beluga stuff now I'm not sure we
can go with you
to gos let's go where's the ah there the
teleportation gos Mountain wait what we
about to gos about to gos goip gosip
about what gossip gossip about new
members did you see the new
members oh yeah yeah people said one of
them are is like my sister e why from
the color the green and the black one I
think it's a two-toned hair probably
oh they're so
cute they're all I was I was so caught
off guard cuz I I literally did not see
the announcement oh the the announcement
no I was the same I didn't know when
they were coming cuz I didn't even know
that there were any coming didn't know
that it was like coming up at all
because they posted like some GTA
related thing right after it and I saw
the GTA related thing but I didn't see
that I like what but there was also the
problem that it's like it's in Japanese
and then you had to skim just to find
the English
part yeah yeah I was I was shocked when
I saw that I was like what what what you
just scrolling Twitter then you see it
and you're like what's going on yeah no
I saw the I saw the the the teaser
yesterday with like uh the regos members
and then said something about flow glow
and I'm like what what that looks like I
have to admit Flo's a a weird name to
say FL glow flow probably because their
lyrics will be flowing and they will be
glowing on the stage bars bars
bars maybe that's what it is then yeah
yeah regos felt a bit weird too at first
maybe but now it feels like normal easy
to say it's actually like devis it's
devis isn't it device instead of device
I thought they saw they call it as
devast though oh it's not device yeah it
was not
intive
it it's it has to be it's whatever you
want it to be I call it
Dev I call it de my bad that's my bad
you don't have to call things the way
they're going to call just like g g it's
a
nickname
yeah come
on did you did you guys see
ID when I saw the the was it a tiger
tiger girl yeah she's wearing like uh
jogging pants sweater sweat
sweatpants uhhuh amazing and it gives
like for yourself no no not for myself
but I I love the the chill Vibe of
wearing sweatpants for your oh default
form but yeah I was thinking oh my God
that style with next to ban sire I don't
know I feel like there's a good Synergy
there and also yeah she looks really
tall and she's blonde and her her art
style I feel like we'll have good
Synergy with Kyla so I want those two be
to be next to each
other and then she got the same kind of
eyes as laa so I want her to be next to
L
too so much good
Synergy yeah tiger and lion perfect for
those two tiger lion and then big
cat good combinations why are we here
are you do we have a quest G oh I'm
just yeah I got to kill a bunch of
gorillas for no reason besides that they
are here the bat gorillas I don't even
remember if I had a quest for that I
also don't remember these are wait how
many optional quests do you have these
are just like I think some many this
one's required oh holy crap it's so
bright why is the Sun so bright here the
sun came out I know but that was way too
fast for the
sun darn deserts oh good God the
bloom when are they Deus they're tonight
right no on Sunday no
oh no no no on the nth on the nth n9th
oh that makes sense a weekend yeah you
always got to give them a few Twitter
only days where they're just chilling on
Twitter let them warm themselves up what
they have
said they have I don't know what what
have they been saying what kind of
people are they I need to investigate as
well something in Japanese probably that
I cannot understand yeah I've been
staring at the but I can't read their
tweets there's one person who spoken a
bit of English they said like I Google
translated this so like I should reply
to hey I wonder if anybody can speak
English from them that one girl
apparently
not I think Rica is like a a rare one
mhm I guess so yeah it's it's a rare
thing that's fine they can still learn
English or they can try their best with
passion engl English what if you just
make them learn
[Laughter]
Spanish someone's going to do it we need
more Spanish
speakers yeah bring them on actually is
it it must be really rare to have maybe
a Japanese person also speak Spanish
thinking about it cuz the vowel
pronunciations are really far
away what this sayy is this a a pet or a
play what the heck do I need to kill
how did you manage to look like
that look like
what there's this like big gorilla here
looks
like like not like the
other characters that I've
seen big
monkey monkey monkey I feel so weird
hearing the screams of the
gorillas W you still oh there now can
I CL cck oh I right that works ah you
can click on a point in the map and it
will move you there did you know that
yeah oh my God quality of life amazing
it's been a while yeah it
has how
convenient I it's also nice that they
lower the requirements for when you need
to like kill things I think back then
you had to kill 26 of something oh yeah
that I I I think I remember that stuff
ing they have to adjust this game for
the times you know that's true the
Zoomer tion span
exactly W how far did you get into the
game by the way like was there a
particular map you
stopped uh I I just remember I was like
max level and all I was doing was like
raiding and and Guild Wars and stuff
like that PVP wow yeah I was so addicted
to all of these anim more pgs and once a
new one came out I just switched to a
new one and then I tried to gr there as
hard as I
could I was a pro this one
huh but now we're
bad I didn't abandon this one but you
know things happen it abandoned us yeah
yeah yeah honestly it did it freaking
did did you ever play maple
story should guys we should play maple
story I have never played St there's a
really really big event that's in 2
weeks and it's the best time to start
maple story so you want me to gra that
one yes look like M it's a really big
event what's the what's the event though
um it's like their hyper burning event
where uh for until Level 250 you level
basically twice per level or like so
it's like plus two on top of the level
so you go in increments of Threes And
then you reach end game well not end
game but mid game
faster are you going to Beluga Bay right
now uh I have to turn into Quest but
I'll come back there so let me just turn
in everything I have cuz I cannot Auto
teleport okay
okay hear the little nashing of the
keyboard G are you doing quests no I'm
just hitting things while where I'm
standing maybe I'll try this are you
guys about to do a dungeon for your
thing I don't know I don't have any
Quest right now at all oh
really you can um you can pick up your
quest or like some some side quest I
don't want to hold you guys
up no I'm waiting for
you no no it's okay it's okay cuz I'm
doing like all quests I can so I can
level up faster oh okay even the side
quest the the small ones oh actually I
found the main quest that I didn't do
yet
which Quest is that one m a Roa 2 level
23 you H it's it is a it
is it it's something with a dungeon oh
it's a dungeon Quest I do the dungeon
you do that one too what the heck why
did I not do that one
yet there we go I'm traveling across the
land Isn't it nice I like traveling
acoss cross the land with my
mount it is so noal until like
everything starts chasing you and then
you die but I don't think they do that
oh healer so
squishy I know I'm squish
squish okay I'll wait by the dungeon I
suppose is it that same map yeah it's uh
at the top right of the map
AA why you hitting me H Oh I thought
that was a player that's an NPC no no
players can't hit you unless you du them
yeah yeah I know what where did that
come from ah here there's another
person must kill H up must kill I will
come stand by the dungeon
too okay
welcome on my
way how do I click
there oh are you
got oh oh okay I
had oh
aoda I assume I can did we not go into
this dungeon giggy last time we missed
it I'm not sure I think we missed it
maybe that's an optional one H it does
say main quest but I don't think you
even have to do any of the main quests
anyway oh wow there's so much like Lion
King
here all right I am here do as you wish
I will try to
join uh so
this are we going in we enter a solo I
guess so yeah Solo solo all right you
have to Quest right I don't know uh I do
not but I will run it I am allowed to
run it oh I remember this I got the
quest in the city you remember that I
don't have the quest it's okay though
I'm just getting XP
anyway so Ro
solo yeah Solo solo okay wait is this is
this again uh where I need to talk to
someone first wait wait wait wa I might
have to talk to someone outside first
again take your time take your time not
like last time this place oh yeah
vaguely I think there's poison in here
maybe vaguely
remember or maybe I'm lying no there's
no poison here this I lied this is not
the dungeon
oh GG's already starting I canceled my
cast I canceled my cast no no it's okay
I canc my I cancel my
cast I'm back I'm back welcome
back all right go my tank I'm
going he the music in here is so cute
what the
heck why do they want the clar we why
are they hating you hey why why are you
why are you AG them sh what are you
doing wrong I don't know maybe you don't
add you're standing too close no you're
standing too close no no you just don't
hit hard enough they thought you were
pathetic I'm not
pathetic no you're fine we need one more
person to join us and be the tank for us
a real
tank I like this song
actually it sounds kind of
like nightmarish or Halloween is it's
cute why don't you like Halloween you
should like it I love
Halloween you are throwing them
again stop throwing
them okay I I wanted to say I saw your
nun outfit so cute oh yeah yeah thank
you like it my go it was blinding my
eyes I I can't help it I'm just a
sunshine
[Music]
salvio your salvation has
come yes you will be absolved of your
sins from Sister
shiori yes uh-oh I'm not absolving that
sin
though talk to [\h__\h] ah oh there's
dinosaurus what kind of quest is this
the NPC is behind
me oops okay you're far away well you
don't need healing right now anyway I
think who put this dinosaur here I don't
know is it gooy
ball in her Halloween Dragon they're
different my bad it's not a dinosaur
it's a dragon yeah those are
extinct this is a dragon
dinosaur
related one day we will get a
dinosaur in
Holo a real one that looks like a
dinosaur and is a dinosaur it talks like
one oh I'm in
okay I meant a grill a grill no no we
are getting a
[Music]
dinosaur a real
dinosaur and then and then she'll let us
like ride her can be our Mount too yeah
yeah yeah and she can carry all of us
little
arms I can't wait for her dance practice
she'll be so cute oh my God on the big
stage and then she's just she needs all
the space she can get or she'll step on
us and then she just eats the whole
audience because she's so hungry oh my
God I'm so
excited well technically she can eat
your kfp they look pretty
Ed they do look
tasty yeah if I had to pick one to eat
probably
them dark dragon jeto that sounds like a
such a chuno
name he's got a bow nice a good bow why
did he not use
it uh I'm a cleric build crap no leave
me alone I'm too leave her
[Music]
alone
die okay dang what is this thing
underground that doesn't look very holy
for sister shiori touch it touch
it corruption
Arc you cannot corrupt what is already
corrupted I thought you were a
sister I am a sister that doesn't mean I
lead a holy chap
what kind of Chapel is this I don't who
knows
that's yeah is a pierce guy outside no
wait the Pierce guy why is it leading me
there no it's probably just outside it m
not work
sometimes fantasy setting and then
there's just like these Mecca and these
cars that go the the desert yeah I mean
the the the one like it
the the car doesn't really fit in so
well I
think the I know it must have really
good wheelster to be able to run or like
in these true areas
true oh I got to kill more dinosaurs
now not the
dinosaurs oh sorry the dragons actually
these are
draks I'm just going to kill
sorry for anyone named Drake my
quest I can't get on my
Mount yeah you have to do it from your
inventory it's finicky so
evil it's evil Eternal evil
Eternal I don't want any of these I'll
take
this achieve and accomplish chenana hero
what
nice but I guess cuz I did the dungeon
here nice
okay shine are you doing a quest yeah I
got to killed this dude named mathus
what quest is that it's just uh one of
my main ones what's you call it's D
though the fifth clue of the Lost
Civilization
ooh and then I probably have to run the
dungeon that we just
did perfect I'm just assuming right now
that I will eventually have to do it
again no
problem I'll get another little small
Quest if I I think I still have a
couple I'm going to go be a mage so I
can are you switching to Mage now is
kind of frustrating to level like healer
classes yeah it is like I'm trying to
kill things fast yeah got to love all
these classes that's why you always got
to like go around love a partner who
brings you through and fights everything
for
you which could be us it could be us
we'll be that for you I'm killing I'm
killing Devils do you need
this oh I I need a rock claw drinks now
oh I need those too again okay there you
go I'm also doing unquenched
first o so thirsty
huh my first can never be
quenched never I am born thirsty never
ever so nothing we can nothing we do
will quench The Thirst you have nothing
you can do what if I try really hard to
quench that thirst
M I try harder that's pathetic talk it's
not what if it's I will
I will yes okay I like I will punch that
thirst don't worry give it a try then
okay puts my leg up on the wall no what
FPS her
hair
hair we're going to see some more weird
fan art
giggy I'm using the one where grabbing
your ass
I saw I
saw it's beautiful it's so beautiful
it's bootiful you yeah it's
bootyful and then there's just half
invisible non Shi in the background have
you seen the M it's like I consent and
then there's like is there someone you
forgot to ask I think I didn't see that
before you're such a meme Lord let me
find it I'll send it to you
Quest done what are these alpaka tokens
and why is this the first one I'm
getting the heck what does alpaka tokens
do collect 10 and trade them for an
alpaka mystery capsule wow you may have
a chance to win fabulous costumes oh
they're fora hey
yo what cash
shopa no way you could get that so
easily actually they were pretty lenient
with things uh at some point
cuz they gave you free outfits I'm
pretty sure they just couldn't be
dyed ah ah yeah true true true I
wouldn't mind using my
money I found
theage ass adult no honestly just the
payment option is stopping me yeah it
makes it so
difficult I remember when I was younger
um I think I also didn't have like
anything proper to pay so I went to the
store and bought the pay safe
cards aw with my little money I bought
like 5o five buck paysafe cards
and just got whatever I could get there
thank you thank
you uh gorilla
[Music]
F single
player is it a
dungeon I think so Shale Cavern I'm
going to level up I'm going to level up
are we going to have to
go yeah you can you guys can
come it's we must
help on my way oh I wonder if we can get
a quest for that too if we
already yeah probably I just spammed all
the quest
here okay let me finish this Quest I can
just run over
there run geky run with your spots run
spatu me and my beautiful spatu spat and
beautiful
ala uh so where's
shelding I'm at sh Cavern aha
oops okay let me just uh redo my hot
keys I just changed into like a Bard
here over here hot I don't have any b b
CL class skills I don't know
torado that's it I got nothing
else how am I supposed to kill things I
have
arrived welcome
shelding C
Cavern a maybe I can't be a b yet I got
a grind someone kill things for me I'm a
Bard okay okay okay okay okay I'm
killing thank you go faster I'm as as I
can you call that f that's pathetic I'm
trying I'm trying I'm
trying I want to unlock bar classes so I
can sing and be annoying bar so cute
actually BS are useful for like hiding
but they changed things they changed it
yeah
why so you could spam this uh burn skill
and it was instant so what people would
do is they would spam it kite and
everyone in the party would help kill
things I remember doing that they made
it yeah it was so useful and then people
would get you to pay them so they could
do it for you really and then they took
it
out yeah you speed that's evil will you
accept
J huh except what you got proposed to
look at your top left oh no what I do is
I leave them
[Music]
hanging
propos what you just leave it open well
yeah yeah because if I ask that someone
else my
right oh is that how work is
true proposal I appreciate you thank you
currently being proposed to please wait
until she Mak up her mind you're
[Music]
amazing okay I'm in the dungeon I'm
going okay I come
there let me let me switch to my cleric
as well I can't wait for Shaman I can
kind of be lazy as a
shaman chill Cavern
okay I'm here yay attack
attack oh what is this what's this
one but it's cloth
armor I didn't expect this in the desert
I guess I should actually she rejected
me let's
[Music]
go actually we do need a fourth player
to join us you know do you know why we
need a fourth player to join us cuz when
me and giggy marry then shiy will be
like alone and third Wheeling she needs
to Fourth wheel it's it's okay I can you
want to get married why
why maybe they allow triangle mares here
in this game I I don't know about that
love is beautiful we need to get married
all of us
oops she only likes to watch okay what
if I just do like I make an alternate
account I never use it and I just
propose to
myself and then no way online at the
same time though well no you can just
make two accounts yeah but you got to be
online at the same time locations I
guess I don't think you can send a
proposal to someone who's offline and
then the other persones it when they're
onl character an account I see yeah yeah
they're going to be like this isn't how
are you proposing to this offline person
are you sure you're opposing to a real
person to a
bot you remember those Bots where like
uh you can buy for levels or something I
mean I don't I never saw like where you
can buy them but I saw them running
around in like Fly for Fun in the
beginner area running around do you know
Fly for Fun damn it I've heard of it
that's where we can fly I think yeah for
fun on the skateboards on the snowboard
skateboards those were so fun that was
like my first anime RPG
trickster never I wanted to play it I
never got like too far though cuz
I yeah me too and I didn't understand
anything yeah say oh crap no please I'm
just a Healer don't wor don't worry
don't worry I'll take care of
him look at me look at me guys
oh good God why does he so into
me he wants cat oo I could use that yes
take it take it g did you just ran past
the boss I feel like you did that last
see it I didn't see it you did the same
thing before only Kara went for it
didn't even see the boss you have an
illness that's called boss blindness I
think she she's too short to see
things Blends in yeah I did not call
giggy giggity but maybe I should call
her giggity giggity ooh this we got to
talk to it has G
healing take it
sh I will I will take whatever wait oh I
need to I need to enter this dungeon in
multiplayer mode not Sol what the heck
but same
thing okay it's pretty fast after all
yeah let me just get out of here but
right now you you did it uh like
solo I do solo okay I we I'll do it h
cuz yeah maybe you can immediately
accept the daily Quest from the soul
Guardian cuz the soul Guardian gives you
a daily quest to do it in multiplayer
mode oh is my notice
or yes it is yeah the guy right there ja
Cavern the the soul Garden
okay all right I accepted it multiplayer
let's go I'm going my
crap
Y is the multiplayer like a little
harder might
be oh yeah
might yeah technically they should
that's why UHS there you go makes
sense yeah they expect four people for
this
yeah they're hurting
me well I hope you like
it I do and then I have a beautiful
angel who heals me right
after yeah damn it I should have
been now I missed the times of being a
Healer you get all the compl so like
yeah it's not grateful work I think
people are ungrateful usually usually
feel like I feel like people were
grateful and I could just feel like a
girly girl cuz I never want to be the
healer I always wanted to be the healer
that's good I never wanted to take the
the sword into my hand and cut people's
throats and see their blood dripping I
didn't want to do that you know I wanted
something more peaceful
Paladin yeah no not my kind of
thing if
anything ma then
magic this time I'm I'm this time I'm
Cutthroat this time I'm coming for blood
we
[Music]
kill I want to be damage
dealer I want to be op yeah I like DPS
too I like being a hunter I think mhm
with the pet in this game or in like any
kind of game uh usually I like being a
gunner in games oh
crap heal me I am I
am too
much you uh thank
you help why are they hurting so much
now because it's multiplayer it's a
little it's not a walk in the Park
anymore
yeah I keep on hearing what you can get
the the those sounds as I keep on
sounding like World of Warcraft um
merlocks to
me do you hear
it sometimes well that also sounded like
a grim I think you're too squishy Gigi
no no no it's fine I have a beautiful
healer you can't be so cocky anymore now
I know you're not a
everyone
okay she's still she's still running so
fast as if it depends on her legs you
see the the boss now I see the boss now
why' you put him there he's
hiding maybe you will regret seeing it
soon kill me
uhoh I know we're doing
good ow is that like is that magic
circle on the ground from you girls or
from the Enemy No it's from them oh see
like those dark circles just assume it's
from them oh it's been a while oh they
Dro better items and more items lots of
stuff of stuff wow nothing that I
need goodbye oh wait oh what
okay mhm mhm gigg just
Runing I'm dying I'm
dying
[Music]
I'm there's a Revival item I have a
Revival item don't worry don't
worry oh good God oh my
[Music]
God oh
no don't the where's Kiara where's Kar
I'm here I'm I'm here behind oh Jesus
Christ don't die don't get even more
mobs also no what the heck in the
dungeon I forgot yeah I'm I'm somewhere
else at the walk
B just run Kiara I'll heal
you after I heal myself just run back to
the entrance okay I'm dying I'm dying
I'm dying run run run where is the oh
y I'm on my way have you have you
learned your lesson lesson not
learned oh no K it's okay I'll I'll
revive you if you just want to CH on the
ground right there yeah but I don't know
if you can get here with old enemies oh
Jesus Christ I Jesus Christ I cannot
they're coming after me they're coming
after me why
they um oh because texting in chat they
ran to the last person left in the
dungeon who still alive what'll it'll be
me once I get
there I I can use my Revival item oh
Jesus Christ don't use the Revival item
why not it doesn't revive you with the
dungeon oh I all the way
back oh okay I'm in the cavern I I'm
here I'm here y I'm here too I'm going
back in hold up hold up
let's dad
brat
brat no no no please
serves your rights to die back this
instance young woman there's a giant
Guardian right
here mhm oh actually I think if you take
too long um Mom supp to respawn yeah oh
I was like why are they behind
us well no that's uh that's because
we're doing a multiplayer session I
think M recruiting
tank for future dungeons
lft
owie girl
girl how can I heal
you ow
owie shoting just to buff you constantly
on gigy ow owie always heal
her I can't attack can't heal you if you
keep running yeah same I can't attack if
you
keep you guys already have like a a heal
buff
anyway oh yeah those beautiful Buffs oh
yeah heart truth that's what had to
learn close to
me no worries I I'm I'm not like her I I
believe in Kiara it
is oh she's so squishy I think you're
too squishy no I'm not I'm not so
squishy we need to put you on the Le ow
ow yeah or we just need to break your
legs how much HP do you have actually I
only have like a 100 more than you but
maybe maybe my defenses oh no because
you're agroing all of
them it's just cuz you're agroing them
and they constantly only hit you they
hurt they should just take them one at a
time one at a time what are we slow
dungeon
clearers see this is what I mean by
being a cleric is
ungrateful we have we have a claric we
can take
more yeah I I would use that logic
normally
probably a he doesn't even get to attack
yeah yeah kill him kill him he let's go
let's go nice nice button mashing
M
mhm MH mhm there we go
nice M crit magic uh more
magic more
magic they're all like magic stuff I'll
take you destroy why would you destroy
this thing maybe this one I don't know
what is destroying this do what is that
I don't know but you can hit it are you
destroying our exit
no what is that Unchained in item oh you
can summon something ah one of those
just okay I don't really care about
that talk to
pierce Yay good job
oh I have so much crap in my inventory
yeah this dungeon really shoved
garbage maybe I'll level a different
class right now
because my my fif class is like maximum
exp but the other one's lagging behind
the main class is lagging behind yeah so
for whatever you wish for well how do
you what's the window again how to okay
okay um
yeah I got a level B too to 35 so I'mma
oh I'mma become a bar now okay
yeah Earth shock
tornado I guess we can both heal
gigy
yay I don't know I deserve it have to
heal her you stff
[Music]
please
revive okay okay what's
next what's next is I got to sell all my
[\h__\h] I got to clear my
inventory
yeah
here maybe now I'll need to use my Mana
pots oh it's a what's my
strongest I need to use use the guitars
right what's my strongest yeah you have
to
uh Marshall handmade sacred 8009
865 wow it's golden
too so much crap in my
inventory
[Music]
same this is beautiful
this is beautiful ah oh I have the
Legacy loot oh yeah uh shooting did you
find the Legacy things did you figure
out how to get those things the the what
I don't know what that is H I don't
remember how I got that Eva I think
giggy explained it to me um it's with
the codes the code you can put a code in
your a cash shop and then they give you
a bunch of items I forgot what was Eden
500K
yeah I did see it I didn't actually inut
the code though oh you should put the
code and it gives you a bunch of level
30 stuff oh wow but we're not even level
30 at least I'm not oh you can wear it
it's just like IEM level
30 oh okay I I shall look into it when I
can it's good stuff if you if you get it
lit too late then it might not be good
enough anymore oh how do you how do you
put the code in
uh go to the cash shop or click wherever
the cash shop is I don't even know where
it is oh yeah it is I and then reward
code and it should be in the cash up
inventory once you put it
in it just opened up uh the site can't
be reached oh there it
[Laughter]
is what's the code again Eden
500k okay
yep it work thank
you oh I didn't wear a necklace yet
there we
go what's this the mission for exive
title of son of
Eternity probably because it's not
Halloween anymore Eden Moon you can also
redeem apparently Global pre-register EV
Eden moon going to try
that I don't know what it does but it
gave something
acquired finished H what's
happening it oh I got a title Eternal
Guardian successfully
read
o it gives a portable bang and a noble
pass for one
day wow
what what the Eden 500k oh Eden Moon
Eden Moon there's also a coat yeah
there's more coats
oh this is so cute thank you for the
gifts
everyone thank you Eden Moon Eden Moon
Yeah like you know a
moon you know how to spell Moon I
hope yeah wait sorry where do you put it
in uh press I and then there's the the
code at the bottom it should do a popup
window and then you can there eat the
moon wow so many codes are they more
that we don't know
about probably like temporary
though
y why are the merchant so far come to
me oh portable bag
nice oh you're a you dies
useless is that maybe this guy give me
your [\h__\h] H might use
this
okay please one
day and my God
Merchant more
more more
more more charms more amulets so many I
need to put them in my bank
are you girl keeping the treasure map
pieces them yeah I don't know for what
though I just have them combine the
treasure maps I thre them out I don't
want
them you hate treasure yeah well it's a
really good treasure I doubt it
wow
ooh level requirement first
pretty perfume the scent lingers long
after its wear leaves close your eyes
and you'll still smell the sweet
fragrant perfume wafting through the air
what does it do effect last 6 hours is
this does this make me irresistible will
people run after me more than they
already do I think you're already
irresistible that's why you're chasing
you yeah imagine you
smell what if you smells stinky and
people still like really like that
smell well some people might see it as
stinky
anyway just because it's too
intense I have to get Shaman to level 30
for warlock oh oh Shaman is
fun can't wait to put totem
down okay I'm going to try to kill some
mobs here with B at level
one let's see oh that's big
damage what the heck there's a
sapling what it's not bad at all thank
you for the however I must be a
woman must be a Som I feel like I'm
stronger than I was with my
Thief what I've learned to skill vocal
bomb what class are you uh Bard oh oh
well Bard's not an attacker they're
buffers yeah but my attack is stronger
like I'm I'm clearing these mobs faster
than with my feet somehow [\h__\h] what the
[\h__\h] did I dis
sumon so
strong already level eight level 9 it
goes fast oh this is a
special special dinosaur or he was a
special
dinosaur but he's no longer
mm he'll be in the history my
books oh my God level 10 thank you for
the XP this is so
helpful myself okay I'm getting my
levels too don't get the wrong idea
getting potions from you you are such a
gracious host I I'm just trying to you
know provide for our family yeah it's a
family once
again we're always a family so
tit our beautiful beautiful family I
think I can go to Beluga Bay now okay
yeah I have one main quest there
oh e guitar sounds
there's what is this let me just finish
the quest here so I don't have to come
back I hate
deserts yeah they're not great looks
just like a desert ravenous
Pumas appeared I want desert really bad
I'm thinking about ordering some
coffee coffee oh wait dessert isn't that
more like a drink I want a sweet coffee
and then it's like a dessert you
know uh why did you get isn't tiam Su
like a coffee yeah that's a coffee
dessert get yourself a nice tiam Su I
want a
tiu I know and you should get a tiam
su all right I want to level up my bar
too everyone's ling
up just
grinding what does this one do oh I
think this is
the oh that's a buff I
see don't don't attack my
healer attack attack I have a a non
Shield heal oh be careful don't don't
attack
them y be nice don't should pull
sto to
Puma oh I need to get
a attack oh I like those I've I've never
seen them before I only hear the legends
of the dino nuggies we'll make you
one yeah they're such fine shapes to dip
ah when you say you'll make me one you
just mean you going from the freezer
I'll make you one from the
freezer okay I mean self-made would
probably not turn out so well yeah
they're genetically engineered to taste
so
good let me put myk you where is my
Mount here I'm going
to
perhaps uh look for a quest instead of
mindlessly killing
monsters
okay however I would also still
appreciate you mindlessly
good I just think that there is a
benefit into my there's a benefit for
all of us oh
[Music]
[Applause]
really well it really helps
family yeah if you're not a beluga Bay
then you won't get the I will go to
Beluga Bay too I will head there soon
then for I now have Quest oh okay I'm
out of quest in that
area Beluga Bay time I love Beluga
Bay Beluga where's the beluga
whale can you make your best whale
[Music]
sound so
peaceful it's also kind of like a how
actually yeah but also whale sound also
kind of more like cing cing money money
money money into the game credit card
swipe I don't think that's I don't like
those whales those aren't my whales um
where's my healer where's my
healer on my way on my way wait I'm I'm
also healer where the heck did you go
why are you so
far I move the jellies I see well I need
to talk to something some soul Guardian
in
here always make sure to activate the
crystals the teleportation crystals yes
don't
forget uhoh my poor healers is being
attacked what's the last game you spent
money
on Fire Emblem
Heroes you mean money as in not just
buying the game but buying something in
the game yeah money
money might have been might have not
done that since Ark Knights I don't know
oh what you buy in Ark Knights new
character all the pretty all the pretty
skins
ah have really good skins gotta PS
aren't they making like another game
yes awaiting it eagerly yeah they're
doing like a 3D Ark knights with mostly
like it's very different it's not a
tower defense system anymore but I'm so
excited looks so good the previews look
so good I need to
BL I want to play let's let's grind day
one
together oh I am so in if we get
perms oh hopefully they had like a demo
and I was like okay you know what we
don't have terms for the game but I'm
just going to try sign up for the demo
anyway um and I signed up as Takara
because the demo was like for
influencers you know oh yeah and and so
you had to put in like your socials and
so on and only not everybody got
approved they approved me and I was like
jenma does this mean I have terms for
the game this is like unusual like this
is not how we normally do it then I was
unsure so I never ended up
playing cuz yeah I didn't really it
wasn't official terms but but I mean
they kind of approved me so they went
through that list
themselves no I missed my chance I guess
cuz I I was I wasn't too confident about
it there there there yeah I've been
waiting for the Ian
release I don't know how much longer it
takes I've been really wanting another
gacha to get
into yeah I'm looking forward to all
these games yeah need another I need
another star I don't think I want to
play Star rail there's too much reading
I like it though I do like the read many
characters you have to get aive my ISS
is like I can't I keep up but then I
stop playing and then there's more
characters I'm like who the heck is this
now yeah and then I feel like since it's
a strategy game they keep power creeping
the other
characters
a so people are like it's good to have
this character because it makes your
team better and now you're behind cuz
you sto playing
N I just do like my basic characters I
haven't spent money on that one you have
it you're so
good I
guess I played it when it was released
and then I was like how can I turn down
the double $100 pack and then I bought
it
who do you always spend money on your
games I love spending money
ons you're the most ideal player that
they hoping for I really good consumer I
fall for marketing tactics really easily
and I'm aware of it yeah do you fall for
like fish scams too like click on this
for a coupon no I don't I I fall for
like targeted advertising when you're
like scrolling your Twitter and then
there's like an ad and then you see it
you're like hey maybe I do want
this G no those are usually like bad
quality weird weird weird doesn't make
you happy that's the question doesn't
make me happy dubdub doesn't make you
happy GG do you like spending money on
these things I don't know sometimes it
makes me happy and then sometimes it
doesn't make me
happy oh it has to do with what I get
you're happy I see
of Goa
yeah my quest is called scrub a dubdub
oh me too I have that oh someone help me
I agroed the big
crab H sorry I'm
busy both of the bars are like
nah
nah I do need to kill some Eagles soon
but that that can wait I do IR claw
Eagles yeah I I'm killing them now I'm
accepting everything first so I don't
have to like come back
to are you getting my kills right
now um I I guess
so automatic
questing no finger lifted get two more
Quest I have to kill a tide Rock Turtle
but I can't find one
I help kill Eagles actually I'll kill
the the shells stuff do you have the
Quest for
biotechnology H I can accept it I have
that one accept all the quest we can
just do
it okay I I must go to accept it though
but first I must kill the the
Eagles what's the it that um you always
have to change your equipment when you
change certain class
oh well at least you can always have the
the cloes on you just got to have the
sets like
inserted oh there's a set stuff oh yeah
just for the cloo clothing not for the
weapons oh that
sucks a little bit of a quality of
life so
H okay uh Iron Claw Eagles you shall be
mine
[Music]
fine that's probably why I never made
like alternate alternate accounts for
these things it's like this is my main I
don't really want to grind anymore yeah
I usually also never made any more
characters than my main except in World
of Warcraft because in World of Warcraft
after a certain level I was like cuz I
was still a tiny baby when I played
World of Warcraft I was like H somehow I
can't get past level
42 and then I kept on making new
characters
and another one and another cuz I really
loved the character creation in World of
Warcraft 2
to I don't know it wasn't even that
special but for me that was like another
way of playing
Sims the dress up World of Warcraft no
just yeah the World of Warcraft
character creation was for me like
playing Sims oh I like the Sims I hope
the next one is a good game uh well Sims
5 is not happening anymore oh really
yeah they announced that they're they're
canceling Sims 5 and just forever
continuing to add expansion packs to
Sims 4 cuz they're focusing on
it they they're doing something else
they're making something else but it's
not Sims 5 yeah it sounds like like some
kind of
multiplayer a movie what's it going to
be the community is a little bit
disappointed I also wanted the Sims 5
well there's a there's an Asian
equivalent I I know what you mean I I'm
interested in playing that too but
that's to me that's just a different
game I I want Sims 5 also that's
true but that be a witch in there oh
yeah enoy
enoy yeah I need to play that I think
actually I think I did uh uh uh input
per request for the I'm looking it
up it looks so good they just moved the
release to
when when die you oh the graphics are so
realistic noise wh yeah it's like Korean
is isn't it like in terms of the models
oh my God gosh
enoy I just want to make my anime voice
in
there 28th March
[Music]
oh I just I don't know I was reminded um
that
GTA is coming soon I thought it was like
5 years away or so by now you had the
new GTA is like spring 2025 or what was
it that's so soon that's crazy I've
almost I feel like it's been in
development so long that that wait what
GTA 6 is it GTA 6
yeah theand simulator feel like just
just a couple of months ago I was like
oh like looking at the announcement and
I'm like oh that's going to take like 5
years
but hasn't it only been it probably took
them a while I think they just kept it
like pushed up okay it's fall
2025 but that's still like like only
like a little bit less is it is it fall
or is it uh winter now what would you
say oh okay then it's a year to
go they seem to be on track so I'm
excited GTA it's going to be good it's
going to be my first trip to
Florida o it's going to suck have you
girls been to Florida before Oh only
once I just hear a lot of Florida
news what I have been once the Florida
news Florida man
oh how how is it just don't be like a
hurricane that's true it's very humid um
yeah yeah that's about
it nice beaches hum they have alligators
if you're is it more humid than
Japan I don't I want to say Japan just
kind of actually I don't know just
assume it sucks
no offense anyone in
Florida oh I remember these
goblins I'm killing Wizards now I have
the punish the Glutton Quest
now shielding you 25 you're like so
close to us now oh I guess so let's go
you're catching up catching
up man I ordered like a a home grocery
service and they didn't even have most
of the crap I wanted so I'm so
disappointed does that mean you still
have to go and get it kind of they only
gave you basic stuff like I asked for
grits like the things that Wen Frozen or
or vegetables they they managed to get
me but everything else is healthy not so
much l I'm so lame I know useless I know
what's the point of paying more to get
it delivered if you're not going to give
me what I want
yeah they didn't even substitute for it
I wanted freaking broccoli they didn't
substitute broccoli where's my freaking
broccoli make your own broccoli you
could like grow it myself yeah grow it
in win go outside rip out a tree and eat
it why you make things so
complicated yeah
probably Trappers
[Music]
small the Yum Yum trees as you like to
say when you feed it to a cute
dog the Yum Yum Tree yeah yum yum treat
yum yum
trees oh trees yes I I watched some some
Samu dog videos and when they feed their
dogos their s dog uh broccoli then it's
called the Yum Yum tree
o I
think very
sophisticated cuz dog likes Yum Yum
Tree like yum yums I like Yum Yum Tree
me
too where the hell are the Trappers
there reminds me of this this has well
the word Yum Yum Tree reminds me of this
Tick Tock cat who sucks on its paws and
then the owner calls it paaw time and
Records the cat just sucking on its paw
and it gets like really anxious and mad
if um the owner doesn't like pick up its
legs and bring its paws to its mouth so
they needed like an hour every day for
the cat to suck on its
paws cute that's so cute it sucks on his
paws so much the paws get all
swollen
a that's a bit
much yeah should give it something else
to suck on why will it it Wass to suck
on
this when my when my when my cats were
still babies when I first got them I
guess I got them like a little bit too
early cuz they still wanted to suck on
something and so they always sucked on
my fingers it actually hurts a little
bit but it was cute so I had to let them
do
it I felt like Mommy they just sucked on
each other I had to get them to stop it
was kind of
G sucked where no it's not cute I don't
know what they were sucking on so I had
to make them stop don't make it so L
it's wholesome it's cute they're they're
boy cats I didn't want them to get
infected if their mouth spin in like
weird [\h__\h] what do you mean where what
do you mean what am I mean what do you
mean you're making it so cursed
cheing it's the cute
thing I don't know I don't know sucking
each other's Paws no they Wen sucking
each other's Paws I I was scared of what
they were sucking was the issue cuz they
were looking for tee but they're boy
cats they don't have they don't have the
girl teeth oh so they're just knobbing
on each
other I think so they were looking for
milky but you you do not get the proper
milky from
that you
you cursed cursed yes cursed cursed do
they no longer do that yeah they stopped
they stopped they grew out of that phase
thankfully I have stopped
it my preventative
measures what if we had cats but the
cats were
[Laughter]
freaky uh I I think if the cats and Shi
are freaky that's too much somebody
needs to be stopped She sto them they're
no longer
freaky yeah yeah they're cats now good
good I took them to church and
everything fall from their
sins cats and
church can you
imagine C Church profile picture that it
was like a a cat with a nun
outfit
a wait sh you you're a cat owner right
yeah do you put your cat in clothes
uh no they don't like it good I did not
teach them young enough yeah no they
don't they don't want to be in
cloes
yeah they want they shouldn't be in
cloves with dogs I understand but cats
leave them alone leave them alone guys
they should be in
clothes no no I will Force One into a
clothes no no
no no I tried to give them a cur hat but
they always fight it m cuz they don't
want to be in
cloves that's true they need to cover
up this is a world where you have to
cover up or you'll be seen
as they're covered up they have they
have fur on them cover them up no I will
show you what's
naked isn't there that one naked cat
like the Egyptian
one oh yeah okay that one's
naked I think I think that cat it would
be cute if you would put a sweater on
that cat a self- knitted tiny sweater
that' be kind of cute but besides that
no so you can only dress up one kind of
cat yes the furry kind yes the furry
kind if the cat if the cat wants to be
dressed it okay
like I'll go to Amazon and if he wants
to
he'll have exactly no but like if you do
it since it was a kitten then it will
probably accept it and then whatever but
if it doesn't seem like it's enjoying it
then don't do it poor cat Man Poor
cat cats have a mind of their own and
they want to be naked Okay their mind is
telling them feel like some cats you
know are so naughty that they deserve to
be punished and wear clothes pigy I'm
starting to hate you
you're such a bird
person
you what shaking head
[Music]
emoji I said that because of you you're
not a cat person obviously you seem to
be a bird person yeah it's a bird
obviously it goes bark bark bark yeah my
barking mhm I want a cat but I'm a
afraid that it'll I'm afraid too I'm
afraid too don't get a cat I want a cat
no no please stay away from the cats I
will take the cats you I'll take all
cats on your radar I get a cat and then
you can come over and take it and this
is just my bait to get you to come over
to take my
cat uh that's a weird strategy
honestly what would it work
only under certain circumstances I think
oh that I don't I hope you don't enforce
them okay but what if it's just to come
over to see my cat to see your cat I've
heard that kind of pickup line before
from crony what oh who wants to come
over and see my cat yeah wellknown
pickup
phrase um oh you get here there's no
cat I don't know I don't know maybe
maybe there is a cat yeah in my case
there would be a cat for sure yes yes
who knows um well if you pay for the
flight ticket I would come over oo what
happened to your ability to just fly
anywhere a phoenix yeah I thought you're
going to drive by I can't I can't no no
that's not why not because hook Papa put
a belt on me and says in like
handwritten on a piece of paper to not
unleash the true powers of me she's
offering to see should show you her cat
and you don't even have the
ability yourself you nowadays we all
have phones if you really want to show
me your cat you can take a picture of
the so-called cat what if what if she
doesn't have a phone anymore it just
died yeah I don't have a
phone it's a broken phone no no that's
impossible you have a phone don't
Gaslight me you
person like a flip phone user yeah yeah
it doesn't
havep taking capabilities no no flip can
also take pictures don't gas like
me man I was I was uh thinking we were
going to do quests together today but uh
I I I need to stop what you girls I'm
just hitting moners I'm doing a bunch of
quest okay you're hitting monsters up
now though
yeah yeah we can 25 now do the dungeon
that's here if you get there what's the
dungeon called I think it's the level 27
main quest called Morty
Kora have we done that already I don't
think we have oh okay yeah when you get
there I guess we'll re reunite yeah yeah
I'm just hitting monsters and leveling
up my side classes
okay what the morti Kora Quest I what
what level would that be
27 oh okay so I'm I'm probably doing the
quests before that right
now go why is there so many quests just
a lot of main quest I didn't
do it's it's I wish in the in the when
you press l in the quest log thingy
where you see all of your quests that
you can have I wish it would
say I guess it does
when you click on it I guess it does say
man that title is I just collect all the
quest I will have to keep
grinding you're so thorough with it I
like it with the the quest stuff oh
that's why I don't have to go back cuz
we going be like oh kill birds kill
birds
again well you know you don't have to do
uh them even if they tell you to go back
you don't have to do any it's more like
the the XP stuff I need it yeah I guess
it's more efficient than just killing
mobs
yeah so
[Music]
this what am I doing here
again what a pig came out of the N
bamboozle what am I doing
[Music]
here I think I have too many quests now
that they don't show up in like my easy
Quest
tracker too many
quests yeah oh Ninja Turtles oh my God I
watched your 3D
model yeah and I saw your
your your wing boobs my wi my wings your
wings your
wings now it's so funny the the boob
collage and
C when I saw crony having it with her
like official model I was like man I
wish my boobs would do that and now my
boobs do it it's
fine
nice you can't relate gigy can you I
can't but I can watch
you I like a fake pair so you can
pretend at least oh yeah I'll get a fake
pair so I can
pretend I don't know I find joy in
watching kiaha move her arm and smack
her chest around thank you I was really
locked
in to that
stream oh my
God you're kind of a thirsty firsty girl
it's it's fun to watch is it not fun was
no one else having fun watching she
studying she's trying to relate that's
why yeah that's what I'm here for to
provide fun for and purposes of course
yes
yes yeah now maybe maybe you can do the
same thing with other body parts I don't
know oh what body parts do CI have that
can like whole
game yeah and her pigtails maybe but
it's not the same huh
yeah I guess someone's just going to let
me have to let me use
theirs don't you have like a mascot that
might have a a little bit of fluff to
something yeah can can it
grow a pair of chest something I don't
know either balls or or chesticles oh I
can I'll
ask okay and resp who are you asking the
gods above okay and then they'll let me
know it can happen or
not is it is it the girl or is it a boy
I I hope it's a boy it'll be funnier
that way poo is a boy po yeah there you
go yeah I had a feeling and then it can
bounce its popo oh
lag you know popo in in German is just
ass oh my God it's going to be growing
it from its
backside yeah yeah what is
thisa Bay mysterious treasure
box where did I get that oh I killed
think someone probably killed something
the the area boss I guess I'm
assuming nice oh my God everyone kill
kill fast these tribal Wizards destroy
them un
Force Must Destroy must kill
did you prefer the black or the white
outfit
gigy I think I really like the white
one I like the white one too actually
right it's it's like pearles pearles now
it wasn't in the music video but now it
is really pretty it is really
pretty I like the way I don't know the
way it contrast with your body it's just
a really good
look I I agree honestly thank you wow
you girls would look good in it
too oh my God we can be backup dancers I
want to be the one that holds your
ass of course you want to be one but you
know that backup
dancer H she's she's not getting paid
she's paying
me it's actually not true okay I suppose
I can't
[Laughter]
to if I must I I'll do it well you know
you're not just there for holding the
ass you have to learn to hold coroo
properly okay okay holding the
ass no no it's behind it I'm going to
train you so hard just for that
moment
easy to hold the asses is that heavy no
there's more to it there's more to hold
underestimated yeah there's probably a
technique or something I think that's
what it is you're not taking it
seriously girl I'll TR I'll train for a
year no it is serious we're just
thinking the logistics of it yeah yeah
what what are you training on which ass
are you holding when you
train um I'll make one like a fake
one I see I'm going to need you to send
me a mold of your
assho have something realistic to use
all right I I'll try to figure out how
to take them a mold of my ass
present well there are you know op by
mouse pads I never made one but I was
thinking of uh like if anything maybe
like an ass mouse pad that would go
crazy yeah that would
help I'm not going to do it though glue
it to my wall aw and then you just stand
at your wall five hours per day
practicing how to hold it to the Coro of
course oh yeah
yeah no you should practice it with
something that can move around like
something more Dynamic like a like a
person where am I going to get it
[Laughter]
at I don't know Higher One I he someone
to stand there so I can
grab I'm sure you can find someone even
like or something I was going to
say that sounds d
[Music]
easy it's worth it for a training
it's just get really flexible and hold
your own ass okay I will start doing
yoga why won't you hold Shan's ass she
needs to come over do you think she'll
fly here
no I guess I have to find someone El
Phoenix
though I also have to run my my chap my
church oh yeah
unattend oh I have the the quest now for
the dungeon I'll stop doing things I'll
clean out my inventory what's the quest
called um it's called Mor deor 2 main
but it seems like you have to do all of
the other main quests first for it I see
I am still not level 27 I am the young
one don't worry I'm still grinding close
you're 26 let's go
yeah you must continue to kill things so
I can level up I'll kill things for
you thank
[Music]
you oh my God there's so many
quests beautiful I have the daughter in
the Pirate Man Quest
oh feel like I did that one too I need
to kill aul
enforcer kill him kill
him maybe not my B is already 24 I can
switch back
to oh yeah right cuz
27 yeah I can get up to the next level
I'm on the next level what is this
anyway what is this doing oh I have
people hidden oh I leveled
up what what is this
button
slam Max Max Max Max oh crap this is a
big Elite
group the class skill CP are they when I
switch wait let me test okay no answered
my own
question Thief simulator
2024 Thief
simulator yay wait another one no I mean
I think a new one came out this year and
I I played it I think it was this year I
only played the first one how's the
second one it's good it's better yeah I
had a better experience I think
that's good we look into it thank yeah
go
feing where is he oh down there Thief
Joel yeah I like being a
thief I like opening locks with my lock
pick you will go to jail for that yeah
but so in the game in in fee Simulator 2
you actually do end up in a jail and
then you have to break out of it and
that was always like the most riveting
part of the game you just keep going
back to jail then to experience that of
yours well it's huge and you can find so
many things there it's really good oh
got to legitimately check it out so I
can see what the criminals are
doing I wish there was a multiplayer
version of
it oh I can do a class now that's that's
not one of the basic classes I can be a
knight oo
ooh I mean that's kind of Co you have
like a an outfit that's kind of like a
night or a
paladin but probably That's Heavy Armor
right but what what what weapon does the
Knight use I probably don't have
one what do I does it use
sword who the heck
is Knight level six how did I I just
switched
class I will grind the CL what talking
to
me no okay you're grinding you're
leveling me oh my God level eight you
I'm grinding I'm grinding thank you
grind me more grind no
problem I have so many quests I can now
turn
in let's go muchos
Experian
atos okay see
see
Amigos who is ltia I don't see ltia
here I'm I'm working I'm working on it I
just
swapped alaca coin Stones
[Music]
Rising Marshall Grudge w
get out of my
inventory does a knight use a
shieldy right
now mer
yeah oh they didn't spawn oh I
see I am I am somewhat of a knight
myself level 11 oh there te is someone
you die oh you killed I see I thought it
was like an
NPC you always got to kill always think
of killing
first heill first ask questions
later exactly rtia hurry up and show
up oh contains witch do let's kill it
Bo boom
boom
um oh thank you for the
help thank you thank you Max Max Max
Max Max Max what do we have Elegant
increases your evasion and your pee
healing party healing focus should
double hit your
he
yeah each time you pee it heals your
soul
uh-huh P attack p
attack I think like single uh single
attack compared to a a player maybe
player not party a
personal
personal okay there's a lot of Buffs
what's where where are the attacks
provoke in increases P attack yeah
probably yeah I can I can get the wait
this is a tank class isn't it I can
finally tank but you can heal yourself a
little oh yeah this is very much a tank
class yep yep okay maybe if G wanted to
be a
tank do you want to be a tank now nah no
okay I don't want to be a tank either
but tank a Tanki K I got to be a tank
[Music]
I'll I'll try to tank a little
bit a little bit today at least only
today but my future is double wielding
blade dancer you know yeah yeah yeah
yeah I want to be
cool you are
cool so wait what does this increases
malice caused by
attacks malice caus so just more aggro
stuff I guess
oh you always oh he I got the the moror
thing now although I I do need a little
bit more XP before like 27 okay can you
not enter it
early I I don't know honestly I think
you can as long as you have the quest
did you just sink we're seeing
yeah that CLI I really love that
moment such a beautiful moment perfect
[Music]
sink orange brain
w we should sink up more of G okay it
has to start with sinking another thing
up first what is
it oh
there first we have to sink that and
then we'll be completely in
sync oh I always skip my period though
that's going to be a problem I'll it I
thought you only skip it when you're
like really stressed stressed just so
are you really stressed right now yeah
you okay I mean I'm always stressed but
uh no no skip it in different ways don't
you know the
ways do you know the way yes yeah I
understand I just uh what is this I just
uh I just don't take a break you know
with no breaks yeah no break just keep
on taking I don't know I talked about
this before in girls talk I'm
embarrassed talking about it like not a
girl gu okay well shion's viewers are
certainly used to this kind of talk I I
don't know about yes they
are the GS guess H this is just girls
talk yeah it's like you guys probably
compare sizes We compare periods I
guess no honestly I I never do that
but I don't know that's common it when I
meet a girl who doesn't know the way
then I like to share the way because
it's surprising how many girls are not
aware of the way I think I might know of
the way because someone has mentioned
this way yeah you just take you just
take it without taking a Breaking All
the the I I I I I swear I I I I
generally I I the real reason I've been
taking it it's for my acne okay
oh I I heard about that method I've
never taken that thing before
though well I take it from my acne for
many years now and and and so my doctor
said I I don't have to take the break if
I don't want to like every once in a
while maybe it's good cuz normally you
take it for a few weeks and you take a
week break and then you take it again
and then you take a week break and then
the week break you get you
know but um I I I don't want to you know
I don't want to I don't want to always
be bleeding so I say okay no I I'll
continue the hacks yeah these
are code girl hacks yeah and for the
girls out there you can also take if you
really don't want to get it because you
have a trip coming up you can't take it
too to try and Dodge it oh what take
what oh you know the your ways oh yeah
yeah yeah to try and get it to skip so
you don't get it while you go on
vacation
exactly yeah yeah nothing ruins the day
more than getting it yeah and also like
when I have like a lot of dance lessons
and stuff it's really
uncomfortable so I'd rather
just yeah always skip it you know yeah
anyway anyway
anyway anyway I can go to the dungeon
which which one are we doing single
player the one at the
end okay more toora iume
yes all right my blue ball should oh
you're inside already yeah I'm inside on
my way
oh solo right yeah SOLO yeah I I did
solo hello oh oh shield
in hello
so oh no GG's the
I'm all
right here's a
b all right who am I I guess I'm
focusing on Kia unless I tank everything
watch this
[Music]
[Laughter]
tank uh is there like a key on the
keyboard to Auto Select the next closest
T is the best that you'll have I think
oh sick GG stop AGG gring don't worry I
can heal myself now I can heal myself
now you taking my bro
got got to pick up the
pace oh okaying
me yeah why is it a race got to pick up
the pain I can't heal you from Far H
don't worry don't worry I'm a bar I can
heal myself die just let us you can't
heal yourself enough if you
keep don't worry oh my God do not worry
okay okay be be happy I'm happy look I
have the whole thing the whole party
here I'm just going to let
her I'm just going to focus
on not my problem yeah let her
stuer wait I can't move anymore what not
with I can't move with dou ASD anymore
oh why must have pressed something
weird oh maybe I'll tab or something
yeah oh that's a big circle I'm not
exiting this die
why do they all didn't they have more
voice LS for the enemies they all make
the same sounds they're all mer I I
don't remember them having voices
honestly it's a thing I like hearing the
guitar sound that's nice yeah here's a
song the song of GG's people
yes are these I suppose I'm too weak to
be a tank you're not
weak I'm not doing my job properly I'm
doubting my my abilities now yeah you're
doing great says the person pulling
everything yeah W I never I never wanted
to be a tank suffering for it so now had
to heal
you
no I've achieved nightm nightm night
Knighthood Knighthood good
yeah level 20 KN let's
go that probably opens up more paths for
me n yes uhoh
help aggro on
me I don't know what all of these things
do we did it good job good job oh that's
actually better but I don't want it I
don't really want it we did it we did it
another now dungeon off of our
books
H imagine what if what if next Ian REO
takes part in Eden Eternal that'll be
fun although
I
no until you done Renee yeah yeaha she
started with members only and I I I
thought you know that would be cool we
would have a four people team but the
only problem is that we would have like
so many different time zones then like
the time that we're playing now for her
is middle of the night so I don't know
if that's going to work
out do that that even though it would be
nice I mean if she wants to join she's
always
welcome of course I really can't move
I'm locked
in you're locked in
locked
negative pressing
buttons try Rel logging okay I'll try
switching channel and coming
back and there's so many stats I can't
keep track of what's good and what's not
right now you got to off of her I did I
did I did tell her like oh wait oh my
God you're playing e Eternal too oh my
god let's go please join
us yeah I don't know what to do with my
class skills should I just max them all
or is there an actual yeah I've been
maxing them all okay depends on what you
want I still I still can't move only Mo
click so
[Music]
strange I guess we're done in Bela Bay
are
we maybe there's a there's a multiplayer
version of the dungeon if you want to do
that is that the
daily we want a daily for that oh no
it's a main yeah it's a
main okay let's do that architect
angle
Garrison so many
Quest oh now the Pirates
ah same same okay we're on the same
thing then are we doing Crusade against
the Pirates or multiplayer okay talk to
Rafi to report your qu maybe after that
we do the dungeon again
weird just kill the pirate
daily and then Crusade against the
Pirates too who is hitting
me crab
you must now become my
food it's
a
you never
mind oh oh I remember this place I used
to hang out here and just like hide in
here in the Fortress I would try to find
places where they would not bother me
and I'll be like he they do not care I
am here I hidden
and now I can kill
faster I have so many self Buffs but
barely any like
attacks oh yeah that's how B
works but I'm on night talking about
your oh I think I'll switch back to
may I got like a lot unlocked but it's
just Buffs Buffs Buffs
Buffs I'll switch
travel
to even that doesn't work anymore I
right click oh it's left
click I thought it was
R oh my God aever LaVine is in this Camp
a
autograph
yeah ail she's a pirate
now s that makes sense it makes sense
yeah with the punk rock VI
fits can you girls believe it's already
like November and Christmas is soon and
the year is over soon it's crazy I I
like the end of the year stuff I hate
the beginning of the year though it's
boring
boring yeah like there's something
interesting in January you get maybe
like what Valentine's and February
I don't know I like the chill months
yeah in the beginning of the year feels
like okay we have a whole year ahead of
us so much time to do things
taxes taes immediately oh God all the
time doesn't matter
when but yeah end of the year stresses
me out cuz it's like where the hell did
the time
go yeah where I had more
time so don't like it
don't like
it Max Max Max Max Max
Max oh I don't want that anyway
okay huh the vile shark
killer vile shark
Mage where's the
killer oh oh my my Val Shar Mages are
being taken care of
it
seems where are they I
here I'm back I'm thiefing
again welcome the wrong weapon though
but
whatever I'm talking to ail oh my
God hey new song called skater girl
want to be your girlfriend no way no way
think you need a new one oh defeat
defeat oh somebody's doing everything
for me kill
kill I'm back to talk to
aine I need to kill a doctor and a
fighter
okay if I I I see them I'm killing giggy
has accepted your quest
Shing yeah I think we're sharing
okay did you get
those uh I assume I am getting
something I need I need some thevs to be
killed okay on my way yeah I'm killing
them so good at killing I'm also
here punch pump
kapow oh already finished collect Fort
blueprint from Gilbert
Gilbert Gil Gil
bird feel like my game is so bugged out
I can't do things properly anymore
what's the the buggy part uh wsd doesn't
work anymore and uh clicking on the
quest to move towards the thing doesn't
work anymore sounds pretty
booked wait now it works okay
move in the mini map no longer bu now uh
no W wsd still doesn't
work my keyboard language no um it
should be fine but let me change to
German no it still doesn't work I need
to kill more doctors you save lives I
take it
away St do
straw happened to you I just move from
the
map uh
what what do you mean move
in move from what do you
mean move in the map I'm you mean click
on the map doesn't do anything on me
that didn't do anything for me
ever it's okay I can accept that's what
you get for studying
medicine gigy Moody has sabotaged the
evil schemes of v shark saving Beluga
Harbor from these scurvy
villains what are you up to all on your
own walking all the way back
I got to kill more thieves man how much
blood this uh do I have to
spill better now it seems I have reached
a a a place where the quest items
rewards are getting better than the
Legacy things so now I have to think and
actually exchange my armor
soon I think that I redeemed the Legacy
and then did not use it
yeah I told you it would be too late if
you wait too long oh I got to go back to
a
LaVine oh there so much walking oh
there's another dungeon so much flying
oh oh it's probably the pirate one that
one's kind of long I think o i remember
that oh yeah yeah who is
Gilbert Gil what you got oh shoot you're
someone I got to
kill I don't even remember remember
killing him he died too fast I
guess the set bonus do I have a set Bon
SP number
two oh yeah it's giving me set bones
then I'll keep it for a while
longer hi good times with set bonus man
I hate the manual Quest it's like I have
to combine something I have to leave
this map just to do it you can't just
teleport me
there uh you have one those now yeah I
got to do like um combine this with a
formula to make a stone and then you
summon something and you kill them and
then you got to report to someone no
that's a video
game okay I'm at the dungeon I shall
await you I will begin killing mobs
you're here you know you can teleport
everyone as the the Mage oh yeah yeah oh
yeah forgot that was let me in really
quick would you like me to teleport you
over here they make they make um the
portals don't
they do they make portals oh yeah yeah
they do well they just teleport everyone
in
general I
remember you remember you remember I
remember the
20 what do you remember
the
TW crazy I was crazy
once I don't remember do you remember do
you you should remember I don't remember
you need I'm sure you remember it hurts
we all remember I'm not dueling
you oh you have mercy yes I don't want
to kill your kfp so I rejected their
dual requests cuz I I can't kill them
this one's
good I would like to be teleported to
the dungeon when possibly
yes once once I
okay let me walk over
there I will bring you right to the
entrance thank you it's so finicky when
I try to get there and like the button
doesn't go like why can't I just auto
travel here no no okay okay I'm
summoning you I'm summoning you all
right make sure to link your soul oh god
oh [\h__\h] girl L with the wrong
one why would you do
that okay I did not want this I haven't
asked for
this okay okay let me let me walk back
okay I'll I'll summon you
fail what don't ever try to be don't
ever try to be a mage ever
again wait oh wait wait I I I can atone
for this skill
you why is I'm not walking back okay I
had that last second
[Laughter]
warning it just happened so
quickly did it
did why did you do it it's a little
funny cuz Maes are supposed to be smart
with their
intelligence I just got so excited that
I was going to use it gigy uses one
brain cell for whatever class she
chooses to use it's for only killing and
nothing
else well a nice little trip into a
different climate but I'm already back
what a nice trip why does this person
have a quest how do I get down there
uh you have to get for the whole Camp
kind of but uh if you just click on the
quest talk to II or so then it will oh
make you move there anyway I have I have
so many quests here I have to go to my
L stop stop stop walking stop walking
don't worry guys just just stay at
beluca Bay Town I'll warp you I'll warp
you there I'll walk I'll I'll I'm in the
dungeon don't warp me it's it's the vile
shark main dungeon right maybe you can't
even yeah yeah that's the dungeon maybe
you can't War me anyway cuz I'm in here
it's leading me to somewhere else I
don't know where I'm going why is it
leading you I just watched you pass me I
know epic music it's oh it's taking me
to Garrison Captain straw maybe I got to
talk to him
first Captain what do you want me to do
how are you at
[Music]
I need I need to stop taking quests okay
just take me there so I can kill
things okay okay okay don't worry I'm
going to link my soul and then I will
spawn
you okay and then I will probably have
to do this at some point again
okay okay okay it's okay you Soul you
mess it up are you ready are you ready
okay okay it's okay we did it we did it
did it we did did it we did it are
you're in front of the dungeon yeah get
in here now okay is this solo yeah
single
player but solo means something else in
our books
well time to let Chi tank everything
together even tanking as a mage you
crazy crazy land you can do everything
you set your mind to what is this skill
Mages are
squishy yeah they
[Music]
are uh uh whatever don't
want okay p p pum
here we
go oh I remember so
well oh there like aren like the free
rooms are so over there there's like um
different holes in the
wall it's a Pirate
Cave oh yeah yeah yeah yeah I remember
that such nice memories coming back to
me I I
missed a lot I think this is this is the
first five player dungeon actually
really yeah you these good
times I miss what was your favorite
dungeon I don't know I'm I like the the
malice one and then the for the world I
like the the world of the witchery stuff
I don't remember those names I only
remember the visuals name there's malice
Palace and then there's a witch level I
I know that um I think like when you're
in aan uh and then you go up to that
church building thingy there's a like a
raid or so dungeon that you can teleport
yourself too and I did that so many
times I think because the equipment that
you could get there was really good
uhhuh uh and we wiped so many times
there too oh but that was that was a
good one it was like a palace looking
place with like big
white uh walls and water and I need to
get there need to get there so we can
remind oh I think I know maybe what
you're talking about
yeah good
times what kind of witch wit roll is
happening yeah yeah yeah yeah it was
like like somewhere in the high
level and it was it was a get there mhm
we'll get there I mean we're only level
28 now but we'll get there yeah we're
going to get there soon we level so
quickly
yeah so fast like old old stuff what did
we start off with today wasn't it 25
level so fast that 15 for me but we
leveled some classes up yeah all of us
yeah that's something to be proud
of so one day when we're more high level
and and we need to do like Dungeons that
are like that aren't doable with just
those free then we we'll get some
viewers to help us some high level
people
yeah they're going to drag us through
the
dungeons make it easy for
us and we Leed I still can't believe
we're going in without like a tank
technically it's okay it's solo it's
solo if you do this in multiplayer I
think it might be screwed yeah might be
rough
very
screwed oh many ring no just one ring I
don't care I don't know ail I don't care
I need to clean my inventory at some
point oh wait leave dungeon why would we
leave D I haven't done I haven't done
the things that I need to do I don't
even know what I'm doing in here well
where is ax Moss where is Kar okay I
guess we got to look for them no yeah
they're in the rooms on the bottom of
the map I'm killing everything
oh I think it's if you like screw it up
maybe I don't know no or if you can't do
the rest of the
dungeon I got another
Quest no there's way more mobs here
still oh God do I have a Healer
here here hold
up uh wait am I following
GG I'm at the Bott the map of the
dungeon are you not in the dungeon
anymore I'm Stu
the dungeon oh God why did you guys
separate I don't know man I went toward
the go okay find
her you guys separated a
little here I just went back to us if
you can uh I'm fine uh I'm fine things
have calmed
down little
bit all right we should not get uh split
up I'm to see ogre
I was almost at uh who do I choose to
save
situation I I would have ran away away
maybe okay you're you're there um we're
like around here where uh you're near
this
section did you go past this person no
there you are
can't attack
M
noise I can't wait for group healing I
think I have to be level 30 for it oh
hell
yeah group healing we love it we love to
see
it okay here should be one of the
actual where here
did you girls already defeat axe moss
and no we haven't been here maybe she
has to spawn if you do a certain
thing yeah where are they he should be
here right
here kills
more Quest says just kill more yeah we
just have to kill the whole dungeon oh
yeah we have we need to kill all the
humanid monsters to uh spawn them it
okay in a big circle what haven't we
killed we've been here each other I must
kill all the humans in this dungeon oh
no I to the left should have created
frog
character all
right I'm going to where G isn't there
something at the pier that we didn't
kill cuz just like a skull icon there I
will go
what did we we can't go there
anyway have to click there this one guy
uh really cuz of that one
guy it's not just one guy there's a few
more okay well let's split up almost got
one
guide I want to be tanked now I can be
like tanking I'm
tanking okay
oh GG there's things down
here I feel like a babysitter there's
things down here oh there's there there
is there a boss there oh yeah don't
don't hit anything yet I'm healing GG
over here okay I'm can just wait
there
Kar Kar you shall
die rally the troops oh he's dying so
fast oh no oh
now we can you should you should need on
that
what did you greed on it you should need
who's but I think you got it did you get
it I got it the
the that's
forist
oh Maes are for cleric staffs are for
the Wizards and Illusionist is a book
has the other boss spawned
now
no should be in that room
again where are they well I'm going to
sort out my stuff so don't die while I'm
busy it's okay okay it just it's
probably just like a few mobs
somewhere totally
doable not here
yeah are you looking
too are you looking mob I'm looking I
don't want to do this right here where
is
it that's a main quest a daily Quest
there's so much freaking Quest I should
not have taken so
much there's 200 free gacha draws what
where how don't I track this
one really 200 free Goa
draws is there any on the
ship
no that was an
event what do you mean in the in the few
days that we weren't playing there was a
200 free gacha draws even event oh wow
is that why you guys get got so I found
a group I found a group of enemies
yay all right I guess we head there
don't start the boss without me though
no you don't even have to go here
they're almost dead okay okay but we
still have to find a
boss oh right I I know where it is oh
yeah he spawned he's finally spawned
okay on my
[Music]
way at least he should be yeah he's
here think I know now why this let's go
why thises the dungeon stay in my memory
so much because in order to finish it
you really have to clear the whole
dungeon and be very
thorough it's also kind of a big dungeon
yeah yay we did
it yay
[Music]
yooo you can teleport us out Chi now
that we're done I mean the ex is right
there too I thought we to talk to the
guy in
here okay running towards
him oh yeah undercover v
shark who do we kill now I don't have a
quest for you the kill Charles oh is
that the guy we
killed is it I don't know who's
Charles oh it is it's the guy we killed
up here
so we're done then well you guys are
done we have to kill Charles again cuz
we didn't get the credit for it is she
there yeah to reset it and kill Charles
no all right teleport us out of here
that's so dumb that's so dumb they
should like no oh I can't use it inside
a dungeon you must leave oh you can't
what's the point of
that all right time to head back out do
we re-enter yeah how do we reset
d uh there's an option when you click on
yourself at the top left I think oh
reset okay oh
I damn Shi
in you know you're way around this
game uh only only somewhat oh but it's
hold up who's this guy I need to talk to
somebody okay I I I I couldn't reset it
because of uh still had players in it
I'm I already went in but I'm coming
back out
okay I need to talk to a
LaVine a d has been
reset hello AEL wait why do you why why
do you what you have to talk to AEL now
oh that's because I I didn't do things
in order now now we can do it again oh
let's go okay we only have to kill
Charles we could just do that and then
teleport out with the soul Guardian kill
everything else for
me okay we'll do it for you okay now I
just talk to seal or whatever oh yeah
he's inside the dungeon oh you haven't
done the
dungeon oh shoot I was about to go in
oopsies all right tank
away so we should kill Charles the last
then if you have to do the thing oh yeah
you to kill everyone to summon him
anyway no we killed and Charles um he
was just
there and then we had to kill him for
the
quest I don't even remember him what did
he look
like I thought he looked like a
bear oh yeah he's
here's ah kill the jellyfish to summon
Charles oh
let's not kill the jellyfish then I'll
kill them
last oh I'm
lagging I like how I can just chill a
little honestly when I'm like play I
just stare at your health same same I
just always have T Bar select it and
just yeah it's so chill follow tank heal
tank that's all you got to
do buff tank buff group oh that looks
like a fancy sword that does look like a
good one good that I got
it is it
good
kill oh it's good better than the Legacy
sword oh too low level
it's so weird when the music just stops
I know where's the
music yeah where's my looping bgm they
need to Loop it
better oh another fancy sword let me to
GRE on that oh but this
one don't
care think it's S as good as the other
one that I got but now I got both dual
wielding one day
actually I can do a wheel
soono level 30 wasn't it I'll I'll turn
back into Bard for a little bit okay
[Music]
okay but I won't pretend that I'm a
Healer uh don't you have to be out of
combat to I already switched let switch
I I got the the tiny time window of not
being in
combat yeah
gg kid
die once again you must
die your screams feel his blood lust 35
okay well got to catch up ooh not cool
chart I will need on this then actually
just what what is that anyway oh I supp
I
think suppose I will we done have we
done the two guys before I ask oh
okay where is whoever that is if that's
the person that we were trying to summon
last time so hopefully he summoned
I I thought we he would show on the map
but he doesn't show on the map so he is
not summoned
mhm okay I'll run around and see okay
all people my wsd works again hey nice I
wonder what the issue was though don't
know
either maybe it was a trial I had to go
through the trial of losing your wda
yeah maybe it was the class Chang that
somehow changed
something learn skill Burning
metal oh
yeahum hopefully Charles isn't here he's
not in here right he's not thank God no
but to got to kill the small ones anyway
first uhoh something's after me I will
save you hands off of our
nun he want to confess
something well he could confess the [\h__\h]
off oh crap I am
stunned wow our healer is so strong is
he Swan oh I see him
oh yes indeed you do he is he is here
with us
oh I see I
see all the way around we go why do I
keep getting stuck on
this W needs to be the one to do what
awkward silence with the bgm my bgm is
back oh it's I need to create a town oh
we can create a guild town now cuz we're
level three okay well yeah you really
shouldn't have given me leader because
I'm not online as often as you guys
and I can't be bothered with that
[\h__\h] but I shall be vice
leader giggy do you want to be
[Laughter]
leader honored
but don't worry guys I will I will
transfer at the end of the
stream maybe always when I stream you
can transfer it back to me and when I'm
offline I'll transfer it back to you
guys oh but that requires some being
like active oh they're active every
single time too they are they are okay
they're
committed is it child's
time I got to talk to first okay yeah
don't
die easy easy I'm a bar
too there are a few addict chickens I've
noticed I'm happy for you I'm happy I
could give this gift to you yeah the
gift of mm RPG addiction PE
PE okay sheing is back nice
y your first am RPG oh my God
what I'm taking your
mmpg uhoh uh that's flirting kill it
kill
this what oh I'm killing what's the word
thank you thank you like I should do
more damage I don't know if I'm using
the right weapon
virginity uh your mmrpg virginity you're
taking that from them yeah she already
did God
unfortunately I can't take yours spey
unfortunately can't take shieldings
either what was your first uh MMO RPG
for GG maple
story I see your like um mine was
probably World of Warcraft if we don't
count like what was it Toontown or
something like that Toontown doesn't
count it doesn't count Toontown should
count though count I don't know what the
everyone's first I don't even know if I
was playing the game
accurately I don't think I was either I
was too young to understand what was
going on yeah there was no one around
pie yeah and fishing and
trolley I don't think I was even doing I
don't remember the trolley one I think I
ran out of pie so I summoned everyone on
my friends list that I didn't know to
kill one thing from
me yeah yeah but World of Warcraft was
probably the the first proper one which
is a great one to start off
with and I played it with my whole
family a my mommy my brother with you
that's nice for the whole family yeah
instead of playing uh board games like
Monopoly you
played yeah it it's fun funny because
like whenever I would visit with my
brother we whenever we would visit my
father back in the day cuz it was like
separated families you know there we
would play actual board games then I
come back to my home and there we play
mmor
pgs the
contrast what is this who's Dominic he's
not in here is he when I click on it uh
I think might be outside of the dungeon
leaving this dungeon
yeah
leaving am I walking to
okay okay I'm also
out I can be on my Mount again I will go
out then yeah she it's over it's over
she
I will have to do this again though
oh
yeah no it's okay it's okay no it's okay
it's okay I had to reach level 29
anyway we can kill
Charles no it's okay I'll kill him I'll
kill him just try okay maybe you can
solo Charles yeah I'll be able to do it
it's okay it'll be a trial of your
streng [\h__\h] in my
stuff why can't I sell [\h__\h] why
not yeah that
dungeon
H quite long dungeon it's not really
well
organized
[Music]
yeah delivering this
Le O an ax who uses an Al probably
tank
Oh I thought you said I'll probably tank
no no no the axes are us yeah I think
[Music]
so can probably just throw it
away I'm
sailing
sailing I'm selling all my crap oh and I
have so much D too and I don't know what
to do with them I think I'm pathing to
the level 29
quest uh explore Wetlands yeah same
let's
go are we going to different area I
think so I'm excited which one is it
well have we been there
already I want to see a new
one what's the next area anyway Wetlands
I remember this area oh TR oh I think
that's the place I like with the dungeon
really go kill things here yeah
oh this place oh my
[Music]
God core memories are being unlocked
again
a I remember just like like I I never
really had a a group early in this game
like running through all the areas
together someone I soloed like
everything and it was kind of chill no
it was chill different experience mhm I
think back then you had to party up yeah
until
solo and then for the dungeons because I
didn't I didn't have anybody generally I
would just like type in the party chat
looking for group for this
dungeon like no one really wanted you
unless you were a Healer or a tank just
so common yeah true there was an
oversaturation of certain classes for
sure
yeah tanks are really popular
not so many people play tank want be
tank yeah
why I think it's because it's like it's
the attention on
you anxiety is real skills maybe it
wasn't as cool as DD for the Healer like
everyone has to rely on you but if you
you can't heal enough or if you're like
too op it's like well
sorry are you guys don't attack my
enemies first
okay rid of all these items unless your
name is gy yeah
yeah back
off I already did
[Music]
that
okay happy there's a happy
alpaka uh
NPC do
a mystery capsule sh oh and it has like
dying headgear
dying was dying no no oh my God my
inventory is so full y yeah did you get
expanded inventory yeah yeah quite a
bit quite a bit
ooh oh wow
M
yeah I need more food chest more give me
your
food
uh stop asking
[Music]
me collect full water
bottles um I have so many quests I I'm
going to leave like the old ones like
this one yeah scw those on Legacy items
can't be sold got to delete
it what a
waste I hate the
ones they walking there
oh people are saying you can archive
them oh yeah where does it
go in an
archive it's like um the archive would
no where is the archive sh is it your
trash can press B and then there's a
yellow icon that's called archive at
like below with all the other other
icons
ah oh
ah yeah I have some memory of this
interesting
H okay I need CU
useless what is this cash up items
n those are not is this just like a
set lost
city but but oh no it is like something
like cash up items I need more alpaka
coins I only have 10 I can get the
copper mystery capsule I'll get
one I'm opening alpaka
goaa for that I just got dye for color
for for
coloring a Packa got you die you'll be
proud as a peacock in this dashing shade
of
lapis wa this is for
you but the the um clothing die for cash
up items and for non-cash up items is
different right this is for non-cash up
items as far as I
know I have no
idea I think so oh I think yeah one of
them's a gacha one of them can choose
the color I think
mhm what am I killing
here Lava Rock Devil
[Laughter]
die what's with the cafe meat up here we
just talk to streamer pay it no mind oh
they're at this region there like they
know us they're at this region yes we uh
yes
yes we are at a region watch our
streams all
[Laughter]
live on
YouTube yes uh M Small Indie streamer
please
forgive please like And subscribe hit
that notification button the Bell button
did you see one of the new members her
OSI mark she has free oi marks if I
understand correctly like comment and
subscribe or retweet it's so
silly but it's so many it's funny but
there's like so many like there's too
many taken now we have to take like two
oi marks instead of one
nowadays must be rough I guess we got
kind of Lucky although mine mine bugs
out depending on the device mine splits
into an eyeball and a like a Yap
icon it's
beautiful I guess
[Music]
so I don't I don't want this maybe I
should archive it
then okay I'll do it later you I guess I
can archive it for you you archive it
for
us
yeah okay I'm going to can I look at
your other archives too what else is in
there no you you get your own personal
archive I have a separate AR for
everyone oh so I I can't take a little
peek at another person alloud well only
if they allow you I have to get their
consent of
course okay what is this a free country
I'll ask I suppose can I look at kiaha
can I look at your
archive uh you can watch my streams on
YouTube okay but we don't call him
archives we call him waa on demand W on
demand mhm W with
wand man kayin thinks that the cleric is
so slow right it's just die please just
die already just
die it's a rough
life okay yeah really those cars cars
are
so cool The Car mounts nah no not
they're cool but they don't match they
don't they don't fit into this world
makes no sense to me is your immersion
being ruined
yeah
100% deliver Adventure progress report
okay I'm on
it I need to play this for members only
as well at some point because this is
such a great Community game yeah it's
really fun I'm I'm so glad they allow
members to play it yeah really
nice
oops we can grind in members only after
we're done watching all bakatari series
seasons soon soon we can do something
else kfb soon after so many months you
will be released from your suffering I
feel that I'm like I can't do anything
until we watch all of Teen Wolf
it for real what what is that how many
seasons does that have um I only watch
Four
Seasons um and they're 12 episodes each
so it's not too bad how long is one
episode like 40 minutes oh okay that's
also quite
[Laughter]
the how many seasons are we watching
with monre series like nine I don't know
how many is it dedicated very dedicated
and then there's movies
is and now there's a new season that's
where we're going towards man I would
struggle with my attention span for
these
things they have to watch it we're
watching anything that's like a really
long thing yeah well we are we're taking
uh breaks you know between each season
and so on like one week break but yeah
one of the it has like so much dialogue
you do actually really need to concent
tra to follow the story yeah so
attention span is necessary cannot have
zoer attention span it will be rough
rough rough rough rough
rough they Yap so much yeah have you
seen have you guys seen monong like any
season seen clips of it like I'm aware
it is a Yap anime I've seen like the
first
season Joi did you just [\h__\h] do that
that was my monster that was my mob you
killed it now I have to wait for the
spawn you deserve
jail absolutely us your room now now
children years not in the presence of
sister you deserve to confess your sins
to the
sister never had a year sentence maybe
one year we had one one year before but
yeah you get five years hell no I had
taken you know you are you have no
choice ah there he is okay the spawn was
relatively fast I'll give you um one
year
instead one year sentence I guess she
will not show up to to see your your
cat never was planning on please you
weren't planning on coming to see my
cat no it's a guaranteed no what I
thought you were you really were
thinking about coming to see my cat wait
you yours yours sure but um before I
come to see it you must show me proof
that you have a
cat well should just show I don't have a
camera P it stop ping me if you're not
honest to me we cannot go anywhere with
this with this cat relationship you guys
have some really complicated
relationship asan what what quest are
you
doing um I am Expedition team fun Story
4 okay what does it require you to do
killing things like these flowers
killing I think the game wants me to do
the
dungeon already wow n maybe maybe soon
but I'm close to the
dungeon
dang now I got to defeat a transformed
flower okay
flower flow I like the music here it's
pretty
calming yeah magical
mysterious
flower at level 30 you get the school
uniform oh now weing a school un um
check
yeah if you look at your quest above it
where it says like you can pick up these
quests and then level 30 gives you a
quest to get that school
uniform you see it
what above my quest you mean an L um
it's the bubble with the exclamation
point above your quest uh
tracker ah that one
self-improvement a
cute you okay you sound like a ching
[Music]
I'm I'm fine I'm fine I'm totally fine I
just love cash up items too much it's my
passion kill it kill it kill it kill it
kill
it okay man I wish it was like a sort
setting for inventory maybe is no where
is my newest
yeah suffering oh G is here
hello oh okay yeah uh I
guess I'm going to your back where where
am I going
to there about Auto
trash are we getting the the school
outfit now oh my God
I like so fast I like my performer
outfit but you know got to got to change
clothes every once in a while
and go through them let's see is it
purple then it will match with my
alpaka
cute
cute cute very cute but I'll stay with
this actually
okay I'm going to go to aen cuz I have
some weird territory War Quest okay
oh and what is that is that about the
guild one and I remember when everyone
was so elitist if they were in the the
biggest Guild or something oh yeah oh
yeah trust me I always was elitist about
it yeah and I was cool cool guil wow
oh my God sometimes so when when there's
like let's say like three uh like top
guilds and you're in one of them and
then there's this absolute huge drama
when you decide to go to the different
you switch to different famous Guild and
your whole old Guild is like what the
[\h__\h] she's [\h__\h] abandoning us and
cheating on us but I'm just going there
why because they're winning in the Guild
Wars like when when when when your guild
isn't doing so well in the G anymore you
got to do you you got to go to the one
you got to do what you got to do go to
the one that's winning man where's your
loyalty that pop
loyalty got to win got to
[Music]
win I for me I would just be like I'm
going to go Guild hop in my other
account see you
[Laughter]
guys I defeat our aselin or
something it's not by the the dungeon
actually yeah I have the dungeon and
done chilling until you guys get dungeon
okay the dungeon I feel kind of bad I'm
not paying attention to the story
something about being Children Of Eden
and eternal ah ah no no need we already
talked about this like there there's no
need to pay attention to the story in
these kind of games I don't think
anybody expects that hey I actually read
the story from Aura kingom and forgot it
I was not reading that I can't pay
attention okay oh a video essay oh I see
Wetlands mystery of the okay I'm going
to go get the dungeon Quest too for the
wetlands maybe we can do the dungeon and
then we can maybe call it a day cuz you
have another stream
G okay it doesn't we don't have if we
want to keep playing My Stream can be
pushed back no no no no I need eat
actually yeah yeah yeah I eat
we'll do the wetlands dungeon and then
we've done a good amount okay yeah yeah
yeah what's happening in here why are
you fighting in
here go Wetlands frog frogy waa must
live here frogy waa where are you girl
you know did you did you guys ever
buy your own merch
you mean in general no in Holo like I I
was forced to now buy a couple of my own
glasses because I only get one sample
right think we all only get one sample
if we want one but I wanted a couple
more glasses cuz I really like the
glasses the first time I asked them hey
can you guys like send it to me like
maybe deduct it from my payroll they
were like no cuz I thought maybe that
way I can um like go around pay paying
certain fees but no I have to buy it
like a normal customer
so it's also it's faster to buy it
yourself though because they take over a
year to give you your stuff not no no no
it's not going to be faster cuz I'm
ordering for Geek ja and that takes like
long time by way are you guys doing a
brand rote Quest or something
else I'm in I'm at a brand root Quest
Branda root
yeah were you a different
dungeon uh she's not in it yeah it's
it's called level 30 The Mystery of the
magic water source and oh is that wait
that's not the dungeon yet maybe I got a
different main quest there's probably
two dungeons here
then I probably I think the other
regions also had more than one dungeon
right right oh my God how did you get
the other
one uh I I just called one of the main
stories oh they're right
outside what's going on in the world
chat why are you so many where do you
come from I love this why are you asking
that name is like if it's brand the
root the will of the one called
Wawa Tak started streaming it last week
and we just joined the game and state
YouTube streamer that's me that's me
that's her
SK get from Ohio what what are you
talking
about don't don't give me a bad
reputation with you
SK all right well I'm I'm inside the
Branda root dungeon if that's what
you're
doing I'm trying I archived all my stuff
I'm trying to find it oh that's the pain
that's the pain now yeah now I can't
where is it in the
archive well I I just archive things I
don't do it organized can you organize
my archive
please
nope please I'm a Healer not an
organizer I I'm I'm not quite ready it
seems for the um dungeon I still need to
do uh it's okay time need to do one or
two more things maybe
lost my
staff almost
there bless you thank
you we'll take a look don't leave I oh
oh I lost my staff it's fine oh no what
happened did you try to fortify it no I
archived it and I can't find it the
archive wait you can archive weapons all
the Legacy ones I think get archived and
then they go somewhere and I can't find
the Legacy weapons you'll find better
weapons yeah
hopefully oh my God raar ubu XD M what
are you guys typing in the
[Music]
chat they're embarrassing in you she
even Eternal Community the viewers
reflect the
streamer no no I I I don't do that kind
of U
stuff that's not me that's
me really
ra ra XD ra
XD sometimes I say that as a joke I say
that I say that I can't believe
you I think I say that more than
uu uu is not for
you it can't hurt you
yeah okay do I have the dungeon Quest
now maybe now I have
[Music]
it what is
this oh
certificates
oh
level okay I'm I have the dungeon
Quest yeah
yay ready whenever I'm inside oh
okay solo okay me
too all right let's do this
giggy will lead the way once again I'm
ready oh wait you're a b now too two BS
and one healers I lost my staff so
I we're we're unconventional I don't
know where my St
is
let's I'm using a a sword and a shield
even though I'm in b class right now
whatever it works yeah whatever
works I'm
buffing
you're I'm buffing I'm buffing everyone
get buffed get buffed debuff the enemy
so hard that it explodes come on wait
what attacks do you even have don't you
have like the slowest attack
technically I have fire and
Whirlwind I see yeah and rocks rocks the
power of
rock uhoh uhoh I think you're taking on
too much everyone's following you uh
uhoh
uhoh uh uh
oh I love it when you say that it is so
calming you do not all
disturbing it's okay it's okay we K
though sing me now don't worry don't
worry don't wor we got them we got them
we got them we have the aooe just kind
of
slow I think you also attracted the bus
yeah I made eyes with him and I aggroed
him oh I
see this is fine we did it it's so easy
yeah this is
[Music]
fine use really not a good combination
of classes but this is fine once they
give me a staff I can
switch maybe I have one lying
around I like how these look like
Christmas trees to
me Christmas trees random Bush they're
Soul trees
yeah but they're shaped like a Christmas
tree should I get a Christmas tree to
here yes I want to see it
decorated them
ah Christmas
tree maybe I'll put a real one into my
garden
ooh yeah but I won't like plant it just
put it there outside it will like stay
fresh longer when it's outside anyway
right this cuz it's like cooler are we
already done yeah fast dungeon
what it's a it's a small dungeon it's
not the main
[Music]
one
nice
okay well
then well then we shall slowly prepare
for the end the end of it all
yeah yeah uninstalling Eden
Eternal what the
[\h__\h] uninstalling eaten
Eternal
[Music]
haers what we care about the game what
are you
talking I care very much about the game
no no I'm kidding I'm kidding no but
yeah uh guys don't spam the world chat
too much okay not not that was funny but
let's uh let's
behave oh you know you can turn off your
world
chat well at least like not this message
thing but the other world chat I have
been not reading the chat at
all I forgot it was there
I didn't read it even mostly but um
let's not let's not disturb them too
[Music]
much all right well thank you
for thank you for the
gaming
yeah
fun we mind this grinding so much team
now
I'm so glad I found more likeminded
people like
you and then I can teach you about maple
story soon right you can teach about it
maying Eden now I can't find another
game okay maybe next month but did you
girl see I saw something interesting
yesterday that Ragnarok online is
getting getting like they're they're
working on a new like on on two projects
yeah like a new Ragnar R online free and
also separately another like game like
that so I don't know it might take ages
Ragnarok 2 is a different experience
yeah that completely not
Ragnarok I was fine with
it but yeah I saw that uh like in some
Japanese news yesterday I was like oh my
God oh my God oh my God
exciting oh not popular huh rocken
online too why
why it
become right that's why I liked
it I
Fanatics like um I I will say like for
example like if we differentiate between
these kind of like what we're playing
right now 3D and then trickster online
which is 2D but like kind of top down
angle and then maple story is 2D but
it's like how do you describe
that
g um pixel side scroller yeah Sid
scrolling technically in terms of the
map so Sid scrolling not not really my
for like RPGs if it's like
trickster fine I like I don't have a
problem with with uh uh I don't have a
problem with pixel and I don't have a
problem with 2D but like sides scrolling
[Music]
2D yeah but it looks cute looks very
very cute and I know it's like a good
game cuz people love it so much for a
long time must be good
game yeah it has giggy's brain and heart
and wallet and
body everything
good for you paycheck has that
too yeah my heart is somewhere else but
that's okay so yeah let's let's play
again sometime
soon yeah but also we can always play
members only but let's keep each other
updated on what level we are okay
okay is there a limit on when we should
stop leveling though no if you feel like
leveling a lot go for it go for it we'll
we'll catch up with you yeah yeah yeah
yeah okay who shall I give
lead yeah who is going to advance this
Guild for us so we don't have to who
hopefully do not dis spand the kill
w highest
level
86 no but this person was all like they
didn't start with us they were already
uh high level before I was like damn
they they're
cing they have experience but you better
give me promotion right away there you
go don't destroy the guild I trust
you I trust you the ultimate rage
quit destroy guil
explode what me yes you you're most
experienced player among these
people so help them out yeah y I got I
became captain and vice leader yippee
yipp and now go make a town that will
surprise me next time I go
online
yeah guilt town I remember that yeah
thank you so much girls for playing
together nice MH it was a blast once
again had a great time playing got some
stuff I think I already have these but
maybe different color got some cash up
items again
ooh this one's cute must take anyway I
will I will send people to whatever
people there are in the streams
y can't wait to do bigger dungeons a yay
more challenging ones yeah ones that
actually require a t yeah and with with
like good loot Epic Loot that will fight
over
okay I think I'll go read some super
chatos cuz I'm far behind have a good
one I will also wander off to rest
goodbye thanks for byee
byebye byebye
[Music]
me and sister
shiori hi thanks everyone for hanging
out just yeah it's just sister shiori I
know I got a few thank you for the gers
ships um it's not goodbye I will you you
will forgive me if I don't start exactly
on time but I am planning on playing
Team fight tactics in the next I don't
know hour within the hour it'll be
really chill a really chill
fun
debatable it's going to be a chill
time very head empty I'm I've decided to
start trying this thing where um I do a
lot more head empty streams I thought
about it while I was having my little
wow life is fleeting and then I was
thinking like oh I don't have have to
work so hard to do different things in
my schedule every week because I'm going
to be here for a long time so I can just
take it by the you know a day by day
there's so much time together for me to
play games that I might as well put some
throw some
chill it's okay to be
chill more maple story maple story
probably when the um actual event comes
out and then I'll see if I can rope
anyone into doing cuz when we started
playing maple story it wasn't a really
good time to play maple story since the
burning was ending and then once the
burning is ending it's kind of hard to
keep newer players playing the game when
there's not so much goodies being given
out to them so now now that like the big
event is happening in two-ish weeks I
think I'll start playing maple story
again and then maybe if no one plays
with me we can get a community going
Community maple story Guild and we can
all progress together and see what
happens can't wait for check's notes
nerfed shade looking at smudged
handwriting on the hand oh yes the uh
the good old
[Music]
shade yeah new people it's really hard
to get new people into maple story on an
off event it's just
not it's not a good new player
[Laughter]
experience okay I'm going to get a snack
probably order some drink I don't know I
was like should I order a coffee but now
it's noon so I don't think I should be
ordering a coffee at noon coffee stays
in my system for a long time and then it
keeps me wired at night and then I get
anxious body Shivers but it tastes so
good coffee tastes so good I was so good
and I woke up early today but it's not
even early doesn't even count as early I
just been yapping I was trying to find
my my supas I was going to read the
supas for this stream and then move on
to get a snack before I start TFT where
is it I always get lost do
Studio am iing with Hyperion are moving
to Kronos the thing is
like I was wary starting in Kronos
because I had r with me too and then I
was like What if we just massively lag
this already laggy
server but if it's only
me wouldn't it just be fine to go
onto the populated server I don't know I
we just don't
know but the thing
is it's like if I do a community thing
then I don't have to worry about finding
a party that much
[Laughter]
right like it matters
less that I have to be on a populated
server cuz there's got the community
going on to carry me in um Monster Park
extreme if I were to do Monster Park
extreme someone would carry me and not
not care that I do no damage and I can't
kill
anything and then I don't know I guess
like oh it doesn't matter I was thinking
ear matters but it really doesn't matter
what you do 5% of ursus solo and then
you time out and then you get the full
rewards I believe it works like that
yeah so even being on an unpopulated
Server doesn't matter too much unless
you're actually endgame party playing
and you don't have friends and then
that's when you need to Party play
because you don't have
friends are any Monster Hunter could
last stream plan no
not until Wilds comes out I don't intend
to play worlds because I don't want to
read the cut scenes even I've like I've
seen the cut scene before cuz I played
the game before but they are
unskippable they're unskippable cut
scenes and I they're
long thank you for this super thank you
tanuk Kazi for this super I sent you my
cat please respond about my cat please
don't flirt with me that's not what this
is about just look at the cat yes please
come over and look at my cat that was
not a come on I just want you to see my
cat so bad
thank you Jun thanks for the g p thank
you Mr JC mus Global when it comes out I
am planning on playing um mus once
Global comes out I've been waiting for
it I didn't want to play on the JP
server cuz I wouldn't be able to read it
and then I feel like it takes away from
the experience when it's all about cute
horse girls running around and um
talking to you so I didn't want to play
on the JP servers but now I'm made
Global horse horses thank you zipley for
the super
thank you I think those are the suers
for the stream okay I will see you all
soon I'm going to get food get some rest
I'll probably just rain into my next
waiting room if you're here for
me and we can just chill and play TFT
and you guys can teach me about the set
cuz I don't know anything about to set I
really
don't
I played like one game at the very
beginning set and then I didn't play at
all ever again cuz I fell off TFT but
then now that worlds happen I'm kind of
like ooh kind of want to play some leak
kind of some leak games hop on the rift
while we
wait me
no okay goodbye everyone where's here go
next to the next stream see you soon and
when I come back this shoren will not be
behind me
farewell I will be back back very very
soon so very soon
[Music]