foreign
[Music]
hello
reverse health
how are you here
oh it's like a dog
thank you thank you okay
[Music]
oh
okay yeah
oh man hello
how how
do you drink how what are you doing how
are you doing here
I'm good thank you thank you for asking
I'm happy to not have to control the
things I'm on the wheels today
exactly wait you're using a wheel to
control obser
using the Mario Kart wheel of course
always
wow I wonder if you could like possibly
like I'm pretty sure it's possible to
basically anything with like a
controller these days right so advanced
technology
controls for obs
until it controls
what four
anyway
um hello I am from Whole Life English
oh
oh you can't say that so easily
I mean if I have if I have to you know
maybe perhaps go on like a uh I don't
meeting you know the channel Belongs to
You temporarily and you know you said
you know also second in command when
you're not away you can also be second
in command for a tentacles or taco can
be sure that's not me as your second in
command I actually will do something oh
what are you doing when I was gone you
didn't really do much with your with
your power
exactly you know the meme with the the
Sailor Moon and Tuxedo mess is like my
job here is done but you didn't do
anything that's me
you're proud of it I see
when you introduce yourself do it
hi
um
I am uh who am I
[Music]
um
no we're sisters we're long lost sisters
separated
actually because at the hospital you
were kidnapped and my whole life I was
looking for you it's just like I know it
sounds like it's in a TV show but you
were kidnapped and I was looking all
over the world for you and now finally
here in whole life I found my long lost
sister
okay okay
I don't know where we're taking this
conversation but I am I'm not talking
we are according to the script creating
a relaxed atmosphere
which I think it's working I think I
think this is creating more suspense
than relaxation if I'm being honest here
anyway
[Music]
um everybody and this is
herself I'll say it for her
it's not like I wanted you to say my
name or anything
I see a right below us we have the
hashtag hello Curie connect
please use it if you want to like tweet
about anything related to the event or
just the stream too yeah
okay reconnect hashtag
okay
[Music]
um
do you remember
okay do you remember
the events collaboration
with Valkyrie connect when we were in
the game it was so exciting yeah that
was
that was pretty big actually remember
yeah they were blasting through like the
Milestones that for the um
without the rewards
yes yes yes
you really wanted your your automatic
cat toilet yeah well so that was really
cool and uh for the people who are
um not so aware because isn't this like
so first valkyr connected uh connected
connect related stream on your channel
yeah I think so I mean I mean I made
like tweets and stuff about it but I
guess they're you know there might be
new fans you know that joined joined our
uh chat you know yeah
if you don't have Twitter who maybe did
not know about this at all maybe exactly
yeah we were like part of a
collaboration uh and Valkyrie connect is
the game it's a jrpg on smartphones and
steam and you know it of course also has
the whole gacha aspect and we you were
able to get us in the game for free
though for free and yeah two other
members from her life Japan pick what I
said
and we got like really cool uh fresh
outfits that were inspired by our uh old
default ones but made even cooler and
and we look like we're just perfectly
belonged to the game right yeah and I
believe like we had like a story in the
game too like how we how we intake were
integrated into the world of Valkyrie
tonight it was very cool yeah we had our
voice signs there too you know we have
to record voices
like like if there's like a
collaboration where we also give our
voice it just feels like so much more
real and cool especially for the fans
too if they don't only see us but also
hear us there then
interaction and and potential and
quality to it right yeah I remember
and I was I was like listening to my
voice eyes along with like my little uh
3D version of uh me and valky connect
like you know yay using the skills and
the voice lines and you
um there was like special event voice
size too actually
for like between certain
um Milestones yeah it felt it feels
different it's like
you know
um
I said that um it was like the outfits
were like uh and our theme outfits but
made to look even more you know like the
game characters that are already in the
game so actually it was like our default
outfits combined with outfits from
um Valkyrie connect characters they were
already in the game
dad I want to ask you Ina yeah you could
choose another outfit to wear from a
character that's already in the game
whose would you want are there any like
biker connect characters whose design
you like
I did choose one I did choose one
prepared but you're acting as if you're
thinking about it
that's fine that's my who for finding
what I [\h__\h] the images
okay
just okay the game was like uh you know
they gave us like a little rundown on
all the characters and like the
character I chose will actually uh
Phyllis wait where's the image
oh wait hold on give me one second the
one okay there we go it was fellas there
we go
[Music]
I
I mean I can kind of see myself wearing
it it's kind of really yeah maybe yeah
and maybe she does have like the blue
purple look you know like the staff
looks really fancy
yeah the weapons they make for this game
they're so cool
it definitely can bomb people with that
uh staff instead of just using Magic
and you can see the belly button the
shape of it oh
oh yeah
she doesn't seem to be wearing
um anything to protect a little breeze
of wind
what a tiny Breeze of wind would ah I
mean like it's like it's like attached
by like a throat sting in the in the in
the middle you know
they do not allow you to wear this
outfit this does not look safe
you know you're not leaving the house
like my mom
no you have to weigh something proper
okay
how old or even then this is not
appropriate no Mom no no wear a sweater
the sweater I gave you for Christmas
wear that one you're not gonna have one
anymore I don't like that one
I have one no it has how big
me how I'm thankful I'm grateful you are
it doesn't have cookies in the front for
that slide I don't like it
you're gonna make your mommy cry wait
why am I your mommy now who's your
sister
okay okay well I just found a little bit
how about you how about you I already
know but
okay we have to choose from a certain
list you know and and one spoke to me
because it just you will see why it
spoke to me her name is
look at those wings
Kara do you have wings like these
um I do but hookah Papa does not allow
me to show them yet
maybe one day I will be able to show
wings like this but I do think like if I
look at the the I mean I don't know for
sure but like if I look at the tail that
she has there you know
doesn't this really look like a phoenix
design yeah it look it kind of reminds
me of your your feathers
you know the warrior type
um I feel like I want to wear like armor
like this it's really cool that is oh I
hope that one day you can get like a
like a reason like a fantasy like armor
kind of design too that's so cool
I want to oh this was an obvious choice
I think you know what I really love the
fact that like you just definitely know
that she's a valkyrie because of the
helmet it's about these are known for
their helmet right the feathers
ah I you can be a valkyrie and the
Phoenix at the same time thank you yes
yes I was born for this I am mad this is
my destiny yeah
okay so yeah the Fire theme and the
wings it's lack of Phoenix so that's my
choice my choice very very cool
character you know we're not only here
to talk about just who we'd want to be
you know if it were to get another
animal outfit or something like that why
are we here for Kiara
perhaps
an announcement perhaps new information
oh more yes some people see something
nice to look at something interesting
this is gonna be all new information I
know oh okay okay we're gonna stop maybe
we can do like a little recap of like
what happened
um with the previous event
so during the last collab event that we
had players were able to get us and make
us stronger
[Music]
and uh yeah play play with us during the
event but during this next event we can
become even stronger and get a new pose
in our illustration by Awakening
Awakening we're telling Bears gonna be a
new event soon
if you can we can us
here
but
um don't you have a line to say
you mean
and Awakening events
you know I should just have a sound
sound board thing with the blunts on it
oh yeah you just take app and canning
and then in between you just make a what
yeah
[Music]
yes anyways
um it's gonna be
what's it oh yeah oh yeah
um thank you for that Inna thank you
very much for sacrificing
for that no worries
today's going to be a special Awakening
event for us before
I don't think this has been announced
yet so I'm gonna make a big one out of
it I should I should have gotten like a
drum roll thing but before
[Music]
the second whole life collaboration
begins
which heavily implies that there is
going to be a second hello life Co
collaboration with this game
we've trapped there perhaps the more
than us involved yeah
for now but but yeah so I can't really
speak much to it but for now we're here
to talk about the Awakening exactly
it's where we will still be around and
it's set for early 2023 I know it's
early for us to say and talk about this
but you know we we we're we were too
excited and we hope that you guys are
excited about it too so that you're
curious about how much more powerful
we're going to be
but you know let's let's uh maybe show
them you know maybe the people who
haven't seen before we can show them
like the first art never mind but they
confirmed the second collab after the
first one ended so
so many that's why it's written here as
if it's already known information okay
sorry not a big deal
wow hello live second haul of clap no
way
whoa let's go
yay I wonder who they'll choose for that
I wonder
anyway so maybe Mrs inanis who is
controlling OBS with her Mario Kart real
can share a first look of the new images
for the okay drift to the right wow
look at it
for
um them being added in for the previous
event first event
but yeah you know these ones these look
familiar so what's going to change about
them
okay let's start with Lapu yeah
you know you get to see the rough draft
of what's gonna be
come the uh awakened
special look at that
in the world wait which country is he
sitting on
is that asking for a friend
no no it might not be it might not even
be Earth maybe is it I don't know
that looks I mean I could be wrong but
it looks like North and South America oh
what we're getting a treat
[Laughter]
sorry anyways she's really taking over
the world now hasn't she huh she looks
like so mature with that pose with those
legs yo you can like just hear her you
can just hear her laugh you know she's
all over the world
what was the name I don't remember but
it's like yeah
setting off to fight to battle
I didn't know I could fly I'll be honest
with you
it's usually this thing on my head you
know I thought it was like like fake no
no I thought it was just one of those
birds that like choose not to fly
because they're just comfortable living
like on the ground
nesting yeah on her head
laying eggs on her head
well yeah this this looks really cool I
really like it I really like
the Frills on her skirt yes
you can't see my mouse right now but I'm
just like pointing out all the places I
really like about there
hi okay where your mouse is right now I
can't imagine anyways another way you
know next time
she's so cute
ha
huh she's an idol
yeah oh so pretty cute
but did the outfit change too or is it
oh wait let's take a look let's take a
look
Maybe
no I think they stayed the same
okay yeah
okay okay
that feeling of you you level up like
the characters
lots of effects
I can't wait to see the finished art too
it's so cute I really love her weapon
like it's just it just screams pickle
yum
it has so much energy
I love this juice I really want the
shoes yeah I was just about I was just
like circling my mouse around the shoe
it's so adorable
so those are exclusive looks for pekuna
Senpai and
now of course we will also show you us
but first let's look at the old ones
again
yeah yo we already had like really
Dynamic and cool poses yeah especially
with my tentacles too I feel like that
was like a really big you know effect on
its own exactly
it looks so cool like I really love how
your like Shields turn into like the
disc that spin around you
um
yeah so cool
it's like an automatic Shield you know
but how did we
how do we upgrade from this yeah um
I'll start with you
early sketch phase yeah I feel like you
went from like a kind of like
let's go to like you're kind of like
dance you know like one of those like
Fighters that like dance like their
moves kind of look like a dance almost
yeah and you're really good at dancing
so I feel like this is really energetic
thank you yeah because like I'm I'm in a
world range of fire yeah and hurt me
because I'm a phoenix very dynamic
I'm looking forward to the finished
product but this already looks sick look
at those hips oh those hips
those Hips Don't Lie
very elegant oh you know even on your uh
do you video man
those dances
[Laughter]
[Music]
no lies
do you love me yeah I want to see yeah
you don't like do you love me
[Music]
well Ina my song says love hates all the
same if you know play the game so play
uh Valkyrie connect whole life
collaboration
hey come on we're we're promoting the
same okay
it's mother to lovers very confusing
that's a fun one
um interesting plot okay
so my Awakening
three two one wait
ah
you know I got kind of tired of floating
so I sat down this time
well you look like you you don't even
need to lift a finger but you can
obliterate thousands of takodachis with
one snap look at that tentacle wrapping
around my leg they're all over that
already I can tell look at those hoof in
the chat you know the Katy teeny hoof
no need for hands
yeah but really it really looks like you
know you're so powerful that you don't
need to put much of an effort into
attacking you just you're chilling there
yeah you know I'll be um
of Pentacles and you know everything
else to do the work I just sit there
your hair is like just flowing down the
tentacles yeah it makes for a nice chair
it's kind of like a few sit on like a
floaty in the pool it kind of feels like
that oh I love that yeah okay right on
the next time
oh wow you're you're saying I oh dear
I'm not gonna like
repeat that better not repeat that
all right
um
oh I bet you guys are all wondering
something right
all this Awakening Ah that's looking
really cool but what about the people
who didn't play last time is there
anyone who didn't play last time in the
Chant
because we were not part of the gotcha
we were free characters you could unlock
yeah
I'm not sure how it is now but now it
was the event exclusive here
oh well I know some people
um weren't able to get us then but maybe
have missed out on the whole event well
your fault but
maybe we can give them another chance in
Maybe
[Music]
I'll press the button
s
wow Second Chance buttons
and you can get the characters by doing
missions doing that a walk a walking
event yay
[Music]
during this new event will be able to
once again get all of us so look forward
to it yeah there's gonna be even you
know more items available Club items and
I know from the last collab will also be
available too so yes yes hope you guys
look forward to that
early 2023 so I mean you can already
install it now and you know get prepared
get ready but yeah
it will happen in 2023 and if we know an
exact date we will surely let you know
we'll see
on another topic I keep on getting asked
by my viewers
with the presents did you get oh yeah so
for context you know
um there were Milestones that
um could be reached by the fans for you
guys for just playing the game
um during the event and you get a lot of
points and we had some Milestones where
you guys can gift us some presents that
we picked now
and uh what was your present y'all
um I asked for uh like specifically
um you know we all got like presents
from a member to member and from fans to
um us and then like smaller gifts I
think and then also like one big gift
that we asked for uh to the WellCare
connect team and what I asked for was
yeah
um well I have two cats so I asked for
and one of those automatic really
futuristic round self-cleaning and
turning cat litter robots
honestly very good idea okay because
it's it's uh I know it's really a lot of
work to take care of a cat so if there's
one thing that can be automated you know
thumbs up yeah I hope they will like it
yes mine is not here yet but I I heard
they are currently like
um packing it so I think they all
arrived at the whole live office they
just have to shift to us yeah yeah and
most likely uh mid-october they're gonna
be arriving at our places and then we'll
see if my cats will accept the robots
cats toilet Overlord or not
[Music]
exciting I have a picture yet for mine
but I heard
there's a picture of your oh yeah so my
gift that I've picked that was actually
um
try and talk about the plushie and for
me
I first say like sorry of how you asked
for this one because you didn't quite
understand what was going on yeah
oh
but after I saw the pictures of it I was
like
[Music]
I was speechless for at least like 10
minutes
you got the whole thing wrong now now
you don't regret it right I think it
made for a really interesting gift I'll
just say that because okay so the story
with the takorachi plushies right so my
first birthday uh March was actually
um it included like a giant bean bag of
a takorachi
you know the purple face on it
um and we also had our six month um
anniversary mascot plushies
they're the um they're the uh smaller
you know they're not that small it's
like pretty big still but when I
when I got the um the pictures for the
sakuraji and I saw a person beside her
scale
I was like At first I was like
because I thought I was just gonna get
like the uh chicken they're just gonna
like remake just one and send it to me
[Applause]
but they actually they actually made a
giant pot
okay I'll just show you guys can we get
even bigger
big big
oh that is a water bottle frisket
that's probably like it goes maybe to up
to my hips or higher Maybe
oh
yeah
it's like okay so this one is 39 inches
or around
a meter tall
Mater 100 centimeters yeah so they
really uh took the giant apart seriously
um could this be the the biggest
takudate in existence at this point
it could I think it might it might be
unless someone made one look themselves
like it's
what'd you guys eat
um
it's running on his face already
but yeah you know
um
I think I've gotten quite a few packages
from the whole life office recently I
wonder
if one of them is just gonna be a giant
box with this
because this one's already failed up
yeah it's and it's not it's gonna be
pretty heavy too if it's like stuff with
like the usual
um you know the usual plushy stuffing
oh well I'm glad I'm glad you're happy
with it yeah
well we could have waited wait for any
what we get actual an actual real life
thing I thought it was just yeah that
was an indie thing because I was like oh
I wanna get that guy in takorachi
and then I told you I was like you know
yeah so I'm getting a cat toilet for my
cats I'm like what what wait what what
real life item what
didn't know we could do that yeah and
then I was like I'm gonna try to talk
about Jake
it's Giant
So yeah thank you
yeah it's uh we're gonna have so many
taco dots on your place you know because
my mom she wouldn't give up give up
these small takorachi plushie I keep
asking her to bring it over but she's
just like oh no I forgot it
so I guess she can't forget this
um well yeah
family is growing
beautiful oh man oh yeah all of these
presents are gonna get to us finally
mid-october maybe the Japanese members
should get it even earlier because yeah
that's true because it's already at the
office so
[Music]
um
yeah
no one's face it's okay I don't pick up
that much space I usually crawl up into
a ball when I sleep
[Music]
it also looks like the the width is also
like I feel like I feel like it's like
wider than tight I don't know maybe I'll
have to see you
hi
yeah
you know I feel like if it has some
weight it can also be like a
self-defense thing you know if there's a
beef or burglar my house I can just
Chuck this at them what what do you ever
watch this this will stop any knife or
bullets exactly maybe not a bullet but
maybe some knives
[Music]
With Honor you will be you will be a
legend yeah they'll never expect a
takorachi
all right thank you very much Valkyrie
connect staff for getting these words
yeah and thank you guys for you know
making this happen like without you guys
playing and blasting through all those
uh Milestones yeah I'm grinding this for
another our presence thank you it was a
big motivation for everybody
so now let's talk a little bit about the
global anniversary event shall we yeah
we have one more thing to talk about oh
what's this the sixth anniversary of
Valkyrie connect oh wow
ears yeah probably older than the whole
life
damn one year old a year stand by
Valkyrie connects
yeah so congratulations
for all the players who have stayed
loyal to the game who are playing at the
moment
so first gift two characters that we
mentioned earlier there's a reason we
went in there yeah they're going to be
free just by logging in you can get the
two
remember uh the characters uh this is
Kiara's this is let me just uh move
those two I hope you guys will find them
useful uh the valkyr connect players the
active ones maybe the ones who don't
even know about us too they will be
grateful for receiving these choices of
us I hope they're useful yeah and we'll
get you far there's also gonna be an
event to power them up so you can make
them real strong real fast you can put
them in the same party as us if you
already got it no question it
yeah and
um yeah it's gonna be starting October
1st
very soon very soon and that's that's
Saturday I think it's Saturday yeah you
will be getting up to 3 000 diamonds and
three strong characters
asides from the ones we picked up when
you log into the events
a lot of free characters free stuff free
stuff yeah
check it out check it out make sure to
check it out happy anniversary
[Music]
yeah you know
that's the that's all the nonsense we
have for today right and we're like a
new show from I don't carry connect now
I feel like we should be I don't know
what bgm you're playing but it would be
nice to have some typical news Show
Theme going in the show theme
how the weather
the street from Japan
a new Awakening event happening in 2020
for a year we are excited and we are now
asking everyone in the chat to share
their excitement with us by using the
hashtag wholekiri connect on Twitter and
everywhere to share the news everywhere
this must be known this must be known
wow
yes
there will be also a second hollow life
collaboration event it is being worked
on right now as we speak whoa oh yeah oh
yeah oh yeah
who will be the new members
I'm just assuming they're choosing new
members as I said I don't know I think I
don't know maybe
who knows who knows who knows you know
if they are chosen though
it means they will have the art like we
did
he also have the voice lines and the
little cute 3D models in the valkyrie
connection
give me your best guesses chat you know
not only in the live chat right now but
in the comments you can be like oh I
wish so and so it could be no offense
someone so could be in the you know
maybe maybe the staff is watching you oh
yeah maybe they can be influenced yeah
maybe they can be bribed
and yeah you know
um do you know how to say any um final
thoughts about you know the whole
um us being in the game returning
Awakening yeah I'm really happy to you
know be included once again in something
like this and that's not over yet
because
um then I I can see you guys play with
kiwawa again cute 3D mini Cuba in action
again and also
um I'm looking forward to the toilet
um I hope my cats will use it because if
they don't use it then I don't know what
to do with it with it because obviously
it's not big enough for well I mean I of
I don't need a toilet anyway because
yeah I don't go to the toilet but
yeah so um please please cats use it
if I don't use it then as I said before
the stream to uina I I can give the
toilet to you
but yeah for my future cats but you know
I can I can tell you one
protection
oh
your cats
you're going to love
the box that it comes in
[Laughter]
yeah I mean the the smaller the Box the
better I think that's gonna yeah but
it's so pretty fun you know it can have
boxes inside boxes so
any cardboard box maybe the cardboard
box can become the toilet otherwise
maybe maybe it's their new home I put
some leather in there they're probably
gonna use it
but yeah well any anything any last
words from you Mrs
Mrs America are you I don't know
It All Leads in one way
it's nicer
okay I guess anyways
um another difference yeah you know I
had a lot of fun like seeing everyone
post about our first the first time we
um we're in the event I'm glad that
those of you who missed us for the first
time has another chance to get us and
strengthen us with the Awakening even be
excited yeah yeah 2023 might seem like
it's far away but then you're gonna
blink and it's already gonna be New
Year's so honestly it's not gonna fall
away anymore
often October literally like we could
always yeah it's basically
mom
oh my God yeah
and yeah I'm looking forward to seeing
you know what they have in store for the
second collaboration as well
I can't wait to see all the art you know
as an artist I really enjoy looking at
all different art of all the characters
and pocket connect has a lot of
different characters and a lot of
different Arts so
um not only you know
Austin Hall live in the game I'm looking
forward to any new stuff coming up for
valkyrie connect as well sixth
anniversary wow what is now yeah and oh
by the time that uh you know we are
gonna be
um awakened woken up by you guys good
morning uh in 2023 I think the stream
the next stream will be happening on my
channel so I'll see you there again
everybody
please look forward to it
yes
[Music]
leave that we're done yeah high five
enough yeah okay high five myself
anyways I I think that was it
um thank you so much everyone for all
your support like those of you even just
watching now those of you who played the
first event those of you interested in
playing it for the Awakening event and
further on thank you
thank you and thank you to novaki
connect staff for you know making this
happen it's been a lot of fun working
with you guys
hey
I think foreign
like sometimes uh I remember like a few
times when talking to other en members
um I don't know why it came up but we
would talk about like the sponsorships I
guess in general and then like I
remember Sammy and members being like yo
I wish I wish I had gotten that Valkyrie
connect sponsorship all those presents
you guys
really spoiled I'm jealous yeah really
good yeah yeah like because we didn't
really know about it until like
afterwards
I didn't expect it to be yeah
I mean look at me I asked for a giant
takorachi plush and look how giant it is
[Music]
for Subway Supply life Supply honestly
that could have lost it for like a long
time
or a big sandwich
dakimakura oh sandwich
oh my God sandwich is like perfect for
it exactly oh my goodness
I'm a genius
collaboration and I'll I'll tell her
about this idea
and she will like it yeah
anyways yeah
thank you so much everyone yeah
[Music]
thank you I hope you guys have a
wonderful wonderful rest of the morning
afternoon evening and uh thank you Sarah
for joining me today I guess I'll join
you for the uh another stream on your
Channel Down Below hopefully before that
too yeah
anyway thank you I'll see you guys next
time
[Music]
why
ready now
I don't think you had the the this
streaming sponsored thing