[Music]
what
n
[Music]
hello K KY
sorry about
[Music]
that sorry for the waight come
give me a moment please also sometime in
the
next
few minutes 10 minutes 20 minutes who
knows I'll have to open the door for
something the crunch
more do you feel the disturbance in the
force
guys not yet
huh I feel it
who wants to get in
[Music]
trouble
oh oh really
oh
really thank you for the
membership
H well what did you guys do that that
made you think you you should be getting
in trouble huh does that make sense
no what did you do that got you in
trouble huh
[Music]
stop streaming Sparks for 30
seconds oh my
[Music]
God okay that is quite the
crime Turkish
[Music]
all right
Dage you're the chosen one
[Music]
he's
gone but I hear him screaming in the
distance you hear that
too I'm just stalling cuz I want to
finish my my
bread that's not me that's Turkish
no not
me oh my
god of course it's not me I'm speaking
at the same time how would that be
possible H tell
me he's he's
[Music]
suffering but hopefully he's also
learning
[Music]
not
okay well well well
well
Dage just like
you
recently many many
chickens of
kfb have been
underestimating number one my power
number two the usual
room and I
am sick and tired of
it you guys are acting as if the usual
room is a walking in the park but it is
not for folk sake it is not some kind of
vacation that you can take in order to
stop flipping burgers at
kfp and when you get out of there some
of you are acting as if they were never
in there to begin with as if it was all
just fun and games and as if you learned
absolutely nothing from going there and
that is to me unbelievable and
Unthinkable and I think you guys are
lacking
imagination so I think I need to help
you a little
[Music]
bit so let's follow Derk to the usual
room shall we
[Music]
shall we go I will not take your hand
because you guys need to learn that it's
[Music]
scary we can take each other's hands but
bamboozle chickens don't have hands so
good luck with
that let's go to the usual
room follow me
so you think it's still funny
huh you think it's so funny
huh you think this is a place to take a
vacation at
it's
not this is the user room where I want
you guys to understand what you have
done and how to get
better but the people the chickens who
are going in here just seem to not get
better it's not
comfy
no I would like to show you guys around
a little bit
one
second oh my god did you see
that wrong there we go
okay well well well here we have a p
chicken have some stuff
that there's not I mean this is not a
place to play but well uh here you uh
will be will receive help to become a
stronger and bigger
chicken we we yeah that's all that is
um
here is uh your tears collected in
bottles wonderful a lot of Tears we've
collected many tears so honestly I don't
understand how people can come out of
the usual room and be like oh it was so
much fun they're actually just
lying that's Sweat and Tears combined in
bottles uh we could probably even sell
them but we're not selling them
now
wait God damn it
again
yes okay
well here we have some chairs but
honestly don't think you'll be here with
and have a chicken for mental support
you'll be here alone we all know that
the usual room is a place to be be alone
and to reflect on your
actions I will not I I cannot explain
what happens in these chairs uh it might
have something to do with what's written
here on the wall watch only me how many
times do I have to tell you that huh #w
#
yolk is that so difficult to
understand God damn it your
chickens unbelievable
up up up here I almost cannot reach uh
we have some images that are constantly
repeating
itself uh Spar is
streaming but it just doesn't
really it doesn't play properly I we
don't know if that's on purpose or to to
you know troll you guys to trigger you
or if that's another technique to make
you guys go
um and reflect and improve on your
actions this is not heaven no if you
try additionally if you try to escape
yeah you know what happens it's
impossible you cannot
Escape at the
door does that look like you can go home
through that door uh-uh wrong
people
no no all right come back
chat come back to me so will you guys
act a little bit better now will you be
better
chickens
huh will you be more
respectful to you one only Tal
mods ban everyone who says
no
everyone
everyone this is a
command B
everyone okay while I'm looking at the
suffering durage in the seat in the back
looks like he's in there right now uh
I'll be reading super chats today while
we're in this room so that you guys can
feel the the not scary totally not scary
the relaxing vibes from the usual
room oh yeah this this is made by our uh
good friend who who uh recently uh not
recently a while ago also made the the
fairy tale readings
uh background thingy T Nar
Nar yeah remember the the fairy tale
reading room he also updated it so many
times uh with like other stuff and and
he also made like a Christmas version
and a New Year's version and however I I
kind of stopped do that Series so
unfortunately I didn't really get to
show off much of it anymore but but I
asked n to make this a usual room
background
yeah thank you n for working so hard on
it this time as a commission and I
commissioned
n good good loyal chicken thank you so
much it looks really cool came with some
extra animations I like the animations
yeah at first uh that that was that was
why I recently let me turn into some
[Music]
music okay uh yeah recently I asked you
guys do you guys imagine when you think
of the usual do you think of
something like dark and scary or do you
think of something clean and like I
don't know like white and empty whatever
you know what I mean and I personally a
lot of you guys said dark and scary and
all that but I personally always thought
of something more you know modern and
and and sterile yeah stal St clinical
yeah that's what that's kind of like
what I had in mind so
yeah there's way more than just Irish
there if you look up here there's Ena up
here and K is in the back and behind the
chat should be
a oh yeah am is sitting there where's
GAA ah here GAA is here on on this side
we have Yago down
there uh yeah in in
the in the fa T reading room we had like
pretty much yeah every whole I've member
that I collabed with before but then I
think NADA increased it to like
basically everything whole life member
was like somewhere in the
room yeah there's a lot of stuff in this
room it's really
cool I can I can get rid of the little
puppets as well if I want to have it a
bit more cleaned
up oh finally a new room for us to hang
out and it's not the most comfortable
one I will not be I don't know how often
I will use this it's not that cozy is it
it's kind of weird and I think for for
new people it's like what how what is
this what does kada have to do like what
what is what is her F what the
[Music]
well well well that that's why you know
only in the worst cases only only when
you guys really don't behave at
all that's when I think I I'll come here
to remember remind you guys what will
happen if you're not acting like a good
chicken
[Music]
house I
understand
understand I want you guys to be good
chicken well behaved chicken I want to
be proud of you I I'm usually quite
proud of you buy do you guys challenge
me you guys challenge me you're
like us funny let me go into the usual
room k
k we to going to the US room please you
guys are
stupid mus room is not a
joke it's not a
joke imagine stepping on those Legos
Barefoot cuz you guys don't wear shoes
imagine that is so
painful and out of those speakers on the
side by the way you there's like
endlessly uh loop what what did we say
it's playing out of the speakers I
actually forgot
what's playing in the speaker some
wasn't it like
uh something but I guess now it can just
be
spikes ah we yeah we could play the
watch only me
Anem watch watch
only ah cat's movie for example yeah we
will adjust it the depending on uh your
taste we will make it as uncomfortable
as possible for you doesn't that sound
amazing
wonderful that's the cat's movie are you
finally taking me seriously now huh
finally taking me seriously
cats is a bit too far uh-huh yeah that's
right
M what would be nice though is like
having a table in front of me that would
be
cool a table a table so I can put down
my
drink wink
wink so we will read super chats I don't
know how long and as I mentioned there
should be something arriving from me in
a little bit then I will have to open
the
door but most of the time I'll be
reading super chats
and this is um I will uh don't worry I I
am privately working on the tiata
design completely revamping it h and
then until the ttrpg stream it will be
finished
so don't worry don't
worry it will probably be very very
different from what you have seen
previously my dear members cuz I was
watch I was uh drawing Tiana in the
members only stream before right
so unfortunately that is pretty much
scrap I don't I I don't know if I like
it I don't know if I like it anymore
and
um yeah the other as as I mentioned
before the other girls are like going
for a look that's like completely
different from their actual uh their own
design our our designs so I was like
okay okay okay that was that was the one
thing that I was like not sure
about uh yeah if I should do something
very original or something that looks
like takesi kiar but they are going for
the original style so that's that's cool
for me I I kind of like
that
yeah I'll be reading more and more Super
CH where am I where are they though wait
a second wait a second also last time S
I reached 1
[Music]
million I reached 1 million and pea had
her 2year anniversary
today what a happy day sorry I opened a
million tabs right
now what a happy
day
yeah it's so
cool yeah I I really I really respect um
P Senpai for
always always working so hard I mean as
from the point of view of a of a fan I
think she's working too hard and I want
her to take breaks and she's too hard on
herself as well because she said like
she said that her regret for this year
is that she once one time one time
showed a negative like a negative
emotions negative feelings and that's
that's her regret but um that hurts me
that honestly hurt me because
everyone goes through stuffff and
especially if you're doing something
almost daily if you're like publicly
streaming almost
daily um of course of course that's
mentally also challenging sometimes like
you're not always going to
be fine and 100%
Ganky um but that's that's not something
to be like ashamed of or to apologize
and
but I guess that's just the the the
mindset that most Japanese people have
um or like I guess in in other cultures
as well that letting out any kind of
negative
emotions is not good M that is uh a bit
sad so I was I was sad to hear that U
because she's always working so hard
always giving us her fans so much energy
so much happiness and of course
sometimes you're just down and can't
hold it back
anymore yeah oh
well I I on the other side should hold
back a little bit more
[Music]
for
w
w yeah she's so so has a huge source of
happiness and energy and
laughs and joy
I don't it would make me sad to you know
see see herself her self like con
continuously constantly forcing herself
to always show only the best and the
positive sides of herself it's it's
impossible and and more than anything I
just don't want herself her to put um to
like say that that was bad and like
blame herself for that that's not
good but in any
case I respect her so much for doing
this for 2 years like like a like oh my
God she's been streaming so much every
day working so hard I respect that and I
really look up to her and um I want to
congratulate her H for doing this so
long and I hope she will continue doing
it I'm glad I can continue watching
her and I will continue seeing her as
one of my role
models really really respect her her
content is so
entertaining I have barely been able to
watch her streams ever since I joined
whole life which is
unfortunate but I know she didn't change
I know she is still amazing she's she
still the same peod Senai that she was
in the day uh when I was watching her
every day and needed her as a source of
you know uh something something to cheer
me
up and also her merch is amazing her
twoyear anniversary merch is amazing so
go get
it I love I'm still waiting for her to
get a new casual outfit but like
apparently St announced on her live
Twitter that it's in the works or
something like that so oh my God I'm so
excited no there's no boing boing mouse
pad for that but I mean I have a boing
boing mouse pad of Pai think that was
what merch was that where did I get that
from ah wasn't that from her birth
birthday or Oney year anniversary nah I
don't know but I do have a P with a
Senai mouse
pad m for
[Music]
[Laughter]
M oh B like you understand your fans
more than most because you are such a
big pck off and you know what it's like
ah maybe maybe yeah could be I I
definitely even before H life I was a
big fan of idols and I I kind of
understand what they're going through
and how hard it is and um
yeah I I just I just really respect
people who put themselves through a job
like that where on the outside of course
you always have to show that
everything's fine and um have to do your
best to be a role model
and be very respectful in any situation
and uh any matter any topic uh it's it's
it's not always easy to
uh be in a position like
that um to always have to give joy to
people or feel feel like you have to
always give joy to people it is uh
really
pressuring
the
the there is quite some pressure but but
there's also so much that you get back
from it
yeah yeah professionalism is really
really important when you do something
like this whether it's uh doing V tubing
or being a real Idol as in a real Idol
on stage or whatever any kind of person
who's like in the public eye uh always
needs to consider what kind of effect
and influence they have on
others uh and I think some people do it
really well and I think I'm one of the
people who maybe doesn't do it that
well but I still
try so so
[Music]
so I don't know where that came from I
don't know where that T came from oh I
just wanted to talk a little bit about P
Senai and also once again congratul for
1 million L Senai is
amazing I respect her so much do I love
her she's such a sweetheart L Senpai
really makes me feel so comfortable and
appreciated whenever I talk with her or
collaborate with
her she's a great
sheep very talented and very very
lovable I admire her a
lot yeah she's like a like a really like
like like a sister like naturally
without without even doing much with her
she already treats everyone with so much
kindness and it's always a lot of fun
to uh communicate with her want to do
more collapse
y yeah
needed some hom this here some fan going
cuz everyone's doing so great in h life
everyone's working so hard in h
life I just need to appreciate that a
little
bit oh also yeah I'm glad M Senai is
taking a little break but as as well as
far as I know her she's probably going
to be back like in less than a
week so hm well we're getting therea
she's she's maybe slowly slowly getting
there yeah I I hope she takes some time
for herself too yeah cuz she was like oh
I can't I can't stream with this voice
but but hey I can I can uh be part of
that collab Minecraft collab that we
planned anyway because I just won't be
in voice chat I can just be in the
game uh okay M
sen take some time for yourself
on
yeah I I really hope to take some time
for herself cuz she's also such a
incredible hard worker all all of the
girls in her life are but yeah Mina is
one of those crazy
ones
who just probably doesn't know how to
stop I talked with her about it a few
times uh told her to to take a break and
she she's like yeah I want to but I
don't know
how once you get started with with Hall
of life it's I talked about this with
other H life English members as well
like it's it's difficult to find a time
to take a
break although I think I have been doing
quite well of that you know me recently
going to Greece and all
that M it is
it is just something you got to do you
got to do for yourself in order to
continue doing stuff like that on a long
term but I always enjoy coming back to
this place not to this usual room but to
you guys I always enjoy coming back to
you I I missed you guys on my vacation
too I always thought of you guys always
constantly thinking of you guys no
matter where I
go
yeah but um
it's fun to reward myself with a
vacation too now oh can't shouldn't
can't speak shouldn't only see it as a
break for your own health should also
see it as a as a
[Music]
reward and I think any everyone deserves
that kind of reward all right all right
all right all right I already talk too
much blah blah blah
blah at
all is my stuff uh coming or
not probably at some
point all right this is a chatting yeah
super chatting extreme
chatting uh we have to read the
Sparks music video premiere or did we
read no we read those we did read
those we did read those so after that
comes the collaboration Super Chat right
so so so so so where is
the where is the file where I saved all
of
them one moment
please I'll find
it is this the one
no
do super
chats okay got
it new layout it's it's not it's not a
permanent layout I'm only using this for
special occasions welcome everyone I did
a little introduction of this screen if
you missed it uh go back to the archive
later on and yeah once again shout out
to Natata for making this usual
[Music]
room hopefully teaching you guys a
lesson with that oh okay scroll down
down down down down down down down down
down down down down down down down
[Music]
okay birthday collab there we
go oh let's see how far we get today
today Saturday right got to make my
schedule like tomorrow on Monday I might
make
it you might not get it until Monday
evening or so I don't
[Music]
know brain brain are you working
yes oh did you guys watch The Knockout
City C it was really short so if you
weren't there for the live stream you
should definitely uh check out the uh
arive it's just for it was supposed to
be an hour but uh we started like 15
minutes later uh because we realized
what the you actually have to get a
get like an upgraded version in order to
play together so then uh a few of us had
to purchase it and then it took a little
bit of a time but but then like I think
I think made s byai was kind of like
thinking uh cuz we said 1 hour that it
would end you know at the full hour but
uh I think we we all forgot about the
fact that you know we added 15 minutes
delay so we should have done it a little
bit longer but oh well it was so much I
don't know if it was so much fun to
watch for you guys but it was so much
fun to
play it was H we had a
blast it was so much fun
[Music]
it's so much fun and yeah we already
suggested to to the others to play it uh
with h English and
Irish already suggested it because
Sixers collab absolutely perfect we had
a blast and I think when we all speak
English then it might be even a bit more
enjoyable for you
guys a bit more understandable what's
going
[Music]
on I tried to get some English in there
but it was a lot of a go it was a lot of
how do you say go Goa in
English it was a lot of
um uh go
Goa yeah games like this always
especially if there's so many members
there's always a lot of screaming a lot
of overlapping of voices and
stuff and especially if it's Japanese
and English it's a overlap of languages
as
well it was a bit chaotic here and there
but it was so much fun yo and uh yeah I
I was I was good I was decent in the
beginning but then I got worse in the in
the
ending I panicked and I was like damn
it every time and every time I died I
was like I up why did I do that
[Music]
oh yeah oh yeah my game was German I
actually like I clicked English when I
installed the game but once I opened it
I guess because I opened it for Steam
for some reason it made it German and I
didn't find a setting to change it back
in the game I could have probably
changed it somewhere but I couldn't find
it I was like whatever it's not going to
be important
anyway no that's going to be important I
[Music]
thought your so
all
right oh wait let me put
the my steam I actually don't know is my
steam German yeah it's German the Ste
steam itself is German but the games I
play are usually English on here the
interface often automatically
but oh
well I'm totally okay with using German
but maybe you even learned some
German you
[Music]
okay we need a thumbnail we need a
thumbnail let's see there it
[Music]
is I I feel so bad for covering up this
this amazing
background I don't want to cover it
up oh well you you saw it you saw it in
the beginning I showed
you maybe maybe narata will upload the
clean version on his Twitter who knows
will he maybe possible very
possible slightly
transparent what the
thumnail or like everything should I
make myself slightly
transparent can I make myself lightly
transparent did I
disappear
uh is it here what is that oh I don't
know what that is
[Music]
there it is be
uh so actually I got myself uh groceries
delivered
uh can I put them in the fridge for a
second
[Music]
okay I am back you
hello wait you don't see
me
[Music]
okay what's the pro what seems to be the
problem I'm a
ghost
oo I'm just trying to show you the
beautiful
background so you can appreciate it
should we make this maybe oh that's is
that no I don't know that looks weird
baby but you know what how
about how
about
ooo how about I move it up here when the
common thing isn't there it doesn't look
that
weird and then I put the
are you guys over here
[Music]
wow or wait no maybe
here I'm a
ghost I'm
ghost
yeah maybe this one
too is that better in the chat box
there's a little bit lacking
opacity what do you
think I'll keep that there
though make it a bit
smaller
wonderful
oo can I come back to earth
now
perhaps woohoo
[Music]
oo is that every backa no you guys have
to believe in me believe in
kakana make me
real am I real or am I just
a manifestation of your
dreams press press why to B
I
believe
Tak it's
real wow thank
you thank
you oh stop stop stop stop EO okay so
now maybe I can move like over here uh
I'm move here okay now I'm not com
covering up that much I
think you can stop pressing right
now also have a
banana
banana M
[Music]
banana need some vitamins have barely
barely been eating vitamins these days
[Music]
chat box isn't
centered yeah it shouldn't
be I can have the
CH bit more here so how about
that OCD kicking
in hey I was about to read super chats
and for some reason I managed to not
read anything yet oh my God it's been an
[Music]
hour now no starting to is
okay okay I'll eat the banana and then
I'll read the super jat
[Music]
very
productive also today after the stream I
want to cook some
spaghetti
M I hope I find time
I haven't cooked in a while now my
kitchen is a
[Music]
mess
M yeah spaghetti B
[Music]
is what happened to the one minute go
button is there it's in my in my a un
I have it it's my hippity hoppity my
property where did I get that from where
did I hear that
before what where did I hear that
before where did I pick that up does
anyone
[Music]
no is it a me
can I take my pants off it's so hot
[Music]
[Applause]
okay I'm done I'm ready to read super
chats no I had to have pants for the
delivery yes yes
[Music]
okay
okay water
[Music]
first okay
okay okay okay I'm
ready
sheep d d are you guys ready too cuz I
already started c d Nate 0560 D thank
you for the
[Music]
pinky since I missed earlier stream here
to happy birthday wish from me thank you
you have brought so much fun to the CAF
and I hope today you get to feel uh even
a little of that for yourself oh thank
you thank you so much for everything you
do glory to kfp vivaana thank
you I appreciate it I definitely felt it
thank you so much for being
there
El
Rock SP Banger thank you brown thank you
for the pinky D soon enjoy your birthday
collab and have a lot of fun with your
friends seeing you together warms our
hearts thank you it warms my heart too
being together with them is always such
a joy so much
fun I'm glad we could do a collaboration
together on my
birthday
P dances with vocal d as Maron D Dan D
gangles 93
[Music]
Master thank
you is evil bre Lea jul Julius jul Danny
SC flowers
d mj7
d second 77 d red dud D
tro thank you for the R so
much sorry I missed the first stream no
bra got sick and had to sleep o I hope
you feel better by now just wanted to
wish my favorite birthday but happy
birthday and thank you for being part of
mine and kp's lives I love you T GL to
kfp I love you too thank you for letting
me be part of your life
M thank you so much it is an honor to be
able to bring content to you and
entertain you thank you so
much Sean from Twitter D car Williams D
TI
again with a sub
account T thank
you for a red Super Chat you're crazy
[Music]
tyy T also I haven't seen you a while in
a in a live
stream probably tyy be watching those
archives T thank you for the loyal and
generous huge support as always thank
you all the love to
you I've seen him a lot
really he was here
yesterday oh damn not today huh maybe
maybe T will show up later Jason
alav Dan ad
Dan K7 10 k k k kitten that could be a
lead speak for
kitten K Anderson
re Fran Fran
Fran
cake thank you for the pink
kfp shiny Hunter thank you for the red
super
chat are you hunting shinies in
kfp shiny
chickens are there shiny chickens I
don't think I've ever seen a shiny
chicken no no no no no not 10 10 was
written in actual letters not in the
number 10 so it's K one7 and then 10 t e
n bro I'm sh Shin as kotoni yeah
kotoni uh could probably be a shiny
chicken I mean no kot is not really a
chicken
but what is CI
actually a mix a hybrid
hybrid hybrid between chicken and and
[Music]
Phoenix ever found a shiny C actually
did I tell you guys the story before
of uh when I played Pokemon
[Music]
Sun
no no maybe
not
so
actually there was this time when I was
playing Pokmon Sun soon after soon
right away when it came out and my
friend was playing
Moon and uh my friend was really really
into uh what was this that that new
Pokemon that came with uh sun and moon
that looks like
Pikachu uh like a fake Pikachu uh in a
in in like a potato sack what's it
called again mimik
mimik mimik yeah yeah yeah my friend
loved mimikyu and wanted a mimikyu
number one uh I I think you know when
when you get into that area where you
can get Mimi kill for the first time and
I think yeah it wasn't that easy to get
mimikyu right like you uh there was a
there were a lot of um those other ghost
Pokmon but mimik kill was not that easy
to get it yeah the haunted building the
ghost Supermarket yeah yeah yeah yeah so
I found a Mimi
kill uh while my friends still didn't
find the
mimikyu and I found mimikyu
and that was the first mimikyu I found
and I didn't know I didn't
notice but that first mimiku that I got
was a shiny
mimik but I didn't know it I I I just
caught it thinking it's a normal mimik
and I was like I'm going to I'm going to
send that mimikyu to my friend who's
like really hoping for a mimikyu
and I sent it to my friend and that's
when I found out it was actually a
shiny
apparently barely yeah and I was like wo
um wo oh oh is
it I wasn't even mad I didn't ask for it
to I didn't ask to have it back or
anything I just I didn't really didn't
really care
much I was impressed by myself like what
the hell what is that luck you should
get a blue
Axel you mean those new fishes the OA
loas
L
5% a rate what for the normal mimiku or
for the shiny mimik for mimiku to begin
with yeah I mean for I got my first try
Trident right so seems like I'm quite
lucky when I don't even try when I try I
probably am not that lucky but see
getting a shiny mimiku without trying
and getting a trident without trying
both on first
try is not
normal it's crazy
[Music]
shiny m
crazy yeah yeah yeah H so back to the
shiny Hunter Super
Chat okay okay
[Music]
so ah in German it's called
mimma don't know why mimiku is a cuter
name and so happy birthday boss I'm so
excited for this amazing collab between
you and your wife you your wife and your
friends not only is your merch TN
already ordered his head thank you but
Sparks is now my song of the summer yeah
good choice what an amazing day this was
you are the best boss a chicken could
have thank you so
much I'm so happy to hear
that
yeah I'm glad I'm glad you like the set
so much that you ordered it I'm so hyy
for
Merch and Sparks yeah definitely song I
I'm so glad you're listening to it on
your own
will thank you it means a lot to me
thank you for supporting me very sweet
of
you well I hope you like the shiny
tangent tell me tell me if you what
about your job next time your shiny
Hunter job thank
you
Al Kuman Ben Wilson than hav child than
soon Alexander John M thank you for the
pinky happy birthday K oh there's
something in Russian
[Music]
here
translate russan to
English thank you for making our days
Bri n
okay that sounds so cool Russian
language sounds so
interesting thank
youen J Powers magnos b
b thank you for the pink
[Music]
super
for electric nobody artist DS D slim
Shadow d d Alex L Ms ma ma
Ms
T thank you T
why do I add son to you thank you for
the red super chat k i it's your
birthday so why does it feel like I'm
the one on wrapping presents it always
be like that right with uh whole life
birthdays it's always like we are giving
presents to
you well we are we all just want to
celebrate our own birthdays by giving
you know the that merchandise and that
stuff we present to ourselves as well
you know being able to create something
that people will get for themselves and
then kind of leaving a footprint in
everyone's lives being in everyone's
homes H in some way it's really cool
M uh yeah spikes is such a bu the new
merge looks amazing too I'm already
thinking of where I'm going to put that
tapestry in my house isn't it dope the
tapestry and the whole day have fun
streams too you're the best boss ever
thank you
than you're the best employee ever yeah
it's so dark this time um so I think it
will look very cool especially in like
darker rooms if you have like some
people some fancy people have black
walls right oh it would look so cool on
a black wall M but not many people have
black
walls if you do though then you got I
put it on the black
wall you call me fancy thanks oh you
have a black
wall
oh time to buy black
paint it would look so
[Music]
nice where am I going to put it I
wonder although like I wonder if I
should even put up if I would put it up
I I would probably put it up in my
office I guess so that if I have like if
I have something someone come over who
doesn't know that I do H life then I can
just say yo you can't go into the office
at least it won't be in the living room
or so I got to put my YouTube play
buttons into the office as well they're
currently in the living room very
obvious obviously
displayed
yeah although people get will probably
get very suspicious and be like why
won't you let me look into your office
well you know the good thing is like I
am
very um antisocial I have a lot of
acquaintances in my city but close
friends I really only have like
five uh no four maybe 54 and they all
know what I'm doing and those are pretty
much the only people I would let into my
apartment besides my family so yeah
let's say five let's say
five good
friends maybe maybe two of them really
close and the rest is just really good
friends but I trust them and um I don't
really like bringing over people into my
apartment other than
that no nobody besides them has ever
seen my new apartment
[Music]
too sounds about right
oh yeah I think I think a handful
of one handful of friends is good enough
[Music]
the thing is though my cat
cats they don't
know that I am doing whole
life and they are walking around my
apartment
freely should I trust them you'll think
they'll dox me and they'll they'll you
know put all that info up somewhere and
be like oh she's she's in her life how
could you not let them I tried to tell
them I tried to tell them but they don't
understand they don't understand what
I'm
doing I tried to explain it to
them they look at me like I'm some kind
of weirdo I don't know why kind of
[Music]
rude no but I love my cats oh my God I
love them so much they're all I need for
happiness and love my
babies
yeah are they wrong yeah
du I by the way I cut I cut some of
chunker's uh a neck fur
today because chunkers when she cleans
herself
um
she her neck
Fair um always gets in the way can you
imagine I I don't know how to explain
this so you can imagine let's try let
let's say she tries to clean her lick
her leg or whatever no she can't reach
shut up she's not that
chubby she can't reach but but like she
tries to clean certain areas and then
her neck get neck hair is always in the
way so she's like generally always just
licking her neck hair and she's always
like
like like she she's like cck cck cck cck
cck and then she goes
like like like trying to the neck hair
is so long and she has to like go
like I can't explain I can't move enough
Cy
Papa I need to become
fruity sorry I sound like a crazy cat
lady cbrs she actually my cats really
never have hair balls which is very
surprising cuz they are long hair cats
and lose a lot of hair it's actually
quite surprising
H and even they have a great D digestion
system or I brushed them often enough
but I don't think so I think they have
crazy
digestion
now sorry I like talking about my cats
but I feel
like without showing your videos and
photos it barely gets across what I'm
trying to
say but I just love talking about my
cats cuz they're my
everything I love when you talk about
cats really
really you know you understand okay I
have a cat so I understand okay oh yeah
well
then I love my I love
[Music]
my I love
my I love this so
much so
cute they such sweethearts
oh man oh tell me guys when the Loa gets
too repetitive okay I have like two
tracks repeating themselves I hope hope
it doesn't get too repetitive let me
know if it does I can I can quickly get
something else I have a audio stock
subscription tell
me it's
good okay
noi never gets
repetitive I I want to try to have more
different songs uh for Super Chat
readings every now and then cuz for me
the the whole life Loi already gets a
bit repetitive and everyone's using that
everyone's using that
now so I came here to nap at you wait
Tanaka did you did I give you a kiss
[Music]
Tanaka thank you so
much for the for the sweet sweet message
I love you thank
[Music]
you
T Tanaka do you know that do you know
that uh gut sky where one of the members
is called Tanaka I love
Tanaka
T Ando
[Music]
I want to watch it again I think I
didn't even watch the one from the last
New Year's or did
I I think I did not
[Music]
maybe I saw it I don't
remember the lion I came here to
electronic May D
parar
Gonzalez G5 6984 534 D what kind of name
is that thank you for the
pinky happy birthday thank you so much
thank you for celebrating with me and
the girls hope you enjoyed
[Music]
it yeah
can we have a session
a that would be a fun idea for a
collaboration cool
[Music]
I asked Japanese Bros if uh like where
where I can stream legally stream
that you can't laugh for 24 hours uh
thinging that you know uh they do that
every year year once per year at the at
the very end of the year
um and uh they have it on live broadcast
on Japanese TV but like afterwards I
asked where you can watch it afterwards
and they mentioned
Hulu
yeah yeah but but hul is like the only
stupid service that I cannot subscribe
to it just doesn't exist in Australia
and that's tried to get it uh anyway for
vbn didn't didn't work ah and yeah yeah
I guess so Japanese hudu probably has
different program than
overse I I have Netflix I have Disney
plus I have
Amazon PR
whatever nowadays you got to have all of
them
ask
Callie I want to watch
[Music]
it oh yeah I remember I remember I
actually asked
Callie yeah I really didn't watch it I
asked Callie cuz she had a TV a working
TV and I didn't uh I asked her I
remember I I wanted to come over to her
place to watch it on on New Year's but
for some reason we ended up not doing
that I guess we were both busy and I was
just I think I was just streaming
but I think Ki was busy so I couldn't
watch it at her
place yeah you guys remember yeah I
wanted to watch it at her place damn it
I really missed out on a
chance ah God damn it yeah the New Year
stream yeah we did a countdown countdown
stream so
[Music]
anyway Ryan eating eating Mike
Tyson pick cucumber electric May Gold
fire Tony the ELD D un CH
rice that you guys like that don't
you PK scratch bronen d h Axel Kai D
Queen Wilder thank you for the red super
chat
oh yeah t I love you no T dot dot dot
dot I love you happy birthday that's so
sweet are you here green
Wier are you in the
chat what a what what a cute
confession I love you
[Music]
too I don't think you're here though or
you just shy now could be
both thank you for the sweet sweet
confession and your generous donation
thank you so much for the support thank
you soon my name is SAR
d k 4 3 51 2 thank you for the red super
chat what is it with these
names get a proper
name what meaning does that have huh
[Music]
nothing I want to complain about your
name
employee happy birthday K it's my
birthday too and my first super ever
best wishes love the song thank
you I I I don't understand uh people
that well who Super Chat to me on their
birthday it um confuses me a bit you
guys should be giving yourself the
money but okay thank you for being so
generous and so sweet and thinking of me
on your
birthday happy belated birthday to you
k43 512
than share the
love Yeah like you should reward
yourself as I always say buy yourself a
Gucci
bag I have everything I want in
general yeah but you could still like I
don't know book yourself a massage or a
spa day or whatever I don't
[Music]
know oh
well thank you thank you anyway m k for
fre K4 3
512 I hope your birthday was great
though I hope you got some cake and got
to celebrate and even if you couldn't I
hope that my stream was some kind of
celebration for you too thank you so
much S7 b42 D eat glass ink D shy shy
face 77 D is anim gamer D Tom Hamilton
thank you for the red super chat
Mah it says happy birthday K hope hope
today fills you with as much happiness
as you always give us thank you Tom
Hamilton very sweet of you yeah thank
you so much very thoughtful than I
appreciate the support please continue
watching my streams and supporting me
that would mean a lot to
me hey he
[Music]
than what a weird super chat
message
p a catfish named Wings CV race SM BR
ever thank you for the red super
chat mot account name says don't I know
your be is actually Fried Chicken day
but it's already T about in Jaan yeah H
it's appropriate because it's a festival
for our
star are you the real M may all your
wishes come true oh also it's a propose
cuz your love also only reciprocates
like once a year what was that what does
that what does that
mean what does that
mean I I feel like you're roasting me
because you always have some kind of
like Su at the
end you love only returns like once a
year what does that
mean why are you trying to tell
me
yeah oh well the rest of the Super Chat
is nice and also I took the day off
after my birthday so I couldn't really
do anything for
tanav uh although I feel like there's so
many cute kind of streams you could do
for tanata but oh well people like coron
Senai uh did that for me I
guess well next year I want to do
something for T about that too I want to
read you guys' wishes and then you know
you guys write write them down and I'll
Grant you wishes or whatever I'll put
them on a bamboo tree yeah I know what I
know what tanabata is about you don't
have to explain that to me but I wanted
to know how motan is is cuz he always
writes a nice Super Chat and at the end
the last sentence is always like
something something
mean I was trying to figure out what
what what's the mean part of this just
time tanata is a
Japanese holiday what i is it a holiday
it's like a like a celebration like
Christmas not as big as Christmas
but everyone in Japan knows about it on
the seventh of July
77 yeah look up T you'll find a lot of
[Music]
info
for resty
Strings fiction not thank you for the r
Super
Chat happy birthday thank you thank you
for the support thank you so much please
continue h to support me and to watch my
streams and enjoy them I hope you get
lots of joy from them and
happiness thank
you John
Smith Nores thank you for the red super
chat happy birthday Tel thank you thank
you for celebrating with
[Music]
me thank you I hope you had a great
time I no fall you always always there
supporting thank you for your loyal
support
good good chicken good
employee hoping to have you around for a
long time thank you so
much gangster of boats D why Blackwolf d
d Randy RJ d akachan d Justin Reinhard
D Frost
hell wind Skittles
Dominic D against J
drop the
m to Evan
stri once you start doubting thank you
for the red super
chat happy birthday remember kids eat
your vegetables and stream Sparks that's
right you got your priorities straight I
see
that thank you very much thank you I
hope you don't get sick of the song
though but that is the right mindset to
have are the vegetables optional yes
streaming Sparks is not optional VES veg
are
optional thank you so much for the
support once you start
doubting thank you thank you for not
doubting me I guess thanin for all the
love Co gallion also red super jet thank
you happy birthday K you're the son and
son of whole life and bring so much
light and happiness to everyone around
you have the best week you deserve it
also since I know you like questions in
your AA chats who is your favorite tales
off character
aha aha another one who didn't watch the
tales of rice stream on the previous day
Co
gallion expose
yourself ah maybe maybe you watch it
afterwards maybe you just couldn't catch
up with the archives in time that's okay
but
uh I guess I'll tell you the answer well
it it is uh probably from Tales of cilia
Miller and from T of bizer
magu those are probably my two
favorite uhhuh you would have known that
if you watched the T I stream of the
Ambassador inauguration
no then he wouldn't have had to ask that
question it's okay though it's okay okay
I love you I love you
nonetheless and it's good the the father
of asking me a question in my super chat
in my red in your red Super Chat to me
is uh I like the thought that that
definitely helps me with having some
communication and and answering a
question to
you it's a good idea I like the thought
of it but you asked the wrong question
cuz there was already an answer for that
the day
before to the usual room yeah we're
already here we're already
here yeah uh by the way speaking of
tailes off there is a tailes off
Orchestra in October in
Japan I want to go I wish I could I wish
I could
go these are the times where I wish that
I would still live in Japan because
stuff like that really mostly only
happens in
Japan
[Music]
yeah for
stuff like that I would totally go for
that if it wasn't for you know what cuz
it's still not easy to get into Japan
without a proper like longtime
Visa but yeah okay next year next year
there probably won't be a test of
Orchestra next year but any kind of like
events I shall go to next
year you care about the music but not
the sales uh
uh I I wouldn't even say that I don't
care about the SES I appreciate good
good voice acting very much I just don't
go as far as like supporting the
like
like yeah making the sales my
oi uh and like being fangirling over
them specifically a Fang girl over the
characters not over the people behind
them but um yeah music is definitely
something I enjoy very much like for
example I I went to a
[Music]
find now this is weird because I didn't
really play any Final Fantasy but I went
to a final fantasy Orchestra or
something like that what was that what
was
that I went to that before though cuz
they had it in my
city and that was really really cool I
just appreciate you know um Orchestra
and like classic music as well and
having like game
music uh life performed with a full
Orchestra is just so impressive to me
this dead worlds that might have been it
you
[Music]
maybe I mean I I like game
music uh so much that I just listen to
it sometimes for like um work like while
I'm working on something but what I
would love to see the most is a Legend
of Zelda Orchestra live
orchestra that would be
amazing doesn't have to be video game
music y y y i I've been to um you know
you know my my country is well known for
a classic music and we have this really
big uh at least in at least in inside of
Europe it's extremely well known you
have this really big um like classic
music festival that happens in the
summer each year it is known it is
known and
um
uh yeah people come there from outside
of Europe uh and
uh it
oh I I uh no not Sydney I'm I'm joking
it's not Australia it's I'm talking
about about the one in Europe in in
between Germany and all that in the
middle of there's a there's another
Australia in the middle of
Europe yeah so there's this this classic
music festival that happens each year
and I've been there before and I really
enjoyed it beautiful Opera is not my
thing
but uh you know the whole stuff without
the without the singing without the
Opera I like
that in Vienna I don't mean Vienna um
there the best one is in
southb
yeah
Sal
F
yeah angry
noises nah the best stuff is in
sbook I love to see the SB Festival oh
it's I don't know I don't even know if
they did it this year probably not but
next year how about you go check it out
it's it's not only one day it's several
[Music]
days it's a bit expensive and it's very
popular but it's worth
M and it's the perfect City for that cuz
it has a great
Ambiance yes yes yes always wanted to
see in person oh I'm happy to hear
that Sashimi y Sparks
Orchestra oh we have that we have that
one one fan in kfb one chicken who made
Orchestra versions of my a few of my you
know songs and stuff before so probably
sooner or later it's going to
happen I see it happening demo he's
probably already working on
it sash me you like my new
room you better be clipping
it the beginning of the stream I did a
whole I did a whole thing I did I did a
whole
act on it you got to you got to watch
the
archive
[Music]
y the beginning was Sublime I should use
that word thank you for telling me Oh Oh
you saw the ghost to thank you for
telling me a new word that I want to use
from now and write it on my list okay
but this this is just Sublime is that
how you pronounce it
even Sublime that sounds that sounds
[Music]
Exquisite you know now honestly by by
first f using uh Exquisite and divine
for a while it has kind of entered
my vocabulary I feel like I can use it
somewhat naturally like uh out of
nowhere now maybe we can make that
happen with
Sublime
okay Kura 112 D Pand gaming D variant K
thank you the red super chat bit late
but Happy Birthday it's never to L
everyday is a birthday every day is a
party thank you so much R Kean for
coming by and congratulating me thank
you for the support than for the red
super chat very generous
NY M NY m d the melon Chef d m VN D un
CH thank you for the
pinky happy birthday K what's your first
stream from work but could not super
from there ah you mean the the the the
the first birthday stream Where I Was
Alone more or less uhhuh I loved the
streams though and was overjoyed to see
you have so much fun you are amazing and
I'm so happy to have found you oh than
you I'm glad you found me really it is
it is fate it is
destiny that we have all found each
other thank you so much and thank you
for even watching me at
work really I appreciate that a lot even
if you cannot listen 100% and give me
100% of your attention you're still
there thinking of me and trying to
support me no matter what situation you
are in thank you
stop
as I am done with
those
yeah nice nice nice nice nice nice nice
nice nice nice nice nice nice nice you
know what's next Minecraft is next
right Minecraft Minecraft wait did I
actually
[Music]
you know what you know ah wait I did I
didn't actually read
[Music]
spikes Super Chat did I yesterday
yesterday I was like oh I want to read
it and then I opened up and then I was
like oh never mind I I W do it was that
what happened I did I didn't read
them okay no that was about that with
the collab okay I put out the collabs uh
thumbnail then was like I I want do it
after all I okay go go go go go
okay okay okay okay next is
Minecraft Minecraft it's not so many so
we should get through them like swoosh
and then it's holot talk then next after
that is holot
talk we'll make big progress today
even though I was around in the
[Music]
beginning what was I just going to do um
oh
yeah okay
so uh a Minecraft
thumbnail which one I have so many
Minecraft thumbnails there we go it
turned out so
cute I turned out so cute but the whole
stream was
like way longer than expected it turned
out to be the longest H life English
collaboration apparently I didn't think
that that that would happen I thought
that definitely there would be someone
that streamed longer than that was
someone surprisingly
not surprisingly you lost sanity GAA
also lost her
sanity man I'm sorry I put GAA for
that but it turned out so cute it's it
was so adorable I'm so proud of it we
all lost it you weaklings
[Music]
it was wor it yeah a lot of Clips came
out of
that a lot of Clips came out of that I I
I retweeted so many on Twitter as
well some of us are only humans not
phoenixes no no no no no no some of you
are only chickens not phoenixes that
explains it too though yeah
[Music]
oh yeah good died so many
times
so it was golden and
Sublime why why golden that's not a
special word
[Music]
yeah she gave up on not dying halfway
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I noticed that
she she she didn't put in an effort in
staying alive anymore she was like
it what of
us I I still think she needs to make the
the
feat I I think she needs to make it but
she probably has a different kind
of relationship with feet
and I
have it's probably already very
triggered by feet but yeah I I apologize
if that's the case but I I feel like
it's very nice to
have that on our server if she doesn't
make it I'll make
[Music]
it good is so weird about right she's
weird about it it's not like it's not
like that came out of nowhere right I
mean also she said that the the foot
thing with her birthday on the cake that
was by her viewers but the viewers told
me that was not
true I I don't know man there that's one
statement against another
statement I blame her chat for being
weird about feed okay okay I I'm sure
her chat is very weird about feed but
I'm sure that she also somehow started
it and kind of plays around with it she
did it on her own well there we
[Laughter]
go uh I was a dead by daylight bet
a I see there's nothing wrong with
feet
okay there's no I mean
no
yeah in general there's nothing wrong
with feet in general you can
totally make it into something wrong but
it doesn't have to be
[Music]
wrong she confirmed that the feet thing
is part of his dreams
what you mean like me saying the US your
is part of my
streams she's making it into quite a big
thing as that
true feet are very versatile
[Applause]
a shark girl naturally be fast you mean
like for example like a mermaid because
they don't have feet and but GAA has
feet she doesn't need to be to be uh
fascinated by it she has her own
feet um but I think I think my idea was
absolutely genius and I want it to be a
thing don't you agree I mean the whole
there there is so much behind that is it
has so much meaning it's such a deep
idea because the feet
represent I don't want to I don't want
to get started again but you're getting
me started the whole you know thing
about you know stepping in someone's
footsteps and and the big footstep
footsteps that the senis have left
behind uh yeah yeah and that that we
will probably never be able to fail but
you know they they left this huge
something
and I I Frank it's just a very yeah it's
very wholesome I think it's very
wholesome and it has I mean GAA has some
great connection with it too and as she
says it's a big part of her stream as
well so so I
mean there's nothing wrong with
that on glasses but
feet oh well uh I'll ask her again at
some point GA are you ever planning to
make that that those footsteps if not
then I will make it for
you for you for you
good p d fix D thank you for the red
super
chat T I'm glad to see that you got
yourself a small break after your
birthday oh yeah yeah yeah I did I did
that's when I came back finally finally
can see you and G have fun in Minecraft
it's going to be a great day tomorrow
thank you yeah I'm honestly so glad that
me and GAA got like like a a longer
stream where we could we're also able to
talk a bit more uh
calmly um because of previous collabs uh
for example the supermarket one and the
the teaching ones those were all fun but
they were kind of short and they were
really really like planned out um I mean
the teacher one was planned out and the
supermarket one wasn't really something
to have a conversation at um so being
able to create something together with
good on talking about all kinds of
things was really really
[Music]
nice why is there no chat
repl I didn't edit anything it should is
there still
no let me see if it got turned off by
YouTube for some stupid
reason I didn't
know uh live streams
[Music]
uh where do I say that again
edit
comments
no where do I say the ah should be here
probably
live
[Music]
everything
uh why is everything in Japanese
a chat replay is turned
on I see life oh
oh let me see oh yeah it is there oh
what the
hell it is there it's there yeah yeah
yeah it's it is there uh but guys if you
ever noticed something like that on my
streams let me know
[Music]
oh
a ah I just saw that the
Yakaz yaku Yakuza stream did
get like the song did get
recognized and flaged but I no no
nothing against no no
Bonks but no more monetization I see I
see
monetization is dead
cusa
CA yeah it's okay it's okay it's totally
fine no problem at all really that
happens
sometimes all right all right all right
uh yeah I was saying though uh if it
happens that the chat if something is
weird Al there was also a time I think
where comments often were like
automatically turned off after the
stream like like they wouldn't be they
didn't get through uh and that was just
YouTube doing weird things if you guys
ever noticed that just Spam me on
Twitter about it and I'll fix it uh I
often don't notice cuz I don't check my
streams that often after they're uh
finished I usually do that very rarely
uh tell me about it and back in today
when I still had a little out of
accidents during my
streams uh I often had to edit something
out and that would disable the chat but
it hasn't happened for a long time so if
you ever see the chat turned off you got
to be like oop something is wrong and
then notify me
okay
yeah no I don't have any accidents
anymore I had didn't have to edit a
stream of mine for months now
yeah all right uh so
yeah
Felix thank you so much g d P1 m
d night night so let's keep D let me try
to read a few more non pinkies and non
Reds now cuz it's a bit faster now I got
painted and my boss granted me a feather
to revive from the void oh yeah oh yeah
oh yeah that was when I revived you huh
this is what it means to be a member of
kfb thanks bus for making this little
fluffy chicken feel like a beautiful
Phoenix if only just for a moment a
you're sweetie you're welcome I'm glad I
noticed because I it's easy for me to
miss miss out on stuff like that uh but
yeah uh that was uh I'm glad I noticed
let me know let me know something like
that happens again just Spam me again
spam spam
me if someone gets banned accidentally
by a mod uh and they can't undo it let
me know
mhm I like d Flor joh
mr76 thank you for the red super
chat oh I think that's a German speaking
person
it
says sorry I'm a little late but I saw
your birthday streams and they were
great thank
you as all your streams are they always
bright nowadays the merch looks awesome
and I really love spikes thank you BL be
the best on
[Music]
our sorry I have a have some troubles to
breathe uh a little bit a little bit a
little bit thank you thank you thank you
for the support
um I'm glad you're enjoying spikes and
the merchandise both of them I think I
agree are really really
great and I hope you can wait until it
arrives it will take a while but please
be patient it will be worth it
hopefully yeah I'll try to oh you are
here I love it when you guys are
here feels like such a
coincident yeah
thank you for being here what a loyal
big fat
chicken chunky cute
fluffy thank you for the red super chat
and the very very sweet kind support you
give
[Music]
me did I give did I give the guy a kiss
old set 176
now I
did I always I I always probably give
them kisses at the beginning and then I
always forget at the end if I already
gave them a kiss short time memory Ty te
thank you for the red super
chat just just some hearts uh heart
emojis thank you
though thank you T I hope you enjoyed
the
collaboration thank you for the support
you kind generous crazy
[Music]
chicken T is a good good chicken
sometimes has to be led to the usual
rooms usual room but doesn't learn
anything out of it anyway keeps on
sending super chats without any words so
I I've given up on you you are a lost
cause but I still love
you angel V D no baby D Doom Slayer
Dragon d Ty dang dang orra thank you
Andra dang Ty Dang d 67 dang night D MH
D Ryan sagala dang gar Legend Stone D
white black wolf D thank you for the red
[Music]
silver redistribute the kisses to the Wi
in
class y'all are working at kfp so why
aren't you all working
class just passing by to say we are not
pushed to talk about feed by Ohi this is
our own thing blinging oh this person is
a is a Chum
Bud oh
n n so wow they are quite honest though
he admits that the this is the the
shrimps the chambad speaking
oh very
honest but wait blink
blink uh
sauce
[Music]
sauce not sure uh what what do I trust
what do I
[Music]
believe did you see what G did yeah I
saw
afterwards she is such a me
Lord Santiago Martin thank you for the
pinky late birthday Super Chat happy
birthday to you thank you I'm very happy
with your new song these last two months
have been very productive for me I'm
working very hard to make my dreams come
true oh and you always there even my
breaks or in the background while I work
you're still my number one thank you I
hope I hope you can make your dreams
come true but if you're working hard
towards them I am 100% sure that it will
come true
hard work will eventually eventually
always be rewarded no matter how long it
takes even even if you at a point where
you feel like wow uh this it's
it's not worth it but at some point it
will yeah it will be rewarded I'm sure
of
it I wish you the best of
luck PUD Li king Godzilla 95
I spent the last two days being unable
to get sparks out of my head it is such
a good
song brainwash
successful thank you for working so hard
you really make each day Bri I have some
chicken love thank you for this sweet
message than
soon
kak baby little Leo thank you for the
red uh Pinky the pinky hey plus I'm
going to need to get my
VX soon but I'm definitely afraid of
needles oh dear would it be all right to
ask for some words of encouragement for
you oh needles huh well first of all
don't look at
it don't look at it look look to the
other side
uh uh I'm sure it will be over
immediately
and I'm sure it doesn't hurt that much I
yeah I guess I guess needles are scary H
and I never I haven't really thought
of
needles that
much
h i mean that kind of stuff scares me a
tiny
bit Yeah but I understand how people
have a big big fear of needles M oh man
well
well it seems like you have an
appointment so you have to go so just
get it over with it will be over like in
a moment
[Music]
don't worry it will be fine you will be
fine die jble it will be worth it don't
worry die
D embrace the
asako
yeah and also you know the the doctors
uh who do that stuff they're also very
nice if you tell them if you tell them
you're scared they'll they'll also be
like it's all good that open but that
will give you a feel feeling of relief
as
well dead LC
Smo King the Ty K King the
Ty kryptox 8536
Shan duke duke duke duke
duke do CQ
funtion thank you the the Chum's
completely lost it nice I'm happy to
hear
[Laughter]
that H Chum's thanking me for that feet
tangent oh I'm so proud of myself
Phoenix
cs105 D Duke JB thank you for red super
CH from Norway so
cool so happy to see like a random rare
countries in my super
[Music]
chats I saw oh you're here I did see it
from the other side I
did I watched the clips and uh also her
archive cuz I was really curious what
she
did yeah she's she's a meme Lord as I've
said oh
man uh so yeah Duke Charlesburg says oh
yeah Havey the birthday Sparks
absolutely slaps too thank you for your
fantastic work thank you for supporting
me and listening to my music thank you
so much you know um watching my streams
is one thing but also watch uh listening
to my music is another thing that is
very important to me
and I appreciate everyone who goes that
far um you know I I I know it's like
generally not such a big effort and all
that but um there's people who just you
know that's totally fine too people who
just very
superficially watch people's streams and
don't follow much what they do in the
background don't don't look at the
Twitter and whatever you guys are
missing out on some stuff yeah but
that's okay too like if if that's the
amount of involvement you want to have
that's cool that's cool but I appreciate
everyone who wants to be a a little bit
more uh deeper in this rabbit hole and
in this fandom and whatever it
[Music]
is I feel attacked
no not trying to attack you twit just
not my thing uh that's okay that's okay
I I understand you don't have to use it
though but if you want to not miss out
on stuff you can just make an account
and follow uh whoever you want to
follow because I do think uh there's a
lot of stuff that you miss out on on
Twitter I also see one thing like the
doomi stuff I I I want to put it on my
YouTube community board because uh you
see that's something that you would only
know if you watch my streams closely
without missing out missing anything and
you follow the Twitter otherwise you
would not know that I am on doam me uh
and that I will be having a meet and
greet yeah no I've been thinking about
uh making a community post about that I
just forgot about about it until now I
will do it maybe after the stream
yeah nice sour of great fan that is true
too yeah for me it's a definitely some
uh uh a method of interacting with
everyone uh seeing what my fans do and
getting their opinion and their feedback
about my streams as
well so s I'm jealous sad us erors but
yo if you follow my Twitter then you saw
my retweet today that um you know
there's a meeting great but I also am
doing uh I'm participating in one like
podcast style of thingy and then later
on I'll be having like a little kok
concert with original songs and some
covers as well and that will both of
those will be live streamed on Twitch so
you can watch
it I don't know if they'll be live
streaming the direct
footage
or some camera that shows the stage that
will be
interesting but it will be live streamed
so you guys can participate and support
me over there uh in the chat I would
appreciate that I know there's a lot of
guys that cannot come to the convention
for obvious reasons but uh
yeah how does the meeting grade work
that only works in reality if you're
going to do me I will be on the screen
in the room and we can have a one-on-one
talk but you have to sign up for it once
again follow my Twitter look at my
Twitter for
information yo yeah well thank you duke
jbg J
reinard
greatly ISAC Abraham technically
Scottish
[Music]
me how why are you writing that in the
Super
Chat
AR r
[Music]
r crispy chicken
d d Viv Viv D whiskey ninja d
you guys wake up wake up wake up Tech
Scottish very
cat a catfish Nam drinks
C thank you for the
red there you
are good day hot wings how are you wi
the C days here's for you brought your R
RI R uh song Sparks you did well working
with K it was Exquisite and divine sent
me to the cosmos Among the Stars than
you you are also Exquisite and divine
and Sublime
j y I love you thank you so much great
accent thank
you did it sound
Australian just got in where is this
this is the usual room
welcome I wanted to show you guys for
once because you guys have been
underestimating uh the power of me and
the usual room too much and it's been
getting on my nerves that people are
like oh yeah send me to the usual room
whatever I want to go to the usual room
so I was like this I'm going
to show you what it looks like and then
you don't want to go in there anymore
cuz it's scary as
hell thanks for the membership welcome I
definitely fear it now very well very
well perfect still usual room isn't that
bad okay hokam you have now earned
yourself a life FL subscription of the
usual
room you have angered me you have
angered
[Music]
me I'm so sick and tired of
it so sick and tired that my arms have
separated themselves from my body
[Music]
you will never never get out of the
usual
room Mo
[Music]
D I hope that is worth
it yes I want be oh you will be trust
[Music]
me doesn't mean that you're getting
away lifelong means lifelong but I
didn't tell you how that life
ends thanks for the
membership you are now an egg
[Music]
hook on you make me
sad I'm waiting for your apology
letter I'm waiting for
it you can still fix
it you can still fix your words and your
actions I am open for it I a nice Tal
yeah
yeah yeah w't that take a year to run
you can send it on Twitter just like
screenshot your freaking memo pad you
know how those Twitter people do it when
they have a long thing to say when
they're being dramatic and like I am so
sorry I apologize this is the reason why
I did it I will never do it again I
regret my actions I reflect on my
actions just use your goddamn notepad
thank you for the
membership um
unbelievable
[Music]
okay pain
SFI
t
no no it's just the usual
[Music]
room God oh my
God uh J you are at least one of the few
people who are who are
not rebelling at least I hope
so thank you g for being a good chicken
I love you thank you you give me
hope thank
you
p
[Music]
chrisa a catfish named t s
D looking for the top d juming
d oh slime blocks at the bottom oh thank
you
[Music]
B bear King thank you for the red super
chat hi the other I was feeling
absolutely awful new job no sleep 2hour
commute Etc but I saw that you had
released your new song Sparks I listened
to it and it made me feel so much better
I started crying in
relief what I just wanted to say thank
you so
much bear
[Music]
King oh B King
F do you can do
it f I hope that reaches you
but life life be a sometimes very
often
actually but you'll get through it
you're
strong very strong chunky chicken
bear we believe in you I hope it reaches
you and but I you seem not so happy
about the new job but I want to
congratulate on the new
job good luck with it I wish you all the
best and I'm glad that my new song was
was able to cheer you up what the hell
oh thank
you I dog retired
her Mis Bishop X
Marin D Patrick CH
[Music]
flap
eat
harine I Am timing you
out no smuggling of food
[Music]
whatsoever uh uh uh not
happening
no
no he's timed out he can't even answer
I'm serious about this I'm
serious it is impos how do you want to
smuggle food for that portal huh it's
impossible you can't it's a waste of
food it will get lost in the universe
[Music]
next
up we got we reach talk super chats
incredible those are also not so
many oh talk with God
guys I hope that was fun for you guys I
hope you guys learn something new in
[Music]
the it's been a while since then uh but
I think it was a decent episode I don't
I don't know I don't know anymore it was
a long h no actually yeah I remember me
being uh not in my best
condition the fact she prefers winter
yeah that Bamboozled me so so it
offended me it triggered
me yeah but I love mat Senai she's
[Music]
fun and she also seems to have a quite
the connection with her fans it's really
whome to see
that yeah I mean I have witer too but
huh a lot of follow-up questions yeah
yeah yeah but also a lot of uh Ki not
knowing how the hell to translate
[Music]
things did a good job at showing the
side of mat people don't see as much
yeah I think so too I think
mat because of her famous Clips is one
of the most
[Music]
misunderstood uh whole L
members or like not misunderstood but
like people have a very different image
of her a lot of people have a Mis
misrepresented I guess so
[Music]
yeah I'm I'm glad we did that
ah yeah on Twitter you guys you guys oh
my
god when I retweet some slightly lude
things on my Twitter which is doesn't
happen that often and isn't even that
bad you guys go crazy like K oh my God
NSFW come
on but
God you know I follow mat Senpai
obviously when you follow mat
Senpai I think you have to rethink your
statements about
me your your
[Music]
complaints oh my
God yeah yeah I'm top right that's right
yep yeah pretty yeah yeah yeah
yeah
yeah I mean I mean I personally think
it's it's it's cool I mean I feel bit
embarrassed seeing some stuff there but
um I think generally like whatever twe
retweet or like whatever you want on
your Twitter uh H I see no problem no
issue with that but you guys you guys
over some of some of you guys overreact
from the uh things I retweet sometimes
very rarely it barely ever
[Laughter]
happens I I am too embarrassed to
retweet something really YY anyway or
even like something really
Yi i' i' I've seen I've I've seen some
some some weird stuff on my timeline
like
t t weird stuff on my timeline sometimes
or not even T maybe sometimes I'm a or
or taco to or or taco or what yeah yeah
yeah have seen some stuff but I I can't
I can't I can't I can't even I can't
even like
it me feel a bit weird uh
the thing is that you know you would
think that comes from Duma it doesn't
even come from Duma there's this one
person I follow might even be here no
maybe maybe not
[Music]
yet my our dear uh akasi akasi
bag likes literally everything with no
[Music]
hesitation
yo and that uh often uh shows itself on
my
timeline yeah cultured yes yes cultured
indeed y
yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah oh that's cute
[Music]
oh that's
cute son through uh the most
recent fan art of mat that's cute that's
cute all right Harbo is back
uhhuh what ohy apologize for announcing
my intent to smoke food to hul from now
on I'll keep my mouth shut uh so I don't
get myself caught
stupid so uh I will put up the Holo talk
Super Chat and then go for an urgent uh
I don't I I I don't I don't I don't I
don't meeting that uh some people
apparently really think I'm going to
Idol meetings and they're like what the
hell all right
yeah y yo
be yo one second I'll be right there
[Music]
oh
oh oh
[Music]
a
no
[Music]
oh
sorry my cats are just too cute to
ignore so
[Music]
cute let me
B become real
again guys believe in me press way press
why I'm fading I'm fading help
no why
[Music]
thank
you Mama Mama Mama's here
mama mama thank you for uh coming by
thank
you happy to see you
here you
[Music]
I can't believe K is real
I try it you can touch me touch the
monitor you can touch me when you touch
the monitor I'm
[Music]
real I believe in B I believe too are
you a believe believer of BPS
feels warm yeah
right it's the worm of the
Phoenix BBS are real
yeah BBS are surprisingly
real let's read the hell talk super jets
guys thank you for thank you again for
like um keeping me company
[Music]
I'll make some spaghetti for you guys
later I'll cook for you I'll cook for
[Music]
you that background is sick do you mean
sick as in yo that's dope sick
Oh you mean sick as
in it's just crazy scary SK
sick no no no hokan doesn't get
food no no
[Music]
no
B dope b super
lit that's sick Bro all right Patrick
Mr
[Music]
SK
for # Hol yay yay py thank you for
supporting
Hol maybe I should put taii as one of
the
sponsors thank you so much
M tyy who do you want to see the most on
on Hol talk let me
know desperately trying to make
conversation okay
Hine out Ed out
[Music]
yep no
mercy j wesby d h S7 b45 42
Dan studio Rob
[Music]
Dan Google translate be like
was my first life she let me down the
rabbit hole see there's
that I'm happy to hear that yeah she did
that with a lot of people that's great I
hope you enjoyed the holot
[Music]
talk how do I translate rabbit hole
not
[Music]
no num num you know
num num
[Music]
oh we found the word a Japanese word to
call it
they call it like like uh in Japanese
they call it like
swamp uh Marsh wetland
like Shrek you know shre Shrek
swamp they don't say pickle hole
no they say Shrek hole get out of my
swamp and here come the green eyes oh oh
ohle was the first
one thank you for the membership welcome
all the green I oh
no I thank you for the red super chat
than
you yeah boy
o if I'm not wrong I'm reading your name
for the first time so thank you welcome
I guess you're a m fan gen
generally I am glad you have found your
way to H talk thank you for supporting
it please keep on continue to support
mat s and possible me as well thank you
so
much
F yeah it always brings in new people
that's nice I don't know if they stay
but they at least come for whole talk
that's cool Heavens play tra the D
although for example Coco saai is fans
uh like kind of like some of them stayed
and uh uh supported me which was really
sweet they are very very supportive very
respectful they they they are
quite Strunk t
[Music]
she trained them
well I need to find out what her trick
was because you guys are still like very
much uh resisting to my
methods I don't know what to do about
it
I can can can we just act as if the
usual room is scary come on I prepared
all of this for a reason can can can you
guys please play
along please
come on I beg
you
yo please thank
you scared oh it's okay oh you know what
if you act if you act scared I I'll give
you a
hug I'll give you a little hug here come
on go come here scared chickens oh it's
okay don't worry about it I'm M here if
you act if you behave then you won't
have to spend any time in
[Music]
here oh oh There are the scared chickens
oh those chickens that makes so much
sense cuz you're
[Music]
chickens I'm spooped
yo mom picked me up I'm scared okay okay
okay okay come here baby come
a it's okay die
night Ka
night boxing
fear mom pick me up and say okay okay
okay okay another one a hugs please
there you
go it
is I'm terrified oh no mama yes yes yes
come here
okay it's okay but don't underestimate
the usual room otherwise I'll destroy
you and your life and everything around
you I love
you hav play tra7
[Music]
I love you I love
you James
MC sat
Satan a
go
d uh being mainstream isn't always good
when you try to appeal to everyone you
lose what makes you unique and
interesting in the first place ah is
that when we when when uh yeah that must
have been when when mat s talked about
wanting whole life to become mainstream
I thought that was
interesting I can see how many people
would not want whole life to become that
mainstream
uh hm it is it is uh I think something
where opinions separate uh it would be I
think
people um would be very proud whole life
fans would be very proud if if you know
whole life grows bigger and bigger it is
exciting um but yeah the bigger you
become the less you can be so direct and
close with your viewership and that is
something that I would definitely
miss we are already like I mean I I see
us is already quite mainstream in in in
in our community I guess that's not
mainstream but I feel like in the anime
SL Japan lovers
Community I think whole life is
extremely mainstream right membership
body thank you for the
membership
yeah I guess that's not mainstream but
like in in our in our world we are
mainstream
yeah she's calling us weebs
no no no I'm not one who frows throws
around that word that
easily uh cuz I I I don't think that
just because you like Japan or you like
anime I don't think that makes you a wee
automatically I don't like it when
people use the word just so
simply um yeah cuz I think there's a
very specific type of person that that
uh is supposed to be described as a
weep I also I also don't think it's
something that should be used as an
insult I think it's just kind of
specific type of person but also not not
a bad kind of person thank you for the
[Music]
membership yeah the meaning has changed
has
it
maybe M I'm not sure about that it's
just people using it
wrongly yeah I guess because it gets
thrown away so so easily that's why it
kind of changed thank you for the
membership
wow it's like simp I guess so in some
way in some way
yeah uh do you I have
D thanks so much for all you do to
connect thean fans of the Japan members
thanks so much for having M on today
oh I was so nervous I was so
nervous about having Raa watching my
stream I was like oh he's going to for
sure be translating in the chat like
I've noticed that before not even Raa
but like other people have been
translating um
holot talk while like like in the chat
in the live chat and I'm like like okay
translating to other language like
Spanish or whatever okay I get that but
some people are translating while we're
talking in Japanese they're Translating
that to English already and I mean I
guess thanks for the help but it makes
me like feel a bit useless like what am
I here for and yeah they're kind of
challenging me who's the quicker uh
translator it makes me feel like they're
just like oh she's not fast enough God
damn it she's she's so slow I can't even
type
faster yeah um it's still cool I guess
because they might be able no are they
are they able to get more into detail in
their chat messages I don't I don't
necessarily think
so I think
my my uh spoken
translation gets into more detail than
the typed out translation cuz they have
a limit of letters and while they're
typing we already continue talking and
so on I think they do skip some things
and stuff
um so in any other stream but holot talk
I think those translations are extremely
useful and dope and I think
um that they help a lot for many
viewers uh but for H talk it uh confuses
me
yeah when it's for other languages then
that's that makes sense but when they
translate to English I'm like what
what what am I doing I mean keep on
continuing to do it if you want to no
[Music]
problem if you want to sure
maybe it's a habit you think they can't
help but to
translate stop translating my English to
[Music]
English we're there for backup should
you forget what you said oh I don't
think that's helpful because the chat
goes so fast that I have absolutely no
way of picking up those comments in the
first place um the translation
comments I don't have like you can uh
apparently put some kind of filter on
your YouTube chat to see it uh see
certain people's comments
only uh but yeah I don't I don't have
that in U but but but but but but
sometimes
sometimes sometimes I ask uh the chat
and H talk like yo what did I just talk
about and they do answer and that helps
but the the the translations are not
helpful in that matter
yeah there's like browser extensions
right I never used them before you don't
read comic of course I do but in whole
talk first of all I'm very focused on
you know translating and listening I'm
already so focused on that stuff that I
barely read the comments in h talk
generally I do but in h talk not so much
unless I ask H talk the viewers a
question yeah
[Music]
Destiny Child Global no I have not
checked it out no no I I only saw like
people pointing out some characters to
me all what are those stupid
translations
[Music]
there yeah there's a lot to do in h talk
yeah yeah it's always very stressful for
me but um it's my thing that's why I
want to continue doing it I got to get
through all of
them until then I cannot rest I cannot
stop
just look at that now no you can
translate
that if you
wna wait where are
we H we're in the usual room isn't that
obvious doesn't it look like you I mean
I think that's pretty obvious but yeah I
understand your
confusion yep ah b b Bend no it's just I
I didn't I I didn't I
I didn't I that was just because uh I I
I had no wait that was
a
uh I
[Music]
[Laughter]
sh looking for
the captain be PE
D and Ty D we're done with H dog super
[Music]
J
huh one day when I'm on Hol talk you may
ask me that question but I am not the
one being interviewed
here I am not obligated to answer that
question
[Music]
okay next uh we already read the members
only super chats
right I read them during the members
only
right so next is the Super Chat reading
super what
iing yeah okay oh my God we're so close
to the
end and it's only 900 p.m. here
[Music]
nice we are very close to to the
end what the hell am I
doing deselect that God damn it
EXO oh
my
[Music]
ow I'm I'm copying some that were in
between the members
only stream for some reason I guess
because I did I open the
stream reservation while I was doing the
members only by the way that members
only stream was so much fun we played
fall guys together with kfb only and
that was so much fun cuz I could play
with like 60 people at once 60 kfb
members at once that was so
cool that was a blast that was the first
time I enjoyed playing Fall
Guys which is kind of sad but
you want to play again I
do one of my favorite members only you
guys really cheered me up too because I
was really
down before the the gaming portion thank
you
guys I can always count on you
[Music]
I love you
guys I love
[Music]
you I love
you I love you
no
you also
um I promise I'll read more more um more
more um um brain I'll read more non Reds
and non pinks uh messages again uh once
all of this is
over
oh but I I'll try to slowly read more
and
more thank you for the membership
yes now reading Super Chat reading super
chats thank
you never ending Big
Love Super Chat
Inception yeah it's an Inception I I
like how I'm still using this thumbnail
ever since the beginning but I like this
thumbnail and I'm not I'm too lazy to
make new thumbnails for Super Chat
readings every time but I think it's a
cute thumbnail isn't
[Music]
it yeah it's cute right it works right
back then I was still pretty bad with
making thumbnails but this one was
[Music]
cute one day maybe I'll make a new one
but for now I I like using the same
one don't change it please all right I
think it also like if I use the same one
it's same one same same thumbnail it's
always very easy to recognize that uh
where the uh thumbnail
uh brain hello brain brain stop it stop
[Music]
farting yes it gives off graphic design
is my passion but excuse me that but
that's an
insult think get
[Music]
V yeah yum yum the brain freeze comments
made me want to eat ice cream I've got
some really yummy ice cream in my
[Music]
fridge maybe
later
okay y me myself let's go
200 200 super
JS
to the green wer D the green oh is that
a rain that is a rainbow where do I
start at the top or the
bottom I think at the bottom I couldn't
think of something cool in time so here
are a couple of birthday presents but
first I didn't say this yesterday
because I couldn't watch the whole
stream life but I watched the V after
and caught you trash talking my
o oh try oh try talking
myself claiming she doesn't deserve all
the support we give her not cool she's a
very special person in many ways and I
won't stand for you sling her like
that all are you here Queen Wilder
that's cute now that's now that that's
out of the way my two gifts are first of
all the gift that keeps on giving a
tangent wow
nice I was happy about
tangents and secondly a possible option
to say it to the Schmucks who sent red
supers with no message
oh for the possible tangent hopefully no
one has asked this before or I'm going
to look real dumb if you had to assign
one of the seven deadly sins to yourself
and each of your gen mates with what sin
would match each of them overlapping is
okay interesting I would need the seven
seven deadly sins in front of me in
order to uh know which ones they are
okay
um let's
see so there's a
gluttony wait where were there
too maybe the above what the hell
fornication
lust greed
sorrow rra
Slough vein glow sorry what's that
boasting
Pride
interesting well
mukashi
[Music]
uh uh can I look at them in
German okay so uh H right even in German
they're using such difficult words I
don't really understand them
[Laughter]
that uh
oh I don't want to insult anyone though
cuz they are all kind of
insulting uh can I just give one to
myself
m i I would give to myself
[Music]
probably wait why is this different than
the order is
[Music]
different what what the hell is that
uh no
[Music]
wait
um sorry my
brain is too
slow uh uh
uh
probably German Pro probably
unfortunately probably probably
n but what is which one is that in
English is it ever
ever rice great and
eny a yeah
is I have this red Wikipedia thing in
front of me I there it is yeah yeah I
guess so no but not but what is this
like GRE oh no wait okay huh yeah I
guess so
[Music]
probably yeah not last because I'm not
B left for sake
yo I'm ver than
then yeah it's not
last I am the okay you canot press X as
much as you want but you I am
the least lustful person in whole
life
yeah whatever I don't
care I don't care
you don't have any
[Music]
idea now
whatever mhm whatever whatever whatever
whatever whatever whatever
whatever I put you all in the user room
all of
you yeahuh yeahuh
yeahuh no I'm not saying I'm the most
say so I'm saying I'm the most the least
last full last yeah the least lustful
one being say so and that I wouldn't
necessarily say it's the same
thing no no shut up of course you're not
yeah whatever okay so continue for your
consideration to use next time someone
sends you a red super chat with no
message no message what a cat and in
case you don't know cat is a real insult
not a misspelling of Chad it means a man
who behaves dishonorably especially
towards a woman not never heard of that
before Oh but that sounds so similar to
one a
[Music]
chat I don't like
it ah green W I don't like
it they have to learn they have to
understand it's not okay so I'll just
put them into the usual
[Music]
room I like it never heard of it wow a
lot of people have never heard of
it computer a design okay a bunch of
people say
that the IT people the IT department is
speaking
out it's an old word it's very British
oh now I want to use it
[Music]
I'm 20th century not a whole
doll okay what a
cat no I don't think I'm use it but but
thank you for putting some F into it and
trying to help you know I appreciate
that very much you are great I love you
thank you so much for the beautiful rain
rainbow for your generosity for all your
kind words and for your loyal
support thank you you are an honorary
chicken you're amazing thank
you Lara Guero D Felix thank you for the
red super
chat T I'm going to miss your stream
tonight again I'll see you in arive
we've been missing out on each other a
lot haven't we saying that prepare to
see the past me a few times to H saying
that prepar to see pass me a few times
today disclaimer whatever past Felix
said has nothing to do with the present
fix do not use it to send present Felix
to the use that is not something you can
just ask of me no no no that doesn't
work you canot say to P pass me every
every you is to pass you at some point
that doesn't excuse your actions but
okay let's see what you got to say later
on let's see what you are trying to get
out of
and your past you is already warning me
about your future you which you then
claim to be the next past you but if you
past you already knew that the Future
Past you will do some and say some
then why not stop the future past
year
huh understand I think that makes
perfect
sense that
[Music]
give
me Shen will you thank you Shen Cy thank
you for the
pinky a little cash to send your phone
to the phone doctor a oh oh that was was
that the day with the
iPhone when my iPhone was being a little
ah well thankfully it didn't have
to go to the phone doctor thankfully it
was just like I don't know I went to the
I went I went to the Apple
Store I explained my story and then they
attached it to their loading cable and
then it worked and I feel so stupid but
I I tried connecting two different
loading cables one of them really new
one and two different adapters and also
uh different uh electricity plugs and
then I also tried to do it for the bin
adapter and without the bin adapter and
I also tried connecting it with with USB
to my PC but none of that
worked and then I came back home with
the new with the new adapters that I
bought at the Apple store and then it
worked I feel so stupid I don't want to
be like that kind of person who goes to
some it sh calls on it person and then
they like turn the PC back on off and on
and and then it works I don't want to be
that kind of stupid person and then it
would always be like oh but it didn't
that didn't work when I tried
it oh feel so
stupid it's so
[Music]
weird it's
yeah I I tried
everything I don't know and that was
stupid
[Music]
phone well thank you
guys it happens even to nurses and
doctors you mean you mean the patients
go to them and then like give them a
simple fix or you mean the nurses and
the doctors actually have stuff like oh
turn the machine back off and on again
and then it
breaks oh well phones are genuinely
glitchy as heck
oh
yeah my my smartphone is doing really
well
generally I've had it
for two or three years and I've dropped
it so many times and the the screen
never broke on until now I'm so proud of
it I always laugh at people with a
broken
screen my iPhone also doesn't have a
broken screen and I see most people who
have an iPhone with a broken
screen none of my phones ever have a
broken
screen yeah but my smartphone i' I yeah
because my my my iPhone I don't I don't
I don't carry it around and all that but
my smartphone I carried around all the
time and I I drop it a lot of times on
on really hard surfaces and the and
yeah but it never
breaks
this I don't even have a a temper glass
thing on top of it or anything I don't
even have a plastic case in the back
nothing it's completely
naked completely
naked actually when I first got the
phone I put on uh I put on uh uh one of
those pan glass uh
thingies yeah loot phone I know right I
put I put one of those uh really strong
glass thingies on top of the screen cuz
I was really scared about the phone and
it was really expensive and back then I
was broke as so I didn't want it to
break and I put it on there and then a
few days later I dropped it and the
glass broke and
uh yeah ever since then I never put on a
new glass on it and I dropped it a
million times but the screen never broke
so yeah so I'm like I guess I'm I guess
I'm fine without
one yeah screen
protector that is called luck
no no
that's called
skill
oh my phone is just bu
different luck skill skilled luck I
pulled all my stats and luck to get all
those Crites Critical Hits let's
go h
ran stri d d r d unknown D Deo
D oh god oh this
is this is when you guys sent the lyrics
to the Rick R and to Sparks and the
super
chats you guys you're so
funny yeah laser guy D de d unkown
d de D Soul D
7il it's weird cuz it goes like Never
Going To Give You Up lying down on the
floor late night and you don't know
don't know don't know what to do never
going to let you down never going to run
around desert you going to never going
to make you cry had to tell what's wrong
what's right if yes or no don't know
don't know what to do never going to say
goodbye never going to tell tell a lie
and hurt you oh my god we've we've known
each other for so long your heart's been
aching but you're too shy to say it oh
and then suddenly there's a message here
guys did you know there's a cool new
song by Tak called Sparks you should
check it out and keeps on going like
that
[Music]
Soom ROM
Sky Magic
R GD D random SP D is still continuing
you D GD
fcy enter the
chat
bot FY
again putting in the full lyrics of the
song R
SP G where's heart Challenger huh
G CH i d i d randoms by
D oh oh with the pinky I'll sing that
for you cuz you wrote the lyrics here in
the
[Music]
pinky let's go of the past tonight
choose the Future on You Define even
when the Flames burn to Bright you're
alive From the Ashes you
rise I think that was actually too
L actually let's go off the tonight
choose the Future on You Define even
when the Flames burn too bright you
alive From the Ashes your
eyes that should be close to
it my favorite L from Spar challeng and
streamer random SP thank you for the
pinky Sky D looking for the top D Alo
penguin ubu
Unown oh
oh oh still writing lyrics everyone
still writing lyrics at this point it's
been 100 super chats by now Rand D Elvis
D green
D oh my God now they're
singing they're singing Rick R kfb
version We No strangers to lunch you're
good with sauce on top of rice I love
that version Dr ghost Jelly D and P one
the gaming D and S come here thank you
for the red super
chatra sorry I probably need to go to
bed now good night oh
no is that right when I started the
stream after all that
delay sorry
s
sorry I up I'm so
sorry thank you for waiting sorry for
wasting your time SOA
Brandon J Santiago
Gomez M thank you for the red super
chat hi tangel I finally caught up to
birthday archives Sparks is my favorite
song of yours yet really where where is
the where's the
hackin the hook is that how you say it
in English too where's the catch where
where's the cat that's that's it that's
it I I thought of it before you guys
told
me where's the cat Spar is my favorite
song of yours yet but the biggest
surprise was how a low voice
cat I thought people were joking when
they called your mama but that was
divine Exquisite M
son where did the tun go where did the
tun
go you're only d did it these days M son
I'm happy about it I don't dislike
it uhhuh only sweet mess was that
because of my birthday and after my
birthday you're going to be soon
[Music]
again haven't seen Moto son in the chat
today though
probably sleeping or working thank you
for the
support low voice changes
Tunes I guess
so thank you motan I'm glad you enjoyed
it so much I'm glad you uh say it's your
favorite song out of my original songs
if I had to choose I
I couldn't really CH I couldn't really
choose but I
might I I do feel a special connection
to Heart
Challenger uh I mean to hotor and Sparks
as well but I don't know heart chall
just makes me happy the song
itself I love H
chall I like them all though no I can't
choose like picking a favorite kid yeah
it's
impossible they have very different
Vibes
[Music]
yeah m
H but that just means that I love them
all so much and I'm very happy with what
I created until
[Music]
now
Dominic uh is that the
same Ruby of midgard D pet dang Pon
gaming D de SLE D recent few month moms
have been real bad but started watching
you a few weeks ago and it definitely
has helped me genuinely smile thank you
for being you and helping me get into
the other girls too oh just a few weeks
ago a
newcomer thank you I'm glad that you
feel better and you're getting some
happiness from the streams that's what
we are here for welcome welcome welcome
enjoy your time here g d d big
[Music]
papa papa go Papa
go deep tone
DT is Papa Korean
translator oh my God there's so many
Korean super
chats what is this one honeybee
honey
honey it's a Korean Korean currency but
writes in Japanese
[Music]
so in
is s of f this
is English
[Music]
keep best yeah okay okay keep D
best the just it was just in the chat
colel Sanders
alas definitely not a g g gav gav dang
Danny Johnson dang fgh Magic Fish dang
pet dang
[Music]
green thank you attention all kfb staff
we have a code orange this is not a
drill should I should I announce
this attention C fre stuff we have a
cold orange this is not a drill K is
hungry for chicken all staff please
immediately Evacuate the restaurant if
Escape isn't impossible apply emergency
hot sauce to your chest wings and Fs
once again this is not a
Dr apply emergency hot SAU because I
don't like spicy things huh a smart oh I
didn't know you do has some kind of like
strategy there
[Music]
no God damn
it
a we're adapting you
are rubs pet
on what was what was happening what did
I say when you sent that Super Chat did
I really say I want to eat
chicken oh my God I'm so sorry I was
talking about vegan
chicken of
course oh my God I just saw you in the
chat so I ReRe your super chat you you
proposed to your girlfriend V fgh Magic
Fish congratulations I guess she
accepted
huh you didn't write if she accepted but
I'm guessing she did wow
oh how did you how did you in the
Universal Studios or or was that another
story that's so
cool
nice happy
[Music]
but see how see how wholesome the chat
is oh I can't help
but feel feel some deadness in my face
[Music]
a
a oh well let's check my Discord direct
messages I got some d m what is this ah
not D
messo
[Music]
oh
okay hi
chunkers
[Music]
bab my chunkers is here chunkers
hello H the cut that I gave her under
her chin looks stupid I need to make it
better
H get into the
basket get into the robot
chunkers get into the robot
Jun get into the robot
get into it get into the robot I love
you okay she she walked
[Music]
away get into the r junk get into the r
nothing oh no she's just curling around
on the floor she's stretching
I love you I love you baby you're cute
you're so cute I'll give you a snack
afterwards okay baby green Wilder again
thank you for the funny Super Chat makes
my day thank you Z2
D coil D eating Mike
Tyson probably a box Tangi milk simply
stalling dang ly carb dang ly carb dang
love
D Alo D take the blue pill 16
D
[Music]
wait
oh uh
this Korean fan wrote uh something in
German to me but it looks like really
good German like like legit German not
even like Google translated
German s them on clip
[Music]
this is uh
I I've been told that in in Korea they
uploaded a clip of me saying something
in Korean and I I pronounced it so well
that they call me
Kim you know Kim is a really a common
last name and uh or the first name last
name last name right in Korea so they
call me that now I'm glad they don't
call me fried chicken or something this
is so much
better
W I'm Korean now no no no
no that's a nice name to
have let's go
L Lou Jun MK
Galaxia bye Chun haris d d love 67 D
surf thank you for the pinky I don't
wear slippers or aprons but here's a
pinky to cover the difference oh thank
you you're doing amazing work and SP is
my favorite original song from you yet
oh from do and onwards I hope more of
your dreams continue to come true n
thank you I hope so
too it's a serame
[Music]
right I am I am very excited to hear
people say they like spikes so much that
really makes me feel like uh it was
worth trying toing you thank you very
much for the support and uh I understand
if you don't want slippers aprons that's
okay too thank you for supporting me
nonetheless d kak l D Valentine ninja
nebula thank you for the you here after
all was that just a joke in the
beginning where you said you have to go
to bed now we still here maybe it was
not a joke and you just forced yourself
to stay awake and watch my
streams thank you so for the r Super
Chat it just says okay dot dot dot dot I
wonder what I
said I don't
know strong yeah
ah I don't know what I said
then do you guys remember oh Dad L what
happened talking yeah probably me
talking about eating
watermelon H oh is that when I said I
was going to I ate his
family and his friends
maybe thank you s don't worry you have
family here kfb is your family now I'm
your mama
Rachel ah spreading the
scenes could be
[Music]
anything it hasn't been long since I saw
Kiana's video but I always enjoy it
thank you for your interesting
interesting videos and I wish you all
the best in the future from one of the
countless fans who supporting you thank
you so happy thank
[Music]
you uh do I read this in Japanese muga
mug probably
[Music]
thank you for the red super
chat question how much wood would a wood
chuck chuck if a wood cheuck wood cheuck
would you know what that reminds me of
for some
reason of the world of Worldcraft stream
when we were running around those wood
chers desperately looking for a a
quest like 12 like 20 wow you guys are
taking this really serious
L I'll say it a few times for you Dave
cuz I think you want me to say
some uh T Twisters all right thanks for
the membership welcome how much wood
would a wood check chck if a wood check
wood check wood how much wood would a
wood Chu cheuck if a wood cheuck wood
cheuck wood how much wood would aood ah
how much wood would a wood cheuck chuck
if a wood check wood cheuck wood how
much wood would a wood
ah how much wood would a wood chuck
chuck if a wood chuck wood chuck wood
how much wood would a woodchuck chuck if
a woodchuck wood chuck wood how much
wood would a woodchuck chuck if a
woodchuck wood Chu wood how much wood
would a wood Chu chuck if a woodchuck
wood chuck wood how much wood would a
wood chuck chuck if a wood chuck wood
chuck
wood all right that's
enough and that one is not that
difficult thank you for giving me an
easy one
Dave thank
you special Kyle
D and lty
D flame CH Al Captain jelly thank you
for the red super
chat it just says big and once again I
don't know what what the context of this
is but thank
you for the support Captain
jelly are you here in the chat
[Music]
too did you know any Russian word and
what it means I only know spba
[Music]
and uh B
bka uh wait is that really what was that
mean
again what
that it's a grandma okay Ah that's me
what what what what that's that uh
that's that the one that says
[Laughter]
that's any Danish no unfortunately I
don't know
[Music]
any babush shut up
okay d
d de again d uh Johnny
another and this one
translate Studio H oh wait this name
also transl stud
[Music]
HUD
super Benjamin and
dang mistress d
1989 can't think of a better name thank
you for the pinky oh my God we almost
done with this super chats guys after
the shadow tournament are you still in
the mood for more mass collabs
competitive Pokmon Elder Scrolls Online
I'm aware that Fire Emblem uh Heroes has
an event mode in a few weeks that works
well for collapse or do you prefer oops
limit
ah I'm not sure if I call Shadow the
shadow tournament and mascap but
generally
yes I always prefer like smaller collabs
of like maximum free people
because it's just easier to have a
conversation but bigger collabs bigger
events are always like a lot of fun too
um depends on the game I
guess uh like like uh the time when amus
was extremely popular in the H life uh
there were some great collaborations
there um and
a lot of fun some
fights well I I want to for example do
the Mario Kart tournament that is where
I will be uh holding a mass
collab yeah
so yeah yeah Ian and ID and now we have
uh we have Iris so now we are 12 people
that is
perfection couldn't be more
perfect yeah so I got to get to that I'm
going to get to that ASAP before before
we get some one of us either ID Oran
gets even more members and then I'll
I'll have the struggle of like now
I have to leave someone behind and feel
bad about it I don't want that to happen
I have to do it while we're still 12
yeah it's my mission
[Music]
I'm super super busy now though like the
the coming weeks are also filling up
with Tales of arice stuff as well
there's like one week where I even have
two Tales of arise things going on and
then H talk as well and it's crazy crazy
crazy I'm really excited about it but
it's it makes me so busy that I don't
really have time for anything
else and next one next week next one is
next week uh that one is uh
collaboration as I've mentioned before
Miss Ambassador yeah I got to do my job
H got to do my
job yeah I'm I'm really excited for it
I'm very honored I I I wouldn't mind
having a full week of tales of AR
rise raccoon is is D looking for the top
D Domino Paris 21 thank you for the
pinky thank you for the support I
appreciate it no text with it next time
write something please F memory D I miss
cing live streams but the vs are still
awesome and Sparks keeps me motivated
during work good luck reading for the
rest of the birthday super chats I'm
already
done stream spikes CH thank you Dum d
ja Guzman T Daisy thank you for the red
super chat because someone thought I
wouldn't who me who challenged you
Daisy uh maybe maybe Daisy maybe your
biggest Challenger is I was going to say
yourself but the perfect thing to say is
heart
Challenger heart Challenger challenged
you to send red super jets huh I'm sorry
about that that was not heart
Challenger's intention does this makes
no sense do it makes no sense stream
heart
Challenger help squat
than wait I I didn't give you a kiss
[Music]
Dy p p
love
[Music]
conqueror don't Li me I didn't Li
you that that was that was a kiss shut
up a rare rare I hate the word rare I
can't say
it so half Squad says my birthday is
tomorrow too okay this is already
belated but happy birthday
I love the work you put into into Bridge
Japan and Ian audiences like with your
concert watchong and H talk oh yeah the
concert watchong are always lots of fun
I hope we will see you in your own
concert soon I hope so
too thank you thank you very much I feel
like to in order to have a proper
concert and it's got to be in frd so no
no matter if I label a Koka dream as a
concert it just doesn't feel right to me
so M I hope I hope I hope what that
comes true one
day and that was the last Super J from
the super
[Applause]
reading oh my
God now Sparks to our endurance we can
skip thank you guys everyone who
supported that anyway wait a
second I called up oh
yeah I mean not completely but my the
ones that I have saved in the EXO file
oh
yeah yep that EXO file bye-bye the ones
where I saved
everything in order just to make sure it
doesn't
disappear oh my
God yakaza in
Minecraft oh my God how many are there
for yakaza let's
see it's only 1 p.m. here I think I I
can still read it one I stream tomorrow
I stream at
what what
time
[Music]
um who tells me first you guys or the
schedule 5:00 p.m. my time thank you 500
p.m.
sip I was planning on drawing uh before
that a little bit
so yeah but still still then P let's see
how many Yakuza super chats we
[Music]
have copy
I am from
theu I am from the
Yakuza
Yakuza most dangerous Yakuza there
is Yakuza there we go okay uh up
until
[Music]
here I don't
yes okay that is how
[Music]
many oh about about 200
M let's
[Music]
go are you guys um up for one more Super
Chat reading
will you guys stay with me for a little
bit
longer
yeah
yeah oh my God manager son sent me
a uh
uh a chicken related Japanese tongue
breaker
[Music]
the chickens ate a
crocodile two chickens in the
garden ate a
crocodile what what are those chickens
made out of they were just built
differently chicken strong what what do
we learn from that
guys you can totally fight against the
crocodile I mean maybe the crocodile was
already dead then it wasn't probably
wasn't much of a challenge
um yeah actually never mind maybe the
maybe uh a certain Phoenix killed the
crocodile for you guys and roasted it so
you guys can eat it that sounds more
realistic I killed myself I highly doubt
that n Chum buts and Cy crisp here that
doesn't make you a crocodile but it
makes you a strong chicken chalk
yeah shark and chicken is sharken
chicken it's still tough skin though are
you trying
to are you trying to boast that you with
your chicken beak were able to eat
through a crocodile skin okay I'll give
you that I guess that's I I'll give you
that wow wow I'm so proud of
[Laughter]
you
oh uh
yeah yeah
yeah my neck oh yeah yeah during the
Minecraft stream I was in quite some
pain but uh today it's not that bad than
yesterday I just I don't know for some
reason I
had
uh some pain that was probably caused by
bad potion but by the way I've been
um I i' even though my neck like
generally after that uh
incident has not been able able to move
much to begin with uh recently I mean
it's been able to move much more but I
have been cracking my neck way way way
way way less than before the
incident
and I yes I know I shouldn't crack it at
all blah blah blah blah blah but I made
I made progress okay and uh I think if
free um you know in uh uh uh improve uh
other things like my chair and maybe get
a memory foam bed topper uh stuff like
that then we will uh
continue uh to uh improve and then and
then one day yeah yeah I can't suddenly
out of nowhere cuz when I am in pain you
[Music]
know don't say shut up
yeah yeah it doesn't come out of nowhere
but yeah yeah we I'm working on can you
can you praise me for on don't be
like stop doing this and
that no
[Music]
excus should I do a neck
workout make get a buff
neck like am
[Music]
oh my God I'm dizzy I'm dizzy that made
me
dizzy want gu
[Music]
muscle thank
you swoll
neck thank
you are you guys going crazy because of
the screens in the back do they bother
you if if it if it if it makes you if it
makes you go crazy actually I guess and
then it's
working I feel like they're kind of
like in like in Rhythm of the
music it's soing
really
really it's doing its intended job
nice since when get did you get this new
room since today I introduced it in the
beginning of the
stream okay let's read the Super Chat
let me get the
thumbnail this was a very long stream
but when I say I'm going to finish a
game in a stream no matter how long it
takes I finish it
yes
okay hle 1375 D
me
m they're
singing spes again and promoting Sparks
in the super chats again you guys you
guys are amazing
you guys might not listen to me that
often but when it comes to streaming
Sparks and you guys are so
suppored I love you
g
forever o thank you for the red super
chat o kfp f
machine thank you so
much
sh thank you thank you for your
generosity than from the bottom of my
heart motan thank you for the pinky D KY
makes 100% more sense when you realize
Kiana learned management from watching
Michael Scot on the office that's not
where I learned it she doesn't want to
scare us but she wants to she wants us
to be terrified of how much we love
her interesting Theory
uh I love Michael Scott but I did not
learn management from Michael Scott oh
by the way update on Brook 99 I've been
trying to watch it and the thing I have
a problem all in all it's okay it's
watchable but the main character the
main
dude triggers me I dislike him very
much s Ona he annoys me
yeah Jake
Peralta he annoys me like he's annoying
in a way that's like really
annoying like for example Michael Scott
is like annoying in a funny way and in a
lovable
way but that character Jake perela the
way they write
him he pisses me up he grows on you
really I've been wondering maybe it gets
better later on
I want to give it a
chance that's kind of his fan yeah he
annoys
me
uh he's like a a jerk he's a
jerk uh his attitude pisses me
[Music]
off is like a dragon must start at
one no I started at like a dragon I
started at Yak H wait do you mean my my
my my streams or uh Yakuza games in
general if you mean my streams then yes
start at one yes
yes but but the first stream is in from
November and I had a bad PC really bad
PC it was really bad uh it gets better
from part two
it gets much better from part two it was
super scuffed in the first
stream yeah uh void
City yeah the first stream was a
sponsored stream from
Sega and but then afterwards I played it
privately privately as in I played it on
stream privately yeah yeah uh but I
think it's a fun series if you want to
watch some more K
streams go
ahead thank
you thank you for the for the pinky I
have this ear warm thing stuck song
syndrome that sometimes there's a song
playing in my head when I wake up and
today when I woke up my head was playing
Sparks what a wonderful way to start a
day stream spikes yeah that's one earb
you don't want to get out of here head
right get out of your head life is only
when you make
it no don't get out of your
head boohoo 72 for plain water Danish
and seix danish and peton danish and
Felix sty thank you for the red super
chat did you have fun today in yaka I
just moved to a new city
o h and going to get up extra early
wait a second there we go get up going
to get up extra early and so I'll see
you in archive as usual the illustration
nail be did for Sparks has the most
blessed bo bo I've ever seen yeah it
does great
boyb I love naom bead's art
mhm and his designs too he sent me quite
a few um ideas for the outfit for Sparks
and I I could barely
choose they were all so cool I also like
the design he did for uh vbe although
I'm guessing that vbe had a lot of
choice and like uh input in that uh but
also like his design for V's like T TT
RPG character and other stuff like I I
love it do you still have them I have
them but I'm not sure if I I mean I
guess it would be my decision but I
would want to ask naon bead as well if
he would be fine with me showing it on
stream um the other designs it's
interesting it was so hard to make a
choice they all look so
good recognized by the eyes yeah yeah he
has a very distinctive
style actually uh hooka Papa was like
really happy when he saw that nail beat
is making the art for that because he
said he really likes naon beat's art and
naon beat was happy to hear
that cuz na beat loves hook
Papa
ti
ti po Papa good taste na beat good taste
artist
T T
oh very much T very much titty as well
yes yes
titties I'm sorry I'm sorry the word
makes me think of
it so anyway uh congratulations on
moving on to a new city by the way cuz
uh that that that is
so exhausting I can imagine I hope it
went well and yeah thank you for
watching my archives and supporting
always feelings thank you soon I magic D
rise off for thank you for the pinky ask
and you shall receive picking duck is
mainly prized for its crispy skins the
Skins are sliced off with a bit of meat
and served in wraps with spring onion
cucumber and sauce oh most meat are not
eaten or used in a side dish like a stir
F oh I didn't
[Music]
know oh yeah yummy yeah I saw it on the
plate and I was like like I didn't I
realize that you eat it with those sides
of like spring onion and stuff but it
looked very accurate besides the shba
Shuba hat that got me in quite some
trouble uh but uh yeah uh oh thank you
for the explanation very curious to eat
it now I wonder if I can get eat if I
can get good pcking duck in my
city I want I just finished watching a
sh clip of her talking about her hat on
your
plate I am still
confused by the fact that you know after
all these reports that you guys have
written to her up until now about
various kind of
things that are much worse than me
having a miniature hat of her on my
plate she gets bothered by that and
completely also ignores the accident
she just looks at the hat and she's like
now this is what you'll get in jail for
and but I have a good uh defense cuz I I
wrote her immediately that this hat is
obviously too small for her for for it
to be her hat so I didn't steal anything
in case that's what you're trying to
claim and
uh
uh and yeah
uh she didn't believe it no she did she
believed it in Discord she was like oh
yeah I guess
so it was just some you know Recreation
of someone made also and then she asked
me like to to for me to send her the the
image so she can use it in her stream
because it's cute so like I guess she
has no problem with it after
all oh man let's see if that HS up in
court you guys better support me in
court
building a case I need my lawyer can I
have a lawyer can my lawyer be am or Ena
Ena Ena would probably or or cie
actually cie would just be like I I'll
kill you if you put my bird in
jail okay I'm
Invincible I don't care
whatever I'm
invincible and the
LI you for the p my dearest oi I don't
know why I have why but I have the urge
to stream Sparks all day that makes
sense the beats are awesome and the
lyrics are super motivational M it's a
song you can listen to everywhere It
just fits you should sing it on stream
someday much
love I guess that was ironic cuz on the
day before I sang it for 2
hours thank
[Music]
you thank you for the pinky hi K since
you liked Fire Emblem have you father
about playing the new I feel like I read
that during during the stream the new
dis yeah 6 it's also tactics RPG and has
a free official Whole Life DLC oh yeah I
think I saw that when it was announced
with VF p and fubuki characters and
voices that is dope yeah that is
a reason for me
to uh play it
yeah yeah I mentioned it before that I
kind of I I was I've been interested in
that game for years now but I never
tried it until now I do want to try it
at some point I don't know if it would
be on stream but privately
definitely thank you for the red super
[Music]
chat
Petri thank you for the pinky thank you
for planning a Holo Ian and I did Mario
Kart tournament and now with a new Ian
cool that that's a perfect
12 R roster ro ro roster I've been
waiting for this ever since the Japan
race I'm so grateful uh to your hard
work and gift for fun ideas good luck in
Gods speed thank you I yeah I need that
Gods speed I know that is the kind of a
different meaning but I need to be at
Gods speet during the Mario Kart
tournament imagine me being the last
one in my own
tournament no that's not going to happen
there there must be a few girls who will
wor than me in Mario Kart yeah maybe
Callie that must yeah yeah yeah yeah I'm
sure of
it it will be all the steering off okay
I I'll
practice looking for
the thank you for the red oh two red
super chats actually almost one uh after
another one says all my homies hate Kuma
you K and this was not even at
the ending but I guess you already knew
what was going to
happen and then the other one says uh
damn T pit back at it again with the
white
man
ah yeah ah that was really helpful the
white man no but
K what
bastard
unbelievable Dave thank you I'm glad you
enjoyed the Yakuza stream
apparently even even though it was
partially very
painful but it seems like you like y I'm
glad I play the game that you enjoy
that's always the best M thank you so
much for the support unfortunately it's
over now but I hope you'll still watch
my streams and support other series as
well thank you MFC
[Music]
P
again
R oh flush Jets I'm skipping those thank
God AR are you guys wake up wake up wake
up we're almost
done the shocked
Emoji ding ding ding ding ding
and Bell
[Music]
K the one and only sound you want to
hear in the morning to wake you
up
K am I
right kak d take the dog thank you for
the pinky oh no
[Music]
hey baby it's been a while sorry I
missed your birthday I was out on
adventure hope you have been doing well
to make up for it I can take you on a
trip where there's butterflies and bees
kisses ki's cheek you don't just get to
kiss my cheek what the hell is wrong
with you I reject the trip as
well byebye Jake I'm not a do person I'm
a cat person anyway r d p gaming D Dave
thank you for the
pinky thank you K CH oh that's when Kio
appeared again yeah yeah yeah I I feel
your love for the for
Yakuza thank you for supporting dangan I
hope you enjoyed it not a good username
dangan Rand D PP if you buy everything
at once in the
rest oh yeah I knew that I knew
that yeah yeah yeah I was I was doing
that uh anyway that's why I got so
drunk not a good username 360 D Dave D
kak R
dfaa 2385 D thanks for the
pinky I just curious but could you use
different thumbnails for Super Chat
readings I lose track of the readings
and like I like when you use f out for
thumbnails
oh we talked about that just the moment
moment
ago uh moment I mean a few minutes ago
no
no no
sorry for all the other ones yeah but
also
yeah um I feel like actually all of them
being the same makes it actually kind of
easier
to uh to like you know follow the Super
Chat readings but but but but but
normally I mean recently because of the
birthday stream there have been having
so many Super Chat reading only streams
but normally I just read them after the
stream and they don't need their own
stream and their own thumbnail anyway so
I don't think you that that issue ever
really is much of an
issue I don't really have Super Chat
only reading streams that often unless
there's just a huge event stream or
whatever
or if I really uh uh didn't read them
for a long time but normally normally it
doesn't happen put the date on the
[Music]
thumbnail I don't think that
even I I don't see how that I don't see
that I don't think that's that
necessary sorry I'm sorry but
no oh
[Music]
no sorry sorry M
ar oh wait Rafa I didn't read that one
thank you for the pinky Rafa good day
Tel if you want to grind fast you should
look for the invest vagab Bon sujon
defeating him G gives you an insane
amount of XP he's in theal
Dungeon is that the one where that you
get at the end and I didn't go
into he's in that one and another one
that's a different thing
oh oh I see okay that's is like datan is
a word for a
conversation second floor hold oh well
we finished the game already but thank
you for the uh advice we were fine
levelwise
surprisingly H I'm I was so relieved
that we were able to do everything first
try except that one time when we were
drunk wanted to root for you now that
you're in the last grinding section SK
go did you ever play again no what is
that
spark
then patri
r kak got 51
D how freaking legendary that you got
majima to get the kill this will now go
into one of the most epic moments in all
life
history ah yeah that was pretty good
huh I guess for fans of Yakuza that just
fits very well because of previous
stories I
suppose no I know Oki but he said
ok I wonder if he just had a brain
freeze there it was very
fitting that's why you guys kept on
asking for me to use
majima Michael Maple Leaf
B Tony Tony
buled D R2 D Arizona anime fan T thank
you Jackson FB d I can only watch in
short burth at work but every second his
wife would keep doing what you do thank
you c d d Pikachu D the real Boulder D C
said
d p congrats on getting for this
wonderful game best of luck in the rest
and save your tears for the end thank
you Joy
Shak
saop I really appreciate you playing
RPGs like these I just b a copy which I
otherwise wouldn't have if not for your
stream oh looking forward to your arise
streams thank you thank you so
much me too me too Cola man D looking
for the top D random
d guda
p oh oh those are flush chats um
get and we have only like 80 80 super
chats left guys not a good username 360
D Ty D pet d kak d DK Jackson FB D the
great Billy means thank you for the
pinky K sent masawa to suplex
City what is that that must be a meme
again I was using a move that was called
something like German sulex something
something but what is suplex City
[Music]
a wrestling meme
ah WWE
reference you guys know anything
huh Jackson FB thank you for the pinky
ra K oh man I did didn't I oh that that
dude was so so easy to wreck though what
the hell that was way too easy but I
guess yeah it makes sense I'm glad that
they didn't make him like super strong H
because it did it wouldn't have made
much sense you know he always let other
people fight for him and uh he used to
sit in a wheelchair and stuff like it
would be so weird if he was like the
strongest boss of the game
ever although I thought it was a bit
lame that
tendo was so
manageable in comparison to when we were
fighting versus uh Saima and
maima yeah that's the usual room welcome
to the stream welcome to the usual room
I was too op I mean some of you guys
said I had really good RNG yeah I was
lucky apparently yeah you did get very
good RNG oh
uh I guess
so he did not God Hand you like at all
ah once though right once and what
happened
nothing broken in a clear example of how
the entire compeition was made in 9
months
oh turns to knock him
out the instant kill missed quite a few
times it failed yeah didn't
it no we don't do raids here
[Music]
sorry didn't expect you to destroy the
last two bosses like you did at
H you only got godan two times and only
one did kill
you a wow okay
I mean killed one character huh this
room this room I will not use it that
often cuz it gives people probably a
wrong impression a wrong image of
takanashi
kiar but it's fun every once in a
[Music]
while I must have been I must have
killed Eddie or
someone Eddie was Eddie carried so hard
in the whole
game that's the right image no no
no no my dentist has
that that one that
one oh man the darts are the
darts man anytime
[Music]
na thank you for the pinky K is going to
put him back in the wheelchair one way
or another no wait that's so sad he no
no no spoiler but
no tacos burritos Rand s Jacob
47 Jeremy H thank you for the red super
CH picking duck fun thank you I can't
sorry I inhaled uh spit um I wanted to
mention this the game was great but
there was one thing that I was honestly
I just didn't understand that they that
they missed out on that opportunity
probably on purpose but I just don't get
it they should
have had pcking duck at the end
even him with someone or him alone just
because uh each of F but they should
have had picking
duck because like throughout the whole
game you were about to eat picking
duck would you never get
to I feel like yeah for conclusion for
like you know in the
end the duck was alive yeah man I feel
like just
for to to to round it up nicely they
should have been picking duck m
goal of the next game it was the goal of
this game too though like a pck ah
[Music]
uh so thank you Jeremy huh
uh I'm still mad about that picking duck
but thank
you games are heart thank you also for
red super chat I told you you that this
game was a wild ride glad you got to
experience it it was definitely a wild
ride so wild that my mom for example she
she said that you know she likes
watching my streams and all but Yakuza
it's just not her
thing I guess it's just
[Music]
I told it I told
him what's what's your what's your
Defence
[Music]
he's he's
quiet he's flustered he's probably
embarrassed too
[Music]
now for
his excuses he likes Tak all right okay
I didn't see anything I'll just I'll
just say didn't see
anything back to topic H so yeah my mom
actually uh didn't like it and it must
be uh kind of offputting I guess for
some people like or confusing because
just for me like I expected the game to
be very serious and scary but then I go
into the game and I was first of all I
was really confused about the the way
how this game is so so not
serious um and in the beginning I wasn't
sure if that's like really the the whole
mood of the game if that is a general
thing or if that's like just a few jugs
in between and that's it but it turned
out to be the whole yeah thing of the
game so that was very confusing for
me but but I liked it in the end I
really liked it I got used to it once I
I understood yeah okay that's how it's
supposed to
be it's really funny
M but my mom probably didn't watch it
from the start and just like tuned in
every every once in a while like
randomly and was like what the hell is
going on with those 40 50 year old men
in diapers uh what's going
on isn't this a game about Yakuza and
then she like probably closed the Stream
oh well well well game so hard thank you
I am glad that you were able to watch me
playing it and that you enjoyed it and
that you were there supporting me thank
you D FL PL thank you for the pinky so
so this was when the ending music ending
ending music was playing I guess thank
you we staying until the end very strong
lollipop d peten d k d smash card thanks
for the pinky D the pinking duck will
eat in honor of K finishing yaku at
seven is real thank you for the streams
thank you for
watching yeah I should really eat some
pcking duck in celebration of finishing
that game I'm really curious to how how
it tastes now
Dr ghost jelly un D thank you for the
pinky it was a pleasure to stick with
you to the end thank you
you
chickens are just so strong and loyal
thank you you guys are
amazing in in such extremely long
streams I know I am torturing you guys
as well
[Music]
but I hope you guys had some fun oh now
we are ready to go on new Journeys new
adventures oh
strong enough to beat up a COC I'm not
sure of that you guys have to show me
that it was one of my fav play of yours
a thank
you I did have a lot of genuine fun with
it no uh yeah did I read
that kak thanks for the pinky proud of
myi not going to lie I thought You' need
two
streams a lot of you f up glad you
finally finished this what a great game
watch every single stream thank you your
yakaza streams B brought me many great
memories but very emotional at the end
yeah I have to say I think I mentioned
it before but the this the the other the
other
death the # no spoiler got me much
more because it was so
shocking um that
one that one hit me much stronger
then the end of the
game I don't know if that was
intentional that was
painful my voice is uh getting really
dry now so I'm I'm glad we're finishing
up K induction Alita thank you for the
red super chat my favorite Idol stength
my favorite game thank you so much for
this
[Music]
oh thank
you thank
you I'm glad to be your favorite and I'm
glad I can play people's favorite games
that's really cool thank you for
watching even though like you already
played it yourself I suppose thank
you the LI take the dog
Daisy thank you for the
pinky I honestly never thought you'd end
up playing Yakuza let alone enjoying it
here's a salute to you for the wild ride
and a salute to Kao in honor of her
favorite series yeah salute hi sh
shun hi hi baby yeah I never thought
evil that I would like it and that I
would play
it a
baby that was very surprising to me too
uh but it motivates me to try more
things that I have no supposedly no
interest in what are you doing no don't
MCH the plastic you stupid chunkers
stupid stupid but cute very cute I love
you I love you I love you no no plastic
[Music]
munching
no no no come get to the
robot get into
it come
on
[Music]
coffee stupid cat I'll just continue
petting her with my
foot yum
yum R dang and dang and thanks for the
pinky W I love this this serious all the
Changers had me holding off on buying it
until you sold me on it that first oh
yeah I guess I heard that in the
beginning that uh yaku like a dragon oh
sorry I'm not moving yaku like a dragon
came with a lot of changes huh like uh
the the battle system
now
and uh so glad to see you take the ride
for yourself stop no don't eat plastic
chunkers you know the drill
glad you like the best most pure crime
boy wait who ichon can't wait for him to
be back in eight yeah he was a great
protagonist I mean I I don't know who
the hell K uh what's his first
name or his last wait what was it when I
said k i was think of kitty Coco I can't
help it I knew Kitty Coco before I knew
the other dude a
k
k yeah yeah yeah yeah I I I believe he's
great too but uh you know Ian is the
first Yak a protagonist that I that I uh
know I like him although he
um he's a quite a bit too naive for my
personal taste
I hear that kumako is not so
naive huh is that
so
yeah K is naive in other ways
oh well like not only naive but like
itan is just way too
forgiving way too
kind
like insanely
just
yeah it's sweet and all and very
likable
but yeah I guess that's just him I
didn't I didn't dis like him
yeah like after all that he went
through how can you still be so kind to
everyone and
[Music]
everything you is Ador but does not
forgive as easily
[Music]
nice that's admirable to me I mean
that's true y d i want to learn more
about Dao I'm Jun I want to learn more
about you chunkies my baby
[Music]
H what are you doing down
there thank you for the
membership oh baby
oh oh
baby she
B she doesn't like to be touched by feet
that much but that's
understandable it didn't actually hurt
n it's like
n she's not that
good
hey
Ty no now you're going through that box
where there
CH
okay
yeah CH is is trying to bamboozle me
right now
[Music]
oh no my switch my switch that was not
drunkers but uh uh damn
[Music]
it okay it's getting more and more uh
chaotic here I have to finish this
Sky rain L
926 thank you for the
[Music]
P each one will be a phoenix on this
bridge
[Music]
thank you for the
pinky oh hi smoothie smoothie and Chun
is here now
hello uh congr un finish this game was a
Pata full of so many different emotions
Joy surprise anger laughter and I've
show enjoy I've enjoyed you slowly
beating it open with your all yeah since
the sponsor stream last year it was fun
thanks thank you yeah the karal is one
of the best things to come out of
Yakuza and um a Pata
Pata thank you for the membership
[Music]
welcome by the way I have never
never hit or had a proper pinata never
that sounds like fun I've only seen it
in like
shows like all kinds of TV shows or
whatever Min same Min
gasp
[Music]
what chicken shap one one
okay Rick bck
620 thank you for the P red super CH
comment I'm finishing the game T to all
the streams we're a crazy emotional and
fun ride hell yeah
it's like the game really takes you on a
roller coaster and that was a lot of fun
a roller coaster that you do not get
sick of in both
meanings yes yes I am very happy that
you had a great time together with me
thank you
f for supporting me for for out all of
it from beginning to end thank you
[Music]
Mary P Dominic Jim Black mus James M
thank you for the red
one I'm so proud of your t w a game
indeed respect it was very very
impressive it it just uh makes me very
curious about the other games and it it
made me realize wow there's so many good
games out there that I just don't really
know of and don't really realize uh they
exist thank you thank you I'm glad you
enjoyed it
too let's go on to the next adventure
together shall
we
Richard for
[Music]
thanks for the membership
welcome yeah I was just talking about
how Pai started out way after I started
with the game uh and then finished it
before me and I was like she started at
a moment where I was already quite far
into games I was like ah I'll will
finish it before her right oh I mean
come on how would she finish it before
me uh yeah but then then my neck thing
happened and I kind of had to take a
break again
so
yeah no side quest I uh I guess she did
no side quest in
stream yeah I wonder I wonder I wonder
what like how many hours she put into
the game I would like to see
her uh she must have sh it on stream at
some point right when she saved I'm kind
of curious if anyone knows let me know
how many hours she
had
Mo thanks for the pinky thanks for the
stream I'm going to miss the serious
it's really fun to watch I'm looking
forward to the next one thank you thank
you I'm going to miss it too a little
bit H till streamed that was 50 hours
really I had a bit more but not that
much more did
I anyway yeah it will be definitely a
series that we're going to miss but
there will be new ones fun ones to come
as well there's always always something
fun that awaits
us it's time to move on I am sick of Kum
and anyway I don't want to see his
uglyest face
anymore
oh is that the Japanese riding for Kum
and the last Super Chat is
someone the last Super Chat of that
stream oh my God how the hell did you
manage to do
that the last Super Chat is a blue super
chat from Kum
someone acting as
[Music]
k a how dare you come
into my area my neighborhood ye come
here never want to see you again it says
nothing it's just a blue Super
[Music]
Chat we're done with that
yay w ah wow I really caught
up now uh the only one I have left is
from yesterday from the Minecraft stream
I will read that tomorrow with the Sims
4 super chats if there are
any oh my God we caught up two streams
to read is totally easy peasy
so e Minecraft was off no I think
Minecraft was on
but for today I turned them off yeah
yeah
yeah okay it's only 11:00 p.m. nice
only I will cook now and then tomorrow
before Sims 4 I'll be drawing and then
we'll play Sims 4 for a little bit I
don't know how long but tomorrow's goal
for Sims 4 will be raising Clara and
hopefully uh other Shenanigans and
chaos will happen as
well you just got to let it happen and
and Sims for
yeah thank you for the stream as always
no thank you for
watching Mar oh yeah marriage yeah cuz
we're only um fop what's it uh uh what's
in what's the word again in English for
that when you're not married but you're
you're uh engaged yeah we're only
engaged oh a Ving huh good idea I guess
so eloping and uh Clara raising Clara
and seeing how she looks like with the
automatic uh Sims 4
generation I don't trust
it she probably going to look really
ugly but I'm going to fix it for
[Music]
thank you guys for being so patient with
the super chats and sorry that I had to
pile them up so much in that birthday
week
[Music]
sorry thank you thank
you thank you very
[Music]
much thank you I I love your Super Chat
readings
really just spent more time of you
thank you thank you I hope you guys had
fun
today I'll see you tomorrow thank you
for spending your precious valuable time
to me for me with me you are all just
Divine and Sublime and
exite M
yeah oh CH no ch
chunkers she's like no chunkers you so
stupid you so stupid I told you
no Chun chus you
baby chus okay I have to leave I have to
stop my cats from eating
plastic you're so
stupid okay there she
goes on to the next Target
and in German we
say
Al bye-bye
[Music]
oh