foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
thank you
she's candy
oh okay okay
hello
[Music]
how is audio everyone how is audio yes
please let us know audio is good how
about you
why do the awkward potions look the same
as the water bottles it's not fake
because it's awkward
yeah exactly
I oh God
um I have a good a good message I am
officially in
um my like Mesa base so at least now I
can come from the never to the actual
nice okay
[Music]
well I went back home
oh I just left you oh wait you're
getting both yeah I have some extra bows
they're not very good though but don't
worry when I use them they'll become
good
I mean I think I can buy some
Enchantment books
oh yeah you don't have the infinity ones
in your shop fauna yeah I don't have
Infinity War wait where is uh honestown
PVP right yeah okay I'll see if I can
yeah it was that like
I have 1100 minus 200. it was that yes
I'm too scared to bring my Elijah today
so
mine's dying yes I'm walking oh wait for
it I can use my basement I forgot did it
work
s the lashes can I fix my electric FFF
sometime
anytime oh okay okay
I'll do that another time
I just wanted to confirm
I can fix anything oh
I don't need Kyla to do it for me
oh are you dying no no no no no I'm just
I'm just panicking a lot but um I think
I'm fine
what am I missing to make a potion of
healing I'm just making fancy water
bottles
all right let's see this see this book
over here yeah it may have some uh
[Music]
it's my recipe book
okay but how do you make it oh wait what
you need you need you need sparkling
melons for healing potions
[Music]
one
um
gas tears I think was it oh oh yeah I
think it is gas cheers
I'm not sure if I have any more
what the [\h__\h]
okay you must die I I'm because I'm in
the never I'm in the never I'm in
another oh remember we're gold yeah
cause I was so far away to look for a
cave to fight in for like 40 minutes
then then I lost my I was out of
fireworks and then I had to find my way
back and I was in the middle of nowhere
and now I am traversing in the Never
back to home I am safe more or less I
just forgot I was in the Never
I never found a cave though so we'll
find one together
so we can probably fight it on like in
like a desert outside you know suggested
I it would
wasn't it wait did I say that why would
I say that a good bit now I don't have
to proof because I logged out before but
but but but proof right here I said a
cave yeah okay yeah okay fireworks wait
can't we make a cave just stick down and
like dig more you know make a big hole
Yeah just dig a big hole and we call it
that's what I tried
though basically no
holes underground yeah exactly yeah I
made myself like a whole huge hole and
then I just came out in the water
oh okay but I mean that is generally I
think a good option to
wait what
the thing in the whole
taking a hole
I am now back home where is everybody
I'm at home I'm
watching Girl play with the Alchemy team
pestering fauna actually I look if I
have more arrows for I have a bunch of
gear at my snowy Village there
[Music]
okay
I go to the Village I will first check
if I have some arrows for Mommy good job
I got some eggs
though I made like a bunch of health
potions too
um
hold on I feel like I I know I use the
buttermilons making my potions sorry you
can share my portions what are we gonna
do 64 Splash bottles now oh my what do I
do I'll take some I'll take him
but what do they do wait maybe maybe
wait wait I have a lot of gold maybe I
can make more spices
can you make spicy melons
[Music]
yeah how
um
it's a business secret don't want anyone
else to get the idea
um excuse me second floor is uh off off
limits ma'am
second floor is off limits oh why is the
second floor off limits it has my
precious my precious you're my precious
my boyfriend
hold on let me let me go make some
melons shiny melons
um where is where is a melon
do you think oh I have some melons here
okay okay
[Music]
golden carrots give some extra HP too
though don't they do they yeah
okay me too isn't golden carrots like
hunger
yeah they increase their saturation
which is good
melon seeds okay good I have some I have
some sparkling melons for you wait where
you guys freckles
all right I'm official fauna I have the
Wither Skeleton skulls right yes okay
okay I just found them free okay
oh sand she'll cry over shark has where
if you have coins
not sure if I have Soul Sand
Wilson
do we need some sand we need yeah
I have so I have one day what am I doing
I should have more somewhere you're
tucking the villagers into bed what what
did you do
oh my God
they're like nighttime milk and cookie
or something
bedtime stories
okay do you have awkward potions
and it's flash water bottles
did I miss you aren't you're supposed to
make
awkward potions first
so you just have 64.
water push
it's just like water balloons wait wait
wait oh this is made of water balloons
actually
another good business idea I guess it's
good if uh someone's on fire but I have
one awkward
potion what happened to the rest of them
it's not makeup
[Music]
good at When jumping into the water she
makes an awkward splash
that's not true
okay I will try to find fauna now
or maybe we should sleep is it night
time
like in the good old Minecraft days
everybody's sleeping all right I have
one bed let's put each other in here you
go game is wrong size oh [\h__\h]
everything's so messy I'm sorry guys
sorry my house is a little loud
Splash is everybody sleeping why are you
not sleeping go to sleep yes
[Music]
they're in my pockets good luck
I came back is it too early no
wait honey
[Music]
Minecraft splash water bottle
splash water bottle why why
foreign
I saw a clip of you hating them
I just don't like the sounds they made
they are yeah very very obnoxious people
say splash potions why splash potions of
water why like I say Splat potion of
water why not what did I do
so many
can't you make things awkward and then
how do you make them in the other world
you were you used the what the the word
the little red
house
[Music]
neither what yes
Another War that's how I made
forced to make it into awkward potions
and then you add in the melons
oh okay now I have one wait is it like a
game of chance no
it is not if you have awkward potions
now
she's made one from mundane
maybe maybe we don't need potions so
much
I've made 45 years
we can use the water balloons I'm sure
it will help yeah what if what if
someone catches on fire you know you
gotta use the water balloons you know
yeah I'll be bound to happen yes yes I
think you'll be healed you will be
healed
well we need a Healer in the group that
it's that easy
who's gonna be in charge of healing huh
wait that's not how Minecraft Works wait
there is no healing character what
why is there no healing staff or so in
Minecraft
wouldn't that be cooling stuff yeah you
can like heal your friends with him okay
let me cook a medic yeah
you can throw potions on people right
the splash ones that's what I'm making
kills everyone is fauna this way
I think fauna is probably this way bye
PPP okay
ready
he's doing it she's doing the chat is it
possible to mend my things over there
still
yes
wait two cameras
oh oh we're fast demanding I wanted some
in my life I don't have to do it right
now you know girl there's two kidney
stands
this is fast can you take me to the oh
really okay
don't die I want to
you're doing great though you're doing
great
it's a loop now how do I not get looped
where do I go I'm ready
what does Monday do
I don't think
I raised it to the max
I'm sorry
um hello it gives you encouragement
[Music]
what the [\h__\h]
don't worry about it
I'm walking though
I think I think she's good there wasn't
even
um sorry
[Laughter]
[Music]
is this guy like immune to anything
specific
[Music]
just blown up here um well I have swords
then he's weak to for everyone
excellent I have one backup sword for
myself
and an ax oops and I have the bow for
moonme with some arrows oh yes please
yay you're gonna set things on fire
again we may becoming a fire bird I
apparently the Wither is weak to Smite I
do have a sword with smiles
never you've never used this machine
before it's their first time no because
every time Kyla said oh don't worry and
then she came back and I never
questioned her for you you want to mend
it right yeah does it have mending on it
and then go smack the fish
gently a fish XP
[Music]
it makes it when you get XP it will heal
it
I'm going in there upstairs enough
oh use the use the sword in here I have
good intentions
oh oh it's fine you could have left it
there oh ice back in the box now okay
why is there a storage here anyway
[Music]
um
oh
all right so yeah look this is an
invisibility potion watch this ready
oh my God where'd you go
where'd you go
let's stop
[Music]
now yeah sounds good
to the basement I made it
I know how to get there I think wait
what I'm gonna guess
where is your your FFF I'm worried
negative 1 100 and and no I see you
flying 1100 and negative 200. describe
the terrain it is
okay I follow you
oh yeah it's on this cake
oh
I miss cake
no no not bad pig
oh
[Music]
yeah
oh I need to do something after we go to
FFF
oh but I joined about that wizard could
I you can fly after us there's another
boat over there this is just a Minecraft
club right yeah right the winner oh
it's gone
are those the never portals that mind
broke you
yes oh good to know
but it wasn't my fault I built it
correctly server plug-in was outdated
yeah yeah fun I keep on telling yourself
that
okay wait where are we meeting
only if you need anything from the fish
farm maybe can you show everyone else to
where the houses
wait I'm running out of rockets does
anybody have anybody have rockets that
they could lend oh so you have to Kiara
you have to like jump up and then close
the
um oh yeah yeah it's been a while thank
you and then there's a sword you can use
in here
there's an extra bow in one of the chips
maybe my bowl would be better used with
good on
what
um
how do I wait when something doesn't
have mending how do I make it
uh no this I think my this one cannot
have mending Canon oh because
yeah it's okay I want to amend my
pickaxe though I hear the poopy puppies
pretty floppy
uh okay uh I have to have one in my hand
right
[Music]
this time all right
my cards here
Mommy
oh well this is fine I can enjoy my
fries
is it working are you using the sword
I'm using my own mending sword
I'll hurry they're hurting because
they're sweeping Edge on it oh
sweeping Edge no
she used the fish sauce okay fish sword
fish sword
oh yeah okay that's faster that's it I'm
walking
here is fish sword back thank you you're
not good
no think I think I'm good um
okay
I think I think Watson Railway needs a
little bit of a maintenance
I mean it is like almost three years old
now let's need a little bit of
checkup
catch it
[Music]
I'm feeding her
I should have just taken air tacos
just taking too long
the room till my my mom gets home wait
wanna you should be the one okay I don't
I don't know where I am
okay
[Music]
you
see that no no I can imagine though you
did not awkwardly splash
or did you maybe you did
yeah
did you did you drink that potion
what potion of course potion
okay scary
big monster in the sky
hmm and it's not good oh this turned out
it's so cute all of a sudden there's
lamps it wasn't like this back in the
day
wait lamb swear like at the entrance of
the Railway oh yeah they changed that a
little bit I was shocked too
what is this there's berries planted
here
could that have been
Rene and moonme oh bird gravy
hey bird gravy we can try to sleep oh
did you read the
the message and just kick these guys out
oh wait can I sleep get out of my mind I
think there's beds up there I remember
there's two beds upstairs
I'm in one of them
I don't see anyone here
wait where are you the fishing Jack oh
not there all right where is
the coordinates are 1100 minus 200.
it's like a building with a Red Roof
is that one
what
[Laughter]
holy moly there's so much
is this one store opening race
understand
no I'm still salty I'm I'm again and
this is less now even we're in front of
the same door and I'm still the one okay
[Music]
I'm almost there
it just has like half a long half thing
but I think I think we'll be fine you
won't wait this Village used to be dead
you revived it
wow wait can I take from the shulker box
there's a bow here
wait 30 day free trials
Mommy
happy day free trial no which my version
is there another one wait you take our
credit card before mine is gonna be
really strong against the weather so
even if you have another sword I would
recommend using this one let me look
they'll be strong I gave you arrows
after 30 days did they go into your
invent inventory will automatically
renew but you can cancel it before then
I think fauna picked up though what
arrows
um 56 arrows
no I think it's a new inventory maybe
I got them oh okay here is everyone
in the house in the big house in the
house
in the the big house
is that Red Roof wait should I take this
bow or no I'll keep this one because I
see their names
because Kiara gave it to me oh I should
take okay 30-day trial without you're
not asking for my credit card before
right and you're not going to charge you
have it right and it will automatically
charge but you can cancel anytime you
just give me a call
okay
um I must be really warm in there huh
where are you you know it's cold out
here where are you
inside let me just light up a match
should we bring back up armor phone yeah
come in because I have one set for
myself but should we have like backup
armor in case we die and lose it I don't
know how we would lose the armor we can
bring that put it in chest yeah I mean
there's not gonna be like I don't know
did the withers explosions
he explodes
oh no Mommy I gave you the wrong bow God
damn it oh
you did yeah this is the one I wanted to
give you oh yeah that's the infinity
Bowl thank you switch switch
I'm gonna take this because it's here
okay yeah everyone can take a set of
armor who's bothering me
oh what I want oh I see oh
I understand
how do we take the armor from here
right click it
I took two pairs of pants
to you
[Applause]
oh no
what does this say
s
[Music]
[Applause]
wait did everybody grab their helmet
[Music]
's name oh
wait is this is cute they have names
you're a kid
yeah
I'm throwing yours at you now
oh nice nice nice
one more try
yo thank you
who the [\h__\h] is he Oru yes now yeah yeah
you see that dirt yeah
oh
all right all right I'm gonna eat it
okay okay
hold on hold on
let me watch
oh wait can you hit me once I'm not
hungry though
oh wait hit me again
the harder you want me to shoot you what
are you doing wait no I'll I'll just see
you
um
[Music]
once more
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay I'm
gonna eat this I'm gonna eat this dirt
okay okay
[Applause]
so everyone should take at least one
stack of golden carrots you should eat
because they're restores your saturation
better your what that's what we should
so it's like how how hungry you are it
keeps you full longer
so get your dog if you don't know the
Wither effect it's the one that makes
your hearts go black and you take damage
and you can't see your health oh yeah
I always like always eat constantly eat
constantly eat your carrots okay okay
more than one yeah
okay hold on I need to get out my
potions
they have a string fire oh really
[Applause]
someone doesn't have their smart sword
everyone should have one Smite sword you
should use that one so your items might
get blown up by the withers so you can
just leave your items here and just use
the
Smite sword probably did you throw a
string at me or
[Music]
yeah probably leave it Elijah
just in case
strange
I need one more
for what I need to make a bow to repair
my bow oh
wait I have a bowl
um
isn't it like a like an unenchanted one
yeah oh please please use the power five
go in here if you want to use that I
want to use my own phone
um I'm very good at hydrating so I'm
going to go to an idol meeting I'll be
right back okay I'm ready I'm ready so
one level I am also ready
hi ladies hi I need one level
I'm gonna train with villager oh
what do they want some emeralds
emeralds though I don't remember
what do you want oh
[Music]
I think Yoshi music has to be the most
empty-headed music I've ever heard oh
are you listening to Yoshi music I am I
want Yoshi music too
da
what's in here
the basement fania do you have some
emeralds good smells
Emporium where everyone works willingly
and happily
hmm of course
unlike Phoenix 10.
what's different about Phoenix sin
well everybody works indeed happily
truthfully happily there uh-huh it's not
a lie
love love
I want to go down
he's so happy he just gets to spin all
day long why does he not let me go down
are you insulting his his co-workers
it's something
are we going to do something about this
guy punch him in the nose yeah get rid
of it
right here yeah
sword
outside he's got buddies oh I got
buddies
like you I'm I cannot
that's a pitbull it probably can't fit
through the door even he's too big big
boy I see you yeah it's shiny
oh no that rock chicken I'm going to die
huh
okay
oh yeah
I'm ready I'm ready ready I'm good yes
okay wait wait these are shared sound
effects huh I guess I'll just buy a
lantern
sure oh we should bring beds
um
big old head full of iron nothing else
what was I doing oh yeah
uh does anybody here do it wait you do
crossword puzzles don't you I do
crossword clue like yes do you have the
app
I don't know what is the app oh
dictionary.com there's all of them on
the PC
wait I don't know if I do that one oh I
was doing them on the PC no I do them on
my phone because I'm lazy I think the
phone would be better because I can do
it when I'm busy yeah
yeah really bad at him though okay great
one today I'm ready oh does everyone
have a belly
it's actually your bed I mean yes
we need to bring a bed upstairs not from
upstairs
does anyone need an extra bed I need a
bed wait do we bring one do we blow up
we need to everyone in their inventory
yes okay I require a bed please thank
you sorry
thank you sorry I'm annoying I'm sorry
I'm sorry I'm sorry no maybe I'll borrow
this bowl
[Music]
your bed
yeah bravery I have the
here's another bed sleeping nothing we
had a cookie that doesn't have any
nutritional value we have a sleepover
before we go one big situation values
what are you talking about oh you're
pushing our beds together
before ah yes
[Music]
actually a half matching pajamas with uh
Chloe without it wasn't even on purpose
but we just so happened to have the same
pajamas
that's cute oh cute
did somebody take my
cake where is it I did here you go wait
yes thank you okay can we do a checklist
yes yeah the idea of the three wither
skulls I have them in my never and my
other chest yes okay you have to bring
them yes okay I'm just keeping them
there for safety I was gonna bring
another in the chest and just place it
wherever we do it
um
does everyone have a bed yes yes yes
because everyone have at least one stack
of golden carrots yes
everyone have at least three totems of
undying yes yes yes
I'll take one more okay yes keep it in
your off hand at all times yeah everyone
have a Smite five sword yeah yes yes oh
no I only have two yes I'll take arrows
yes yes
okay we don't have Soul Sand we don't
have sauce oh okay okay let's go then
where do we go though we don't have a
location yeah we should go very far away
desert
or can you I think cave is slightly
easier well I think we could handle a
desert too are we bringing elytra's or
are we walking down we're walking we're
walking okay
which direction
away from me from please
what about source
so we should probably go through the
nether
okay I mean yeah we can take one of
those exits wherever it leads us
I tried my exit but there's like so much
Mesa around it I feel bad for doing it
in the middle oh it's true
where would be a good place
what's chatting
The bunkeroni's Underground King
just joke isn't that what bunkers are
for
protection not for fighting in hmm But
the outside world will be protected can
you vary it somewhere where I lost my
Ikea fish
but that has like it was pretty big I'm
right here but I'm not sure where that
wasn't the resource server actually back
in the day so good don't jump
[Music]
your foot let's do a backflip no do we
um
what ah I'll catch you know let's go
ready
your belly fat
hmm
don't even
know I don't know we can go to a desert
already desert can we dig up I still
don't see why we can't dig a hole we can
let's just lay down cheese Strat like I
think it'll be really easy oh yeah I
watched the video it looked really easy
if you did okay so we're gonna run
around like chickens with our heads off
okay is it we don't need all of this
stuff yeah okay
women don't scare my viewers please with
your statements oh well did you know
that or a test
did you did you know that
um never mind
you know what I say I have to confirm
with Google because I forgot the exact
amount of time that the chicken will
keep running with its head off oh I mean
is that why there's the face or phrase
all running around like a headless
chicken yeah oh
oh where are we walking we should
probably walk what about both
I think I can multitask oh oh yeah it's
a long it's a long way oh hello
creatures
yeah
how do you get here oh
oh there's more rails here what where
does it go oh there's quite a few
what how many I go left or right this
way
be free be free
might kill it it's gone no it's all how
far are we going
we're going to kill it I've never been
there before bunkeroni where's that wait
we are going to bunkeroni just
is
yeah what
there's rails to it
yes
I I I just missed you I missed you you
gonna shoot me in the head
yeah
oh I'm craving your attention oh this is
great we have High full attention I'm
like popcorn there's no need to shoot me
in the head okay
let's go back to karaoke
[Music]
never mind when do we get off yes
I don't know if you want to know is it
about the chicken it's about oh yeah
about a certain chicken a certain
chicken the mic apparently lived for 18
months after his head had been cut off
what
what apparently what
is this something what does it mean by
Liz was their brain in their stomach or
what
like how did it get nutrients how would
you define live at that point
what was
what on Earth
is it like the opposite of dead inside
is it like a rose inside but dead
outside
roaches can live forever
but this is a chicken
that's true like
um
missed the jugular vein and a clot had
prevented Mike from bleeding to death
although most of his head
[Laughter]
I guess this is sick
[Music]
and our team otherwise it will be over
too fast yeah wait there's pictures
[\h__\h] right
caught AFK in 4k
hi
bring me another card with her
oh she's back I'm back all right where
are we going this way
oh don't let the candies by the way
don't look at what oh yeah the attendees
is it up or down down down
[Music]
I almost looked down
the door behind you close up
oh yes I still have foxes is this
crony's bunker
yes yeah
I've never been here before out of
respect
oh it might be the only one
this is like a sauna but actually this
is snow this used to be my room oh it
was supposed to do snakes it's all gone
they're all gone oh there's a point on
here
chickens
I guess Fox just say book book
but we need like a golden
helmetics I Have Nothing Gold I have
something going you have your heart
oh damn
this way
okay
oh I remember this place I helped I
think
how do you use like many memories ages
ago when I asked I told them you how to
play Minecraft totem works on its own if
you have it in one of your hands
ideally The Shield hand I I've heard I
don't have a shield do I need those okay
okay just keep a totem in that hand yeah
just eat all the time okay always eat
carrots always eat carrots okay
oh I eat Berry for now though you know
these potions would be a lot better if
you could stack them
yeah yeah it's kind of bad you can't
why am I faster
oh I wasn't running but
[Applause]
is it saying
no flying cat
El fauna how are you feeling so far
good right we're not like holding you
back endlessly I'm pretty sure it was
voices not the Wither so I was thinking
it was a person making a cat noise and
thinking we're saying how cute to a
person making it
you really really is a cat
[Music]
it's a it's a cat voice actor you know
what
a cat voice actor meow yeah the guest
is a cat yeah have you heard the slow
down voice of Yoshi speaking of
like some dude going Yoshi and I just
got it up really fast
or whatever
yeah
Yoshi kick today because I'm I've had
Yoshi
pounding my ears Yoshi brain have you
girls all watched the Mario movie yet
because I have no yeah
I did wait who who has watched it
besides me
no one no one
it's so good I give it a 10 out of 10.
it was so much fun I was like smiling
and laughing yeah
big recommend go watch it now yeah I
want to see it I was asked I asked and I
was told it was what you expected it to
be and I expect it to be a minions
I forgot
oh they're still here
I know we lost you guys because you ran
so fast
it's going straight
[Music]
actually I forgot
what what well
I was behind you but I sprinted and I'm
tired
well if I eat my cookies
one second
second oh I'll run after you guys in the
moment I'll be right there
okay
are we going to where the Wither is I
don't know I don't know where we're
going but I'm just running oh
on your left wait I'm going ahead never
mind let me just what happens if you're
nice to the Wither is he nice to you no
he gives you a kiss Rose
are you supposed am I supposed to be
like this is a zombie
wait was that a Wither that beat me up
and that girl's dungeon this one is nice
did you wait for me oh yeah why are you
so sweet
I think this one let me check
nothing oh wait man wasting arrows man I
have Infinity
I have only one yeah
this is good
anyone know that shelf
the chicken cow shell yeah
Nickelodeon he's a very young very
cursed shell I like the sausage man
Mr Meaty well I guess this is the end
okay wait wait wait
oh it's kind of cramped are you thinking
of a different show is that the
claymation show
Mr meteor cursed puppets
[Music]
um
so we might want to sleep outside okay
go through the portal
oh wait were they were they puppets and
not cleaning oh they were puppies go to
sleep puppets wait what show were you
thinking of I think I forgot that it was
um oh my gosh I've I'm gonna look up a
picture no for some reason animation the
Mr meanie show I think
wait a minute my hands meaty meat is
this oh oops here's face ooh and we
can't leave our beds here oh no I just
picked it up oh you put it back down
inside your spawn I put it down
a bunny
wait don't leave me I'm looking up
things
okay yeah I'm thinking okay
why'd you do that everyone ready yes
there's a creeper oh creeper oh no oh
yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum yum
yum
yeah oh
those are nice okay
is that a temple
oh
I shot that wait there's not a parent
wait careful there's a creeper over
there oh there's a lot of creepers oh
there's another creeper yeah we told you
one today
oh wait someone's been here there's even
an in the chest here noise yeah whoa
what happened what happened to you
well then I'm gonna parrot bringing the
Twitter skulls
this is a nice open area if we need it
yeah but we should go a little further
how do you get the birds
he's green oh they want a cracker I like
cookies
foreign
[Music]
cookies but parrots can't eat chocolate
in real life so then oh makes sense I
thought I had my Legend oh is that
jungle file over there I don't know
uh where did you oh never mind see the
team team
yes
[Music]
well here don't worry we're not running
away fauna this will be a good
experience for you
maybe there could be a cave
no wrangling necessary or wrangling
ourselves
on a day-to-day basis
I'm wrangling with myself
oh
that's the cave maybe he's confusing
wrangling and mingling
and wrangling we can mangle the Wither
Mingle
are we still looking for a cave I mean
just one big open space
it was okay
I
don't know how big it is but there was a
cave
wait what's the Strat here because we're
in a wide open space
um I don't fly yeah so he might like
like fly away and destroy you know I see
I say I see oh is that the mess of mine
I'm here
here too oh my God it's everywhere maybe
it's the same one oh
it's definitely not the same one but it
could be close holy cow it's halfway to
Halloween German wait wait wait what was
that what was the Austrian flag
red white red it's red and white blue
it's red white red
[Laughter]
you and your your knowledge is
hmm
I have about his
like she has more knowledge of it than
me though I'll be honest oh I used
another continent I don't know Europe
was a continent
well there's gold here did she we could
play them here probably
again
where is everyone we got distracted by
the gold
who would have thought that Ina would be
the one to get lost in that movie or so
hey if I'm not going to like things I'm
I'm I I'm good
and yeah just run towards the light
where is she
um where are you in a coordinate 130
minus 8 300. go to the top and look down
do you see Mesa
they see Mesa I'm still on the sand I
see you stop moving stop
stop
I remember where the beds are you have
so much
[Music]
oh this bunny should get out of here
oh are we doing it here I feel bad for
real for real here out in the open why
not are you sure
right here
is that oh ocean I'll be an emergency uh
I have no blocks to get up
um
[Music]
Julie
I can place my end the chest somewhere
oh there there seems to be a big hole
down there I'm kind of scared oh yeah
I'll fill it for you place the inner
chest in this hole well it doesn't get
exploded don't you think that we
maybe we should have brought our beds a
little closer well here yeah he might
wander is the thing okay and the chest
is here if you need something oh okay so
I don't want him to blow up our beds
not a little that would be bad well the
potion of fire resistance be useful
that would be bad yes
yes I don't know maybe it's too far
that floor to walk back
um I should screenshot yeah but if we
die and then respond there yeah just
just oh my God
yeah that is a that is a good option
what's the shortcut to putting is there
a shortcut to putting something quickly
in your right hand
um from your toolbar f
F oh okay nice
so in this game I can't get the beds and
then we could like bury them
yeah
they were not that very moment
I didn't realize how I said it
um
she's off the bed exactly
oh Berry the best
I guess it should be fine I guess
I think we'll be okay
um we just he's gonna not die
but wouldn't it be boring if nobody died
we wanted to die I mean feel free to I
think it'd be funny if we beat it in
like less than a minute
but okay we're making it even more
difficult by doing it out in the open
now
you want to practice
don't do it put an apple on your head
Coulda put an apple on your head all I
have is a fish
fighting here
I'm sure we'll be fine right here oh my
God
rabbitman man
Mr Robin don't wander too far you're
gonna get lost there's a nice big ass
cave over here and we're just gonna
ignore it
[Music]
yeah the odd some girls are seeing it
I see it it's like endless with the
water
ah
toilet paper toilet paper
paper
I mean
I'm just gonna Flex my bow skills
bet you can't hit a moving Target
oh
I didn't say I was the target wow
well
oh
I've been all challenged since getting
real low yeah
[Music]
okay I have I have I have my light
sticks oh
I need phone I'm scared
mommy phone now
ah I almost killed myself guys yeah
excuse me I don't wanna do you wanna no
I don't mean no it's Gonna Fill my
pockets with unnecessary clutter
you're in a hole
I've done this haul
truly the error of my ways is this the
twerking rabbit it is it's the dumpy
rabbit oh
oh
this is
um
[Music]
forgot where you guys are oh is that you
that's you
I I literally
no no wait who did I hit sorry I'm gonna
do that I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
I'm sorry it's okay
do we have a place to put the Buns here
we go camping
as a family I thought we were camping
right now
can we tell our stories before we sleep
again back in my day
in Minecraft I had a dream about oh last
night
it was so good everyone fell asleep and
woke up in the morning
okay we should put the beds um
should we put the beds in the cave
you want to see the okay follow them no
no follow me
behind you over there I'm playing Horse
Race theme currently it's really good
music
I want to play classic music
what was that epic soundtrack yeah wow
can you battle music careful
I I forgot where it was
this way it was by the cacti
which one which was there's
here okay why you remember better than
me
bigger brain using the brain
that's just because you have a bigger
head go down I was gonna say have you
seen the size of it oh yeah that was it
we could put the beds and we could also
fight the weather here but I guess not
has nice shade too so we don't get
sunburn nice
but I probably have already gotten a sun
moon
hard too get out of the cave yeah
can make and then we can at least put
our beds here yeah it should be safe
right yeah yeah he's not that enclosed
is the thing
make our own cave yeah yeah
I'm just digging a hole for the beds
okay
bye bye cave I will explore you one day
surely
I'm getting heat stroke like like drink
some water you probably right yeah
sorry I'm sure that you brought water
bottles like sorry but I'll share with
the class it's my fault that you're
getting a heat stroke
maybe we should dig a hole here oh
yeah although it's sand here maybe like
right here
it's unsanitary
[Music]
nobody uses our board
oh
thank you
oh no almost killed her
oh my God
[Laughter]
I got lanterns I can put some nice
lanterns down here
um I'm just a little worried like if the
if it blows up the beds that would be
really bad oh yeah deeper maybe we
should dig it a little deeper
we gotta go deeper
because then we'll respawn like back at
spawn yeah
that's very far
I think that's good
it should be good
I don't think he can fit in here did you
know that they reverse engineered Roman
concrete
I told my child as they found out that
there's a lime inside of it and lime is
like a selfie it was like when it when
it got wet lime would expand and
self-heal the concrete because like how
did this live for so many billion years
it's pretty cool
lime it's also like the new cars have
you seen the new car grills lime if you
pour water on it it self heals the
scratches we live in a crazy it is crazy
times I'm also a little dissolve with
acid rain no lime I guess they didn't
have that
we but yeah
okay
it is really cool very important
oh yeah very important touch the bed
oh wait only one bed I have milk I have
beds only one is lots of beds lots of
beds beds beds beds beds
I think I touched it I'm gonna do a
double chicken just to be safe wait it
adds to be I don't know if I don't trust
my touch touch okay I'll do it one more
time as well just in case
maybe you should touch it again
left
it's like you touched the pillow and my
chat asks me right after I saved the
game did you save the game Kiowa maybe I
should save the game I just saved I just
saved honestly you can never save enough
when you're working on something you
know it's drying videos I'm scared this
isn't this nice no we can't get in this
looks so nice oh Oh I thought it was
nice
huh it is nice
I think this has to be a one one Higher
yeah why sure
nice beautiful nice bunker all right all
right
I feel like we should fill this in
because there's a giant falling Pit of
Doom where's the end chest yeah right
here
like over here in
[Music]
like right here probably
gravity
I'm gonna do some gardening
oh let's just make sticks
why is my sticks they're so stupid are
we ready
[Music]
how does this happen what's gonna happen
I didn't Google or study before two
phases the first one he flies around and
shoots explosions at you so hit him with
your bow and eat as many carrots as you
can he's gonna give you the Wither
effect so you won't be able to see your
health you're always going to be losing
health so just eat as much as you can
uh-huh
where he goes to the ground and spawns
skeletons and that's when you want to
hit him with the Smite sword
eating and try not to die
would you say that one shoots then one
each then one shoots then one each is a
is a good way to go or should it be like
I should have waited
oh should I use do it should we spell or
the potions or
are we good which is it good for like
yeah I have some
it's okay I'm strong
on my own
I believe in the potion chest outside
okay
I got it exploded if you put it outside
there will be a lot of explosions that
is true the boom booms and he can
destroy items with his explosions so oh
I don't want to fall out Kelly
Kelly
scaling skeleton okay this is fine I'm
sure this is fine this is around run
around
run around shoot run around
shoot eat shoot
oh okay
okay are there any more dangerous holes
trying to fill them almost bought him a
little further away probably like over
there yeah
on a flat round area here you'll
probably like move around quite a bit
though so okay and right here seems like
a good place to be able to see
[Music]
okay
isn't that a massive cave over here oh
my God is this the same one
um
she's doing it she's doing it
so sure just just on top right
stubbies
on top one spread out but will he be
right in front of my face should we
sleep first no no more no more why are
we Sleeping Sun is kind of exciting and
it's fine my ball is ready I'm gonna get
the first shot
dang it
come here it's kind of small wait
because he doesn't like take damage yet
does he he's not oh no not yet not yet
gotta run away it's gonna do a lot of
Dance Performing right
okay
[Music]
I guess I'm the pig
can't aim oh I got him
come on guys
I'm running out of there way too far
away
I need a hit compilation cow characters
he sucks
I'm missing somebody okay
this is
we can get right underneath him
I'm gonna look up his skirt
wait what the [\h__\h]
I'm in a hole I want to fight but I'm in
a hole oh gosh oh gosh he's almost half
pounds no
it's nice
why can't I eat because you're not
you're not uh
hmm
I might rely Invincible right now
I don't know I'm still running though
nice nice Nina you're ready for a
marathon
it's really scary
[Music]
[Applause]
is that it
is
[Music]
we did it that was it
so we have the beacon
the biggest star
who's the superstar
that was lame I want another one did he
drop it took so long to get the score oh
yeah that was way more difficult to get
the skulls
did it drop
does anyone have this flower I don't
have it nice
[Music]
looks like a tree star yeah I deserve it
I did the most work I'm just kidding
yeah how many gold medals do you have I
haven't hold
there's Golds no
I'll try to make a joke
I have gold defense I have gold healing
and I have gold
um where's the Platinum wait so I made
all these potions with nothing yeah we
didn't even die no one died
it's for it's purpose
who wants to stop
should we go should we go back should we
go sleep in our hole let's let's go kill
the the what's it called the warden
let's go I'm going right now yeah I'm
sorry
what the skeleton
let's go for the next let's go let's go
the warden is terrifying yeah
nothing's terrifying with this team of
professional Killers
oh watch out for the creeper no problem
then
I forgot hold on I guess it's not for
bed time for bed
we only have we are missing your bed
too easy
Tetris down here
[Music]
with what we can get okay we don't have
that much uh that much up square meters
square square square feet
that's mine
another star or maybe I should because I
feel like uh maybe Fallen is the most
responsible here to hold on Tiara's idea
though so she maybe haven't maybe yeah I
should hold the nether star or even here
too oh we have to take a picture anyway
oh yeah
I'm gonna get my box back please oh oh
yes sorry thank you smart
no oh we can take a photo and somebody
can draw a really bad Ms paint one and
like him in the background or something
oh yeah
in the sky like kind of faded out
yeah like fire like clouds
oh this dude almost looks like him
close enough
oh is that a zombie yeah desert zombie
let's take a kill more things in front
of our cave how about that okay okay
oh you still have more salsa sentence
we can pretend
oh yeah I was like yeah we're about to
summon it right now yeah
we need to find skulls you can always
summon another can someone somebody
should stand up too oh you know what if
you stand behind on a block behind you
could look like the head babe maybe
there we go
wait I have one because
that's Anya
what where's get those from what's wrong
we need one more everybody else
what's the ID with her
waiting Kyla who's got Kyla's name
I have no head at all even even at home
in my base
yeah it's okay so I might take a take a
while to get it but
um but no no we can't we can't we can't
put one remember
when we put the third one oh yeah okay
okay what is summons though
oh but then I can't take the picture
very well some is Kyla
she is the final boss
uh yeah be better if someone yeah
hello
uh um
can you stand next to Google
I got space
that was a good shot okay and cheese
easy
[Music]
okay I think I I got it what was it F2
and yeah wait I want to take one more
wait can we all squeeze in here you can
squeeze in there oh hold on
there we go can we get the sorority
squat
[Laughter]
yeah cute
thank you
[Music]
all right more
okay one more one more
everyone say cheese cheese
[Music]
I'm good
and now and now
don't forget the heads
man I mean we can we can raid something
Canada
I don't know we can talk about our
deepest darkest fears
it's you mommy you are my deepest Stars
oh
should we go make a beacon
what's up you can do
I just used to light up on the sky
yes make the bacon
bacon yeah do we know where we want the
beacon no
I do not care at all where it goes I
leave that thing
oh here oh my onions
my Anya
can you imagine if it actually like
summons something can we put three of
them did you get it no I did I did I did
I did I did oh thank you
let me know when you don't need the
chest anymore the under chest
is someone a gold star
that should go into the inner chest
maybe
yeah yeah
okay okay
shiny
[Music]
I think it should go wherever fauna
wants it she's the most active out of
all of us I think
but yeah we can discuss that maybe in
our little Minecraft Discord
[Music]
mmm for real though like what I mean I
guess I should be happy that it ended
early because it's like half past 1 am
here
we are efficient as a team yeah yeah
exactly but for real then let's next do
the warden that's so difficult that is
an actual challenge that girl is going
in her basement yeah how did she do that
how did she bring him to her basement
like for real I don't know
[Music]
thank you
I want to fight the warden me too
I found the castle the other day
where are you yeah
thank you
[Music]
yeah the warden isn't meant to be fight
but I think with our strong ass team I
feel feel like we're perfect we're a
good match for it hell yeah
we have to first set off
the or no we want him to find the place
with the Lord's a warden right under the
spawn of the new server
how do you know wait what is he look
wait how do you what what yeah
little tentacles on the ground they go
through ourselves at it
what stuff
yeah
we should oh my God have you girls
noticed how in the Japanese server they
all like they're they're guilds now
they're they have guilts we should be a
fighting girl too
let me call it our Guild
are we construction or fighting or bulls
we're fighting at least I'm fighting
shark
Phoenix
[Music]
Taco
um
it's for what what's best for
Christmas
but you have to separate it
oh we're like a radio channel
[Laughter]
owl nature Kiana I'm the only one with
the name
shark owl what'd you say shark Taco owl
nature shark Taco owl nature
yeah I guess we're the stunks wait which
one am I oh oh owl
what a song sounds like something
oh we're making stonks with our with the
quests that we fulfill in our Guild
it's true we have the economy behind us
like look at our fancy gear we have so
much stuff wow
even more stonks after I I did like I do
like stonks yeah wait if we make it wait
when we move to make a guild base
good good idea
yeah should we make it in the new server
because I haven't built anything in the
news
yes yes
should we uh I mean if we're gonna do
something big we might want to do it
another time if we want to make
something small we could do it now
I mean we can at least like claim a
ground or something okay yes
[Applause]
[Music]
claim the ground for free free real
estate
someone is US
lies lies what
[Music]
oh you cut it off
here can we make a Guild Art out there
a guild what
oh yes oh yeah who's out here disturbing
the peace
oh
[Music]
okay I'm coming upstairs I'm putting you
down okay
he's ready for you okay thank you
thank you how long was the weather live
like three minutes that's so sad I don't
think my bgm even looped once
I mean he has no like epic
epic bgm and I don't think it even got
to finish
I was just like one of those people who
are like on their jogs with their their
earbuds in with like Luffy playing
except there's like the world is burning
and exploding around them
when the world's ending and you have to
listen to One Last Song well I'm just
listening to some lofi
isn't it Lo-Fi Lo-Fi just like how it's
leafy
yeah
why do people always read her name wrong
no the music
and and
um
okay
shall we go back so we can go to the
news
[Music]
about Wi-Fi is different right Wi-Fi
what is Wi-Fi stand for
wireless internet if fun internet
Wireless
[Music]
it doesn't stand for anything
where did we come from wireless fidelity
where did we go
apparently it's wireless fidelity Wi-Fi
what is wireless wait we what's we in
what does it mean oh no why why I'm fine
why I'm fine why not fine Wireless
[Music]
infidelity is that when someone cheats
on someone
like an enemy
well it could be an Infidel yeah that's
the word I think of
Infidel if it's just means a traitor
right which is also someone who is
infidelity the enemy
the wireless briefly is the opposite of
that movie hmm
hmm what
yeah
we're back I'll be back no that's not
quite it
it's in the forest right somewhere
[Music]
else
guys remember
um
the red thing is right the tower
over here it looks like it
a spine
where's everyone
getting lost
look up look up
what look up where's the door down from
the tower though
how do we get in the woods
yeah once
you know got lost the second time I'm
still in the desert
um
I'm coming for you
you've deserted your sense of direction
where is she
I do not see you in the forest now ah
now you're in the forest it's not very
deep in the forest not very deep I'm
going up oh is that the tower the big
red Tower yeah oh
okay I'm fine I'm fine I'm fine I'm fine
oh I see your name I see you guys
okay I'm here hello
oh hello
it's right here
oh sure it is right here well
oh is that the Mark is oh
yes
[Music]
oh yeah
oh he doesn't care about no gold
no that was too dead inside to know or
want anything material
man
no chicken
come on cow
are we just naming animals we know
where do I think I'm thinking of
something but it's not
I don't know never mind nothing no it's
something but I can't tell you so it's
not nothing it's not nothing it's
something cat dog cat dog
no that's not that's a that's a great
thing to think about but that's not what
I'm thinking about
oh that looks kind of scary
cat dog what kind of shark are you in
shark form because I watched a shark
tier list I just want to know and one
whatever I think you are I'm a seven
shark
salmon is that a face like salmon
no but yes it is a thing it's a thing it
wasn't in the tearless so it probably
isn't really relevant is it
no they look like tiny gray ones they
look really angry but they're really
small you can pick them up with your
hands and stuff they don't do much
they might I'm not sure
do they eat salmon
I don't know I should know this but I
don't know is is that really a shark or
is it more of a salmon than
um
it sounds like a shark
um I'm about to Google it what if it's
just like a salmon and then it goes like
I want to be a shark so it's a salmon
shark yeah no he's he's shark I promise
you this is real shark
we probably caught a salmon shark
because they eat salmon oh they smell
like because it's so small
[Music]
that's all I have I have no other
information about this
how do you not know
what else you want to know
um
it looks like it's the size of a salmon
oh I don't know your specks I want to
know your stats your stealth your
intelligence your your stamina your HP
your defense I wanna know it all you've
been playing too much of that jrbg game
I am the house that's on fire
part 300. I want to is there three of
them I had 90 hours of gameplay in that
damn good Lord
nine hours yeah what's like the longest
three the longest game you girls ever
played game with the most hours hmm
please
[Music]
free jelly
they're so tiny and really long slinkies
okay nice clean up okay
clean it up somebody said faunas DOTA
for sure
I don't know if I would even count these
kind of like endless going games though
I'm in like more like something that can
end at what point do you count like MMOs
to you know like play time
they also don't count in that matter
oh we're back in the bunkeroni all right
let's go to the new servo
um I'm so excited
everybody has seen the new Sarah by now
right or you know hasn't maybe has you
have you I have yeah okay okay
that's where I found the warden you know
oh did you just walk into oh sorry
[Music]
wait what that means what type of owl
are you
uh are you a snowy owl
I like to change my my type of owl if
I'm I if I'm stupid I'm bar now uh-huh
what the barn owls are cute they're
screechy though and annoying yeah stupid
yeah and that's stupid oh you're not
screechy though
or wait or annoying you're neither
you're neither you're neither of those
things
and she liked the warden wouldn't kill
us but berries would
that's a very bushes the berry bushes
will definitely kill me one day
you know where the portals are it's
Peppa beer is it a mythological creature
okay no I mean no it's it's real it's
real
[Laughter]
but was it really tea
what would it be otherwise I'm lost I'll
come back
Hi how are you lost I'm not lost this is
The Stomping Ground you live in the
bunker I'm not lost I'm not it's lost
I'll shoot an arrow for you Hugo I'm
found I was just lost in life not lost
you know
understanding [\h__\h]
you're not behind me
never find
oh there she is is that you
hello
she's over there she's gone
[Laughter]
so about hitting those moving cars sorry
no ma'am
are you stood in front of it you stood
in front of it ma'am you stood in front
of it you have no gun safety your gun
safety skills are
I have sword safety but I'm gonna throw
it out the window oh I fell I'll forgive
you this time
it's like it's like
rejecting our Quest you are part of the
skills now you have things to do no
there's some suspicious things going on
in this in in here no there's there's
there there's you know team kids
why are you stuttering it's team
building
okay
I just want to say something
yes say something that makes us all come
together again
just be stink
[Music]
s
let's go oh it could be something else
okay before the words I've been playing
too many across words this is getting
dangerous what are you thinking
inspirational
okay cheers
is there any place that we should have
it close to for like the sake of
what about the trees
maybe we can cozy up next to them yeah
challenge the other guilds Village
so pretty
yeah
bless you do we have something to claim
the ground with like torches or a sign
anymore so
[Music]
I know blue
too I want to help Ah that's like pecora
versus
Senpai guilds versus
oh my gosh I don't know if we should
build it next to here
comparison might be
better
[Music]
quality it will be easy she's gonna make
it out of wood and then call it no
sometimes that's the hearty Elder Shack
where do we go though
Chief Building on the ocean
oh God
[Music]
where's the ocean I don't know if that's
delicious just water
I see you I know there's I don't know if
there's one like nearby but there's like
water here what is your problem
don't haha
okay
I feel like there's there's a lot of
land taken over here though
um
let's go west yeah
where's West
this way where's this way this way
okay okay
are those pandas
[Music]
pandas oh wait when did they put pandas
in this game a while ago a long time ago
actually what they came with the jungles
right what maybe it's still going west
be careful they're aggressive when
there's a baby around okay but only a
panda baby if if you find one with a
panda baby you want to stay away where
where are you guys heading to we're
going west where are you West
Virginia
oh the frames they just dropped all of a
sudden you're aware
we passed the we passed the pandas yeah
we passed the pandas
yeah you passed them okay
pandas pretty good
are you guys still at the panda
no we went past the panda past the
pandas only a little bit oh
[Music]
another portal
what
pasta very pretty ones
what is all this the beetle are you past
no not past the beetle why where are
they where are you
oh frog
there's a different Panda place
can you come pick me up
wait I don't think we were going west
what is that noise what is that noise
it's a frog it's me talking to a frog oh
it's beautiful
water bottle yeah no I may say it's
reacting to me
what wait is it creature sound I'm doing
that well I am a frog partially so you
know
that's the other Panda spot okay I see
someone pick me up
um are you scared you know the blue
building Guild building no we saw with
the canyon no no if you look at the big
pecora building like when you would
stand in front of it go right the Big
Pig but like be further away from it
well it was not it was I'm going I see
you and you see me yeah we were going
south I think look up oh there's there
you are I thought you got their
skeletons I was about to take out my bow
yeah
you went South
yeah or we could build over bike I think
fauna and my Trident we're kind of close
together we could build over there yeah
I was talking about the ocean oh yeah
I was shocked that you built something
it looked really good
thing yeah wait what does that mean
I was shocked that it like it looked
pretty much like finished but I guess
then I went inside and I saw it really
wasn't finished and then I was like okay
that's good
[Laughter]
are we going to the trident
there
[Music]
yeah wow wait I don't know where you
guys are
um wait one ordinary
no go back to the go back I see the
pandas that you saw
we lost her again
the portal
I've never been in this area so I don't
know what you mean when you say like the
blue Guild and stuff
um well we went back to Nature
we're gonna pick you up
what are you near them
I can go near the Nether Portal here I'm
just gonna go
Are You Gonna Save here it says
okay I'll be I'm near the pandas okay
we're almost there or I'm almost there I
think I see you okay
scary
oh it's wonderful
this okay one yeah that's a hotel
it's the hotel Lego I found a hotel yeah
with an ally inside
I like prism
sounds cool
wait who's m
me
ume okay so I've mixed them all up some
of those like first letter names some of
them are
owl and shark and huh
where where is everybody now oh we're on
our way okay
are we gonna build it around good as
place now
okay
[Music]
bling bling bling bless you boys
allergies are kick my butt what allergy
do you have
every all of it um
allergy testing before
pieces of skin out of your back yeah
they prick your back they put your back
they prick my arms it's either back or
arms oh but you can't see if it's on
your back though Stacy what does that
use hand do they like cut out a piece of
skin or they could take a picture
probably but I didn't really want to see
no they like Cricket and see like how
your skin reacts and oh they were like
yeah you're allergic to everything
especially everything in nature
this is the one I was worried about I
was like this is okay this is all that I
want to know thank you thank you goodbye
you're good this is a good spot
something around here right yeah
how to claim it
makes like a like a square with our
some red red sand yeah me too I'm pretty
free I have normal sand should we ride
like a big en or something oh okay
or a big Stone kill them stunk big stunk
yeah I'm gonna try
can't wait can we make it into the shape
of a turnip turn up our icon well it's
just completely stocks crafting
reference
yeah
wait we don't like piss FM now
uh here's some signs that we could use
what noise
I'll take it
where are we putting it here I have a
sign
oh
thank you this whole area if we want to
make like a big building so from
I'll just
uh
Guild
wait sorry
oh wait it won't work on
I'm writing an S oh stunk I'm writing an
S
um from that side wait if this is wrong
yeah I guess it was like easier to see
and now I can't go up do you want to use
this box wait no they might be easier
um I want some orange terracotta oh my
God
[Music]
oh stunk there it is that's an s
who wants to do the T
everybody's looking at this
it's a nice ass wow
[Music]
oh you can do it oh I'm doing the oh is
that enough room for your tea
oh I don't think so oh wait show me the
cameraman
hello
sorry
your tea can go in between there yeah
noise
so oh it's very short tea
nice nice oh it looks so
Builders wow I'm impressed like we're in
sync well wow beautiful
um it's definitely readable
oh
I can just write stop
it
I also want to do that I was like
surely you won't notice if I oh no STC
don't
this is Santa I can't Stone do you want
it to be a pee yeah
um
should they be an N yeah
what style stunk right now shouldn't it
no why are you stopping don't stop
stopping bro
okay okay but we're riding stunk okay
we're not as in sync we have to work on
that well I forgot one wonderful okay I
guess that works yeah that works it's a
clear message
I'm gonna make an exclamation mark then
here wait I I want to build it okay
oh thank you
stop
in the name of the law
for what what does it mean wait maybe
it's me though get rid of all this
shrubbery
nice nice Mommy
beautiful
I wonder if someone's gonna be like but
why
you will see you will see eventually it
will all make sense
we will surely we will build something
here right in the next yes in the next
three months we will make something here
Shirley surely
okay that's a good reason for me to play
Minecraft again I I was waiting for
something like that never give up a
whole bunch of stuff around it that's
useful
anesthetic
and maybe okay we can also like
eventually the first thing we should be
doing is like make everything around it
a little bit flat so we can have a
building
oh Planet you heard the lady
just like the area where we're building
murder
we have a robot here robot
robot robot went bad do we have Guild
rolls
is there a sign up sheet for the guild
rolls can I be the dog
I think we already have the shark
instead
we can have an owl too they can carry
letters
can I be the owl
um
can I be
okay so we got the ocean and we got the
sky where's the ground one
the Phoenix
but I'm in the sky too why
brain hurt
and Kane walks on land it's true she's
the Earth bender
I just don't isn't it a goat it's the
cute little
cute little rodent cute like a little
chicken make sure they rodents
[Music]
Ambassador for international affairs
between ID and Japan girls Etc okay that
will be my role wait we need to write
this down
I have no sign I mean
I can be I have a book
I guess uh Aesthetics uh another
Ambassador Ambassador ambassador
I'm not very good at designing buildings
though
help me blueprint the beta I can be that
that's the I don't know wait what are
Guild rolls anyway
I can be the one that turns on everybody
who may I please know
wait
uh and the I'm the consultant of many
affairs
yes
[Music]
what kind of thing what kind of building
do you want to do you want something
like natural or like futuristic or
modern you know minimalistic
fantasy Korean theme are we going for
I've seen so far a lot of like RPG
fantasy style builds in the server
so you want something modern
minimalistic no actually I like the
fantasy style okay okay so but which
style of fantasy are we going for are we
going for like uh uh you know like the
classic in town look or do you want more
like uh you know like a special area
kind of thing like a in the forest kind
of building oh the cute mushrooms or oh
mushrooms sounds cute that would be cute
or like a castle or oh or you know
Gothic Castle or like a normal Castle I
like wood
like wood yeah
easy material oh it's kind of like cute
a little hot like like the hobbits kind
of design
yeah there we go can we have a Hobbit's
uh hole
that's a real Dome like maybe that might
be a little difficult but we can make it
happen yeah your your roof is already a
dome you know how to make it oh yeah
Taco Dome actually I'm quite proud of
that though let's make a shy or have it
Shire have it home okay yeah all right
[Music]
talking about watching Lord of the Rings
with everybody but yeah you know kiwawa
and guda already be watching it I don't
know about mummy and Inna have you girls
watched a lot of the Rings watched it in
theaters oh
nice is Mumbai the only one who hasn't
really watched it at all oh wait no it's
not here right now
oh but then it's about time I know
Florida rings
oh I want to listen to that soundtrack
now but have you guys watched
the Six Star Wars movie back to back oh
I've never seen one
yeah
that's a good recently I have time to
one um two Star Wars movies in my
members and I've stopped watching them
because I I refuse to watch anymore wait
which ones did you watch which ones did
I the first like the the first ones that
got released the first two ones okay you
didn't like them
um
um well I prefer a Lord of the Rings
do you like sci-fi no
I do not like fun you should watch anime
uh my anime uh aliens watch Aliens oh
alien is good well
[Music]
depends which but I did I did enjoy them
yes I need to watch Avatar the blue one
okay I was like
is there a new one coming out so I need
to watch the other two out oh it's
already out I gotta watch it
I guess probably not sleeping that's
because she's not here
because I I just said it
said it's did you think it was me again
I'm not sure what do you think again
that was fun that was fun before the
stream I don't know
I don't know where I put my bed
um
oh wonderful There She Goes
good morning did we just leave our beds
here yeah we can do that
okay so we have our stop sign we have
some of our rolls I just stops good as
the flashlight I don't know we could
change it it's whatever you want to be
what's a stoat
I don't know that's what they said
trying to look it up because is it like
it's not a rodent it's like a weasel
yeah yeah it's like a little vicious
weasel yeah you
okay well then that was uh way easier
than expected but we finally did it
um it's a warm-up you know
hell yeah
I'm excited for that
and then let's run into my house if you
go in my basement you can hear him oh
oh
is it really or am I getting
yeah like a cross over there do you see
uh-huh see what like I see a castle
I see a big tree did they so did they
just like build it on top of it isn't
that cronies the warden built it oh the
word the time warning
oh my God
thank you for that oh who's that oh
[Music]
okay where may I put my guild
resignation
you can't it's written and it's sealed
in sign contact your further inquiry now
you can't back out
you'll have to come before the council
before you remove yourself from the
guild that's the law
we're in front of two of them yeah
and I say wait no we say what do we say
[Applause]
we say you're trapped here forever now
listen to all the soundboard and two
times
[Music]
okay I guess I have no choice
I am content yeah me too
I live here now and from the stop sign
that's all we need to lift these beds
okay then I will okay yeah I will leave
um we wrapped it up today yeah let's
wrap it up wrap wrap somebody rap words
are wrappers
oh
somebody rap for us
yo um
stunk stunk stunk killed the Wither like
it was uh never played in my Netherlands
next time we'll kill the warden like
it's in our garden uh catches Next Time
watches or else we'll all be very upset
rhyme but that's cool that's fine
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay thanks girls hello
um thank you guys putting it together
okay
organizing flower asking if anybody
wanted to beat the Wither and yeah but
yeah go ahead and beat up the Wither and
I learned what the Wither was oh there
you go and yeah more experience in my
life yay yeah yeah
maybe the weather was the friend we met
along the way oh but we killed him the
Stone Cold
the stunks
nice yeah okay okay
and and in strong we say auf wiedersean
bye-bye
bye bye guys
[Music]
thanks for watching
um
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]