thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
hello
[Music]
okay
welcome to
Pokemon
Scarlet yay I shall embrace the spoilers
oh don't worry I don't think we'll get
so far today
at least nothing really important will
happen I think today is just the very
beginning
um because I don't have much time
I've been in character creation since
like 40 minutes oh wow
uh so adults
um I have a recording
at midnight and I still need to prepare
for that
some things
it's been
um kind of a stressful
day well first of all I woke up I I fell
asleep so early but
um then I just woke up too early
and then I tried to fall asleep again
for hours which I eventually did but
then you know at least I had everything
prepared the night before mostly for
whole talk so everything was cool
um but yeah I've barely eaten anything
and now I'm gonna power through Pokemon
Scarlet then I need to cook and then I
need to prepare
and then I need to record at midnight so
I am very stressed I'm feeling very
stressed out but I hope that at least
playing Pokemon will make me feel
um relaxed
now it's just a recording for a whole
talk on Sunday but I need to do it at
midnight because I need some help
um you know any camera uh help and I
need acting out help uh so that's why I
can't just do it anytime I had to set a
time and a date for it
um
[Music]
so anyway hopefully this will help me
chillax
and so let's play wait a second let's
play
Pokemon
oh it's a kind oh I hope you hear the
bgm oh which language obviously German
just kidding not German
I'm like
all over the place
ah chat goes here I still had the memo
pad from her talk open hi John no not
Germany for fun English
oh
okay so I heard that the character
creation is quite intricate right in the
beginning that's cool
um I will use
ah we'll just use her as a starter
and one second
I don't like it sometimes oh it doesn't
in this case Okay sometimes it gives you
like recommendations on what you should
be typing
it didn't this time
we'll just call myself wow
should it be kiwawa
here you wow okay
yeah yeah okay no Capital left I'll
cover capital letters
well are you ready to start the game
with these settings no no no no no you
can't change your language or name after
starting the game aha
no problem I'm happy with that but let's
see what they got I like this hairstyle
already it's cute but should I get
something that looks like me or
[Music]
ah
I have to click a okay should I get
something that looks like me can we get
something that looks like me like one of
my hairstyles I got many
long and straight kill don't know
[Music]
if they have like a double braid then
that would look like my casual one
uh
what's that oh pump a door that's what
you call that
short crop nope I don't have a hairstyle
like that
what what what hair color haircut
[Music]
two block cut
ooh girls with that haircut are quite
interesting
spaceman's so
cute oh they even have braids in the
back there
[Music]
so cute
love it
this was cute too
this one's cute too
and but none of them look like any of
the hairstyles that I have
um
there's nothing that looks like me
[Music]
like maybe the closest
is this
to my
um what's with that
some parts of the hair look weird but uh
maybe that because it looks like a
little bit like my main hairstyle a
little bit like my my Hema cut from my
kimono
yeah
and then you must have orange dough
[Music]
you got like two types of pink
you got green you got white pink and
what fruit that's a pink
have they forgotten about Orange
huh
let's go
it's like orange oh thank God okay
what about the uh eyes and eyebrows
there's four different pigs and
this probably is yeah this is like a
purple I love Ash purple
ah another green no honestly why is
there no normal orange orange is the
quite a common color and yet they throw
in so many Randomness colors
uh we'll go for scarlet then
okay I can change it in the face page
okay
uh yes
[Music]
change look okay
I see girls with orange all the time
on YouTube right
anyway but you don't see more girls with
green hair than you see girls with
orange hair if we talk about real life
right
oh
oh my God cute
[Music]
oh they're all like kind of similar
because they cut off on the sides
because of my hairstyle
um but this one speaks to me
and then uh purple
nice looks like me now
hey
yeah uh ultramarine senpai
wow that's pretty
the eyes are pretty oh wow
oh
okay but we go for purple what's poppy
red
cute lavender oh
[Laughter]
[Music]
okay oh eyelash oh they're separate wow
oh
oh I like this one
I think I like this one oh oh those
lashes
oh pretty I like this one too
[Music]
you know that those wait which ones were
those
These Eyes they remind me of
um four blood kiwawa
[Music]
yeah the art style
made me look like this a little bit in
terms of eyes
but koala in reality here if you look at
me don't have so many lower lashes
ah
so if we really want to make her look
like me
that's probably
I don't like at least like a lime dough
a little bit
and a bit more on the top it's really
like I can't see the side Stone
um and that's where it's important but I
guess then it doesn't matter
I'm thinking too much about this anyway
I'll go with this this is good this good
question
next oh
wow
what what about Scarlet if I really make
it look the same damn my eye lashes if
you look at them they are indeed more of
a brown and on the sides they kind of
turn reddish
fancy I know
so I guess it would be good to go with
like a
um
I'll just go with a
or maybe
yeah but I like the contrast of Darker
lashes and in this art style at least
okay eyebrows
oh the shape
oh my eyebrow shape
by the way let me like fix my position a
bit
okay
my eyebrows shape
[Music]
it's not completely round
but
oh I like these thick eyebrows
oh those are like ash eyebrows
oh wow fluffy I have a caterpillar on
your face too
Phyllis
okay these are too thick
I'll um but I also think they're too
high are there any like lower ones
no not really this this starts kind of
low
I'll go for this not my favorite but
they're lower and I like that
and then we make them
Scarlet screw it although no no no no
actually no
I want them to be kind of um brown but
like a reddish brown
bright
huh
I mean that
whatever we will never look at her so
closely ever again
but I don't have an Uber mouth I wish I
had an ooVoo mouth
in my VR chat models I got a and also
froggy one I got an Uber mouth
I really like it
um
I do have a big mouth though don't I ah
I guess we'll go with that big mouth
and then
[Music]
yeah I think I you can't you can't
say it but I have like a really light
pink tone on it
but let's see the other options oh
oh that's hot that's hot
it's kind of hot in reality that would
be hot
it doesn't suit her in this game
why is your face so long by the way it
looks so long when I look at the OBS
screen it looks better on my screen
okay no I'll go for her
I'll go for that
[Music]
but I want
foreign
no thank you freckles
I don't want freckles Chihuahua with
freckles would be so adorable
[Music]
but I I cannot have freckles
yeah you we want freckles right yeah red
hair equal freckles freckles for quilts
I'll take it
until I confirm the B okay
[Music]
it's different from the other one
this is
me I'm exactly where I'm supposed to be
now yeah freckles
foreign
[Music]
close to myself but the freckles I could
not resist
oh my other phone is orange still oh
yeah cause Scarlets
[Music]
it's me it's me
enrollment complete
okay
yeah no it means Orange
no oh
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no
[Music]
wow with that
oh my God so many books I will never
read them never
taking this one tradition going stronger
and greater oh it's time for you two to
dive into the world of Paul come on
what are you waiting for for me probably
there we go
oh
you guys wonder what Pokemon I'll take
right
I'm still unsure
direct look different like the blah blah
director clavel head of the Naranja
Academy
is sprawling is a sprawling region
bursting with Lush nature and
magnificent landscapes
it is also of course home to the
mysterious creatures known to us as
Pokemon
they reside here in great numbers in
fact
that looks like a mix of Pikachu and
evely
but this is the new Pikachu Pokemon as
I've heard
[Music]
finally Pikachu and Ebony are united
it's probably the ones from Pokemon
let's go Pikachu let's go Italy they
found each other and we're like Let's
Get It On
Pokemon can be found living all over in
the scenes and the skies Even in our
cities and towns we humans coexist with
Pokemons as we both have one another to
live and thrive
oh Evie I mean Evie yet
Naranja Academy is here to help you
learn even more about these precious
partners
within our Halls people from all regions
Gathering to study together what is that
on the table is that supposed to be a
Pokemon
it doesn't really look like a Pokemon
but
because the bottom of it could be like
eyes
this is a Pokemon
it's weird it's a new one right
and it's Pokemon trainers they have
their Pokemon do battle growing
alongside them
while our robust curriculum of
coursework helps our outside just a
fossil
Rock hermit crab Pokemon oh okay
helps our students drop off their
fullest potential
it is Within These Halls that you will
find your friends
Academy we can't wait to welcome you
with open arms I skipped something
foreign
it's my bicycle
bicycle bicycle
[Music]
wow
we're flying
Pokemon
the terrorist
thank you
ebony EB
oh that just looked like absolutely
normal
um what are they called the pink boobs
they just look like normal ones
like the actual animal Flamingo oh it's
just flamingos
huh
Landing in the water
hello cute
they look like the Minecraft verbs
the parrots
this house is nice holy it's such a
perfect
location too we must be really rich
Pirates didn't exist before Minecraft
exactly well even my curtains are orange
I think I chose the right Edition
while some Pokemon stickers at the Apple
One killed
I feel like that Apple Pokemon that's on
the sticker could be besties with the
the Apple crocodile Apple dragon and
apple crocodile
I think it's perfect
hmm
uh-huh what are we thinking about I look
you know I I when I first reacted to the
trailer of this game on my stream
you know I really did not like their
faces
and to be honest it's still kind of
weird to me but I got used to it quite a
bit and it's less weird to me now
you know after looking at myself but
this this kind of face for a while
still feels kind of off every other
character looks like a proper Pokemon
person to me
but the protagonists not they look like
Barbie characters to me
yeah the uniform yeah is that like I
know you can change the backpack and the
shoes and the uniform and so on but can
you only change the uniform into another
uniform or is there like no
oh
[Music]
first write a little d-pad this is the
only thing I get ah can you like only
get there's only four uniforms no they
no they're cute
cloves in the previous Pokemon games
Steven the sword and shield no
[Music]
no
sad
so sad but holy this house is crazy
well Mommy
Mommy good morning Chihuahua
oh already in your uniform and
everything
she looks so young
well this is your first day at your new
school after all I'm so excited for you
so you might want to cool your engines
before you go racing out the door the
school contacted me and said that you're
supposed to wait here a little while
longer
uh that one's not mine apparently
there's something very important for
your first day that still has not
arrived
maybe I've adopted
no one just dyed my hair okay maybe
that's the very thing we're waiting for
okay while we'll get the door would you
I think it would have been nice if the
mama automatically had the hair color
that you pick in the character creation
but apparently I'm adopted I even have
different uh eye color
foreign
[Music]
I'm supposed to open the door right
here
do forgive the intrusion
you are Miss Cuba warriors on behalf of
the Academy I must apologize for the
later arrival of your enrollment
documents
and also for my delaying introducing
myself
I've got all the balls more balls than
you do more balls than anyone I am the
director of Naranja Academy you may call
me Mr clavel
the director and you came in person to
help my daughter with her first day gasp
Lucas
well I'm responsible for the entire
Academy including any failures on its
part so here are a lot here at last
order enrollment documents that should
have already been delivered to you
but we laid off too many people at the
Academy so I have to do it personally
you really needed
there's no one left since you've come
all this way can I at least offer you a
cup of tea
oh no need to trouble yourself
I've got a thing or two to discuss with
the director here why don't you head
back up to your room and finish getting
ready for school you'll need your bag
and your hat as well hot yes
don't want to show my Egghead
now Mr clever Hill you simply must join
me for a cup up
[Music]
cup of coffee
or a cup of tea or is the copper thing
how they say it
what's a Cuppa
hi a cup of tea
[Music]
well how can I refuse such a kind offer
don't know what you're talking about
though
a cup of tea a couple couple
we have a Kappa at home okay
yeah isn't this supposed to be in Spain
is Spanish
could it be
oh it's sparkling well
let's put it on that's a big hat my head
must be huge
ah
okay that's pretty cute look how cute I
have the Hat on OMG
[Music]
you can press the x button to open the
main menus okay so like the save button
from this menu to save all the progress
you've made on your adventure so far
well you will feel better go find some
key out of the side including your
adventure Guide check it out whenever
you want to review handy tips like this
that you receive along your adventure
nice
cute kind oh boy I like the Hat I'm like
a what preschooler how old is the
protagonist like nine
oh she's looking at me judging me sorry
tender
mouth
[Music]
preschool I don't I
I preschool list I don't know
uh um
[Music]
I know what what kind of school are you
in when you're 10.
Frisco Five Oh I thought that was
Kindergarten
[Laughter]
oh oh third grade
wow
elementary elementary right
[Music]
um
I Have Been to Spain before not Portugal
though but Spain uh at least once I
think only once foreign
[Music]
oh just look at you all ready for your
big first day
oh yes the uniform of our story storied
Academy suits you quite well indeed
I learned that those 10 year olds get
sent to school instead of being released
into the wild alone
ah you mean as opposed to other Pokemon
games
yeah true
true
will be tomorrow in Valencia what
your first time enjoy it's like really
nice there yeah not so crowded either
um
[Music]
OG Pokemon is kind of brutal
I guess so
traumatizing Forever Kids
oh gracious how very careless of me I
heard entirely forgotten that I have
something else for you miss q101 a most
important thing but your living room is
hardly the place for it would you care
to follow me outside
[Music]
yeah yeah I guess mommy lets me go with
a stranger
on the top right
that thing that doll
is that a Pokemon doll if yes or what
because I know there is one one viewer
one listener whose Twitter account
um profile picture is that
it is
possible that's why he's got that name
too
[Laughter]
oh they must really like that Pokemon
then
I was I don't know I recognized
um the the thing there but I didn't know
it was a Pokemon
[Music]
oh it's not a Pokemon oh it's like ah uh
attack where you send out like a
substitute for yourself
Ah that's why it doesn't quite look like
a Pokemon there's something missing
um
[Music]
I wonder what this important thing might
be let's follow the director out and see
shall we and we're not even the Pokemon
Universe
every country
has this kind of thing where they send
their children out to do Pokemon stuff
or if it's only certain places
[Music]
or certain cities
and are there like any normal kids who
don't do it
I wonder every country
um
technically spin-off games are different
countries so no
[Music]
only the cool places to it
only because I wonder if she would move
here because she's like I wonder what
will happen if the mom moved here
without knowing that this is a thing
here that her child will have to get
into Pokemon stuff
for rather forcefully
because basically she's going to a
Pokemon school or so
right then dear Pokemon time to come out
of your Pokeballs
we got the started so early
well
you guys know I
like them all no
we provide each student entering the
academy a Pokemon of Their Own
do you always offer them these free
though probably not right
damn you give me quite
a difficult choice
I'll ask you to choose which among these
free you'd like to have as your partner
sprig or Tito the grass cat Pokemon
it's it's it snows looks like a heart
the fire Croc Pokemon
Loosely related to the fire dragon
Pokemon that we had in sword and shield
because we ran out of ideas and cruxley
the duckling Pokemon how come we haven't
done this before
I guess we have done similar things pop
pop
you say pump
they're all very good company why they
usually refuse to even leave my side
what's this
um it turns out they're more interested
in you miss kiwama than familiar old me
I do wish I could stay and see which one
you'll choose but I must be off to my
next home visit
I'll be at the house just over there
house
you call it a house
a Villa it's a castle almost
take your time of your decision then
come find me once your mind is made up
everyone's Rich here
now if you excuse me until next we meet
hi bye bye
it's Mansion yeah
fellow that director of yours is
these three are all lovely but you need
to choose just one right not an easy
task
I can't stop yawning why not take this
opportunity to walk about with these
little ones and get to know them I'm
sure they have lots to teach you me
they're babies
Oh but before you go I got you a little
something to celebrate your big day take
it with you if you're going out on your
own
nanny
I wrote down Brown
you put the random fun in your bag key
items pocket okay latest model of
smartphone what was that badonk sound
a Pokemon called rhodium lives within it
and it can be used to run all sorts of
Handy apps
according to the instructions you can
check the map app
I I heard I heard aloud to donk again
behind my headphones is confusing
why button okay
it will help keep you from getting lost
so take good care of your new Gadget
okay no off you go have fun
we'll see about why we're not a lot of
fun you can't tell me to have fun I'll
decide whether or not I want to have fun
it's my decision I'm not part of your
system
no can't tell me
okay
what the why are you not following
there you go
I really like the looks of all of the
starters but I did look at the
evolutions even though I am really
confused about why Pokemon until now
has still not published an official
source
the only way to know it officially is by
playing the game
right what what oh there's one Pokemon
missing
oh there you are
like what what on Earth
I understand not spoiling but
by now on the day of release would be
cool if they at least put it on the
website like
not everyone looks at the webs on anyone
but I have kaboboko I have on now
um hello
Community but it's all
I have looked it up you guys told me you
guys showed me the non-finance versions
the movement is weird the power of
science is amazing if you connect with
friends you can head out on adventures
together up to four of you at a time
um interesting I wonder how that works
maybe we'll test it out
but yeah
so Evolution wise
I don't like the duck
the cat and this one they are
more or less equal to me
I love cats you know that
but there's something about this apple
Croc
looks so funny Caleb look at him looking
at me oh
there's something about him but I also
freaking love cats
and I kind of I feel like I kind of
prefer the
cat final evolution
but also a crocodile is just cute
I don't know
it's not gonna be this ductiles didn't
impress me and the final evolution looks
weird
she's floating on air
cute girl
is that an orange
looks like an apple but I think it's an
orange
well you suck
don't know how to use your fire yet
maybe I should teach him
[Music]
oh
not quite whiskey always here to make a
choice you see
I said
oh
come on
it's so cute God damn it
um
Buenas we haven't met yet have we
buenos dias buenas noches
I must say I wasn't expecting to see you
here quite so soon
hang on director is this who I think it
is
but am I Legend already
yes this is our Academy's new student
Miss Kiowa she will be attending us off
today
okay
am I the only one who started today
weird
so you're that kid who moved up in up
the road my new neighbor I've been dying
to find out more about you
I'm the Mona normally I live in the
school dorms but home is here what are
you say new neighbor Wanna Be Friends
no
no no no
[Music]
no
huh what's wrong did I scare you off
maybe I came on a little strong yeah
not anyone can be my friend I don't
trust people so easily and
I don't know I don't wanna no
miss them oh Mr Mona is president of our
student council on the champion rack
trainer and her own right you better
respect her old spank your butt
don't worry about what he just said uh I
absolutely love Pokemon battling in fact
we should battle right now you and me
because you know you two will be in the
same class so we will have plenty of
time to battle later
and get to know one another better of
course
we're gonna be neighbors and classmates
nice we'll be able to battle all we want
on that note Miss q101
which is it
um
[Music]
uh
so cute what
ah
doncio
I don't know and especially I thought I
was fairly certain before the stream but
now that I have the choice in front of
me
I'm less sure about it
fires my element I am a verb but I love
cats
how could they do this to me
can we just throw them all in the mixer
in a blender and
take them together as an abdomination
I hate it I hate this
flip a coin no I mean I wouldn't mind
hearing what you guys say
I'm not taking the doctor
and cut
please help me influence my mind
let's get there don't blend I want to it
would be so much easier and I have to
test out my new blender and bought a new
blender
I need to test it out this would be oh
wow
this would be perfect
whoa
sick sick so how's it going The Croc is
winning
bye
um nine percent
what is that 11.
damn most little girls took the Croc and
no fauna took the cat
um
oh oh Croc is winning one more queen of
findings The Croc
bikini trainer
Sparks like the flame no fire
ah
I
chose
yo
just kidding just kidding just kidding
let me undo let me undo
okay I'm just kidding
no
but when you lie between two you should
take the the leftover one right
barely anyone I think only
took the duck it's kind of sad
man
ual questions
okay I Choose You
you're red like me and you're cute
I'm sorry I'm sorry I'm sorry
I love the cats too you know how much I
love cats but I don't know something
about them too you know because the cat
is just a cat but this thing
it's so freaking cute
I know it doesn't stay lined up I also
saw the revolution
uh it's less funny later on
but I don't know the tooth looks cute
yeah it's so cute it's an apple
crocodile
burning hot spikes
with scatters we'll fry any and all
plants in a Flash
you heard it here burning hot Sparks
what choice do I have
yes
you chose
would you like to give for a cocoa
nickname
yes
um
box
oh I got a female
now here we go not that I care
yeah capital letters I I think this
is so weird I saw this scene before but
standing on my noodle arm with that
thick legs
how how
[Music]
does he do it or she do it
seems to have taken quite a luck into
you miss kiwawa you better start lifting
otherwise your arms will never be both
enough for him this is your first
Pokemon yes please raise it with love
and care and of course be sure to keep
it tucked safely enjoy the Pokeball
yeah
ah no can I keep it outside please all
the time
I can't believe you actually chose
flickago I thought you liked cats what
the hell
well then whatever
I will then chose her instead I mean
like way to make the perfect choice for
you you two make such a good combo
can I choose one of these Pokemon too
they're at the club out
oh but did you not receive a Pokemon
When you entered an Academy Miss nimona
no I had other Pokemon I was focused on
raising at the time but now I want to
raise a new Pokemon alongside kiwawa
while she raises her own new partner
um
is that fair she gets one of those
strong starters when she already got
started before
and these are like pretty strong I don't
know man I don't think it's fair
if you wish to raise one of these
Pokemon equal footing with whiskey while
we're here I shall be more than happy to
allow it that's so weird it's not fair
that's not fair
it's like
what
no these are supposed to be for someone
else no like wasn't he didn't he say
he has to go to another
student or so to give them a new Pokemon
as well that's but then we came here
it where's the logic and and we first
he's like you want one too that was not
the plan but we came here
so it's supposedly her but he's still
like hmm I guess like a show I guess we
can do that huh
yeah yeah to this student but then why
would he be like um
didn't you already have a Pokemon though
because that means he wasn't planning on
it but he came to this house with the
plan on giving someone a Pokemon
understand
well yes correct freaking corrupt
uh since kiwama chose political I'll go
for this little one I'll treat her
nicely I'm stealing this cat
oh
my stairs so cute
[Music]
she got this movie can I name her
Pokemon to Smoothie please
all right then now that we've chosen our
Pokemon we have to battle I'll be
waiting for you down at the beach beach
come join me when you're ready
hope you don't regret choosing that Croc
as you may have noticed Miss pneumonia
is a child overly fond of Pokemon
battling but I do hope you'll join it
for a battle it will help you get to
know your own Pokemon as well
yeah I I just have to deal with it maybe
maybe we can get the cats too as a team
member
probably not though right it won't it's
like not available anywhere else right
unless I didn't play like a randomizer
kind of thing
potion I can shred oh true
let me look for some stuff oh
antidote
we're approaching
we'll
we'll some stuff nice can I get some of
the oranges please I love oranges
um
oh man
oh man this is always a Pokemon so sad I
feel like bad for the leftover Pokemon
poor baby please don't take it
personally it's not you it's me no
actually it's kind of you
sorry
how deep can we go oh
scrambled back out of the water I wanted
to go
to go but okay
I don't think we were ever able to get
so deep into water before in Pokemon
okay before I go to her let me look
around here
oh
Nani
secret path
sacred pass oh
nice oh some music suddenly starts a
Pokeball cool yeah oh yeah finally some
music oh and it stops again what the
hell
fine I guess we're not allowed to listen
to music
oh there's one more
oh the RPG player in me
interesting
uh needs to find all the items
[Laughter]
um
no comment
let's
[Music]
go
[Laughter]
anyone can be at Pokemons right now as
long as you bought a game for 60 dollars
and it's our duty as trainers to help
our Pokemon grow stronger through battle
so you ready to battle me kiwawa yay
Perfecto I'm so excited for this battle
I think I'll use
Miss nimona what did you just say before
how was that about equal footing
oops a good call director I was about to
send out one out one of my usual
Partners right off the bat I guess I'll
take this chance to try out my new body
instead
she it's still not fair even if he
starts with a new Pokemon because she
apparently a ton of experience
right so what the hell
if she's my rival then
this is the least Fair rival ever in
Pokemon history
I am challenged challenged by Pokemon
trainer nemuna
knock knock
oh no
oh
battle
Leah
empty Leia is German for empty it looks
so German to me but it's probably like
Leo
why don't you get to attack first do you
have more speed
oh my God
clear in Spanish for read oh I don't
know but in English it means just
looking I guess
so cute I will forever regret because no
matter who I would have chosen I would
have regret my choice
[Music]
I'm so sad
well level up
crunk is so happy
wow not bad neighbor
thank you yeah you're stupid for
choosing the plants Pokemon
why wouldn't you go for the water one I
guess you just preferred the visuals
over
the fact that it would be smarter to go
for the water one
so wait that's so sad like the duck must
have been thinking oh she's gonna choose
me because I am the most logical choice
to make after her choosing fire
and the deck must have gotten like
really excited and then she goes for the
freaking cat
what the
yeah recently I guess they changed it it
used to be the other way around right
or wasn't there a French and a rival
and the friend would choose the weaker
one and the Rival would choose the
stronger one
right
um
that was only in Jen's life
I'm eating cookie
I got kind of caught up in all the
excitement
um
I'm really sorry koala same to you
political too huh
let's battle again too
[Music]
I think they're becoming friends no
we're not I don't know friends
huh
I want to be a loner
we got the Pokemon
yeah I am
Pokedex will automatically register any
Pokemon you catch
it's a must-have for Pokemon trainers
it's a super handy app our homeroom
teacher Mr Jack actually made it himself
back in my day as I am a boomer we used
ordinary paper and handwritten notes to
compile our pokedexes it's quite the age
we live in now
what the why would you no don't
vote for her
oh man I'm not 100 happy with the
decision either give me a break that
crocodile is so cute
and they they even
they even promoted Sparks
um
we're gonna try to get both unless we
find a different cute cat
the more program on your counter the
more you'll find yourself growing and
changing
go work on your pokedexes
with her parents okay
um
we're going to the academy apparently
why why are they wearing like bathing
shorts by the way
looks like bathing shorts
for the uniform I mean I understand that
we're at the ocean but still
I'll leave her in your capable hands
[Laughter]
you didn't even consider I would take
the Croc what
yeah
you showed through teammates favorite
even gets a cafe Familia
why
oh bubble bubble
[Music]
bubble
maybe I ought to make a little more time
to work on my Pokedex along with all my
battling
all right speaking of pokedexes you've
probably never caught a wild Pokemon
right
I'll show you the rubs before I take you
to the academy come with me
what see she like zoomed out of the
window
or opening your Pokedex press the minus
button to open the Pokedex app on your
working phone in the flash you can also
navigate your Pokedex by pressing X
buttons okay
oh I got 300
um polka dollars in price money follow
the Mona where is it
how can I follow her this is just trying
to find her not following her
uh
ah here she is with my mom
okay Baba I hear that Mona here we'll be
taking care we'll be taking you to
school
that's right ma'am leave it to me
so you've already managed to make a
friend
no no no
don't call her my friend
and I read about all the wonderful
teachers you'll be looking you'll be
happening looking have a look at you
you'll have looking after you at school
plus so many handy this is
a facilities I can't read you
can use as much as you like
add in your new friend the Mona and it
sounds like your school life is shaping
up to be fantastic
[Music]
oh you'll be staying in the school dorm
so I want you to promise we'll be
sleeping in a school though
what wow at least there is a place to
sleep I guess
because I guess in other Pokemon games
you just keep on traveling and traveling
and traveling and traveling and
traveling
well okay
[Music]
um
and lunch hmm
yummy I wish I had a sandwich right now
um
I know everything in your new life is
going to be full of exciting experiences
far from home
try to savor them all the good times and
the hard times too
but if you ever want to come back home
you know your bed is always ready for
you
where's my dad by the way
if he left my mom
then how
did he think he could score better than
this
um
oh all right then it will have better be
off I suppose take care on the way to
school
I'm gonna go home and use Tinder now
time to meet the new guys here
your mother is so nice kiwawa
oh
oh but I was going to teach you how to
catch wild Pokemon come on vamos vamos
you're gonna use little Spanish words
here and there that's fun maybe I can
remember some vamos is what come
I've heard it before vamos
vamos
vamos Amiga
adios
let's go oh vamos vamos
vamos vamos
vamos vamos or vamos
vamos
I Wanna Know
vamos okay
Mama's
all right this here is pocopath
um
everything's so round all these Pokemon
it's the path that leads to Adventure
for you and me out here things are
different than in town you're gonna see
wild Pokemon out and about they'll be on
the path and in the grass and such
hmm get too close to one and you'll have
to battle but you've got four Coco for
that right and if you want to try to
catch a Pokemon you gotta use
a good old Pokeball I've got tons have a
few thank you
I have no idea who to catch and who I
like because I've I don't know
but we'll try to get Pokemon in the team
from this generation preferably
there were a couple new ones in the in
the trailer so
um
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
but I don't know if I would put this
thing in my team
time for some learning by doing try
battling this little chunk it was a
chunk not already
is that new
um by pressing x button throwing a
Pokeball when you're having a hard time
trying deal damage okay
this one's new okay
[Music]
don't kill it don't kill it don't kill
it okay
yeah
don't do that little cute butt
Pokeball go
catch the chunk s
[Music]
wiggle wiggle wiggle wow
I saw by the way that football
shinies did she actually like
try to like purposefully get them or was
that a Quincy dunk
does anyone know I'm curious
the chunk
she was lucky it was Pure Luck
yeah
well put that I saw her Twitter tweet
you know about oh we already got two
shinies this must be a good sign we
probably will get a shiny Magikarp this
time then and I I have to say no you
probably used up your look
to be honest I like the name Le chunk
I like it
it's very chunky
oh number 10.
little cats
tonkatsu a true
is there a Spanish word like Yoo-hoo or
that was awesome you caught the very
first Pokemon you went for I'm crummy
when it comes to actually catching
Pokemon maybe you should give me tips
anyway I have some more pokeballs just
in case not not every catch works out
even more oh okay
never heard of that maybe in Spain
yeah because like the Spanish and Spain
is different right from like other
spanishs
the Asia salad oh yeah Allah
we can the Pokemon then throw the
Pokeball remember that and you'll be
fine
now go back to those wild Pokemon and
catch some of them not all of them just
some of them she gets me that's what I
was planning on doing just some of them
not all of them
hmm
let's wait up at the Lighthouse over
there you can see our school from the
top
bye bye Ben against wild Pokemon yeah
bye bye it said something about said our
button what was that I didn't expect
anything important what is that art
aha
I get my Pokemon
outside of the Pokeball
oh my God there's so many items
everywhere
let's try tomorrow
the ocean is sparkling wow
Alice to aim ah okay thank you
I'll keep it in mind I like this this
speed up Pokemon it's so cute but so you
can see shiny's like
appear you know on the map right but
I've heard there is no real random
encounter foreign that's interesting but
five of me
so okay I hope I found a shot
[Music]
in the show oh what is you
you're weird are you becoming a
butterfly in your evolution
does it become a butterfly is it news a
new new Pokemon
a beta
gen six butterfly so it does become a
butterfly
[Music]
it's from X Y oh it's not meal oh okay
hold on
I probably know the butterfly when I see
it but not this form
I kind of like the speed that I want one
of the speed dance
stop speeding
oh maybe I should have thrown my Pokemon
on it looked up that would that have
given me the advantage
tala
foreign
Revolution
oh we might have to throw it out if it
looks too weird
round
s around
oh I killed it
oh
you're so cute too I know you're an old
Pokemon though is it powerful
probably not right
[Music]
grass flying
it's just fast
not not powerful um
I was looking at the terrain forming
different versions of itself
um
[Music]
it's final form is pretty good from the
flying one
hmm
with the bacon
and you're my dinner
winner winner chunky dinner
spikes learned around or what
see you see that
what
okay
cool
cool a very flexible
um Terrain
kind of stay flexible
it does stretches every morning I
respect that
I want to catch the speed arm maybe I
can get a higher level speed down
hahaha
okay speed that's so cute okay let's try
not to kill it uh oh fire was super
effective what is a grass
you guys have to help me with like you
know types and all the time like
last time because I never remember I
mean I remember the most basic ones bug
type okay so I think fire against Grass
is two times effective and against
buckets four times or the other way
around
foreign
don't you dare resist me
um
what is this close-up
what am I supposed to call it
[Music]
um
it's
so cute
um
what do we call it speed okay
ah
but in Germany
ah but I guess this is better
because more people will read it the way
it's supposed to be read
Pizza
spita has been added to your party party
wow
[Music]
screen
oh
wow what's that what's that
what's that why is it sparkling oh and
there's like hidden items because they
don't show up as Pokeballs
I don't really like the looks of this
one I like all almost every single like
Pikachu of every generation
for this one
it's kind of weird to me also it's
really tiny huh
it kind of depends on what it looks like
later but maybe I should catch it for
now could be useful
looks like a bear
I guess so no hay chickens bears but
I don't know
ugly at all
she's not ugly
we have Pikachu at home
huh why what is this point of view what
is this angle oh this is better okay
all right
no it does not displease me it's okay it
shall lived
inside a Pokeball you know then we have
some yeah good variety we have an
electric type we have a a bug type and
the chunk is normal I suppose
fire so
look at variety
um
thank you my captured see you are now
part of my game documa are you here
's Taco menu Taco man is the one by the
way who made um the famous kfp chicken
and uh yeah
and the the members icons
and my couple of my loading backgrounds
yeah
let's go oh
vamos vowels
mammals
thank you Mama you're getting the hang
of how to catch Pokemon okay she says to
me while we are on the hang of a hill
wait hang that's only German I guess
oh I didn't see it
let me see so far you've got oh wow
hey Pokemon oh no she's surprised about
something else what was that
I tried I did try
Gaga
I've never heard that kind of cry before
could be some strong Pokemon or
something I say we find whatever made
that cry let's
whatever made that Pokemon cry and a
mean mean bully Pokemon must have made
that one cry just kidding I know I'm not
funny but let's take a look around
kiwawa just be careful there's a kind of
unsafe cave not far from here so steer
clear I know your rooting phone can help
you save but watch your step by these
clips anyway
is probably my bicycle right
or the legendary Pokemon is there a
legendary Pokemon besides the bicycle
hmm
see Maybe
oh what why is there so many items
way more than in previous Pokemon games
foreign
[Music]
be careful
be Kiara phone
oh
it is being bullied
I think the taco man
oh
um
[Music]
how can it be bullied by those
[Laughter]
oh my God intense
shout mate oh
made the the mountain Fall Apart
damn yep
uh you good
I guess I wasn't so incorrect about the
bullying
hello bicycle
you are not a dove you're aware of that
do you think you're a doll must have
done something with your head the
mysterious Pokemon seems to be too weak
to move
maybe you can give it something to help
it perk up
hurk up uh
no that's my sandwich
maybe a potion
can I get a potion instead I keep my
sandwich
damn it did I at least keep the potion
done
I did okay
it's my sandwich I was looking forward
to eating that I'm hungry
yeah
photo share
no it's my mom my mommy turned it for me
to eat it
um
you better appreciate it
and become my bicycle prisoner forever
my my sandwich look how sad I am about
my sandwich oh
you look you little
even though you don't look cute at all
um
I'm all impressed
wow what a magical sandwich
bye bye
bye yeah acts like a cat
um
oh
wait
us
huh uh-huh
you want a bully back bully the bullies
that looks like a coffee
bean his eyes closed
looks like a coffee bean oh
what's happening
hmm
well holy I look cute
it's standing on two legs now
wow
those feathers all undertale are quite
pretty
um
[Music]
bicycle can walk
I follow I guess
and now I am forced to walk slowly again
let's go faster or suddenly I can run
again ah if I get too close then I can
only
walk
I think a lot of people prefer the
design of the Violet one
I honestly
think both are weird but
I just chose Scarlet because of scarlet
because of the color
so you said are hot as
there you are Chihuahua wait
there you are kiwama are you okay
you're not her crying
I'm fine
[Music]
thank goodness I was really worried
he's got in the hood because I said we
should go looking for whatever made us
cry no never mind dad right now we've
got to focus on getting you back up here
you've just gotta find some way to climb
out of there if you can get close enough
I'll try pulling you up with one of my
Pokemon's moves
okay let's go
why is this Pokemon even like bringing
me in here I guess it's the only way but
can't it Fly too couldn't it just fly me
up
all right I will not question it
let's not question it
wow that was amazing that Pokemon might
be strong as mine stronger and stronger
and then it cut off immediately when
when Dude wait
what spooky
staring at me from above like that
quite intimidating why not
I did catch a little junk yeah this is
stuff
on the ground
invisible one oh I thought there would
be a
Pokeball there
what the what the what the
what what what
okay
what I am allowed to go here
what what what
just here I can't walk
where where does it start and where does
it end that wall
what I don't
I don't be here or not
I'm so confused okay but there's a
Pokemon ball over there so
let's go there
huh okay well we can't now
[Laughter]
bugging through something but I think
I'm supposed to be able to go there oh
no
what do I know wow immediately
top okay here I can go
um
you tell me that now we have already met
those
[Music]
right now I can walk normally
and now it's normal
that one's weird
oh
glowing stuff reminds me of um
glowing stuff
in every game
hahaha
I guess they had the Minecraft and ryzen
and other games
it looks cool
oh my God it's so strong I wonder what
that move was can you ask it can you
speak Pokemon come on look on
something's coming
um
is trying to break in and kill you
[Music]
oh my God it's coming for blood yeah
it's coming for blood
ah crunch wait I wasn't able to attack
was it I pressed attack what happened
huh
oh I didn't look at the level level 40
I guess my Pokemon was like I'm not I'm
not gonna risk that
wow
eat that tail iron tail or something
like that
no
oh wow wow wow wow wow
oh spread licks wow so spread
don't open it so much because they're
just gonna bite the middle
close your legs
rescue
bicycle
[Music]
yo why are these Pokemon so aggressive
they didn't look like they were like
particularly
influenced by some sort of evil magic
I thought Pokemon are mostly unless
influenced weirdly not aggressive
towards humans
their nest very territorial
[Music]
way to go for a second I thought you
were both but both goners
rip fastest Pokemon game ever
what does it look like that
it melted into a puddle and Ale oh this
is not do well on the Sun or
does it need more sandwiches
maybe it used up all its power do you
have another one of those sandwiches no
no more you already took the one
sandwich I am well this is Pokemon
anyway it kind of looks like a cyclazar
I've never seen one quite like this
before and now it looks so different
from a minute ago you think it's okay
um I don't know man
foreign
well anyway I'm seriously glad to have
you back up here in one piece
you know that battle down there was
really something you and this fella
looked perfectly in the sink facing down
that Houndoom
funny way to call it
what you didn't even tell it what to do
I guess it's not like you're just
Pokemon trainer yet huh
yes I'm independent Beach
oh oh yeah it perked up
happy again
do you think this fella was the one
making that mysterious cry we heard
before meows
oh man oh man oh man the more I look at
this Pokemon the more mysterious it
seems if you do become a strainer you
gotta let me battle against it yo don't
think you have any chance against it but
you may as well try
I will for now just use it as a bicycle
I guess or maybe not now maybe we get it
later
let's exchange numbers with the Pokemon
that review of course so we can get in
touch if something happens
oh I guess the Pokemon has no phone so
I'm exchanging with you after all
yeah this will let you teach your
Pokemon the move to help it battle
stronger opponents Swift
is that good ah the Starship race attack
think before you use it though TMS can
only be used once
you've opened through an app for a
minute I think we better take a breaker
let's just go to Lighthouse that would
be a good spot to relax
weren't we going okay I guess I'll go
first
I am apparently the adult in this
relationship so
I go first all right all right
back to so many years but craftable yeah
yeah yeah didn't they make it like non
shut up I'm trying to explore
not like more than one time used before
and now it's back interesting I guess
that's fine I think that's okay
hmm
why why that little
it's got fluffy nice long hair I like it
what are they doing what are you doing
here oh it's yours
I'm not talking to YouTube you can shove
up
wow Ruda
wait I know you aren't you Arvin you've
enrolled in the humanities track right
and aren't you the son of that Pokemon
researcher Professor Sada
oh he's so mad yo The Sideburns yo
doesn't matter who it is or who I am
the real issue here is what in the world
this Pokemon is doing out here and what
is this performance in
uh
I met it at the bottom of this cliff
see we heard this strange cry and we
tried to investigate but koala fell off
a cliff
that Pokemon saved her but it seems like
it wore itself out in the process it got
kind of slumpy afterward but you should
see you should have seen it before it
looked totally different it was
unbelievably strong
well yeah as it should be but it can't
fight while it's like this The Forum
Corydon takes in battle that's its true
form
status Pokemon's name how do you know it
I don't think it knows its name I think
I think it thinks its name is agnias
hmm
you can't go in the lab it's locked
I don't remember ever seeing you around
but given a uniform you go to the
academy too do you don't you do you say
go to the same school
code I don't listen to sort of Pokemon
that any old trainer can hope to command
is special
hell you mean oh my mom told me I'm
special
uh no I don't think so you'll think
you're up to ordering code right on the
round then how about I test your
worthiness
I don't know we have a difference
Pokemon
I guess we'll just do it
gosh
she's so angry and why I thought he was
nice when I like saw his character
design
I've been feeling all out of sorts so
I'm gonna use this battle to blast these
dull Dreams Away doldrums
you were challenged my Pokemon trainer
Mountain
alrighty alrighty
square
okay by the way I just remembered
something these members are leaving a
bad taste in my mouth and I want it gone
all right one second
I need to do something yeah I'm still
here though
[Music]
I'm gonna use an asset made by magical
mayonnaise
uh
for sure
[Music]
a lot of people made like Pokemon
related assets it's really cool I wanna
use
uh
pink what
oh my God that's amazing
we have it for normal and pink
holy is Pink
I want the shiny one
too late now
okay wait I'm just uh putting it on my
body
but
uh
okay
wow
okay look look in three two one
long and
I'm holding it I am
um
the one you get at the start of shiny
lock well then how do you how would you
get the shiny if the only other way to
get it is the trade
[Music]
operating oh
okay then I guess whatever
that's too bad I don't feel like getting
into breeding
what the other one's just watching
what's what is it doing if it's is it
trying to clean its nose or catch its
own tongue I think it's trying to catch
its own tongue look at it
look at it in the background
yeah
go get your tongue go catch it
reminds me of till plus from How to
Train Your Dragon oh it's true I don't
know what you mean yeah the face shape
is similar I think yeah
a general body shape too I guess
[Music]
foreign
he was talking himself up yeah what the
with a loser
uh you had such good luck getting a
female started burning and Shining would
be totally possible
but do I have to breed it with
a vehicle
or any
any Pokemon
doesn't have to be a political call
I didn't know
with a male did or did I just uh gender
loss
I could use a ditto
whoa
any Pokemon of the egg group
oh little
okay I'll try that
Maybe
but
don't you have to like walk around with
the eggs in order to
uh make them
um hatch
breeding is a lot better in this game oh
okay
and it takes time
I might try like a few times but I'm not
gonna like breed 100 eggs just for the
sake of getting a shiny
oh
you're gonna do it while you read super
chats true
hat during the previous game not sure
about this one maybe not we'll we'll
find out can you not just like leave it
in the like uh in the hands of someone
else and then come back like a week or
so later
um you can breed an egg with any male
Pokemon in her egg groups and you can
affordable oh cool
okay I'll look into it then
that's why you guys were so excited
about it being a female aha
I just got a shiny one
smallest I want this
one unlike any shiny really even a shiny
little chunk would be amazing people so
rare because of that reason oh
I feel I feel special now
[Music]
I guess well but you're a different
person
okay
so anyway
what is it though what does it matter
with this dude
what's the matter
why are you so angry
it's tough in old games on fighter
fighter a Psyduck in blue oh cool
okay wow that was awesome you totally
kicked his butt he's not so cool anymore
now
I guess I was never going to stand up
chance using some Pokemon I'd only just
caught
the Pokemon he just used I guess fits
his hairstyle and color but if you
really think you can take Corydon off my
hands for me you'll need this it's a
bookable that brutes brutes been captain
[Music]
quran's Pokeball
oh thank you for giving that to me so
easily what the hell
a boy named Arvin he doesn't look like a
boy to me and looks like a man
so why do you have it why'd you have it
anyway that's that thing's your problem
now not mine good luck
huh
did you steal it
what the hell
um
one over here though
indeed
but see how oh my God the colors this
was my hair with my Blue Hats oh my God
we're kind of matching
that iron guy definitely knows more than
he's letting on
next time he and I are battling I'm
gonna ring some answers out of him
but all right we gotta climb the
lighthouse can't wait to show you the
view for school okay what the word
laughs
okay but first I walk around it I must I
must oh
can't walk here okay
[Music]
sorry
are you boy
no
we're just making friends right you just
don't bully him
be nice to each other oh nice
nice chunky monkey
[Music]
[Laughter]
s watching oh my God so cute what the
Out of Nowhere Man
it's so cute
and
the thumbnail got you welcome
the fun thing I actually
I made that in five minutes because I
had no time
if I had more time it would have
probably looked very different but I'm
glad it's getting some people to come to
the Stream
yeah
oh wow wow wow
oh
is there an item here too
no okay
let's hold hands shall we
no kiwaba I don't want to because you've
been so mean to me but I will show you
at least this that's messagosa
and the huge building with the Pokeball
on it is our school
wow
damn
it's very
Flex flexing
bam it's gonna be so great having you in
the same class queue out same
here's older
all the schoolwork that
don't think of it as schoolwork think of
it as tons of chances to learn about
Pokemon battling well I mean it's school
is about that mainly then hell yeah I
don't mind that much then
so yeah being Brazilian Portuguese what
does it mean in Spanish
I don't know does someone know
it's probably just like big city or so I
have a feeling that's it could mean that
is it awesome what you can see from up
here
mountains forests grasslands beautiful
nature stuff as far as the eye can see
yeah
beautiful
girls had to enjoy something my friends
Zara goes on
next between Messi plateau and Zaragoza
in actual City ah ah Zaragoza I thought
there was a Pokemon when I first read it
okay could be a Pokemon name
and you know what's waiting for you all
over this natural real spaces tons of
Pokemon
which are also waiting for you to kick
their butts consider this me officially
telling you welcome to paudia
but anyway like you can see it's kind of
a hype to get to school from here and it
really is damn
by the way there's so much space to
build houses why couldn't we have had
one closer let's make it to Los Platos
for status that's right on the way
now we could have lived there
okay vamos
come on vamos vamos
and learnings Espanol
Okay add yours big tower
okay why don't we run into them so
easily
why are you just standing right there
like chunk
so chunky
forced to run into it
anyway
South Province area one oh
oh
leopard Berry ah
Anton
Anthony
don't scare
oh hello
wow so many Pokemon
they're just hanging all the water tops
[Music]
although I don't know if that one is
water
I don't know it's cute I like that one
it's so old though isn't it
a reason from the south of Spain
and it's so cool
ah I want
how to get
oh there's also like a shark or
something no just a normal fish
what kind of fish a goldfish
have to how to get now you I want the
worm
sneak up how do I sneak
how do I
know
left stick flying taxi oh
B to sneak off oh
look at them
it's a powerful dog so football got a
shiny one of that
is
why I was doing a sneak
I want a shiny too oh what the
shake shake and then said R oh ah okay
from a distance okay
not too far
[Music]
how close can I get how about this
huh
Wiglet ah wiggle wiggle wiggle wiggle
wiggle is it is it related or is like a
different version a Paleo version of
that brown Wiglet Pokemon isn't that
also called Wiglet
oh don't kill it
long boy ah it is a protea version Oh no
that's Diglett ah but they're definitely
related don't kill it don't kill it
this one's cuter
I wonder what it turns into though
and I don't know if it's powerful what
is it though is it water water ground or
uh
hmm
no comment
we call it sand
it spawns into free oh so it's also like
uh
yeah okay cool that's cute it's
it's water oh I think
I think a lot of time yet
um
I have a feeling that other members may
have called him this but I can't help it
no boy
[Music]
is it a boy
I actually don't know
it is trendless it's a girl well it's
still long boy
it sounds cuter than long girl
he's a long boy
long boy
you guys tell me when you see a shiny
okay which will probably never happen
ever
ever ever because I'm not lucky enough
the ground keeps on changing holy
long boy
love you long boy longer boy
long
time
[Music]
so far so good
going quite well I have a full team or
almost a full team now
[Music]
Awakening oh
The Awakening
ah
this world is pretty big man oh
it makes me want to like walk everywhere
and check out everything it's gonna take
a while what is that I thought it was a
shiny for a second and since the TM
ah and yeah
and door and door
oh I have more here what what was that
oh that was you
[Music]
we're certainly touching grass yeah I'll
be touching some proper grass
um next week
oh hello
that's that um Treasure Chest Pokemon
thing here
oh oh my God I'm stuck
okay I'm really stuck can I jump
oh
well at least the game recognized that I
was stuck
okay oh
give me gold coin interesting
what is that can I not fight the Pokemon
or catch the Pokemon
[Music]
wow maybe something about this version
only being on oh
Pokemon go and then the treasure chest
being available the treasure chest
version of it being available in this
game yeah yeah I've heard that
because I feel like I got lost I don't
know which direction I was supposed to
go
it's okay though we're just exploring
trying to find more Pokemon maybe a
shiny one
but yeah anyway
um next week
I am going to Italy with my mommy nice
so next week I'll be um we brought oh
[Music]
I'll be rebroadcasting
let me look around maybe I find a shiny
one
I'll be rebroadcasting the cutout okay
and I got
um a new kfp 101 video coming up
and
um
I'll lose one more video
[Music]
so aggressive here
ow
that's that's an old Pokemon
is that a shiny no it's not
oh it's a turtle
I don't need a turtle in my wait this is
water against fire oh but it doesn't
even use a water move
interesting
anyway this is stronger
oh it kind of feels
[Music]
what is that polish
water electric electric
electric right right right right
no I'm not doing a Nuzlocke but it would
still be embarrassing if my Pokemon died
here
what
oh my God
damn
oh we learned a new attack and so I want
to yeah heal all the heel feature will
automatically select items on your bag
and use them to heal your Pokemon to use
other Hill highlight the Pokemon you
want to heal from the main menu and
press the miners button okay we can try
that
oh although healing will use up items in
the following order
huh so I guess it uses the weakest ones
first
oh
that was a big one though
okay
so oh I can't go there right because I'm
just uh Brown
I need to get my bicycle to lead me
first
um I still want the the pink butt there
it is
foreign
let's fight wait it looks really just
like a normal flamingo
soon
is that really a Pokemon or are we
fighting an animal by accident
cat but it failed um
it's just a flamingo a flamingo amigo
amigo
don't kill it try to not kill it
what what is this Pokemon's
uh
elements
fire
maybe fire ground or fire what now fire
water is crazy
fighting flying
oh
so much for flaming amigo
but okay they better make the evolution
of that more interesting because right
now it looks like a freaking normal
Pokemon
uh
well you are my amigo was it a
that's Amiga right
Amiga
it doesn't evolve well that's lame what
all those when it spreads and swings it
looks pretty cool
but what the hell okay oh
Anton swimming around cute go inside yes
into the wall you go you can do it I
believe stupid Dental no wonder you have
head horns
you try to swim into a wall
I wonder
I am lost but that's okay I am
purposefully lost
foreign
[Music]
yet so it's okay but there's like a like
an interesting structure over there
oh
psycho Pokemon isn't it oh and these oh
hello
oh give me coin thank you
oh my God please don't attack me I don't
like this Pokemon at all
[Music]
come out when the streamer collects like
a shot
[Music]
you heard that's a shiny comes out when
I when the streamer clucks like a
chicken really all right you know let's
test it out if it's not true then you're
going to the usual room for one for two
months
foreign
for you
that door was so weird what door
we're gonna fight or what
that's scary now away no way
oh
okay excellent student
that's not a very Spanish name
squawk a building
yes
[Music]
but it failed
is this effective
pretty good probably not the best but
pretty decent
[Music]
it has a fancy hairdo yeah
oh and oh nice critical
[Applause]
strong
wow wow
this mod could be behind that well wait
I lost were you still thinking about the
door what door
one door
[Music]
anyway I did say I'm going to Italy
right well I hope you guys won't miss me
I'm I didn't you know want to go on too
many trips but it looks like I'll be
going on a couple trips you know Italy
and then a Japan but
Italy thing is
um you know because of my mommy I wanted
to
have um invite her to a trip so that she
has
something of a vacation for once because
I mean it doesn't work but I feel like
she deserves a vacation too
every once in a while
and she doesn't I don't think she's very
she's been a vacation since I've kind of
not go up there come on
since I have um I don't know I guess
since I was like a teenager and we went
together on that door
oh there's so much to look at
yeah
um I don't think she's been anywhere
since then so it's been a long time
interesting
[Music]
cute
you both enjoy thank you yeah I don't
think I'll be streaming in this case not
like when I went to Korea I tried but in
in Japan I also try but for this Italy
trip it's not so long and I have um some
videos
so I'll just rely on the videos yeah
oh look at
look at me I thought was literally
transformed like every
[Music]
everywhere
oh my God
damn cool that's a strong one I think
you're cute
[Music]
for um that's pretty rare ooh could I
use it for him
breeding
is it always female maybe yeah it's
female I guess I'll fight you how do I
not kill you does tackle tackle won't
kill you right
okay
well if you find if we um come across
something that I could use for breeding
let me know
because I don't know what you mean with
same egg group
well of course I would have evolved it
first
before using it as a baby to breed
of course
happiness Amazon that's true yeah
uh charge for who
uh-huh oh
[Music]
um
sure
I don't think I'll use it
Alia thank you
we'll be waiting for you very gladly
just wanted to please prepare for both
stop putting Mamma Mia at the random
when you speak Italian
I really miss being part of kfp well
what what you what were you part of
until now
why did you take a break what happened
were you busy
um
[Music]
mommy I'm happy to have some Italian
viewers that therefore are happy
uh that I'm going to eat Dolly had a lot
of work some problem I couldn't keep the
membership oh but you're fat well come
on back
you can give six Pokemon in the party
okay
ah egg mommy my Italy uh well basically
because like oh it's close and my mom
basically I challenged her to prove to
me that she can still speak Italian
and um yeah
that's
where she will prove it to me
and there's a city that I want to check
out anyway because I haven't been there
like I've been to Italy but
um
I think it's always kind of been like
just like cheap vacation cities but no
[Music]
no like like I don't know like the
typical
um sightseeing cities
[Music]
just see some kind of chilly
I don't mean that shouldn't be an issue
you will find out later where I'm going
I feel like I kind of like mentioned it
before
but that's been a while I'm not gonna
say it clearly now
not gonna say it but I'll tell you I'll
tell you once it's time oh
okay okay let's try to get back on track
foreign
[Music]
and it left the coin for me oh it's dead
too bad too bad
oh what the hell
aha items I can't stop maybe maybe the
dead body of that coin Pokemon is down
here no no no okay
[Music]
wow okay okay okay okay okay
um there's a train over then let's go to
him
no foul damage I can jump really
I was thinking it might just like
refresh me and like pick me up and send
me to where I jumped off that was why I
didn't try
cool where am I
uh
well this is the map
oh my God wait what
huh I came from
here baby is that my wall I think so and
I instead of going there I went oh man
oh I totally like in the wrong direction
I just lost myself
[Music]
oh the B Pokemon is over there
there is fast travel no I want to pick
up the item Zone like
so many flowers
[Music]
I heard a bird call
okay let's fight
I can spawn infinitely it was really
really
let's um that's a first I think
[Music]
doesn't look very dangerous though
careful
oh oh oh oh uh what is that time I need
to change it's rock time
what do I have what's strong against
Rock time
so you wanna
okay what a boy long boy no girl
on boys
whoa
it's just a warm it's so cute
attack
oh how what was the level oh my God
wait why
what
what what a lot of seven
oh what else do I have
and the defense dropping
Amika Amiga
I mean Amiga hello HP
buff
or spita
[Laughter]
uh wait a second
fighting type move
damn
well
double kick but will we even be able to
attack first
[Music]
sheesh
or maybe I should heal
let me heal then
uh
and then I attack
the wings are so cute
yeah but once that oh he used something
else not attack okay
oh he's got quite tactics
um but once once he uh even pokes my
Amigas legs they're gonna
crumble
double cake
double okay okay
nice
safe even the critical hit oh we may
have not won if that wasn't
uh a critical I feel like I shouldn't be
here I'm too low level
I'm a bit too early here
hmm
bite
um
uh this
[Music]
I would have won without the current too
you think so
um
[Music]
uh Le chunk
I don't know the chunk is normal I don't
know what's strong against normal it's
like chunks normal keep Amiga in oh
isn't fight strong against normal
ah okay okay
his name is Alejandro
double kick wow
nice okay what else you got last one
I mean I'm not gonna keep this one
forever in my team but at the moment
it's I guess helpful
oh wait what did you say Michael hey oh
that looks fighting
uh well so what's effective against
fighting
oh flying oh nice yo we got a good
combination of moves here
fake out oh
I couldn't move I finished no let me
find there we go
oh okay one more one more oh don't
don't
oh it's not an attack move it looks like
it was gonna attack me
[Music]
yeah
wow that was an experience
I defeated Alejandro de black belt on
black belt and what color karate maybe
but besides that
you're weak I mean okay not that weak
though
Pokemon where
pretty good it's pretty
pretty good
some of these Pokemon are so tiny
it's like kind of hard to see it
his boobs are tiny that what is that oh
the sunflowers seek tiny I would
just run into that
I guess it's realistic
was that supposed to be their size so
[Music]
that's fine
now
I barely saw that
uh so where is the stuff oh where are we
going
am I going the right way now life thank
you
roughly more or less this is where I
left the actual path
[Music]
oh
thank you for 22 years of years to try
to maps of membership
oh
22 years
um
yeah that's um
probably not gonna happen
hello
where the shiny shinies
it sounds about right does it feel like
22 years
at 22 years your icon becomes Chihuahua
yeah we can do that
oh that one that was pretty strong right
especially the evolution
is it grass hi
on it or not
oh
another bubble bubble Pokemon cute
and the dog the dog is
n't what is this time I don't want a
psychic and this one
is it fairy is this one's fairy right
something fairy
two years this one's just fairy ah cute
you couldn't use the bread that's just
free okay please be um male doggle oh my
God
this joke didn't have an evolution
[Music]
elbow does that work still
oh
oh it does
really
Fido or vital fighter fighter so many
puns
does not look for breeding
but but very cute nonetheless let's try
to find a male one and I'll put that in
my team and I'll also um read it but for
now I'm assuming maybe bite is effective
or it's the other way around
okay yeah okay oopsie
oh that's better
[Music]
just lick me oh huh
[Laughter]
that's my problem with dogs they use the
most effective attack against my Pokemon
but if they use it attack if they used
that attack against me personally
that would be an insta kill
oh that's another one
oh they keep on spawning
I'll try another one
please be a boy be a good boy be a good
boy
it's not a good boy it's cute though the
back has like a like a braid on his back
on it
let me run
because I killed your sister
they said she killed bread dog
oh my God
okay
we'll get this one
yeah
do not kill it Sparks
Get It Go Get It Go Get It
then we have a long boy and a good boy
evolved version is immune to fire oh
does it stay fairy only
[Music]
yeah well you guys already know
everything
yeah
Fido will become
far far
and hmm
it's a party
wait don't I already have a fairy
Pokemon like one of these had a fairy
move I think
I can't look at it now though
um maybe in
[Music]
oh so many females
I don't have another fairy not as a fair
yeah but I think one of the fairy attack
okay I'll get rid of um the trunk only
[Music]
no no no no no no no
no
I heard that you wanted to play the game
like yesterday but your game didn't
arrive in time right that's so sad
he's only really here I didn't see him
I heard her voice from Chad wait is she
really here
where did the high oh there is
not the Play-Doh
it was a
Circle choice for me though
I also wanted the cat to be honest it
was so difficult it was really 50 50 in
my mind
so I'm really sad
come on Santa is it outside are all of
them outside
you can come here to take care of a lot
of things related to your Pokemon but
I'll leave the explanations to the pros
here
happy to be of service and welcome to
the Pokemon Center I'm here to keep
everyone's Pokemon healthy
here my left is the Pokemon counter you
can buy things like Pokeballs and
potions
hello we accept payment Bob and cash and
LP League point settings one LP is worth
P1
[Music]
is the technical machine machine
what
Technical Machine
TM machine for sure
it's your ticket to making DMS which you
can use to teach most of your Pokemon
[Music]
you'll need to pay an LP to supply the
machine with materials that Pokemon drop
ah
LP comes in handy both at these machines
and at stores I've got a lot here we
have some
thank you for your donations you think
about charity case or what
I feel insulted oh yeah and some of
these too
oh thank you I'll take that
yes give give
I guess I have a charity
oh
[Music]
not the union Circle you can connect
with other trainers to find yourself
some adventuring companions oh
foreign
never look at the NPCs in the background
guys just saying never in this game
don't look only look at what's very
close to you
come visit come visit us at the Pokemon
Center anytime you need any help
well thanks
remember I had a rough Adventure get to
the Pokemon Center
uh-huh
is that surprise supposed to be rhyming
it doesn't quite sound like it's rhyming
sometimes you have to know this sort of
stuff for quizzes at school but
mnemonics help out
are you ready then let's go
what
[Music]
what's that
new one is
and what
and what is that
memory rhyme this is the rhyme though
what
I mean the other thing maybe with some
imagination Rhymes but this did not
mommy are you ready because you press r
[Music]
it hints add the iron your controller
oh because I because I walk with r where
no I don't walk with Argo
anyway okay let's not think too much
about it
uh goofy shirt but it helps you remember
you can send your lead Pokemon out of
the r but okay
[Music]
um
this explanation is
against
too high level for my low level brain
that way you can have the Pokemons
that's walking with you go pick up items
lying around or go battle on its own or
other stuff like that oh the Pokemon can
do it too
okay
when your Pokemon is low on energy which
happens when it's HP is low it won't be
able to go exploring on its own so if
your Pokemon gets weak try to heal it up
okay when your Pokemon starts to battle
while exploring how this only you won't
need to give any orders it can battle on
its own with all the battles meaning
that you can keep searching the area for
new discoveries while watching over it
from nearby
all the battles will be decided by the
strength for the types of the Pokemon
taken part in the battle so keeping keep
that in mind when you're choosing watch
if your Pokemon to send out on its own
hmm
okay
[Music]
all right next we're supposed to go to
Mesa goza I hope I didn't miss out on
anything uh I think I've been really Pro
so far oh cute little town a village not
even I wouldn't even call the Village
with the big mouth I like this one
it looks so funny
it's cute wait maybe I should heal my
Pokemon yeah you're right
I just remembered
uh can you do it
no I didn't talk I want to talk to the
lady oh I talked to all of them at once
[Music]
I'm about to eat the child oh we
need to save the child
yeah bye
[Music]
summer I've gained an all-female team
yeah mine are also pretty female I could
have gotten a female dog but I went for
a male one on purpose
[Music]
I reckon the information you're giving
me is not very important
oh what is this
juice ice cream ice cream
oh
that Baskin Robbins
sugar and ice is that purposefully made
to look like Sati one Baskin Robbins
it looks like even the like this one
that the packaging looks like Baskin
Robbins and honestly some of these like
the top four ones are obviously not the
bottom two ones because what the hell is
that
but this looks like Baskin Robbins
did they get permission to do this
also one of these things does it like it
gives me like effects but it Paula this
one gives me egg power
this thing
a device such as pattern of letters
ideas or Association of the system
remember something The Alphabet Song is
an example oh
thank you for letting me know
whatever she did was not very helpful
though
I don't know what the effects are for I
guess we don't need them right now
maybe I'll find out what it's for at
some point
item
I do not like mint chocolate ice still
by the way I also don't like mint
chocolate or so in general
South Province area one
well oh there's more of those
of the doors and of those those Pokemon
where is the shinies though
why do you hurt me like this what you
want you because you want
I just don't like it
oh
that's the word power
Pokemon
they're so cute
there was my favorite Pokemon routes
is it the one with the green hand
self Province everyone oh I guess I'm
already which is the right direction
direction
I'm not sure
that's the one from home yeah I think
it's pretty popular
um
yeah it turns into Gardevoir and garden
was really strong right
I don't necessarily feel like you know
getting an overpowered team doll I just
wanna
I don't know choose whichever Pokemon
speaks to me and even if it's weak
we're gonna try our best to be a good
trainer
yeah
that's the spirit
but one shiny would be nice
talking about it just like seeing other
people get Chinese really made me want
to get one too I want to be lucky I want
that legendary stream of moment like oh
and everyone loses your mind
over it that's what I want to happen
yum
what is that
I just speed that
I'm gonna lose my way again I'm sorry
guys
what do you think oh item of course the
more I explore the higher other chances
of getting a shiny
that's cool
this wall is really big I don't think
there were Pokemon worlds this big
before
[Music]
it feels like really big
so that's a good thing
a good thing
the grass looks good too
mostly
okay I'm just gonna say positive things
those negative things I will not say
they're obvious enough I'm not gonna say
anything
what's that a squirrel
somebody sues
only need to place less items but that's
a negative thing
so I will not say it but I'm just saying
that I'm I can't
I was gonna say I can't control myself
there's freaking items everywhere
ah
got home from school hello
let's fight
oh speeda wants to watch so cute see a
positive thing
that the Pokemon are watching you
partially oh it's walking away already
lost interest she's like this is
going on a tangent
what do you think
gold pen
uh
I don't know what's effective
what should I try poison I don't know
what's good against poison
now Amber should work alone
[Music]
you're gonna make me yawn even more
foreign
[Music]
oh that's it okay bye bye
I'm going downwards I missed some stuff
look I also Mr trainer actually
yeah I totally did
should I go back
is my Pokemon sleeping now
are you sleeping no no right you don't
stay asleep right
you can get a Pikachu with mystery is it
like a special Pikachu again
like with a hat or something or it's
just a normal one
small
uh
seeing a child that small in such
clothes
irritates me as the flying because
oh also is what is this thing again
water oh man does this bite work maybe
maybe I should switch
uh
Kuma
no no
thanks
oh well hopefully it works with dakuma
too
ah uh not exactly ago only a couple
games I have to ask specifically for
Catherine
oh
oh let's try this
water after ah oh
wow and analyzed
steak
oh
nothing happened
he really
foreign
[Laughter]
oh my God you're right we have some
water here I'm running out of water
Where's my water thing oh I think it's
in the other room
I'm gonna go grab some water okay
[Music]
foreign
who needs a cat in the game when you
have two lovely cats
in real life huh
spreads
that's not a secret though
I got chunky wonky on my lap you know we
were home when I was struggling to sleep
uh she was really helpful in
making me sleepy again
letting me
keep my hand on her belly the whole time
no
and purring and purring and purring
so much she's a good cat yeah switch
should I switch Pokemon Hound door
that's a double I don't know is what
type that is
[Music]
she's so boring I think she was sleeping
uh should I use Wiglet
okay
long boy
[Music]
oh wow you look cute she's still so warm
yeah new here it's getting really
freaking cold
holy Wiglet looks huge from this
angle okay find my chunky monkey I'm I
will miss you I love you oh boy
it's pink long boy is Big Boy
[Music]
danger noodle
and one more
and a perspective yeah I think this one
is this oh actually wait
the boy is
like it's not even just the angle it's
just the warmest like way bigger than
the boy
cat hair
this wasn't supposed to be such a big
Pokemon though I mean look at me in
comparison and then just look at that
thing the worm could eat up the boy and
it's even longer because like you
consider that some part of it is in the
ground
that shit's terrifying
poor kid
having to see that
is
what the hell means poor boy traumatized
for life
what's up here
any shyness
I'm so hopeful I still got so much help
in me
sooner or later
none of that will be left don't worry
the grass is like a jungle to him
foreign
[Music]
Iris
Iris I was on the break now right and
when she comes back she'll
[Music]
go
should look different
right
I'm sad because I really liked her like
OG looks
I really did like it I don't know if I'd
like them
especially like this seems to be like a
pre-evolution but I think it's the
monkey because it looks like it
I don't learn I don't really like the
monkey I don't like it
no need to catch it in my opinion
a monkey
oh yeah the whole attack
can I be honest I I feel like
I didn't do her justice
because how can you do her justice in
one and a half hours
like there's so much to talk about
there's so many Clips I could possibly
show
and yeah
and uh yeah in this case otherwise time
pressure too so I had to rush for the
questions I didn't want to do any less
questions than that because it felt like
already I wanted to ask more things
nah you could have done an eight hour
interview it wouldn't be enough exactly
couldn't buy us because
you know
but I don't think it's just that I
really think
it's just hard to do her justice in my
opinion
especially when her whole
thing is you know being a great
Entertainer so having a serious
interview
well not
and it's not easy to
give up the same Vibes I mean we have
some have some moments
like the monkey moment
but
um
[Music]
foreign
I mean you guys are very nice and all
but
I just had this feeling that
it was not so great
um I mean it wasn't like outright bad
either but I feel like
you know the good thing is I guess that
I didn't really need to do her justice
because everybody knows because
like even if you don't watch
uh Japanese YouTuber mainly you still
like see Piccolo's clips and you see her
everywhere I feel like it's hard to not
know her and not know her greatness
and her charm
oh another of those monkeys
I don't want to kill me on the Pokemon
you guys
thank you
[Music]
I had to cover three years of pickled
history in 1.5 hours yeah I mean I kind
of
managed to
to do better though with the others who
have been in whole life even longer than
her
foreign
so much to talk about you know
um
wow that was not even effective was it
I mean not super effective
damn I'm too strong
[Music]
I'm not comparing myself to others I'm
comparing myself to myself when I did
better
uh covet what's that
I'm daringly important to try and steals
attacks held on him oh no I don't care
about that
I don't think we need that doesn't sound
strong
um
nah that's just because it's Petco door
simplifier
well I mean as I said it wasn't like
just really bad it was I just felt like
I could have it could have been better
in general
um
[Applause]
I'm not so 100 happy but
I think
it's also important to be critical
unless you think you could have gotten
out of her I don't know I mean
the questions
you know I chose them from the audience
and some of them were my own questions
um
[Music]
it's hard to say
the pencil color well that was her
choice okay and I respect that but in
the end she said secret so that's good
we got an answer you can just put secret
onto the the
the compilation thingy
I like this one I like this Pokemon
also I was happy that morning Senpai was
watching wow quite surprised
she must really like pecorro said bye
you guys talk about hello project yeah
and I wanted to talk more about it but
at that time we were already over one
and a half hours and
um due to I guess like she has to make
it like shorter because of her voice
being kind of rough so I wanted to
end it around one and a half hours as
she asked but I couldn't there's just
too much I was so blah blah s for the
questions but like what can I do
wing attack ooh
60 hundred oh that's definitely better
than Peck
hmm
I am very glad however that I got her
um to participate very grateful for that
before the
um anniversary
and now I'm done with the third gen
I know I am missing a certain
local princess
but yeah we're gonna move on to those uh
fourth gen
foreign
[Music]
let me go over there there's an item
is there no opening should I have
entered from that side or can I go over
the
ishi no
oh
well hacker
oh can't wait for Luna you know him oh
um
luxury ball
oh yeah
nice I feel like normally you wouldn't
find such a ball
so like early in the game
they are quite generous
anyway
anyone you
um
yeah I I was also really nervous and
really stressed
uh in general today and I was not
the best
I hope
that the 25th episode will go better
because I want that one to go well but I
think
25th episode you know is gonna be
special
because of the 3D gimmick and all that
so
yeah
so afterwards I'm gonna be
um after the Stream
I have to get into VR and hopefully
everything will work smoothly I still
have to compile some questions for
myself though
so that's what I have to do after the
stream quickly compound questions and
cook something yeah
[Music]
yeah next part kind of long
this part I still have time like I feel
like maybe one or two more hours
is okay
but it's gonna be a long day for me you
know I I kind of I wanted to fix my
sleep schedule a bit for you know the
sake of going to a trip with my mom and
also in general because yesterday I was
able to fall asleep so early so I was
like oh that's great but then again I
have to stay up quite long today
because I have to record that thing at
midnight oh
[Music]
I have time to meet the red girl really
really
wow
foreign
circumstances if I didn't wake up in the
middle of the night I would have easily
gotten up at the latest at 10 am today
and would have still gotten so much
sleep like I literally fell asleep like
at 1am or half past one or so
so stop on me I was just
especially tired yesterday I don't know
why it's not like I didn't get so much
sleep before that but yeah
yeah I fell asleep so early but then my
mind was like I'm gonna wake you
up right now and Trigger you
um I don't ever have a whole live
Indonesian Hotel yeah I think I will
um
I said seven
and yes that is for me in the middle of
the night because I was in the middle of
a deep sleep
there's about some trainers on the hill
bet your Pokemon are getting stronger
how about you show me how much you all
have learned in the battle oh
okay I did not expect that I should have
probably expected that
all right nothing like having a friend
around
come on QR let's have us a fruit from
Battle
um
why you go so far
come closer
pulling off
what is that like
what is that glove is she like a
superhero
[Music]
oh now you show me that
it hurts azina's cat
you seem like you're getting better at
this so I'm coming at you with two
Pokemon this time oh well I got a full
team baby
[Music]
wrist issues oh no on
if you don't like our Fridays or so
yo I feel sorry for her
go next
the cats
being burnt into ashes
Tommy oh I'm not the same Pokemon
um
I don't know what's effective against it
though it's electric it was strong
against electric ground
maybe flying oh no
ground
ah wait I got this one that's ground but
it's also water
flying is weak oh
[Music]
well
I'll try anyway
Crown makes it immune to Electric oh
[Music]
look at cool that's a good double type
then
foreign
[Music]
part two sometime I don't know if that
will happen but
[Music]
oh it's not double tap upstairs hello
anyway
oh it's the crystallizing
I
still alive
[Music]
parasolizing is always a solid strategy
it gives moves of the Pokemon stereotype
more power
it's not fair not fair
[Music]
illegal Paris flies and gives a real
blue see
I did not I was not warned about that
what the hell
[Music]
long boy is no more boy
I don't know what to do
go go can I use that too why can I not
use it this is so unfair look she
knows I'm new
Skyline on me
oh no no hold on uh
[Music]
unbelievable
no
what yeah wasn't I faster before
huh
what the
was it a time a speed time oh is it then
random
[Music]
anyway this should kill it please
spikes
wow
that looks to me like Pokemon abuse
crystallizing your Pokemon it didn't
really
look healthy I think I must report you
to the authorities for Pokemon abuse
man I can't believe how fast you're
improving even though I totally cheated
by using something that you don't even
have access to yet which is the gimmick
of the game and makes the Pokemon way
more powerful yeah this was totally a
fair fight
[Music]
amazing what gets you taking on a
terrestrialized opponent and winning no
problem it was a problem
come to think of it you can't dress the
lines your Pokemon yet huh I totally
didn't knew that and totally didn't
abuse that
you guys are trying to defend her
you should be on my side
don't worry I'll get you taken care of
uh-huh you're better you still got the
Pokemon battles I forgot how new you are
to the stuff sometimes uh-huh uh-huh
anyway it was fun to tell you here have
some advisors thanks
sure that's why we're never gonna be
friends
that's exactly why
keep doing
what he's doing one's dead
oh you guys make me angry
[Music]
now messagosa is waiting just past his
gate at last the city and where our
school is
there's a ton of hills and stairs and
stuff in the city so I'm gonna take a
quick breather and then we'll catch up
with you soon
okay
are we going inside I want to stay
outside
okay
though it's okay I'm on this movie side
me too
but reals movie that's not familiar when
you see in the game if that's what you
think
[Music]
um
well oh my God it looks like rhizome
remember
I think ryzer too
[Music]
it looks like
like uh
um
how do I say this
rhiza two
um I had a city like that that looked
like this
um but
prettier
all right here I am we finally made it
huh
look it up look my strings look into my
streams and ride the two
where's this one sitting that had kind
of like the same Vibes and uh was like
also colorful like this and it had like
you know like over there you see those
flags up there yeah and had stuff like
that it was very similar I think it was
also trying to have this kind of Spanish
flare I think
um
the biggest city in paldea
it's been a big trade Hub since a long
time ago lots of folks come here to
learn about advances in technology and
all kinds of other stuff
Disney World nah
there's a hair salon that was a dog face
though on the logo was it for dogs or
for me well you can change your look
plus places with tasty food and fixings
when you want to see first koala
on the hair doesn't have other
hairstyles though because if not then I
don't care
[Music]
I didn't have you packed for a big
either
well I guess I'm not a big eater but I
like foof who doesn't like foof
we don't have rice at his home prices
based on Barcelona good thing it could
be but that's smart you can't battle
well of a growing tummy right
oh and speaking of battling I want to be
sure you'll be able to terrestrialize
your Pokemon to kiwawa there's a few
things I've gotta I gotta get done for
that to happen but I'll take care of
them
meanwhile you just have fun looking
around the city a bit
there's so much to do grab a bite buy
some accessories to spice up your
uniform you want my if you want my
personal recommendation you've got to
see the deli bird presents they sell
handy items for Pokemon to hold
this place is huge
once you've seen your fill we can meet
up again in front of the school just be
ready the stairs after school are no
joke
can we not what about
well this this place is not built for
people with disabilities what if someone
is in a wheelchair how are they supposed
to go huh
[Music]
later then get pumped for some
parasolizing
um
pretty life for watching five minutes
Oh you mean what's happening uh uh
NYC no no no no I I'm that's just
they're just showing it but I'm not part
of it I mean they're showing my thing so
I'm part of it but
pasqui lava is part of it not me
[Music]
there you go there you go
vamos vamos
item found
what did I pick up
a click to the wave because I tossed
this thing
that looks like a bottle opener it is
right it's supposed to be a bottle
opener
that's funny
so let's go for discrimination
maybe I will maybe I will if they
underestimate me maybe I will
ooh stairs more stairs
no escalators no AB elevators no ramps
nothing
fun
I love crabs
[Music]
chill chill and more ice cream
but the crabs oh they look good
yummy yummy yummy
thing
oh sliding down the stairs is dangerous
don't
that's not how that is pronounced it is
almost drowned myself
and where to go next
ah
I went sideways again but I probably
should just go straight
ahead to not waste too much time should
I should I
don't know
I'll go straight
I'll go straight I'll go straight what
is this balloons can I have a balloon
Oh
I thought I could buy one they look cute
looks funny
okay I go up up up oh thank you so cute
Hello me save the bees
oh more ice cream
ice cream new screen
and things can I enter
oh
go For Broke Grill
oh oh
Spanish food oh I've had this a couple
times before
I have a Spanish friend
every time we meet at conventions
I get a taste of a potato tortilla yeah
[Music]
it's like an omelette but with a lot of
potatoes and onions with a lot of oil
a lot of oil I wonder if you can make it
you know airfryer but I was told that
Spanish people they love to
um use a lot of oil when they cook
hmm
this I don't know is
[Music]
the roast vegetables have a pronounced
Umami flavor they're great as a side
dish or even
what is that
what what is that
I can't really it looks a little bit
like a lot of tacos next to each other
but I don't know
versus vegetables but like what
[Music]
eggplant and bell peppers
mm-hmm
it looks good the pictures the food
pictures look so good
I don't like seafood but this looks
incredible
which is what
helpline
oh
can I go in here why is it free of the
same next to each other
ananya
Seafood fresh Fresco so much Seafood oh
but I look so good
[Music]
oh my God
wow
maybe I should get into Seafood
oh my God
the food is like
highlight more crabs and what is this oh
ski ones
Kebab
um
oh well you also have rice balls it kind
of doesn't quite fit it I guess but
maybe
like pinchitos
why is it called kebab
that's not Spanish but pinchitos is
Spanish right
yeah
was to stop shopping online
Cafe
Seabreeze Cafe
what's that Alpha horse the light
country texture is very enjoyable these
treats go well with like a bit of coffee
what is that what is it looks so good it
looks good okay
I've had this before too
[Music]
um
making me hungry
[Music]
that dessert looks so good I have to go
to Spain on a food truck but I don't
really like most of the seafood
if it's like not Broad and
I might give it a try
hey
yummy I think I had a quesadilla in
Italy though
I think that's where I ended I'm pretty
sure
but what am I buying oh
oh okay no I don't think I need any of
this now thank you though good to know
that's here
um
fashion
we have to look at that
Spain has the best food markets
lots of other food aside from Seafood
now the potato omelette for example what
is this gloves
mittens
oh they're cute but I would if I spend
some of my money now then I would spend
it on something that's like more visible
than the gloves
but that's a cafe ready
yeah a knockout
um
I'm Gonna Change oh this is shoes
ah
socks
glasses
hats
I like my hat though one about pants
is there
No Pants Store them
new kicks no no necessary now oh wait
that's that's something too and that's a
hair salon
backpack wow
and what about time too what is that
[Music]
it was the first one
last deep out for clothes
tablecloth
why
do we need one
oh is this a cup
bottle oh all kinds of like picnic stuff
a yarn ball
for picnics hmm
[Music]
what
oh
wait that's it
someone said left on the d-pad
wait I can only change everything
besides the uniform
and no no
I mean in terms of like we only saw like
shops for socks and all that but what
about
what about the clothes themselves this
part
head okay sucks to be a student can we
go back to the way things used to be
because
wow those are some oh oh hello obs
was I gone
wow I like this hat so did you hear what
I said I was saying interesting how her
color theme is exactly like my color
theme white orange and some blue and a
little bit of black too
it's exactly my color theme hello
everybody
um glasses they look nice
but uh how do I get rid of them
whoa leave about changing whatever
so I'm sad I want to change my outfit
why do I always have to wear the uniform
I want to graduate right now
let me graduate
oh what is this
books
these look like I can't enter most of
them
don't be so dramatic you guys oh bread
what is this
I think I've seen that one maybe
is this
looks good
huh what is this stuff
fresh promise look no further than Delhi
Kyoto
what is that
whoa yummy combined and make into
sandwich oopsie
but not now since I'm not really buying
anything anyway right now I should
probably go but oh this is
these cheese
it could be cheese right
sure cans oh
oh never mind it's not cheese I thought
it was cheese
canned food
okay okay okay okay stop wasting time
okay stop wasting time stop wasting time
I go to these one more time
Pump It
didn't they just turn the other side
when I was on the other side
[Music]
oh yeah there are some buildings you can
enter I think
but most of them have no interior at all
[Music]
but I mean I understand because there's
so many places here normally I think oh
it's that L button lock on okay
I think in previous Pokemon games the
cities were generally smaller so
yeah I guess here because the city is so
big
it was not feasible
I would guess to make everything so that
you can enter it
and trying to trying to defend them here
not not saying that it's that it's a
good thing but I do understand the
decision
I think oh
open camera
oh
is that girl
and people are also from our school
don't you get it if you join team star
you can shine as bright as anybody
that sounds positive also she's wearing
high heels I just saw
what's with you don't you want to burn
bright with awesome friends like us
not really
look we've got a quota we're supposed to
fill for new members so just sign up
already
um I'm driving not
hey oh okay oh
okay I'll help
it's like if I'm not ready to fight I
guess I could
[Laughter]
huh you want it on this too
if you're here to sign up we'll get you
next we've nearly got this one in the
bag
my team's that kid we burn some bread it
hurts to look at us what's new then
right
uh
is that like your slogan
and I don't know what to say about that
that is a bad slogan I don't know if
you're trying to insult yourself or
impress me
it's really giving me mixed signals
ah
yeah
oh yeah I knew that
so you know exactly who you're messing
with and you're still coming and as with
that attitude
you're scary kid if you join team star
you'd be looking down from the top in no
time
oh oh that's it
that's a praise they're impressed by me
oh
why is she reacting like that hey we
can't just let something like this line
it
do one of our teams on the line so we've
got no real choice but to about what
what did I what did I do how did I hurt
their honor
I even said I know about them
how did I insult their honor
different
did I do it's like I can't do anything
right
am I tell I guess I'm I'm interrupting
them okay that's enough cause I guess
and
that's true you keep watching on that
little four eyes over there I'll make
sure this fresh face Nobody ends up
seeing Stars
AKA team Stars
okay that was good that was good because
you know when you die when you kale you
have like stars over your head that
[Music]
was a good pun
ah you got this monkey thing
that doesn't look like a monkey at all
in that stage
I'm guessing it's probably dark time
so maybe not the best Pokemon on my side
I don't know can I switch
poison normal okay that does not help me
at all
just Amber it really
foreign
oh that's pretty good
[Music]
how long are you stringing for
um
I think not much longer because I got
some things to do I'm sorry I'm really
busy today I had a whole talk and then
immediately I am here doing this and
then afterwards I have a recording and
then I have to sleep
yeah I'm sorry I am also generally tired
I need to take care of my throat but hey
tonight I I did turn on my my humidifier
and I feel like it helped I haven't felt
like I felt the other days when I woke
up
I just had two more hours but that was
half an hour ago I said one to two more
hours half an hour ago
I think
I am tired but I'm still holding up
pretty well say holding up pretty well
yeah don't forget to eat later yeah the
thing is I have to cook first I could I
could just order or sell and save some
time but I have hellofresh ingredients
to use up I really have to
when will the next room you're just
communicating with me for the super
chats
um next stream will be on Sunday
whole attack with myself wow
the way she beat you does that mean I
gotta battle this kid though since I'm
high up team Stars ranks
hello Buena what
pero Bueno Bueno means good
and what is pero pero pero pero what do
you think you're doing
it's that student council weeaboo
she's gonna report us if we don't book
it
oh but
but good oh well it's like well well
I can't believe you koala you don't have
to go find Randalls to battle you'll
have all the battles you'll ever need
with me
scares me
that's not really what happened it was a
team starplunks um
wait they picked the fight with you wow
I read that the wrong way sorry
you don't seem to be a good reader
I get it now you two have got team start
written all over you for sure
I bet he were trying to pressure people
into signing up again weren't you oh oh
no how evil oh hi we were not doing that
we weren't weren't not doing them well
that explains it as head of the student
council stopping this type of nonsense
would normally be my job
but there's also the perfect chance for
you to try my amazing and ultra rare
gift to you
oh
is it time
[Music]
Tara orb wow it's so sparkly it's a
Pokeball
Pokemon
an orb that holds within the power to
crystallize when it is charged with
energy it can be used to cause Pokemon
to characterize wow
wow I've got the power that is fancy let
me take a throat candy
[Music]
with this tear up you can direct slice
your Pokemon during battle let's see
after terrestrializes I'm pretty sure
you're full of cocoa will be a fire type
normally you've got to take special
classes to being able to get one of
these Terror orbs but I put in a good
word for you
correct
just once again
proves the corruption now time to give
it a whirl you learn how to use it
faster but then if I just explain it to
you
wait what you want this kid to practice
wailing on us with a terror Pokemon
there's the other we got a problem you
wanna battle me instead
never mind I'll take my chances with
these new kids
then take your places and battle
hmm
power of nepotism
wow
thank you I guess
I'm gonna mention where when I did not
mention gura
you seem to be
you need to take a chill pill dude and
reach the rules
tarantulas here in the Paleo Region
Pokemon can crystallize through a
strange phenomenon the people call this
terrestrializing you can terrestrialize
your Pokemon by selecting the tourism
button in battle
when a Pokemon terrestrializes its type
changes to its terror attack moves of
the same type as this stereotype will
become much more powerful than usual
but do I see there are Terror type in
the
Pokedex
when I catch them or not in the I guess
not in the Pokedex but in the in the
report of the specific
I can see it okay okay okay because not
everyone has the same type as their
original type right
me you want me to name a Pokemon after
myself or you want to name your own
Pokemon after yourself you can do that I
don't think I'll name a Pokemon after me
though
okay
after tarantulizing on Pokemon once you
won't be able to respond to Pokemon
again
until you heal up in a Pokemon Center
oh okay
but
unlike the uh
like sword and shields
I think it's sort of Shield
you could only like what was it maximize
or whatever your Pokemon like one
Pokemon per battle or so or only special
Pokemon but terrestrializing you can do
with any Pokemon right so basically I
can do it six times per fight if they're
all
ready
[Music]
or can I still only do one terrorist
analyzing for a fight even if I have six
of them
one charge per Pokemon Center
only one Pokemon per fight okay oh
I guess I'll do it with you
foreign
[Music]
I like the effect
I think I like it
wow one hit kill
wow so you're like
okay I know what you want I like it
definitely yeah
yo the girl is dancing in rhythm
he cute
[Music]
nice kiwawa you pulled up to
rationalizing no problem most of your
Pokemon stereotype will hit even harder
when it's to rationalized you know
sometimes you'll find a Pokemon whose
stereotype is totally different from his
usual time
it's gonna open up your stretches your
options gonna charge your Tower orb at
the Pokemon Center after ever used by
healing up your team though
um
that's a bit annoying
well I'll be on my Merry way then yeah
hasta la vista me too
baby
indeed
so yeah Teamsters basically a group of
students that like to kick up travel
they hardly ever show up to class and
when they get together in groups their
real headache even the teachers don't
know what to do with them from what I
hear
uh excuse me
oh
I just um oh thanks
uh see ya
oh
very very quiet time
you won't need to use Terra Crystal
often
yeah yeah it doesn't seem very necessary
maybe only in like big important fights
like trainer
um
Arena trainers the bosses
ah look at Yuki Wawa already becoming a
big hero around campus I don't think
I've seen a girl around maybe she's a
new transfer like you yeah probably
she's the new one who was supposed to
get the new Pokemon not you but maybe
she'll get the duck
that Evie back though I love that fluff
it's a cute bag
anyway it seems like the travels died
down so I would better book it up to
school
get ready to climb the worst steak
staircase in the world
um
I hate stairs upwards down is okay but
that's crazy
insane that's not even all because like
you come from all the way down there
it's that time's free what the hell
are they trying to like
kill us especially like there's surely
students who have asthma and they're
gonna get an asthma or heart attack
trying to get up there
I don't think
that that is very safe
and if you you know I have this this
phobia this is maybe the only phobia
that I have if you can't even call it
that
um
falling down like stumbling over my legs
and falling down the stairs
I like so often I imagine that while
going downstairs I absolutely terrifies
me so I always try to hold on to the
rail because I'm so all right like
can't
nope nope nope nope nope nope nope
that's so scary because if you fall down
the stairs
that can be very painful and dangerous
especially if it's quite a lot of stairs
um
[Music]
Magic
oh heal
nice
should I just go straight up
I've been like running around so much
but we do need some story
because I'm trying to get like as far as
I can
today I mean it doesn't really look like
I'm trying but
I try as much as I can as an RPG addict
but uh yeah the thing is like next week
um
I mean I think I will have some time to
play Pokemon next week
but not too much and I uh
I
yeah this is the only time I can play it
this week I think
on Theory I could maybe play it before
whole talk on Sunday but I don't know
how much time I'll have really because I
gotta edit the pre-recorded thing and
stuff
I'm probably gonna subtitle
the whole talk rather than
um you know
drop myself
after thinking a while about it
hello guys you got Style with those
glasses
those team start gets a little scary
don't you think
I hear that team star race is around
every night running on weird cars of
some kind oh
thank you lots of Honor thank you
happy you think so
thank you
I like the music here
[Music]
no um you mean our subtitle team no no I
have to do that myself but I think
um you know I was thinking I write
things down so fast on my memos all the
time when I do hard talk but subtitling
properly is quite a bit of work but it
should be enough time if I have a day
be all right
it may not be as pretty as
a professional subtitles do it but
I'll be all right
he's waving at me this here's the
entrance hall
oh holy
what are all these books about
it's like they didn't know what else to
decorate with so they were just putting
books everywhere
yeah I will never be able to say Psyduck
to that thing
you can sign up for all kinds of classes
at the desk behind me really and those
Halls off to the sides lead to all
different parts of the school
it's only big enough to let loose and
battle in here but for some reason they
banned Pokemon battling in the main
entrance oh well that's fine I think
that makes sense
it would be kind of in the way
Miss nimona
how did you find your first school
commute I I don't think I really
I guess commuting is going to school but
only the path to school
and not going inside the school
being a day in the school
just a path is it just a path
well then
then I say uh it was
um full of tangents and long as
but we had a blast
um
I imagine Miss pneumona's High Spirits
helped with that she's a true asset to
our fine Academy
not that I was expecting any less from
our champion ranked champion
okay whoever was
um protecting defending her when I said
it was unfair
when she was fighting with me
then you still want to defend her do you
still think this is fair
okay maybe they already said that I
don't know but I think
this is the first time I read it out
loud at least
holy
how can you still defend her she's a
champ who says um
[Music]
and over now so I can Flex to little
kids who are just starting out I'm gonna
fight them and pretend it's fair
unexperienced new trainers who are
smaller than me and have
absolutely no experience
just to make herself feel better and
push her ego
am I not the champion now that I beat
her
but I guess it was not an official
Champion battle and maybe the actual
current champion or someone else
also she's even council president
everything
he's rich
she's council president she's a champion
she lives in a mansion
oh my God
what is it with her she's like
overpowered
champion
foreign
protagonist she's the protagonist
clearly
well I know how to look after my friends
[Music]
oh but speaking of which we saw some of
those team star kids in town director
you date were
it was down the stairs from the front
Gates they were hassling the skid with
an Eevee backpack
but it's quite new so are they still to
be found out there
it's like wow flexed on them
that's right I did
and ran off
you don't say
of course it's a fun thing to try to
help a fellow student Miss qwell but you
might wish to show a bit of restraint as
you find your feet here at Old Academy
excuse me
what was it supposed to do
and Mr Mona do you remember that the
school staff is here to resolve any such
troubles oh well if you're not there to
help
because you're just hiding inside like
cowards because you know they
won't come to school because that's
their whole thing not coming to school
maybe if you want to protect people from
the ones who are not coming to school
the best place to be at is not the
school
no too much logic
excuse me I'm so sorry I'm so sorry
ah right yeah whatever sure you make so
much sense director
a child with an Eevee backpack you say I
suppose that might have been miss penny
I'm relieved to hear she's come to class
at least
oh and Miss nimona if you'd be so good
to report to Mr joke about this team
star business as your homeroom teacher
who should be kept apprised of all such
goings on you got it sir
am I coming along for that please tag me
take me to
oh but look at the time oh no YouTube
has better hurry along classes will be
starting to oh are we actually gonna
like see
classes
um
hello
oh
really
[Music]
this was not a happy really
I mean it's cute because we had desks
like that also in green but okay okay
good morning
[Music]
hello hello everyone we have some
exciting news this morning who wants to
hear it
oh my God
[Music]
laughs
I suppose I should have told you sooner
but we have a new little friend joining
our happy home room as of today
[Music]
whisper whisper whisper wait where am I
I don't see myself I guess I'm not
sitting down here oh I'll be in second
row probably
I wanna be on the window
s sits
[Music]
you really should just make them all sit
still
so that I wouldn't notice
because the ones that sit still I see
them blinking in slow motion but it's
less noticeable
could I trouble you for a few words
introducing yourself no no no I do not
talk
what oh the difference
did you hear that she seemed super
friendly and fun
looks like everyone's eager to get to
know you keep one one all right then who
wants to be the first to ask our friend
a new question and that's kind of
uncomfortable
it's not a blinking
[Music]
can I have a question who who dares to
talk to me is out
respect
what's your favorite thing about Pokemon
uh
the Pokemon are you asking about Pokemon
the game then I would say it's Pokemon
but if you're asking about Pokemon the
Pokemon
one of my favorite things about Pokemon
is that I can kill people with it
just kidding I like
Batman collecting playing no
[Music]
I like everything about Pokemon
everything
really awesome
I saw him wait who's talking the boy in
the front
the girl on the right is killed her eyes
are so cute
come on
[Music]
does anyone else have a question for the
new classmate
[Music]
nimona really
me I have a question
you went to all the travel when rolling
here so spill kiwawa
that doesn't fit in she's too tall
what do you hope to get out of it you
must have some kind of dream right
I want to be a strong trainer
I should say I want to be a champ I
guess our protagonist doesn't really
have the goal of being a champion
oh I just know it you and me were going
to get so strong battling together
well thank you for telling us a bit
about yourself
I missed a joke I teach biology here at
the Academy I'm also completely confused
about how I should be talking
[Music]
that's your seat second row from the
front
oh
okay
thank you
all right you ragamuffins be nice and
friendly to our new classmate
[Music]
it's interesting how it does not affect
um nemona and me
hmm
[Music]
oh that's better now it's way better
I'm exploding a bit on your own okay so
now it's fixed
I would have expected the opposite
because that was a cut scene but okay we
can now move around to school try
checking out a place on the map where
you see that someone might be hanging
around perhaps you'll discover something
not just a location I started exploring
oh
oh can I stay in the classroom
yeah okay
oh it reset
it's pretty
it's like kind of old school but it
looks like they kept everything nice and
clean and intact so I'll be the teacher
now
I am the teacher so
uh wait where's the Moana
is in here
the disrespect
namona is in the staff room ah told you
it's correct what is she doing well I
guess she's the student council
she better be doing student council kind
of things
oh I like that lady with the fluffy hair
and the the tight black pants I liked I
liked her already when I first saw her
which is cool she's cool
very well Champion
I trust you to handle this in my state
Sure Thing You Can Count On Me In fact I
bet this is gonna be fun
I'm glad to hear it a good day then
you're so cool
[Music]
Style
Shadow the Hedgehog me
I like her she's funny
just by existing she's cool just kind of
cool not my not my type you know but
cool I appreciate her existing
um
okay well hey oh my God I'm so surprised
to see you
good eye she sure is that lady is well
they call her La Primera oh she did the
head of the school
she's strong she can do pretty much
anything she's got a cool practical way
coming out of her ears she really does
she's basically everything I want to be
or that any Pokemon trainer would want
to be really
oh which reminds me remember in homeroom
when I asked what your dream is
well since you had already set on
becoming a really strong trainer I've
got an idea for you you should try to
reach Champion rank like me flicks
yeah I will I was planning on this oh
well hang on though I've got a whole
spiel
game I want to give you here goes uh uh
the trainers who reach Champion rank are
the ones who raise their Pokemon really
strong their protein Battlers their
moves keep crowds absolutely on the edge
of their seats
you have to prove yourself that the
Pokemon League to officially get the
title of champion
and to do that you have to do more than
just take classes here you've got to
take on eight Pokemon gyms it's always
eight
I think it's always been eight
and Winston you can collect their gym
badges once you've done all that all
that's left is a special test the
champion assessment yeah okay but it's
not always the same types right
and same types of Arenas I wonder what
Arenas there will be
the first one is usually like
grass or water right
I think
Champion assessment and once you pass
that then at long last you'll be a
champion
it's every Pokemon trainer's dream the
coolest type of anyone could ever hope
to get
or Rock
not to brag or anything
or it's dramatic on the side and the
edges
I reached Champion rank during our last
treasure hunt you know oh the treasure
hunt is a special independent study
thing we've got here
it happens soon our last one started not
long after the beginning of the school
year it's great you get to leave school
to go have an adventure and learn
however you want
I guess you could say my journey to
becoming a champion was a Treasurer I
found maybe aha I don't know yet if
that's the answer I'm looking for
um
so in the end we'll not really be going
to school afterwards because we'll go on
the treasure hunt huh
okay
anyway I've Got a Feeling
that tonight's gonna be a good night
and tonight's gonna be a good night
good good night
let me go ahead and save the Gym's
locations in your map app in case you
decide to go for it oh
be so kind
oh ah whoa where's this one I haven't
seen before I think
several ones and one is like completely
turned around oh yeah yo sauce
the medalli gym
there's a couple they haven't shown
before huh
this is open to my order okay yeah oh
cool oh yeah right so there is no first
one
but do they adjust the level to what
level I am
because how else would they do that
no let's get it well then it's not
really a choice go wherever the hell you
want well will they at least tell me the
link recommended throughout because I
don't want to suddenly stumble into a
Arena where there's like level 60
Pokemon
like I understand that probably like
montevera class Seattle they're like up
there in the north so probably
you would think they're more difficult
but there's a couple ones around me like
the artisan and the other for NADA and
the courtondo gym
it's probably even AutoZone or cotondo
hmm
and the app for another person kinda
kininado I'm curious about her because
she had purple hair and kind of looked
cute in that little icon but I could
barely look ah give it some thought
oh my God there's so many I didn't even
see yet they were also not introduced
officially yet right
game says the buck gem is the most
recommended okay okay
so cool I wanna look at them
they only showed like a couple of
trainers and they all looked so cool
I'll go oh the dude is here
firefighter versus a bug okay that's
good both grass and Bug are close by
oh they're so tiny
I'm like this Pokemon talk to me look at
me
[Music]
I like this one
oh yeah
what are you doing here you don't look
like one of the kids
uh I I just um drank a lot of milk I
still drink a lot of milk
anyway
you remember me right
I don't think good man what come on I
gave you cooler items Pokeball did I
forget to introduce myself
maybe you did I don't know
well the name's Arvin
I've got beautiful hair and that's all I
care about
whole school seems to be talking about
you don't need a kid who showed up with
the president of the student council
yeah I'm the chosen one
is back forgets huge so Overkill
I normally wouldn't even thought of
showing up for class
really goes to class
when I came all the way to school today
just to talk with you our new celebrity
hey yo
so popular
you've gotta help me out so I can
finally make my dream a reality
my dream to talk to me was this dream
called your interests have I you want to
hear all about my dream right
well this might come as a surprise but
fact is I'm all about the picnic life
okay I did not expect that
The Great Outdoors the perfectly
prepared sandwiches all of it but that's
really a badass hardcore she
ish
now the backpack makes sense too though
carrying a cute adorable traditional
basket
skin
[Music]
not how bad a cooking either I can tell
you
right now I'm researching new recipes
that will help Pokemon feel better real
Health Food see I found this book the
other day and another section about
these Urban mystical things basically
there's some kind of special herbs that
heal our Bay Pokemon as soon as it eats
them
now there are a total of five different
types of urban mystica based on what I
read just taking a little lick of them
once they've been powdered will get your
blood flowing provide oh my God
what is that
his age is low-key showing
I stay like shadows in his cheekbones
and so on he's trying his best to hide
it
he's really trying but the magic is like
starting to fade
I think it's time for him to reapply his
makeup
[Music]
uh predating
two about that
I I see straight through you dude
literally it will even boost the immune
system these herbs seem like they're the
real deal only found here in paldea and
rare to boots
[Music]
this book says they're all guarded by
Titan Pokemon meaning that it's gonna be
pretty tough to try and grab or even a
few streaks oh Titans
I think they've gotta be things like
this
oh
Monsters of Ariel zero as for this
channel forever into area 0 we began to
catch glimpses of mysterious Pokemon
so we wondered that these huge ferocious
beasts were indeed Pokemon at all
oh I wonder if that thing counts as one
of them the bicycle
one of our team suffered a brutal Blow
from such a beast and was mortally
wounded forcing us to retreat for a Time
Paul monsters area zero a member of the
server team captured his Photograph by
chance I noticed a passing resemblance
to the Pokemon known as Don fun ah yeah
differences such as its sheer size and
the shape of its back set is apart as do
its great tusks oh I guess wait that
don't fund exists already so hmm
maybe it's just big and evil versions of
existing Pokemon
I really want to get those herbs for
myself but I'm not very good at Pokemon
battles as you've seen before don't have
any friends with strong Pokemon to lend
me a hand either and that never you're
the end of it if I went crawling to that
student council girl
but yeah you what's up like that
Austrian that you are you've got to help
me out with this you'll be perfect
just because I'm an Austrian I can't
even wall still to be honest I can't I
don't know how to Vault
but whatever I did was not Waltzing
trust me
nope wait I don't need an answer yet I
just registered to places where it seems
there might be titles in your map oh
okay
yo
oh he's
yes
we have a stone a steel a sky an earth
and drag a Dragon Titan
oh
I guess if you knew Pokemon really well
you may already know what these are just
by looking at them there although except
the Earth one like what the is that
nothing
the Titans layers have been added to
your map app wow attack on title Titan
no no no no okay
[Music]
they're all new Pokemon oh that's cool
let's do a bit and we can get more into
the details later and in the meantime
take this a little gift for listening
[Music]
thank you
bye bye
can I go give the idea some secret spot
please
dramatically too
weird though
he looks good but he's so weird though
this is kiwawa correct I have your smart
I had your smartphone so I could talk to
you hope you don't mind is that the red
lady maybe did she hack my smartphone
did she hack into the gate
she hack a girl
Castile pale that could be her
my name's Cassiopeia but never mind it's
you I want to talk about I hear that
your trainer with serious potential if
that description is accurate there's
something I'd like to ask of you
tell me kiwawa you know about team Star
right
gonna make him feel worse about
themselves
nice try but I know for a fact you've
already crossed paths with them
team stays a group of troublemakers run
by some Academy students a while back
they cause headaches for the school and
try to bring other students down to
their level and I refuse to sit idly by
and let them get away with it
oh wait you're
against team stock
wait I really don't know was she with
her or against them
I don't know what it says then but I
think it's the red lady
so I've come up with a plan to bring
down team star and force them to disband
for good I call it operation Starfall
oh sounds cool
maybe it should just be operation Comet
I don't know
operation suse
do I need allies to carry out this
operation and I'd like you to be one of
them
hot lady hot fire lady no need to reply
the second we can discuss the details
some other time
till then I'll leave you to it bye bye
keep on flaming like that burning hot
Phoenix your eyes
kind of switch it up burning like that
flaming hot videos you are that's better
uh Miss Kiowa
please do try to keep your voice down if
you make I
what one word and that was no
you're more noisy than I was just now
and
then whatever dude
Alfred whatever I don't know what the
I think he's evil
I think he's no he said he's the he's
the the one who gave him Pokemon he
can't be evil but he's a piece of
this I guess this is just School you get
scolded
even though you didn't do
because someone else was noisy
and then you get to be scolded for it
I want anyone else overhearing any
personal information after all honestly
there are so many things we need to be
careful about this day and age and not
only go then young lady
well that pisses me off
huh Team Store you say well you would
have heard that if I was more quiet or
not me but the phone
should be happy that heard that
oh I'm being called to the director's
office
okay
okay I'm scared
what the hell
anyway let me look around here we
haven't looked around here yet can I
read the books wait there's a book that
I can read right oh
types and moves yeah
maybe they're 18 18 such types and all
and every Pokemon species has at least
one time some have two
and Pokemon use a move that is the same
type as they are that moves Powers
increased by 50 percent
um
all the time
this is like going to a um
chica tattoo Subway
damn
[Music]
yeah step I know stab
I know
hmm
what did you call me here for we just
met thank you for coming Miss kiwawa
have you been enjoying your time here at
Orange Academy
um
that is most wonderful to hear
now let me confiscate your phone because
you're not allowed to talk to anyone
no you're dangerous
nah let me show you this reason why I
asked you to meet me in your office
it seems that a friend of mine has a
rather serious matter they would like to
discuss with you
uh oh
Red Hot Chili Pepper lady
TV TV
[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Applause]
[Music]
hmm
Uka
so is it the same I don't know if I'm
supposed to give her the same voice
hello it's nice to meet you
she must have like a lower voice we're
all trying to do low voices my name is
Professor Sada how can I do a little
sexy woman voice
this sounds sexy to you
um
hello
flower
a flower
oh
my name is Professor Sada I carry out
Pokemon research within the great Crater
of Foley I'm so crazy
ah great creator of paldia and that's
better
at a site known as Ariat zero
it's still though oh
oh my God
oh
the professor is in fact a graduate of
our fine Academy as well as a splendid
researcher
oh
hot
well allow me to get straight to the
point
s look at ID number 805 c393 it's just
like kfp
you are a student who travels with the
unusual Pokemon Corydon is that correct
not really I don't really like use it I
have the ball for it but wait was I able
to use it already
no
[Laughter]
why would you attempt to lie you appear
in any number of flips from security
camera footage
together
[Music]
that's impossible I was with them once
like at the beach pretty much
was I expected to take out
that thing
since then
this is so
many foot I thought they were like still
gonna teach me and give me the power to
use it could have already been using it
cameras all over this is uh scary the
fact that they have cameras everywhere
outside what
no okay then
the lighthouse was her house and left oh
oh I think that's a spoiler but I'll
take it that makes sense
okay I'll talk normal I don't want to
use the voice changer
uh not that I do not mean to offend you
in fact I wish to ask for your
assistance
yeah
I love how Pokemon always gives you
choices there are no choices because
it's the same
oh how good to see that you were well it
has been quite a while since last time
we met oh wait that was was not the dude
was her oopsie yes
Cold Island was once in my care you see
It's Pokeball was also originally mine I
assume you received it from a young
crazy man called Arvin
see he's a man
not a boy
I'm no longer in any position to be able
to manage this Pokemon myself
this is what I would ask of you we'll
continue looking after code item on my
behalf
um why me
[Music]
what did I do to deserve that
I do appreciate your agreement
has been greatly weakened and is
currently incapable battle
and you know I'm only with it during
good times not during bad times that's
when I push it away and have other
people deal with it
in all likelihood it will require some
time to fully regain the capabilities it
once had like driving around and flying
around and being a boat I will provide
you with my contact information if you
would please get out your phone
mm-hmm
I'm the only one able to unlock its
sandwich Powers
no then she should have given it to my
mom because my mom makes the sandwiches
I will be in regular contact going
forward to keep tabs on your status oh I
am so happy to hear that
I have a beautiful lady keeping tabs on
me constantly honestly I'm not saying
that ironically I'm so blessed
until then
this Pokemon have its Origins with Aria
zuro
possibly
don't tell me you actually did it dude
what
indeed what
stalker though yeah like kind of scary
but she didn't she doesn't look like she
would be evil
at all
this dude looks like he could be evil
but the fact that he gave me my starter
Pokemon
makes me rule out that option entirely
but it would be a big bamboozle
[Music]
hmm well it seems though the professor
is asking quite a favor of you
but of course they killed him he's
always here to support you in any way
that we are able
my throat hurts sorry I'm gonna read
them normally uh or not read them at all
do that voice so long
uh
I don't know I've been talking so much
today
[Music]
what's up oh you're still here kiwawa
getting called into the director's
office on your first freaking day
I feel sorry for you
[Music]
Mr Jack wanted me to show you the way to
our room in the school of school
I have a private room to share when they
have bunk beds
[Music]
what oh my throat
I know certain dorms aren't like this
holy even the kitchen
that kitchen is double the size of most
kitchens in Japanese uh one one person
appointments
foreign
[Music]
why am I getting a double bed I'm like
10 years old
I don't need a double bed
I'm staying in this place alone right
oh
from today on this is your room camera
yeah I I mean I'm freaking impressed but
this was not necessary
oh my God
[Music]
I can imagine a lot of students who had
to endure student dorms
are very very jealous
actually it says new to me as it is to
you never been in here before
damn you got a double back we could
share that if you want you must be
pretty worn out from all this stuff
happening on your very first day look
like rest on the bed is all you need to
get this yourself and your Pokemon happy
again
I'll see you tomorrow when you press it
up then we can battle even more take
care even if
the hair dorms were like shared with a
lot of people right
[Music]
because we keep on comparing it to Harry
Potter but
damn
does this count as um
rest that you got a Pokemon Center and
my
characterizing being fixed up again
Harry pita
uh-huh
oh the days quickly fly by after you
start your new life at Narendra Academy
that's a tree house up there on
the top left and then at the last day it
arrives for your tour at last a day
arrives we just skipped all the school
life
damn
okay
[Music]
easy speed running school I wish that
was possible just with one Mouse click
just skip everything like not skip I
still would go through it but I don't
have to experience it really
same as the beginning of an important
new assignment please assemble the
schoolyard where I will explain in more
detail
ing
oh
it's time it's just so motivated
I've been waiting forever for this come
on let's go out to the schoolyard
oh wow wow well you would think right
that I would go to the schoolyard but
I'm gonna leave it on this clip
oh
yeah because I'm extremely hungry I had
one single tiny
crepe
today and it's 9 p.m and those hockey a
couple of them
cook and prepare some I think it's
a good spot to end yeah how do I save
oopsie
that's awesome that's it that's it
yeah babe
hmm I would love to stream more if I
didn't have a recording later I would be
streaming like even past midnight I
don't care
and it comes to Pokemon but
yeah I gotta end it here I'll be meal
comes out comes out tasty I'm just gonna
make something quick though
um I think
I'm so hungry
I like this game oh good I'm happy for
you you should get it for yourself too
then
I hope you did
I don't care thank you
okay we're just trying to look forward
to the next spot thank you
you're gonna post it on Twitter oh
actually I didn't post what I uh cooked
the other day even though it was pretty
good just because it didn't look so
special
um
but yeah I don't know
so I can maybe upload it maybe
I'll think about it picking up my prayer
tomorrow oh enjoy Scarlett on violet
did you guys get the game yet did you
get Scarlet or Violet tell me tell me
I feel like I always go for the less um
popular option in Sun and Moon I chose
sun in sword and shield that shows
shield and Scarlet Violet and choosing
Scarlet most people choose violent I
think
um
[Music]
oh
well when I'm starting with Scotland you
got both
but most people I see they chose
violence
um
we're on the same part yeah but you're
probably gonna get ahead of me unless
you wait for me because
I won't be able to play for a couple
days
um
yeah it will be a while
but you guys have so many other Pokemon
streams to watch if you wanna there's a
couple
uh almost everyone in the whole life
this is streaming Pokemon as expected
but uh yeah I'll continue next week
and I'll see you on the whole talk
okay after tomorrow Sunday oh and if you
want anime NYC
um tomorrow I'll be having a little
thing with fauna
yeah
so
um wish me luck with what I'm doing
after this because I'm
tired and stressed out
[Music]
okay okay and in German we say
how to wish luck in German uh feel good
feel look good look
that you with two dots on top
thank you I appreciate it
and bye bye
hungry tired
bye bye bye bye it was so fun first uh
episode let's do more soon
[Music]
shiny I did not
foreign
[Music]
thank you