[Music]
he
sh
[Music]
Musa can you hear
usy I might be yelling today
H it's kis
kis and and moris also there Morris kis
Tak moris
takam takisus talk morus
C it'll come back iug it back in um I've
been seeing comments that there's lag
but can't help helps all right
transitioning over hopefully it'll get
better hi hi hello shall we introduce
each other's hands yeah yes I guess we
should cuz mine are so sausy they're not
sausy I cut holes on these gloves but I
don't like how they look a little ragged
but it's fine you look like a street
urchin like a musical it's like it's so
oh cute oh is this Iris finger reveal
yes it is my finger
Ral sa they're not sausages I promise if
I could show you my wrist I'll show you
guys it might are the most sausage like
no they're not mine are but hold on look
my hands are literally a sausage fest
look at that thin wrist though hold on
no what are you talking about everyone
has nice fingers it's the angle it's the
angle it's the angle please my angle is
especially like unflattering what the
[\h__\h] man I need to diet my fingers
specifically your fingers there finger
diet I don't think so finger diets maybe
like maybe like stress ball squeezing oh
maybe man oh yeah okay I'll try yes
you'll get you'll get actually I think
your fingers will get thicker yeah won't
they get like muscular Muscular fingers
lift things with your thumb wow welcome
to the nail
salon oh no hey guys check this out duct
tape oh yeah duct tape yes we don't have
to worry about reflection no
reflection so what are we doing today
we're doing a a hand cam off live stream
with these cute girls and we're going to
do each other's
nails and they're going to be gel nails
okay maybe some of you guys don't know
what that means I think they does
someone want to explain they are nails
that are extremely hard to come off oh
yes they last they last long and they
they they're very shiny shiny Shin it's
not like your regular manic here yes
thick
where regular manicure usually comes off
like within a week you know it starts
tripping off it starts looking ugly gel
nails you don't have to worry about that
until they start
lifting a lifting yeah they start
lifting and then if you go like you know
if you take a bath like with lifted nose
you can start getting growing
mold
you there's a thing called green nails
if you keep your nails on too long you
sound like you have
experienced yes yes no I I've never I've
never it hasn't gone green but one time
like I had like nail that were on for
too long and they started lifting a
little bit and like I think the the
bottom part of my nail like just a small
small part of it started turning blue I
yeah it's a thing it's a thing horrific
yes you have to grow it
out so I've never been to a nail salon
before I've only ever done like really
basic nail paint like when I was
younger you would think I would think
that you would go like almost no cuz I
also think I also think it's really
annoying to have something on my nails
to begin with I prefer them to be like
you should experience yeah we we'll
experience today but you girls or at
least for for C I see your nails a lot
yeah I got M cute yeah mine I got some
really good ones done and then I had to
get them professionally taken off for
the first time in my life because they
were too strong oh yeah and so they like
had a drill and they were like drilling
around all the parts and stuff like that
I was like oh my this must sound so
surreal like weird to
guys the trail for your nails moldy
fingers I can't believe it sounds like
fun yes things girls do to you know feel
pretty yes we got to do it we got to do
it so we got like these clear Nails yes
and we're going to I guess first stick
them on our fingers and then paint each
other Nails oh no my shaky hands no it's
okay don't worry be so shaky I swear
we'll take care of your fingers for gel
stuff and we have some decorations I
don't know if people can they see it
yeah they can see it yep that's
it colorful stuff too like this
yes and oh this this eyeshadow palette
looking thing is really interesting
right yeah it literally looks like
eyeshadow indeed but what is it unicorn
powder probably I mean it's apparently
magnetic but it's either called unicorn
powder or magnet powder something like
that the True Unicorn color is this one
hold glue gel huh it's glue glue gel
what do you do with nail glue for nail
okay this is this is to put the fake
nails on on Al so I didn't needan to buy
a glue I guess not I mean it's good you
got it we have remover an glue I don't
get why it says four in one though what
four is in one of maybe it's just super
strong I mean it could be like a top
coat and glue oh my God but the warning
is so scary it says avoid all skin
contact if redness or other signs occur
stop use
immediately
prob so we we have like oh this is
really interesting we have a builder
nail gel UV light oh yeah right cuz we
have a UV light right we do you will
never see it cuz it's too refle but
maybe they see the blue light can you
turn it on let's see oh yeah so
bright is it like 100% necessary to like
make it work yes for gel if you really
want it to stay yeah you got at the end
when we're done we can hold these things
like this you know like the influencers
yeah like the
influencers very bougie yeah so yeah I
got all this kind of stuff and then
there's a top coat base coat top coat in
between is the gel and some cute stuff
oh there's a a bit more over here
stickers yeah they're like stick like
little gold
thingies it's
not M oh they have like they have like
flowers music not yeah yeah there's a
bunch of different
options so you girls went to nail Sals
before but you've never done these kind
of nails yourself right no no and I'm
usually dozing off when they're doing
this I don't remember anything I don't
know after buying all this stuff I'm
kind of interested right you even have a
lot of stuff that didn't even arrive
yeah yeah stuff that didn't come in but
I mean honestly in hindsight this is all
we really need I didn't show the GL a
lot of glitter that's a lot of glitter a
lot of glitter yeah there's so much so
many options and we can probably use the
nail glue for that as well they have
like yeah I don't know what are those
like little Stones oh these are like for
the the abstract looking nails and
little yeah oh it's so cute the [\h__\h] is
this is this there's a broken
one there's something oh yeah please
don't get that on my
carpet it's um it's not it's not um
there's nothing inside and it's like
broken a thief yeah an Amazon Thief no
malfunction production yeah it is broken
there's nothing in all right I'll just
ignore it see let's just like can you
see this yeah they can a little further
down it was just in there like this yeah
just empty there's a thief there's a
nail thief from no I think it's like
production failure that could be a my
left foot is like so asleep you do what
you get
SE stop SE okay you're torturing
yourself so um
we both have two hands we all have two
hands so like and there's like two other
people right right so I could say One
hand is will be Cali one hand will be
Iris made and then same like for you
girls right Co that's a cute idea I like
it they will be totally unmatching
perhaps probably probably that's fine
fine oh no I just noticed I had my
fingers in in the dust okay we can also
do our feet just kidding feet get oh no
that's that's a little bit too much fan
a little too much
F off camera hands are enough off camera
they don't need to
see okay so how did we start this I I
guess we first we have to uh figure out
who has like which size right the size
of and maybe give like you you you find
your si want do we want to glue this
first or do we want to I feel like it
would be cuter but it would be easier to
have it on here yeah it would be but I
mean
um vote what do you guys think what does
chat think what do you girls think I
think either way if we're thinking about
ease definitely just probably directly
on this but if we're thinking about oh
cute girls you know yeah each other's
nails and stuff then then yeah it would
make more sense to do it directly
yeah also when we mess up like if it's
already glued on
yeah yeah kind of SC if we mess up like
this we can still get a new one but
technically I think once uh if you paint
it and if you mess up you can kind of
wipe it off until until you harden it
with the the the that thing over there
yes exactly yeah one UV light once you
UV light it it's it's over it's over you
have to only you can only paint over it
that's your best option okay then no
still maybe we'll do it directly okay
yeah okay so we'll glue these on first
then
right yeah afterward huh oh I thought oh
directly on here yeah okay okay that
makes sense but uh we should I guess got
to select keep them on the on this side
I no I tore this one off oh well I mean
if you think about it they're all
different sizes right so I feel like you
really got to choose which ones are
proper cuz whenever I go get mine done
they like they choose they fit a bunch
of them and they're like oh this one
works oh this one doesn't they glue
automatically the one that fits so we
might want to select the sizes first
yeah yeah that's that's what I was
saying but uh is it easier to keep them
on here I mean it might be paint like
this it might be cuz like if you already
tear it off how do you hold it to you
have to use like a I don't like a
tweezer or something to hold it it is a
little annoying so maybe we should keep
it on there yeah okay then I'll I'll
let's find our sizes our finger sizes
that's what works fine for me how do we
let the other person know can we mark it
I wish we could maybe there must be do
we have like tape or something that we
can mark on the edges like a duct tape
or something or an eding and we just
mark it like on the stick thingy here
yeah like a marker or something like
that let me go see if there's a mar I'm
pretty sure I got a Sharpie somewhere in
that pen thing over there yeah that
seems like the best way smart
smart Solutions yeah oh any ideas like
what colors and what kind of style you
girls
want what's your
I want to try the I want to try the
powder mhm me too I want to try the
powder just powder yeah maybe like a one
color with a powder okay everybody gets
a gradiation how about that yes we have
to try it out right oh yes that's great
I'll use yeah
Mi all right um so maybe we just for
example I'll show we do like um image
color like pink orange what's your image
color dark pink uh Pink
it's like it's like it's like hot pink
hot pink and more like baby pink I'd
prefer black and white not good just oh
you want you don't want to go girly you
don't want to go full on baby pink no
back to your baby days no no no I'm not
babo babo sorry sorry to disappoint but
I'm not wear penc where did they go
sorry both um this one there's a there's
there was only one black one and then
there was like a couple I think
I think that that's one of those um that
you have to like really push in oh yeah
they're not used too gay okay and then
Iris punched me guys Iris punched me
could how could you your first off coll
sorry I I'm I'm physically abusing her
already I'm sorry message you want to
send I'm going to call the police that's
so much that's so much yeah yeah it it
leaks be careful oh yeah just tissue
tissue oh those are my signing pens
yeah there was only one black one that's
why H yeah I can definitely lend this to
you guys in just a moment after I get
this one hand figured out Sor I won't
use them too
much
t Okay
so these
good pinky pinky finger cop pinky finger
w
it it should reach the edges properly
right yeah I would say so okay right I
think I got my first hand figured
out I think the they're both both hands
are pretty much identical right oh I
would
say it would be weird if they weren't
it's not like a boob where a boob can be
a different size we're soly talking
about
boobs ladies oh no oh no I I think I've
admitted to this before
do not destroy their dreams pure
identical take it you can't take it it's
to it's too much well you know what this
is like a special edition of girls talk
stream welcome to girls talk off collab
Edition we start talking about girls
body parts yes girls things can they
handle it girls things can you handle it
can they handle the
truth it would be a very girly thing
thing really I'm done here would you
like to use black done already you
figured it out so fast I'm very quick at
measuring Chago would not be happy with
these hands here use little sausage
thingies but guess what
wrist look at look look at these wrist
this I'm wrists look at that bone it's a
good looking
bone
what okay I might have a thing for
wrists look you have a thing for wrist
for that are you are you serious for
ladies for ladies ladies wrist lady
wrist lady wrist he can you judge my
wrist I'll look at ler cover it up I'll
show you my
wrist hey I'm not sure if it's too
big and do you also have like two
fingers somewhat the same size like the
the middle finger and the pointy finger
I mean I just assume well I mean kind of
n they're a little different really my
middle finger nails I would say big
enough to Warrant a different size
really is your middle fer bigger than
your normally they should go from
biggest to smallest right
like maybe yeah I think it goes around
like smallest
small wait these are not the same size
as these no no they're not they're not
they're slightly different yeah yeah oh
there's numbers on them what there's
numbers on them really numbers oh my go
it is 7 s 99 they're the same they're
the same to the number on the opposite
sides they're the same Oh I thought
they're slightly different oh my God I'm
just okay same same yeah that's why I
just kind of marked same same same if
you look really close yep okay so we
could even tell each other each other
the
numbers but could be but I hate math and
I hate numbers so I'm cool to just mark
them I don't know why this one looks
feels feels bigger
than I want something in between
yeah seven and eight or is that is that
a nine no six something between seven
and six
please then okay maybe two of them then
I need another one are you using like
two of the same sizes for like two
different Fingers um like it doesn't
seem like I think like my middle finger
and my pointer finger might be the same
that's what I was just like noticing
yeah yeah cuz there's nothing in between
cuz if you go to the next one it's way
too big
for same girl same just like me for real
well if there's extra then I guess you
could probably just grab that and use
there's 120 nails or
240 no problem easy okay so I need I'll
I'll I'll maybe I write it
down I'll I'll have uh two number sevens
one number threee L A this is large this
is small three large seven
small extra gel extra Sparkle extra
shine shine I'll I'll memo it so w was
two small
sevens seven just to really make sure
one you don't get it wrong
big one big
[Music]
three Big Smoke order
um okay that was that was a seven then
this one maybe is a six can be a six
thumb oh
this okay now we're at a we're at a
beautiful
proud F no
eight I'm not sleeping Chad Chio I'm
looking at you that's why my head's down
I'm looking at you
you she's looking at you guys you she's
giving you guys attention should be
happy about that without reading the
chat out loud or interacting but I am
reading I'm not reading chat at all I'm
too busy I'm too busy looking being a
fashionista and the smallest one might
be too big for my small one yeah it to
be like that
like do you have it where's the extras
the extra um Nails right thank
you hey you guys want to peep what we
found really quick I wanted to show them
what more
found one number nine in acuba what's
that oh Wafers I thought we could open
them and see what cards we get yay yeah
so I bought a bunch one okay and this is
my order
okay but uh so you both make me one hand
so and I make
also one hand for each of you man maybe
I should write mine down too I only
marked them that's I didn't write mine
but you should probably Mark a second
set then
oh what how is this 12 120 it doesn't
look like like we don't have this one
anymore sounds like a big fat lie I mean
depending on like what size you are
there might be like leftovers in between
which ones were you uh give me that one
all these these ones
oh I just marked them with a pen those
are two two number fives
yeah okay H are they different they're
for both hands oh no wait oh no there
are two number fives okay I didn't use a
number five so you can probably I can
use you know the fives from here mine
should be these or did I use the number
five okay
cool these oh you marked yours right I
marked mine I Mark mine look at how
prompt kiar is she just writes it down
on a piece of paper I'm
like um dark docks so I guess for now
like we can focus on one hand each so we
just do the first set so do we want to
start with pinky first or do you want to
start with thumbs
pinky Oh I thought we do like the for
now just like the whole set of one
person like one hand of one person okay
okay so this is Mor's hand so I should
give this to one of you guys I guess
yeah Okay who wants who wants ugly ones
no why why ugly ug ugly cuz I have
really shaky hands I I I don't have
confidence in doing a good job we will
both get one of yours oh okay so you
okay very unbal go I just want Iris
hands that's all okay let me take a look
at okay I'll start with one one for you
yeah I guess um and Kelly you can take
mine from these thanks they're uh just
go by the Numbers yeah yeah Min so my
thumbs these are my thumbs mhm and then
these are my fingers so I used two of
the seven I I want to make pretty ones
for you but I I don't want to disappoint
you oh if I disappoint you
disappointment is a part there's no such
thing as disappointment four where's the
fifth nail uh one small oh wait no think
about this one this one this one that
should be one hand probably one two
three right four five no no no so this
is the one thumb one thumb this is for
the extra other thumb this is for my
other hand this this is one thumb this
is for my pinky um uh middle and pointer
finger aren't you missing one finger
wait
wait no ring finger okay ring finger
middle
finger one big and didn't you have two
of the same size yes I do and then poter
yeah and then poter
yeah you are what you want
girl what
color can you which one
can you make
something autum me Autumn e for me so I
think orange is fitting orange and like
uh gold Sparkles all right maybe some
elegant is there elegant Brown can it
look good I mean I don't think if you
want you can just maybe like test the
colors a bit wait Kelly don't you have
to do base coat yeah we to do base coat
first B coat base coat base
coat no this is the glue gel this is
glue glue glue base coat Co that is true
we did have a conversation about that we
did have a conversation about that you
you yes all right so your thumb is the
one big three correct uh yeah the
biggest one is the okay Kelly which
one's your thumb is it the one it's the
biggest one the biggest one okay that it
would be my thumb yeah maybe an orange
no orange gold gradient please can we
all right I'll do it what do you want
Iris I am
thinking what colors do we have
gray it's in my hand P we don't really
have pink do
we I think we do do we oh there's some
more that we didn't unpackage unbx M
sorry can you grab those yeah careful
there's some plastic onass maybe open it
here okay I wish I had paper towel sh
all right Sor what is this it says Ultra
base on it I have no idea what I'm
supposed to do now
those are colors those might not be
colors it's Ultra Bas and then the oh
Ultra Bas this
one's gigabase three in one clear I have
no idea what to do cie I mean I'm
confused now I think that those are just
repeats of the ones that I got
specifically for making gel nails oh
those are that's the normal nail polish
the C maker the pink one this this that
yeah this is like unicorn color unicorn
color it's not gel right no
yeah we canip that no pink for Iris it's
okay we but this one's like a pretty
nice color I don't know what is this is
this brown it's like a red it was like a
pretty strong red ooh oh it's very
magenta this not ref your hair color got
the base colored down it looks black
on so do I stick it in here I wonder
call will it be lighter um outside of
the package on the actual nail I would
say so yeah like you're scared just like
maybe um dip and then like put it on one
of the nails you can always wipe it off
and see and then like okay and then test
your fing you want that it's really it's
really red but yeah I think it's cute
can you mix these colors I'm sure you
can you can
try this is like a weird color you can
definitely mix colors I don't know if
this is like beige but if if we put some
red in it it could become pink not
inside it but okay I put the base coat
on you can't see but it's it's on there
it's on there this is definitely pink
this one yeah it's like a it's like a
nude
[Music]
pink or graad gradiation gradiation yeah
gradation can you gradiate these gel
colors um I think most gel colors can
right I'm pretty sure I'm going to miss
n it'll be fine it just takes mix mix it
becomes mix dark pink like this okay
I'll I might try it then for you that's
what you want yeah sure okay so this and
the dark one yeah and basically what you
do is usually I think you put it on like
a palette or some somewhere and then you
mix it together like like paint you know
okay and then you do that yeah B Co
stick it in here I wonder for cie like
the I said orange I don't know how
you're going to do an orange me uh black
and white do we have black and white
pretty sure we do jump
scare a gray I see a gray
there's there's
gray and I guess you could mix it with
the black powder yeah that would work
let me see how this one's oh this is
green what's it the hole yeah what is
this hole it's a cable hole right it was
supposed to be for tea or something like
that but I kind of just ignored it tea
yeah you're supposed to be able don't
look at the hole just ignore
it it is the forbidden hole he wants to
be
ignored Christ are you done with the
base coat for all just the one I guess I
have to put it on all of them huh okay
okay okay where's one which one's the
gray again the gray this one one small
eight this one was like dark green this
is like Navy yeah it's like it's like
Navy greenish it looks so gray yeah when
you open it I think it's it's pretty
green oh this one's not open N9
seven eight that or it's just how are
you seeing green did you put it on the
nail this is this is gray no it's green
what are you talking about no I swear
it's green here how is this green no
it's it's green I swear here looks like
color let me let me try May on the nail
it's greenish I don't know I haven't
actually touched it on the nail trust
it color
blind eight that's green no that's green
no it's green it's green green code okay
it's like a maybe a military green yeah
it's mil like have like a lighter coat
yeah who who wants that I some people
like this col Shrek green aren't you a
shre GRE it's a real it's it's a it's a
nose green nose inside green you oh snot
green yes yeah boogers Boog booger green
I don't know can you guys see this is
this uh what am i showing uh uh got so
much on my here gloves let's okay wait
how
about
how about this oh
painter so this one is like weird green
weird as green okay let me wipe that off
oh they saw it it's matcha matcha nail
matcha Nails actually that sounds kind
of cute the moment you say matcha all of
a sudden it's just so appealing suddenly
suddenly want it suddenly I want it how
about matcha Nails oo nice you're done
with the base cat oh nice okay stick it
jump scare under the uh did you do the
base coat for all of it already yeah for
all of guas okay okay then you do next
Okay youv jump maybe you should use the
paper yeah I should use the paper too
yeah sure otherwise I'm ruin your your
table yeah do you have more these papers
yeah for us all to like do it paint on
top of a good point for the colors we we
don't want I mean we're already a little
bit ruining I it goes It goes off how
did how did that get on there you can
pretty easily scratch it
off not that big of
my fingers got really
sticky what yeah I prefer Shrek Nails
okay if you guys come to our nail salon
you will be getting Shrek Nails don't
worry and donkey and Puss and Boots and
all the characters did you guys see the
new Garfield trailer I did Chris Chris
what the f more Chris PR are you serious
who
needs also I don't think he should be
voicing Garfield because Garfield is a
precious lasagna orange cat and I don't
want to be okay well what if Chris Pratt
could also be a precious Las Sonia cat I
mean you never
know give him a
chance he doesn't no I don't like it I
don't like it at all he's just like
everywhere now well it's your entitled
to your opinion I'll go look for more
did you cure all of those at once or did
you do it oh okay yep all right I'll go
for a paper it seems like Cy likes Chris
PR I don't really have much of an
opinion I just believe in giving people
a chance Kara you got enough chances
give other people a chance I don't know
I didn't actually watch the Mario movie
and I wasn't it wasn't that bad yeah it
wasn't the the crisper voice acting
wasn't as bad as I thought it from the
trailers it was actually pretty good it
was fun I liked it too but I don't want
him to be
Garfield strong Garfield opinion of
course she loves her cats I watched a
different Garfield movie also an
animated one and that Garfield also had
a really low voice I like that one that
was fine too I don't use these plac mats
W okay placement let's
[Music]
go
I do you want the place mat instead of
the ratchet paper uh I'm fine with the
ratchet paper for now okay I'll
eventually maybe I might switch
depending on how messy this paper gets
oie dogy yeah however you want to do it
girlfriend
secr you you I want to be your
girlfriend there was a Japanese version
made of that song really how does that
go hey
[Music]
hey something like that hey
hey I forget the lyrics it didn't like
you know change my life or anything like
that she was like really not in a bad
I'm not saying this in a bad way but she
was like pandering to like Japanese
culture like she had a song she yeah so
I guess from that just like Gwen
stefaniw hold on too much too much gel
on the my face never moving I'm so sorry
guys why not moving why sorry I'm too
close to my got a prioritize the nail
painting yeah that's where the action is
happening oh Callie is starting yep the
painting process oh W she's fast sorry
let me I'm almost done with the one hand
take your
time take your time
Co all right you wanted the gold
gradiation correct yeah if you can get
some orange going there that's cool too
otherwise just don't like something
goldish we can defo gradiate something
interesting a little gradiation
gradation gradation how do you pronounce
it is it gradation or gradation or
gradient gr gr gradation I I was first
saying graduation but we don't hear that
word right panic panic
pic you said the G word everybody's
getting jump
scared gradiation besides cont grad I
mean graduation is usually not a bad
thing yeah it's actually a good thing
yeah you would be happy about a
graduation normally normally outside of
our
community uh is there a gold is there a
gold color that looks gold to me I think
there's something that look goldish cuz
I'd love to do like a gradiation but I
just kind of oh no maybe this one could
also be something like that they often
look very different when you open them
okay let's see what we got I think I'm
done how fake are you did you like make
the base coat just like a basic
coat a base coat thick I went really
thick in the beginning but I went
thinner and thinner I kind of regretted
the thickness actually I'm not actually
I'm not done but I'll just I'll just do
this first this kind of looks like ass
right Kelly can you can you put this
inside the curing machine bet oh you
have to cure the base too yeah you C you
cure each step yeah cure I don't think
they recognize it as fingers I'll put my
in there come
on
really come on [\h__\h] oh does it only
work with fingers I think it only
recognizes it when your fingers are in
there yeah can you turn it on manually
don't nope I don't think
so there we go nice there we go okay for
now I'm just doing five base coats yeah
I didn't do the big fingers yet this is
this is the size of Iris bump guys just
so you know for reference so if you want
to make a 3D model of Iris they go that
much in detail oh her thumbs are size
six size seven size four nice good
information forget three sizes this is
what's interesting to me nail size how
big are your
fingernails thick tells me everything
super thick uh okay so everybody got
their B oh you're you're done already
yeah holy shoot you took like 20 seconds
on that I don't know what you guys are
doing this whole time I was I was I was
painting it with my I don't know what I
was
doing ah I guess uh this also has to go
in yeah only only that edge and uh oh it
turned off is it done yeah
done in like a minute or so I'm the cook
over here I'm the chef she's cooking
she's cooking she's cooking let her cook
her cook thank her name all right yeah
this is the one you gave me right both
both okay pop them in the the top the
smallest one on the big one
gotcha let
cook let her cook fancy okay the orange
actually isn't looking so bad right now
it looks gold to me but that's fine too
yeah I can I
see it's not bad right will there be a
focus yeah it looks focused enough they
can tell that it's
orange okay good to me it's it's gold
but it's beautiful it's like a kind of
an egg yolk gold yeah almost I can see
that I'm going to get a paper towel with
some water on it so that we can clean
the brushes on the camera it look yellow
but it's not that yellow in real life
yeah take f after word for those that
want
[Music]
to #
you only love K hash Yol y was that what
yeah there's hash Yol and hash voke and
hasht voke is uh only we only no watch
only kada every day that was it I
haven't thought about it for a long
time I came up with that like three
years
[Music]
ago
you guys almost almost 30 anniversary
right you guys we're done
with over over no it's okay I thought it
was second year for some reason I don't
know why oh you thought oh you thought
we we just had our second one but you
were saying you almost have your just I
forgot I forgot can you give me my nails
no yes confused
child
and uh oh how do I know which one I
painted I can see kind of okay you'll
figure it out all
right
oh um that's funny I what happened it's
funny I may have had for some reason a
cat hair on the nail when I put the Bas
call you can kind of see the the line of
the hair where it once was it's an
accessory a feature bye we'll probably F
right when to put some stuff on we like
cats so much we want cats are on our
nails it might not even be my cats guys
remember I'm in Japan now and Cali has
cats the ghost cat mm I'm a ghost cat
cat hair is a bonus I totally agree I
should okay can you put these in I you
got them you uh smoothie and junkers
Nails oh
W radioactive green and and orange but
oh nice okay there's still time what was
I what was I doing for you the the red
color right the red and the pink and you
mix it or I don't mind just the red or
gradient to Red with pink gradient yeah
I will try that oh the red is here nice
okay yeah where's the pink again the
pink I think it was this one was it that
mhm let's see it doesn't look like it
from the outside but yeah it's the
closest to
Pink oh maybe
down
no no that's definitely not it it's that
one it's this one hey guys oh is
this I think this is
probably somebody gave that to me a
second ago no no I have mine I gave you
I know I gave you the most recent one
that I gave just now was that was mine
probably that's for that's Callie's I'm
going to put some golden stuff on yours
oh I got here on mine too nice uhoh
kitty
cat can we's cat can we's cats all right
now now stowed away yeah they're they're
just watching look at ghost cat he's so
chill right now watching us can I has a
brush yeah that all yeah when Cobo came
over um poor ghost cat hid behind the
litter box wasn't even wasn't even in
his bed he was afraid but that's okay
coobo gave him like a treat later and he
came around so are you also going to use
pink oh those Doo thank you H I was
thinking maybe KY wants black I'm going
to try I'm going to see if I can get
unicorn it might be grayish sorry if
it's grayish no Pro let see how it turns
out let me see what color this is first
this so
confusing these little accents I'm going
to put on
KS sparkling Sparkles Sparks Sparks
light stream Sparks No One need to
stream Sparks anymore that's an oldie I
don't care I want to stream Sparks
anyway let's stream something new do you
and pineapple and rospective
greatb there's a lot there's a whole lot
I feel complicated feelings that's I
think that's normal to feel complicated
feelings about your music this is so
gray man I'm I'm not confident this is
this
is I'm going
in it's so sticky is it because I kept
the container open maybe that's okay
don't worry too much about it how do you
mix this in a graduation graduation uh
you just have to go over it and over it
again and again and again until it's
like perfect but it takes a while you
don't it doesn't just happen whenever I
go to get my nails done and I ask for
gradiation they like go over it many
many times yeah they do like two or
three
layers I could do a gradu gradation into
a transparent kind of R need some
graduation nails graduation nails please
yes scare
everyone
they're they're is it normal that
they're like pretty transparent I should
do a million yeah you'll need a couple
codes I'm pretty
sure
not and so girls yeah yeah what have you
been up to recently tell me sleeping oh
iris is finally happy again I had you
with s yes I'm finally I finally stopped
coughing by now I'm like so in a good
mood right now can't believe it what did
you have like Corona ew no it wasn't I
tested for Corona it was
negative excuse me negative you know I
like to live my life positive so okay
well
e e so negative go for a gaha can I go I
can't go with a likei this um brush into
a different color can I there's nothing
close to Black Cow not maybe if you used
another nothing close to I was thinking
more like this like something from here
okay here try and like gradiate with
like a different color using that maybe
I'm just going to go with gray then oh
sh whatever works do you have any other
color you want like maybe like an accent
color red or oh you know what you could
do like a like Cerulean do I have
Cerulean oh Canan triy them oh like blue
yeah yeah bluish green do we have a
bluish green here well I'm mostly
looking at these um it's so ugly certain
colors it's so ugly it's good to me do
we have any water yeah I was going to
say maybe we should get cuz I have a
kind of slightly wet towel you can use I
don't know this this brush is so dry
that's why like I'm I can't I can't seem
to like get the paint to like may we
should get like a we have water I don't
want it to be super wet but yeah maybe
here just rub it against this towel this
wet the wet part of this towel maybe
here you go okay thank you that should
help a little bit damn this takes longer
than I thought yeah this is going to
take a while damn maybe you should only
do one set of
nails one hand compl just one hand
Beauty takes
time one hand will be the beauty and one
hand will be the Beast the Beast yeah oh
shees Callie's actually looking like
something oh no it's something on I
could do more smaller little Glitters on
it just cover all the ugly Parts with uh
stickers that will be my
my strategy o that sounds like a
plan oh yeah did you cure it between
those steps yeah in between so I did
like a base coat and then I cured it and
then I did the color then I cured
it yeah okay I could not do the
gradation with the gel stuff but I think
I I got a nice color anyway somewhat so
I will just make the gradiation with the
powder if that works yeah that should be
fine I'm
sure e [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] I'm [\h__\h] it up oh oh I got like
uh stuff on the back side damn it on the
back of the nail uh-oh that's fine it's
cool not it's fine it's
fine not so
cure Callie is this your second off
collab today it sure is wow L of Senai
so nice very G how was that was that it
was fun Kara said I sounded tired
well I only I only I don't know I just C
caught one moment I don't know de beats
do you guys think I sounded tired right
now you're sounding tired too yeah what
day but during that stream I was pretty
Ganky I felt but it was afternoon I see
a lot of fans sometimes being like Mory
sounds tired today and I'm like I'm not
I'm very Ganky I'm more Ganky than I've
been in my life sorry though maybe I'm
just more calm I'm trying to be more
calm these days I guess calm down a
little bit you know maybe that's like
how I um often get told when people see
me like oh you look so you look so tired
I'm like I'm not tired it's just my eye
bags of Doom excuse me true I can never
get rid of my eye bags which eye bags
eye
bags you don't
think I feel like like that's like
totally something you can just cover
with makeup cuz it's just color mostly I
guess yeah it wasn't like this it wasn't
like this a few years
ago understandable was it like this uh
before Holo um Hol the like Holo was
like what two it's only been like what
two a bit over two years so far it's fun
but you definitely stay busy yeah I
can't get how does yours little it's
it's just very I I need to probably do
more than one layer I'm doing the first
layer so far mine doesn't look pretty
it's okay mine's is probably going to
look disgusting Kylie's going to have no
friendship vomit on her on her Nails I'm
sure it'll be great vomit it's vomit
from Iris you're happy about that right
vomit WR vomit r i don't want these
lines I kind of have something going on
here
fck this orange which is a fall color
yay y yay kind of also a Halloween color
but yeah also my image color
so it can I like fix this part Kelly
like underneath underneath I mean I
think it'll just dry and it'll be no big
deal okay because I can see it Shine
througho I already did like a million
codes really let me take a
look see what do you
think Mrs professional n lady I mean I
don't think it's I sayd at all just
because it's cuter but I don't I think
it looks completely fine I think you're
being a
perfectionist you guys are so fast I'm
still on my third nail take your time
fast I'm on my first me too but you're
finishing one completely first fin one
yeah my God one
first she's doing it ah there's another
hair uhoh those cat no I have to do the
cat again it's all right it's it's nice
I get to take my cats with me no these
are for Iris oh just kidding you get to
take my cat with cats with me you get to
take my cats with you wherever I Go's
cats will always be with you to support
you there's ghost cat with me cute form
of a single
hair EDM yeah oh B is here in the chat
hey babe we should do bail if we had
time we should do bail set I know she
only has to send us her her nail size
nails can you send me your nail size
nobody knows their nail size I think for
now you can cure this okay um and the
powder is after the curing right I think
so after the base coat yeah I think no
idea how that will work something like
that all right I'm pretty sure that
that's a nail
done oh my God all these
hairs I think it's
cute it's looking
cute yay well that's one kiar nail
y now I got to do the four more four
more to go for one hand right we're
talking about one hand re oh yeah oh my
God what time is it right now um it is
uh uh
1017 okay 10:17 it's been almost an hour
and we started pretty late sorry G what
did you expect
I don't go to sleep early we need some
we need some girls um topics girl
topics all right ladies take it
away what what is there girl topics I
so when I saw cie the other day I
noticed something new about her and it
got me really excited what was that she
got eyelash extension oh did you get see
it yeah you can see oh you do you're
longer extensions I like them I don't
know I used to get eyelash extensions
until I realized how much of a pain they
are to like you know when you wash your
face you can't have like a shower head
like directly on your face cuz it it
comes off and when it starts coming off
it comes off in like like uneven way so
one eye would have more eyelashes than
the other so that's why I stopped doing
that instead whenever I go get my
eyelashes done instead I I just get them
permed oh you just permed the eyelashes
you already have okay explain the
process for the people who don't know
the the difference between a perm and an
extension for an extension is where you
glue fake hair little by little little
by little one by one onto your actual
eyelashes so you need actual eyelashes
to do it but you make you make it longer
by gluing on EXT like long eyelash
existing eyelashes yes to make it longer
so you that's why usually whenever you
get a plan you ask like oh they ask how
many how many uh extensions do you want
you tell them oh maybe like 100 100 foot
both eyes so it' be 5050 you know yeah
and then depending on how many you want
the price goes higher they ask what
style do you want like do you want it
super curly do you want them to be
longer at the end for like an elegant
look or do you want a cute look where
the the longer ones are in the middle
toward the middle of the
eye I'm just like I have no
idea and uh uh the the other one the
perm is just like shaping your existing
ones right yeah yeah it's just it's just
like oh how curly do you want it really
and then you don't you don't you don't
lengthen it you just curl it but because
you're your eyelashes are usually not
curled you know it makes it look much
longer when you curl it and also um you
can just put like um mascara on top of
it to make it longer for for extension
not for extensions no you can't you
can't do it for extension for perm you
can for perm you can use but for
extensions like when I look at Callie's
eyes I feel like you don't need you
don't need it you don't need it and you
shouldn't
you you don't need it but ruin it it's
basically you your ey you look like you
have makeup on already but see that's
the thing is I want to wake up and not
have to put makeup on exactly so it's so
convenient you have less steps in your
makeup routine exactly so nice I I
wouldn't do it though cuz I feel like um
the process scares me cuz like I saw
pictures and there's like they put like
these these cotton pads on your eyes and
then they put like glue and whatever
really close to your eye right like
right there actually have a hard time
with it because where's the rest of
Kell's Nails I put all these in here and
then I'm not sure cuz I gave you that
that's only for your thick nails I'm
right maybe is it those cuz these are I
think mine this is
mine this is these are these are yours
yeah yeah yeah this is my um yeah yeah
know it's just that you know um because
I use two of the same uh so for 10 this
this are the um the rest of the two this
is right okay okay so that's mine but
I'm just like where did I put the
sheet underground maybe she sh where is
it I don't know good question we lost
the nails I lost like like six of Call's
nails were they marked in Black too yeah
they were marked in Black too that's why
I'm just
like I
[Music]
wonderoo nail CH Wonder have to find
them seriously where did I put them
where could you have put them did you
stand up and go somewhere and take them
no why would I why would I would I wait
oh is it are the it's not these is it oh
it's those it's those it's those they're
like right there I'm blind okay oh by
the way isn't like oh no maybe not you
doing my whole hand nail yes I'm doing
your whole hand oh wait both my hands
you're doing both my I'm doing one of
your hands it be different perhaps uhoh
I I did I did the the big nails for both
hands oh okay I will try to in that case
in that case you want to do the smaller
yeah mix them mix
them mix them mix I did the so these are
like I think her cie's big and her her
thumb and her collab her pointer that
would be nice mix and match collab nails
for me um I was going to say I I have a
heart I'll just I'll just I I won't
touch this and I'm just going to
continue layering on this one okay okay
I don't recommend getting um eyelash
extensions if you are prone to freaking
out from like sudden like being afraid
you're going to go blind cuz like when I
cuz you're not going to but when they
don't they don't open your eyes though
no they don't but when my eyes are
closed and like I feel the tape and
whatnot and I feel the air on my eyes I
start to kind of freak out and I have to
ask them s let me sit up and like look
around for a second because oh they take
it often yeah the take they take off the
tape in Midway for you yeah just because
I have a b of panic attack go whenever I
go I always go to like a tapeless salon
oh nice they have there are some SS that
don't use tape so you don't have to
worry too much that could be good H
those are a little bit more expensive
though because they have more skill I
feel like these two girls have so much
like experience and these like enhancing
things that are so nice but I mean it's
nice and simple I don't go often I only
go whenever whenever I'm just like I
feel like it but once in a while once in
a great while cuz I I really like the
look of the extensions extensions are
really cute but I personally I have I
don't like especially when you sleep you
can't really like sleep with your eyes
like under the pillow because like then
your eyelashes will definitely come off
and you it'll bother you it'll bother I
heard that I heard that so you have to
sleep like face up you got to be so
careful moments and whenever you rub
your eyes when you're sleepy you're like
oh [\h__\h] and you see like the yeah it'll
hurt for whatever reason also um when I
do when I do Studio stuff in our special
suits right fabric on the gloves you're
talking about the invisible suits right
the invisible ones yes um that we use to
ensure that we perform our best at the
studio whenever I use them there's like
a fabric on the gloves that we can't see
but I rub my eyes sometimes and it does
not agree with the eyelashes and it
tears them off my eyes ooh really and
it's extremely painful yeah so I can't I
can't touch my eyes when I use those
gloves oh yeah they do not agree with
the eyelashes so you got to be careful
it's so painful I like screamed in the
studio holy [\h__\h] that sound that sounds
like a Horror Story yeah it was bad it
was extremely painful okay I got the
base color of this you guys what ni but
I'm going to gradiate them white
gradiate is that a word I'm going to I
don't know you know I'm going to make
them F will with white color oh white oh
yeah you have the wet slightly wet gold
and white is like pretty Christmasy
thank you yeah I like gold and white I
still think it looks orange it looks
orange to me what color which one oh
golden gold the gold I'll show you in a
sec hold in here they look orange if you
look inside oh they do did you put the
the powder on it not yet how's oh that's
the next Ira so confy she's just
dropping
sbms is that not so she
[Music]
talk maybe it's it's okay it's my
channel we always swear
here it just means that we're in very
much girl talking
mode all right what oh yeah right I
wanted to say
um don't do this without me but yes
after a nail salon we could
do trust me we could do a hair removal
Salon I'm good I'll pass on that
one thank you for inviting me I to CL it
would be so funny hair removal where
which what hair are you talking about
you have hair what you mean like Wax
yeah oh that sounds painful so what do
we do pull it off and then show the
stream the the hair that we pulled off
our B no we don't have to show it like
okay I understand like you know air
maybe what if we start bleeding you know
like waing some BL I don't know I've
never actually waxed remember you know
the legendary stream from uh one of our
Senai back in the day I do remember that
what there was a there was a Coco sampai
she did a she did a wax stream legendary
holy but she didn't show it of course
you know but the pain just hearing the
screams alone was satisfying enough oh
yeah okay uh I'm
good yeah I'll pass on that I pass I'll
pass guess myself some ID Girls done I
don't like painful do it they W do it I
don't like the painful experience this
is kind of neat looking I did get
eyebrow waxing done though once yeah
that's fun yeah ey waxing is fun and
then they make sure it doesn't hurt like
they like it's fine yeah I mean it's a
little painful but you look right after
yeah it looks
great did you only do it once no I've
done it a few times um uh recently I've
been like you know I've been he comy so
I haven't gone but whenever I feel like
active I go but well the only like
Beauty enhancing thing so to say that
I've done is um
permanently uh not just temporarily
permanently removing uh certain hairs
like my leg hairs ah yes yes you like
you're talking about not waxing but
you're talking about the um not even
laser laser um it's like another step
above laser laser is cool cuz laser is
like you get rid of the hairs I think
for a few months or so but eventually it
becomes like um permanent right you if
you go if you go often enough I don't
know about that but the thing that I did
is like forever forever is that not
laser it's not laser it's like different
like it's diff a differentiation is
there it hurt a lot though right it hurt
so much I cried so
traing that's scary but it doesn't hurt
for everybody apparently it's like it
hurt just for me because
I I'm very sensitive with that and and
my my hairs uh for example my legs were
like kind of thick I also did my my Wy
Wy W those are also pretty fake and
those are like sensitive areas you know
certain areas like my knee for example
weren't so sensitive so I didn't really
feel it on the knee but other areas are
like pretty yum
the inside like here the inside of my
thigh mhm I can imagine lower F yeah
that sounds painful that heart heart I
think I just throw this in though I
can't make it better no problem please
yeah leave it to me I'm the baker I'm
throwing mine into when that one's done
oh we put both them put both I'm a thug
I'll fit them both in okay all right no
problem I'll be
careful o you think what Mr I would
approve a a permanently hair removed um
Walky I think she would prefer them
smooth cuz she always appreci pie walkie
pie pie where walkie pie yes yes yes
Walky pie where's this wet towel here
wet
towel the communal wet towel so
cute o these These are these brushes
specifically for nail the nails probably
I use these brushes to Loop switches too
though for for keyboards what really
yeah didn't R get you a keyboard yes she
probably Loop the switches for you
what's looping switches you put you put
Lube on inside the lube Loop not looping
I heard looping yeah no no it's actually
it's it's it's not it's not the loop you
guys are thinking of it's It's keyboard
it's keyboard Grease Grease oil that you
put you brush it into is it specifically
for the keyboard yes
is it like the like the
W what's it called again
w w chat know
KX grade zero yeah we've got some
keyboard Enthusiast in the WD40 yeah
what's WD it's just a general like for
doors and everything that need oh yeah
no no no it's not it's not that heavy um
I don't think it's that for heavy
lifting like
that
okay oh is it done yeah I where you put
it under the mic I when are you now that
you have shown your
fingertips yes are you going to make
your fans happy with maybe a keyboard's
creation stream I want to I thinking
about it oh my God I got something
really thick on what is this I got red
stuff on W well the baker was a little
sloppy it looks like it might be a
little bit the the oh yeah okay sorry no
it's okay it's your nails it's your
nails so I mean that's cool I can take
it okay part of the process I'm going to
do one more later what keyboard switches
are on your keyboard right now Iris uh
oh um I think I have multiple keyboards
so the one I'm using right now are I
think they're the milk
uh milky silk switches from from some
sort of I forgot what what website was
they were colorful yes it's smooth but
they weren't smooth they were supposed
to be pre- lubed like Factory lubed but
they kind of sucked so I had to um them
myself Jesus Christ Lo
it milk and there's so many different
s okay the switches wait where's the top
for oh that's not really gir you doing
the gr gradiation now is it working hold
up I think it looks good it doesn't look
like powder wait let me see it's
interesting yeah I mean it's can you
guys see the gradiation gradiation oh oh
I want to see I want to see it how does
it look good on stream it's pretty good
how' you do that just started just used
the P this she just put the powder on
the top wow you're like a nail
artist you don't have to go to a salon
anymore you can just do yourself doing
what I see the pros do let's go I don't
know a new hobby maybe yeah you got so
much stuff left over chilling out after
stream with my cats maybe just come up
with some designs I don't know might do
it sounds cute okay then I'll I'll
attempt the same thing yeah
um fairly easy to do if you're an artist
you've drawn before right yeah I was I
was yeah no you draw some excellent
stick figures they're beautiful oh yes
yes works of art I love them no more
graphic design passion now nail art is
is our passion exactly it is much
girlier than graphic design that's for
sure I would say so does not work for
me oh wait okay yeah it just takes a
couple
coats you really got to be magical yeah
it's it works it works also this is not
unicorn but this is just uh this is
gradiation powder the ey Shadow wow yeah
kind of like an ey Shadow
deal pretty cool pretty cool
would you guys get your nails done in
Our
Salon you better say yes you better say
yes yes I'll be mad if you don't no
matter how expensive it
is you will say yes you will say yes
it's not an option yes yes I'll pass hey
yes yes yes most people say yes I think
they're lying but um they're being nice
and you know what I can appreciate that
thank you um that will be um 200 bucks
per nail set per nail set per per hand
or per finger maybe per hand maybe per
finger would be good yeah per finger
sounds about right let's let's be
business ladies yes
yeah new Shark Tank offer yeah dang it I
wish I had that idea nails for vtubers
yeah people do actually sell like nail
nail chips that you can just glue on
yourself afterwards yeah but they make
themselves and everything custom Oh you
mean like on Etsy or so yeah Etsy or I
don't know other other sites yeah but
yeah Etsy too I think they sell nail
nail
chips potato
chips I like those to
mina yum potato chips you I always got
jokes today yeah this is like incredibly
efficient and and effective isn't it
cool wow yeah Best Thing I bought for
sure it that actually works Wonder this
hair get on here right cats are sne look
at this gradiation guys gra
[Music]
gradiation
here that looks good I mean the lower
one looks darker but I don't think it's
actually that much
dark maybe it
is I'll just put a little bit more looks
like strawberry holy moly that's good
nice looking nails oh thank
you st nice contrast Irish nail na is
going to look good yay Kelly you know
you're going to make the second set for
her right oh of course so would we
should we try to make them look but
that's difficult cuz like yeah getting
them look the same would be difficult I
think although I think I can recreate
that cuz like basically you just used a
golden a couple golden coats then did a
white gradiation gradiation and then you
put some cute stuff on top yeah I think
I can recreate that definitely possible
you uh oh no wait those are for me yeah
these are for you oh so I'm not making
those I'm going to recreate those yes oh
so far just gray for and then I'm going
to probably put something like black or
white or something on it nice black gray
white would be really cool black berry
white black to gray to White would be
really cool the face black yeah and then
the tip is white maybe in The Middle's
gray how would that work would would you
do the gray first and then so here I'll
show you an example so the um can you
can you pop these in the oven oh yeah
pop them in the oven thank you yeah okay
so for example this bottom part you just
do some black and then white top part do
some white and that would be it oh white
and then just blend you blend how do you
blend do you blend it with one with one
oh okay so one side black one side white
and then just kind of blend it into the
gray in the middle pretty easy okay I'll
try that you give it a shot if it's
impossible don't worry though so an idea
so top okay what else we should talk
about something I'm almost done with
with girly stuff girly stuff what else
is girly um ladies oh when's the last
time you cut your hair um I mean your
wigs my wig wigs wigs wig is
our no no so you know the the hair that
you see the hair that you know um
because us us be tubers obviously even
if we cut our hair we're going to have
our hair looking the same the next day
for streams I got something in my eye oh
my god um C no Iris it's just you says
bells oh my God shut up no this is my
real hair I don't know what you're
talking about it's all wigs how do you
think we have short hair the one day and
then like long hair the next day I cut
my hair this morning when I collabed the
Subaru Senai and now grew
back I was going to take you seriously I
I cut my
bangs
stream no wonder if your bangs look
really clean U oh but no I didn't really
styled them today um but yeah I cut them
yesterday your bangs or do you just cut
them I cuz if you just cut them then
they kind of just I cut them and then
with a straight iron I curled them
inwards I'm so scared about using
Straight irons cuz like why like one
time like my mom was trying to curl my
my bags and then she burned my forehead
uh sometimes I do that too yeah that's
not that's scary but no mostly it's fine
mostly it doesn't happen it's easy you
can also do it differently you can use
like I don't normally use them but you
can you know do you know those like
clips that are like a roll oh the roling
um the rolls that you put you roll your
hair on and then you use a dryer on them
can you pass me yeah I got you but I
haven't been in but at an actual hair in
a while I should I should go because um
well I haven't gone in the hair salon in
while I need to reapply the grave
gravy gravy in your hair what what color
gravy are you talking about oh just just
you know my hair chicken yes the chicken
it needs gravy yeah to shine as
everyone's does but mostly Phoenix's
mostly yeah gravy Phoenix gravy
delicious we play gravy but I currently
couldn't do that I couldn't even afford
to go to I talk about my taxes on stream
oh don't worry my taxes took up
everything now I'm not liquid I am solid
which one's black is it this one or this
one I'm color blind I'm pretty sure it's
this one right here this this one's kind
of bluish this one's definitely black
this do you do you want bluish or do you
want black let's do bluish that could be
fun a fun twist try what did you use you
want it on the base right and then the
white on the tip mhm what did you use to
apply the stones and stuff glue
glue let's get that top is
disconnected okay I'm going to put some
cute H stones on I nails
[Music]
yay no uh curing after between the
powder and the the stones I think it's
unnecessary I mean I cure it anyway but
cuz you if you want it however you want
to do it I'm sure it's fine oh fine it's
fine it's fine how did you stick them on
just with your finger yeah don't really
have any special tools for sticking them
on right
now how to open
this going to open it and going to like
scatter bur out everywhere that's all
right I can dust bust it
open it's uh you turn it so this is open
and you turn it depending on which one
which gem you want oh there's an opening
oh so
good I'm going to make Irish some girly
Nails all these nails are girly
yay what could I think give me the
girliest Nails possible hell yeah yeah
get them out you just got to kind of
dump them in your hand and then put back
the ones you don't
want that's the best way I think are
there's several ones of the same ones
maybe I hope so I'm pretty sure there
should be it's hard to
tell oh no yeah yeah there
are oh nope that's
[Music]
wrong okay I'm almost done with
Kiara we're very close is it time to
stick them on might be maybe we should
wait till the end don't you think yes
until we have a a full hand
yes okay I
can't how is shiky hand Irish going M it
is somehow working but the black is
really strong that's cool though I like
it the white is like it's not blending
in like that you should show what you're
doing more to the camera cuz like yeah
it's just so the camera is so far away
from my
hands to put it's all right show them
every once in a while check in you know
it looks I think it looks cool even just
like that even without the white if you
don't want to focus too much on it I
already I already did the white so I'm
just going I'm going to continue try
okie dokie well it looks cool thank you
yeah okay there's a broken one in
here hey toss that bad boy out
I got finally the UV LED cured which is
the final final
coat it's the final top
[Music]
coat yes yes that is
me have you girls watched any girly
movies recently Barbie Barbie oh yeah it
was so good I L that movie it was super
cute yeah I Lov Ken Ken was the best KU
he's kind I want that Parker I loved all
the outfits so much it was a sweet movie
yeah I went to go see it with my friend
milky Queen she's another vtuber we had
a good time yeah I met her before I
remember yeah yeah we all went to go
hang out for a little bit it was fun I
was really surprised that even though
the movie was like made by the bar
company
that they like were so okay with
roasting themselves I know I respect
that pretty cool respect for self roast
self irony definitely appreciate
that okay l oh yeah the was the the one
who wasn't Ken um are you what Alan Alan
yeah I think it was Alan I love him too
also he's like in a rested development
which I love so much anybody who what's
a rested what's AR rested you seen it
yeah I've seen AR rest let's go it's a
really funny sit sitcom can you call it
a sitcom is like a drama like a drama
series comedy very comedy so funny quite
comedic freaking love it so much oh my
God so funny Ah that's where Iris yes
you know whenever I see uh um or
whenever I see the name of mum's first
original song uh new start new start an
I always say an
and the thing is for me it's a reference
to rest of development cuz there's a guy
he's really funny he's stupid uh he has
a car and he wants to also say that with
this car he's driving to a new start but
he couldn't fit it so he wrote Ana start
on his car on the on the plate that's
where Ena t comes from yeah I think I
don't know is that did they come up with
that joke it's pretty funny for me I
know it from there and then people s it
from M song so I was like ah the start
let's
go it's pretty funny I hope she doesn't
mind to much I wonder if she a rest of
development I wonder it's the first time
I've ever heard it in a start I really
like M's new original it's very good so
emotional it's very good for her as well
just fits her perfectly I think
mhm a my thing s great
song
I I can't differentiate these
colors what the hell let's be close to
the end here one last one final cure I
think this the thumb is finished for
sure perhaps a Holo cure a Holo Holo
cure
hure so good great game yes can't
believe it's free what else do we have
here there's also
this W okay stars all kinds of
stuff I like the gradiation best though
that's my favorite thing yeah we have
here that is genial pretty good to
choose Game of the Year changed my mind
well your game of the year it's
definitely a great indie game I agree
great fan game
incredibly good stuff I love the the new
update the the hola house yeah fish the
farming fishing farming it just new now
all we need are like heart events for
all the characters ah yes heart events
yeah you know like
a be friend then yeah bef friend is what
we would probably do most of maybe Mary
function
too oh
God all right kiars are finished let's
go show Closer here you
go here are the not thumb
ones do you see them
guys we'll have to take a clear picture
ah that was kind of clear for a
sec it's kind of out of folk God damn it
but there you can see that there's love
in there they're made with love what
about like no P there's all of focus on
this right in Fury I think so we'll just
have to take a picture afterward okay
hold this here's the here's the thumb
it's pretty oh let me see I need to look
at it closer oh cute there's a bunch of
stuff on there yeah so that's yours now
I have to make Iris Nails cute I am
still working on Kell's four nails gay
take your time sorry take your time are
they cute prop I shouldn't touch them
cuz they're a bit sticky
right they felt a little littleit a
little bit teeny tiny bit I cured them
multiple times but maybe it's okay even
if it's sticky it should be fine even if
you touch it yeah actually for reference
I should probably give them to I oh yes
you're going to make the second set oh
my God they're so
cute I don't know if I could do the same
oh my God I did my best uhoh uhoh no oh
no where is it where is it oh oh there
oh it didn't go out at
[Music]
all I tested the whole yeah we did shake
the table a while I just have glue on my
finger now okay there there's tissue
tissue tisue where's where's a wet
one last one to use I think I think it's
there the wet towel chaos yeah that woke
me up good morning morning good morning
rise and shine sleepy head wake up oh
yeah it's really early in America right
now right true it's morning sorry sorry
I would have done the stream earlier but
I was
dancing
so yeah she was dancing danc tomorrow I
have hatam
collab what are you and I thought it
would be funny to do like a meme review
but like kind of like from the past
eight months when she was gone so that
like catch yeah we can let her catch up
with memes
basically this has been going
on ooh yeah you got
it pretty I like these it's such a huge
brush what if I want to put like really
tiny things on oh um you use that yeah
use there's more sticks that we can can
grab from the table like things yeah do
I put the glue on this table so like you
you I think you get a tiny bit of it and
then you just actually no you put the
glue on the nail first and then and then
you put the thing on
topy like this as long as it
sticks all nice cured Nails these look
good thank you look good I think I'm
going to do another layer to make it a
little bit more blendy hopefully o it
looking like
um kind of looks like a painting I
feel but like good way what's ne ne in
English I thought you were saying
Maybelline or something maybe it's
Maybelline someone here knows German in
the chat and English both I only know
PES and BR foggy it looks foggy like
mysterious yeah I like it it's
cool it's not blending as much as I want
it to
though I don't know what I'm
doing well Kellie you could the start on
Iris Nails yeah do they have to match
the same as yours kind of I don't mind
them being different however you want
maybe because you know Iris you've got a
dual like personality thing going on you
know yeah I don't mind having different
hands with different Nails yeah tomorrow
she's going to take them off going to go
to the nail salon and be like please
take these off please I can't give me
some actually good ones it's okay though
gr cuz you're hii so it's not like
you're showing these nails to anybody
yes we'll be fine what are the other
Iris are these the other Iris Nails
these ones
uh yeah these are these are the leftover
two um oh okay there number two here
they're like stuck on this on yeah
because um yeah I I have to wait for you
to finish yours I think K I mean I think
you could cut them if you think you can
work on it when they're cut okay yeah
yeah yeah I don't have a problem with
that okay I'll cut them off for you oh
my go it's I think her Pinky and her
ring
finger okay nail and you're making the
other
ones I'm just finishing the first hand
yeah and then and then there's a and
then there's a thumb one more thumb one
more
there
okay we're going have to file it
thanks now
you the file these bad boys oh the the
tip yeah I the
tip I hate the feeling the sensation of
of fing something anything so zigzaggy
also like in school um back in like
what's before Jia high school elementary
elementary yes um in like uh you know
there's a class right where you like
craft things crafting things craft arts
and crafts arts and crafts there's like
this file paper that we would use for
like wood m objects to make it like oh
yeah sandpaper yeah sandpaper I hated
that so much what was what was wrong
with sander because it feels the same
way like it's so it makes me
cringe sandpaper cringe so [\h__\h]
cringe nail files are cringe taking 2023
it's true though you said I don't know
how I else to describe
it they give me like this this shiver
over my back oh I see I mean I guess
that is kind of cringy
sort of I would describe that as cringe
yeah yeah I would say maybe that's the
original meaning of cringe cringe has is
the original meaning about cringe like
ever since is that a be word I mean no
the the word goes back a long way but
it's changed the meaning it's taken on
multiple meanings over the years what
meanings would it also have besides the
cringe that we know cringe paper well
like you cringe in disgust from
something if you smell something yucky
you can cringe it's like a it's a a jerk
reaction to something unpleasant that's
exactly what I'm saying then then that
fits I would say I would say yes correct
it's not is
unsuitable yeah
well but I don't know sometimes I hear
people say that things are cringe but
they're referring to it positively and I
don't understand positive cringe I've
never heard of that girl you're so
cringe I love it it positive I've never
heard I've never heard of the US
positive contact just internet people
who I don't know I feel like one of the
one of the first things one of my good
IRL friends said to me when we met for
the first time was oh my God you're so
cringe I love you and we became really
good friends so I don't
know was that really a compliment or
just honesty God Mor you're being so
cringe I love you so much we're going to
be great friends I was very confused but
what I took it and ran with it and I was
like okay cringe cont just sounds like a
good thing it seems like it but I know
that's funny yeah who said that I won't
say I will punch them it's a
secret it's a secret a very sweet person
just don't worry about it just just a
funny way of saying
things interesting
suppose okay cringe
affectionate affectionate cringe yeah
basically sandpaper is like nails and
chocolate yeah I don't know how anybody
can tolerate it I don't understand
pretty
much okay please cure this oh yeah no
problem thank
you I want to put some some some some
kind of stone or something on I want to
make it sparkly but I'm just like is
there no there's no sparkly like um
glitter oh we have glitter we have a
[\h__\h] T of glitter we haveen us glitter
yeah we totally forgot about it oop have
glitter wait I have like a lot next
to are you top of those little bottles
yeah how do you how do you do that
without like a like I was thinking more
like you know bottles of like like
glitter I don't know so much I mean the
closest thing we have is this is kind of
shimmery but that's it I guess you could
attach the bigger ones one by one I
guess yeah if you want options Wonder
there you go I think another one is oh I
get I know how to use these never mind
um so if you want to if you want to make
your own glitter you mix like the
probably the the like a if we have I
think
there's like an ult one of these
probably three in one clear I think you
use
Clear clears and you mix it with the the
powder yeah yeah ooh smart idea yes I
think that's how that's how the nail
nail artists do it ah that is very
smart wow okay let's go do you want it
glittery sure or do you want it do you
want it not glittery do you want just
like maybe stones on it or stuff I think
just some Stones would be lovely okay
let's try do stones in St if you feel
like getting creative I certainly won't
say
no I'm but yeah we can make it glitter
if you want to do glitter I think that's
how you do it okay cool okay Stones what
where are the stones all these all these
yeah the four in the middle interesting
we need two more
black fancy black fancy fancy
I'm going to do I'm going to do pale
pink for eyel wow so you are making like
different ones yeah yeah well you know
Darkness and Light right you're doing
Darkness
ones kind of turned out darker than I
thought yeah for despair pearls are cute
yeah pearls yes but I just figured they
would be really difficult to apply I
don't know what color what color Stones
do you want cie just uh neutral like
white and black would be good okay
okay guys do you have some questions
about girls to ask girls like you know
anything really anything that is not
considered sexual harassment yes is also
how can I date a girl we can't help you
I I Feel Like Our advice is not going to
be great not that you know not that we
don't know is it like for heing yes duh
are girls real duh real real maybe still
under scientific hair extensions yes or
no oh I think we have some experienced
people with hair extensions I've never
had hair extensions they really hurt a
lot they hurt hair extensions sleeping
hurts cuz you rip it off bed well you go
to bed and it's like in your head and
they sew it really tight it's
uncomfortable but after a couple days
it's not that bad that sounds that
sounds scary yeah
M it's whatever no but it's expensive
see that's the that's the kicker it's
expensive very expensive the hair is
expensive cuz a lot of times most of the
time if not all the time it's real hair
what kind of questions are
these um let me get
something whatever these
questions I've made a mistake this is
really hard to do not attach to the
thing but that's okay I'll do my
best what are these question half of my
life is where did I put favorite piece
of silver
wear such a random question what green
grapes or purple
grapes type of muskat yeah I would say
green depends on the mood I like both
what is this Japanese way of describing
green grapes as
Muscat green grapes say Muscat is that a
Japanese thing I think so really cuz in
in Austria we just call them all grapes
but there's green and purple grapes can
I start over cuzz this is not working
yeah sure so hard to paint them what
would you detached from the ah they sure
they sure but I'm actually done with
these so but there's not the same ones
on here anymore all right maybe I can
find them here extra more bigger ones
here cuz this is not working out this
this is a line of normal ones okay a
smaller
ones okay thank you we need any more
sticks oh nice thank
you oh nice oh okay I'm I'm also almost
done figure out what color what sizes
these were this one is I'll show you
guys in a minute I'm doing really
detailed detail work so I don't know
what number it is I can't read
it
oh let me read it's like not on there
anymore just disappeared fent
away wait do we not have bigger stones
are these the the biggest we have be it
damn it's uh actually um kind of gone
yeah I don't know what maybe when I
cured it it it like melted away oh and
the the base coat kind of covered it oh
I see something but it's hard to tell H
well they were the two on the corner oh
two Corner ones okay so these right I
you know what I'll just test it like
this I'll look at them next to each
other
that seems
correct maybe
oh what what is this don't know how to
break this without being a rain on your
parade but a study found correlation
between repeated UV light exposure on
and skin damage that led to harmful
mutation I I quim where where we to
trust CNN I what I why can't k w i m i y
k w i m what does that mean what the
[\h__\h] is that not a clue of course I know
that like what what I've heard about
what I've heard about from nail artists
though is that the UV light is one time
using the UV light over in the lamps
over there for the light for the nails
is equivalent to like 5 minutes in the
sunlight so it's not really that I mean
you don't do it that often you know if
you know what I mean what that means uh
harm uh skin damage that led to harmful
mutation if you know what I mean what I
don't know what you mean what do you
mean I see I see you see it I mean I I
get that they're they're just giv a
factoid oh yeah okay it's not good
obviously mutation at this point in life
is just like everything's mutated
everything's mutated we are we are
literally mutations no true yeah we're
not human that is true I think ah do I
want a bit more
oomph or is just she wants oomph guys
you tell me in chat you tell me for
Irish
Nails
um wait those are cute uh see oh those
are so cute very cute oh Pinto there's
Pinto okay so uh this is the fum over
here the one with the extra stone is the
fum oh the painto is gone but maybe it
will come back
so
confusing and there's like three three
black stones on each and there's a gra
gradation Mickey Mouse nails
no you ruined it oh no you ruined it
Chad it's over
now oh wait that's wrong different
character go should I do more I mean
this was already so much work so let's
let's keep it like this I think it looks
great I wish Nails hand number one done
I'm going to wash my hands cuz they're
so stinky yeah go for stiky sticky
sticky sticky sticky with
Mickey oh my God they're not talking
they hate each
other you're not even denying it Focus
Focus decided I'm going to sleep over
just
kidding but I want you
C you can come say hi to them whenever
you're not busy the
wet wet towel the communal wet towel
sure thing communal wet towel okay I
need to make CI Nails what were uh did
you oh wait yeah need to make feel is
did you make like a second one for me to
paint on or did you only make one with
the marks just one I think well there's
this one over here that oh is that from
you I'm pretty sure yeah that's mine are
you still painting them Irish those over
there I know yeah you said I'm going to
do half of yeah yeah yeah half of her
hand except this ended up being more a
little bit more than half I'm doing four
so you can you can probably do like 1 2
3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 oh okay 10 in toal
okay yes cie does not have 12
fingers I'm going to try to copy what
you're doing so that cie can have
presentable Nails cuz she goes out a lot
right for business she needs she needs
to look good mhm for her business
partners we don't want to embarrass kie
yes so I'm doing I'm doing uh one two
three four five six normal like small
you guys could never embarrass me
they're all base coded right
looks like it uh no I don't I didn't
base coat it it does look base coat sure
did I base coat them they look like they
feel like it's maybe I base coated all
of them I don't remember anymore I think
I did I don't remember what I did so
sticky IR hands do Irish hands are so
far from from the camera it's like if I
want to say hi every once in a while hi
yeah them more often hi or like paint
like I did like hold and look I would
Shake too much if I tried to pain SI
sick it'll be exciting once you all have
the nails on we can show them off like
this
exactly okay nails so you did uh which
grade did you use I used um c c06 c06 c
this one this is4 this one should be
that okay and then for the rest is just
the is just the yeah the powders all
right baby three layers of the gray and
round three layers okay well well well C
I want to do the
same I'm using this yeah this
color can
Nails yeah the Hope nails are looking
good well I know they just look solid I
guess right now what color are you doing
well it's kind of like a whitish pink
kind of
deal but needs a little needs a little
more Co a couple more
coats stiti after I'm done with these I
do Karas right yes yes see make them
look nice please I would appreciate it
if you Tred to make them look similar to
what cie did okay I'll try I'm lucky
that I have the the hope of Des spair
theme that
I
indeed so Iris how does it feel to have
h two personalities oh I just feel very
bipolar that's all it happens do you
actually ever
like do do people in do do your viewers
ever feel like uh now is despair
time I don't think I I don't think I go
that hard on I don't think it's just
spare so to speak it's more just like y
y I'm sure Iris doesn't know what I'm
talking about but no I have no idea how
how Y is is Yus anyway is it really so
yabai no people are OV exaggerating
definitely definitely over for sure for
sure never beaten the yabai allegations
what's the most yabai thing you have
said or done on
stream good question surely there's a
compilation somewhere yeah by
compilation you going to look it up
more than you think she's
lying show us your true side
no they are overreacting I swear to God
they're definitely not exaggerating
somebody
says definitely over
exaggerating oh
what why is that your virus moment do
you know White Flag by
D what is that your
no nothing nothing is that just a song
no so I think I sang that I sang that on
um or or someone requested and I I
repeated the name I was like wa I think
I said White Flag but I added an L to
the detail
what it was an accident what do you mean
accident no no no so okay I was looking
I was looking for the song I was looking
for the song and um like you know caraan
right I was looking caran I was like
what is this white flag by I I didn't I
thought there was an L in I read it out
loud and and then I noticed what I said
yeah my God was that in in a public
stream yes I need to find the clip it's
it's it's an AR un archived so maybe it
surely there's a clip right I mean they
would be fools to not keep an archive of
that oh God but you know the artist
right no I actually don't you don't but
have you heard the song I've heard the
song
[Music]
in
yeah White Girl Anthem yeah mam Mory
Anthem and Mama Mory is like the the
white girl extraordinaire a yeah is she
like is her music taste very basic yeah
she loves Madonna she grew up wanting be
the only Madonna song I know is
the the the the like a like like like a
lovely girl like a lovely nice girl like
the very first time like a virgin yes
[Music]
T yeah every time I try to sing a
Madonna song in an uncraft stream I like
I I just never really thought about the
lyrics much and then I start singing it
and I'm like I get more and more
embarrassed the more I sing of it yeah
that sounds about right I asked mama I
was like mama myy the dead beats want
you to sing like a virgin with me and
and she said absolutely not no why that
would so lovely she was like no I want I
hear that do you think she will maybe do
it for me if you request it from her
specifically maybe I feel like that
would be perfect maybe maybe for the
very first time uh-huh uh-huh I see I
see I see yeah it to be like that wow
those look really good look at those
pretty
[Music]
wasn't there like a music note sticker
somewhere just went away oh no I
Disappeared oh it's my battery
Ry let's see is there a different you
can have my cable probably have a
charger take
mine yeah I think it would be best to
use that one right now cuz it might take
a while grab the
other open Siri I don't use
Siri please I'll say your name she'll
come back no no no no no I've never
talked with her before we're strangers
Siri doesn't know what you're saying
Siri feels offended by that Ser now now
I'm gone from the room am I not because
I opened Siri uh oh that's fine you'll
come back k out Siri I'm serious here
just don't do this to me I get it
serious oh wait I reach how would you
use a stand when you have a cable do you
upside sideways but sideways I wonder if
you could do upside down oh it could do
sideways okay we could do sideways don't
track as well but do I accidentally oh
never mind I'm already back yeah you're
back thankfully wow technology isn't it
great y technology I don't understand
technology really the only thing I
understand is oh no sorry I very you
standing on top of everything Iris I'm
sorry o I'm standing on the table right
now Bad Manners excuse me a man all
right no problem I'm going to have to
Giant WR or also smaller r at the same
time
you think you could possibly move
yourself down with your my yeah just
because I have to plug in the mouse let
me
try oh no make yourself kind of big I'm
overlapping no it's okay it's all
good might take a little finagling it oh
no I'm too big now uhoh that's fa you
got this you got this where did K go she
is okay there we
go am I too big I can't tell a little
small yeah little smaller smaller he
them out smaller actually little bit
more little more little yeah stop stop
stop stop and maybe shorter that how to
use a stand you to strike a wacky pose
and it comes out naturally JoJo
reference why I say A Jojo reference
well stand stand no Persona is yeah so
you know yeah it's like Persona where
they have like this thing this this
oisan behind them right it's like a
their superow it's their superpower but
it's like it manifests itself as
something kind of well it's not always
humanoid sometimes okay pass me the did
you already do top coat for for these
you did right yes I those are all done
okay where where are the um the there's
base coat B co uh UV and this is tough
coat okay thank you and also where are
the sticker looking things somewh there
like the I want to put a I want to put a
music note for Kelly a are there music
notes in
I saw I swear I saw a music note maybe
it's in this
one yeah yeah yeah it's in that one yes
yay oh music noise oh cool if only done
was a skull too oh yeah that would be
perfect right that would be perfect but
I doubt I doubt it
well I ruin
Co yay these are looking
great yay the cleanup Up's going to be
real fun yes it's going to be a blast
looking forward to
it K's head looks like it's bouncing
between Kelly and Iris like a pink she's
so bouncy she's so
bouncy KY children are so bouncy yeah
very very
bouncy that is true to True Girl how do
you open this uhoh need help it's like I
made a hole in it but then I don't want
to like I don't want to like spill
everything and make this bag like no
problem
let's
see yeah you might have to just kind of
dump some of them into your hand to be
honest okay one round of curing please
or this like somewhat okay yeah should
be fine yeah looks looks
clean yeah oh this is nice solid color I
tried to make it solid I'm almost as
solid solid a snake Solid Snake yeah not
not yeah metal metal gear I would play
Metal Gear if it it wasn't like you know
one of those where you had to like set
you know get permissions ahead of time
games yeah it is a little strict it's
hard to plan those yeah yeah what is
this question do you keep bridesmaid
dresses or try to get rid of them after
the wedding what of course we keep them
why would we throw them away we can use
them in another another okay a cocktail
dress or something cocktails yeah with
the ladies you think we we ladies we buy
dresses and a waving away after wearing
it w yeah that's a
waste do that that's a big waste there's
a Nintendo Indie Direct in if your house
I know I
saw sometimes there are some in Nintendo
directs where I have no idea what all
these games are like what are all these
I'm still waiting for 1080 snowboarding
to finally be released on the online
Nintendo fan cuz they announced it a
year ago that they will be releasing it
eventually snowboarding 1080
snowboarding it's like a retro game like
they they were releasing so many retro
games to be playable for free on the
online
Nintendo like f f I haven't played the F
991 so fun yeah and there's this game
that I I've been waiting for because I
played it when I was a child and this
was like I was watching this Nintendo
Direct and they were announcing a lot of
exciting things and then they announced
the stupid snowboarding Game T 80 SN
1080 snowboarding and it was the one
thing that got me like screaming at the
most excited I was like [\h__\h] yeah is no
and then they they still didn't release
they released everything else that they
said they would release except for 1080
snowboarding what the
[\h__\h] well surely it's on its way yes
soon something to look forward
to I need to go snowboarding cuz I am
too traumatized to go skiing in reality
but I did go skiing after our incident
in
Austria and um I've never gone skiing
before time to go maybe C can take you
in the winter I love H my favorite place
ever is SK is it is it easy no is it
doable I wonder but if you if you never
done it you can just start with like
getting a little teacher help you for
like an hour or two you you can pick it
up quickly I think but definitely doable
my problem was like I learned it a long
time ago and then I was pretty good when
I was a child was I just did it for a
week and that was it um in like a school
trip and then many many many many many
many years later I tried it again and
suddenly I was
like I sucked at it I couldn't get
better at it immediately and then I had
this accident and
H and that traumatized me so much oh I'm
sorry you were traumatized it's not you
why would you apologize I don't know
it's cuz we went together I feel
responsible no for no reason but it's
the freaking snow the snow was like so
hard what the [\h__\h] yeah like other
skiers they say my friend she's a really
good skier and she says she likes it
when it's like more of a like
solid no but interesting I wonder why
like almost like ice yeah skiing on
straight ice I feel like if it's more
fluffy then it's easier to like make
curves and all that cuz remember it was
really difficult you were like pizzing
down yeah Pizza the whole way yeah you
going back and what do you mean by
pizzing down like have the skis like a
like in this angle yeah they're in Pizza
mode rather than like straight parallel
you if you if you want to stop like if
you want to slow down you can do pizza
um but yeah K just went straight down
the pizza mode but like normally you
should like have them parallel and make
like curves right I would Pizza curves
somewhat I guess here please that's so
difficult oh these are done oh I didn't
noce okay so you use the this one or
this one uh this one this one and next
okay it's powder time I love the
[Music]
powder the gradient so fun oh yeah we
had pizza before doing nails I wanted to
eat pizza too but I got caught in
traffic big big traffic like I have
never been in such traffic ever it
happens but you got the rest of my
margarita yes it was delicious thank you
not a drink but the pizza right not the
pizza pizza pizza good the pizza pass me
that please yeah I'm almost going to be
finished with cie's nails finally and I
can finally start
on okay wait let me just do the last top
coat and I'm done I'll put some some
cute gems I know it's a little hard to
see but there's definitely a little a
slight Purple Gradient at the bottom
maybe I'll choose a deeper color this
purple looks deeper I'll do that one
which is the is it the Builder nail I
think so or is it the which is the top
coat uh it'll say top coat on it you do
one of those and then you do a UV coat
huh which wait wait wait wait this is
the top that's a top coat and then the
UV coat is the black one yeah that's
probably build two long skis oh so you
do two more coats you do top and then
you do yeah oh okay
okay that case I still have two more
layers okay I'll use the new
one and maybe it is maybe it is Builder
first but I mean I think either way it's
fine as long as you keep putting coats
on it and like curing it I think it's
fine but you might need to do the UV one
and then top coat after it's okay you
can do top coat I did top coat it's okay
you can do top coat UV and then top coat
again should be
fine that's what I did and they seem
solid so should be top coat UV top coat
yeah I think that'll be fine okay just
sticks of nail Sal yeah it's a science
it is a science a F very it's not easy
you know no or else everybody would do
it the hell what's going on what's going
on
this it's not applying on one side for
some reason yeah it like can you guys
see
this yeah that's weird like it just
stops applying on this it's kind of hard
to see you know can you see I can I saw
try try try push it a bit more it won't
it won't do anything no I put like so
much color on here and try rub it on it
doesn't go on it doesn't go darker so
weird maybe this part was wet or
something still so weird what try curing
it do it again try try C try car it at
once and then um try do try do it one
more time maybe a second layer would go
smoother I don't know yeah but I'll do
the other first um the is it just that
finger that one I think so I'm going to
borrow this oh yes
thank
you how many times you think to
graduation what kind of question is this
what did you get a math question how
many times greater do you think the
college graduation rate is for women
over men I don't care I think I I don't
know that is such a random question I
don't know I can't I can't help you I
don't care I'm sure that Google has the
answer Google Google a Google you can
call from now yeah Google Google gaga
very smart baby yeah what do you think
about Taylor's series to demonstrate
integrals convergence can you explain to
me what the [\h__\h] are you talking about
they're justor they're trolling y give
me girly questions I mean I don't know
girls can like science a lot yeah but
like I mean like more ask me something
about fashion or nails or
hair what the best way to plan a heist
well there I can help you oh yeah that's
a pretty good question actually I can
help you that to
B man I want to do like a huge like GTA
collab well I'm literally it's funny you
say that because literally wait where's
are you seeing that channel too did you
see it huh was she WR I request look
Iris you don't check out the the
channels that much yeah not really not
really what do you just like when you
see all the P do you just like sometimes
when I see the pings I I I noticed but
sometimes I'm like I I don't notice cuz
there's so many I have so much stuff
like piled up on my you just keep them
pink cuz I could I when I see ping I
cannot leave them there I have sometimes
I see p i see ping from like channels
that aren't even really active anymore
and I'm just like and that's why I
always have like at least two or three
ping like just piled up and I don't
notice if there's another one I should
really get I should I we should I should
really leave some of the channels are
already like you know like birthday
channels for like two years ago stuff
you know cuz I could never leave
something like unread because it bothers
me when there's even just one ping it
bothers me I need to get rid of that
Mark from the Discord icon on on my
TK maybe I did um I did beg I'm begging
right now for to make a yeah GTA online
uh role playay server and it looks like
they're going to do it role play it's
the same one that the um some of the I
think what was it the a lot of JPS do it
a lot of JPS do
ITP yeah yeah yeah yep uh they seem
receptive to it so it looks like it's
going to happen but it might is it for
only Ian or is it for like all of I'm
going to start off with Ian only I think
and then we'll see there's only 15 of us
right yeah yeah we'll see how it goes
after that a lot of us would join that
that sounds like fun you you're talking
about the one where like you can either
be cops or robbers or even like be
Sheriff being a baker and stuff yeah
exactly role play yeah they have like a
lot of random jobs I just played the
normal like GTA 5 and four like ttrpg
extreme and
GTA just role play it's fun I didn't
know you could do such thing yeah can
you pass me that it's a good time what
are these
nails this is so it's still not working
no it's like it's it's weird it's not
working as well as I my my first Nails
worked W it's okay that's fine it's that
DIY feeling you know do it yourself
okay maybe with the stickers on it will
look better
hopefully yeah cool
these are going to be very girly hope
Nails oh they look cute right
now oh my God little bubbles oh I'll
show you in a second chat hold on sorry
let's try to cure
these to any favorite anime this season
I I want to watch fre I started I'm
watching I read I read I'm reading all
of fre and up to the recent chapters
good W yes no frean is a it's it's very
emotional
yeah my personal recommendation is mik
Toad Micky toad yes what's that about
it's about these twins that pretend to
be one person ooh nice they put oh so
they're like they're trying to they want
to be adopted by this old couple but
they only want to have they only want
one child so they sneak in as one child
even though there's two of them cute
it's it's a comedy yes mystery comedy oo
that sounds fun yes cool it's by the
same person that did Sak yeah I love
that one oh it's so good I love good old
Sakamoto okay girls help how do I talk
to girls I can't seem to shake the fact
that they're girls from my when I talk
you just forget the fact that they're
girls yeah easy but he can't shake that
fact
off how to talk to girls
imagine I guess that he can't imagine
they're just a dude I would say but if
you can it might be kind of tall order
are these these yours you
all did you did you cure them yeah I
cured him okay nice thank
you all right I'm just missing a thumb
for Iris cuz you have I still haven't
even started on kiars oh that's okay
take your time take your time take your
time
[\h__\h] it's already halfast uh 11:00 p.m.
shot time flies let's speed it up let's
speed it up girls can I have the communo
wet towel please the where's the commun
wet towel oh where go oh thank
you wet you B time really does fly when
you're having fun I know I guess I'm
just really concentrated good thing
tomorrow I I don't have to get up early
yeah taking a what time is considered
early for you to wake up uh anytime
before
10 okay so iris is making an interesting
face okay so so wait that means um your
normal waking up time is like 10 12 12
okay okay that sounds normal yeah huh
what's normal about waking up at 12 it's
not really normal for me for me for you
oh wait so did you what did you think
when I said 10 anything before 10 is
early for me what was your thought cuzz
you made a funny expression well I
thought anything before 12 was early for
me oh for you anything before 12 was
early
yes yes that is exactly how I feel so
whenever I'm streaming I wake up at like
like 2: or
3: oh and people kfb always oh you want
to show it oh here let me
show it's kind of hard to see but
they're they're girly they're a lot of
like uh Pearl looking ones and like pink
Jewels you'll see later pictures there
it is oh there we go wow cute Pinto
PTO yeah they're hope Nails cute that is
so cute H
Nails cute it's how long do you stay up
Iris I stay up until like 6 or oh my God
that's worse than me wow that's K me
don't ever don't ever criticize me again
for my sleeping habits what time do you
sleep 3 to 4 these days that's so
healthy so Health it's so healthy I
don't remember the last time I Ste slept
at
three oh my God you guys call not so bad
right cuz we have to like yeah what time
do you do sleep cie me um I go to bed I
sleep from about I go to bed usually at
about midnight and if I'm playing games
you're a literal baby oh my goding games
I'll be up until 1 and then I wake up at
about 9 or 10 one that's like beginner
numbers what
yeah I mean I mean I used to be able to
stay up very late back in the day when I
was in comic school and I had a lot of
difficult deadlines but um I'm getting
old shinigami's getting old too old for
that no thank
you not for me I mean I've noticed maybe
it's the age I've been um able to fall
asleep faster way faster these past two
years yeah that's a big TASC and no
trouble sleeping right let I I do when I
try I have a lot of trouble
sleeping Trel true like now thank you
like now I can't I can't sleep through
even though I'm
tired and then I do one more top coat
right I guess yeah oh this is yours yes
this is mine top coat here's the top
coat great bless you thank you so you're
supposed to put the UV coat before the
top coat yeah it kind of like builds it
but you can still put a top coat on
first and then Build It Up wait I didn't
do a top coat oh you should do a top Co
you should do yeah you need to do the
top coat do that top Co I didn't I don't
think I did we cured them at least after
I put the stones I'm pretty sure we did
okay but yeah so it just cured the glue
I think yeah
yep um important important right so
you
e smaller smaller smaller Black Stone do
we even have so many left how sure we do
we we should right were T I used a bunch
of them too are they the same they're
the same black ones probably yeah but
where the where the pet go that was that
palette right and I need some of those
golden um no no no I I just I just
poured them on on here so if you need
some just grab
them it's hard to get them much come on
okay come come on you use the music note
anything El music not just the music
note no that's all I used oh you use the
the golden or the silver side I used the
silver side
[Music]
okay so
cute um do you have any more probably
not that was oh no there's one more
music
note oh nice good eye yes that's a good
bird last is that the last one oh
there's one more there's one more here
there's one right
here okay just one you know matched them
to what you made and then just some
black Stones right yeah black and then
and the and the Crystal regular Crystal
Clear Stones okay Crystal Clear Stones
here these
ones no you didn't use um it's in in in
this one yeah
go no problem hey Kelly are you done
with everything almost I'm just doing
the thumb I think I'm going to do a
little bit different it'll mostly be
purple and then maybe like a bit of dark
they red at the bottom I don't know
we'll see okay we'll see what we're
feeling Crystal Clear
ahu okay I'm going to try to be fast I'm
going to try to be fast too okay hey y
you you're doing it so so pretty
so you're you're doing it fast and
pretty taining T what's tting in English
uh detailed uh properer proper yeah
intricate skincare routine I do want to
hear skincare do do you even have girls
a skare rou skare routine I've recently
been I've recently have slight pimples
but um that's cuz I've been using
something that's
really yeah no they're not there they
they don't exist but um usually I do
facial cleansing and then after that
um I've been using Milano sleeping yeah
before sleeping and after in the morning
too um Milano CC and then it's just a
bunch of J Japan cheap products and then
oh but recently I've been using this
Lane reset and something reset IM IM
Immortal reset Immortal reset for
vampires this sounds really I don't
know wow that sounds imortal reset cool
that I received as a as a birthday
present from B nice
W immortal so
metal very cool it's a cute bottle
though like it has like these little
yellow like um Bops inside them that
like are supposed to be like Shia beads
or something that is good for your skin
I don't know Shia and stuff like that
that's cool and then after that just uh
oh
Sho
um uh milk essence or whatever you call
that you know the the
cream cool
yeah I don't really do much to my
face yeah that sounded like you know
plenty enough if you do too much it's
worse you'll hurt your face oh there you
guys went
away oh what again uhoh yeah oh no what
I'm
back I see us did I leave Oh that's oh
oh you're loading back in you're loading
back in actually for I see on my side
the it was like the stream was goodoo a
little bit maybe it was an internet
issue maybe thank you um okay yeah for
me um I just wake up in the morning and
wash my face wake up in the morning
like um but I do that and then uh after
well I I do like a facial scrub when I'm
taking a bath which every day not every
day once every 3 days okay this is Kiara
and then I use a moisturizer before I go
to bed yeah and I have
this is one hand right so does that mean
you need um one
two yeah yeah and need another another
two of these sizes right do we have more
of those maybe on this one I think
so nail yes the one big ones small
this I'm I'm going to Mark those away oh
you got that it just works out
perfectly thank you yeah I think those
are done
done those are done wait unless if they
still feel sticky maybe put them in the
machine a little bit more yeah bath
every 3
days can I get a black Mar they're
trying to criticize you for having a
bath every 3 days no that's not what I
meant I meant the scrub I used to scrub
every Jesus Christ no someone corrected
them Jesus I bathe every single day now
I wash my hair every other day not
shower well first you shower then you
get in the bath I so you do a j Style I
get in the bath first and then shower
interesting but that's only only if I'm
using only I'm like only if my
grandmother's not using the very
Japanese are you no no no your own btub
I I'm pretty sure that's what that's
what she's more Japanese
really I I don't know I think you can do
it anyway
but okay wait I'm trying to think oh
wait oh yeah you need these yeah big
okay I guess I I got to let me cut this
um wait where's the scissors
those scissors the sofa
scissors I don't like taking baths I
only like the shower because bath is
like I I lose my patience I tried
sometimes with like Lush back bmps but
even then I can't take it and I even
watch
Netflix you must be terrible at on we
were at the on I think that was kind of
fine cuz I had someone to talk to but in
a back up normally I don't have anyone
to talk to I just watch videos why not
watch okay what colors what colors did
you use Cy um I use just the orange just
the orange P which is the orange um
where did it go great question can I
guess as a reference yeah the other C
Nails yes here talk to your cats I'm I'm
not crazy okay crazy cat
lady I don't know okay um I to K orange
and then you put the white on top of it
mhm as the
gradient oh my God this looks so
nice thank you I did my best so
pretty okay I'm going to try copy this I
really tried
g g final where's the base coat base
coat base coat a base coat
here there you go Bas base coat why why
does she have her coat here B
jacket hey ba funny ba ha silly get it
it's Bae so
funny
silly do she move in or why does why are
her clothes
here Bae I wish you would I'll always
have an open space for BA
[Music]
a two sleepover every day
o when I said I'm going to sleepover a
moment ago you were
like your intentions are you know cats
isn't that
understandable I mean maybe you want me
to cure this yes please cure that I got
the base coat in there oh yeah of course
my attentions are
cats
understandable always always just all I
want is cats all I want that's reason
but I'm going to
meet C how many cats does she have she
had had one until now but she got a
kitten yeah seen the kitten I haven't
touched or seen a kitten in a long time
a your cat starv I'm so excited yay it's
going to be my highlight kittens are
special I'll take that
outow yeah cuz I'm doing a k off collab
of Robo Senpai yay well that sounds fun
what kind of songs you going to sing H
not tomorrow uh The Day After Tomorrow
Tomorrow is hot Tom we're going to sing
like uh each other's originals and then
a lot of like Japanese like I don't know
vocal honey Works Etc fun
stuff fun can you do these too thank
you getting tiny stones on there is so
difficult it's the details that matter
how to I dropped it
uhoh I got it I got it I got it have you
guys ever seen Perfect Pitch what's that
a Pitch Perfect a yeah perfect it's it's
one of them it's something like that
almost almost I've seen two how could I
make a
mistake that's
cute that's very cute was that not the
name
have you seen it me yeah yeah yeah but
it was
justand yeah something
like
song when
I'm going to miss me when I'm gone can
you create C that one good luck yes good
luck yes that sounds
like
you
[Music]
when I'm isn't that nice when
I'm you're going to miss me by my hair
you're going to miss me everywhere yes
bu my hair yeah I don't know about those
lyrics it's
okay does the person have like a a cut
off hair strand from the person and you
know you're L lying next to missing
could be by the hair why never
know what does it mean what does it mean
by that one second here you go all right
here thank you're welcome but did you
see the second movie no there's a second
one there's free I think or four even
really I think four is a lot I think
free and I I saw the second one recently
with my members okay I got you and there
was pentatonics in it just saying
what's
pentatonics oh my God what are
pentatonics please in lightness oh she
even she doesn't know see I don't know
what that is what the [\h__\h] we do not
know what pentatonics are what are those
is it Panasonic
[Music]
pentatonic uh with X at the
end this a acapella group Super Famous I
was going to say it sounds like a group
The the name of a group that I've seen
somewhere mentioned you probably seen
them before maybe maybe they're like
like the most famous A Capella band just
because they have a huge YouTube
presence oh have the communo town please
there you go one sec
sorry you're going to miss
me they even like they're American but
they also did like sometimes they did a
perfume perfuma aella remix really it
was so good that's rare perfume that's
really rare they sell out huge venues
crazy they became famous for YouTube can
you imagine that's pretty awesome just
like ass p p pic ponics
panas not quite the hair dryer group
hair dryer group ba knows ba actually
knows
something you seem so surprised I can't
believe iris is no
BOS she wow really what the hell that is
pretty rare I mean for this kind of this
maybe well B you have ba a big Zoomer
you do have a you know
reputation I I know all the things you
don't know she didn't know how Game Boy
Advance was Y what the
[\h__\h] are you kidding me Bae that's a
joke right you joking right I'm pretty
sure what we were talking about that was
D string check cast wa really
oh I remember that whole that whole
thing she's like I only had a DS or
something I'm like my God are you
kidding
me ohos what are we going to do with you
she's still she's still watching I feel
so bad cuz you know she kind of wanted
to participate in this but she's not in
Japan yet I want to be be here but now
she's just watching this whole thing
maybe imagine she was here right now
babe we're totally doing your nails
right now okay oh my God you have such
cute nails B hey girlfriend can you hand
me that uh top coat Co this is a
glue this I've been Glu with
timey no no way it kind of works though
I mean yeah it still works people what
thank you I've been gluing with a top
coat Mama Mia and I will continue to
glue is this you making this uh no so
the ones already done are from Kiara but
the oh no from you right and then I'm
doing the other ones the I I just color
did the did the color coat so far base
and then the the the orange color still
yeah what they already here
I think she was already here but since
she's just too busy she can't do today
yeah I couldn't do the 12th and then
yeah I originally wanted to make it a
little bit earlier right like on Sunday
Sunday yeah I couldn't do 12
but wait Bae could you have done it
today
B oh my god did we [\h__\h]
up oh
no no no I am
sorry no wait she's not replying
anymore maybe she's taking a there she
is no d w w w w d don't worry worry
worry worry worry don't worry worry
worry next time we'll get to hang I'm
not worried we'll get to hang out with
each other
surely okay I'm now finished I wonder
what kind of Zoomer Nails Bae would have
made yes Zo zomer Nails Zoomer Nails you
just automatically write them off as
Zoomer Nails yes but hey Zoomer Nails
can be actually kind of dope Ba's nails
are always yeah they're always very nice
so I trust her fortnite nails all right
guys peep this hold up is fortnite like
a Zoomer
game I yeah I think the like I never
played it but like from what I know the
biggest player base is like young kids
under 15 hip cool kids it definely is
yeah Iris Nails all complete wow I'm so
excited to glue them on now I need the
top coat for real but I should I I
should cure it once right yeah well
maybe you might want to put the UV have
you put the UV on it yeah yeah yeah okay
so cure right and then and then what top
C the UV well have you been putting the
Builder gel like the UV gel no okay
maybe we put one of these coats on it
okay can we can
we these on too and what are the
individual ones that I gave you the uh
which ones we talking oh yes right here
yeah yeah I got you thank you what's
what's rler rler Nails RZ Riz nails like
what probably really shiny and
glamorous right
ve have I've never I still haven't had
beite me neither really I thought that
was a EU thing oh never mind no it's an
Australia thing Austria Australia I am
from Australia yesr austral Australia
all right I'll put you I'll put the UV
on these I think Bae U was like I think
she invited me to the veg my challenge
thing that she did but I couldn't do it
yeah do it again BS do it again nice
I'll be there yeah could be
fun brand new challenge oh there they go
they're back what was Marmite what's
Marmite H that's an equally yucky thing
I think oh wasn't that the British thing
yeah it's the British one so hard to B
what's more dis on the singles it's
really hard season two
yes beite what are you doing why you
panicking cuz I I flipped over the nail
the single nail the single Nails hard
are pretty rough yeah oh is the curing
done wait are you doing it for me yes
I'm there for you so cute
yeah cuz I mean it's just easier to do
that
way cool thank you no problem that
should do the trick so then you cure it
and then you do the top coat
yeah I keep flipping it okay let me also
do a u coat on my own cuz I on the iris
Nails cuz I didn't do it here you go
thank you careful top is not
secure K is helping me I want to be a
helper because I'm finished so oh my God
y shoes it's okay take your time take
your time just hanging out is there a
danger that things move around I don't
really think so I would like to cure
this single nail do you go of with do
you go over the stones too yeah yeah you
got to kind of include them I
feel kind of
important wow these are so cute you guys
did great on these oh I they're all so
cute even though we're beginners they're
turned out so cute all of this very nice
it's not as difficult as as I thought
yeah totally possible a little bit of
practice and maybe more planning ahead
of time like what do you want to do and
all that maybe yeah can be even greater
I think so as
well W dad moved what so much for being
glued you little [\h__\h] get back there
what are you using the glue for no this
is now the UV light
thingy but I'm pretty sure for the Irish
ones I really used glue mhm pretty sure
I feel like you did
too at that nail just a
sec well well maybe all the coats will
solidify it I think so hot glue hot glue
would be a solution hot glue I'd love to
have hot glue on my hands right yeah I
bet that would be beautiful something
kind of avangard
yeah yeah why do you sound so
glue thank you here here's this one
should be fine thank next please drop
that you I got
you believe it all we're getting there
we're getting there how many coats of
orange did two two
okay two coats you remember your coats
mhm I just I did like 20 coats or
something I don't even know anymore I
mean that's good though the more it
coats the thicker it is indeed the
better I mean I think yes we love thick
okay um curation please you got it
all right let me grabb this Iris
Nail all right there you thank you no
problem and then all right we're curing
the iris
Nails all right time to bake and then
this too right yes please Okie doie damn
she got a whole Bakery got a whole
Bakery right over here leave it to me so
M
[\h__\h] yay you know this way doing it this
way we're not exposing our skin to the
new be less damage
precisely so smart Callie will these
nails allow you to select the proper
songs on roller coasters what shut your
mouth shut they love making of I picked
the great comments what happened all
right it's okay so I went to Universal
Studios Japan specifically because I
wanted to ride on the Hollywood dream
coaster and listen to ad's show
cuz I love that song a while ago um
before our trip no no no it was after
after um you know kind of close to
Halloween is right because Halloween
song and uh I literally just wanted to
listen to that and I tried to select the
song on the roller coaster and my nail
was too long so I couldn't put it touch
no inside it was a button inside of like
a little like you had to push and maybe
like you can go like this I couldn't put
my Knuckles was too small was too tight
they're like you guys assume that I
don't have you should was there somebody
sitting next to you yeah but I didn't
know them but you can still ask him
please my nail girl things my nails to
long was embarassing this one
song Whatever how how long was it longer
than these yeah much longer damn girlly
yeah I didn't know because the the claws
I mean the salon lady asked me she was
like how many centimeters and my
American brain is like I don't know how
many did you answer inches yeah if if
you if you live in Japan maybe it's time
to learn centimeters I know seriously I
just made like a guesstimation pretty
much and that was wrong and it ended up
being much too long oh Dam
it thank you you're welcome now I guess
another top coat or should I wait even
longer who knows you oh don't forget
these here you go I'll wait a little bit
longer I just wanted to pop these in
here really quick to dry I also have
these that I want to pop into okay all I
can do both yes please
look really good nice oh yeah um uh I'll
top coat the Irish ones can you top coat
the the C ones yeah oh I already did
done yeah UV and top coat yeah both girl
I'm not doing anything over I finished
she is I'm just hanging out speed I'm
Speedy I feel like this could be your
secondary job maybe I don't know it
seems like a good hobby yeah maybe we
should take a picture of these like
disconnected laid out on the table first
cuz maybe we don't want to put pictures
of our hands on the SNS you know yes I
mean I'm fine with it but if you guys
don't want to I understand I think I'm
fine with it I mean where's the
difference yeah gu that's true can put
some beauty filters on them yeah Beauty
filters yeah make them look like baby
hands all the shinig gumy wrinkles get
them out and okay that's a girly topic
do you girls have like a go-to beauty
app I don't like uh yes I have one I did
but I don't really use an out I don't
take selfies don't take selfies not
anymore but like what what's the app
that you like to use it was one called
b612 that's a one the Japanese girls yep
back in the day several years ago it's
available outside of Japan too guys in
the App Store b612 it I did go back to
it recently a little bit it's a good one
I also use it sometimes yeah it's a good
memory mm I'm too lazy to use the the
filters now it takes too long to to edit
right what am I going to do send like an
edited picture of me to Mama Mory like
maybe or to me okay maybe don't think
about it thank you I use Beauty Plus
mostly but that was such a it used to be
such a good app but over the years they
keep on making more and more features
that used to be free now uh not free
anymore it's like what the [\h__\h] those
are basic features what are you doing
don't take this away from me girl I feel
it honestly pisses me off sucks you're
very valid when I rip up and then I go
to cuz like there's so many other apps
we all have the same features and like
they're literally like destroying their
business because I can just download a
different app and then you know true
that
girl yeah you tell them you tell them be
plus sponsor
me I wonder how that kind of that would
go I did recently think about um a
sponsorship that I would like to have
that maybe sounds difficult at first but
I know how to do it I want to I want to
get a a ideally I want to get a Dyson um
sponsorship cuz I want those fancy hair
dryers I have a Dyson the vacuum cleaner
would be cool too but I want the hair
dryer I want the whole I heard that one
doesn't I heard there's also one that
curls your hair the cuz the the the hair
dry has attachments yeah and also like
basically what you do is you just put it
close to your hair and it automatically
wraps your hair but I heard it it's nice
it's cool but it's not not very like
aici time effici you have to master it
you know but I want to try it out with
like a a a wig head oh yeah just for I
like style wig yeah that' be cool that
reminds me of something there was like a
product um on they used to they used to
have this product you know when you'd
call like
$19.99 someone in a chat's roote you
have an ionic haird dryer I have an
ionic hair dryer is it like the Dyson
one it's not Dyson no it's much cheaper
than that no I haven't but they say talk
about Iris Iris talk about your ionic
hair dry I I have an ionic hair dry I
have an ionic toothbrush what what's
ionic what is that it's it's a it's a
thing I don't really know how to explain
it but it's a thing that's very popular
in Japan I do see it on the use the
power of
ion what the [\h__\h] is that I don't really
know either but it's apparently it makes
your teeth really squeaky smooth when
you use it cool I like sounds neat the
hair too a hair too ites makes like your
hair smoother yes when you dry it with
it I recently am too lazy to dry my hair
so I leave I leave the house with wet
hair and just let it air dry inside the
taxi whatever works that's what I did
today too nice Tas I see
Theon yes also a lot of products in
Japan yeah the power of eon right power
of eon maybe that's just a Japan thing I
don't know but it's you know a lot a lot
of things a lot of things have
it
they're atoms molecules with an electric
charge I don't know how they used to
science what Atom molecules with an
electric charge tldr static electricity
to get ionization going static
electricity it's everywhere what I think
maybe what scammed R
scam stop saying that if you're saying
that a lot of people in Japan
believe in that okay eons are not 100%
scam if these products work is another
thing
though you guys don't believe in Eon in
the power ofon all the people in Japan
believe in the power of I I swear
marketing gaming okay well I'm in Japan
and I don't believe in the power of you
don't well I haven't seen enough proof I
feel like I I bought a big pack of them
what big pack of what ionic toothbrushes
there was I bought a 20 pack on accident
not electric how do you buy so
many electric no no no they're ionic
they can be ionic
recomend so I bought them and I didn't
notice the difference I noticed right
away there was my teeth become super
squeaky but your was electric right no
no it's just you you put your thumb on
the on the part and it's it's the metal
you have your thumb on the middle that
sounds like a scam no it's expensive
it's cheap you know you know what you
should use instead actually Iris um
there's this thing called the smile
scrubber stop stop you ruined it I had
such a straight face
present is call trying to scam forget it
my face was so straight I was ready to
throw Iris through a loop I was so ready
D I should have given you a sign Kiara
bear with me no Kiara has
K will never accept my what were you
going to try to do to me shark uh Shark
Tank um I did a shark tank stream
yesterday with re sh yes and we got a
lot of like girls to participate from
and ID to make me like proposals that I
could invest in if I want to if they're
good
Kellie so brilliant had very many
original ideas original Super original
things that don't exist just so you know
ooh and one of them is a small scrubber
yes so it's this thing where like a
piece of plastic and it's got bristles
on it and you take it and you like scrub
it on your teeth and it cleans them so
it's literally a toothbrush I've never
heard of that item in my life it's worse
than a toothbrush because she doesn't
even have a handle okay well you just
hold it's like a sushi it looks like a
sushi looks like a sushi she she Lally
that was part of the cute design I I'd
be fine with putting a handle on it you
know but I don't know toothbrush I've
never heard of that before that sounds
her second idea
was
um the the paper taper the paper taper
like when you have Pap well when you
have a bunch of papers and you want to
organize them right so you get your
paper and then you use my my piece of
tape the paper taper to tape them
together to hold them cuz what else
would you use to hold your papers
together right besides the paper taper
what is so funny besides a paper taper
yeah honestly the paper taper such an
Innovative Innovation so Innovative oh
my God you're genius thank you nobody
would have ever thought of that ex you
third thing was that you brought you
gave three I yeah the problem was the
problem is she says the problem is that
you know you only have drinkable water
at home nowhere else how are you going
to not like dry out
outside how do you don't you wish you
had the drinkable water outside of your
own home like if you could take it take
it and hold what
I that is talking about a water I know
what that is I've never heard of it my
life have you never heard of a water
bottle that's not a real thing that's a
fantasy object the hydro holder is my
patented idea yeah she just came up with
something like that Hydra holder idea
what's the difference between the Hydra
holder and a regular water bottle please
do tell what is a water bottle that's
not an item that I've never seen that in
my life where did you get that where did
you get that stop showing me fantasy
items in my home wait I've never seen
that in my life what does it do it's
clearly a ripoff of the Hydra holder
they're stealing my product they saw it
on your show do you have tape somewhere
that I could show you no forget it
forget it I I it was a mistake talking
to you about I knew you'd never seen my
Brun forget it whatever so funny fine am
I the only one still doing it yeah I
think so excuse me it's okay no you're
very close I'll do my best to get this
done up hey meow meow what are you doing
hey meow meow she just oh ghost cat is
just chilling he's sleeping yeah he's
not shaking he doesn't look scared at
all he's happy cats are still w huh yeah
he was weirdly okay with subba Senpai
even though we were quite loud sub
Senpai is a loud lady both both of us
got pretty loud but no ghost scat was
just chilling and he wasn't afraid of
her energy and like she's intimidating
she was was she like nod was she
screaming screaming directly at goad
maybe that is the problem she did sit
outside the cage and put her hands and
and did start talking pretty loud at him
but but kobo's so cute and she doesn't
mean no Kelly
Koba needs to learn where to bound the
RNA she understand I don't think she has
any fur babies parents are discussing
how to
raise she's un
raisable yeah I mean it's okay you're
you're all right little buddy right now
he's okay he just he's shy he gets
nervous did you do two layers of the
white or one layer um I did two okay let
do one more then
yeah cool
yeah we're getting to an oh but actually
we have to file them right after we cut
them off no you think it will be like a
clear C oh maybe might need to file them
a little bit do we want to start cutting
them all yeah it might be a good idea
yeah it might be a good idea since you
have time
okay danger scissor by Irish leg oh yeah
B oh no I'm going to cut my leg don't
hurt yourself right here you
go you're really matching the vibe looks
good sure okay um I'll cut Iris ones and
then we just put them on our nails can I
put these on two sorry thank you so you
want to file them K even though you
think nail files are cring I would not
file them person but W they might need
it right oh yeah well then why don't you
cut them and I file them okay that
should be the flow should I cut them as
close as possible to the it would be
T um where is the nail here it is I love
to file some nails don't you Lads Lads
Lads Lads do you guys like the file
nails they're still a little sticky so
some people F yeah I'm just like wonder
why they're still so sticky right it
concerns me it concerns me that they're
really sticky yeah they're supposed to
be really smooth right it's okay sticky
maybe you shouldn't put them on
today cuz now when we go
somewhere how safe is maybe more human
be light does does that dry them yeah
it's supposed to yeah maybe after we put
them on we put our hands underneath the
light ones that could be a good
idea okay these ones oh these ones are
oh CI C's uh the CI ones that are made
by Iris are very dry I think oh nice
nice okay
lucky I I put them twice inside the UV
so that it would dry cuz I felt like the
one time was a little too
[Music]
wet okay oh to is having a she having
dinner yeah she's having dinner she
hasn't eaten dinner yet her first dinner
yeah she eating until now I heard her EA
dinner again dinner again and also
dinner dinner she's like a Hobb cat
dinner to yeah
exactly oh oh this one's so feels a
little bit so not so dry but oh well
mostly fine yeah
to my cat emotes are being used for
babies Oh I only now noticed that the
thumb is is not gradiented oh for
Callie's side that's fine I'll I'll it's
okay to be a little different M it's
quirky don't worry about it quirky I'm
so quirky too oh my gosh really she's a
quirky girl oh my God and a
quirky Lord have
mercy like
[Music]
static that one is so liquid that you
can see it all over the oh yeah that is
really liquid what happened what the
[\h__\h] it's all liquid liquid did you did
you do the top coat at the end uh these
ones uh I think C top coed they did they
go in yeah they went in maybe they need
to go in take another another
pass I
think should be fine after yeah yeah bit
okay one more
pass they are definitely more liquid
than my bank account oh my God liquidi
lots of lots of money jokes
frustrations fingers are so
sticky
is Yum Yum
Yum oopsie I covered the camera I have
where is
the an Irish should arm wrestle for the
title of Queen noodle well we can't do
it here right now the whole table is
like yeah there's too much stuff on the
table didn't you destroy crony Iris that
was
um what was that that was insane yeah no
I I suddenly I suddenly had extreme
superpowers um that's wild yeah yeah I
don't know what happened it was just for
like just for that one one to two
minutes all of a sudden I just
grewed strong really strong know she she
made Bay fly way you know that was
amazing yeah that was one of my
favorite
funny oh did you put a star on this yeah
yeah oh thank you yeah [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] uh can you put this in like this in
this way scissors explode I don't know
this one's already done never
mind okay I think oh it's toilet time
I'm sorry if it smells really bad she
stinks so terribly it'll go away the
weakest myth versus the weak excuse me
I'm was that the
weakest between me and G we had like you
know the like maybe depending on the
hand I won oh stinky I won versus she
won
Fu cuz when I was when I was wrestling
good I with my left hand I won but when
I was wrestling with my right hand I
lost cuz I'm left-handed right that
makes sense I mean it's kind of hard to
judge with you because you're
left-handed I was are you right-handed
I'm right-handed yes damn am I the only
left-handed Ian I'm sure there's more
left-handed than you right no I don't
think so none and myth wait Kelly you're
not left-handed no oh none and myth and
Jesus Christ tutu God damn it it's okay
you did a good poop oh my God is it only
is it only tutu has sticky poop yeah
ghost cat is clean as a whistle
interesting booty don't don't poop shame
her I'm not shaming her it's just
Jesus God she's so stinky that's why I
use my Robo toilet hey I have a robo
toilet too but they don't use it they
don't like it especially ghost cat he
enters it and poops outside of it to
spite me I love that I love that for him
yeah a lot of cats get scared of that
toilet should I cut them
off yeah are they dry enough
so no now there's my my um fingerprint
on them maybe one more round just one
around I don't see your fingerprint
silly just a little bit that is that's
why I think I thought why don't we put
them on and then do one more coat
but not no more coats maybe no more
coats just UV light okay
oh
wait I didn't want to do that yet wait
sorry sorry can you give that back to me
real quick thank you no problem just did
a little she said sorry sorry my poop is
stinky I forgive you for now for now any
games you anime girles are planning on
playing coming up um Super
Mario what is that what's that is that
different from regular Super Mario yes
it's a remake of an old very old very
good game really good too like from what
has been shown so far people are happy
with it I'm hype I'm hyp and I'm going
to play t of arise DLC of course o nice
S
tails I'm also going to start building a
lot more in Minecraft I think I have a
lot of really good ideas I want to try
and I need to find it my own soccer
biome I really want to your own I told
you you can use mine really in the
server yes give me those cords girl I
can I can give you a tour so you can
find them o yes please do we can play
together sometime soon I'm trying to
make my own Island so I I wanted to get
a bunch of Sakura seeds I guess Island
are you making like an animal crossing
Island well yeah just a myy island you
know that's such a cute idea that is a
really good idea trying to recreate an
animal crossing Island in Minecraft that
is amazing actually genius that's what I
was thinking you guys were trying to go
with that would be cool yeah lots of
different Minecraft ideas these days I'm
so bad at building a Minecraft that's I
never build anything but you built that
amazing watermelon Farm
yeah that that took a that took a lot of
looking at the YouTube guide while doing
it it's very very convenient cuz like I
I get a lot of watermelons there and
then I bring it to my phoenixon Farmers
they like to trade the Watermelons I'm
glad it's useful I mean I haven't been
playing Minecraft like that for a while
but I'm happy CI is back in the
Minecraft world yeah I didn't really
think I'd get back into it but after you
like swore off of it completely never
again never no more Minecraft yeah I
don't know I was kind of super done with
it but I'm having fun
[Music]
recently wow Minecraft is one of those
games for our whole life like everybody
plays it so if you don't it's like kind
of missing out a little bit maybe true
but I really want I'm more excited about
the GTA thing yes GTA I'm so excited
really want them to hurry up I'm ready
for that I love me some
G yeah hand s hands oh people are coming
in and haven't seen hands in a while I
guess
handsy my my hands are very busy right
now wait time to get
handsy my Knuckles really pop out sorry
about that hey you watch yourself there
lady pop out yeah you me to crack my
Knuckles a lot
so I've already cracked too
much nice
good hey very nice can we get a
pin yeah
y that is iris's uh kiaha Nails inspired
by Ci's kiaha Nails yes very good some
of these are from Kelly oh yeah some of
these are
from which ones we keep a secret these
are all of Irish snails are done I'm so
excited to actually see oh they're so
cute oh my God up hope in
despair oh my God are they sticky still
no not really okay they feel fine to me
hopefully they don't get on my futon
when I sleep tonight you should be they
maybe wear
gloves oh no when I take off my gloves
and nails are going to disappear I'll
forgive you if you were looking like
what K loves corn and
pineapple I love corn and pineapple
together I mean no separately would be
ideal but you
know it's past midnight by the way it is
16 minutes midnight is
okay and we still have to record that
thing
[\h__\h] damn it I already told I already
told them that I'm going to be a
daylight a daylight yeah yeah you can
record it I'll record
tomorrow I I don't know if I I I I have
a microphone now for the Airbnb it's
this one's really good is there a pearl
where's the Pearl um Pearl
I just don't know if the Acoustics are
acceptable in the airbn beam what about
the
studio I am not using I am using it
tomorrow maybe I can do it tomorrow yeah
be I mean we'll see but I am using it
tomorrow okay do you think you think
I'll be forgiven I do it tomorrow is
today the deadline no deadline's
tomorrow okay okay I will be forgiven
yeah no problem y work is never done it
really never is done never ends it's fun
at least it's fun
right I mean right now um I feel very
stressed but the dance lessons that I'm
having with other people not solo are
very fun it's nice to not dance alone
you know yeah nice to have someone to
dance with and learn a dance together
with cuz that's a nice bonding
experience more fun that
way
Bond
okay very soon it's all coming together
oh
boy it's all coming up
[Music]
wah okay Nails getting there there's one
part that doesn't want to
have are you singing pineapple
yeah we're talking about corn and
pineapp yeah cuz they should I make a
corn song after pineapple should I make
a corn
song that's going to be very farmer is
right it doesn't really have a great
Ring to it maybe I could sing about
someone being corny
corny oh
my every time you buus C I wouldn't say
it so blatantly but pineapple I don't
know if you've noticed it is quite a
horny song really M yeah I didn't notice
I would say so it's not about um just
watching the PV be like oh it's
it's not about swingers though just what
what's that is that the common theory no
yeah people have pointed out to me
because pineapple is
apparently a symbol for if I understand
correctly old people getting together I
thought that was lemons no that's
pineapple a swinger party right swingers
right swingers I'm going to probably put
a pearl to cover up some of that stuff
that's okay no worries do what you got
to
do but has nothing to do with but still
pineapple lyrics are kind of horny even
though it sounds like a fun cute
song I see I didn't come up with it
sleep talking is also horny yeah true my
my my lyric writer Mooney might just be
horny maybe mhm I told her the her I
told I I have did she confirm or deny
she she just laughs about it okay she
like no please understand please
understand but all her songs are horny
if I don't tell her to write something
not horny it's always horny it's horny
girl be like that horn horn yeah horn
okay I think I think we got the mo nails
are done now Irish horn Irish IR have
two you surely hav't told that before
right what Oh you mean my horns my
lovely horns yeah they they've grown
shorter though they've grown shorter
they used to be longer so you're less
horny is that what you're
saying in the beginning maybe because
they're shorter they're shorter happened
what what happened since whole life that
made you less
horny
Jesus what is this
conversation she had four horns before
yes four yeah I had like two some
smaller horns extra edgy yes it was
extra edgy I respect it only have two
horns just internalized the horny H what
you have just internalized was it
externalized before
internal this is the girl talk I was
waiting for they grew inward so how
she's that if they grew inwards that
means the the horns are stabbing my
brains right now stimulating your brain
oh my God no wonder no wonder I can't
think straight
recently no no no no no what I'm just
pointing out the horns in this
[Music]
room you haven't eaten your your ultum
Mami yeah a we were too busy with these
nails also with these sticky nails I
don't want to touch the ultam where do
you get the where did you get the the
big the big
flowers um you mean the kind of foil
looking ones right the big ones I only
have the small ones those oh should be
in there I opened should be thank
you's going to walk around because I've
been my legs have been like folded in
neck Hort yeah I had a big L day today I
did not skipe L day today cuz the the
choreography I was learning is like so
Leng intensive my walking machine how
many do you need just one big flower
maybe okay
hey that stinks that's pretty stinky I
thought fin don't sure than
you try to use a
silver
you hear her of course I hear she wants
me she wants you oh are you hungry so
bad I need to wash my hands so I can pet
tutu my leg they're all so far away
now will meanwhile I'll Pet
Chat Iris yes I'm trying sorry I worked
so slow embarass it's okay you got to
just take your time take your
time can't rush
s isn't she so
cute if only her poop did not stink
stink anymore story of my life it's fine
now but
God
little
[Music]
little she she getting aggressive in
terms of cuddling she's cuddling the
fence yeah intensely she really wants to
cuddle you can you
come where's the other nail where the
other na I'm coming
back not going to leave you not going to
leave you please don't leave me I'm
never leaving we're back we're back
sorry I had to throw some trash away I
apologize no it was no no we here we
never leave us thank you never leave us
maybe we can start some cleanup yeah
that might be a good idea I'm still
doing this um it's okay okay wait can
you can you put the this in there sure
yes thank and can you take that one out
the one damn it I just washed my hands
and I'm stick again guy in there there's
just a little dude here you go thank you
all right do you want to keep all these
like boxes for to uh don't need the
boxes I'll probably just put all of them
in that that box with the glitter stuff
in them is where what I'll put all this
material
into s hats can I try
one try them on try them on I like
hats I like a
balloon she's so excited about this
she's so excited about
this is
the it's not even what it's for handing
can you like I like this oh my God oh
God it's for hand holding
I it's nail
salon hand holding oh no this is this is
what they wanted to see though I'm sure
Jesus okay can you put this in
please maybe it's really so that your
nail nails your fingers don't get sticky
like mine always do maybe
protection to get not
sticky
protected Irish yes put one
on do
it she told me to do it she told me to
do it okay wait chose this I don't know
I don't know pure pressure pure pressure
pure pressure oh it's so wait it's
so she hit with one hand I mean really
with one hand how do you how do you put
it with one handy look I'll put it on
the best finger which is the Nai you
just use the other
fingers so oh my
God we sensored pointing hey here let me
help
you yo you get you get your
Ms is it okay to point you when we have
these on o oh can we put them together
like like you know like it looks like
it's a part of my glove cuz I white
gloves cute cute question mark is this
cute what you doing all
right had enough of that I need to
continue with my nails
okay I think I can just
do top coat okay um top coat Co want to
reuse uh irises wait wait wait do a like
a piece sign four in one nail what
happened this what's this what was this
for what this top coat oh there you
go Justin Jesus bails are you still here
oh no hopefully she's getting some good
sleep yay
not you are too excited about those oh
my gosh if you try and pull it off pull
it off it's really really hard to take
off oh God it's stuck was easy for me
o why aren they stuck I know it's hard
did
they well um this is for nail Sals guys
it's
legit cool mhm I'm sure it is what if we
pet tutu with this you think she'll like
it I think she won't sense a
difference I don't think she'll notice
the [\h__\h] is this
think she I think it's just to get to
keep the gel from getting on your
fingers I think bail just Li
do a that's sad she wasn't there for the
genital jousting jokes it's all right
she'll see you tomorrow
surely wait did anybody else end ended
up playing the game absolutely not right
I was like no no no so many people in
chat were like oh please no no no I
leave it to
bails yeah been proud of her she's she's
so brave you
know Brave bals yeah only a Zoomer like
her can pull that off yeah yeah I'm
proud of her very
proud I'm going to put some
back and people call me the yabai one
there are plenty of yis
yes those full of Y put this one in too
you bet this one
Ino thank
you
okay and here's this one thank you no
problem after that I just have to do a
top coat after I'm done with this this
current coat top coat and I'm done all
right and then we can start sticking
these on now no and then yeah just shake
start use the glue I guess the nail glue
is this how does the nail glue work I'm
scared let me
read uh nail glue gel for nail when I
get them remove how do you remove them
after before right how like can you just
use normal nail soak off I don't know
what that means um before before please
this is for nail tips so thank you thank
you Nails nice nails no not nice nails I
cut them
short and also one can you
tell this one where the other small nail
go my sa fingers what the [\h__\h] is that
the one that I haven't that's the one
that the star one the star one okay it's
already done right yep okay and there's
this it's been
cooked go short yeah ah get it away from
me what are my fingers too sausy for
[Music]
you don't you I mean German sausage you
know what Amelia Watson says oh what
wait hold on my walking machine is
making sus noises what does she say
Amelia Watson says all the better to
[\h__\h]
your huh
for the mom mom jokes yeah didn't she
say that I swear that that was an that
was an a quote Oh God everything
everything that has to do with moms is
always ay
yeah well I think we have all reached
our y qu for today yes we should be very
we we're Idols remember if you didn't
say that sorry I made it
up that is not an AM quote are you
sure
thank you it's closer to what I would
say maybe ah true I don't think she'd
use that language but
okay top Co okay this is top coat Iris
hasn't made a dent in her
quota yeah still not quite there yet
what you guys make it sound like I'm
doing every single I'm joking
the the qu there's no quota it's just
pure pressure forget about it forget
about them that that finger hat was
pretty was pretty
cute I'll never forget that well I
honestly regret not using them since the
beginning of today I mean what were they
supposed to do to keep my fingers from
being sticky they're so sticky this
whole time during the process every time
I mean maybe so
sticky finger puffet stream again oh
yeah that could be cool where where is
oh my God she's so
excited get back on there right now oh
no it's actually J Jal
J the live action oh kind face would be
good I can't do a good one
anyway oh this is so ugly and maybe do a
double double for that cuz that's the
top okie dokie
hi oh my God what what's his name what's
her name what's his name her name I
don't
know um look bullu IMA bullu good name
uh please um uh Joe okay Joe good name
amazing name yeah that works he needs a
friend why is it like why is it doing
this what the
[\h__\h] Joe needs a friend Joe's friend is
um Jan
Janette
okay Janette is that a name that yeah
that's Janet j Janet Janet Janet yeah
that's a name Janet I think in German we
pronounce the name Janet Janet Janette
Janet Janet so fancy I know it sounds so
so tasty yeah I get yeah names could
have a
flavor I guess say hi to uh Joe and
Janet if only I could turn my fingers at
each other then they could kiss but but
no you have to break your bone you
should have had it be the thumb if it
was the thumb you could have them SM
yeah man that's so sad they will never
kiss what a shame never what a
shame okay so it cute I know if that if
it did no it's fine okay it's all
good corner
here Cur it how's the nailist doing we
could put these on you now yep sure can
I guess I just do you need help I'm okay
I can do it
myself have you you've put the sticky
one sticky ones on before indeed you've
done before really yeah and how do you
get them off yes how do you get them off
they fall off but what if I want them
off earlier what if I want to go to nail
Sal and get them off professionally no
it's easy I think I once took these kind
of ones off just with normal nail
remover sorry one sec it's not sticking
no worries non acetone nail polish
remover I think that also works wait non
acetone acetone yeah I didn't use that
funnyone Iris told me to get acetone
remover and all I saw on the package is
here it said
acetone I didn't read the N the really
big n this this one worked IED this one
in thank Youk wait how stupid am I it
just says nonone and then underneath
acetone and I thought oh that's acetone
my eyes are literally just looking for
the word acetone this is still pretty
wet I'm going to maybe double double it
double down it tunnel vision for real
for real the tunnel vision maybe double
down all of them maybe put them all at
once they might just be sticky forever
but yeah but but you know just maybe
just you know I don't know why they
shouldn't be sticky this one too you do
that
too n is the brand I don't know I mean
that's confusing you you think so oh my
God and this one yeah just put guys are
defending me and just maybe once the
once the like turns off put it turn it
on one more time yes one more can't have
enough over oh it's looking cute so
sparkly under the light
yeah pretty I'm pretty oh then then
still need to be filed right yeah filed
and then done okay filed and then done
this is not sticking at all it's not
sticking at all not even not even
pretend sticking like it's in fact I
think it's flying off
oh no on purpose to fite me no we made
nail chips that we can't put on our
nails supposed to be nail it's not
sticking nail glue gel for nail tips use
this one that I bought extra maybe this
one better hopefully this one's better
maybe it's this one's not compatible
with these nails oh yes there's a
plastic on
okay we've done it we have done it yes l
ladies ladies ladies ladies ladies
ladies yeah what's Co I'm being cool I'm
going to wash my hands real quick okay
go for it for that um oh yeah the these
we want to put this back in yeah okay
wonder if I can get it back in it's such
a tiny
package yeah just do your best if it's
not possible just I'll vacuum it up in
the DiCon oh no what a waste that is
what it is I have more parts coming
tomorrow that's true all right all right
all right all right all right right okay
okay okay okay okay okay now
ladies what's cooler than being
cool all right all right all right all
right all right all right all right okay
okay okay
okay I don't think they're going to put
non acetone on
different what are you defending me it's
definitely it's definitely not
necess but yeah I I would make the same
mistake Tru the most winning birthday
I've ever had it's your
birthday there's this um K and Iris fan
called Evans L you know yes I know I saw
a tweet he's so T and he was so happy
all the K kiaris Karis has finally have
it's not even a first time collab yeah
this is the first um closer yeah off
collab and like closer one cuz like
we've maybe done bigger groups but not
like this yeah definitely I would
special shake my hand wrong
hand oh my
God sh sh Jesus don't knock the I I
wanted to do I wanted do do oh God oh
God oh her warm hands are enveloping
mine Jesus ladies some restraint oh this
your hands look so small but we compared
and it's not like that why do my hands
look so M badly oh
manly hands manly hands oh my
God the stream oh no oh no this is our
18 content oh my God I will go on a hand
diet after this hand diet foods that
make your hands Slimmer for
really how to get my uh my fingers look
slimmer slim fingers if you want to make
your finger spinner your effort should
focus on exercise as well as creating a
caloric deficit in your diet Lifestyle
Changes such just avoiding foods high in
sodium and drinking plenty of water also
your fingers look thinner I know that's
not just fingers that's just D guess
what dummy I did all of that yeah and
the rest of my body changed and my
fingers did not focus on your diet try
hand exercises upper body workout hand
exercise what does that upper body is so
so vague high intensity interval
training electrical like what do you
want musical instrument playing like a
flute guitar oh May guess that makes
sense well flute is more finger like
right and physical exercise reducing
stress and adjusting your
diet most of this sounds like
[\h__\h] sounds big the truth is the
actual size of your hands is limited by
the size of your hand bones no amount of
stretching squeezing or strength
training can make your bones any longer
or wider that's that the hand is powered
by about 30 muscles and they can grow
stronger and more flexible with a
variety of exercises learning so much
about fingers right now I don't know ma'
when I look at my hands like this I'm
like oh nice I'm not done yet not done
like o nice slim fingers and when I put
them under the camera I'm like what the
[\h__\h] I think they definitely look
slimmer once you put nails on them like
cute nails and teeth then they look
nicer could be could be could
[Music]
be no hold on you can't Target places
for fat
loss but you could build muscles in your
I'm going to try file correct pass me
that I'm going to try
file file I good luck file good luck
okay I'm going to start playing flute
from tomorrow okay learn pineapple learn
all your songs does anyone know how to
whistle here like actually like
whistling a
song a song oh she can I can't I can
only do what what's that song
pineapple sped up SP up I can't do it so
controlled I can't control whistling can
we stop I'm
[Music]
going okay oh okay here we
go I like the harmony oh my God how do
you guys do that how do you guys put
Pitch on that I
can't oh God is a little difficult how
do you how do you guys get these off did
you just cut them off or scissors and
then file so they're tiny scissors I use
them to clip my cat's nails oh wait no
CH they're all bad at it can you whistle
with your fingers and your mouth it's
not a girthy whistle absolutely no right
me
[Music]
NE me it's a little Airy but what can
you do you're more on tune I do try I do
try with my
[Music]
whistles
butter gum butter gum
butter she's cooking okay Iris give me
your best
whistle good that you closest on the
microphone
try she's
trying an effort is being made she has
to close her
eyes there's
effort it's like you're doing a like a
alcohol test with the police
like oh my God
bre oh my
Gody
okay bio finally aw for opponent why is
she also bad at Whistling or is she good
at
Whistling it's one of the
other there's like almost a note
almost
almost very close there we
go can you do a sexy whistle
like oh I wish I could
I fold I give up immediately yeah you
could do it you did yeah you see see
that that's it you got
it oh that's perfect nice perfect we're
making progress oh my God you know what
I can do it so well because I I do it a
lot the ladies the
Ladi isn't like whistling kind of like
how you blow bubble gum in bubbles like
the bubbles in the bubble gum that's
it's the same mve right I can't do that
I think same movement in your mouth I
can't do that so what are we kind of
thinking here I can't bubble the bubble
gum bubble the bubble bubble the bub you
think not really not really oh sort of
yes not quite that's why I can't do
it they look they look edgy they look
edgy as F they look edgy oo I show prop
I can't I have to be careful what I have
to be careful because I get nervous
about my wrist oh come on no
worries light the fire light fire fire
fire light the fire let the music Take
You Higher those are not the lyrics
sorry we're going to take a proper
picture afterwards yes you'll see L like
a like like
this like all the nail people a
[Music]
it round two round
two how how's the did the glue glue work
did the other glue work the other glue
worked oh nice no problem can you put
mine on later yes can you put mine
on will be you guys know how to put on
your nails save me save me I take too
long doing things should have put y on
first faster okay I'll help where I can
yay thank
you you obviously like you you're going
to scratch all the businesses all the
proposals you have given me and instead
just going to do nail sellon from now on
so maybe your destiny this one's falling
off what the [\h__\h]
no it looks a bit big why why does it
not stick is it aren't you are you
supposed to maybe cure it or I don't
know maybe it's but that's so weird it's
just glue it shouldn't be curing glue
it's so odd just give it more time it
more time okay now this is not stick
more
glue glue the others are fine not the
thums only the
thumbs don't I'm just testing it too
much
[Music]
this stream has inspired me to want to
paint my own Nails Now anyone else want
to join me well you are joining us right
now might have gotten some glue on my
tongue maybe heat will seal it but it's
it's normal um nail glue it doesn't need
UV strange there's more time maybe yeah
it's probably just takes a while like
regular manicures take forever to dry
each layer I took take hours doing that
I mean not that we didn't take hours
this time but takes even longer honestly
it's almost 1:00 a.m. oh God we started
at 9: right 10 oh my God it's a 4 Hour
oh wow almost 4 hours I underestimated
how long this would take yeah I was
thinking more like maybe maximum 3 hours
was I was thinking that's fun I'm I'm
happy we got to spend this time together
and I'm happy you girls wanted to do
this idea with me thank even though we
have to show our sausage
fingers
you know what I realized is that you
know probably a good reason that these
aren't staying on is you know whenever
you go to the I mean you might not know
q but when you go to the nail salon when
you put it under like it starts to hurt
right like the UV like it hurts because
it's really burning it like yeah it
hurts so you know what you do when it
starts hurting you pull out your hand
once and then you put it back in when it
starts burning yeah that's what they
tell you just for a second just for a
second like you know you let it cool
down for a second and put it back in
again to let it dry it helps yeah it it
really hurts sometimes don't don't leave
it like that you'll actually burn so bad
you'll actually burn your nail beds if
you keep it like that you guys all have
lovely hands no stop it's very
kind I'm glad that you think
so you I don't know I I don't really
have like any I think in these gloves
they don't they just don't flatter me
you know could
be I think they're
fine well well well
I was just filing my nails giving it the
Finishing Touch done
finally where' the other nail
go we're losing Nails oh it flew it flew
here oh what was this again is this the
the hardener I'm not sure yeah it's the
nail
hardener nail hard I I I think I used
that once in my life just on top of
clear like normal and naked Nails cuz it
gives a nice thick effect to your nails
that's cool Dimension
Dimension could be
nice it's definitely the
gloves sometimes the glue works really
well and sometimes it does not I'm
confused yeah well the gloves got to be
there okay C is pretty
thanks thank you
one two three four five six seven eight
where's the other two there we go
yeah I'm I'm so excited to see iris's
Nails together cuz they're like the only
ones where we really did like two
different pairs oo yeah but they're
still going to look
exciting just like my half angel half
demon personal Powers everyone says
neims are not actually half angel half
demon but in my in my lore that is yeah
you decide your lore you do it that is I
mean no it was It was decided for me but
it is what it no one gets to choose
their upbring yes no we can't choose how
we were Bor guess so am nope true
true and so what is it actually I don't
know according to Google it's like um
half demon half human actually oh and
you're half angel half demon half angel
half demon yes well that's like a Next
Level better it's even better just like
Mewtwo sad
one what I don't know what they're
cooking but they meant something by that
some reference what do you want to say
about
Mewtwo okay I I I I I I filed them all
but I don't know which which one is
witch finger again I'm like I mean I
don't know either I'm just guessing
technically they are biblical
Giants oo you you look pretty giant when
you were on top of Tokyo that is true
yes no Iris is very
tall tall tall
R I'm supposed to be the same height as
Cali magika I think really I a bit short
shoes no it's supposed to be I think
with shoes is supposed to be 166 oh um
167 oh okay 1 cm little same as you
or 64 okay but I'm always wearing
sneakers flat sneakers are we sure
they're flat there's yes we're not
having this discussion again cuz you're
going to lose you're going to
lose I don't
know yeah but Iris madebe just looks so
tall cuz of her legs and her super short
skirt super short skirt super short but
like you know the like the idol outfits
and stuff like I'm like I'm so much
taller than you in that was Str 3D model
I'm taller than you I'm just like wait
that really why I don't know why like I
look as tall is crony or even maybe even
taller than crony I'm just like why
crony is like supposed to be like 3 cm
taller than optical illusion Optical I
have no idea yeah just like so big my
legs are uhoh they're
[Music]
dead that sounds right are the nails
done yes they are done oh my god let's
go done okay so this is the this is
these are thumbs nail you can't
hear thumb that's totally gonna stick
with no glue just like that it's totally
gonna
stick thumb wait a second is that does
it this is the biggest one it doesn't
fit anymore anymore doesn't fit anymore
too curv it's too curved maybe maybe if
you is there like something inside you
just got to slot it in there got to slot
your finger in there you're slotting
into
a the price of pain price of beauty is
pain oh no it doesn't fit anymore is it
the right finger yeah it's the biggest
one we didn't paint the wrong ones did
we couldn't be did you get my order my
my my order right was
definitely that was that was the right
one yeah so this is the big this is the
biggest one it changed it curved from
too much paint it does look much more
curvy than look at that curve it does
but I still feel like you should be able
to put it on like
look you try stretch it try try try
flatten it with your with your fingers
don't crack
it I think it's all the Coates that made
it like really stiff like this
maybe it's like carving into my
thumb what about the other ones
cute which one is
this
a this one could be okay it feels a
little bit curved but it's still okay
I'm very happy with these nails yeah
these are much curvier than before a
don't oh these two the Irish ones they
feel curvier yeah no wait what did we do
wrong where did we go wrong this also
incredbly curvy maybe we were supposed
to keep them on our nails while we did
them oh maybe they curve they under the
UV light when they have nothing to hold
on to oh no but yours work but mine are
fine I don't know can I can I cure this
one more time this is really sticky yeah
[\h__\h] when I double cured um's ones they
get much harder so maybe double cure
them okay can you cure
Nails how to how I say this off of like
not on your fingers yeah on your nice
nice F fake nails like f nail nail um
people have surely done before so I mean
must be fine but want to double cure all
of them yeah might be a good idea yeah
cuz caras of them are much drer when I
double cured them
mhm okay I don't
really oh
ghosty maybe drop them all in here yeah
just drop them all in
[Music]
there
um cured Nails become
curvy I don't know maybe we're just
fools maybe we're just big dummies it's
all in our heads it must have gone wrong
somewhere cured Cur these aren't very
sticky at all we drop them inway drop
them in just in case just in
[Music]
case there's a theory maybe we over
cured it Mi is that a possibility that
you can Poss overcure it there there is
such a thing as over
caring what happens when you overcure it
it
curls no not necessar a lot of things
can
happen um
but I I can't really find anything
about specifically
curving
there I want to at least for a photo I
should be able to put them on on somehow
the the pum can just like worse comes
worse you just put them on your fingers
take picture my and then it's over and
it's yeah worse comes worse you can keep
the nail chips as as a
souvenir and one day hopefully they'll
fit like Cinderella's last yeah exactly
what a fairy tale yes let me try to take
at least one picture is the backside of
this clean probably yes probably I think
so one cuz they turned out
beautiful you got to do Iris or or do
yours also I'm dble I'm double curing
them but they might be too curvy I don't
know we'll find
out okay Kelly's are you're okay yours
okay yeah they seem fine but I'm I feel
like they're going to fall off I don't
know the glue is fine on a lot of nails
and then not so fine on others so I'm
wait which one feels fine all of the
ones except for the thumbs H thumbs is
the is the biggest nail so you have to
dry it out more yeah true are these both
thums cuz they they look very um
different I'm going to start delivering
these nails to you
guys delivering Nails thank you you're
welcome which one is this one is this
thumb thumb yeah oh wow they're so small
now they they'll fit
but very round
now yeah they have definitely shrink for
mine too boy
do it'll work work
but is a hope nail okay how do you use
the glue so you just put it on like nail
polish just put one and then you put the
thing on okay let's try this and how do
you okay how do you remove this again uh
just twist it I mean how do you remove
the nail it just comes off it comes off
what if you want to get them removed at
of nail salon do you just just tell them
and you say hey I used nail glue that I
got at Don keyote or
wherever and they'll be like oh okay so
how much nail do you put a lot of nail
glue on your finger or decent amount I
would say like regular coat which one's
are which why do these look like teeth
look so small are these really my nails
there's no way is that the pinky I don't
know which one it would be but I mean
that could actually fit ma'am that's
what you ordered that's what your order
was I can't help you you know these ones
at the stars they kind of look like like
beach oh yeah like sand SE sea sea star
what do you call him yeah oh starfish
starfish Patrick Yeah Patrick that's
exactly what you call
him
Patrick did I actually line these up by
the person who made them maybe I use
maybe I think so yeah yeah maybe yeah
okay I'll take a picture of this just so
I have one nice picture yeah just in
case o them nicely lined
[Music]
up W what the photographer is at it
again oh
yeah
SLA
yes put these bad boys in here
again nice o they look they're so long
orange long they're pretty long yeah
they look
so cute so proud looks
good I
proud very proud We Made Beautiful
Things yeah we did we could frame them
honestly yeah and set them up in a shop
as example Nails oh yeah you know hell
yeah I think so example Nails Kelly do
you need help taking a picture of your
nails or I'm okay I can take a picture
okay well maybe maybe it would be nice
to have are you forcing them on yes I'm
forcing them on I I I just can't there's
no way I'm going to get the thump on
there
ouch switch switch switch exerise
display at whole wait you know how last
year at Expo there was like a like
crafts set you made and streams Expo we
could Expo Deans that would be so funny
that would be really origal that's
really good idea oh don't throw them
away when you get them off when I get
them off I wonder I I hope the nail Sal
doesn't throw it
away no tell them tell them you need
them it's a memoir cuz your friends you
friends made them to G exctly they're
special I can't get this on I can't get
the pump on I could get the others maybe
on but I just kind of like push them on
like you know and hold hold them for a
bit of time after after putting the glue
on yeah actually actually once you put
the glue on it actually it works pretty
hard but it's not going to work for the
phone
I don't
know
maybe I love seeing them be girly well
we are girls yeah we are ladies I know
it's sometimes hard to see nice can you
show them off some more please oh my
gosh
okay
stop which hand is this is the the one
no no y eyes it's
fine this is I think only wonder who
made this one sure not sure I made the
the big one are you guys seen this look
at
this P oh
P where's the
fum here you go Thum joh thumnail it's a
thumnail oh thumnail god oh so
God
extreme wow oh so pretty oh the other
hand please it's this it is the pretty
much the same we we created you wouldn't
know you wouldn't know that two
different people M these no you wouldn't
here very
lovely
wow this is what I order I would order
this at a [\h__\h] that material yeah I
order this at a salon hell yeah like
really good yeah I'm happy with it first
time you guys did very
well very very well show you guys
like y we will get a pink on these ones
for sure oh wait oh yay pink so I I
don't know if they're in the right order
definitely the thumbs are obvious
MH they look a little bit like those uh
American candies oh yeah candy corn yeah
candy corn mhm oh I'm so so hard to tell
where to go why can I not do this
properly well you guys get get the gist
right uh like here
okay okay now you don't want to
pin Focus CH it changes mine it's
because the paper is like
wobbling not covering it was though what
they saw it they saw it they saw it
right you guys saw it forbidden candy
corn because the cvas mirrored yeah
that's that's so confusing candy corn
nails actually sounds like a good idea
around hallowe I sure I'm sure a lot of
girls do candy corn nails on Halloween
what are candy corn nails and I love
corn huh candy corn nails this all candy
corn right what's candy corn are you I'm
not even American and I know I'll show
you I'll show you Iris what's candy corn
I never had one though is it corn corn
candy candied corn like candied apples
no no I'll show you it's a candy um
that's orange and white and seen this
like oh yeah I've seen those before I've
never had those they Amic very americ I
like them how what what flavor are they
are they corn flavor Hot Sugar but like
a little milky it's hard to explain
Irish IR taste like I don't know much
about candy okay I'll get you some candy
corn next time I go to America please
yeah of course you guys can try I I like
it personally but there a
lots I dot do you like getting dotted I
hate getting dotted I hate getting
dotted especially when I'm playing FPS
was like don't dot do dot me do not dot
dot dot dead beats love to Mor dot dot
dot don't you dare dot dot it's a common
phenomenon huh we all get dotted get
dotted all the time dot me you dot me
this doesn't really fit my I will give
these to jenma tomorrow in the hopes I
don't even know if they're going to do
the the thing again I wonder well we
might as well try just in case I want
them to show these people can look at
them this is so cute that's so cute what
we did that's so cute the glue really
works yeah I can't get it I wanted to
REM move it and do it again but some
people I guess it works huh it's
actually working go Iris go go I'm
almost done she's very close I want to
see the final product
sure I like the matte feeling for these
Nam right they somehow they turned that
matte I think I thought they were
supposed to be more um shiny for I don't
know why they ended up being very matte
I kind of like it though for me
personally go Irish go go Irish go go
it's 1 a.m. it's 1 a.m. 1 a.m
sh
cuz my plans tomorrow are very
late just feels so wrong
yeah sleepy sleepy more I got to clean
though I got to clean and spend some
time with my
cats cuz we didn't spend a lot of time
today there's so many small parts you
should maybe not iron vacuum no I can't
let them out until I've completely made
sure that all of it's clean so you guys
you guys are going to have to nap for a
little bit
longer look peaceful they don't know
we're talking to them they have no they
don't know what's going
on don't know 1. is thaton we've been
doing nails since like 4 hours yeah no
Nails take a while I mean considering
how even professionals take like 2 hours
to do your nails true then it makes
sense that us being you knows we're
amateurs you know first time we fumbling
around makes sense it went though stick
I had fun y yeah I know it was fun I
would have never done this otherwise
yeah well I like to do this kind do
these kind of crafting streams I want to
do
more crafts with uh K kiar
moris
Morris takam moris yeah takam moris
it works Morris show yours too can we
I'm showing them although the color
doesn't look so good right now it's a
really cool color it just doesn't look
good on the camera yeah with the pink
paper is like weird
yeah W it's cool I promise
sparkly
cute your nails look so nice aren't they
on point thanks to you guys nice so edgy
love it very much my style
freaking edgy Shi would love those yeah
I know right shot and I are one and the
same when it comes to Fashion what do
you guys think do you like Callie's
Nails yes yes I like Callie's Nails
maybe just for a picture so we can put
our hands together I'll just put on
these four are going to try GL no no I
would put them put only the four on not
the Frum though cuz it doesn't go on
really even even with glue did you try
it hurts oh
just kind of like push it
in but we can do like you know like this
yeah
okay let's go okay yay k can you do it
fast do what my gosh I'll try let's go
all right let me get some of that glue
though oh yes are you done yes I'm done
let's go yes I am done just the oh my
gosh it's so
long that should be enough okay I hope
that's the righted one pinky Pinky Okay
feels a bit big but I think it's small
one pretty
pretty I love
beautiful PR Closer
Closer tips are you guys seeing this is
it Focus it's probably not focus but I
was so bad at focusing it it's okay can
you see this beautiful oh my
God they'll be back they'll be
back'll Kelly can you see which one's
the bigger one this is the
smallest this one looks smaller no this
one's the smallest one really this is
the the second
biggest they they'll come back I don't
know where they went they they'll come
back to me the middle one no no no I
think the middle one is um I think it's
supposed to
be that's the small one the one this the
smallest yeah this is the small wa this
is the smallest to biggest right wait I
don't know what is this what's kind of
take to small where's the next small one
on my finger oh that on your finger okay
okay wow already looking less sausy than
ever before wow the magic of nails the
magic of of long nails longer Nails
feels weird okay well let's let's um
what do you think is the next
one um ring finger ring
finger it's hard to tell ring finger
this one okay I'll
try yeah feels right
please R
mm said I'm I you wrote on Twitter I am
not Teo I'm
Noto see or your love is not take
yeah oh my god oh they're not too long I
like it but it feels does it also feel
like like it's pulling a little bit do
you guys a little but go away but it
goes away I mean it's still it still
kind of feels like that for me but you I
think you'll stop not really getting
bothered by it eventually oh this one's
curled a little
bit it look don't feels
small you're too small you guys can see
each other right in the room uh no we're
not there well yeah we don't see M
where' we go where do we go this time we
went
missing missing children maybe it's me
exit yeah I think it say I'm still in
the room all right I'll go join I'm sure
it's me hold on a
sec so
small let me in there they are there
there
ladies well let's try I think it's it
small oh this is the nail painting that
they wanted to see
yes this is what you wanted TI Titi TI
okay okay okay that should be enough uh
this is really too small Guma Gamba it's
just for a picture just for a picture
yes suffer for beauty you must you can
like see see yeah I still have meat but
I can see my bare nail too maybe they
got smaller they must I'm pretty sure
they were fine my thumb doesn't really
fit honestly that's okay just for pigs
it's just for
pigs wow such instagrammers take them
off and treasure them that should be
enough all right then they will all have
glue residue when we give them to staff
yeah they'll be like wow this is
disgusting but would sell for a lot on
eBay they will treasure from English
members yeah you think maybe one hand
yeah one hand is fine fine we all do one
hand yeah one hand come here
[Music]
wait T there we go yay y oh
cute is it pink is it Focus yeah really
that's good to
[Music]
me pretty
nails so girly they're so
long so
loud let's see
oh this Thum the the these thumbs though
there's so many parts on them yeah I was
really proud of that pearlescent one oh
uh yeah that one too this one they're
pretty those give me really big beach
Vibes beach beach beach
beach
well
I'm sorry I keep leaving them oh I think
it's a those are like they look like to
me that they were done in a nail salon I
think so too maybe a cheap one with bad
reputation yeah but still legit nail
salon pretty professional looking like
the design there's like you know s got I
really like this thumb like there's so
many pearls on I I worked hard like a
chain like
a I know got to take a picture properly
yes I'm glad that you liked it yes I
need someone to take a picture yeah we
can see we can do that after the stream
okay so thank you guys it's really late
it's past 1 1 um a.m. but we did it it
was a lot of work a lot of work yes I
was I was so busy concentrating
on I like it thank you girls for joining
in thank you everybody in the chat and
the viewers for joining in and yeah
maybe you get your nails done too how
about
that
gotcha
yeah thank you guys for watching good
night see you
[Music]
soon say
zp top top
yeah it never ends but let's go
you're I love so much bye everybody
PE wow
very cute byebye bye bye goodbye for
real bye for real for real bye bye
[Music]
bye