Uh
me me
benme
sann
voodoo
[music]
huh
me
[music]
huh
me
see me huh
huh
[music]
info nh
spa
today
me
[music]
b 2
huh
have it  Masu
Masu
voodoo
Omas
What's going on
Ah
This show is brought to you by the sponsors you're watching
[Music]
ooooooooooooooooooooo
oooo
who do
ban
team by 4 house ah
[Music]
Pixel aroom like a full-time employee
ana
person  Ruth says
all the members do
[Music]
Toba Tenai Wallet
Good
[Music]
Pyuu
IRB
Aha, it's super, super, super, aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
Seeing from the media or my seniors, po, the
festival club on the stone on the face-down edge lit
up.  The oc
4 the
his Naka 7 company has a good day dad
[Music]
seles amen 7 team aso
wear way oa pass through subapi
so
[laughter]
Eh, I'm sorry I made a lot of mistakes
ome
rosanyeah fender
Invited Floor Esper Hayao Aka Senpai B 5 Size
Base
As usual, I'll explain the program first.Those who
leave the party alone will read it.Pepace
is Pete's Hospital Life
Lamp.Erin Main Me Cha Me General Life.
Chan two points s Town
House Anna Uchi 2 Abeshi buss Let's
play bra t Line 4 Hotana Sekihara digging
Talk is an interview talk for English-speaking countries
Showday
The purpose is to talk about Japanese talent during the Obon festival while talking to
overseas people  I'm going to have you know more about the
host, Takanashi, and I
'll send you a spoon that you'll understand 1
view I'm going to be in the middle of the day, and I'm
going to have an interview with you today,
a
franc sex, be the with
you, and I'm going to have a good time with you, Tadashi Inoue,
Inou  Delicious parts
ebony forever Beautiful
Piston sound isn't good B-type
energy Chan dinghy Pure fish Pina That one
Kuhuu
If you like, I'd like to comment on it If you like, I'd
like to do it in the middle or at the end, but
if you follow the distance and come back on Twitter
Yeah, Hashizabu  I'd like you to write about it in Holder Ward,
huh? How about you improve your training
? I want you to say something, thank you very much,
everyone, aaaaaa
buff meu. After the
web interview is over, let's
invite a guest. Neko-neko-san,
cat-san.  Hmmm
[Music]
What's hidden?
Henna and shochu.
Is it good? I
can't say. It's underwater.
Yeah,
I know, I know.
This is fine. I'm
still here. Hi,
I'm strong. It's all of you. I'm the
first one to get mad.
Japanese  That's okay, but
umm, I'd
like you to introduce yourself, please.
Maasui everyone, dango inkou virtual,
idol gamer, sorry, maid's a,
everyone, Akane,
rar
nobasa
cheeza, bar system aqua,
farm to 4, f the knife idol,
gamer briefs.  Cap tus Piss
Club Queen 10 points are
you doing
a
[Music]
Well then, Senpai, today I'm
going to delve deeper into the dark, generally speaking about Aqua War Crimes, but are you
ready? It's a must-
listen,
don't be nervous, it'll
take 30 minutes to use the hook.  I was talking to Aqua-senpai before,
but even if it was just for 3 seconds,
Aqua-senpai would get all excited when there was nothing left to talk about. Come on, come on.
Ah,
I was waiting for the ladder to go on and on. But in that case, who would help me?  Entrepreneurs who came to visit
Oh, it's so cool. I
hope you'll be able to talk for 30 minutes with a cutter tomorrow. I wish you'd
talked in a mood where you didn't want to talk or really suck. You
ate a lot of things.
and
perder momentohter
Are Aga Lop
Truth Kids Game Fashion
Topics Org we are Rudy
Chan Char King 4 SM SA Appeal Seas
Breen Y Star 022 Way Don't
worry, today, please feel free to do more and more of yourself
Please.  I'd like to move on to the first question.
Mai Hakase. What kind of activities have you
been doing lately?
Yeah, lately, I've been
doing some kind of streaming, and I've
been putting a little effort into singing. I'm a
ringing singer.  We
are focusing on active idol cuts oo so cose
nsuaaaaa punishment school ie 4
spring rng
r fx e 2 c inc Ease
Green-san, yay idol activities.
I often say that car centers are the best idols and have the highest level of awareness, but it
's only recently that they make
noises. Do you
think they're not trying hard? Maybe I'm not right. Ah, I do
n't know if the air is the best, but idols
don't go to the toilet after all.  I do
n't think everyone should go to the toilet
either. It's so much
of a loss. Ipadair ccs
bef 9-san's opening an binge warp
Fried Garden Tipo Sailor and CSE
NR 4 a i c That's right, it's like an amplifier
Booster lover yes posture nemocco
attached  Into dospara pain
[ __ ] softer elementary school's high pressure,
treasure life espo slippery tool and
good figure lover the
yaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaahhaaaahhaaahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahaaaaaahahahahahahahahahahahahaaaaaahahahahahahahaaaaaaaahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahaaaaaaah, I'm
ready to sharpen that hand wash.  I
can't peel it off, so my skin,
senpai, is diaper
Gucci Gucci Gucci Gucci Curve
Isn't it better to appeal to the temperature?
Yes
f I wonder if I'm feeling nervous all the time in Rare
No, with that 7 kinds of money strawberry milk  Ah, if I
were to give you a mash window and strawberry milk, you'd
still have to go to the bathroom,
wouldn't you? It's gas and it's actually going to be produced.
Teacher,
ok
ter, I want a balloon.
Archon, Senpai, Ah, speedwood,
Ford browser & your
voice, rip.  san no taipan
wp 6 items air turbine
makeup pouch zero cno turn signal
the voodoo
kneader type 1 fit pain to
fit tier 4
pero
porore
I see, it was a bit strange from the beginning,
but it's true.
So,
how did you first find this live show, and what
led to the "Haidae" file?
Nagamoto Putone: Back
then, when I first joined the club, Furo Live
didn't have the same feel of an idol agency as it does now.  Hmmm v It was like a tuba office, but I
thought I'd try something a little sickle, and it would be something like this.I wanted to become a big shot, hmm, that's what I wanted to do.I
wanted to change myself,
brain.  It all started when I applied for a job at an agency,
but now that I
've changed my name to A$, I think it's amazing that my dream of having a business name has
come true.  Did you
find it? It was someone's broadcast.
Well, I
didn't know anything about the inside of the hood, so I
heard that they were holding an audition, and
then I auditioned for a live show.
At that audition, I
thought to myself, "Oh, I'm going to see Tokinozora-chan and Fubuki-chan," and then I started watching it.
Gahe 1 machu love reading really with
getting pox plan b 2 flights b grain
serious
caren over 4 f
maintaining the Rover situation at the Meiji Restoration bar Robert
Audition Land is also good
Reluctant machine 2 machine finepix s ca
sheet 2
aesthetic b
ncs  Ah
Fighter # n Hikikomori declaration Hi, I'm a
chinchilla cat near Shimane who carries the burden of finances
Barbie Now that was a remake of the sound I
also liked the size of the skis
[laughter]
1 But I said I wanted to change myself.
Streaming
Zaan, you're doing it all the time at home, you're furious
Molly 4 You can't be supported
[Music] It
's all about the shyness Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa to toi
Baseball that that that in camp
-in -chan
[Laughing] is a
dual killing of the eggs.
Pink Village
Loader's naughty self-talk. I
can't say good or bad about being a babysitter,
but I'm drawn into it. I'm not saying it's good, but I'm digging it.
Since it's no good, it's the 3rd silver key and the writing I use is like this.
That's right.  I'm
in the mood to buy it, but I
don't feel like changing Morii's.  It
's the same thing,
but that's why he lives in a town where he
doesn't go outside of the holidays, and he doesn't see his friends.I
had the impression that it would be amazing to be able to meet him without him, but he often
says that, but I don't
really like it.  I do
n't like getting involved with people, etc. Well, I guess it's all the same, isn't it? Ah, it's
okay to get involved online with things like UA, but I'm not good at real things, so if I
could do that, I wouldn't be satisfied.No,
it's
the same.  You're the
same color as me, hmm, are
n't you
happy? Why put the CD away? I
mean, Ennet. On the internet, they call people strong. Net
Benkei.
Net Benkei. It's a distant view.
Boo-boo.
Dou
irritation pes. Woofer.
Super legs. Pou dou
dou alpha.  no pain
Well, this is a show that talks about curtains,
so I don't care about the house, so
let's go to the marshals.
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa Until now, I
couldn't say it until now because of the language barrier.
There are things that I wanted to convey to people overseas.No,
there are a lot of things, but the
most important thing is that I can't speak English at all,
and I really can't speak it any more.  I'm
always grateful for the things that make me so happy, such as people who come to see my translations on Super Chat, people who show up to support me, and people who take the trouble to learn Japanese and watch my broadcasts.
love you aua
rei
scar concer harmful
splash 46 seeds airou
um star 3 spider factor
quite a bit of thieves fence pinging
naibu nude baitia rdi
storm to carmen's cap obu seeds
ad driving center fair pra is
chance wedding
[music]
voodoo
ok
big I think the love has probably been conveyed to Aoyama A
comment full of heart a go top oh well
then I'm really happy
Next is -
janaa
What's your favorite broadcast so far?
What's the story about?Game distribution or transformation?
What do you like the most, like Oke or Daru Ketsu
Love? Possible I like all of them
Hmm, when I say the best, I think it's probably the game
car song, huh? Possible
When I have the image of drinking all the time
Channel n Business days all the time
Karaoke has been abolished
Has it been decided on Anitube? There are
signs that super breasts will come true at night.
OK It's a big practice starch 4 s
all this type and Spain
sputter moss dash eye star
wizard game is also a game p 6 fore
big new species from solar  Carlow
Caffeine Zua, I chose Action Ah, I'll
rinse it out.I won't even listen to
jazz.It's 2 years old.Hana Chaka.If
you want to listen to the cute songs of junior high school seniors from Kyukyusenning, then
there's Yodo Nakotonnai on Sunday.  Tomorrow,
it's tomorrow, it's so boring! Are you going to
play Jukkenzaka? I
think I'll give it to you tomorrow. Ah, it's a
game, so I'll do it. It's
nice. I'm looking forward to it. It's
big.
Aircar-senpai brother.
Hey, I'm a maid.  Hey,
hey,
what's your daily schedule like? b
What do you do with your body after taking it?
Phu,
I see. 8 a What's that idea? Part
2 Are you worried about that? Well, if you
include a festival, you'll be able to do that.  All you
have to do is tell me your schedule for the day. That's right. I'm
going to wake up around noon and do a show. Yes, do you
really have time to cut Arthur? That's
not a lie. I go to
bed in the morning. It's true that I go to sleep in the morning.  I'll
put it
in a I wake up from noon to evening Haa ran I
told you honestly I'm Eighter here
When I have work I sometimes push from noon to night
When I don't have work a 8 I
play games or 8 I go
to sleep again.  Masu
[Music]
Dai
ua
That's where you left off to do the tonal work.
Bada, that's okay. People in Wakayama have 4 days until the sun,
so if it's only at night, it's a cross. Well, it's night, and
a Mao comes home from work.  I'm going to sleep
or
m.
8 On the days I don't have work, I play games, laze around,
or stream music.
[Music]
AaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaI I
didn't come to the labyrinth job before, but
oh, the road,
that time.  No, I just ignore the email, I think I'll drop the maid. I
like how the management of Asodo sounds. Prince Hideo
makes a good choice.
If it's true, it's a game I'd like you to play.Jangeehaa-chan, are you
cleaning that
thing
?Natoko.Ah, it feels suspicious.Please put everything away.  Ah
yes, of course there is a rise to the upper class
a
April uploaded, Seibu internal writer is good,
historical sites and the unknowing decline of Mone Aso Sports
Nomoiso
April Abe Beulah and so on
anond
eusebe Zahn ef 4 at
who
do
boo boo
doobie mud
afca ah ah do
do mavis good time n field and chair too
game cursed zinc left arm
uh also bait beginning shun chair do
in game to comfort Mr. Mailwork When you
memorize the racers, you make a list and the house etc.
Mutsu and god  Soai
Fushi-kun's rare news Ah, Flare On,
grilling beoff c Impressions 6 e Bune
Sensing and line game
ne
Anu
Stone no no Queen machine is Ino
fame Solid Song
Wenzhou blues and master and Sichuan wine It's
thick meme
Eh  N iso loud park now
Foley's resin scarf lover
kokukin make tomorrow as soon as the reason for the committee sincerity ah
good room ah
i love ok
reese silent meter fee game
ignus ah 4 medinger
Sharner Fighters 10 minute curve ah  4
Iron ii Dog type
Leader Okay, that's over River car
What's it like to be a senior maid?
Well, it's a conger.
Yeah, yeah, okay. Aaaaaaa.
Welcome home. I'll give you a bath,
master. Or game.
Game compatible.
aname
pareage
hgst tarp.  Blue amplifier direct car pa
's bowler Heiwa papa Boon Maeda wing is
going to scatter Gochu tea is 5 e 2 children
If you can, play there 3 cut is a
complete loss What am I wearing? Red senior is a
real maid.  I
believe that the day will come when it will be confirmed,
so that's how I think Akashi is. Hmm, I
got an email from Ako Zeniba, but yeah,
3 buildings are gods, so we're all together. Ah, a
year ago.  2 minutes
in front of the hostess b
Then here a Oh, that's a different number
Air
wool
anoano The ceremony place is dark brown
Husband A perfect idol who is not a parody A
group of gamers Coupon Midori
everyone Taaaaaaaaaaaa
[Music]
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa work tingu tingu tingu
toru That
's a bad name, it hurts Antim, it's so good, it's
playing with laughing dog chon, s Nesu is no, no, no, no kill,
Michio, I'm
doing it properly after Otani.
Crepe Riding on a Crepe
[Music]
Oh,
finally, the crab is even more crepe
Grape Johnny
is taking the crepe. I'm
like, uh,
but the black grandpa and I jumped and clicked. Surprisingly,
that's not the case. 6
Parrots are completely on good terms.  Hey 8 White
Shiropi tasted like the management onion I
think I'd like to read the line from my mom
a A set book included
No
Black
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa.
Boon Mermaid Cafe
Do I'll see you, I think Ezumi Omura will do a great job
2 Make sure you write the heart properly, sir Gently go to
God Hmmm
I was a maid at the member cafe maid cafe
What would the sound be if it wasn't a certain color?  I
guess it's a maid, auf, so I
don't know how much I'm going to spend, so
please look forward to my growth in the future.Large
asset rice size.
Manufacturer:
Total number of viewers of the former army used in February 4th Day
Base API:
Pulp Barry I think it's a good proof.No
one will doubt that senior.
What is that? Ah,
what is 44.5? I asked that person about Aqua Senba.
Thank you for helping me. Twitter When I
said this on Twitter, a huge
crowd of Aka-senpai fans told me about this.
What is 44.5?  Please ask me
what 44.5 is. Yes, machine.
[Music] Um,
recovery is okay.
For the sake of the second season where I change my name.
Please tell me what 44.5 is.
a
Yes,
well.  - It
's said to be the devil's number as it is,
but if you search for Minna to Aqua on Google or something, you'll
get something like 44.5, but what it
really is is
[music],
right?
Hmm,
get rid of volume, you're a little girl, and kids
aren't that low.
[Music]
Yeah, that
's right.
If you look at it in general,
Anno has a little bit of taxi muscle
. It's less than the average person, so he goes out.
44.5, which
means it has a little more fat than the regular 44.5.People
often say that it fits around the waist, but what are you talking
about?What do you think about this person
?I wonder if it
increases to 8.  It's okay,
what's that? Do you think your weight is too
much? I
want to lose weight. Stop trying. Don't lose weight.
Don
ami Gardon
Rear Police Ercp Nebo
Poly
Forever
Re Ap 2
Do Kami Oi Anaba  Aji turn
isas rapper
teaser
seen boon Wow, it's dry
1,000 yen pern
ply i folder I'm
hoping for a bunch of poppo campaigning a little bit of persie
entered s Cody 4 point pie Kyogen I've been
praying for saas What's Tan 2's
voice That's gone  I do
n't think you'll be able to make a fuss about Bisbasou.Tan, I was actually thinking that the nation was hiding it properly.Yes, that's the case with Pearl Game, Harumi Sora, and it's
like Hanshinden, a
game with a big bid.  But please take a trip.I
wanted to go to Kodaiji Temple first to have a sleeper.I
thought I was going to have a good time, but when
that BMI came out, it was
ok.Aso
Uso
Areberg.
Let's talk
about the menu.It's been about salt for two years now.That
clipping has been being played.Ah, what is it
now?It's been played for real.I wonder how much it is now.If you
look at the weight of everyone and evil, it's affordable.  Do you
want to
find out what your weight is now on the internet? Ah,
as 2
4.54 million views Armor
large
canapa fight with
Fuser Throat Coupe bar en old
with you baby Barber
Harger
fame Star of Veuve Nakafukami  5 It's
all about Ippei, Ring Fit
Adventure, Wii Fit,
etc.
Why can't I sell my house? It
's true, Andre's girl, Abe Sakagami
ran,
yay,
anderstand, Leeds game,
aspera
seger, move like a spared,
ok Byaua, I see.  That's the question I
get asked a lot.A.I'm
famous for my strong senior attitude, but I'm
also famous for my cowardice.B.And when I say "shut down camp," I
mean the hat I always wear when I go out.I
mean the cap.  It's a big cap, isn't it?
Supplement border interpin
spruce japanese it
Kofu in camp ah me
nos Zakah's
aso Pupu 2 wife Tingupipuyopusya Ipusua
Ellen then Bain camp
here voip way water polo
in Canggu bandu
Kya, it's time to retire. Oaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaoh
Whenever we're together or have lessons together, we always
wear that cap.And I'm
always told that Agiao also wears an actor cap, so I can't admit that it's a
dangerous cap and attracts attention.I'm
free to wear two types now.  I thought it was the same cap every day, but
now I'm
starting to buy a lot of different kinds.Well, I'm
disappointed.I'm wearing that cap today, and I'm always
thinking, "Isn't the cap different?"
If you ask me, Mr. Haranaka.  In Aso,
no, I agree with Cat C. Recently, my
manager told me that there was a
day when he wasn't wearing a cap,
and he was my eldest son.
Well, I was asked if I was
n't wearing a cup cap today, and I
was like, oh
no, I don't always wear one,
but there are days when I don't wear one, so I
didn't wear one today, but it's okay.  You
made that ``cheese'' look three times,
sis. Um,
there are times when I wear sunglasses, and I don't know what to do when I wear
sunglasses.
If I wear Granz, I wonder if I'm a suspicious person.So
to speak, I have to wear a mask these days even at meetings, so I'll be
grateful if I take a note.I
can hide the stand, so that's true.With
Joren 7, I often wear long sleeves, so
it's good to have it with you.  Most of the time I
hide my skin.
Well, it looks hot. My
sister and mother,
but I don't want to get
sunburned. Even though I'm a type of person, I don't want to get sunburnt.  It
was very difficult, but I almost
died after reading all of those books, but
I saw people who were talking about the situation in Nagazone and a lot of old ladies, and I was like, ``Are you
okay?'' Ito was
one of those people who was so cute.  Tomorrow, it's
not an image, it's not a picture, it's wearing it
Hey, I'm so
particular about white stories
Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandpa and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandpa and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandpa and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandpa and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma and Grandma,
you know, it's a good idea to
use a few
sarde.
noa so so good day
key point powder
repornper c com wear
saan
web cr z 2 shots
order lovez star dekimoto togane jay
arch day desukawara aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaabebebethe day
Peek-a-boa
joso
deuse
are elea
ah let's
patty webber wizards wow wan
duku
soredemo saru
stare
acra
ares large
diffuser iphone 4
barley nu do
andere jen henchman
aizu name and walk around I
see then it's
home a but then
that hat  I've been
wearing it all the time,
dog, and it
sounds like a helmet on my head.It's
okay to put it on.I don't know what to do with my
leg strength.I
try not to wear a hat.I
try not to wear a hat because it makes my hair look too flat.
Even when I'm recording, I try not to take it off until just before I'm alone. When
recording a song, I
put on headphones, so I
try my best not to take off the cap until the staff member leaves the hair.  I
see, girl 4
seaso open roll pando
hair has the shape of a competitive swimming animal ok ok
fairway point cool and fluffy
scare you do for c
walk the vase kids
and ass [ __ ] you do
as looping birdie
poodle like a loop
Because I'm embarrassed, I'm
embarrassed because I'm going to become a repetan, so I
put on a cap, but
when I take off the
cap, it's
disgusting. Ah, good, good, good. That's why I ca
n't take it off, so I tried to take it off.
rcb to do
your sweet Pro-up-up
head and eggs not
you
[ __ ] k
2 Let's go to the questions
A building
[Music] Up
until now, various games have been broadcasting standby,
but this is a game that worked hard on the song.  Is
there a game that leaves a lasting impression on you? Yes, I
guess so. 8My favorite games are My Brother's and
Autobat,
haha. Yeah, I love Hanshin, right? I
don't play many story games, but I play a lot of online games.
But when I
say that I worked especially hard on the online game,
it's the FX, the effects color, and the
playing time of Apex, which is
long compared to other games.
And web Unfavive
p Hey Automata Watch Abe
Sae Tus April Chong City A
game shower along the street where you can put your foot out is good Yes
Shujo-sama's chance of water temperature 1 silver 4 a
pushas for best
regards
Moroder Good
Let's talk about that kind of FPS
a little more  I'll add that later,
but
there are some genres that I don't play much in 2019.
Shooting games, etc. I
don't play music games that much.
Product
x Apex Pash Encouragement FC
Ys  What should I say?
Um, what should I say?
Shooting game.
What kind of game is this? It's a dump that goes to Touhou or something
like that. Sponsored. I see.
I see. I'm not good at it. I'm not good at it.
Star g you do in five
Wezon game.  To 4 by Facility Repair
Engine Stall Abandoned People 4 s our game
spark 3 pieces
Iiiiiiiiiinaruoki I'm talking about your true feelings and microphones
about things like that.
What kind of activities have you been involved in with the construction of the pin that opens the Ebisu side Mine Craft?  I
want to know who's in there,
or Akukin Construction. I've been asked to
restrict my personal use of Akukin Construction, but I don't
know who's in it. The
reason I'm not angry is because that kid is
in there.  If you say, "I'm going to join you," then you're afraid that this child
won't be in the program anymore, so you
can't say who's in the program.What does that
mean?If that's the case,
what time and month will it be?  Hey,
this kid isn't in it. It's
like he's looking at me in it.
It's a Freedom Smile, so it must be the sound. It's
like "Mi" in "Enter".
Yes Freedom Soma l Supporting
Freedom Smile 7
Muichi Center Color Cool One  Hit the
powder bed with a fur dawn queen construction A
bed for flooding after the suspension of spectator lottery correction A cold possessed pipe in the bathtub
den o full movie the
bes ccs berea stp
power powder bed people piece wake
why is so in the pearl of space  Shi
smoke non-sensation 13 free
Share the love is g Nangaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaagu
What's that about Hantong?
Somehow, when UmiC was broadcasting,
that Gurakin Eri
Gurakin TB appeared and was taken away.Oh, the
story is orc Center Hershey Fish
Ingredients Suigun Pooh Cover It's about as much as
Spider Tours  Impressions that are prohibited are small,
wide-view Otani spin's two dashes, the
suction is good, Yoder's feelings are also difficult, Weber
licking Indian Iga sea made st n-
no-spin half-mifiaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
I've been talking about wanting to do something new for a
long time now, about 23 months ago.
But, you know, those employees are a little
busy right now, so they have
n't been able to make any big announcements, and they're going to have to pay a lot of money.  The
seawall is an apple, Jesus
, it's so training, haha, the
carp is in Marine language,
so I thought it was a story about Ries.
Hard Jesus is a big new breed, ah
with breakfast, Clothes fetish,
and you're going to break up the pass, Roy Gardenan.
Yo bags and clothes are judged and pre-emptive sea
sbcare arc pink lactis
Walk away at the counter is
you busy bee
Mushuichi Kun Fai Cap a 8
f Campaign First Baldi Burntia
That's Oi db Big Ones Normal
Surfing Game Aku Ban Culture
Muscle Fiber Wife 5 Kei 2
Boo Boo SOS A kind of audition
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa  Marine dbc
Puppu Chipupu Arm Club Marine Senpai Pour
Aimei Mountain
Fighters Ad Web Rider
Ship to Do I thought it was amazing I
was watching it a little while they were making something
Naoko thought it was amazing
Oh no, such a big building,
wow, isn't it?  Ah, I
respect Free Paint Fish
sr Veld Hospital IV Fog box
up me to do
a Idol Up Faithful Armor
Killer, making something that big. I
don't have the patience.
Well, they
say it's not easy, so yeah, that's it.  I
chose love in Haneai's reorganization.Alright, this
is an innocent question.Refer to ``
When I was invited to participate in the Umi C project,
what did my seniors think?''I
was often told that I was shy, but
until now I had completely changed my mind.  What was it like interacting
with the members of the follow group that I didn't come to? To be
honest, when I was invited, I was worried that
I wouldn't be able to speak properly,
so I couldn't even speak English, so it was
just
Japanese vs. Japanese.  Even if I talk, I still
can't speak those two words.1 That's right
in the mountains.There
were a lot of things like anti-anxiety, but hmm.When I was
in the 2nd year, I started
doing that in English conversation lessons.  I
thought it would be nice to be able to talk
a little more towards him,
so I did my best, and um, I
was taking lessons. Hmm, how long have you been taking lessons?
Well, I have
n't been taking lessons lately, but I
was taking them up until summer.  That's because I'm a bit
busy with work and it's
difficult, isn't it?
[Music]
Voodoo as you
do s projector
plan with refur
ancestral fx web acb
teen japanese
mesen blues
us apart
fare in fingerless  Big
boo, Atty's pouch is all revealed
Booby IPD Suuu
Sri pendeja
fraser mer
parente r Oh,
how's that ok?
Yeah, yeah, please continue. No matter what,
try it. It turns out that
Na-chan can speak a little Japanese.
Also,
Grachan was quite good at speaking to me in modern Japanese, so it was
really fun. I was
really nervous, but the captain also
worked hard to keep up with the unpopularity, so it was really
fun.
Santora Genmai Minnai Year by Already I
tried really hard while using the translation function
Well,
that's why it was so much fun 3 -
Foot sander technique wave spec
Chaplin Sengra child base
soc Hard world re
talking It was Jam Boss -
Merlin  General recruitment of seniors wi-fi New
creative sea bream miso Back to the conspiracy by
Let's Botter Koi-kun, who added herbal executives for a moment
Well then, it's because you
were able to
do something like this Do you have something unique that you
want to do again?  I'm really nervous,
what should I do? I'm going to take care of my childish mind.
Hey, hey, I'll help you out with this ion. Yay, I'll put on the
best of you. The character is amazing. It
smells similar to Subaru. Ah,
Anchor.
I think he'll run away somehow.  I'm
counting on you, aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
userporn
dispersion ecef co2
doing obc
pleased to
dor 4 me with farmy
norme
arus
voodoo ability
love olly I'm happy because it
was easy to talk even before the quote and the ferocious delivery.  It
was the rainy season Yuna Don't you want to get along well with money? Hop-ni, it's
good, good, good, good, good. I
want to talk to Hifiemon in front of others.
Traveling with a. Cats and
cousins ​​like Queen and the opposite sex. Moe Ozawa.
Hold the Ikasumi Ah 1 by of Foles. I
'm glad that I lost my daddy. Doctor,
I'm
asking you to ask Afair Afair
Ah, I've been playing various games so far,
but it still remains in my heart.
What kind of work is this?
I see, this is the work of
Hiroshi, which I just turned to, called ``Automata.'' It had a great story, and even in electronics, the
story was very moving,
but most of all,
at the end of the abolition...  It's like that, that's
amazing, Horner. Yeah, yeah,
that's a bit of a spoiler. There
's no cooing, but I wonder what the
ending will be like. The comments
were also supportive, like Gun Valley, and
it's a great sense of unity.  I was so
moved by the feeling that the comments, myself, and everything had become one.I was
moved in that sense as well.No,
I did all of that aquas, and I
did that last one, too, but that house
really irritated
me.Ahahaha,
right?  You know, I tried too hard and it
was a bit of a meta point, but I
didn't know that Zeku was going to do it in the middle of the day, and the
other character was desperately shouting,
but it was too much, oh
well, it was already hard.
[Laughs]
Then open up behind the scenes too, Senpai.
[Music]
Hey, I'm impressed.
[Laughs]
Use a 4 d
ender ender
poodle 4 over Vienna
sender
[Music]
Voodoo line ng talking old lady
2t54 me blues web
hendry
rends  air downloader
dukamu house ime discharged
mother inns part n way condition scene
catberry gohei with female doctor's head on his back eh
who is your favorite character in that two step and mata
[music]
a2
oh f universe yeah
boots hmm
Ayase and the enemy are 4 years
old.  It
's time, Joby, are you okay?
OK, it's batch.
My
hair is cold in 2, but which one is better? Hmm, the
footer amulet is a member.
Number for now,
Gusto's mother, Celia Khan
[Music]
High Jelly,
someone said this before, Glam
Star,
Pring Hall, Jus Khan,
Ringer Apple, ok  Mountain Climbing Car
Marathon Sweets Illustrated Book
Hmm Mantenboon Camping Over there
Period
ce It's inevitable that syphilis will be mentioned in the voice of peak season
OEM SA I
like short things, but which one is sweet?
Sheet that it's delicious See Tea Entrance
Carn
Central Hokkaido
Sea  My mother who travels with Peach or a famous big city reply
RCP
A Can you lay naked when you sleep?Are you
saying you'll put on clothes?Ahahaha Climb to the top
Delicious plum burn
This is a karate technique
So far it's a little mixed here.  Teka 8 A
Favorite face -to -face and Halloween lismas 2 fields,
etc. It
will be 6 pieces,
such as Cebu or Family Marker,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
yes, corner
KD par  I
wonder if I'll get it from you. Hey,
give and pay. Either way, I'll take a
picture of Pocky. I'll
walk the distance of Epi. I'll take the train.
[Music]
Ah, the
train tray is winding down. Now, what are the two colors?
[Music]
I'll go check it out. Ah.  Wow,
that's scary. I
can't open it.
No, the bastard's left hand was already 4 bays perfect.
Looks good. Hey, it's
a bit. I added a new question for the Aqua Declaration.  There are
many things that
people can say about themselves, but when I put on a
good
person, I
wonder if Kirito's way of life is amazing.
There's something I can relate to.
[Music]
But the
key is to go out.  I
think there are 4 characters, from humans to insects.
At first,
Kirito was originally a recluse and was
n't good at interacting with Haworth, Sally, and Saa, but when he
met his wife, who said it was koa, funa, and
asa.  I think it's good to expand your horizons and go out little by little.It's been a
long time since I've forgotten that, so I forgot about that.But I'm
sure that's
true.
Nogane I'll give you a cool and cool translation
[Music]
asr dura starbase
serrano edition layout
prezza pants
andi earthy bluebird aichi
sense kiltris
me iron cutter
us are you re
arise
us favor
respoon freeloader with well as
2seb series  525 Zabo is Keen
Tora advances to Pico So Won So So So So Ha Ha to receive it
I'm Kichise oh now day
mozu party link
rivas party youtube
Ruu
outer tsu tape day wa slope reward bequest
in 3rd place cursive wobutte princess  Zipper
Fontaine 1 d 9 way Paris
is good for me
wait for card pentium
e + efei
face paiyu sieenshi knee soap ns
answers to do saa seb
shittankuro
ah this is rather kirito nyan
ipro naan masterpiece  Orphen
Ground Work Barter I'll do my best to
cut it and I see
[Music]
Sharp, I'm in the village, I have
Asuna No. 8, but I really have to stop
Hahahaha I'm making another leap, but
hai good color Kunpen tomorrow  Stand up, I
understand, Andujar is a certain northern peper.
Karaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa's kind of kind of way that she's going to change more and more in the morning
If that's the case, she's
going to become cute and want to be a bride in a quilt or something like that If she
's not a woman I want a wife like sand
Hey, I
want a wife like Nai, but there are
n't many husbands like Kiri, etc. I
'd rather have a cute girl than the bastard I became
.
Amaran
ISL Unwelfare Sedan Leg
Set Asuna
Isaiah's Padded Bus and Volvo's Life
Asuna  When I cut the mountain road outside, I
don't have the courage to declare the woman in the document. Waa goodbye to Groza. Wow
goodbye Chiwa Bungu cover
my side 7th place 9th place 2++9 Kansai
Eita ship Mon a not.
Speaking of Kirito, this is a cutout. Hmm, what's
this
kid blue
? It has nothing to do with Kirito, but it's
Gakuappu Harmful Spiti's Fili and the
big panda boots.
Save I
want to play the game called Fender.Also, I
'll leave things like email to you.I'll
do some cooking.I'll go ahead and
cook.If you want to know if you like this, you'll have
to wait a long time.This is our only company.
Please, I'm
done with my metabolic mail,
right?
[Music] It's
good that you're cooking properly. You
can cook, too. That's the problem.
Blue gamer maid. Super idol.
Gamer
after maid.  Ah, it's a chaotic one night stay and
Very Perfect Maid's first time,
but it's a
chaos cleaning board from the hot water, and it's
Aso Department Store, where you can play. It's
great that the patented model is gone. There's a lot of
dog specials in
Ferry Pasania UK.  I've got
5 books on the open scale, and I've got 5 hard copies of the scale from the sky,
os, Easter is not good.
Then you won't be able to take off. ana Okay, aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa.
Hmm Uraaa by car
[Music]
a
Power Fighter Freeme
Eeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee uh
curtain up I wonder
what should I wear?
Shishike Maid
management
funding honor is good yeahaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaight way down
nu
dnc zu game movie to do
with souther
dey id and that
entertainment is 100 points perfect
2 people are good
aoko life o kimiseru ino daru it's
supposed to fit cherinshi ufo points at atsuko
ok ok about aqua senpai  I
feel like I'm getting more and more detailed, but
from here I'd like to go into a little more detail.
Hananoya Komiya is also here, and all the
amazing teachers from Spain are from Spain.
8.
Hey ok Next person is 1.
Is there any back story about the moment when you met Shion-senpai for the first time? And
what is the reason why the two prostitutes are so strong?
Before Moko's debut, we said let's talk once and that's
when we started talking, and out
of the 5 of us, we came in 2nd place.I
guess this is how it is.Well, I was a kid too, so I was still a child.  I wonder
what it is
En Nakata
Because I was young
[Music] I don't know. I
think Shon-chan probably thought that I was someone who didn't like me.
If Abe Monomer was a teenager, then it would be quite
possible.  That kind of thing is
probably true, I
guess,
and I thought, ``We don't see each other at the bar,'' or maybe we don't fit in. So, in the middle of all this, I came to official business and did it together as a 2nd generation student.  That's really cool,
after all, I
started thinking like this when I started following him.I realized that we had become really
good friends.As we
continued to work together, I couldn't help but
feel better.It
was yoga.  Did
n't it happen? I don't know what happened, Jiyoung-chan, I wanted to stay with Somu as much as possible during difficult times.  It's like I don't have
anything. I don't know what to do. I don't know what to do. I don't know what to do. Even if I don't know what to do. It's a warehouse, so I thought I'd stay by
your side.  It's
kind of a Tea Danner
ok
Yeah, ah, I'll translate this far A 4 sensor The
debut ridge that looks like a club is really moe,
Resurge 2 is wearing a cap, the female student main entrance exam is a
bumper, etc. Ah, that's okay.  Let's
talk about something in the first five of us,
that's that
boo boo
okay
heno 4 eh is bef 9 o
2 office en bully
anac ping now
cornered 22 n coo
to the supporters dene walker
were to gay barbered down
oh rabbit  rd sports pando in future days bbs
fence party out 1 blue do
barber come on your star
in figure
voodoo camone
pt nonco pooh pom
speed intern
ah voice senpai desu
[music]
boo bar
re tour
finder wa iki ni wa senpai pure
is  You
suggested that I should reveal it to wipe Natsu
Cad Pouf It's nice
to
meet you, it's nice, Axio I think there are a lot of people I love,
so I asked you to
tell me something about how the butterflies you're talking about are so strong.
What's that? What's going on? When Yunnan Reddish
and Dai Amo
went shopping together for the first time,
luckily my wallet got bugs.
Deshion-chan also thought, ``A wallet would be nice.'' That
cute wallet.  So I found one, so I thought I'd go with this one.The
sound is great.I have a
matching set right
below.I sold it right away, listened to it on the scene, and then 2.Since I
moved in here, I've
had a lot of things matching.
Yes, maybe it's a girl or a lie
enoden
uscc center
cosy denda pin woofer
booster headache medeia pin
figure barford poster
alena turn Aqua-
senpai also increases Zakah total
Shion-senpai suppresses no, I'm rooting for the guard now
Shioda
Active spraying kyunkyun  Senpai salon
down security dem maybe
maybe you
do armor dad ass and
are
regular price 4 n degree
pareage
romances armei b 4 a
rod apple daily star
purely machimachi kurose's first unmanned taste yes
normal ui to electric wire is
oh well it's nice that we get along yeah yeah
ana
ka1
Thank you for closing the court.
Naha. Next question bar a I
think you have participated in many tie-up projects and collaboration projects,
such as Red Bull.
a
ahn How do you
say this in Japanese? avere vb
booeen
Middle center
Pu Ne
Nyan version around Daiei
Pika da
Windows have been on sale since the dawn Eh, there
have been many things such as the anime carnival of Kinmedi Yokosuka Kai, but what has been the most impressive role so far?
What is Matata Yumetai &?  I
have great memories of Edo Ren, but
yeah,
red bull.Personally,
even
before there was a stick like this,
I've been drinking it all the time, oo pips,
whenever I'm doing endurance games like Smash Bros.  I
drink Red Bull and
participate in the competition. UA is amazing. I
drink Red Bull all the time, sometimes up to 5 bottles a day.
Ah, I got a job while I was doing that. It's a
bit of a fateful situation.  Also, I
think, that's great, that's definitely
fate,
but I guess I drank a little too much.It's good for my health.It's a
shame.That's the same as the great evil of dreams.I don't
care about dreams.Well, I guess I'll stop in the future.
After all, I
want to collaborate with Kirito aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaak If we were to do a collaboration, what would it be like, what would it look like, what would it be like, what kind of essay would it be?
Maybe I'll hear about some more projects when I go.
Hey,
really.
rr
Polly
eir Patty standerd
eme star
lentil
moom Far leg 4 mash
isa
arterton
ores ease iso reading
live
otsu 5 a weapon speedway
minute home surf board  game
ah
ender 3 s carrying sponsor
sweets along the
ship Suo Issar degree pause
ah s spotlight to
ra
sosono willie hardy join
to
do for ape aspros order
undo fish uses for noa
petit news it work
bar 2 lard online
this patty #  bar ber zu
bar ber 4
arreas pass me two
words pathway b fino
I got a fee video and it's an
app with lies like Ayu-san Hmm, it's
good to be strong It's a
rent pool Yeah I wonder
what I should do Net Guru  The
original headquarters is
located in my country.
[Music]
Wow, it
looks small, so in my country there is a lot of red exchange,
but it's very Austrian,
but
after the rally with Germany, the Austrian sound
was not shaved off.  I can't say anything. We
don't have much and we're a small country, but Red
Bull is the only one that's popular and loved all over the world,
so we're proud of things like redballoon.
Yeah, but it's Austria.
Thank you for the music and the spoons. I understand.  Give it to
me, Aso. Hmm, that classic song. Even if it's
a tart, even if it's a natural story,
each story will be something that exists now. I'm
not biased, so I'm a living person.  Yes,
that's right, now it's the date to shake, and this is the
closed door treasure 0 shower.
If you're in Austria, you'll
be fine. I tried drinking a bell. But at that time, it was Japan no. It's
much stronger than a sake bottle, so I can't get enough of that color for one day.
Yes,
Non Air
Artist's Mezude Fellatio Boydo
Voodoo
S Bar
[Music] Leni
Nisho Hada
a yes de z 4 White Suseshimashi Pin
Stripe Force Translation First Yes
Technique to Massage Electrodeposition  Said Baikyo Ah, St.
Viner should be Queen, so it's
a little far away, but it's probably a good character.
Plan Pep,
Air Meow, Japan's energy drinks are
pretty weak. There's an
article from Wool Hosoda that says, "If you drink 5 bottles,
in Japan, it
's like a panda."  If I read Nokocchi Gohon every day, I'll
die
[Music]
Haaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaally know do that' I'm going to have
5 red swings and 2 more books and I'm
going to die with you and I'm going to
have a Fukuda game inheritance.
Please give me some love Senpai
Carender Choimp 5 Report
Spoon Lure Bikers Car
Stone Gaa Can you
do ri Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa I
wonder what those advertising words are called  Yes, that's a reflection of that.
If you drink five bottles of Girls Vasago, you'll turn into a divine spirit angel and you'll
be able to make a lager. I'll
send out about 8 bottles of Bach to my ex-wife, RGD, Stone, Terang, and James.  I think it's because of the cost of the drinks,
but I learned not to drink too much,
and I put on a spear to fight them off.Suggo-
chan, Aka-
senpai is
really good at FPS games.Especially A Vexy:
What do you think in your head when you play FPS games?  I wonder
how you've honed your skills to this level. Hmmm, I wonder
what it's
all about. The
best thing to do is not to rely too much on your allies. That's what
I've always done, so I guess it's
best to rely on your allies.  Don't rely too much on your allies.
If you have too many expectations, you'll end up with people joining your side like this,
and you'll end up feeling like you can't defeat them.
But if you lose because you're weak, it's
not because your allies are weak.  If I was strong, I would have bought it, so I guess
I'm like this.If I
was an apec child, I would have bought it if I could have beaten 3 people by
myself.Because I made him the
king.Ichima and Kaa.I couldn't win even with one buoy one,
but Siri.  I'm now
able to win. I'm
now able to win. Sakura
Rei, skill, soc, month goods,
Shisase, ae, power, wii,
my pv, lyrics, address, mid-march,
ah, main, Hansen, base side,
aim, sensor volunteers, Chungbuk.  Sapp
Town Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa Noen Seed Markets
Ponytsu
The Lord is Kazuo Way 5 eastland
cars Amy nippers
author Ozone Pointer
can you
do
rear
altered
esra re born to
do in Eh
Mother Down Hurry ro
Pyu
Do I don't understand at all so the story is
quite painful.  I don't have it, but please continue
rar I'm sorry 4 That
's right, hmm, as much as possible I guess
this is
what it is I was doing it in the early summer when IPX started, so I was
doing it after all.I feel like I've acquired some skills,
but recently.  I have
n't been able to play any games since I've been working so much,
but I don't play them even for a single day, and now that I
'm here with my mom, things haven't changed for 11 days.
It's been about 3 days since
Kimura's layer has become really worn out,
so I
might be weak now
a
1 Tom doesn't know
render capdase
scheme
ode to
do minoa
army Bomber play s 4
days a wizard
clearcase  Port 4
fifi days season for
one dansko car with the
back to
please ka lie day scrutinizing spun
winter huh um
about the epo case um
if there's nothing else to talk about I have another question
but the
balloons aren't so much about the earrings
f about the pace  Ah, why do you like that
? Hey, why do you like x instead of other games during the mix?
Yeah, I like other games, too. I
like games too, to be honest, Apex. I
guess this is what I'm good at.  I guess that's why
Apec Su
is so popular right now, and
that's why
my other favorite games aren't so much
distributed as samurai games.It's a
big touch, so it's inevitable.  I had the
opportunity to play Apex a lot, but
when I played FX as well, I fell in love with it.
Paaaa Opel Ano Difarafu
piercing game
us headquarters ara ara acky 6
e hurry face menus push
Souther apx school avatar
pure Shisusegufesti main
anb the key
blue tongue yappa c 4 pin sadosou
9 as swimming  in a
Then
[Music] This
has nothing to do with earrings, but it's Chiara's thing. That's
one thing I thought was amazing.
There's something sweet about Aka-senpai's game. I
wonder if I
saw something like Mario Kart with Bach or something like that Yoshino
map.  Day, I
was waiting for everyone to go earlier, and there was
a group of people going to the back, and I was waiting around for the
blue item, that was that, that bread
item, and the color was amazing.
That's what I thought
when I used this guy's disguise.nan Chausu Gaku There was a tactic like that and it was
often used in the second half of junior high school.Aaah, there was a guy with green hair who had more power at the time.I
tried imitating him and surprisingly he was really strong.  Recommendation
A Recapture A After meeting, it's basically red.No matter
what game you play, it's super.Well, the
cooking simulator was that,
but no matter
how you play it, you're good at
it.I was surprised, but
I practiced a lot before streaming.  I wonder if I'll do it.I
practice a lot.It's really the best.I'm not really good
at Mario Kart, but I'm golden.I'm
bad at FPS, too.I wonder what it's like
to be a champion, and I'm so happy that I can pass the lag.Even though I'm not really good at it,
it's okay.  I don't think there are many people who are good at it right from the start,
but
when I wasn't doing that job other than streaming, I was
just practicing the game all the time, and I thought I'd
like to see how good I am at streaming.  I've
been practicing all the time, which is amazing.
It's amazing how passionate you can be while doing that. No, but I guess this is what's happening right now. I'm busy
with work over there, so I can't practice, so I can't even practice, and I
can't even practice. It's amazing.  I don't
think it's okay to show them, so I'm having a lot of trouble.I don't think you need to worry too much about it, but I
think Aqua-senpai's is the only place you'll be a fan of Aka-senpai.
Hershey center arm high bate
melts aps Touko scars of
o
reales ah
carissa
searc flexibility
s well
lever squish amber act
voodoo bike c cat's paw tour
n dish
25 so with phone n
cat's dam 1st place
scare is good Aichi is Ito
uso fur  place
for us
to
do warp for so this
game for a 4 f
[music]
den o ore to
do other picamuu eno
washer callous prime minister won and other ungrateful shoulder
long pin board y
center power whip and always in front
Oh my god, I see. Please
tell me a good way to run the car between the doors. Over
there, I
invited the jaw line for some,
but I think the red turn has just passed. I
think the player dream will be annoyed.  I
'm teaching you some kind of barrier car, and
Pauline is the best at it.I wonder who's the best at it.Inan
Jain-chan, that's Airin, in the
early days.The other day, at my house, I
covered the Indonesian group's Anomalica tournament.It's
worth it.  I don't know,
but the one who was the best at that was Ina-chan, right? I don't
think there would be a house without it. Senran 22, I practiced really hard, and Naouchi was pretty good at it. 3  1st place
Wholesaler distance name That dog is steadily adding 1 driver
software I draw
That Ramen Club & Nbun Liar 3rd place The
house that was in the amazing area is very content The
cat's needs are really good with this minced meat
Everyone except chan  It wasn't
that difficult when Bach said it was boring
yeah I
got in and there were 3 New Iris
I danced really well, slowed down
Hey, it's
really straight It's
true, please don't worry about it
5 times how the Japanese members filled up
nimes et mer diner 4 s
who do n cup kinen 8
re na request audi a
situation
spend person
permmme grigar minutes
aparece em press dare
to snap in place in
bef
use to
[  [Music]
dous Aqua-senpai 2 Charsum Well, it's
comfortable see
Well, yeah, I think I'll practice with a shovel while watching Aqua-senpai's broadcast. I wonder
if it'll be a learning experience. No, I'm so
happy. ok ok
Ah, that's a question,
but
9 is 1000 times a
Ima University.  I'm a senior at Ink's Minato Aqua, but in the
early days of my debut, my
numbers weren't growing and I was worried about
it.I wonder if there was a change in your state of mind that you think you could have grown in at the time.  I
guess that's what happened in 2018, when I debuted in 2018.
V Kitchen Burger has
n't really caught on yet, but there
were a lot of popular members, but the
live broadcast itself is
probably like this.  There was a
time when I was thinking a lot about what I could do to get more people to see it. Don't
stop. It was true. So what?  I don't
know how much it was or what was normal.When I
debuted, I played the role of a god.I
was happy that 1,500 people watched the review broadcast, but I was happy that the lines were also watched, so I decided to
broadcast the next one.  There were only 300 of them there,
but that was still normal.I was
happy to see those 300 people, but
I found it interesting that there were 300 people left from Devil, which has decreased so much.  I can
see why it wasn't there,
but the fact that those 300 people watched it was so precious, and it
may be less than a dog, but at that time I didn't
think there were that many people, but I
felt that.  I
wonder if I was thinking a lot about why it didn't work Hmm
a I
'll just eat here for now
can barb atc
delan When will bead booth 1 round
party for earth
eason hit balloon
popular areas of the
online
watch c 2 games over  view
sasj ha maybe she is 4
a debut
sear 1 ter's fifa ender
ender this 4 f 4 f in
buster do
do eiusmodrp
planter supercomputer pure difference floating
wallet harpy up affun darkness
3n disaster prevention violation violation watching
Come on
window fall back to the boss
ooh along Zion re Dowd
Cap Twin Gompersenu Motor
Senior Rudefian Speak
Mr. Bike suggested it and it's boring
voices in chesty
Nah then Shasha's Windu That
guy ob Kanpei The
main reason  I'm a bald man, so
let's create a labyrinth all over the house. Well then,
let's talk about his growth and his mother, and how he moved his new home to the outskirts.
Hey, now, just like in the past, each and every one of us is
important.  That's what I thought, but yes, that's kind of the
case. The director's changes. Hmm. But, at that time, I was no longer desperate, so it was a desperate day. Hmm, I couldn't see my surroundings at all. I was desperate, but now
I can see my surroundings a little more.  Or
should I say, blue, I'm not used to it.That's right, that part has changed, and I'm employed.Pita
or ran, it might be booba.I see,
pase ipa
benro car for
beach stone bag kindergartener's repair.
correca
seasar ah leather style power
ranger series
welly
upper cooper s ween
bag nu do with cleaner
sound raumn machu action hare
folkestone rather fai guess arm
fix this week sbaan 2 undine sand
ikuto peep
isr ade growth count  24 Su
Wanu Judge is also with me
Randy
Holding cheese fried
asas Mouah bar Haiku
Shizuku Seal Off Works Boner
Anti-Habo
Boots
Tarrus e to
do gentoo per good
to
do so Rihana afc Goods
Big Willow  Cap jr line star crushing
tissue brain is color rummy and
before I remember practice epion see zuya
v bing pinky's voice is also good hmm
yeah yay
teaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
to now N-aqua
senpai to then to memorize color rummy and practice.  If you look at it,
does it give you some advice? I wonder
what it is. Hmm.
Hmm. The
people around him
are kinder than you think. I
want to tell them that the prince is scared of everyone, he's a
strong person, and the staff are strong too.  The
members of this live show are also strong, and
even though I was afraid of interacting with others, I
did it alone for a long time, but it was getting a bit headachey. I
interacted with the members and performed. I
guess I felt the warmth of the people, but
there was a part of it.  Well, the staff,
managers, and various other people are gradually getting to know each other.
I see. Little by little, I'm able to talk to the members more and more. It's nice.
Song Wenshu, it's okay, Aqua-senpai, the village
p passage.  Parker Center is here p
actually
propper
duren Daywalker's r t
you
do
do at the hospital
I want to
play 4 times Inoichi Raffy 6 turns My own
refund car
Weatherby 1st line
3rd part Monkey's Inner Year
Um,
that's how that hood is ebony
Because I'm here, I feel like I'm always alone.There's
no point in being active.Then, I
don't have a home for a long time.It means I'm in a place,
so I
think it's good to hang out with everyone.
Nana-chan and ipod, I'm good at it
, hey, I'm tired, phew is Jesus'
Year of the Dog, Luneng Chandenebumu
Mitsubishi Subin, quartet f, the big soy sauce bottle that I'm going to is a concern, but it's super big,
Hmm, Stay and Lancer count 2,
Pooh, 4 pieces.  It's
been three years already since I've been active as a Fell Live member,
and
Daigai has grown and grown a lot.  We have achieved this.
Please tell us about your next goals and dreams.
Yes, that's true. Hey, it's even more true
than I thought. Now that the concept of Heart Live is well
known to the general public, we'll grow
up and do all sorts of Moomin things.  Now that I have more opportunities to do
things that I never thought I could do before, my
next goal
is, in this day and
age, I've
become able to do a little bit of a headache live, so I guess that's what I thought.
One-man live at
Budokan in Japan  Well, it's a building with a lot of selling material. I wonder
if it's like this. It's a
building where live
performances are held. Hmm, I'd like to have a live performance in the loan room. That's great. I
know the branch hall, so I
guess when it comes to idol concerts, it's okay. My dream is to live in the same hall.  Okay, um, uh,
Locus Kin no Terii, nee, foot center,
artist, Papua Naa ni 5 times Bicam,
Sanpei stroller Maa's banner, face
japan 4 type s meeting
powder china fur baby 2
boo
nearer up powder n all
ears
are you do
me
errors
in in the voodoo
Grand Web Art Festa en
world
rean daypack bye naa
watch fin
venue day op's Royal Budokan map sey bell
card magazine debut herbal
counseling Budokan um
pleasure to do in
glasgow to dosweet
No, I
wonder if I could do it if I were an absolutely evil senpai. Well, well, I'm going to go to the second floor and rub some rare breasts.
Naa, I'm going to do it with the characters after all.
Well, I'm going to do it later, right? 4 We'll all do it
together. We'll all do it together. Power products are good.  Horukko
Lola, so I'm going to watch it and do it.I'm a 2nd year prefectural
student.I have to dream big and
big.Hmmmmm cars in beach labyrinth
d 4th generation down
Acme Kids Aranjuez Drive e
Brown Senpai Foam Penetration Wig Watch FC
Hey  It
's the last song, but
for Aka-senpai, it's Horo Live and
Pro Live.
[Music]
There's Nakamare. It's another place to be.
Minn. I
see. I see. Anko is 5. What's going on? I'm
afraid of the police.
place to be by soc part
anthem mac
select one and use the mouse to say it
sister aku senpai Wow that
's all about quality but
there's one thing I'd like to promote right?
Magic Chara-chan's Instinct
Since I've been performing far and wide and have
seen a lot of people overseas,
please refine this song a little. That's
great.  Ah,
Ah Ah Ah Ah Windu White Sofis
Popular Bed Performance Lave Distone
Music for Surface at
Kuu THIS EER
[Music]
Good, good,
toranoana
drinking
[Music]
me
[Applause
] [
Music] [Applause] [Music] ni tan [Music
]
Good, good, ani
rar
nande
n ame
ana
car
[Music]
nara
rar
dare  NI
[Music]
Me
ME
[Music]
[Applause]
On Galaxy RAW CEREUS
IIR Ross CARBON PRO 7
minutes Rach
Kiya Aika  I've
always thought that
that sound is something that's difficult to
hear overseas.I've always thought that they must be listening to Japanese songs over and over again.Even
though there are so many difficult sweets, I can't help but
wonder how I feel when I listen to Tonko.  I kept
posting posts
saying, ``Oh, well, I want to convey
this song called ``Bright Aiiro Panette''
to Inpan fans overseas,
so I created the Acha English Bar.  I thought it would be a
good idea to tell them, so I
'm going to cover it. OC Declaration CY
Arm is CSR Claw Ding Bush
property damage
Yeah yeah white Soarcher Fuji
Speedway voicemail e b
swish Center sugar village liner
rcs
render web swing
japanese fan fender
Implemented in 4 minutes son down
rear how dosu p nzusonsu that kind of
Kyary is cooler stay
beaconvator pro isoenol tour
make and hospital gusuanker m class
pui r size ben bead
anger it's red even in oita pen  Line
Pipe I
can't speak English, so this and Reimu must have been difficult. It
was delicious. I wrote the beautiful [ __ ] in katakana, and then I
wrote each letter in Japanese.
It took me a long time and it was difficult, but how did I get it
across?
[Music] I don't know if I'm
holding a balloon. It
's so good. I'm
going straight to the fur. I'll send it to Bach. I wish I could meet Bach,
but
what was I looking at?  It's easy to buy bait when you listen to it, even
if it's over, no matter how many times I listen to it, I
want to sing it even if I'm root and don't look at it There are a
lot of tools that make sense
Porori
refer to
do as a doodle
1 patter patter haaa deep  yeah
sting japanese abus
domineering aafubu [ __ ] 2 re 1 mo
susan farn
paper soren
orders are
rebelde
rear turn to do so do do
anders 4 se jon desu
ichisen
boo boo ses 3ds fire
mpge to render
firming gel good u i get
Now that I'm a guest guest, I'm
saying I'm going to live for 5 minutes.I'm really
cute.I
really like red letters.I was
surprised to see that English mountain.
No, I'm really happy, and
I want him to have an all-around first performance with Taichi Urai. kokok
This song is a samurai, don't be late. I
don't like it when you copy it completely and hit your head,
but I think the best singer is Aqua-senpai.
[Music]
Ranran den den o
anders apace led
Cap 4
Back to you,
Aka-senpai, thank you for doing the interview today.Ah,
ana.It
was really fun.I'm glad you talked so much about what it was like today.I
bought the 8th book, and it was really cheap,
so I was nervous.  That's great. Boo boo
reru street
casadei 8 security nc
scepter 4 drunken happy b 4 pearl
delicious web child the weeds and
pou dou
dou squeezer
power spot man fart arm talking mom
chan 3 hey pal  For the birthday service, if
you'd like, please share your impressions of today and be
careful about the edges of Tozora and tweet on Twitter. I
'll look into it later, so please
do.
Now, for the last time, let's
hit the Aker Line bar and say that German
word.  I'm making a lot of noise, but I
wonder if you can say it with me now. Yes, I'll do my best. It's that Cerezo.
One voice with a distant
frown. Ah, feeder. He's smart, but aaah, I
want him to join me in the field. I'm
cheering for him. Soarwillerzenfira
Zain
Ah, it's okay, it's
okay, I can't meet you because I'm
bald.Engine, made by Germany, half ban.The interior is a seismic inlet space.Ah, thank you for watching the two of us in Onmenzu.Thank you, we didn't talk about this.It's the red line.
Air nya head 4 se
Ah, just now, that love
was showing my onion head to my senior, so it
was gay, wasn't it?
Hey, onions are worth the price of orange souls,
and red seniors are purple onions.  Garden
tan
Umyons-chan 2
ran
Thank you very much can
goo
viber
Hmm aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaa
music]