[Music]
so
i'm
i'm hungry
be right back getting sandwich
so
[Music]
is this sandwich still good
5th 5th october
oh that egg looks suspicious
[Music]
hmm
it tastes a bit different than usual
[Music]
so
um
isn't it interesting
how an egg
can not only be an egg
as you know food
but also wait
i limited the frame rate is it
interesting how an egg can not only be
an egg as a like a food thing
you know the white thing with the yellow
thing inside
but it can also be a chicken
and then it's meat
so it can be
vegetarian but it can also be not
vegetarian
think about it so when i have a
egg sandwich in some way this could have
been a chicken sandwich
what in some way it is a chicken
sandwich
what so when i eat a vegetarian egg
in some way it is not vegetarian
because i mean this could have been a
chicken what
oh my god
what okay last bite
[Music]
excuse me that was a pure
that was a pure top right moment okay
wow by like that that's just like
an egg can be anything an egg
can be so many things but an
egg maybe cannot be
all these things at the same time
so me being
a phoenix
maybe i don't have to be too many things
at the same time maybe it's okay if i'm
only one thing at the same time
that's some deep [\h__\h] bro
some things are just not possible you
know you don't have to force yourself to
do certain things
because you know sometimes it just
doesn't work and that's
how it's supposed to be
but no i'm not a chicken
and that does not make me a chicken i
said i'm a phoenix i think you all heard
that
wow wow
i'm a very wise bird indeed
welcome everyone welcome everyone
welcome back
today was supposed to be only one stream
but here i am doing two streams
or you could you could ignore the first
stream and this is the only stream today
you guys know what i ate for breakfast
today
no eggs i did not eat any eggs because i
i'm waiting for you guys to grow big and
become
chicken so for the meantime i'm not
eating any eggs
cause what if i accidentally eat one of
you
that is not good so i for breakfast i
ate
a huge cinnamon bun
warmed up oh my god it was so good
i ate it with my bare hands because i'm
a cave person
i ate it with my bare hands and shoved
it into
actually no i didn't even really use my
hands i only used my mouth
let's be real i only really used my
mouth
but it's just so big so my whole face
was covered in
cinnamon uh
cinnamon
liquid what glaze
thank you i was trying to find a word
that does not sound
wrong but like
okay
today or now in this stream
so i went from top right to bottom left
again in like five minutes
wow great i've i've come so far and then
suddenly
i fall into my usual corner again oh
no
what was i going to say oh yeah we're
reading super chats tonight
and having some chit chats along the way
this is how fast you can go from top
right to bottom left
it's just sad it's just so sad how fast
life changes how fast your image can be
completely
ruined
welcome everyone to the membership hello
welcome
actually i was almost late to the stream
because uh until five minutes before
stream i was laying in bed and checking
reddit
um
everyone from reddit thank you so much
for always
trying to cheer me up it's
really sweet and i really really really
appreciate it
but i also feel like um
a bit bad about it because it's like
always like every day it's like
oh my god kiara cried let's help her out
so
people who don't know me probably would
be like oh my god she's crying every
[\h__\h] day
so
[Music]
maybe every once in a while it's fine
but if you want to cheer me up every day
just go to my twitter i'm like reading
all the replies because
i can't stop scrolling
so if you want to be nice i really
really appreciate it
no i need those pets i need i need them
but maybe not too much on reddit it's uh
i i really i'm really happy about it
though don't get me wrong like
when i see those posts and then it says
piara let's support kiara it makes me
really happy
but i also feel like maybe other people
might be annoyed by it
or if they might get a wrong image of me
i mean it's i guess it's the right image
and i'm crying every
every goddamn stream i guess it's the
right image but it's not the image i
want new people to get
so thank you
thank you for your support though thank
you i love you all
i wish i could hug every single one of
you
i need more hugs i need hugs
i want to go to a cat cafe but like
every time i go to a cat cafe they
ignore me so i haven't gone to one for a
long time you know oh my god do you know
how this feels like
the other day the other day i guess last
year
last year i went to a cat cafe and uh
usually when i go to cat cafes i know it
will take some time to
bond you know and make a relationship so
i usually like stay there as long as
possible like for hours and i don't do
anything besides staring at the cats and
trying to make them love me
but so i i sit in this cat cafe trying
to be still
and like interesting looking interesting
to the cat
and i wait and i wait but every time
they just go away from me
if i try to just sit still they don't
come to me and if i try to go to them
they go away
okay which i kind of get because in a
cat cafe that's why i don't actually
like going to cat cafe so much because i
feel like kind of sorry for the cats
because i actually uh
i've raised cats and i've lived with
cats before
and if i imagine them being annoyed by
strangers
every goddamn day like so many strangers
in a usually not so big
room too
i don't like that i i i can understand
why they don't go on why they don't want
to chill
with humans or phoenixes
but then get this
new customer comes into the cat cafe
where i've been in for two hours already
customer comes in with her friend so
there's two girls okay so they sit down
next to me
on the floor with you know a legs like
like how you say crossed i guess you
know when there's a space between your
legs
and your ass
so there's a space there okay she sits
down like that one minute later
not even one minute a cat comes
up to her and sits in that spot
and i'm like hello
hello cat what about me and
the thing is i was wearing you know how
my my skirt is super short
you know what right
okay i can't sit like that person does
apparently that's a way of sitting for
the like really lures in the cats
because they want to sit
in that spot that's like a perfect hole
but imagine me sitting like that
in a room filled with people strangers
if i sit like that my skirt
will either rip or
go up to my belly button and you'll just
see
whatever i'm wearing on the teeth
so on that day of course i was wearing a
short skirt
and i saw that cat sitting
like in between the legs of that film i
was like [\h__\h]
i want to sit like that too and i tried
but it was impossible
nicole
oh well that's the struggle but so ever
since then i
since that visit i haven't been to the
cat cafe because first of all i'm salty
like why don't they come to me why
and second of all i'm not so sure if i
like generally
how cats are like in a small space there
like that but there's like cat cafes
that are like
like part of a pet shop for for example
so those and but then there's cat cafes
where
like they rescue cats and that's how
they get their income and that
that i do want to support that i think
is a really really really good thing
that's a really good solution to
financing
uh you know rescued cats and
you can even like if if there's a cat
that you like you can even get it
and then bring it home that's so awesome
right
i have been to an owl cafe as well but
it was like a really tiny room in square
meters i would say was like
maybe five square meters and they were
like
20 owls in five square meters or maybe
um
[Music]
i'll leave that up to you what you think
about it
they were really cute
[Music]
they were really really cute but after
that i never went to an el cafe ever
again
no oh well it's a lot of fun
i want to go to a dog cafe though like i
know i've only been to
the cat coffees but never to dog cafes i
wonder like
they must be like okay cats are like fu
i don't want any business with you but
dogs must be like touch me touch me yes
touch me touch me touch me touch me wrap
my belly butt rub my belly yes yes
please please please
whacked out
on the coffee
oh my god is someone is someone gonna
clip that and upload that out of context
oh my gosh uh yeah
probably someone's to do it
okay fine i guess
okay
so now that now that we have talked
about these important things
yeah i guess i'll start
reading the super jets the super chats
um i'm starting
with the first one from
the minecraft stream
here and
how is everyone doing by the way how are
you
today is fubuki senpai's birthday by the
way
happy birthday for looking senpai
happy birthday happy birthday
to you happy birthday to you
happy birthday happy
ah she'll have a should have a stream
um at in two hours
not even two hours from now anymore but
in one and a half hours approximately
she'll have her birthday stream so i
hope everyone will go there
and wish her a happy birthday because
she's such a
wholesome wholesome awesome person
and she's not not a cat
[Music]
actually i wanted to start streaming uh
like
one hour from now or so but i i switched
uh
the times um but a bit early here
because of
uh i thought that i'm probably not gonna
get this done in one hour with so much
talking in between
so i moved my slots
i wish
i wish they had fubuki song and karaoke
services
because i really i really like safe
homes
i really really really like it
with that i show i shall start
which i already said like minutes ago
maybe one day i'll sing this little
version
[Music]
uh
don't mind my strange sounds
everything is confusing and as i told
you
i am i cannot be an egg and a chicken at
the same time
it's just i can only be one thing at the
same time i'm not a multi-tasker
there's only so many things that i can
juggle
after every name and i read some
of the messages that he struck
stand out to me
i didn't admit anything i just said i
can't be an egg and a
chicken at the same time but maybe that
means i can't be any of them because
i'm finished
did you see that long string of tweets i
sent yesterday i wanted
to super chat the message but there's no
way i could have fit everything
i did see it yes easies thank you
there's i received like so many replies
recently because you guys are so
wholesome and you guys all want to cheer
me up and i'm so sweet
ten thousand dollar mattress i really
like
uh why do people there's always people
who wanna misunderstand me but you gotta
understand
up until now the tweets that i've sent
out
often had some weird phrasing and
sometimes it's on purpose
and sometimes it's not so the one where
i wrote to kelly that i'm hiding in a
closet
that was not on purpose
but i realized quickly after what i've
done but the damage has been done i
could not have deleted that anymore
because everyone already saw
i was just you know i was writing that
tweet and i was like uh
hiding heights in i was like where could
i
what could i write that i would hide in
i wanted to write first i wanted to
write like
heights in corner because i i thought
like kelly would maybe bonk me
for deciding on a on a hashtag for us
which by the way i got her permission to
do so on discord before
i did it officially but so i'm like oh
what should i write what should i write
and then i was like oh maybe closet
would be a good idea because i can close
the doors and you know it's a small
small dark space where i can hide where
she will not find me and then i write i
write it and i tweet it out and then i'm
like
oh
actually i think i didn't even realize
it myself i think the tweets
at me made me realize and i was i was
like
oh it fits well i guess it it fits well
and that's a mattress thing though that
was also not intentional and
first of all okay there was there was
more than one misunderstanding there
some people thought that i was flexing
with money no i wasn't i was
just trying to tell you what how how
good the support
feels to me that i get from you it just
feels like like when i
when i uh like you know
fall back like when i get punched in my
face
and i fall back that what i land on is
this
really comfortable mattress okay so i
was not
flexing with money because first of all
there's no money yet
here anyway and second of all
the other misunderstanding was then that
people thought i was uh
playing like like hinting on
coco senpai's mattress
i didn't even know she has a ten
thousand dollar mattress
i wanna sleep on that ten thousand
dollar mattress
so all of you were wrong i wasn't trying
to say anything with that tweet some of
you just think too much into things that
are written on the internet
for real though don't believe
everything you see on the internet and
don't always
maybe maybe also don't think that what
you what you
think you understand is really what it
is
things are just not always the way it
seems
okay well good that we
issues so buying an actual 10 000
mattress
would be a good investment in the future
but what does a ten thousand dollar
mattress
do
really i i wonder
how
foreign
spinningly
yeah some some things just cost too much
money you could probably get the same
quality of product if you just buy it
for five thousand dollars probably as
well so
some things are just uh you know they're
expensive
because the purpose is to be expensive
that's ridiculous that's why
yo there were some times you know i'm
actually like
really help actually i'm really careful
with spending money
i'm surprised about that myself too but
there was a time where
i was um you know in my previous life
i was uh under a training in german it's
called
leia it's like when you go
to a specific school
i haven't even read more than three
super chat names yet
this is going to be fun i went to a
specific school
for a specific job like 10 this is like
a
system that exists in germany austria
and so on
so i went to a specific school
for three years only but only two months
uh two months in a year
so in total that would be six months but
the other ten months
you go to work at a place that is
specific for that
thing yeah it's called apprenticeship i
guess it's the closest word
but i also wouldn't say that it's 100
the right way to
describe it anyway so i did something
like that for three years okay
and i you know it
you get money from that but it's like
especially in the first year it's like
nothing so i would actually like
my my dinner would be bread that i took
home
from work and that
that taught me like also oh my god my my
my phoenix mom
eventually after she found out after i
was already done with these for years
she found out after that how much i was
uh
struggling with money and uh
she was like how the hell did you even
do that because for example okay
i don't 100 remember anymore but let's
say my
my phoenix nest rent was like
500 and then
living alone and then my
phoenix job uh well
income was 600
so i had like 100
to buy food every month and it actually
kind of worked and and my mom after she
found out about that she was like how
how f did you do that
i have some really good survival skills
you know in minecraft it might not look
like i have the best survival skills but
i do yeah
yeah even my my phoenix mom was
impressed with that
so that's when now um
when i'm in a situation where i have the
choice
between spending a [\h__\h] ton of money
on something that will eventually will
be resolved anyway
then i feel like wait for
it to be resolved when i know for sure
that it will be resolved anyway in
the near one somewhat near future you
know what i mean
i
especially if things work the way they
work already
they kind of work they there is a way to
make it work
then maybe i don't need to 100 you know
throw out all that money that doesn't
even exist yet
don't want to waste money i mean it's
also an investment of course at the same
time but
the investment would officially be
wasted at the point where
i i get to the point where i don't need
that investment anymore
i'm speaking in riddles i'm basically
talking about the pc
issue now i'm just um
too much in survival mode still it's all
about survival
for me that's why i'm saying also you
guys
please don't donate for me to get a pc
because the one that i use today is a
different one from usual
and the one that i used before yesterday
is maybe not the best one
but it was good enough to stream fall
guys minecraft
fire emblem whatever
and eventually in about five months
i'm getting back my gaming pc which is
at the moment on here
and yeah five months might be a long
time
but i don't pc
wise it's not really such an issue right
now
from my perspective i don't think it's
that bad and
it was just today because i used a
different pc
but yeah
yeah and then when i got that normal pc
again
let's say i buy a new pc in between
until that time in for
for five months that's like for me
that's such a waste
yeah a long time for me like
it's not time is passing so quickly but
i am timeless
it's a it's not a a place where i can't
reach it
i have i have already invested okay
for the people who say invest in your
job i have already
invested even okay let me
clear this up one one time again then
i'll never want to talk about these
things ever again
but i have already invested i bought
expensive mic expensive audio interface
expensive mic
arms because that that was okay that
made sense
okay but guys keep in mind
i am still in survival mode
poor phoenix
but that made sense the microphone made
sense pc
i'm not at to me not at this point i'm
sorry
and it worked i got
if it wouldn't work yes i understand it
but it works
i i streamed minecraft with no issues
the other day
i streamed fire on them which had issues
but that was because of the capture card
now that's something
else we can talk about that's something
i'm still trying to figure out
and there's a lot of things that i'm
trying to improve anyway
so one after another okay
thank you
let's move on amazing blocks thank you
tissue box no i'm not using a tissue box
anymore
i bought a roads road road
roads where it's my car i'm okay
albedo the kfp giant
is that what you wanted to all your cute
little eggs checking your stream there
we go
okay no more
thank you so much thank you for the
super chat thank you for your support
again
thank
there is tori sugar no kamen rider in my
stream right
and there's tori sergari no ghost in
kelly's stream
are those the same people and changing
their names
because kamen rider i guess is a joke on
like a
spin on my belt
and ghost riders because kylie has a
ghost ride in front of her
place
is that the same person and just keep on
changing their name
because they're here every time
please ame start the investigation this
is a big mystery i need to know
emilia
very interesting must start
investigation now
immediately i i shall write a report
and send it over to amelia
[Music]
i think you can make something out of it
if i give you the meat
this dr what
the move is all i thought yeah well i
thought the move is over but here i am
again somewhere else so i guess the move
is never over
the move is not over until
march 2021
thank you
explaining the situation thank you very
much thank you sean
takeo one two three thank you soon happy
birthday takeo
happy birthday
becca murphy eleven thank you
thank you
[Music]
what
saucy coach one two three thank you
darren wait thank you
thank you bloop thank you
thank you mickey mouse
oh yeah the stream was very fast and
there were many people
at the minecraft team thank you so much
i was actually really happy
to have so many people i think it's
probably because no one no one else
from her life ian streamed today
like even later
like i checked the schedule but i don't
see anyone streaming
is it uh yeah you know
but at what time america
okay for me that was not today yeah yeah
that was not today for me so like for
did for today it was like only me that's
why i was kind of also hoping that it
would go
well but oh well yeah
actually that there was like wasn't
there's a day like that
last week was it also monday where i was
like
okay i want to take a break but then i
saw no one is streaming so i was like
okay damn it i gotta stream cause no one
is streaming i can't
have a day where no one from hell ivy on
the stream is the last monday what i
think it was also last monday
i turned out the video only one stream
oh that's so funny and then on that day
after my stream we were like on discord
and we were like
girls we we should uh do something about
um all using the same day as a break day
we should it's a weird coincidence we
should maybe not all take the same day
off
but apparently it didn't work
today again i was the only one what's
that guys okay today it's good like uh
at least someone is streaming
yeah monday is a lazy day i totally feel
that like
if one week is over need a goddamn break
i know that feeling
i feel ya it's okay i'll see it as my
chance
to to have everyone look at me
let's see how next monday goes
maybe monday will forever be the day
where only kiara is streaming wouldn't
that be funny
mondays are for kiara exactly monday is
kiana day
oh my god now i really want that to
happen next week if it will be only me
again that would be so funny
oh oh okay so
speaking of next monday uh
have a bad bad information
i mean i'm hoping it will not
affect you guys as much as it affects me
but i told you next monday i'll get my
internet
and i'll be able to stream from home
again from the new home where i just
moved into because
they moved the original date 5th of
october to 12th october
but they moved it again and
it's now the 26th
so for three weeks
i don't have internet
at my place it was originally supposed
to be the fifth okay
[Music]
it's unbelievable it's actually
unbelievable
unbelievable it is so unbelievable
is that even legal
yeah but yeah i mean
uh it i i think in the end it will only
affect me
and not you guys so you should
see no no
no influence or whatever why are you so
unlucky
please i wanna know i want to know thank
you for asking that question i would
love to know that
what's their excuse i don't know
honestly
it's like you know when you there's like
you can like
set it up on the internet and you're
like i want they give you a bunch of
dates
which are available and i chose the
earliest date which was the 12th
october at the second time first it was
the fifth okay
and then yeah so that was supposed to be
it but apparently today they decided
that's not it
it has to be the 26th
amendment took all the luck stats
i think yeah if you would if you put if
you would
take the five whole live en members
and say like they all
put all the points into one stat
for ahmed would be luck apparently
for uh ina what what's that would be
fitting
like i would say creativity or talent
but like that's not really a thing that
usually exists
and ah intelligence oh yeah that makes
sense okay ina would be intelligence
kali i would say would be strength
because oh my god the beats she's
throwing out there i like boom boom
[Laughter]
and gura guda would be speed or
something like that
so what what what the hell would i be
what where would my is there a stat
that's called unlucky
or like bullied bullets that
charisma okay thank you i'll take that
as a compliment
i think you're right guys you might be
right
charisma interesting interesting
so i'm charisma
eyes speed wait what's the normal term
for that in rpgs what's with the
what's the speed
what's the one for speed
agility ah agility okay
gude has everything skilled on agility
inna has everything skilled on
intelligence
kylie is everyone skilled on strength
and anna has everything skilled
on willpower or wait did i say something
wrong did i make something up
no not real power not luck luck is luck
and me is charisma that sounds
funny uh
when i played mmrpgs in the past when i
played a healer i would also put all my
all my points in intelligence so
actually no it depends on the mmrpg
because sometimes it works differently
and then sometimes i when i would play a
damage dealer i would put it all on what
was it
something that gives me like crits that
was it was it
what was that
yeah i guess it was just called cr no
dexterity really i never heard of that
before
yeah maybe it was luck but maybe it was
also just quit damage but
whatever who cares
uh i miss playing a good mmorpg i was so
addicted to mmrpgs in the past
[Music]
not anymore though unfortunately because
there's nothing
that really catches my interest
i did play ff14 before but i prefer
nmrpgs which i like in a cute
anime style so i'm looking forward to
blue protocol
2.0 when they fixed the things that were
kind of weird
and excited satanic sunshine duncan
thank you for the recommendations but um
i'm not gonna upgrade my manager's
computer
if anything yeah i'll upgrade my own
computer but i don't even know
how the hell do you open up a pc and put
something in there and close it again i
don't even know how to open a pc like i
don't even know that that's the problem
anyway uh facs01
thank you for the mod recommendations
over i really actually have to look into
those at least
um but it has to be mods that are
allowed and legal
because i don't know if we're even
allowed but if it's something that just
increases speed i guess you wouldn't
see it if i use it so
that's like magic though that's magic
[Music]
what are you talking about
because my first language is german
often when i read
when i want to read w i always want to
read it as
v v we we i want to read it as we
why is w so long why couldn't you just
have it
pronounced as we so when i read
wb hooky i want to read we be hooky
why is it not in german it's v
eh
like a b c d everything's so easy and
then there's w
but okay opposite the other way around i
can tell you one that is easy in english
but difficult in german
i mean not real difficult but still it's
weird so in english there's
y right in german it's
upsilon but no one ever
needs to say a single upsilon
so it doesn't really matter
unnecessary information you are welcome
red sox thank you oh i'll get the new pc
front
get one of those rtx free eight okay
okay
how much does that cost you guys are all
like insisting on
holy [\h__\h] that's expensive
is it actually really eh
give me the amazon price
why does it show me the quadro rtx 4000
though
it's not the one i want to see
that's so expensive i don't have that
money
and i wouldn't even know how to put it
into my pc
okay but okay oh yeah okay i'm not gonna
buy a whole new pc
but buying a new graphics card is maybe
something i would get
onto because then at least that graphics
card i can
bring over when i move countries again
that is something you can talk me into i
guess but then i need someone to put it
into my pc because i don't know
anything about that
we can talk about that cpu
okay what was it again someone said the
cpu
is good but the gpu is bad better
wait no cpu is
what i'm trying to say is that
the pc that i used until last week
has either better cpu or better gpu than
the pc that i use today
and that is why it has issues or
something i don't know
it's which one was that
what today's pc was was the cpu
bad or the gpu bad and what is that
anyway
today's was c gp today's problem was the
cpu
maybe the ram i guess okay okay okay but
the pc that i used until until last
this last week has good cpu
and good ram what's the gpu
i'll diffuse the graphics ah
[Applause]
that is interesting so i guess
i guess so if anything i would maybe
look into the into a graphics card
because i guess i can just use it on my
other pc when in five months again
people were a bit confused about all the
different pcs that i keep on mentioning
let me explain to you one last time
because people just keep on
like i see it all all over on reddit
twitter
and everywhere when people talk about my
pc
issues okay right now i'm using
pc of my manager sound which i'm really
really grateful for because
even though there might have been some
freezing it was a really good solution
for last minute solution for the collab
yesterday
so thank you that however i will not use
anymore i think
tomorrow we're gonna pick up the pc
that is a rental pc that i've been using
for the past month uh
a that is in the house
which i moved into this weekend
and then there's another pc that is my
main
pc and that is my gaming pc which i love
and
it's precious and it's beautiful but
this one
i did not bring to the current place
where i'm at right now
because i was so scared it will it will
like fall apart and whatever
because you know flying isn't the safest
thing for pcs and even if i would
pack it into thousand kilograms of
bubble wrap i wouldn't have trusted
myself to do it properly
because pcs break easily i didn't want
to didn't want to risk it so that pc
is somewhere else and i will get back to
that pc
that's the first fruit pc actually
that's the first pc
if you would say i think think of it
that way that
i will reach that pc again in five
months and i can't wait because it's
beautiful i love that pc
so there's three pcs but the the pc i
use today
is already out of the picture again i'm
using it right now for this stream
but i think tomorrow we're gonna just
pick up
this the second pc the rental pc
and then my house because it was good
enough for streaming so we're gonna pick
that up and then
everything will be back to normal i'll
be streaming minecraft or won't fall
guys or
file them whatever we'll have fun buy
another pc
a fourth pc you want another fourth pc
in the picture
um
huh
please please don't make me
don't make me go crazy where the hell
did that go
where did it go what
it is not in germany
you guys are being fooled
you guys are big food
but i shall let you be fooled
because i enjoy it
you know nothing jon snow
[Laughter]
i will not say a word
keep on thinking what you think you
think ah what do you think you know
there's a pc building simulator
isn't that basically like a surgeon
simulator where you just like
do it very wrong very wrong and learn
nothing about how to operate on a human
body i don't think i'll learn anything
from that
anyway red sock thank you so much
is that like the newest the bestest
graphics card in the market right now or
why why do i keep on hearing
about that graphics card you make me
want to play minecraft even with your
lava jumping and lag lol also you say
iron like
oh yeah i did read that in the
livestream as well but
well because that is the right way to
say it do you think
it is a coincidence that a dragon
and a phoenix both pronounce it as iron
and we are mythical creatures who have
been
around for millions of years
and how long are you guys alive huh
think about it
thank you so much for your support it
will definitely
once it arrives in the kfp bank
it will be used very wisely david james
thank you
kkk ninja movie thank you brandon wilson
mark mark sununu kfp employee number
nine
thank you soon a quick kick
before going to work also don't be
scared of the never i just want to give
you a warm welcome
it just wants to give you i i wasn't
scared
i wasn't really scared scared of the
never i've seen i've seen enough streams
of
safe journeys to the never
that eventually ended up in death but up
until then it was safe
[Music]
yeah i told you guys i can rap i was
just trying to speak japanese
i told you guys looking rap see this is
when i just speak
what do you think how good it will be if
i rap
if you thought that was rap then see how
it goes with my rap for real
actually guys guys guys
are you listening
okay don't tell anyone don't tell anyone
never mind i will not tell you yet
i'll not tell you i wanted to tell you
something but i first gotta clear it
with my wife
and then i'll tell you
you know i should be angry if i just say
stuff that she doesn't want me to say
i don't want to make my wife angry
i'll i'll deliver you the information
once i have received permission thank
you
excellent
[Music]
oh yeah i never make a map huh i never
made a map before it maybe eventually
i'll make a map
thank you
brah moment thank you swaggatron 64. and
x armor thank you
hello of course i have i love spatzles
i even made some myself before
was a really disgusting looking but it
was delicious
sapphire kitten thank you and how to get
i'm driving home from the airport oh
if you get to the never before i get
home i'll give you my nutella stash
i want the nutella stash though i'm
running out of nutella
i did never make it to the never
can i have one of your nutella stash
like one one glass at least
i'm asking you again for
a nutella
please steve thank you
brandon james thank you it ain't much
but you deserve this
it's it's march it's much thank you so
much love your content keep up the
sorry the chat made me laugh
[Laughter]
i love your content keep up the amazing
work i won't get
to see your streams for a while but when
i come back i'll donate
10 times the amount
good luck on your career and
relationship did you already go oh my
god
don't why would you do that
thank you brandon james thank you
[Music]
and yes thank you for wishing me luck
with my uh
relationship with miss morty
i will need the luck
thank you a freaking skeleton
on a cat thank you and seraph thank you
derp muffin thank
to my favorite haul i can't speak
anymore hello ian member thank you
also thank you for using some german in
your streams even though it seems you
don't like to as it makes me feel like
not all my high school was wasted
yeah i've um i've heard
sometimes that some people learned
german in school
very interesting i think
many of them were american
it was really surprising to me that you
guys learned german in school sometimes
very interesting yeah in europe it makes
a bit more sense
but not as a second language obviously
in all of europe the
second language you learn in school is
english
everyone who is trying to study german
good luck
i'm planning german teaching lessons
for my memberships but first of all
german is very difficult apparently i
cannot really judge but apparently it's
very difficult for people who are
learning it
so er good luck
and second of all i'm not i'll not be
teaching you seriously anyway
video
well what was i gonna say
oh [\h__\h] that says everything me
forgetting what i was trying to
say in five seconds says everything
never mind i'll shut up
good luck refusing my streams as the
german
lesson input
thank you
[Music]
i forgot the german word for suspicious
but german is my first language
what the hell
fantastic fantastic
duncan gabriel chronos thank you
algebra on your nelson kitchen
do you love 67 thank you thank you
the again goose game and any local
multiplayer
any local multiplayer game you can use
steam remote to play
steam remote play oh yeah i never heard
of that before until today is a
minecraft stream
but i gotta check it out steam remote
plate
not a hotdog
thank you for that information very
precious information
thank you and jacqueline duncan evie
gamer
thank you
don't worry about it in a couple months
this kind of stuff will be something to
laugh about and reminisce
i think i spelled that correctly will it
will it will it though
will it i hope it will
imagine
but even still i'm not anticipating this
[\h__\h] crap sorry
sorry
are you proud of me swearing i learned
many english words i can use them very
well are you proud of me
i know words
thank you thank you thank you
i should just be saying it in german
this is i say how can bulk of this
yeah i can't even think of many swear
words in german
like there's like many swear words in
german that
i just don't want to say especially not
on stream
but any any swear words that are
okay to say on stream there's not so
many i can only think of
scheissis
yeah everything else just seems so wrong
to me
to me damn is not a swear word sometimes
when i say goddammit you guys are like
don't swear but i'm like this that's not
swearing
what is swearing about that that's not
hey that's a master
oh he's not swearing
okay so here is the the divided opinion
some say it is
i'm saying it's not
ah well
anyway i shall
i shall i shall um
think up some more swear it's in german
and then teach them to you
most important most important thing to
know swearing words
thank you love67
[Music]
i can't say that word
i feel bad about saying you know in
english i feel fine saying the effort
but in german i never say that
actually okay maybe i do actually i
guess i do
never mind i say it a lot in german but
uh
i don't want to say it on stream i feel
so see i don't i don't feel bad about
swearing in english but i feel very bad
about swearing in german
rabbit mod 87
let's just saw the other superchat rome
wasn't built in the day
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
and chiara's full potential
was also not built in one day i wish it
was built in one day but
it's not it's not
we are still building on it
logan anderson hello nice duncan don't
get sad get
glad glad force flex trash what bags to
put all those
what what
glad force flex trash bat what
glad force flex trash
bags to put all those negative feelings
in
to what what
is the conversion i don't understand
what the hell i'm reading
yeah is that even a sentence what
you have nothing to worry about with
literally watching blank screen to hear
your voice thank you that's why i love
you guys
maggie [\h__\h] thank you shin war gamer
dan kishan
bronx 819
thank you please don't get upset our
phoenix is supposed to wear smile
exactly i will try
thank you the rabbit hole thank you
thank you
some guys
and thank you and hi burp diamonds only
spawn at
or below that 16 16
that's a lie builder click access shaft
and then a
two to main tunnel and
yeah i was trying i think i was trying
something what you're trying to say
steve hold on vegan
youtube would prefer you to swear in any
language other than english yeah that's
it
isn't that youtube um
how do you say does it only really
detect english swearing because like the
japanese
senpai is not alive they swear a lot in
but doesn't seem to be a problem
yeah it's only detecting english that's
discrimination
detect it all or detect nothing
swearing discrimination
righteous
[Music]
are you having a rough stream this takes
time to figure out and we're all
happy to be here to support you always
thank you never cry baby
oh hey there guy with the sick doggo
from earlier streams she got the surgery
and is recovering well
ah happy
good doggo please send photo on twitter
please please send a photo on twitter
to show me happy doggo face
i want to see happy dogo face
[Music]
reaction to minecraft 117 up you mean
the stuff that all
it came out when was it was yesterday
because i saw that today on twitter yeah
i just started out with minecraft but
there's like all
so many new things coming now is it
already in the game now
oh next crack like some of those things
looked really nice
only you heard that
what 2021 what i thought it would be
like here and now
summer summer
how dare you tease me with that now
what i'd have preferred to not be teased
at all
gosh i don't understand when when
companies announce games for like two
years later like what
i don't need that information two years
before whatever i'm gonna do
i can't even mark my calendar because
you only give me
such a rough date of two years later
what the hell am i supposed to do with
that huh
god damn
although i was quite happy about seeing
breath of the wild
2 being announced but like
so so god damn early what am i supposed
to do with that information
so god damn really
ah you don't know
someone in the chat didn't know
how did you miss that if you're if
you're a fan of breath of the wild
how did you miss that there's like a
second one coming
kiana teaches japanese i'll be waiting
oh
let me her teach you
should have made this up
let me copy
it where is it
i there you go
here okay there you go
those are
important nihongo
you read as chimimoya
[Music]
now this we will use in everyday life of
course
it's a a word used
very often
you can flex with it
go to your friends and be like boy
look at this this is the japanese that i
know
you could you
foreign
[Music]
you know how you know there's like a
thing where
um you know japanese people are like
really really really really polite right
so when you when you're like speaking to
a japanese person
and you're like
so all of my friends complain about
being told this again and again and
again and now there's me
who speaks like japanese like like this
you know like a rap god
perfect japanese and people japanese
people they don't even react to my
japanese anymore
then
there's like often like um
people are like but japanese people are
like
they think i'm a like half japanese and
then i got
like raised in japan or whatever
no sorry like i i want to be nihongo
joseph
tell me my nihongo is
foreign
did she change her mic can someone tease
please tell me
i changed it yes a while ago welcome
back to the stream
where were you hiding
these past days or weeks
it's been like at least a week or not a
week now right
i think i don't wanna do it
[Music]
in the closet oh yeah just like me huh
just like me
no no
and where away me me
and also thank you to all the members
who joined by the way
thank you welcome to kfp
i should be like every time someone
joins the membership
819 bronx
my boy
stop stop investing so many stocks into
kfp
it's not good for your wallet please
take care rabbit mod 87 thank you thank
you as well
for the big investment but please take
care
of your wallet
what are you talking about i was
thoroughly entertained despite the pc
issues
you could ever have you could have a
crude ms paint drying up yourself on
screen with you just talking i would
still watch it
i love you i love you that's such a
that's such a
what's kokuhaku in english again
[Music]
confession oh yeah it's like a love
confession to me
it's like saying i would love you even
if you gained
100 kilos
thank you then i shall proceed
to turn into an ms painting
how dare you allorette martin thank you
knight three six zero three thank you an
airborne cat thank you
here you have some amazingly bad luck
yay
it's amazing how you can keep as calm as
you do i'm really trying to stay calm on
stream you know
i'm really trying ah you should
understand we're here for your gameplay
or not but love your child keep strong
and it will work out thank you so much
thank you guys
there's nothing wrong with what you are
doing it happens and we deal with it
as fans love you and your content we
would watch anything with you
guys i love you i love you i love you
i love you you know what uh actually
like
i guess you you guys probably know how
it is like when when you feel bad about
yourself and someone
says it's it's all okay don't worry
like obviously those words don't often
don't do much right
well when you guys told all told me that
it's like it's technical it's just
issues and
it's not my my fault that really
really helped me because yeah
i just uh i'm happy that you guys
at least you guys acknowledge that i'm
trying everything i can
and that is in my power please
i love you
ah you guys are the bestest you guys are
the bestest
and one day you guys will be such
gorgeous chicken nuggets oh the best
chicken nuggets i have ever raised in my
whole life and i'll eat you
i'll eat every one of you and i'll i'll
be
so happy and i'll say gochisousa made
looking forward to that day i hope you
read the
the small written things on the contract
when joining the membership
it said you can never leave this
membership
you will be raised as a food stock
and we will never let you go
trying to not sing the recall song right
now
trying to control myself
an egg becomes a chicken nugget
this is how it goes
you cannot cancel you cannot
escape
chicken nuggets
chicken buckets oh yeah
well i'll first make a lot out of you
this one is not enough the drumstick is
not enough you have to fill up a whole
bucket and then i'll eat you
so you everyone who's in the membership
now has exactly
two years until it's over
okay let's stop it here
[Laughter]
how can you be into that [\h__\h]
at least eat me with seiso sauce okie
dokie
i was planning on that i eat all my
nuggets with taser sauce
[Music]
i don't want to read out these messages
because they make me
get emotional but thank you
chronos
master 195
oh yeah i really was planning the whole
day on getting ice cream
to end this day i definitely need some
ice cream at the end of the day
definitely oh yes gotta get some hugging
that's
and girl duncan
oh i'm sorry that your temp computer is
giving you trouble i get frustrated
seeing you get upset because your tech
isn't cooperating but please
remember we all you you love you
so much and we are here for you no
matter what happens
thank you i'm so glad to have you guys
one day i'll hug everyone and then eat
everyone
excelled
rex fort b thank you master 117
streams go smoothly i hope so too no
matter what happens it's always nice
watching your streams thank you
tentacle time eternal thank you
and do you love 67 thank you sundance
so i can't stay up late but after what
happened in your last room i filmed my
previous super chat before you started
can look means i don't even know which
one
thank you though don't worry about it
it's all right i have a bird brain
anyway i already forget what everyone
said three seconds
i forget what i said three seconds ago
alex crowd
this is my last donation so i'll make
this quick yeah i can't tell what you're
feeling right now but if you're sad just
know
we really care about you so please don't
cry yes thank you don't worry don't
worry
don't worry
so i will
now refresh thank you everyone for
joining membership
i will refresh the superjet
and i think
[Music]
i can't english
everything coming
after coming
in now will not be read
what yeah whatever
okay oh it's too big
okay got it guys i give you uh
i give you one minute everything after
one minute will not be read
so i'm since i'm the refreshing and i
don't want to do this
forever because fubuki senpai is having
birthday stream
in 15 minutes
foreign five six
seven eight oh god okay guys you're
getting dizzy
one
i'm getting dizzy
one two three
five five six
seven eight nine
ten ah eleven yeah 12
what 13 14 15
uh 16 17 18
19 20.
[Laughter]
making herself pass out on her own
okay oh my god oh my god okay stop it
now
guys it's over
you guys done are you guys done
thank you very much i shall refresh
now caution
bronx was the last one congratulations
[Music]
but also thank you itself who said
selfies
okay there we go
where did we start oh god with all that
i forgot why we stopped
[Music]
wait i know
is that it is that where i stopped
oh maybe somewhere around oh yeah oh
maybe here
oh my god well you can donate i'll just
not read it
i will not read it too much thank you
okay i think i hope i did not skip
anyone now but let's continue
nagel thank you
alberto lucia vera hang
here's a daily dose of how much you care
free employees love you and will
follow you for the worst of technical
difficulties to your happiest day aka
getting married with kelly
thank you shane
everything is new and we're here to grow
with you for it all for all the hard
work you put in
piano we are just an egg now but i'm
sure that in time we will hatch into a
magnificent bird
yes i'm sure you will all hatch into
magnificent food
thomas thank you captain please thank
you
for
[Music]
i have no real use for money anymore so
consider
why do you not have any real use for
money anymore what happened in your life
can i be in that position thank you
sharon thank you
monkey hand sanitizing colors
[Music]
when i say i wanna ask
tell me why ain't
nothing but a heart ache
tell me why ain't nothing
[Music]
i can't sing that uh
is better though another good username
360.
leave
you may face a lot of text difficulties
but that won't stop us from watching
your streams thank you
your content is fun to watch don't ever
downgrade yourself again it makes me sad
we aggies love you thank you
thank you thank you vienna
kw thank you
this melancholies sound cringe but
whatever no matter what issues
difficulties you may face
your lawyers employ you your loyal
employees and ex will always be here to
support you for your information you're
my favorite in hawaiian
thank you thank you sweet egg
thank you employee thank you investor
thank you
so far i got the goose game after you
mentioned it it's really fun oh
looking forward to your collab with
subaru my cat ignored me almost the
entire week i was at home and only hung
out when i had to pick
love but my my own cats don't ignore
me my own cats love me thank you
i'm registered thank you and you've been
so fun and amazing even with all the
unlucky tech issues thank you you smile
and love cheering me up and i'm happy to
hear
we help you help cheer you up when
you're upset really thank you
ex-dragon id dan kishan registerius dan
kishan
the other ones i don't really know thank
you though thank you
ghost two hundred extinction cute anime
girls are the best thanks
thank you so fat thank you
for
is
got my paycheck and i forgot that i had
to pay to be a kfp employee yes you have
i haven't seen the technical issues but
i hope you're getting better we all love
your attention keep shining with your
presence your beautiful phoenix
thank you soon thank you so much
michael rivera thank you shane finger
puppet thank you shane patrick chen
duncan
vega my friend love and thank you where
is your original computer mars
i know you probably can't say exactly
what geographically
but why would it be so far away because
of
the place where i'm in right now i am
here for a temporary time
and nicolas thank you i was heartbroken
in your live stream no i don't want to
break your heart i want to
make your heart go
your girls have been under a lot of
stress in these very complicated times
and as a physician
it worries me as a physician what does a
physician do again
super support each other and look for
help in need by the way gooda seems
quite stressed too did you
think so by watching her stream
but yeah i think all of us have our
our how do you say that
we all have something to carry i don't
know
so yeah but the thing that really
keeps us going i know everyone says that
and it's
cringy but it is you ha ha
burdensome i guess so yeah gouda lost
her bread like what do you do about
it when you lose your bread life is over
i totally feel it because like i love
bread
when i saw it i really felt for good out
because like that's like
really hard on you losing your bread
oof
um
[Music]
when you cannot move your body enough to
show what you want to
do i was trying to show you the stonks
the thing the arrow the stones arrow
how it goes like up
[Music]
we've only known you for a little while
but you've already made your lives
brighter
thank you for all your hard work and for
spending time with us thank you for
spending your precious time with me as
well
thank you pink carnage thank you
oh thank you i really appreciate it
don't worry about it like any any amount
is definitely something
bradley thank you thank you i told a
friend that donate to the first eon
member to do a minecraft stream
this is the first chance i've gotten to
catch one of your streams live love you
guys thank you
[Music]
red super chat for being the first one
in en to play minecraft oh wow
i deserved it oh no fubukki's starting
in two minutes yeah let's go
chris thank you and jonathan koslowski
otp thank you
[Music]
i cannot just sweep over at 250 super
chats
red super chat like that thank you
okay guys thank you everyone for
watching
the super chat stream thank you for
hanging out with me hope you enjoyed
some of the in-between stories that we
had
i love you all and see you soon
[Music]
we say auf wiedersehen
i'm gonna get some ice cream now ice
cream
[Music]
um
do
[Music]
oh double music
is
[Music]
oh my god