one two
[Music]
3 light up lights let's begin with start
stage ride and Sh
on ready to Ste the show we're
jumping's go up secure the bambo keep
on in
hand it's our greatest moment yet a
spectacle we'll never forget
show we go on and on tell them that
we're here to stay and spread the news
from Tokyo
toway
scaming together weing
all so bright now we're feeling all
right the day we met we been
going and we keep moving right
along so keep on
yeah you bet ain't nothing going to stop
us for a
perfecty no matter where we go it's to
be don't you know we're going to feel so
live when it's so fun ready to put on
another show
[Music]
there's a time to celebrate the mood is
fun and we're feeling
[Applause]
great from the Raptors to the out they
just laugh and I make
it we'll slay them like we always do
make no BNS of
better when I'm with you it's divine
it's
Exquisite I'm Lander in water we've
never been hotter feel so BL we're
friends for
[Music]
all
Jo the work our and going to keep you in
my heart we
stay together
Miss
[Music]
for anony is s turning like a merry
around on dream another dream with me
now it's time to change the
key light the blood lights keep on L
night it's dark night and we've got a h
get in line beside me now it's almost
time to take another
bath
track mus
go
you the go and hand show w
[Applause]
[Music]