Good morning, good morning, you can say it again today too.
and
More layered colors
find your dream
Stay with me
Let's go deep into the future
good neighbor
Empire
Horaheko, who always looked forward and sang
I'm playing it, but it's okay. I'm sure it's for you.
You can do it
Right?
[music]
Kindness that I want to share
Just like that
listen
I'll meet you here
there
There's probably no point
[music]
Even if I stumble
Even if I get hurt, I'll come back from here
Let's get started
Even if it's Monday or small
Let's sing
Teru
what daily life
of
[music]
still hope
I want to believe 10 times 100 times correct
[music]
Unraveling
into words
Not when
[music]
In Seoul
Naru song and a strong smile
[music]
[applause]
to today
So
[music]
Hello everyone
Dododo tonight
I was able to eat infinite green peppers today too.
Square rolls are no good
Is the sound okay?
Can you hear me tonight?
More and more
Great
Infinite green peppers are delicious! Infinite green peppers are delicious!
You can eat it.
That conte is with sea chicken.
Let's do this with the remaining green peppers. Mugen again.
I just ate today's green peppers.
I was eating until the very last minute.
Irritation
I'm always on time though
Always 50 minutes
I thought it would be okay until about 50 minutes.
I'm eating till the last minute, so there's only 5 left.
I wish I could stop eating food so quickly.
Hatame is eating till the last minute.
I won't be able to go home because the characters are too great.
Sorry
It's always like that for about 50 minutes.
Are you okay? It's not okay, but is it okay?
I ate my rice cold for about 50 minutes.
Becauseit is
Because I'm eating while lazing around.
I'm usually about 3 minutes late.
That's right
[music]
Today I finally visited this sneaker house.
I'm thinking of making one.
It's such a waste of time
A bit of a sneaker egg
Will all but one hatch?
I'm not sure whether to do it or not.
[music]
welcome
When you increase the number of eggs with a sniffer, use eggs.
I was born to become
What can I say?
moreeggs
Something
Butlers and stuff.
There are cows and things like that.
It comes out the way it was born
It grows with eggs.
hatch everything
The egg will be born, okay?
This is a wasteful disease at all.
It took a lot of effort so I thought I'd release it.
Okay, three.
I want to hatch it
Okay
Let's go, let's get ready
I think it's okay
Materials are ready
It comes out as an item.
The turtleis
camera egg
Isn't it?
I wonder what it's like
There are so many things I don't understand
There are also three moss blocks. Is it okay?
Turtles are items that have eggs.
I won't come out though
It will be installed
Installed type
egg-mounted type
I see.
So sneakers are an item type.
Why don't you go to the Ajman shop before that?
What is Ajman Shop?
In case a customer came, I'd like to go there just in case.
It's a crazy night, but I guess everyone isn't sleeping.
It's okay
Let's go
What the heck is going on man?
what starts
Redness is the Nether, right? God and Lunathan.
Masune
It's Shion-senpai.
Yay, you did this!
Visit to Ajman Shop
thank you
My head is
I see, it feels like Anpanman here.
I got Smoo-chan's head here.
A new face from
[music]
I guess that's why I don't need this face anymore.
Maybe it was replaced?
Shall we add a museum?
Shall we do that?
replaced
I did it
It's selling really well though
stock
Even though I added it, it's still selling really well
state of affairs
I have to make it again, see this and my sister too.
What a blessing they gave me!
Seriously, let's decorate this a little bit.
neck
Decorate your neck
Okay OK
I have 4 that made D popular and made me laugh.
Thank you for giving it to me
Then this
neck
The hand that adorns my neck
Ah, I need that.
With a signboard
We need a sign and a picture frame.
beheading
beheaded
Hanchama reminds me of typing
I took it to Shion-senpai's house.
and that
Decorate it
Is it possible to decorate without having science skills?
I don't think he's a scary person though.
I'll take it with me once again
Chicken trouble
Take it according to the temperature or shoot it at will
I did it but I'm happy
I'm so happy
I feel like he was a shining person.
Great job
I think it was white birch.
I'll decorate this neck
belongs to everyone
[music]
Where should I display it?
It has increased.If you look at it like this, it has increased.
worry
Hey, I guess it's this way.
No, what should I do here?
Hmm
Huh?
It was the right kettle.
Is this a bit like that?
Something
With a signboard
Next to the actor Next to the after
here
Should I move next door to the lively place? Should I leave it blank?
Kajaa
It would be possible to create a donation room.
A little more
Let's decorate it
Maybe together now
Sadako-san, look at me, Sadako-san.
What is it?
What about Sadako?
Then this one too
It's a horror thing to decorate your neck.
Tokuka
A bit like Sazae-san
It's finished
sandals DX
What is Sadacon TX?
It feels like Matsuko Deluxe
This is how it is
added fish
Sadako-san Now, this week's Sadako-san.
begins
donated items
The taste begins
Existing products, what should I use?
SSM
That
parent
purpleshion
S
I wonder if it's a bit like M and SM.
I guess that's what you mean, it feels kind of hard
I do
What should I do?
It's a neck, okay?
Well then, SM
heart
Might be annoying to dirty people
But
For beautiful people
nothing is conveyed
Here is the purity of your heart
I'll measure it
It would be nice if you were
What should I do?
There's only one that's dirty
[music]
Mr.
Hmm, I can go home now. This is amazing.
You can change it without destroying it.
amazing
convenience
Messed up
[music]
convenience
Until before
I broke it though.
So that everything can be rewritten without destroying it
This is a nice update
Wow amazing
Nice update I've been waiting for this
Because it was a hassle
nice
Yes, it can't be fixed without using honeycomb.
It is also possible to cheat by easily rewriting the losing record.
Masua
I feel like I was doing something
a
Nico-chan at the corner-wrapped rock-paper-scissors sign
It was locked
It's a failure
[music]
I haven't seen that yet
It's unreachable
That's fine for now
I've got a sticky note. I'll go take a look.
What does it say?
I've noticed, I've noticed, I've noticed
I finally realized it
I have no choice but to go see it.
It's time to go to battle
let's go
Oishoato here too
I deleted it for a while
here
I also cleaned up this place a little bit.
I was a little worried after preparing it.
Even though I thought about it, I'm still worried about this.
a little bit
Must be clean
I also removed this
While watching Nishikawa's big brother's rock festival
[music]
It was amazing.
I also adjusted the position a little here.
It was amazing to go through the night
It became like a medley of songs, song after song.
Amazing!
Let's go for a while, rock, paper, scissors
But somehow
Looks like Nishikawa's older brother will be interviewed.
I watched the video too.
I'm going to sleep before the performance
Here?
Enit
I bought it again for exclusive use.Next time too.
I feel like I lost the canned food again.
However,
from now
You did it
I'm doing this. I'm doing this.
here later
Should I put up a sign saying "Turn right"?
And it's actually locked.
I can't dry it out again
I'm talking a lot
This is painted with honeycomb
[music]
Faster
There is pink
Oh my god, pink dye too.
Is it still stuck?
Is the duck still stuck?
I'm so happy
I get along well with Maru-chan.
Zama-chan please
Asia Asia Asia
get caught get caught
A mysterious cobblestone that fits in. This signboard is also a bit
I might have to replenish it.
Should I bring a sign? Going back and forth
Have 1,000 more ryo
Bring me the honeycomb
Hero caught in the middle
A sandwich shop
I'll get caught
I'll go get some
Yo
I'll get caught
Right, so that's the way you sleep in bedding.
Interview with None Bedding
Is that also a case? A video has been uploaded.
I'm going to play with the candy wasp
That's why singers are the ones who sleep before the performance.
It's taboo for me, but I have to sleep.
As expected, it doesn't last long.
After rehearsing
He said he was going to sleep.
So I woke up about an hour before the actual performance.
in
wake up
They're going to do a live show
That's amazing
The story of my older brother
Let's go back to my brother's story for a moment.
That's amazing
Pump up your body too
How many people are there? Do we need that many?
Na
Hoi hoi
Hey
I want to make them all
No, if it doesn't work, the fluff will disappear when I go to sleep.
I won't go back unless I sing a lot
The pink line is pink dye
There aren't many
Let's increase
It's a slow starter to go out there.
I hear a voice when I wake up
Iato Honeycomb Honeycomb Honeycomb Honeycomb
Ah, cherry blossoms are fine, okay?
honeycomb
Kanikamu Yoshi
OK, let's go
-
Is your voice cute when you wake up?
I don't like it when I hear about it later.
Too sloppy
What will happen?
It's not rough, so it's okay.
Maybe it's not the rough type
Should I add a little more?
I'm sure I'll lose, so I'll put in more.
Gahaha
Let's include this one too.
A longtime ago
So here it is
You're doing it
right
I'm doing it
It's not a good lie
Watamiko seafood
It's prevented
fraud on fraud machine
It's unfair
Also
It's a loss
Right?
You're here again. It sounds like a song.
That's great, that's strange. We lost again.
But Watome is less in love
You promised not to say that.
Although it's true that I've lost recently.
I won at Gomoku
Gomoku is easy
If it shines too much, it's weird, but this is bright.
must
Okay
Okay, okay, okay
It's perfect
Even if I buy a shrine maiden a gomoku
Like that
People say that even if you win, it won't last forever.
Not shown
I haven't been told anything
They say things like that won't lead to victory.
Not shown
[music]
It was said that it was like a bye.
It seems
I'm sad
I wonder if the fur will settle down in Das?
He's the worst of the four heavenly kings
in a sense
Strongest in a sense
I would like to make it here today.
Once this
Put it
[music]
Okay
No, but this is it
Ah, I wonder if I can put it there, but I have a minus one.
See you tomorrow, with Sora-chan.
I'll do whatever I want to play
Summer wear
Personally
darts
I'd like to try a little with you.
Hey, it's strong after all.
Sora-chan is good at darts.
I want to try it
But
Hey
I feel like that though
I want to try it.
Sora's darts are awesome
I feel like my score was amazing.
I guess he's doing something really good.
Not just games
I only do watami in games.
Karana
Well, I have to go to almost 20 triples.
That's the level
yes
Some real darts
It looks like he's doing it, so it seems like it's true.
Battle at the top
Well, I'm going for 800 points or something.
sassola
I'm already getting worried
Is it okay?
I got a hole
There's a hole in it, I want to take it out
What will happen if I take it?
I want to take that, but please give me some white birch.
It wasn't
I want to go through with it, but I don't know what will happen.
Tara
Ah, if I had eaten the Gum Gum fruit.
I can be though
Ma
have it later
Today's dress
Good evening
welcome
Yes, if there was a Gomu Gomu no Mi
Nahoihoihoi, I'm addicted to it
While eating pasta in the morning
Because it was a bit like One Piece Amapura
difference
I thought I'd see it
While eating and watching One Piece,
Think about the message you draw with your sign
But
The feeling of sunrise and sunrise is amazing.
It's so refreshing, like it's a Sunday morning.
When I see a dress that makes me feel good
strange feeling
Maybe
The song is
I wonder what that ending is.
Right?
I just chose it
The ending is
What is Icchan's first ending?
I thought it was really nice
What the heck is Wheeler opening?
That's right, but it's Winner.
I saw the opening, but it was already 3 o'clock.
Zoro or Usopp
Gene is in it, right? The opening touches my heart.
small
Since then, someone has asked me to follow the map.
If I was there
Tatatatatatatatatata
[music]
La la la la la la la la la la nice song
Is this enough?
nice
It's okay though
Oisho
It felt like a great Sunday morning.
But
it was thursday
It was the middle of Thursday
Alright, arrived
It was right in the middle
hopper and barrel
to minus 1
Because I have to put it
What should I do now that it's completely visible?
That's not a minus, it's Hopper.
The one that looks like a barrel is the previous version.
It's written in the guy, but it's a new line case.
So you don't need this?
I thought I couldn't do it, but from the floor.
It's okay
I see.
Just something has been updated
I thought you might have posted the previous one too.
I was wondering if I had to do it.
a
Fixed
Thank you. It's okay.
Yo
Thank you for your help
This is fine.
Then you don't need this
Let's look at it again.The sharp part is the head.
how much
Thank you for the correction
But this
Once that's over, it's time to play slots and stuff like that.
Medals and things like that.
I want to go to
That's what I think
Anything that says it will be republished from now on is fine.
I wonder if
Is this it?
That thing
roger that
Let's save this
Finally Lamb Vegas
Should I make it?
this
overwrite it
OK
Finally the casino
It's tough
Because it's Hiro
It's probably difficult
Okay
Close-up view So this is what it looks like.
Once
I wonder if I'll break it down
and
It smells like a big smell
Earn money
Let's earn money
Watame is a sigh and people leave too
Gahaha
It's going to rain money
rain of money
It's going to rain scary money
Management is here
Take this once
Take this too
123456789101112131415
beyond
[music]
12345678910111121315
beyond here
Then
OkOk, let's break this down for now
Please welcome
thank you
Good evening, please work hard today as well.
Today too
I will do my best
Should I take this?
Hoi hoi hoi hoi
Hey
Hoihoi By the way, recently my song
Thank you for being played so fast
Yes
My song is a little like that
The time will come
I'm grateful that you still listen to me thank you
There is
I'm happyand thankful
Amazing influence
Thank you so much
100,000 views in 1 week
How far have you been?
That's amazing
Thank you
thanks
No matter how many times I listen to it, it makes me cry
I'm glad it stung somehow.
Thank you everyone too
Not enough yet
In the never-ending rain, I still feel like it's not enough
thank you
Is it because of that cutout?
Hoi hoi
That seems possible too, thank you
I can't buy CDs with sweet songs anymore.
Is that so?
disk
It's fleeting though
Umm
[music]
If yes, there has always been
Yo
Download method
If
If it's digital, it's digital after all.
If it's digital, words can't come out.
Masu
But I was also talking to my voice training teacher.
However,
I was asked if I wanted to play a song like that, so I'm practicing now.
I just started it
What are the latest songs?
I wonder if it's true, no matter where I take the opportunity
It looks like it will be played on tiktok etc.
There are a lot of lively songs.
That's why I don't listen to that ballad too much.
I wonder if that will disappear in the future.
I guess there aren't that many
surely
Yeah, that's for sure
I haven't been singing many ballads lately.
don't listen
I don't see it.
Many of them are short and catchy.
I wonder what will happen music
Around the area
That's what we were talking about, but...
Tame-chan looks good as an idol
I know what you want to say.
yo-no
Probably this
Because it's a wakame habit.
I guess that's because it's a singing habit.
Untara area
Yes, that song has seaweed flakes in it.
from
I thought it would probably fit there.
It was really there
Oh Elijah
What is Aqua?
Something like that
34691011213
Welcome too
The sound of sheep's footsteps
Whata tree
I wonder if it's called Gion.The footsteps.
It is visualized
It's the sound of footsteps.
Well, I don't know, after all.
At first glance, why is everyone saying "Dodo"?
What is dodo?
It will happen, right?
What's going on tonight?
What is it?
That's why
When I debuted on Twitter
There's a lot of dodo dodo on Twitter.
running around
From there
Even the greetings became a bit messy.
It's like I'm about to start making tea.
What do you mean? Is it like Ajimaru?
What is dodo? Well, I can understand it.
Is it something like Dedede? On the other hand, what about Dedede?
On the other hand, what is the name of Dedede Loud Volume?
I'm curious
name
I remembered
Dododo is not a name though
What is Gegegege from Gegegege no Kitaro?
What is gegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegegege
Hey, it's an insect's cry, cash.
Is it scary?
I didn't know
Hey, that's right
A little bit of this
Let's do it in the opposite direction
Okay OK
I didn't know, I didn't even know
It's a bug
It was a cry
It seems like it was originally Kitaro of the Graveyard.
Not Genka
I wonder why I got so upset.
Because it's catchy
Because gegege is more catchy
I'm not being reckless.
Choki Kitaro is a serious story and the story is dark.
I guess so
I feel so cute right now
But
Kitaro
The author's nickname is GeGeGe
[music]
Ahhh
of
It's a gate
Hey
Because it grows
It's not a bug.
Handicraft store's
Shigeru
So it's Shigeru's Kitaro?
[music]
I see.
I learned it for the first time
Uncle can go out
I wonder what it is
There are quite a lot of them.
There are a lot of characters with 3 letters.
Na
What is Dedede's uncle?
Surprisingly there
Is it related to oden?
[music]
There's also La La La.
It's a mystery
ah
Lalala is also there
That's the name
It seems likethough
So, I wonder if Lerere is also a name?
He's an uncle.
It might be a lovey-dovey name.
gaga
be on one's mind
[music]
That's interesting
Rere's 0 points
Because it's a catchphrase
I wonder if it's the uncle of
[music]
wonder
3 I can't sleep
12123456
[music]
There are also Gagaga babies and Gagaga SPs.
Right?
There are also SPs
Pocky block is here
It's amazing how it keeps spreading
There may be quite a few if you look for it.
So this
1231234
Okay, okay
There are plenty if you look for it.
So
Rabbit to the other end
Are you talking about Peko-chan?
[music]
I won't collect the bottom part.
Well, if I'm making it now, I guess I can't collect it.
I wonder if this can't be recovered?
I wonder what it's like
I made it possible. It seems to be okay.
thanks
in 1
[music]
Mr. Almond Sada
You're doing it, Stroke.
I think they use Honda
almond
That'sa lie
Well, it's an almond after all.
almond almond
Leave the hopper
That I admitted it
almond almond
This is a happy lantern
It's like a ring name.
I wonder if it's called Edmont.
You'll get angry
Maiden-chan
You're licking it, aren't you?
Something
I was told the opposite when it came out
He's my senior.
You're underestimating Matome-chan
I remember saying something
Certainly during the 10,000 yen project.
I recently built a shed.
surely
in
put down the barrel
I didn't know that potato chips were also banned from Yamazaka Kyushu.
I really didn't know that.
There wasn't.
I just sent you some potato chips that I really love.
Yes, I was waiting for the money.
There is no such thing as
[music]
Which way is this barrel facing?
That's why I only recommended it.
Is this Taro this time?
This won't work unless I add a hopper or something.
Takana
This is not connected
I thought it was a good thing, but that's just how it is.
Try throwing a little bit here or there.
I guess I haven't been there yet.
This is because it is not connected
I guess this is it
OK OK, now we're heading towards the barrel OK
is
So
Bring me the soil that you plowed with a bear.
plowed with a hoe
Soil cultivated by earth bears
Soil ploughed by bears
What is that?
You can cultivate it after placing Zeon.
I'll bring a hoe
Or soil?
How many times do you say it?
soil plowed with a hoe
I was so surprised
That's what it is
The soil I tilled because I said it five times
what does it look like
I had a lot of things to do, so I decided to buy land first.
land
Is any kind of kuwakuwa okay?
Anything is OK, even wood
Warm
It's like I've ever planted carrots or something.
I wonder if it will turn out for you
There was
Soil in the field is OK
[music]
I get it
Mr. A Mr. A
Oisho
Then this
number 1234
1234 here this Wednesday
in
[music]
Is this okay?
kana
water first
It's true that I gave a lot to my dad.
surely
There was a lot of scary stuff, trash, trash, trash.
I told you
Oh, I'll dry out without water
Oh, water, water, water, water, water, water, water, I'll go back.
Without it
I guess I just have to cultivate it again.
water worms
love
This
One more time
This is fine
[music]
This feels good, I guess I should start plowing again.
The color changes, I'm awake, I'm coming
It's coming
Dad
The trip wasn't wasted, I threw away a lot.
But it's scary
I'm tired
It is permeating
Mysteriously, this ladder is said to penetrate.
It has a strange way of transmitting water.
It's permeating. Don't say things like that.
It's okay, isn't it?
It's a game, so I won't say such details.
Not
It's random
Why this?
Equal commentary is dead, dead, after this
If this ladder closes
All
hobbies pass
remove scales
Hoi hoi
It comes out
Let's leave it at that for now.
Dark Oak Stairs
dark oak stairs
It's fun to jump after plowing it.
He's a bad boy
Are you going back?
drink
Wow
this
in
You won't be fooled, right?
If you make it with that, wait a minute, flower pot pot
I feel like I haven't brought it. Oh, please bring it.
I don't think so
Should I use a piece of pressure point?
[music]
I need two
Let's always make it
If you want to spend a lot, take it
Dad's trip wasn't in vain either.
Oisho
bricks and pieces
I'm thankful that it's a sweat basket, but I haven't used one yet.
I didn't have it, so I just assembled it.
Ah, so this wasn't this?
Do you like this?
Now
3 people
This is what I want to do for 3 people.
Is one brick enough?
This is the third side
Become a figure
Len said, "Let's try one out."
picture
Let's go
a
Is this okay?
It's hot so I can go back
cute
Hey, sneakers.
It's cute. Let's make another one. This is it.
this
It's going to look like this
So cute
Perfect for sneaker homes
Oisho
[music]
What is this mushroom?
this
halo
Welcome back
Hello
I like it, there are a lot of Minecraft people
I'm so happy I'm nervous
Something
It's crowded
[music]
I'm getting excited
I like it, it's exciting today
[laughter]
It's exciting
This is sneakers
[music]
this
Something's wrong with me
What will happen to this?
Great
[music]
This one too
It would be a shame if there were two sides
Is this a waste?
I feel like it's a waste
Should I be stingy?
So just destroy it
picture
To break it
A sword?
Chin
I need one more Ade Brick.
brick brick
Let's be stingy
Then I'm missing one, what's with this hand?
limit
Because it is a valuable material
I'm gonna fix this I'm looking at that killing thing
I saw the clipping.
Something
Watame Talking Store
slow
A store where you can talk
I thought
That's what caught my attention
Is that a good thing? Well, let's get together.
He asked me to look at the cutout.
I'm kind of slow at speaking
I'm so sorry, should I bake this?
Yeah, I made a little change here too.
Here too
Something
Can you tell me if the ore burns faster?
I got it again in Minecraft
It's okay to take it slow
My speaking speed is completely different from everyone else.
That's what I thought
Change this, if you put it here
I can't walk
Is the viscosity different?
mosquito
Open and open
It's burning, it's burning
Isn't this a trace?
I like the way you talk
Okay then?
Warming means coming to be healed.
surely
Well, this
If you lay this side down
Is this okay? This is fine.
Is this okay?
Welcome to join us
Yes, I'd like to wait.
Is that ink?
I don't think my mind is very fast.
Because there isn't one
that's why
everytime
I'm speaking late
It's done!
-
everyone goes to sleep
Oh no no no loki loki
Okay, okay, okay.
dangerous dangerous
Hmm, no.
I was able to
OK
Abu Abu OK OK
When I talk to Asgar-chan, I talk fast.
hey
Certainly
It's true that you talk fast when talking about important things.
That's something
I was guessed
It's like that store.
I'm starting to get inspired
Yo
The interpreter's
frame is not long
That's right.
It's scary even for me
put water here
Where can I put this?
Is this not enough?
kana
Is this an infinite water source or all water sources?
OK
Then maybe you need more water.
water worms
Wet water water
Adanbon is not a crab for a moment.
Is it not enough to rent a rice field?
too
That's enough
Where should I go and who is here?
If you have two, you can create infinity.
I don't care where I go
open thomas
Oh, I just put it here, but here it is.
Click here and there to skip a line.
It might be better to take it once and then over here.
This way, this way
Take this
This way
of
Yeah yeah
This way
Wow, no waste
[music]
Unkocchi
I got it
It's done, it's done
I did it
[music]
Look, I'm sorry
Come to think of it, that's what I'm saying in that vein.
It might not be a good idea to say it this way.
I don't know
As expected, Watame may not be that good.
I'll write a short essay
It's okay
Not related at all, Tamagotchi
It has arrived
Tamagotchimi
yellow one
It arrived but I haven't opened it yet.
I have togrow it.
Tamagotchi has arrived
What will it be?
proceeded
I just bought it
Next
Is this ok for once?
Emiko-san turned into a graveyard again.
Tatsuha
Hmm, how far did you see it touch?
But that or touch
Mikochi's coincidences
La la la la la la
[music]
Suo passed away
Eh, that's it
That's sad
ah
How fleeting
Even Tamagotchi is a total loss.
Oh, you're going to die so soon?
Pikmin are also wiped out.
If it was wiped out, it would have ended immediately.
Pikmin are also wiped out
To all Ross passing away
The moment I went outside
It's finished
Waaralaralalala
this is
grass grass
Please bring it
everyone is giving me grass
I need grass
Pick up that grass
Bone meal is fine, I don't understand
Kan
So let's roll it up like this
Yoshi Cop Magon
Amebachibo welcome back
Welcome back to membership
Take this cup here.
Wow, it's more fluffy than I thought.
Mosser
Let's reap
[music]
Something like this is fine
mosquito
Washa Washa
Please bring me a dandelion button
Pom-pom
I haven't brought Poppy either.
Do you want to take a dandelion?
And Poppy-chan
Dandelion Dandelion
Good job
[music]
Pom pom pom
It should be here
of
Dandelion
Poppy-chan
theater
Wasn't there?
Shall I get Pea-chan?
good night
Go get me some
I'm now in a trap too
Hey
It's convenient. I'm glad I made it.
That's amazing
Not cherry blossoms
What was this?
Something is done
To Lamy's house
Lamy's house made by Chi
Rami is here
but
It's cute home
Something
There is also a bath with flowers and pandas.
be
One with extract
everyone is taking a bath
Akoko watching the cherry blossoms on the blue seat
Cherry blossom viewing
[music]
Let's also include an amazing kiss that also has a toilet.
Extract for
this
Something like that
It's from Lamy-chan
Another eye from upstream
Includes episode men soup stock
This is lamy water
Awesome
Contains watame extract
It's amazing, it's like it's actually there.
It looks amazing
Is there a glass or something like this?
Na
Ah, amazing
It's glass
[music]
That's a great idea
Awesome
I wrote it on the signboard so I put it in there.
The soup stock for the new soup is also included.
I did it
Can I write on the back?
kana
Secretly on the back
I'm sorry for putting this in my head.
Karana
Then behind Towachi
New
Seaweed Brush
Also eye soup
too
I entered without permission
oneself
The soup stock for the sake was also included.
drinking infusion
In stock again
Secret Immigration Bureau
Seaweed soup stock
Hidden taste in parentheses
I entered
Is this okay?
Contains seaweed soup flavor
There's something hidden behind this signboard again.
It's really the secret ingredient
There's a secret ingredient in it.
Cute cat signboard
It's cute, but there aren't many characters.
Because it's small
I see, this is the first time I wrote something of this size.
I'm sorry to bother you, but if you notice, I'll leave it behind.
Kana head
this is
That's bamboo
Ah, is it Japanese style or a bot?
Kaha
toilet
Japanese style perhaps
Japanese style?
It's crazy again
Fully visible from outside
This is completely visible
What's going on?
It certainly does look like this
It's completely visible
[music]
But I'm not good at Japanese style.
I'll hold back
It's fashionable.Sorry to bother you.
It's okay to disturb me
I came to get Poppy.
I don't really like the Japanese style, my feet are numb.
Someone who tightens their legs or sometimes takes them off
I'm there
I don't like that.
Sometimes something
Enande
There are times when I think, Poppy-chan.
It's not much, but it feels about half as good.
I'll enjoy having this
Someone has bad aim
I don't like this
Damn it just stinks
Don't say nice things
Say something nice
No [ __ ] aim
It's delicious though
No, but that's how it is. Amazing
Welcome to the flow of this story.
yeah
Welcome in this way.
Dandelion
I want grass here too, Dandelion.
Pootandelion
Dandelion Poppy-chan
Odandelion-chan
Danpo from Ponpopo-chan
Good morning, I'm eating Karinton right now.
year
Apparently there's a cat or something.
the owner
When I eat Karinto, I feel a little depressed.
Looks like there's a cute cat
What is that?
like me
There seems to be something
the owner ate it
This is it.
rabbit get
It seems like there is something
Saw it on video
Here is the grass
Also, I threw some sand towards that Karinto.
put on
Doing gestures etc.
Apparently there are children too
What the heck are you eating?
Finishing touch
Stop chasing
I'm sorry I don't have one
I guess it's all about looks and stuff.
Is this good?
I feel sorry for the people who are eating curry.
It's okay because it doesn't matter again
one two three
in
Seedling
many seedlings
Why is curry made from curry so delicious?
Wakame also eats a lot of curry.
It's delicious now
Should I take it?
Seedling
grass
No, it's painful, but you can't do it 23
Seedling
one two three
Grass grass
Let's touch the soil once
It might be spicy even in the middle, it's always medium spicy.
I put a little bit of sweetness into it.
I'm blending
23 in my house
dandelion
Dandelion 12
But the curry is delicious when mixed.
Sweet or something
I think it tastes better when blended.
[music]
Feels good
The zombies are moaning but it feels good
[music]
gear chrysanthemum
There are no cornflowers or white dandelions.
This is fine
It seems that the flavor of the house comes out depending on how you mix it.
Neato
I feel like the taste is completely different depending on the roux.
magic
There were no tulips, so that's how it was.
oh yeah
The secret ingredient is also different, isn't it?
What about the ingredients first?
Stir-fry
Some places, but none at home.
I've never fried it
Button-chan here
Set Button-chan
Ah, first of all.
I think there are more people who fry it.
We didn't fry it
What's going on with this door?
I don't even fry the onions.
Cooking option
It takes a while, but let it simmer for about an hour.
It comes out though
Kokana door
Ah door
20 doors 20
Wow, I see. That's why it's Dodo.
It's a door door
This is also a door
[music]
nice
You can also enter from here.
convenience
It's the collection point.
[music]
wonderful
I see
book
It hurts here, it hurts
You made it with me thinking about going to bed.
The pain from the door hurts too
It hurts, it hurts, it hurts
I want to make this table look nice too.
12345 Plate glass here and there
No.
This board is one
That
Is Tangs going to have a second stage?
That's right tomorrow
It seems like it seems like that.
Now the 1st and 2nd stage
I'm confused
I'm glad I didn't have to do it
I'm glad it stayed like this
Where to paste it here
Should I put up a skull?
But with painting, you can do that easily.
Okay
With this cat
dark
This is Dark Oak
The place that changed my life
Hey, can I just bury this?
That's right, the skull that started, there's no end to it
Maybe if
Suba cotton
Maybe I didn't want to play
That collaboration
I guess the second stage is good.
Second step is good
It seems like Skargo Sensor is having a hard time with this.
But
Place the Skulk Sensor on top of the hopper
Yes from Minecraft's prank
It was just a chance, but at that time
Even without Minecraft
That Subaru cabin
I was scheduled to appear on the show, but I never expected it to be like that.
What will happen?
Probably if it wasn't for Minecraft it would be normal
I'll probably bring someone with a voice like this.
I don't think I could have said that.
I think I was a little shy
With me
Piston, do you need a rail?
rail piston
Maybe the content was different too.
matchmaking skull
I don't seem to be able to tie it.
But this place
rail
piston
rail rail
rail
piston vist
[music]
piston
Lever or button for night
There are levers and buttons
That
Did you have a piston?
no
fixie
Shall we go to Mumbai?
I'll make it
I'll make something
search piston
piston
It would be better if it wasn't sticky.
normal piston
board cobblestone
iron
It's better if it's not Akashi ok
cobblestone
iron redstone
Board material
iron
board red
cobblestone
Board material
Itadai
cobblestone
Board material
iron
There was a red stone
where
iron
That
11 hours
Well, once
leave
I've used it a lot
In stock
won't come
dubious
[music]
Wow, I guess I'll have to go digging again.
I think there was one in
But I think I'll probably use it a lot from now on.
slots etc.
It's true that you can get the extra people.
surely
I'll be using circuits a lot from now on, so I think I'll be able to use them.
That's the feeling
Okay, I have a rail like this.
I have a piston
to the guild
I might even ask for frog legs.
If it's a god
Thank you for bringing so much
It looks like you have a lot.
I saw God's broadcast the other day.
That netherite
He was very good at digging
It was so fast. See you that early.
I can't do it
Dig it, put some TNT, look at it and hit it.
That quartz while approaching
Take traffic
The workmanship was amazing.
Netherite Hotel every time I look at it
That's amazing
It looks like he has a lot of red stones
Now
lightly
Place the sensor on top of the hopper
Is it a potion even if my sister is anti-anti?
It's okay because I have something.
I wasn't impressed at all.
put this
Run water over the sensor to silence it
silence
run water to silence
Should I put it here?
[music]
I'll draw it
I'll call it
I've never done it before.
Please put it on.
shut up
It will look like this
Hey
I can do this combination technique.
What is that slimy thing?
It's called a Scalco sensor.
But yeah
Looks like Sakko's sensor from the ancient city.
If you put a lot of things like board materials
It's okay if it's something like astronomical observation.
It was so shiny and beautiful
use the rail
Drop the trolley lightly onto the sensor
I guess it's Skulk Block.
It looks like it could be made like a planetarium.
I thought it was pretty bright, it was shining really well.
When I saw it
Planetarium where you can observe astronomical objects
I thought it would be a good idea to make one.
Now
Is this the rail here?
My heart is pounding
But if I made one for Planeta too, everyone would go Bingong.
Is it possible to clear astronomical observation?
This can be cleared
[music]
Isn't it this way?
It's used in Iron Fee's UFO.
Wouldn't it be astronomical observation if you looked at it?
What is this?
Drop a minecart with a hopper
I cleared it by watching Miko-chan and Sui-chan.
Because it's water-based
I see
put it on the rail
Must be pressed
Should be pressed
press it's the boss
of
[music]
Wait, wait, let's go home
How is this correct?
this
What is the correct answer? What is this Poko?
I don't feel like I'm stuck.
I see.
I thought of course
I want to draw sweet fried chicken.
In this way
thus
Is this okay?
This or that
Is it okay to just ride? Is this okay?
you
I got hooked
It fit nicely
Isn't it addictive?
good
That's what I was thinking
Wow, that's great. There's electricity.
This is fine.
Use the piston to place the note block.
Masu
[music]
It is OK even from the side
Place a note block next to it and use the piston to recommend it.
death
There was some kind of music game like that.
So-and-so should bring a musical note block.
block
Should be placed aside
So Bishibashi Camp is not a music game.
Bishibashi-chan's explanation
You can play with up to three carefully selected people.
There's a collection of mini games, right?
piston
3 people did it once with some stupidity.
Not this one
Ah, no.
1 time
Ah
you know what
That and that
Just leave it here once.
This is a workbench
this
leave
OK button
There is a chance that there is both.
this
I recommend it
Now press
[music]
I'm being pushed all the time
This is OK
Destroy it with this
[music]
I keep saying something over and over again.
If it's noisy, put some blocks on top.
Please leave this behind. I've been waiting for this.
I see
[music]
Should I put on some kind of headgear then?
Interesting mechanism don
Dun
in
This is Tenten
Note Block
in
I wonder if there are three more? Bring them.
3 more to go
Or this
[music]
green pepper
OK, I wonder if it's okay to put this somewhere.
I wonder if it's ok to say something like
[music]
Yes, some people have come now.
Masu here
and here
[music]
And bookshelf
Let's put some soil on it
[music]
It got really quiet
A new silence
visited
a little bit
lonely
yeah
I guess it's the plate glass after the pain.
a little bit
lonely
After you are silenced, can I have this too?
A little bit of service and a little bit of this too.
I want to change it, but I'm curious.
Don't worry about Maruishi, it wasn't here.
Not really
Should I take it?
Around there too
The people around me are probably like that too, I got them all.
Excuse me a little
That's right, it's different here too.
Can I buy it?
The plate glass on the side is
Let's change the wood
Broke
I'll clean it up this time.
Here or really or here too
Can I buy it here too?
reform reform
Who else should I bring with me?
Huh?
I wonder if you two are en?
It seems like he'll pick up some kind of nose seed or something.
Don't give it to me
I'll give it to you, but I won't give it to you.
Kurenai is dyed or not dyed.
My car if I can't get this or not
Ginger that cannot be removed
Something that those sneakers dug up
I wonder if they'll collect it?
There may or may not be someone to comfort you.
He's not there anymore
There's no one left to comfort me
This me who has been dyed in Kurenai
It's like a note block for that purpose.
Oh, it's just not enough
I won't hide if I don't have enough or if I don't have enough
Is it dyed or not dyed?
This me who has been dyed in Kurenai
There are stalactites over there
[music]
There's no one to wake me up anymore
ice
[music]
I'm using ice somehow
I get it
So
Letmeetouten Nether Porter
[music]
See you at the Nether Portal OK
Google on
hug
nice
I just want this coal
I found the new ending I want
Getforyouwant presents
present
of
chance
Where is the present?
Does that mean Hold On is waiting?
I see, I'll go get some stones.
I see
Watanabesu
Where is the present?
I think he got some elytra.
I think I got two.
Now I'm surprised
A surprised enderman?
It's a different pattern than usual
I thought there was an Enderman.
In that small gap
It's an enderman
Sumikkogurashi's Enderman
Please come today too
Because it's coming into the family
But keep it simple, Enderman.
I guess you're giving me a gift
here and there
gift of earth
I'm removing everything
It's okay if I put it here.
There's something here and there.
Yona
Endermen were also oversynced
Delivery
Exactly
Oki souvenir prices
I'M
in Front of the Nether Portal
What is "front" in the middle?
OK1think
BOOM wait OK
I want some of this
front or front is front
I thought it was in the middle
Infront is in front
It's educational
OK, but I'm starting to understand a little bit more
Some English conversation
Sometimes it's a little different though
Are you saying something like this somehow?
Something like that
Somehow
It's still not perfect though
This is dangerous, I'm going to jump here
VC in one minute
1 minute
That
One minute is 1 piece, 1,000 pieces is 1 piece
seconds
OK
VCOK
[music]
Sensitivity is 1 second
I see
It's educational
[music]
Study from people's conversations
Well, I wonder if it will reach here?
[music]
Oisho
What, what are you inviting me to?
Column Cif Billies 2
I know you're reading this.
Moreover,
Why did you find out?
Middle Box Vehicle
Why don't you find out and tell me to give you the coin?
What are you giving me?
Is it okay?
What are you doing?
I'm inviting you with my voice
Return
I'MIN JAPAN
VC
It's okay
I just want to go to the toilet
What do you mean when you say it's okay to eat?
Im fidgety
PLEASEWAIT
Please way
wait a minute
prince
join
Can I come in? Wait a minute.
So I'm going to go to the bathroom for a bit.
Please wait but this
If it comesout
I can't see the reply, what should I do? Is it okay?
Is it okay if I go right away?
Hurry up and keep going like this
busy
Did you get a reply?
yes yes
I'm saying "huh" but it's okay
I'm not surprised by that, but it's okay
Is it OK?
I'm worried, but I'll put this in once.
Maybe just show your face a little?
Are you there now?
Let's go listen to something for now.
OK
Then let's have a call
I'll show my face on the phone
Let's go
What
time
The volume is really annoying
It's small and breakable
Its been a long time
OS
[music]
It doesn't seem to work with the code
Is that so?
senior
Watanabe postponement
OK
[music]
Google
I have no choice but to lower my voice and raise my voice
I think it might have turned out nice, Max.
[music]
OKOK
I can't speak Japanese
By the way, it was Tekaki-chan.
I don't understand Japanese
I don't understand English
I already have a sniffer for the makeup I'm making.
I have it
I see that you have it, but I actually have it today.
sniffer
That's what I'm trying to find. I'm going to go now.
I'll probably go a little later.
with Kayla
nice
A little bit of Jamai-chan but different from me
Because of that, it's something like that.
I'm really sorry for the misunderstanding.
do not have
Sorry sorry
So let's talk until we go, OkOklet'
sTalklove
and
The two of us have talked before.
[music]
Sports day
Yo
That's good. Maybe I won't participate this time.
Maybe something like that
invitation
If you don't get invited
I guess it's because it came out last time.
[laughter]
[music]
i will participate
I'll do my best Japan
When will the group's sports day be next?
I don't know
No, maybe I'm not waiting, baby
Maybe
[music]
strike
I'll do it
God is
[music]
on new server
yesNEWS
I want redstone. Redstone, yeah.
now
Kaido-chan is just there.
Is it?
There's Kaela-chan who will do it for you.
[music]
1 stack
Do you want it?
Which one is better?
Dust is fine, let's get the dust out.
Google
[music]
Then Kaela-chan is that redstone
Apparently I'm looking for my blue ice cream
I just want to look for it
Sorry, I have work to do.
As expected, he will do anything
Return
Why did someone write a song like that before?
white button
I'll do something about it
Kaina-chan, will you do something?
The melody will do whatever it takes
There was a warm melody
I'll do something about it
lion's mother
Please do something
[Laughter]
But he will do it
anything
[laughter]
That's right, the God of love
Beauty
is
[laughter]
What kind of house will you build? Sumifah's Edon
already
I wonder if it looks like a forest.
Looks like a forest
Grass Forest Calliope Molly Point
meter Japanese
Themorry
Watome-senpai
How are you doing lately?
stress
A song that comes to mind
old song
Just the stress of stress
TheStress
Certainly viewers of
Summary Senior
That one in the list
I'm sweating under that shirt
What do you think of people who remove their [ __ ]?
[laughter]
one more time
A story I heard from a friend
Remove your nude bra
It's gone
Hurry up because you'll fall
I took it off.
It was okay, no one could see it.
It seems like it didn't happen.
[Laughter]
I don't wear it. I don't have many. I usually go home.
Watch Favorite
BLACK
black
where
What is your favorite blabla? Favorite blabla
I know that I know the
day I see
[music]
Normal Normal Normal
It's the one with the wire in it.
I like the one without wires
For some reason, my back feels like it's going to hurt.
in
It hurts
That's why Nu Brown is also helpful.
But.
According to a friend
It will sweat and won't stick.
Ah, I see
hey
[music]
I don't know, I don't know, I don't know anything
only what i know
Do you two have anything you want to ask each other?
[music]
[laughter]
hey
Mikuji Miko-chan is nice
choice nice
[music]
Summary When seniors enter that Hololive
Did you say that? Hololive's recommendation hurts.
it hurts
from
I've always loved you though
Even if it seems like that, it's true
I wonder what happened, but the one I fell in love with was Baekura-senpai.
It was
[laughter]
That's all
Is this all?
Na
Of course I
I can imitate my seniors, but I can't do anything else.
I wonder if there is? Let's go home
[music]
Wait, wait, wait Hello
Delicious and delicious
cool
A senior's good impersonation is
Crayon Shin-chan
crayon shinchan
It's not Hololive
About Peko-chan
in the voice of a senior
can i buy cigarettes
They don't look alike
I wonder what it is
I think number 27
Number 7 please
[music]
I could do better
I have to practice again
I can your
ofmypecraftation
[laughter]
[music]
It's like when I sing a song
Sometimes I'll come up with something really strong.
There's a certain way of singing that you have to have.
be
Can you understand that curly tongue?
Like
That's amazing
I can't figure out how to wrap it.
I can do that though
I wonder what it is
It's a little bit special that you often hear in Japanese songs.
There is a way to wrap it
Yes.
Yo
[music]
It's a little different
I think seniors can do it.
Can I do it?
Should I run away?
Please tell me, you're like a raora
Yeah look
Look
please tell me
where
Summary of what is being rolled, senpai, where is it being wrapped?
how do you
The one at the top is amazing
Just under the bottom
It's rolled up
[music]
Redstone for summary seniors
before you bring it to me
Looks like they'll bring some ice.
What's your name?
I understand
[music]
camera camera
I've already found it, I've seen it, I've seen it
No more camels
It's called "camo" in English.
That's right, it's a joke
If you can get your pores covered too
Kaela's name
mix
I said I'd give it a name.
Ella and turtle, camera, camera, yeah
[music]
Summary: Senior, today starts at 11:00
It's streaming from 11am.
I start late and go to bed late.
I'm reading it now
But at that time, I'll be in Austria.
There's almost no one there when I go to the same hospital.
Basically it's true
Me too
That's right, most of the time there will be no JP members.
Something together
Let's explore
[laughter]
Next time I'll go to Sumitomo-senpai.
I think it's ready, it's ready, it's ready
Apparently he's on his way
[music]
But he's a god
Japanese
your
SOK
[music]
Google
I see
How did you manage to compile it, senpai, even though you cant speak Japanese?
delivery of
I asked if you understood.
It's a cutout
honest student
Even if you watch it on stream
Even if I don't understand it, I kind of like the atmosphere.
from
It's so calming
Watanabe Senpai's
delivery
I'm glad it's Comfy Stream
oh yeah
Studying
Studying Studying English
Let me go back to Mesteri English again.
[music]
thank you
There is
[laughter]
[music]
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay
Google
You're going back to my place
Thank you for studying
Good for you guys
get what you want and need
Thank you for the indirect kiss
What should I do?
I thought it was a good time
That's right because it comes back to him.
See you then, Ok, thank you for your hard work.
is
[music]
see you
It's okay now
It was okay after all
It's okay, it's like my senior is here.
I'm home now
sweat sweat
I was happy
Was it nice to play?
I also received some redstone.
thank you
I feel like I can talk to Kyla-chan somehow.
I want to be more
hey
Somehow I've come this far
What is this?
That
I brought Kun and he's still screaming.
I'm glad you told me your happy name.
Please bring me
So
Snipper
Is it ok if I let it hatch?
Let's take a look at this
Again and again, more and more
That's amazing, but how can you prepare it so quickly?
Yeah.
Awesome
so soon
It's amazing that you can prepare it
There are enough red stones for a lifetime.
Which one is that powdery block?
It seems like you want
I was surprised by the question
My heart is pounding
Hey, they gave me a carport for one lap. This is amazing.
Is it God?
2345678910
weekly
How about redstone?
I can't make it, teacher, I probably can't make it.
I have to dig.
I wonder if it can be played?
I've been digging all my life for things like trading.
[music]
villager's
Exchange?
Mahoru feeling
you
witch drops
[music]
Looks like I'll be able to get something if I go home.
I see.
I saw amazing deeds of God.
It's amazing because they've been digging all their lives.
Well, I'm sure
I have an image of me digging all the time.
[music]
Because of God
Tell me
And he's a good kid
thank you
Kairappa
Looks like you already have it
I hope you like it
There's nothing more I can give you
Why do you think so?
So above this is a dunk.
Feelings are important
I gave it a name
sign
It would be nice to make a movie about it someday
I think he'll be really happy
Kaela-chan statue
Is this stable?
I don't want to go home.
this
[music]
They were cute
He said something like an indirect kiss.
I'm so excited just because you said the comment
Heart pounding
drink
What did you do in the comments?
There was something called joint kins, so it's something in English.
I thought that's what you were saying
Isn't that what you were saying in English?
Is there something called joint in English?
I wonder if the comments are telling me that.
That's what I thought, but my eyes were just saying it again
That's it
Justa little bit
Embarrassing joint kiss and eyes only uncle
It was
Well then, I'll take you to see me for a while.
Is the brightness okay?
Only wakame
Is everything okay?
It's okay if it's more than that, so is it okay?
Looks like it's okay
Is it okay here?
It's totally fine, ok hey
I don't like the zombie voice.The brightness is fine.
thank you
Thanks
I'll bring you
I can't see anything on the leaf block, it's totally fine.
N
Open it a little more
Shall I bring him?
Be it
Kunni
I'm going there
I wonder if I should give her a pen.
Particularly true
They won't be born right away.
It is better to stop the work each time.
Then I have to get a fence.
I need seeds first
I have to step on it
There are only
Then fence
Connect it here quickly like this
Should I make it feel like this?
While the eggs are laying
Shall I bring you?
What, eggs?
here are three
Is it okay to leave it there123
Just leave it there
OK
It's okay to leave this open. I can't fill it up so quickly.
mosquito
Do it one by one It's pretty big
I'm excited to have one piece at a time
make one piece at a time
Just place it
1 piece each
I left everything behind.
What should I do?
[music]
Well, let's start with one as a trial.
I'll put one up then.
Huh
Yes, I'll get one for now.
Hurry up
[music]
I'll bring you
Oishio Oishio Oishio Oishoa
It was shiny
The egg hurts, it hurts, it hurts
My heart is pounding
Let's go! Which Arie is the secret?
Give me some seeds
Which child should I take?
Why did you choose this name?
Goodluck
No, but it's easier for older children to carry.
Good job
Shall we go here and there, Alekreit?
The brush is dripping
I'm not going at all
Let's go that way.
Let's bring two to
Shall we go there?
Let's go to work.
Good job
Oisho
It's work
Can you come out?
nice
It was torn apart
Shall we go?
Hurry up! It'll tear apart.
I think it's bad, so I'll do it one by one.
went
Hey
Where did you go first?
terrible
Hey, I'm being born
Where did that go?
I shouldn't have gone that far
What happened?
I wonder what they were holding? I wonder if it was some kind of soil.
I wonder if it was
Shall I bring some soil?
Oh no no no
what range
I guess he'll pick it up
return
I wonder if it's in the room?
It was a fish
It can come out about a centimeter
Oh, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts
Good
Was Takata there?
where did you go
Sorry for coming upstairs
I wonder if I can come?
Panel?
I wonder if I can enter it from here.
Yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes to to
yes
Oishoto
Okay, okay, okay, okay, let's close this up.
kana
Hoi hoi
Okay okay okay okay okay okay then from here
Bring it
It's hard
[music]
It's stuck here
I'm going
Yes, I'll go here and there.
[music]
Let's
Go ok ok ok
Good boy, it's dangerous
Ah, something is sticking out.
[music]
I hate it
I guess it fell out of the glass block.
So
It came, it came, it came, it came, it came, it came, it came, it came, it came, it came, it came, it came, it came, it came, it came, it came, it came, it came, it came, it came, it came.
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, nice.
Nice OkOkOk
Something is sticking out here.
Endermen came too
I feel like something is cracked.
Should I add this?
Then come out through the gap in the glass.
I wonder if it's here
Is it really okay to close this?
One came back though
It's okay if you see it
Oh la la la
The egg will break
can't go back
[music]
After putting it in, only the upper part
Hoi hoi
be born
Why was it open there? Take me away from here.
I was thinking of coming, so I opened it.
If it's from over there
I thought it would be small
But even from here, it completely disappeared
What should I do?
rice
Nice welcome back
perfection
perfect perfection
Good boy
The English that came
perfect
So what?
Not until I'm an adult
It seems like they won't pick it up.
Apparently they don't pick them up or dig them up.
It takes quite a while.
So if you could dig up those seeds.
This
Give it to the kids
kana
What role does this note play?
of
sneakers
This is the one I dug up.
my brothers
pick it up
So
I wonder if you can bring it to the sound side?
Ah, when a note sounds, or an item is placed there.
throw
Hey, then should I take this?
N
It's amazing how they drop it right where the sound is.
Well, I have to open this.
I see.
I'll put some soil in it and try it out.I'm sure.
Shall we take a look?
Try it once
It gets a little noisy though
So soil
Is this it?Yes
I can't reach it, yes.
yes
Mmm yes
[music]
born
Born
Oh, I'm throwing something
Will this fit in?
entered
I've been bitten and all sorts of things.
Now that I'm in
a little bit
Should I put it there?
yes
I'm climbing a tree, it's okay, I won't fall
I see it's a shitty aim
I'll come in someday
I'll come in soon
There is one in there.
It's in
Looks like the fall damage is fine.
Don't fall on the egg
Let's do it again please
[music]
cute
Messed up
I'm climbing though
Is it okay?
I'm worried about falling
I wonder if sneakers will take medium damage?
a
Maybe it's better not to climb trees
Buy domestic
Come down!
come down next to me
Something amazing
Array is flying to you
Sound waves are overflowing
Ah, I took too much, but it's okay.
I can't ride this
I can't ride
[music]
That's proof that I'm sensing it.
flying
sound waves
This kind of thing seems to be okay, I've been watching it.
That's right, the sneaker cord pattern
I guess he liked it
Do you like high places?
Isn't it noisy?
[music]
Sound too
Higher is better, so lower is better.
[music]
It's too expensive
It's so expensive
[music]
I like this sound
I liked it
So let's do this
Then do you really do it?
What should I do?
Don't smell it
[music]
cute
hey
[music]
It smells delicious
Is it wakame?
This is just in case something happens.
Should I put up a fence?
So cute and fluffy
Kun Kun Kun Kun Kun Kun Kun Kun Kun Kun Kun Kun Kun Kun Kun Kun Kun Kun Kun Kun Kun Kun Kun Kun Kun
born
It seems like a moment
It's like the moment you're born
[music]
Someone whose name I haven't decided yet or a name tag
Maybe it's not enough
I think I'll grab a lot of name tags next time.
Panda and other names too.
I want to wear one, but I don't have a name tag.
I guess it's not there for about 5 minutes.
a little bit
Should I wait slowly?
If it's a fishing spot
I wonder if I can catch it?
[music]
Something's wrong with my right ear
I wonder if they sold trade?
Umm
I think they sold nicotine.
Let's go take a look.
while fishing here
wait
Well, what if he was born while I was going to pick it up?
do
No more eggs
I'm sure Asora-chan was exchanging it.
When something happens
Shall I go take a look?
Also, fishing is something other than that.
If it wasn't quite wide, I wouldn't be able to catch it.
nametag
Oh, I think I'll be born
Looks like it's going to be born
pounding pounding
Looks like it's about to be born
Oh, isn't it bad to have a roof?
If the top is not empty, you can't fish here with a name tag.
Na
pounding pounding
It's as exciting as a Pokemon hatching.
Different colors appear
Doki Doki Doki
So when you are born
See if you can exchange it with an attack.
I guess I'll just collect some name tags.
pounding pounding
It's true that the musical notes are like heartbeats
Teacher, is it about time?
Maybe a little more
6 voice nipper
Fan of Yamitoko player
Is the teacher still here?
keep an eye on me
[music]
My heart is pounding
teacher
Is it almost time?
The purity of the heartbeat that sells the pulse
will be born in
1 minute left 1 minute left
[music]
It's groaning
My heart is pounding
[music]
Still cool ASMR sneakers ASMR
Voices coming from both left and right
My heart is pounding, but if I turn there now
may be born
Hmm sorry now
[music]
Because the egg will break
Maybe you want to pass
Sorry, please wait a little longer
[music]
born
It's born like this
[music]
Was Pon born?
connected
It's like a train
Hmm
[music]
It's soothing
I'm glad you did your best, cute
[music]
They are twins
growthis
I'm looking forward to it, I think I'll go check out the name tags.
[music]
Looks like I can't ride it
It was the first time I saw you being born so cute.
It's not Ecchan's fishing hole, it's a real fishing hole.
There is a name tag
Let's take a look from a higher level
I was born
mona experience
So cute!
[music]
birthday
There's a name tag
Double is fine.
[music]
fine
It's expensive
220 That's not there
I
I don't want to fall anymore
Uncle, are you going out?
Are you closed?
After all, everyone is 20.
South 10 steps
passed away
What's up with the raid passing away in the update?
I should be lucky
lucky uncle
unlucky
Hmm, only one person was killed.
What the hell
lucky uncle
It became like this
Not really
It's not her place.
What is a fishing pond?
Which fishing hole are you referring to?
[music]
Was it flagged?
Robo-chan place
I guess it was this one
There's a lot more over there
Maybe over there
Is this it?
Hello it's over there
a
There are so many
I'm about to leave
I wonder if I can get out here?
Is it okay if I get this?
I don't know if it's something I should get.
It's free. What's here is free.
Ah, it's free
draw
It's bad if I don't sleep.
Can you sleep?
Hey
I can't sleep
I guess it'll be okay if I stay in bed for now.
I wonder if it's okay to sleep until 93?
Try hittingit
I'm probably working on it. Is it okay?
thank you
Senkyu
I was saved
Even though I slept with Mr. Q, I still slept with Shinsaba at night.
I wonder if it won't happen?
That phantom bug
Farewell
bug phantom
Well, I guess I'll just get three.
I told him that I had just received 3 pieces.
I guess that's it
thank you
There is
thief
Should I send it to Robo-chan now?
I'll forget it
Robo-chan Robo-chan
Well
hello me
minecraft
Name tag with halo box
I received 3
I stole three things
Isn't it Erobo-chan's?
What does it mean?
Isn't it?
The one that Matsuri-chan and porridge caught.
It seems like it should be
I put it in because I don't really use it.
I haven't put my likes and dislikes in, so I guess that's it.
I wonder if Kana is okay?
Well then, what do you mean by sending it?
It looks like it will be. Well then, that's fine.
It's okay, I need a pot, so I'll bring it home.
Monne
Its rustling
Should I go fishing if something happens?
OK
Oishio Oishio, what should we name it?
seems to be concentrating on work
Something like this
I wonder if that's what you're doing
electric railway
It's amazing that you haven't noticed
[music]
in sight
Because it wasn't visible
They're laying something made of iron, aren't they?
Good job
Great concentration
What should I name it?
Don't worry
I couldn't get in from here.
charcoal
sneakers
Don't worry
loafers
-She said her name was Tame-chan.
I thought it was okay
Oh no no no
I thought you hadn't replied
I thought you were saying something, but I panicked.
Tae, what should I do?
[music]
what's a good name
It's kind of warm-hearted, isn't it?
Su-chan brother Fan-chan
[music]
I'm sure if there are 3 of them, Sue-chan and Ni-chan are fans.
Maybe it's ok
[music]
Well, let's do that, Sun-chan.
brother fanchan
[music]
Hello, there are people who just came.
I have no plans to increase it.
I guess I can't come now.
Plan to increase
but
long ago
I've bought a hamster
At that time
My name is Ai-chan Love-chan Yuu-chan
I once fell in love with your name
Most of the time, my grandma took care of me.
Ai-chan love-chan Yuu-chan de i
loveyou
Should I make it cheeky?
Ai-chan, Ram-chan, Yu-chan
No, but would you like Su-chan and Fan-chan?
Ordinarily
I'm worried
Kare-chan Kia-chan is a baby
The member you were talking to earlier
once fuutan beef tongue
I'm sure it's a commemorative one
[music]
be happy
Kia-chan Kaya-chan Hata-chan
Dog, Taachan, Meichan
Wow, I'm worried, what should I do?
Ma-chan Bo-chan Tofu-chan
Chan-chan Maki-chan
Don't worry, it's okay to name two people.
But I came up with my own name
Just put it on
Embarrassing
Shall I call you chan again?
It's a little embarrassing
Well then, Su-chan bro
Fan-chan?
Sue-chan
twenty three
That's it.
My wife's
Isn't Su-kun sorry?
You just put it on without permission.
[music]
Let's go to Sue-chan and Fur-chan.
Brother
[music]
Fan-chan
Okay
Now
go
just a fan
OK
It's decided, let's give it a name.
Call me brother
Brother Sun-chan
Even though I'm excited, I haven't named it Panda.
But
Only the sneakers have a name
The goats in Arusman also don't have names.
Someday I'll hang a name tag
Hey, what do you mean?
Come around here.
I didn't have it and came very close.
What do you mean?
OK
I'd like to give it a name, okay?
That's young
I won't push you away
We're having some kind of fight.
Sue-chan is walking gracefully on top of it.
Chan
big brother
So you're my brother
[music]
It's kind of cute
My brother and Hwang are not on good terms
It's okay to look away
Well then next time
I think I'm probably an adult now
Seeds etc.
Let me have this array
So I guess I'll try the casino.
I thought I would collect it.
Oishio Oishio
collect
Now let's take a photo
picture
When I grow up under the tree
This is suffocating
I'm suffocating
[music]
This is about 2 squares worth.
I guess it's okay as long as it's at the height.
Don't suffocate with leaves
Are you okay
But I'll be a little sad if this key disappears.
Right?
OK
Should I also add this?
Only one thing
It's missing though
Thank you for the sweat test.
It's okay, put this on.
You may ask for a photo.
screenshot prince
Take this off once
Oisho
[music]
Eh, why don't you have eyebrows?
Seedling
A cherry tree sapling on top of a pot
I need to get it, Sakura Maigi.
Lost things here
Maybe the back too
Gi
[music]
I'll fetch the screenshot Cancel
need
cherry blossom sapling
The plants are just cherry blossom saplings.
Huh?
Is it okay to have two each?
So
cherry blossom sapling
gold
Decorate something in the pot
Uekicho is here.
Let's try it here
To this
It feels like it fits on a flowerpot
Ahhhh
This is how it will be
I see
in
like this
[music]
It's so beautiful that I fell in love with it
It's beautiful, just the right size
Let's do this too
There is no hit detection on the protrusion above the pot.
I see.
Ah, I'm sure if you look at it like this
Let's go
come
beautiful
My voice has become rough
It's beautiful
It's beautiful there
Let's take a photo
mosquito
Remove this once
My voice suddenly became hoarse
Take it from the outside once, then take it from the inside as well.
kana
Thank you, it's okay.
Yesterday
A little bit of audio about those three
Please do your best to submit what you recorded.
Because it happened
I think there are some people who came now.
Delete one comment
OK thank you
Do your best and be great
[music]
thank you
I went to bed pretty late, too.
Maybe that is also the case
A little hard to see
mosquito
Is it something like this?
Let's take this one for now and then take another one inside.
Let's do that, let's look good and then look nice
May I ask you to take it?
[music]
according to
It goes with the sound, right?
I'll take it, Senkyu.
I'll do it according to this sheep sound
Gacha
Around here?
Would you like the middle?
Feels good
I want to include bad kids too.
It's just barely inside, so it's okay.
He's so cute, I'd like this please
[music]
Please and please
Got it
I got a good deal
[music]
Almost 100 people
She looked like a model.
I got it thank you so much. Now this
I'll put it back
thus
Thank you Senkyu later
Everyone's copy
Take a screenshot
Should I clean up?
I'm happy
A wonderful snipper house has been created.
thank you
I don't want to have to clean up after myself.
Because it's going to happen
Good job
[music]
this
Delivery is until cleaning up. Put this in and do this.
Maybe this too
It's great that everyone is watching
kind
sense of responsibility
rail
Thank you for watching over me
[music]
workbench
Is the hoe on the other side or the lever lever OK?
Lead too
Add the lead and you're good to go!
No, it's helpful to be sensible
three blocks of meat
pain
panel
Received
fork plate material
Is the trap door up?
dark auction
stairs
approach
turn
button
Or higher?
this is here
leave
rail
trap door
Leaf stone button
bucket
Leaf
You cleaned up quickly, didn't you?
I've found a place now
Cop'un
[music]
I can hear the tingling here too.
piston piston is this okay?
Chanko piston that can be heard a little
sticky piston
wheat seeds
Top
It's a wide range
this is
enderman's gift
I'm grateful but
Ah wheat seeds
Would you like to eat that?
This is how souvenirs are made
Is it a sneaker birthday gift?
Congratulations
There are so many endermen here, why are they like this?
It's probably full of endermen.
Thank you very much
Why are there so many endermen?
I guess it will spring up
Is it a comfortable place to live?
Because the house is big
I'm afraid this is ok
I'm there every time
Do you like yokan?
Is it easy to roll yokan?
In the kana ender industry
It's nice here
After all, there are endermen living upstairs.
Are you calling me?
This enderman
Maybe
I want my fellow Enderman back.
That's scary
So let's clean up.
Thank you for watching until I cleaned up
I got it
I'll leave Minecraft here for today.
A little super after this
I'm going to try charlie reading.
thank you
Messed up
Actually, I'm holding back from going to the toilet after chewing so much.
Let's play the ending and come back again
It might be a little late to come back.
I don't want to go to the bathroom.
Good night to those who sleep, those who still stay
Please stay behind. I'm off now.
please
[music]
I like it right now
I'm just in time
It was like a broadcasting accident.
I washed my hands
As expected, there is nothing that Oyasumiyama does not have.
But
There are times when it's dangerous
Sometimes
If you don't make it in time, you'll have to go home.
This doesn't exist.
Various things are bad
It's really a broadcasting accident.
Somehow I made it in time today as well.
Thank you for waiting for me to say goodnight.
thank you
I'll hold on, Ignine, but just a little longer
It's quite difficult when you think about it
You can't do it, right?
No, today too
Time went by so fast, it's true when you play Minecraft.
The time is passing by quickly, but the last part
but
Messed up
I'm sleepy
hey
That music too.
amazing
healing
inside
Because it's the music I expected
It's kind of soothing, isn't it?
But.
This is how I do it Superchar
Reading or something?
delivery
After finishing it, my eyesight becomes clearer.
I wonder what my voice sounds like through those headphones?
I'll hear it when I get home
Will I feel sleepy?
Stream something
After finishing, I took off my headphones and went out to eat.
Something happens when I eat something.
I can't believe I'm no longer sleepy
[music]
There are quite a few things like that.
Django, it's possible that your own voice makes you sleepy.
Yan
you gradually
[music]
Maybe my own voice is making me sleepy
do not have
It's Django
It's just because I'm watching One Piece.
I also started watching the One Piece anime.
But it's quite different.
Manga and
I don't know what it is, it's the same, but the way to proceed etc.
It's different
Already from the beginning
There are waves
We haven't become friends or anything.
What is going on?
Also, Armida suddenly left.
Tari
Is there an original?
It's still early days, and it's not even 3 o'clock yet.
But
Still season 1
I see.
Expand
The order is
I was surprised that it was different.
Also, your voice sounds young.
innocent
It's refreshing to feel like Zoro is new.
I feel it
Young or whatever you want to call it?
I'm sure this was decades ago.
20 years ago Is that so?
Is that so?
Mr. Nakai starred in Zoro for the first time.
a
I guess Zoro is my first regular.
It's already now
Messed up
It's the image of a famous voice actor, but it's my first time.
The regular was Zoro.
That's so innocent.
24 years ago, now he's a big name. Listen to his voice.
It kind of looks like Mr. Nakai.
Understand level
First time since quitting my job
voice actor work
[music]
That's right, that's right, it's delicious.
Will it be?
[music]
I learned it for the first time
That's right
The voice gradually became more husky.
I've become Zoro
Until then, it was just mobs.
I wonder if it bloomed with Zoro
I quit my job and went from hunting pirates to becoming a pirate.
Because I haven't watched One Piece
I only have an image of a ring
mosquito
surely
Is it possible?
It's kind of a gift from Ebon.
I'm sure
What happened to the teachings? The teachings?
This is also a gift from Ebon.
A button
I'm sure
That's amazing when you think about it
Same goes for Gintama.
teeth
Don't stick it together
Why does G have a machine?
[music]
But it's fine, Luffy is still like that.
I guess everyone has that innocent feeling.
20 years ago, everyone felt like it was new to them, but now
Even if you are a veteran
Is that so?
Hey, your voice is young, Luffy when he was little.
The voice was amazing.
I was loud and said it because Krillin was doing it.
That's true. I see, Krillin too.
Laputa's pan zoom too
Damn Demeteran
amazing
It's full of roles
Originally a veteran
I'm sure that's the case, too.
TAAN
Thank you for your first comment
welcome
Akirimaru might be like that too.
Maybe so?
That's amazing
but
Puzzle I won't become a pirate
I'll become the Pirate King I won't become a pirate
I'm the pirate king
Naruoya
I'm waiting
How ironic!
It's kind of interesting when you think about it
Why did Pazu become a pirate?
I'm doing it
Because we are strangers through life
[music]
That's interesting
Do you have a favorite voice actor? Well, my favorite is
My favorite voice actor is Iizuka.
That girl named Mayumi
He's the one who does Kasumi's voice.
But the comment disappeared, hey
haze
I'm going to passionately talk about Mayumi Tsukasa's story.
I thought the comment disappeared
welcome home
Comments are welcome
Yes, Kasumi and others.
I like seaweedStar Ocean
stone ocean second story
I think she did the voice of Lena in the anime.
I wonder if you're welcome?
I also like singing.
I also like Mayumi Iizuka's song "Pure".
That song is my favorite though.
Laplace's songs and other songs too.
It's cute and bitter blue
It's cute too.
Chan
I'm picky.
cute
Well then
Hmm?
Very
The only person I really liked was Iizuka-san.
Maybe
I was wondering if we could meet somehow
I wonder if we can meet somehow somehow?
What
Sometimes I think about voice actors.
Oh no!
Voice actors sometimes go to voice acting schools.
I went there as a special lecturer, etc.
There are some people who can
Or something like that.
It's coming there
It seems like we're just doing it
That's right
My heart is pounding and I'm feeling sleepy
Something like that
Well, when you turn on the switch, there's a lot of heat.
Well, I'm the type who goes full throttle.
That's right
yes
But if you actually see him in person,
I couldn't say anything at all, couldn't even make a sound.
It's my type though
It might even smell nice.
But what?
The male voice actor
[music]
Is that that?
Inosuke
I think it was Mr.
I think it's amazing
It seems like he's trying his best.
Amebashiperasher even at rehearsals etc.
No celeb clubs here.
Let's rehearse and rehouse.
Because I really like Betelgeuse
Also, my favorite, Petelgeuse
It's Romane-Conti, so that's part of it.
Well, it's not Kirito or anything like that.
I learned about goodness from Romane-Conti.
of
That's where I learned from Betelgeuse.
It's tough, but there were voice actors as well.
That's what I thought
you
That's lazy
I like special content that is unique.
I thought it was kind of amazing.
He's a nice character, he's tasteful.
amazing
I thought he was an actor.
Is that so?
Na
The reading play was like that too.
It was amazing
I wonder what else
Even if it's simple, it's a good love
Ai to Ai to meet me
I probably don't use SNS at all.
It's like there's no internet
I wonder what the type is?
Nowadays, voice actors who use SNS
There seem to be a lot of them.
quiet
hard-headed
That's what I did a long time ago
That's why I don't know much about the details.
I don't have that, but not much.
Is it better not to dig it up?
I was worried about your blog.
I don't know much about the details, so I'm black.
It's history
Better not dig
I see.
So, see you later, what can I say?
the
What type of character do you like?
That many
I think that's probably why
Um, the same goes for Romane-Conti.
Same goes for Inosuke.
But I still like Icchan
Mayumi Iizuka
[music]
Uhihihi
It's cute
yes
It's haze
Hihihi
I felt safe at home.
After all, it's not a DVD.
So cute
[music]
That's the thing about being a veteran and being cute.
But
on second thoughts
Nozawa
Masako
Mr.
It's amazing. Even now, my energy is vibrant.
Um, a video that was circulating on Twitter
Messed up
It was cute
Support something
Masako Nozawa
Talk about what you supported
Maybe Masako Nozawa
I'm not even a legend, but from the bottom of my heart
I thought it was amazing how you expressed your emotions.
Something like this, here and there
I want to become a car
That's cute
I wonder if he was watching baseball.What kind of teacher is this here?
It's so cute
He has an energetic way of speaking.
It's hot
I want to be a grandma like this
I thought so.
cute grandma
It's hot, isn't it?
kana
The flowers have bloomed so much
Prepare superchar
David has been active for 80 years, which is amazing.
What?
Awesome
Wait a minute, okay?
I was only able to read part way last time, so this is a continuation.
to the point where you start from
I would like to read it, but not too much.
to
For now this
Part way through
I think I want to read it
Thank you, thank you for not overdoing it.
Masu
Huh?
Sisson cup from someone with a delicious name
Maybe from Mr.
Hololizer for now
Thank you, don't push yourself too hard
You're so kind, but yesterday you were so sleepy
The reason I was doing well today was with my smooth voice.
Do it
Thinking
There are a lot of voice-related submissions.
It was still a long way off, but it wasn't until August.
Even if it's just taste, I'm done with it.
That's it.
I'm thinking of doing something that's a long way off now.
Your voice is fine
I already submitted it.
I don't want to accumulate tasks
hey
Think about tomorrow and do it in moderation.
Because it's a collaboration
Well then
I would like to read it
But tomorrow too
Collaboration for about 1 hour
From about 11 o'clock again
I was hoping to do a solo
Hey
If you watch Holonjour now, ASMR is amazing.
It was supposed to happen
I'm thinking of doing it from 11pm.
I just checked from the default
I bought a lot of ASMR
ASMR era
[music]
If it doesn't seem possible, I'll give you that sign.
write
silently
Not distributed
[music]
And the world is exactly
ASMR itself
So
I would like to read it
A little tea bowl
I'll be doing Yoma Mecha Mecha soon.
It's a waste of treasure.
Even though I have it
Amazake
I'll read it
nothing
I'll read it.
[music]
I'll read it right away
I'll call you now
why are you worried
Thank you for the 3 minutes of cheese
queue
thank you
No no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
I read it I read it
thank you
Today is my second birthday as a member.
I'm very happy to have you
Last year, while I was showering and exploding,
In addition, the eyes continue to work hard every day, and that hard work
I will make my wishes come true one by one and move on.
It was morning when I saw my eyes again.
I don't do weather forecasts here at all, so I'm determined.
I thought that was an interesting sheep, but when did it happen?
Let's follow Nomanka as she works hard towards her dreams.
It has become next year
Please continue to support me so that I can become a rainbow-colored sheep.
Finally, thank you as always. See you soon, I love you.
[music]
Thank you Booster
Thank you Senkyu
Happy birthday too
Happy birthday to 11 years
to
No, I'm happy
But I think there were quite a lot of people like that.
Including myself
I think it's from the beginning
I don't know why, but I was making singing videos myself.
Really likethat
It doesn't feel like a peerless Utaman at all.
There wasn't
Ah, I guess you like singing.
I think it was like, ``Good luck!''
Everybody here too
Something weird is stupid again.
I was told about the weather.
nose hook
hair
shaved
I did but
After all
Things are still weird now that they've released Orichoco.
I think it's true.
It's just barely okay, but it's weird
I do it all the time
Probably around the time the Olympics came out.
I really got down and started singing.
So April Fool's Day or something actually happened
Sometimes a lie becomes true
Even I was surprised.
But I thought that my efforts would not betray me, so I did this.
Karamo
I would like to do my best
Yeah
I've been saying for a while that things are changing.
But
Whatever you say with your mouth
I can say it
It's like trying your best, though.
I can say with my mouth that I will do what I do.
Actually, I'm going to do it and tell everyone by taking action.
There's something I want to show you
So from now on, I will continue to live up to my word.
do your best
I want to make my dreams come true
Thank you very much
Stick to your word
Thank you so much Buno Spa and look forward to your continued support.
Please, thank you everyone for being here.
No, I can do my best because of everyone.
thank you
Thank you Mr. Han from Hangul
Thank you very much!
Thank you, I am really trying to overcome my weaknesses.
It's amazing, I respect it, and I do everything properly.
I was able to eat amazing dragon fruit too.
I knew the name but I'd never actually seen it.
When I saw the contents for the first time, I was really interested.
I want to eat it again, so next time I'll buy it somewhere else.
I think I'll try it
Thank you. Let's all continue this summer together.
I hope you enjoyed it. Thank you.
Senkyu
Today I made infinite green peppers and how to make them
Someone asked me to tell them
But with a reply
first
2 green peppers
buttocks and
I guess you could call it flat, but take both sides.
vertically
Vertical and slightly thinner to match the fibers.
Cut
Cut it into thin pieces
So
Put the cut peppers in a bowl and set aside.
About half a chicken
Even if I narrow it down a little, it's too narrow.
I squeezed it a little too much today and it became dry
Because it's gone
It removes a little bit of oil, but not too much.
I think it's better not to be too much
a little bit
narrow it down a little
Put it in the same place as the green pepper and go from there.
Wrap at 500w for about 2 and a half minutes
I will chin
If you can pin it
Remove the plastic wrap and use canned chicken for peace of mind.
sesame oil
1 teaspoon
in
chicken stock
In summary, it's a downstream thing.
1 teaspoon of chicken stock
Also, season it with salt and pepper.
Just mix it up and add white sesame seeds at the end.
only
Very
It's easy and delicious. Can I have an away par?
Mone
If it's simple and easy
Cutting peppers is more troublesome
Cutting peppers is the most troublesome thing.
That's what I think
Arrange as you like
If you add bean sprouts as well
It might be delicious
Yes, but a little
The flavor of green pepper remains, but there is no bitterness at all.
Without it
Flavor too
Because it gets diluted like this
good
[music]
delicious
I'm eating deliciously
If you can't eat green peppers, please give it a try.
It tastes almost like canned tuna so it's fine.
Hey, it tastes good.
Yeah, give it a try
please
Look at your face before adding carrots etc.
So what?
Bell peppers first
Soak something in cold water
It seems that if you let it sit it will remove some of the bitterness.
Ice water etc.
It seems like a good idea to do it
There are quite a few things that I don't like other than green peppers.
There aren't that many vegetables though.
Assist etc.
Fresh cream and marshmallows
And then there's that internal organ system.
Lever or something
Something like cilantro
weak point
It's no good, the hormones are no good
Cartilage, etc.
No cartilage
There are quite a lot
I'm not good at health
[music]
I learned to eat green peppers by following my example.
wonderful
[music]
It was delicious
It's great to be able to eat so much
wonderful
I can eat mayonnaise
I can eat ketchup, but I don't know which one.
I guess it's Kechara
Great
Watome is great too
But it's still a bit bulky.
too
If anything, I prefer ketchup.
is
Thank you very much
thank you
Thank you sheep keeper girl hamster
Agoya may not be good either.
Maybe I don't like bitter melon
Is it no good?
Thank you very much Tanabata-san
Bingo with green pepper and dragon fruit
Chilled as a snack for congratulations drinks
Remove the cotton from green peppers and refrigerate them.
Cool in the refrigerator and season with salt, pepper, miso, etc.
There are some dishes that you can eat with a side dish, but with beer.
It goes well with alcohol that has a bitter taste.
[music]
It's not bitter, but it's bitter.
goes well with certain alcohol
I don't drink alcohol.
But lately, I've been thinking about that alcohol.
There are projects, but there are no non-alcoholic projects.
Is that so?
There are people who make normal and non-alcoholic products.
No, but I wonder if they can make non-alcoholic ones?
I wonder if it's no good
Non-alcoholic
People who can't drink alcohol
But with Nomar who can participate in the evening drink distribution etc.
I wonder if it will happen
I'm thinking of trying non-alcoholic streaming.
It's difficult, non-alcoholic is like that.
But quite a bit
I've searched before
There are many kinds
[music]
First, start by saying Puha 1000 times a day.
cooked rice
But I'd like to try it once, non-alcoholic.
There is
delivery
Someone with a drinking history
I wonder how it's different
I'm interested in juice
Thank you Gyokuro-san and Super-chan.
I may have never drank Masu Senkyu.
Complete the bingo row by eating all the infinite green peppers.
Congratulations! No matter what your goal is, you can always compromise.
figure
The attitude of accomplishing things is nothing short of admirable.
I respected you even more.
Thank you for making me happy
I'm kind of having fun doing it.
thank you
Thank you to the ramen shop with Kiwami Elbow
It's closer to alcohol, but the taste is more like that.
kana
Thank you for the sweet pepper texture
Yes, it's not 0%.
Thank you Makunouchi-san
Happy snacking and Blue Journey
Congratulations on the live performance and thank you
Spacha hoping that Gen-chan will win
Thank you very much
This summer will be busy too.
Thank you everyone
It's not completely zero
I'm looking forward to Bolger, Summer too.
I'm looking forward to it
I'm looking forward to Blue-chan too.
I have to try hard
Now that I think about it, it's that summer.
that
[music]
What's the name?
Makushita or something
The watermelon has arrived, but maybe this is the last one
It may be the addition of
Videos etc.
revival
It might be the last time, etc.
Thank you Yosuke for the super bike
Thank you
Thank you Kangaroomini
I'm sure he won't refuse to share with Kazutami, I heard.
Never before
thank you
Thank you Nippon-san.After that
I think it might turn out to be a real thing or something.
Or something
Thank you kangaroo
Thank you Mr. Tripon
Paripi's glass is also in the bag.
If you put on the charm, we will meet for the first time.
I was able to meet up with Wata Mate smoothly.
So you can tell at a glance between these Watamates.
That's good, isn't it?
Thank you for adding it tomorrow.
Thank you Toriko
It's definitely a meeting or something, I understand.
It might be easy. Then, at which station on this day?
At a meeting or something
At events, etc.
It's near the entrance of so-and-so.
Hook the paripi sunglasses on your bag
It might be easier to find it if you say, "This is a sheep."
At a glance
in the chest pocket
When I plug it in
It's noticeable
Thank you super chasenkyu
Thank you Na
Senkyu
It's easy to tell that it's that person.
Hey, maybe that person
It's just a matter of timing when I get a reply.
If you touch your smartphone, etc.
It might be easy to understand
Yes
Thank you very much gkj child
It's my first time baby recently from shift work.
For day shift work
It is quite difficult to travel and come to stream.
The situation has become such that the frequency of going to see
Seeing each event less
It has become difficult, but I will always support you.
I have
I almost missed out on buying a birthday gift.
That's a secret that's only here
Thank you, right?
Yeah, everyone has their own life too.
After all
Your phone may change
Habits and such
Please come again whenever you can.
Thank you very much
If this is not the case, please wait here.
Good luck with your work
super chasen cue
nick
&Thank you Les Superchar.
There is
Senkyu
Oisho
It seems like there are some good days today.
Quite
I think it would be difficult for people to come every day.
I think it also has to do with my physical condition.
I wonder if it's similar to the one I answered before.
No good
About 2 minutes
past
Neso wa of10 no friends only
WifeWhatiswhatis
similar
I think I answered
I feel like it sounds familiar
family
Family only, which one is it?
Also family family score 100
Family score one handling
You'll become part of the family too.
scared
Yay family food
family dinner
You'll become part of the family too.
family punch
Kana Super-chan
Senkyu Well, there are various families.
Because there is
Some people say wakame is my wife, and some people say seaweed is mine.
Some are daughters
There are people who think of Watabe as my sister.
Ba
Watanabe is
There are people who think of me as my sister.
Ba
Maybe it depends on the person
thank you
Thank you for the powder copy
Check out the summary of Blue Journey costumes
I'm happy, I'll always love you and thank you
Yes
Blue Journey costumes are popular.
I'm happy, it looks good on you, thank you
Thank you Senkyu
I saw that comparison right away.
When you lean forward like that
They say your face looks big.
That's what you're comparing
There was a cutout, but it was really big.
It fits the width of your shoulders, and when you layer it together, it really looks great.
It was huge
Thank you super chasenkyuo
I hope you understand
Thank you mom, Lost
Thank you
Senkyu
thank you
Congratulations on overcoming it, thank you
I also made it while watching the stream, but the machine's
It's all about me, who doesn't like green peppers or vegetables in general.
It was delicious enough to eat
It was a bit surprising.
If I didn't have the chance, I wouldn't have eaten it.
I think so, thank you for the warmth, it's amazing here too
I can eat it.
the number of sheep increases
thank you
It's great to try
Nightmare Prinny
Thank you super chasenkyu
There is
Is it your birthday?
Little Beatway and BadHappy
Birthday-chan
Congratulations Senkyu and thank you
I'm a little late but happy
Thank you for the birthday
Masu
It's already been a month since Senkyu's birthday.
I can't believe it's been so long
Mr. Zaastral Walker
Thank you Senkyu
What the hell are you reading here, Island?
I think it was Drifting Symbol People or Island.
I feel like they taught me how to read.
Thank you super-chan
weak point
Thank you for your hard work in overcoming the delivery.
I can read it.I've been busy lately and haven't been able to watch the stream.
It was tough, but today was the first time in a while that I had a real tie.
I felt better when I heard Detame's voice.
I reserved a full set of birthday goods.
Thank you for the wonderful goods. I hope it arrives soon.
I'm nervous. We're mates again.
After that, I looked at it again at a recycle shop etc.
I've been buying lots of goods.
Why can you sell off your favorite goods?
Because there are people who sell and sell my products.
I'm grateful that newcomers like me can buy complicated products.
Thank you very much for your feelings.
I wonder what it is, but it's still
It's amazing to have support
hand
I feel that way
oh dear
There are many kinds of flames
It's a reason
Isn't it?
But thank you
superchar
thank you
There is also the possibility of thoughts of severing one's intestines.
Sometimes
Its true that the environment has changed, and its true that
Marriage or certainly
But when you bought it
I'm so happy that it arrived
Something
It made me feel happy.
If so
I'm happy
At that time
Thank you very much for this island
The drifting people of hope picked it up.
If you think of me as P.
I feel happy
thank you
Thank you
Thank you Carol
The hellish food we ate on this episode
The fruitis
Titan and
More in Taiwan
It seems to grow sweetly in Fukuoka.
Hey, if you eat too much, something red will come out.
But
Please rest assured that there is no harm to your health.
thank you
this fruit
4 pieces approximately 1.5 times the size
It sells for about 400 yen.
Easily find even cheaper prices
Yes, it's 400 yen for 4 pieces.
Yeah, but I'd be surprised if you didn't know.
I'm sure it might happen
I'm sure it's okay
this is bleeding
You might think that
But apparently it's delicious, isn't it?
It's sweeter
Really, really
I guess it felt thin
That's what I ate for
I felt like it was kind of thin.
I want to try something sweet
Thank you so much
The purchase deadline for anniversary goods is that I know Wakame.
I bought it when I was just starting out.
It wasn't there, right now I really want it
But I can't help but take care of the cutting-edge goods properly.
I bought the full set thank you
Well, that's true, because you don't know when it will fall.
hey
The feeling is
Because I don't know when it will hit me
there's someone just like me
I knew something existed though
Quite
I won't go until it's distributed.
Well, I was broadcasting it.
The deciding factor is not that moment.
It was just now
It was probably like that last year.
There's probably a moment when something sticks.
I guess
Thank you very much for being here right now.
Thank you for giving it to me
Thank you super chasenkyu
There is
Senkyu
Thank you very much
Even if you know that from the beginning, watch the entire broadcast.
I thought about it later.
I guess it was because it came later.
Even if you look at the initial technique name
It's possible that he wasn't bitten.
I think there is
Well, I guess it's about now.
In terms of appearance, there are various costumes and hairstyles.
Increase or something
I guess there is something like that.
These two people love pigtails and this kind of bun.
Like
I feel like that might be the case.
After all, each one
I wonder if there are times when I think
Thank you, Hatsumi-san too.
Welcome
Senkyu
Before I knew it, I started opening this stream.
there was
thank you
The merits of the changes are difficult to convey at a glance.
I don't think so, but I understand.
I understand, that's why
I know, I'm not the type that stands out like that.
Something
Loosely
calmly
I'm doing some kind of activity.
normally
You won't know unless you come here, that's for sure.
Squid taste
That's how I feel
I was drinking in an instant while chatting, I'm sure.
Absolutely
No comments
I thought so, but
I'm going for a long game
Before I knew it, I was typing a comment.
I think there is
I saw it, I saw it
thank you
I feel like I want to comment
I heard you're picking up a lot of comments.
I saw what you said in the clipping.
surely
It's hard to do properly, I don't wake up at all
My mate was also praised.
I'm sure I'm embarrassed
Umm
The same goes for the comment section of the previous song.
Everyone is very accepting
I feel like there is no one there.
that's why
That's also something
The atmosphere of this Wakame stream
I think it has become
Thank you very much
Acceptance system
thank you
It's definitely nice to see the group grow bigger.
Therefore, I will follow the spirit of "I might be able to drink"
is
surely
The first time I saw it was "Don't go home." The first time I saw it was "Don't go home."
Welcome!
Of course, there are some people who are not seeing this for the first time.
Noda Dashi
You can stop sleeping, but sleep is the way to go.
Which one is it?
Chun-san Super Chasenkyu
thank you
Thank you.
There are
Thankyou
I'm commenting while I'm sleeping
I'm going to sleep
It's hard to sleep
I realized that I was going to sleep, that's ginger
There isn't.
It's a nice gift. Thank you.
Falling asleep is also Yamanashi. The delivery time is like that.
Entering Amehashi Poker, where sleeping is even more difficult.
Welcome back
Thank you for the super chat, Hachimitsu-san
I felt like I was being called to the goods.
Ta
I bought it because my birthday was July 9th.
It's late, but it's my birthday
I'm looking forward to receiving it thank you
Happy Birthday
happy birthday
I hope it will be a good year thank you
I write with all my heart, handwritten.
Senkyu
Thank you Rival
Thank you for the snack money
Mugen green peppers looked really delicious.
Do you have any cooking skills?
I can't imagine the taste of dragon fruit either.
It was delicious, and above all else.
Seaweed bra is so nice
A beautiful woman wearing white clothes and a cute navy blue hat
Fixed ribbon and long skirt
It's very Oceanic. Wait a minute.
Armpits without costume type
On your way home
Thank you, but I really like the bra outfit.
It'sin
cute
Pollution is noticeable
I went to watch the broadcast today Yes.
Thank you for coming.
Please come anytime
That's right.
The original neatness is oozing out
thank you
It does look a bit like an adult, isn't it?
Thank you very much
I'm happy
Thank you Funsan
Thank you Akemi-san
Thank you thank you
Thank you Mr Johnson
You don't know the meaning of neat
Well, I guess I've never looked it up in a dictionary.
Thank you, Taro Grasshopper
Akemi Karukino with seasonal level 691
Mr. Sanyamashi
thank you
Talk about how to take a photo of gratitude during a chat
It was interesting
Maybe she's worried about her head after all.
size
Thank you
Dragon Fruit Pikmin looks strong
There's a Pikmin boom coming now.
I have a segment bone, I have one.
I have it I have it
I haven't pulled back much though.
I don't use my personal dictionary much.
I want to make a new Pikmin game that looks as good as Pikmin.
I'm thinking of doing for
When the retail version comes
difficult points and pikmin
03Thank you
Thank you Mikami-san
Senkyu
Pikmin 4
It's my first time playing Pikmy, but I hope it's okay.
The trial version is coming, but...
I can'twait
Try the trial version
I have to wait about a week from 21 degrees for release.
Don't go
I can't wait
I forget the operation
[music]
body temperature
You seem like the type who wants to do it all at once.
Red Pikmin, which is difficult to learn if you don't remember its characteristics, turns into fire.
I'm strong
blue pikmin
[music]
Water resistant
gold pikmin is
Don't drown
blue pikmin
yellow pink gummy
It's electricity
High Flying Friday Pikmin
purple pikmin strong
[music]
Where is Pikmin?
Fly high and resist electricity
Also in pink
Crybaby
But that
Poison Pikmin
towards the enemy
I want to throw it and feed it something.
I'm gonna cry
I'm crying
sacrifice
Will you be a sacrifice?
[music]
Tears are running low
It seems like it's a last resort.
cruel world
It's the prey of the weakest
Isn't that a naive tactic?
Playing Pikmi for the first time seems like a lot of fun.
But
I think I'll try my best.Not much lately.
It's a long story
Because I wasn't on an adventure.
Shall we go on a trip?
With Pikmin
Thank you ordinary people
Camera work Both rolls are delicious
It looks like you got it, and above all, congratulations on the bingo.
thank you
I'm glad you enjoyed it thank you
Masu
Thank you for the chair book.
Thank you, eat infinite green peppers and get bingo
Congratulations on your achievement!
thank you
Thank you for your hard work in recording. Thank you.
It was really hot recording.
Very
I wiped my sweat with a tissue
Something
It's not like I'm sweating though
I feel a slight pain in my forehead
Something about sweat
It's not so much that it flows though.
I'm sweating slowly
air conditioner
I might have turned it off while filming.
Because it was a very hot day
Over there
I don't bring it
[music]
I wiped it with a tissue
But I got quite a lot.
I've been filming a short video.
hey
various
From around August
I wish I could give it to you, but that's why
From now on Saturday and Sunday
every day from morning
A short video for me
It might go up, but it's really short.
It's really only a few seconds short though
various
I think you can see 3D seaweed.
Let's try our best today too
[music]
Something
It's because I'm sleeping
There is though
It's like a one-off story
What is today's wakame?
[music]
I took it for various reasons.
Look forward to it
In a loose manner
I haven't decided on a time yet.
I'll try to give it a loose feel.
yes
Mr. Shapeshakin
Thank you super chasenkyu
There is
Congratulations on overcoming this, thank you
It's been a long time since I've had a real tie and it was fulfilling until the end.
I had a great holiday
3rd anniversary goods were also released the other day.
After it arrived, my house gradually started to be filled with Mr. Watabe.
The goal is the sheep room
I'm looking forward to the birthday commemorative goods.
More and more
It's getting hot, but please take care of yourself.
Please, by the way, what is ASMR?
Do you have any plans to do it someday?
Is this the age of big ASMR?
First of all, thank you very much for the goods.
Acousters and other things are difficult.
I think it's supposed to be
Thank you for arranging it
I'm happy, I'm sure it will sell after all
I'm happy, aren't I?
Something funny
I feel like you're looking for me
Thank you for your ASMR quote
I want to do it again, but not yet.
I haven't decided on a date.
[music]
Next
Anniversary or something
Should I do it?
KU100 minutes
[music]
I want to try something like amber sugar.
Eat sweets
Sweets that make ASMR sounds
buy a lot
Please stop in case of sudden defection.
A lot of exchanges and public release
It's embarrassing, isn't it?
Open to the public
It's hard to be embarrassed
Something like that
Anyone can see it
It's no good.
Even humans haven't come that far.
Something
Feels good
I feel like I'm okay here, so I'll do my best today too.
hand
That's great. Well, it's good to hear, but I'm
I feel like doing it.
I like listening to it though.
I'm embarrassed to say that I'm embarrassed
I don't remember that happening
I don't remember what happened, it was weird
There wasn't
[music]
Something
I feel tingly
What does it feel good?
ear cleaning
Let's make it beautiful
hand
Non-existent memories
It's mostly because of the storm.
I'll do it then
[music]
I'm kidding
I can't do it because I'm embarrassed.
ASMR horror all back
What I would do in general if I had the courage to do it
But it's pretty rare.
Power supply ASMR is rare, even once in general.
I've never done it before.
I'm thinking of doing it again with humans soon.
Even in Senkyu, vocally
I've been told a lot that it's a good match.
Hmm
Thank you very much Mr. Aruto.
Toe Senkyu
It's great to be able to eat it all
Thank you, I can change the picture diary whenever I feel like it.
Let's go
I'm good at drawing and it's different
Hey, I was told I was good at it.
Thank you very much for the square scroll altar.
I live in a space surrounded by Matome-san.
I'm happy every day because of that.
I bought quite a lot of goods other than that one again.
It's an image of you, but I'm sorry.
Thank you for banning me from the altar.
Well, I'm glad everyone decorated it.
Thank you very much
I feel the love
Everyone decorated it
thanks
room that can accommodate that much
I know what you want
[music]
It's already difficult just to have stuffed animals.
It became
Thank you for collecting more goods for me.
Thank you very much
More room for everyone
I'll fill it up
Thank you very much
Thank you Uchitoko
Senkyu
Thank you
I think it was difficult to prepare the camera etc.
Thank you for taking the plunge this time.
I had a great time
Thank you
Thank you Senkyu.
Quite a bit
to prepare
Although it may be a hassle or something.
But I'm glad I did it
After all, the camera is exciting.
sometimes
not much
Because I'm not used to it.
exciting
I won't allow rock-paper-scissors.
I'm always playing rock, paper, scissors like that.
strongest
This is what I got from the camera work.
It's superchar
thank you
If you look at it with a camera
I feel that way
Next is the prefecture
Thank you very much
Change thumbnail
Thanks for reading, that's it for today.
Well, let's do this for today.
It's a little rough.
Oisho
I really like the thumbnail of this
I like it
cute
Studying is no good
Her face that looks like she doesn't understand is cute
It's no good if you don't seem to understand anything.
Looks stupid
I can remember if it's okay because of the face
I can see Hatena
I'm stunned
It's no good if you barely understand
cute
thank you
Also, that's it.
Lately, Sawatame has been acting so violently.
the noise
I'm running though
I've been hearing some noise for a while now.
I'm curious about what's going on
It feels a little tingly, doesn't it?
I was kind of scared.
yes
Listen a little
I've been wondering about that for a while now
I wonder what it is
I'm not running like that. I wonder what's going on.
I'll have the management investigate.
Also, what are the specs of your computer?
Or is it?
Well, I already asked for it.
Because there were people who were worried about me.
I thought I'd say something
I'm in the middle of that consultation.I wonder what's going on.Other people are also here.
Maybe it's an app problem?
If it's not just for sleepiness
I'm sorry, it seems like I'm not a big fan at all.
No, that's not what I was worried about at all.
But the people who tell me that are my mother's
It seemed like there was no one to do it, so yeah
I didn't report it because I thought it was okay.
I thought it was a computer thing, but I'll tell you this time.
Because you gave me
I think that's how everyone sees it.
Then I got serious about asking.
Thank you very much for your help.
thank you
Unless you're the only one concerned about it
I'm worried about everyone watching.
I thought it would be nice if it didn't happen.
But
That's right, thank you for letting me know
Well, this is it
If you want to become more beautiful
If you want to look more beautiful to everyone, it's better to listen.
Okay?
thank you
more beautiful
But if there's some kind of noise running around,
It has a virtual feel.
Something
A bit cool like a hologram
I'm cool
Sheep from Virtual
Now that's our virtual wakame roll
There's something terrible happening in the world
to you
I came here to ask for help.
Cybership
Our world is in trouble right now
great adventure
[music]
There are RPGs
Anime is not interesting
That's yours
Hurry up and put on that G of VR.
Come to the world
Yeah
Don't let it get into the screen, okay, that's yours.
VR
If we have the device, is this the follow earth?
That kind of thing that looks like a crappy AI
That machine at my feet, that opportunity, somehow comes to mind.
Put it on
Maybe I can come when I turn on the power.
Fluffy
Maybe this is what it is
Could you please take a look?
That's sloppy
Second Nemunem
This is the second Nemu Nemuki.
Can you sleep?
Thank you again today
The first Nemunemuki from the end
Thank you very much today too
Today from 9pm
On Sora-chan's channel
I want to play there is a collaboration
After that
My throat seems fine
If you're fine
I think I'll do something from around 11pm.
Masu
I'll think about it after I wake up
thank you
Thank you very much for today
I want to do Astrong too.
Existing Characters
I want to touch something
That's called
I have feelings
I want to find a character that suits me
I think it's interesting because you have to do it.
There are some cute ones like Carrie.
[music]
I might end up with Zangief.
do not have
I'd like to try it.
If possible
15 or 17
Night fever almost
I'm thinking of doing it
Obatatsu-kun and me
Lalalalalala
bad
I want to dream
you and me
sweet happy
[music]
I think I'll try it
I was gradually drawn to it.
I think I'll give it a try.
Shall we sleep today?
thank you
Thank you very much
Also the voice training video
That was done
It was really hard
It was really hard.
Gigafile delivery on your smartphone
Download that and do it
Download by sending the URL to your computer
It was easy until
It's not over
The video is called MOV.
extension
And its size is huge.
MP cannot be converted using the usual conversion method.
to 4
So how do I convert it?
Search from MOV to MP4 size
search
conversion search
Check it out
I can't do this either, even if I can't do it
It was super easy
It was really easy, something on the computer.
I heard that you were able to convert it completely with the one that was included.
The time it took to get there was tough.
It took
There's a lot of information coming out.
Which one is easiest and which one is best for me?
Is it suitable?
Is it better to pay or something?
I was confused though
Convert it to MP4 somehow
Video on
Add a thumbnail or something
I installed it and managed to get started.
After that home check is finished
I'll try to post as a human
That took up so much time
But I can do it now, thank you very much
Should I sleep?
Thank you very much for today
It was fun, thank you, come and see me today
Thank you, those who are going to sleep now
slowly
Please take a break from work, school, etc.
If you have something to do, wash your hands and stay healthy today.
Let's spend time together
Good night, let's meet at 9pm today.
rest
Gunnai Senki
Thank you very much
[music]
Thank you for today too
slowly
Rest me too
holiday
Good night