[Music]
um
uh
[Music]
my
um
[Music]
hello everybody
don't worry about it i'm worried all
right
what a lovely sight you have some nice
bones
[Music]
okay it's like one day what a legend
today we're playing
don't starve together and if you guys
don't know the objective of the game you
should reread the title because it's in
the title we're supposed to
starve pretty much we're just supposed
to see how
long we can survive for and that
involves uh
foraging for stuff crafting not getting
lost
and working together as a team as you
can see we've already had some dust here
over on the
and right my job a little too well i'll
try my best to guide them
but i don't know yeah i was born with
the most experienced playing this game i
think
they're a little fragile
oh this is a dog and i found
it's so cute i've never seen this before
it comes with it comes with my character
what's up
[Music]
so pretty much you just spread out we'll
find stuff you gotta find carrots and
mushrooms and when it gets dark we can
go back to the sponge it's getting dark
if you look up at the top at the top
right corner you can see there's a
little red section that's just like the
twilight
that's like a sunset it's not dark dark
yeah okay yeah okay
it's not dark dark it's just uh dark
almost
dark yeah it's just dark it's not dark
though
you guys we can all go in the same
direction it looks like we're going
north so
if you get really hungry you can collect
these seeds on the ground and you can
eat them
mushrooms you gotta cook before you eat
them uh or else you'll get sick
and if you collect this oh it is never
mind
sorry my bed i like my character he
looks like um like a tim burton
character like someone that johnny depp
would play
oh you're talking about the lantern oh
the pumpkins those are pretty useful so
like you can use them for
like torches the torches are really
important if you want to travel at night
oh what is this oh wait okay these guys
are aggro they're aggro
no don't go near them uh so so what
happens
like around day 14 or so there will be
wolves that will try to come attack us
and we have to fight them so we have to
find wood we gotta find trees uh we
gotta find sticks we gotta find rocks
the basics okay
okay yeah it's like minecraft yeah
uh if you guys find it's rocks and also
[\h__\h]
yeah um the poop you can use to make
farms with to fertilize your crops
oh of course it's innovative
give me this cry oh my god uh i think
this is like a peninsula thing i don't
think there's anywhere to go up here
okay we'll go back down we gotta go back
down anyways to get into the spawn
what is this you can catch a bird and
eat it but sometimes it'll only give you
feathers instead of giving you meat
feathers shadowy creatures what can i do
with binoculars
oh
attack we can hide there and then
they'll like attack them and then
they'll fight back
sorry bubba's outside
my uh my johnny depp character is saying
i'm so hungry
uh oh oh i have berries for you we'll
we'll meet at the spawn
oh we can share our resources
okay hold up we'll go the skeleton is
still just here
all right here's berries for whoever is
really hungry
okay we're gonna die okay bye
everybody's on their own
[Music]
i'm dead on the first day i got confused
on the first
[Applause]
[Music]
if you go to the spawn beacon and you
click on it uh
you can't oh you had six dudes yeah i
did
we're supposed to make a fire oh i got
it i'll come i'm gone
away okay i think we're gonna keep going
no no no it's okay
we're okay i got fire i didn't know we
had six
the next time when you guys have sticks
and flint you just find it right on the
floor you can make a torch
okay oh okay
oh my gosh you can eat raw carrots
that's a good thing
oh and picking flowers if you find any
flowers that'll help your brain juice
oh brain juice cool uh i need a bit of
wait
we lose all our stuff yeah but you gotta
pick it up it's on the floor you can
pick it up
oh minecraft it was like where we died
[Music]
and if you pick up twelve flowers you
can make a flower hat
also cool i want a flower hat
and it's how much you're saying a little
johnny character
you look nice in a flower a flower hat i
think
they have to be the same flower oh no
they just be annie
you guys just explore and then uh i'll
make a vase for us so
we don't hide when it turns night again
[Applause]
[Music]
oh i'm bringing company i got coffee
how many are we talking how many i think
they got boy
i think he went i wonder how we make
weapons
let's see weapons fight it's under fight
you can make a spear
so if you collect a grass but i need to
make i need to make a
a science machine wait what okay i'm
gonna go back to the display i've got
seeds don't eat seeds
you can think of this rabbit to come
over to our country
i guess we need to find our audience
back home uh
guys i might so loud to you now because
my audience said i'm too quiet but maybe
i'm too loud for you guys now i'm still
saying
to me i'm good to me perfect now yes
okay
okay where did everyone
if you find uh like a twig bush it's
like a little thing sticking up on the
ground
how do i kill a rabbit uh you have to
catch it so if you make grass
when you take grass you can make a trap
and then you can trap the rabbit and you
can kill it with your bare hands
cool i make grass oh you gotta you want
to collect the grass any grass you find
i have the bread
okay i'm gonna make uh what we need now
if any of you guys have flint and sticks
you can make an
axe and start collecting wood and then
with the wood
we can make a machine that can make us a
bunch more stuff
so we can survive i don't i i have an
empty elixir do you need that
uh it kind of sounds useless
all right i'll go back to exploring
[Music]
how do you pronounce that faux fangs
i think it's yeah that sounds like a
halloween costume thing
no no no
[Music]
are these pigs nice uh there are nice
pigs actually some
some don't attack you and they can be
your friends get saddened i got
carrots i'm scared
usually pigs are like carnivores so you
gotta give them something
yeah okay hello all right i'll make the
base here
we got berry bushes i should have
collected more rocks i need
all right i'm giving you guys a job
who's here this guy
i'm here hello okay you you take that
you you guys collect the wood
you too go chop down some trees
oh there's a turkey i light the turkey
on fire
oh okay can i come in can i will they
let me in their house
uh no that you can't go in the house i'm
gonna drop torches at the spawn for you
guys okay or i'll drop
one torch uh you guys take care of
yourself i think i have
i think i have a light ah oh yeah if you
have a lighter
you uh might be able to use it okay
i'll stick with inna then oh okay okay
okay if you guys have
any twigs and foot you can make your own
torch too yeah
what does what does the flower do uh
when you pick up a flower
it increases your sanity so it's good
and you can also use it to make a hat
it helps your sanity
on the ground right oh yeah yeah you can
get it from rocks too
uh if you make a pickaxe you always get
flip from rocks
okay i'm gonna i think i have enough to
oh
i need two pieces of wood and six more
rocks to make
where is that permanent fire
who is that ghost oh is that that's like
your friend that's like your i think
it's supposed to be like your dead
sister or something
hey look there's something in the ground
oh there are many things oh they're
sticks
what the hell race dirt over here
[Laughter]
what is that
i can build a campfire so i'm going to
go back to the base and i'll build a
campfire there
you guys go back to the spot and fight
near this yeah let's go back let's go
back
if you follow the path you walk away way
faster
i see it now yeah
[Music]
oh you had friends can i eat this
mandrake
happy birthday you can't but it'll put
you to sleep oh no i think you have to
kill it
i don't nice wait watch it do you need
anyone else
you can turn that off uh because you'll
run out of fuel and you're lighter i
think
i don't get it also you can cook stuff
here so if you have
like a mushroom or you can cook seeds
they give you more
more i have carrots
you want carrots you can cook carrots
you just uh
hold it click it in your inventory and
then click on the fire with it
in your mouth
wakey wakey nice now you guys can also
see
you can switch orientation of your
character too
uh-oh okay everybody sticks together
oh no i think we're just gonna say about
the fire right oh my god
the shadow scared me that the shadow of
the tree scares me
i have one here i'll just drop what i
have because i don't know what it does
okay yep we got a glove
there's a monkey paw what does that do
uh
who wish i don't know actually i don't
know what that does oh maybe chad can
tell us
[Music]
usually the night time cooking elixir
oh i have you cooked berries uh
i think you can you can cook pretty much
everything i'm
clean i have butterfly wings
carrots here decorations for the
butterfly wings
oh i was about to cook you're over the
fire drop
if you press if you press q and e oh
somebody gave me carrots
[Music]
uh you can make healing potion but uh
it's a bit difficult so like
if you find a spider web you want to you
want to collect
spider web from the spider nest and uh
it's kind of dangerous but once you
build
traps out of grass you can catch the
spiders and they give you spider web and
use that to make a fishing rod
and you catch fish and then the fish
make they make good heel
snacks oh eat them and they heal you
yeah
i got binocular fun oh binoculars that
sounds really good
useful i don't think that i don't think
you can use it
yeah i don't think oh
she just died i saw that it was
[Music]
uh so yeah you're probably in the swamp
areas in the swamp area if you walk by
too slow uh there are tentacles in the
ground that'll get your stuff
they'll hit you maybe not what the heck
what is that
well what what is
do you guys have any wood has anybody
collected some wood
yeah i have a pen i have ten
oh okay i'll two i'll take some i'm go
i'll go back to the spotlight we were
friends
tentacles here okay
what is this great hand
what a hand stage hand
it's like a table with some flowers
around it oh uh don't touch don't take
the flower
don't take the flower but i did i did
take a flower yeah
okay maybe it's okay yeah
i'm like am i curious i think you're
sanity so if you check your brain
here at the top you should be able to
see whether your sanity is going down
actively and if it is it might be that
the thing you picked up
it uh it's not good for your head i
think
okay there's a frog on my tail
so wait okay stomach okay brain
yes what is the other one uh
what stomach brain and health so much
more no not november
i can plant a tree i found nuts
some of the tree nuts you can eat them
but sometimes if you don't plant the
seeds
okay bad things will happen uh bad
things
yeah i have to pick them up but i have a
full lemon
[Music]
i brought you some wood oh thank you i
already got some
um but i'll pick it up if you just leave
it there nothing will do spawn like
minecraft so if you just put it on the
ground
let's stay there forever i'll put your
lighter by the
uh by the base
[Music]
as well no you gotta make a pickaxe and
in the chocolate
no it's pretty easy i bet you have
enough to make it it leads to my new
friend
what freeze gimme
no goddamn why did the rabbit sound like
you died
[Music]
a turkey i found a big turkey kill it
i'm getting ready to catch with oh yeah
i won't give up
i'm used to chasing things with sharp
objects uh-oh
see we have a fire at the base if you
guys get there and uh
there's no fire you just put grass or
wood or anything you can burn in
in the fire and it'll it'll like oh
oh that big voice is going okay i could
really
fellas are the pigs dangerous
uh the ones who try to attack you are
dangerous
there are some nice pigs okay
you'll know right away actually the pigs
if you give them like a
piece of meat to eat they'll be your
friend and they'll trap they'll chop
trees for you oh
we'll have a sweet of them this is where
the basement
you guys are standing near this science
machine i made here you see that new
tabs appeared
on the left side so now you can make
like rope you can refine
you can make rope you can use that to
make traps and you can catch bunnies and
spiders and frogs
here's an episode of dr stone nice going
watson
probably is literally carrying yes
i was going to say thank you amelia most
helpful
welcome oh wow
anybody want some trap you can use that
and you just
you just put it down on the ground and
it'll like be automatic
okay i'm gonna go catch some rabbits
it's gonna get dark soon
just be careful all these times
okay oh kyrie
okay
yeah i have some i have five [\h__\h] huh
here we go
there buy [\h__\h] i think jamaica to
make farms well
you need the seeds that you get and then
stones and fertilizer but
uh oh yeah right here food you can just
make one here oh yeah we have enough i
love
that our camp is just surrounded by
skrellingtons and things
actually we can't destroy the skeletons
you can it feels like home
i like decorative
yeah they're a reminder of our humble
beginnings how about that
what but
oh a backpack you can make it uh uh you
gotta refine your rope
and then i think it's under survival you
can make uh
uh yeah it's under survival you can make
it
not the candy bag no it might be grayed
out because you might not have enough
sticks or grass
i guess it's not rope it's just uh just
grass
i think there's a more advanced backpack
you can make with that
can you make things like chess oh in
this instance
yeah you can make chests okay cool
[Music]
i saw i'm hot the night is gonna
progressively get longer
and longer and so you just have to
survive you can kind of still explore at
night if you have like a torch or
something
uh but it's better to just stay here and
cook or sleep you can make a sleeping
bag and sleeping at
in the night time it increases your
insanity levels if you're getting low
okay okay
i think my salary levels are always low
yeah some characters
[Music]
if anybody ever wants to sleep there's a
sleeping bag here but it's better not to
do it now because it's going to turn day
time and you'll wake up immediately but
you can do it when it's in the red the
sunset time
you can sleep then too
all right i'll work on i'm trying to
heal if you guys want to find stuff if
you find any spiders
you can trap the spiders you can fight
them
and then we can use the spiderweb and
we'll go fishing
okay video bye bye
all right we'll meet up again at night
okay
sounds good i'll go follow you i'll go
do some more
things
do you have a trap i do
put it down anywhere around the pond and
then go near that frog and make it
aggressive
okay and now go to the frog and like
tease him you want to taunt him
and and then he'll follow you and you
lead him in
and you can cook it and eat them oh
yummy
not raw though you don't want to eat
them wrong
listen get them
eat some food well i ended up
yeah we gotta make a chest and like
store food in there or something because
yeah oh god you have seeds here eat
seeds you're a bird you can eat seeds
but i prefer fried chicken you know
so i don't think there's any chicken in
this game but there are turkeys pretty
similar yeah i did see one
side of streaming i saw a turkey you
can't run i've cornered him
i've cornered oh no yeah turkey's scary
no it's in the water
no it's in the water i made one you can
probably use it
guys if it's in the water it's in the
water
next to the the sea oh and
no fish it's not for you pick up soggy
drumstick no it's not for you
i keep running towards the water and
it's not letting me pick up
oh uh yeah you can't go into the water
unless you have a boat
sorry kelly want your hardware you can
make boats yeah you can make boats and
we can like sail the sea but
it's pretty dangerous so i don't think
we're ready for that
pick it yet as long as we have good eye
the sea is not dangerous for us oh
that's true
exactly it's pretty cool because like
somebody has to control the anchor and
somebody has to control like the
steering wheel and somebody has to
control like the sail or something and
many ah twigs
desperately need food goddammit uh okay
i'll go back i'll have i have some food
we should we should make them huh we
should make a crock pot
we gotta burn trees a crock pot yeah
and you can you can put four ingredients
in there you can make all these like
different
recipes and stuff and then you can make
like cupcakes you can make meatballs
okay sandwiches and lasagna
fried turkey how about that right you
can't make a turkey meal i don't i think
you go you can make chicken nuggets you
can make chicken nuggets
really yeah but you need honey from bees
oh i just literally ate my honey oh it's
really good for heels so chicken nuggets
they give you like a lot of hp
i did it didn't though it did not yeah
not the honey by itself yeah ah okay
oh well oh we're gonna build something
now
nice
we want to make a functioning base we
gotta have like
a food source we gotta have somewhere to
store the food
and we gotta have defense stuff so if
you guys wanna like
uh you can just see your recipes and
stuff on the left side make whatever you
want
i'll help you find me i am not lost i am
not i got the monster
god are you lost i am not already back i
think
oh yeah you're here you're here yeah i
find it tentacle
there you go wait oh but then
i forgot how to shift oh control
[Music]
[Applause]
maybe i have something useful for you uh
i have a bunch of
rocks and it's really useful oh dear
maybe i should keep them here uh
and you can use it to build stuff if you
want
huh are you okay good uh
oh we're back
okay we're good uh if anybody wants to
sleep if you're if your brain juice is
low you can pick up this sleeping bag
here and you can start sleeping now but
it'll take your hunger so you got to
make sure you got like a decent amount
or else you'll wake up i'm hungry
i think i'll wait with that and not do
it right now yeah
i'm really lonely i didn't notice how
hungry i was
i do have one uh chicken leg though wow
nuggets
i think uh i ate some bad meatballs
didn't know i had said something so
useful the whole time
i can make a compass is that useful
we're in the picture
i don't think so i mean we have a we
have a map so it's not it's not we don't
need it
it made
why are these lanterns lit up are they
always were they always lit up
no i put them there a moment ago oh nice
why is the game audio getting louder is
that is something
i hear something too
oh i can't hear the flies from the poop
hey yeah
let's pick that up there we go
[Laughter]
i was like those flies are really loud
it's really annoying really
oh cal do you have any wood i can make
chests we can put some stuff
away i have a ton of i have logs
yeah yeah yeah there you go thank you
wow welcome i did a lot of chopping
today
okay we have i think i have enough to
pick one now thank you
bro okay let's put the chest over
pick up flowers where are flowers oh
uh there there are some flowers down
south
and to okay east also
okay it's still not nice right now right
it's still twilight yeah it's about to
turn it's about
night yeah
if you guys guys ever have any wood you
can add
uh you can add uh planks to it and it'll
like
make this big fire like this oh i have
planks i can make a i can make a chest
does anybody do we need another
challenge to die oh yeah the chest the
chest don't you don't have them
can i come meet you
there's a table following me the table
where it took the flower from
a table
where are there you are
uh did the table follow me though i
don't think so no
i don't i don't see it what are you
talking about it wasn't there
it wasn't there i'm not crazy
[Music]
yeah actually if you make a camera you
might be able to
yeah desk oh that's what the yellow was
i was burning
i was burning myself alive i didn't
realize oh
you're standing in the fire yeah i
didn't know that
getting nice and warm really close to
the fire would do that funny
i get i have a job for you come here oh
okay
come down here where's the flower i'm
really looking like johnny depp take
this don't equip it yet but take it
all right don't wait don't equip it
and now i want you to come over here
equip it and set these
these scraggly trees on fire oh
but of course
i need the chocolate baby
disco oh i'm happy you finished that
yes
[Music]
what a waste of wood yeah you're telling
me you can catch
fries you know have you have you tried
that before i can show you how that
works
oh yes
so if you find a frog by a pond you just
put the trap down anywhere near the frog
and then you
you bait the frog into into walking into
the trap
i look perfect now i can't show you
wow my ghosts are so smart they killed
it killed my my frogs for me
oh yeah the ghost will attack your stuff
like
enemies enemies i love my ghosts my
ghost is amazing
flint nice why does that feel something
thank you i think so too [\h__\h] good
where did i even get my ghost from i
don't know why don't i mean you don't
have the clothes right
uh i love crystal balls question kiara
you don't you don't have
you play the same character but you
don't have the ghost right oh yeah
because uh
if you there's like a flower in my
inventory and if i click on it i can
summon the ghost but i have i just
haven't done it yet i probably should
wait hungry found a bunch of good stuff
need one more flower to make a hat
yeah let's all get matching flower hats
how's
[Music]
but my hunger is still uh not very good
looking
yeah i'm making crock pots now so we can
make more stuff wait nina did you want
me to show you how to catch the froggies
oh no i i think i thought
nice try a loser that's a really daring
looking giraffe come on
what was that again what is this
i don't know why is all the audio
getting louder
is something am i dying uh
that might be sanity what's your sanity
level set up
which one is that a brain hover over the
brain with your mouse i'll tell you a
number
30 30 oh okay uh where are you come to
me
i'll give you a present
makes me sleep i found a man drafter oh
yeah you can kill it but
yeah it'll make you sleep if you eat it
i mean i kind of do need to clean uh
here you go
thank you you're welcome and i'll make
i'll make you work i'm making food we
need like we need to kill rabbits we
need to kill frogs
and we start to fill the crocodile with
make meatballs make some weapons oh i
have uh
i have some mushrooms yeah yeah yeah any
vegetables or like carrots you find
that's really useful my carrots i'm kind
of looking
hot i just need like a few more twigs
and i can make one i need three more
tweaks nobody have twice
i i have five ways thank you
useful i'm just you're welcome just a
kiss
by the way if you guys should click or
control click on something uh you can
have
it and then like oh okay that's
cool how big is this map like
this is uh yeah it's pretty big you
gotta move your dog in this side
oh sorry somebody pick up this what is
this on the ground
crystal ball thingy i see it right no
thank you
maybe i can't put it on the path
all right now if you fill the crock pot
uh usually like it's
as long as you don't put anything in
edible in there it should make
something except for monster meat
if you put too much monster meat in
there mine is it chester
oh chester yeah i thought that yeah wait
who found chester
you that's not mine is that goodness
i don't know what did you pick up a bone
do you still need some twigs oh no i
have a ton
what thanks okay what's the gesture
okay there's no fun oh we can cook it
there now okay yeah yeah so if you put a
bunch if you can put like different
vegetables and stuff together
there's like different recipes it
doesn't tell you the recipes
but i'm dying why are you dying i don't
know
sorry i can't
what should we do i'm very hungry as
well uh wait
do we have anything cooking okay i'll
make something with you here come here
oh okay yes chef yeah
i'm just gonna put monster meat in there
oh the monster means
oh is anybody happy now what is it maybe
i can cook it
okay maybe i'll just put i'll just make
four carrots
oh you guys can cook your seeds give you
a little bit more power
if you're cooking yourself does it give
you back more
more hunger oh maybe not actually i
think it does i
think it does what i was looking at was
hp
how do you make weapons because i feel
like if i had a weapon
yeah then i could kill a bunch of things
and get us a bunch of meat actually
there's a sphere right here on the floor
i don't know whose this is but
you see this spirit i'm standing next to
it you can pick it up and you can use
that you can equip it you can attach
them
cool okay let me see how i tried who's
who's the hungriest right now what are
you what are you guys
hunger levels 55 55
what's the one next to her i think it's
stuck in the skeleton
oh okay i make a uh i'm sleeping
need rocks to make a hammer does anybody
have rocks
let's go oh i see i see the rock i see
i'm gonna take your rocks
i'm feeling refreshed i stopped like
really well
damn and i have full hunger now
here it is okay i can get you that oh
hey let's go wire to have you make
everything watson no it's okay
[Music]
i promise i'll kill a bunch of players
oh oh it's nice
yeah it's gone never mind i think i
think i can make you a spear though
where do i go okay ah yeah i can make
you one
i just need grass
i'm going for bottom left oh i'm super
hungry let's see uh what can i eat
we jumped over my job
who sees noise noise
you perfect i'll go kill some things
welcome here we go
will they will they kill me for doing
that i wonder
um man i need to go
no leave my ghost alone come with me
ghosty
wait so the stuff everything like
respawns every day
uh not every day there's like a cycle
some depending on what it is it might
take a few days to come back
yeah not every day yeah oh
what the hell
ah there you go since when are frogs so
dangerous
yeah they take items from you too when
they attack you
oh you're joking
i found the factor nest um ah did you
make
the pig is so nice to try to kill the
spiders for me
uh he killed maybe one i got some silk
oh
nice yeah we can use that to make up
stuff
i probably shouldn't try to kill the
spiders on my own right it's probably
gonna
uh you don't have to kill them you can
you can make uh the flower traps
sorry i don't always have flour you can
make the grass traps and then you can
uh put them down on the ground and then
walk into the traps
and they'll they'll jump into it i
killed them oh i killed
all the spiders you killed oh with your
ghost
no with my ghost and my pickaxe i got
like a bunch of meat and
spider webs and silks be careful with
the meat because
that meat you have to you can put like
one in each recipe in the crock pot
otherwise it'll make you sick okay
hey uh amelia how does one make a trap
ketchup
you need uh grass and twigs and then you
gotta go
next to the science machine in the base
got it okay i think that's maybe the
next thing i gotta try and do yeah
how do you catch a rabbit do you just
put the track down yeah you gotta
it's kind of hard to catch one because
like they're so fast but what you can do
is uh you wanna put the trap stand on
the hole and then put the trap like
right on the hole so then when they go
back in and when they come out
they they trigger the trap and they run
into it
damn
it's in big trouble because i'm super
hungry right now i'm trying to catch
these rabbits but
uh yeah it's really bad catching rabbits
is more of like a long-term thing
like uh you can't catch them right away
you probably have to come back and
check on the trap like a day later i go
like a real trap
hunting
it's fine i'll find other things to kill
if you find um spiders you can kill
those you can kill frogs
the turkeys moles
there's like little mole wrap thingies
oh that mushroom is happy too look at
that he came
back home there's so many spiderman
i'm gonna die can we eat spiders
i have spiderman yeah oh but we have to
cook it in the recipe
yeah i'm going back now
and we can cook some stuff so we can all
eat
let's have a dinner tonight my ghost
keeps like putting up a fight with these
spiders but it's
like killing everything legitimately wow
[Music]
okay uh i'll make food now thank you
chef
the mandrakes are really good they like
give you i didn't know they give you
full hp
and full house yeah sleep it's so good
it helped me up completely
that's open
[Music]
okay callie when this thing comes out of
the crock pot you can eat it
you next i'll
actually kill a bunch of things you'll
see okay
you'll see
wait did my frog sandwich
some sort of sandwich thank you oh it's
a teddy bear i was wondering what that
was that was
whoa
my sanity is dropping it's not too loud
always picking a fight abigail
can we just live in happiness together
with these creatures
i wonder if there's a way to like
unsummon the ghost because i
know you have to summon it i don't know
if it'll ever go away though you must be
awake
if you guys ever need more stories you
can pick up this bone and
this little chester guy this little
monster doggie
he'll follow you and if you click on him
he has a storage
oh yeah rock
oh nice i got tools now baby
progress baby all right so if uh
i can give you guys some tasks if you're
like what should i do
what should i do okay you know i'll give
you some tests
uh your task is to go collect a bunch of
rocks
and there's a rock area if you go to the
east
and then and you go south yeah there's
a whole rock area i don't know if you
can see it on the map but
it's like a desert looking area you can
collect all those rocks and we can
oh yes okay uh
how do we boost our sanity again fish
right something like this
uh boosting sanity you have to sleep but
if you
are hungry then uh you'll wake up
immediately or
you can collect flowers but man picking
flowers really helps with your sand if
you find any
oh okay i have mine but there's a
there's a sleeping bag it'll be in the
chest
oh i'm sleeping once okay good well
uh is it when as soon as it reaches
morning you'll wake up so you wanna
next time when you sleep you sleep in
the red time
uh at the start to get as much out of
the sleeping bag as possible we can make
more those are really easy to make
it looks like it could be something uh
delicious
it's time to kill things check out the
butterfly if you guys collect any
vegetables or mushrooms or berries those
are things
that you can put in a crock pot or a
mushroom
yeah you just make it'll make like
meatballs if you have two meats in there
and those are really
healing
oh wait how do you put it got that
cheese
i'm going to put that in the crock pot
not my mouth
oh i think we might uh be getting
attacked soon i thought i heard a wolf
health
does it happen to look like a giant
teddy bear
yes
[Music]
you guys are getting attacked by wolves
run north follow the path north and
go into the beefalos and like stand
between them and they'll
kill them i need more berries
[Music]
okay
yeah so you guys just come come up north
follow the path and
run into the beefalo you'll be safe okay
can we kill the wolves yeah you can
attack them
if you have wood too you can make armor
or you can make grass armor too i'll
make some grass you guys don't have
time oh they're they're coming
it's armor huh okay i can make that oh
god this is so bad oh
dear oh run gonna hide us wait what is
what is that noise the
the room oh the wolves when they start
attacking you guys just run north
i made i made two fishing rods if
someone wants to have one i'll put it
over here
[Music]
oh my god
sometimes
[Music]
thank you for protecting me
i had like two wolves running up to me
but my ghost protected me
and now i'll go fishing all right kelly
i stole it
[Music]
are you still alive you know oh it's the
wolves
[Music]
should i fish anywhere or should i go to
fish somewhere where i see some shadows
in the uh you also want to fish in the
pond so we have upon
a uh pond pond pretty close to the spine
you'll see how it works it's just like
fishing okay
i'm coming back for my sky lizard are
you here inna
nice job kelly yeah that was interesting
you got food yeah so and when you make
the recipes in the crock pot you can
only put
oh no oh no i'm really not doing well
huh oh why is the earth shaking question
can i eat this you can eat seeds these
seeds
why are there meteors uh in certain
areas it's certain areas there's
immediate
oh no i guess the moon
only fish in ponds okay wasn't that a
pond actually one of the really
small ones right here really small okay
okay
one thing i gotta get the berries so i
can make more what was it
crock pot oh yeah yeah yeah in the crock
oh no there are wolves at the campsite
watch out should i come to kill them yes
i'll use my ghost
behind chester finally because he's
[Music]
you
there's free ghosts now what the hell oh
[Music]
back can you cook never mind that's a
stupid question
you can put sticks in food but it'll
it'll change into something less
uh filling like only one stick you can
put
oh okay
can't still light up the crock-pot oh i
think it just goes automatically once
you put enough stuff in it
ah there we go no oh who put in those
carrots
is it
i can make a shovel what should i make i
can make a pitchfork i can make a raisin
why would i save my face though my face
is perfect
that's a long shadow i think you can
shave your beard and like put it
oh who has the little house right now
no freaking glue yes please
[Music]
we're talking about armor you want armor
no i want the skins
but also armor and i still don't
understand how i can make it back what
exactly do i need because it doesn't
lock up
i only pop what is that it's a hand
that's trying to grab our fire
what's the lore chad what is the lore
there is no lore find me
i wonder what we need the lord they say
is don't
uh we need to build an alchemy machine
but to build an alchemy machine
we need electric dudettes and you can
get those by like smashing
sometimes you might just find them but
you gotta like smash some stuff that you
find like that
there's like really weird gear stuff you
can you can make a refrigerator in this
game but
i don't remember how to get all the
materials for it
because your food your food has a shelf
life it will go bad
not nice
i oh not let you get away
come on baby girl faster
stupid
stupid piece of [\h__\h] oh my
barry i eat you with berries that's how
it's supposed to be
oh my god there's so many frogs here
wait where is everyone i am i am
in rockland i'm in frogland
okay stay hydrated how do we stay
hydrated in this game
i got it did you also just get a super
cat saying stay hydrated
at the same time they're telling us to
stay hydrated how sweet of them thank
you
hi thank you i need to drive the rabbits
away from where the holes are
okay i'm making a bunch of food all
right have you caught any fish science
machina
i want to get another foot so i can get
a pickaxe
huh i have something
uh i'm kind of far oh okay okay yeah
you sure you'll find them in the same
area where like you would find flowers
why not oh morsel what is this
oh my god oh my god oh
my god there's so much stuff at the base
oh
so many frog legs oh my god
i got gold nuggets
pretty bad
[Music]
oh i'm fishing for the first time in my
life
nice oh i should go back got two rabbits
what are you doing i'm food
good burger i'm good
okay i have two gloves can i make
something now i have two abigail
chili uh i don't know you can do this
all right we're making rabbit tonight
baby
do you have any pickles yes i tossed my
grass so i could carry the usual
cloves why can't i cook them
i have this wait uh cook what i'm trying
to cook the rabbits that i killed but i
only have two
ah did you no i don't have anything to
put in there you need to fill the rest
of the slots it's got to be four so if
you have like berries or carrots or
mushrooms
one monster meat or one steak you can
put those in there
okay
[Music]
oh you can put it in the crock pot if
you want it'll make um
tasty meatballs
i really love meatballs now hungry i
don't know how the
how how does it work the fishing
yeah it says hook and then i click on it
one time on it
uh yeah yeah you uh put it in the pond
and then it's like there we go minecraft
or i haven't got it okay i never i never
even
fished in minecraft i got a fresh water
fish
i oh here i don't want to eat all these
meatballs
it has meatballs too okay
[Music]
okay living life on the
if we find edge spider glands we can
make like this
uh potion it's a healing potion oh we
need spider glands
allen do you need food am i good for now
i'm gonna wait till it gets real low and
then i'll eat my meatballs
yeah oh cool good idea i would catch
some more rabbits
that was fun
i brought some ice
make some easter eggs i think you can
make
like a you can use it in recipes i know
you can put it in the crock pot but
i don't know i think you might be able
to make a ice cream or like some sort of
drink with it too
you gotta have like the different
ingredients ice cream
yeah you can make cupcakes in this game
and uh you gotta like look up the rest
you gotta like google the recipes
saddle doesn't mean you can ride stuff
you can like uh
i don't know maybe i heard her now you
can ride a boat
it's [\h__\h] dead with a battleground
boober
yeah not with a saddle
yeah oh my god that was that was
funny-looking
no you did like a weird pose oh i messed
up
[Music]
it's a gorilla i'm just eating okay
gotta curse you're cute i'm trying to
not starve okay
unlike you understand about hey there's
nothing wrong with starving we all have
flower crowns
except for you kids
[Music]
i really want to grow the beard so i
really look like a real johnny
yeah you can also then you can shave the
beard and like
turn it into a jacket or something like
a vest
legendary all right so maybe
maybe we should build a boat if you guys
want to like work towards something we
can build a boat
idea yeah let's build a boat
okay actually i'm gonna go catch some
more rabbits but you guys talk about
building the boat well i'll go catch
these rabbits
[Music]
i just need i just need a bunch of wood
i need
planks oh okay
if we need a bunch of wood to make boats
so
as much wood as you can collect you like
chop the one yeah yeah
all right no that's my bad finally i
made a backpack
finally 10 years later
congratulations you just took me five
million years
bird trap who would ever make a bird
trap that's poor bird
that's how you down oh you're asking how
to get uh chicken that's how you get uh
some chicken you get a little uh
chicken legs from them no no no no
no that's not too much
oh wait i love the i love the chops down
there i wonder if anything got caught in
it
rip it down
how much wood do we need a bunch wood
you can get
yeah as much as you can carry
now we probably need like uh
uh probably like thirty or forty
five forty oh oh my goodness yeah we all
get like ten
that's not that bad yeah yeah
abigail go with me abigail
i should probably store some more things
i still got all my silk and spider
glands
oh i can humor wine glass is that for
the heart or for the hunger oh yeah yeah
it's for uh healing
it's for we can make like a healing
style for anybody who's low hp and you
just it's really easy you just need
rocks and ash and i have some ash so
oh yeah thanks for the drops on top of
the whole thing
that takes a long time yeah you can get
ash by burning down like little bushes
or grass or twigs anything you put on
the floor will probably turn into ash
oh do i burn it down with my torch yeah
i just want to make sure fire travels
like between things you got to make sure
like if you don't want to burn down the
forest or all of our stuff for example
you got to do it far away
oh it's gonna ask you there's like a
certain way to cut your fire doesn't
hurt me
no problem you just hold space you can
hold space and does it
teeth why does it take so long
they're fishing stop stop stop the
burning
oh yeah it takes a while bam
there's two rabbits i'm starting to be
good at that
catch a rabbit oh you caught a few
yep nice i have a rabbit trap here
you're kidding me
little things like uh like a grass bush
or if you have twigs you can you can
drop individual twigs
uh i think with a button
[Music]
i see okay i got the grass i don't
remember where i put my rabbit trap
oh no i think it you should you might be
able to see it on the map
maybe oh good good uh maybe i have it
i found did you find it oh no let me
give it back to you
that's what i've been using the whole
time to catch wrap
no it's totally fine
you can have the meatballs that we that
we make with them
rabbits like cotton you can have them
oh gosh i keep going the wrong way
i was just like man i really lose stuff
so easy
gosh here i'm dropping it on the ground
it's only got 25 left
if you want to catch more go for it i
don't know no
i don't even know how to use it really
um
[Music]
oh sorry oh you're good you're good do
your thing ena
your thing i'm glad you have enough
stuff to put inside the pot
yeah i just put a lot of berries in like
i like hunting because it's simple
and i can do it give me your wood here
sleep
yep
[Music]
is stone and wearing the potion in the
menu
oh the uh it's under survival under the
little rope
it's like at the top it's called healing
south
ah okay got it
whoa
good night
wow i'm like a professional survivor
[Music]
damn
my what the wood other one i have no one
for you
not doing so well i'm amazed with myself
i'm i think this is because my mom was
like a survivor mom so
i think i learned it from him i have a
survival mom
really she taught me the ways yeah she
can do anything
with with no tools she survives in the
in the wilderness
they're cool i really that's insane yeah
my mom is the survivor mom
she's like
[Music]
i don't know it's the third one four
three two one it's oh it's hunger
oh she's dead i was trying to
feed you all right i'll take your wood
dryer
okay rap chewy
i just thought you needed eggplant for
that
ah i think all right yep
oh god what is this music it's the hands
they're trying to steal our fire you
gotta step on them
okay okay hey that's worth you
hi yeah
oh the dude with the scissors i remember
when you showed me that and i was
absolutely terrified and
uh jeff is terrified by german fairy
tales oh my god
look there i have limits okay listen
i don't want these pinecones oh wait
it's interesting that things spoil in
this game too
yeah i gotta cook my monster meat god
damn it i need some
i haven't i have berries now put sure
i'll put
three berries in there
thank you yeah okay
okay i'm gonna look for a suitable place
to put
our water stuff i think this is no this
is not the ocean
what we might make another base by the
water because that's we're gonna put the
boat
wait do you have my wood i took it
it's mine very nice toilet can i leave
it at the base
i gotta try it i'm gonna build it i
don't know what it does
oh can just pick up land with it
i put one uh one meat in the pot if
someone wants to add a berries you can
make a crock pot
uh
i just need some stone and then i can
move stuff over
oh oh i'm on my way to get some snow now
now stop but yes don't you know are you
collecting some stones
oh yeah i have seven rocks oh can i have
some
yes i'm on my way back okay
i need my potion again
i'll survive because i have my ghosts
[Music]
yep
oh yeah i have i have a [\h__\h] ton of frog
legs i got 16
frog legs if someone needs food i i got
too much
oh you can make uh sam you can make frog
like sandwiches with those
in the carpet oh hell no
have you guys ever had real spock like
before
no no from what i've heard that just
takes a chicken i tried it once but it
was at like a really
uh shady buffet and it tasted really
close oh my god
i'm not surprised have you guys had
sure it was really frustrating oh snails
it look it was a frog like
it was a frog like yeah
i prefer fried chicken but okay you go
with what you like
right so what exactly do we need
to make a rock sandwich i got that if
you just put one frog leg in there
already i put berries you can make one
side
does someone want um some meat
like actual cooked meat
there's someone i'm okay for now but
maybe later maybe you should say
now melting ice oh
the meatballs are in the chest if
someone needs them
nah no darn it what is what is oh eyes
never mind i'm done
dad didn't even make a sandwich then
made the same thing as before
and sitting out of the game
no no darn it
that's it give me my trap i'll continue
i got so much more
that's the minute thank you
um so if i put four meats into the pot
will it still only make one meatballs
for everyone
uh yeah yeah so it's good to like uh
there's like a balance so if you put
like two meats and two vegetables it
should make meatballs but if you
put like too many vegetables and it'll
be like a vegetable based dish
but you can use filler like uh monster
meat you can put one monster meat in but
if you put more than one it'll turn into
like monster lasagna and it'll take away
hp
yeah and if you put a stick in there
it'll make a
like a kebab or something give up okay
unless it's fish then it makes fish
sticks
oh it's special let's just be honest
um i'm confused because i definitely
killed three things today and i only
have a one morsel in my pocket
okay what do we need to do anyway there
are two things in the pot so
and i was gonna make a boat but we're
not really close to the water so if we
made a boat it'd be like a long
i bet you know what i bet i was trying
to put them into the pot and i ate them
god
bite me don't see it
we're gonna go
[Music]
yeah you can yeah wow put him in
he's trying to make something oh it's
already cooking okay yeah as long as you
don't put anything like
weird in there it should make like some
sort of recipe
a lot today i don't know why
cute noises everywhere
hey balls
uh we have like stored meatballs here
too in the chest
hold on someone is at my is at my abode
i will be back in just a moment
okay i'll keep going don't die it's
getting night now
okay oh god i should go back oh my god
that's a full moon
okay oh it's still bright oh but
it's okay yeah yeah thank you oh
your sanity might go down but it won't
be too bad
oh thank god i'm too far away from that
anyway
ah there is an ocean it's to the north
we'd have to i have to make a new base
up there
do you have any more stone without all
the sun i have lots more spelling ponies
oh wow thank you this is more than
enough abigail
i choose you abigail your turn
[Music]
um
don't kill my ghost what i'm over here
oh oh yeah i can't look after my mother
i have no responsibility for what they
do so question when we make the
meatballs does it make one for everyone
or is it just one meatball yeah it's
just it's just
one set of meatballs it's like one dish
that's terrible that makes me
sad we should have enough for everyone
well there's some extra meatballs in the
chat so if
people get hungry they got food there
yeah okay well i'm gonna go
catch some more things and kill some
more things that's what i can do
i'm building another base up north what
the hell is that
can i help i don't know what to do yeah
you can you can come with me get up
help me make decisions about the boat
okay
where are you i'm up north yeah by the
missile
pick up no no no no no no it's your
death
i found the ancient ones um oh oh dear
bye-bye abigail
you're not gonna survive that or maybe
you are well let's try
i will be following i love your staring
eyes
fine i picked the fight that was too
dangerous to me
button yes i got an interesting one
i see you i think what the hell was all
that that's not a black rabbit
oh right oh nightmare
it turned into nightmare fuel vegas do
you have any wood
uh i have twigs
okay i go get wood i only need two so
you just one tree
man is there any way for me to get
abigail my best friend
back what happened to her she got killed
by the ancient ones
[Music]
while she she walked in on on the i
don't know
how do we make this my sanity higher
because i'm unable to kill rabbits now
oh uh we gotta sleep uh you can make a
sleeping bag with grass
i think you just need grass okay cool
i'll do that
it's under survival at the bottom got it
yeah
grass and a rope but you see refined at
the science machine oh okay
sure i can make it up already i think
well i
you made one once then you can just make
one again sanity
they're always so low uh-oh
grope with grass
kelly oh god
do the rabbits look normal to you gouda
it looks brown and fuzzy to me
a flower
saturday when your sanity gets slow it
starts to change how the monsters look
[Music]
is
saturday that's restored by sleeping and
picking flowers
thank you so good idea i want to pick
some flowers my crown's
gone
i'm so hungry like uh outside of the
game like actually hungry i'm so hungry
oh
what i need a ton of wood okay i get
more wood yes
thank you i have an axe i should
probably i should probably chop some
darn it um
can make you one oh thank you please
[Music]
okay i'll leave it at the base thank you
hello i thought it would chop faster if
i help others i don't know if it does
maybe it does kind of seem like it did
oh my axe is gone that was a funny noise
i could really use a healing potion i
got like one heart left
uh yeah you could you couldn't but then
you had a spider gland right
yeah i still have two spider glands left
yeah they just
and so two rocks did you get ash pom pom
yeah yeah you want to share that
sleeping bag with me
oh i would love to but it's gone it's
one use
yeah i'll make you another one i'll make
another one
i really want it i'm sorry i would
that's okay i have a bunch of grass
actually i need two more guys i have
found here
here
[Music]
we go did we find out whose bestie this
is
uh whoever whoever picked up the bone
who was the one who picked up the bone
i don't know
okay he just appeared here he's cute
he's cute
i already have i already have lobby
yeah do you need ash oh i can't i can't
take it i can make ash
that would be dope
salute me
i need to pick more flowers
i wonder why the table hasn't tried to
uh f word with us yet
i think i think you have to like maybe
it's because kiara took the flowers she
has to be near it
you guys step on the hands when you see
them
look how peaceful cali looks
like
[Music]
oh stop on that okay i've been stopping
stopping you
go away monsters i'm scared
i gotta protect you from the monsters
thank you kiana i do appreciate it
i appreciate your sleeping child oh no
i'm real hungry yeah that's not great
here
you're losing them oh something yeah
there's meatballs
just meatballs in the dress uh i ate one
so there might not be anything
cooking with the tables moving monster
[Music]
you always want to eat the seeds oh yeah
i have the ash that you
that you're talking about
yeah real hungry while sleeping
it's like a trade-off you get more brain
juice for less
hunger
i do have frog legs though i could
probably cook them right
yeah you can put them in a crock pot uh
you can put one stick frog leg and then
fillers like berries or carrots or
mushrooms cali cali i'm gonna draw some
wood here a bunch of frog legs at once
i'm getting more wood okay i put wood in
the middle
okay i fed you my wife oh my god
you have been fed thank you for the
assistance
thank you for the assistance
i do appreciate it how do you make an
upgrade engine
oh yeah uh well you need gold to make
the little i have enough to make it but
i was just waiting to make it up at the
base up top because uh
i'm making a new base up there i'm gonna
make one right now if you want to follow
me
uh i'm gonna make it right now yep uh
where are you north i'm going north
follow the path
yeah planting trees
we did by the way reach show wanted to
have
ah yeah yeah yeah good huh
time flies probably about that it has
been fun
we should do it again sometimes yeah one
is part two one part two is it if we
leave the server is it gonna stay like
that uh it pauses as soon as i shut it
down so as soon as i exit the game
everything will be uh exactly as we left
it
but you can go back to that state that's
awesome yeah but i
actually don't remember it should be
fine
maybe hmm it should be fine
it's better staying like that i want my
ghostbed
i'm not gonna tangle with this frog
today
dance with me frog legs leave it for
next time yeah yeah
all right sounds good
nice job today guys i wonder what our
death counter was at
oh boy uh
what about you girls uh-huh i think it's
probably the same
yeah i think i died oh 13.
i died at the start we all died at the
start yeah we all did huh
another extra time well we really didn't
do a bad job i mean
i would think i would have thought that
i would have done a much worse job but i
survived long enough
yeah oh and by the way uh if you guys
ever want to stream this game alone
there's like single player
two it's just called don't starve and
there's like a lot more content in it
and there's like a different island and
different biomes you can explore just
like minecraft
very the art style of this game too in
the field it's very nice
i'll definitely do that sounds good well
thanks for tuning in everyone
thanks for coming to hang out with us as
we tried not to starve together
yeah thank you for watching thank you
thank you everyone
[Music]
bye
remember guys kiara singles releasing
next week
don't miss it go buy it you can buy it
listen to it stream it
okay bye-bye
[Music]