[Music]
do
um
[Music]
good
[Applause]
uh
[Music]
hmm
so
[Music]
okay
good morning
[Music]
it is um 10 30 a.m
meow what is it i gave you food already
smoothie john
no no no meow no no no meow no
no no no no no no no no no no
i woke up 20 minutes ago need to put
money okay
judy hundis
uh ah did that not turn on slow mode
wait
um
10 seconds there we go
so we need some museum
at least for now wait uh wait
the the thing should already be open
wait um
watch you live ooh what's life
what's going on here oh
oh it's uh i think we can play that now
no i don't know
the the waiting room music is just
normal hello live music
could probably play that place do it
[\h__\h] it everybody no no no
no no i don't want to like and i changed
i don't know what did i do last time
what did i do more cat error
[Music]
hi
oh flower stands
oh wow oh
they got them anyway even though it's
not actually happening
live you know oh yeah should i do low
latency mode
[Music]
okay well let's let's let's let's let's
uh
talk about you know what's happening
today
so today
isn't it today this is so quiet this is
kind of too quiet probably
[Music]
okay ah well no i'm not sleepy anymore
i'm
and just usually need like five minutes
to wake up
and there we go ah so so so
so today once again we're doing a
concert
watch along today is um
from first that is the name of the
concert
what does it mean it means that the
first generation members
only are part of this concert
yata and
[Music]
it is also as far as i understood it
is also at the same time like a like a
three-year
uh anniversary concert
[Music]
three years three years away that sounds
crazy wow
that sounds crazy yeah uh who's
performing how to senpai or hatchima
[Music]
and um this time different from the
other concerts
uh it's not on nico nico it's only on
spawn
i hope you got your tickets right now
guys i told you to get them early guys
i told you you know
[Music]
apparently apparently said yesterday
that hadamard is the one performing and
not hot on them but
i don't believe that they can't do that
that would be uh scary
oh who's hotdog
who is that don't say that you guys have
been brainwashed oh no
yeah the first wait is itself
no ah because so the fingers will spawn
they don't do that
first 30 minutes thingy they don't do
that
um but because they don't have the nico
nico thing right now where they usually
did the first
30 minutes everything uh they have a
youtube
uh stream going on where they
show the first 30 minutes indeed yes
so it's on the official hello live
channel uh you if you can't watch
if you can't buy a ticket and want to
watch a little bit of it anyway
uh go to the official whole live youtube
channel and they
are currently um yeah they have a stream
going on there
where they will show the first 30
minutes instead of nico nico because for
some reason nico nicole is not available
this time
[Music]
um
it's starting in 20 minutes by the way
and
i am here today
to watch it together with you just like
the other concerts where we did that
as well today is a bit early for me
but of course i wake up for this purpose
yes yes yes and i think it will be
a really really cute concert i wonder i
wonder what songs they're gonna sing
it's probably
mostly gonna be oh the whole live
original song so i
i reckon personally and they got one
one um first generation only original
song recently
uh what was the name it's such a a
weird name what was the title of the
song
how power parallel para pow
po plus magic seasons what does that
mean
[Music]
plasma and magic as well if you're
asking for plasma donations
anyway that sounds really cute pretty
pretty adorable um
[Music]
ah cat hair yeah
i got it oh that's a long one
[Music]
to the donation center i go let's go i
still made some plasma
okay i need why did why is it so dark in
my let me turn on the light can i do it
with my headphones on no problem
what is this cable mess can i hire
someone
to do something about the freaking
cables everywhere here oh my god
i mean i can handle it but
[Music]
hello
uh i was just turning on the light and
saying hello to my kitty cat
meow meow all right
so of course i am not showing the actual
concert on my screen
i don't know like somewhat sometimes
people think i do that even though it's
pretty obvious and it's also a print
comment
i will not be selling the actual concert
on my screen please get your own ticket
um
[Music]
since uh i think the archive gang is
gonna be
having no issues with that but uh
us live gang we're probably gonna have a
little issue of delay
a tiny delay where i'm a bit later than
you guys unless
unless you do the big brain thing where
once the concert starts you pause
the stream for like two seconds not my
stream the the concert stream
okay i'm on low latency yes you pause
the concert screen for two seconds and
then you unpause it and then you might
be around the same time as me i'll tell
you though what i'm saying
is
[Music]
try try it out i'll tell you what i'm
seeing
[Music]
thank you guys everyone for coming to
watch the concert with me
the moment i heard that the concert is
not happening
in real life anymore but only uh
here online i knew it was my job to do
this
[Music]
katya what the [\h__\h] i mean okay
[Laughter]
then why are you here in the first place
[Music]
let's get to
yeah i mean i think well good question i
think
i think on youtube the one where they're
streaming the first 30 minutes
i would i would say yes but i don't know
i think yes
well we will see we will see
i would hope so for you guys it would be
also a good way to
uh um show off the concert
for people later on
how long does the whole country last
good question i do not know i actually
have an appointment
after this uh so i can't read super
chat's evo probably have an
appointment with my tax tax person
my tax secretary or whatever uh
yeah maybe it's archived for a limited
time that could very well be maybe
they're just you know trying to
do it the same as it usually is on niko
nicole
um um
it's very very complicated you know
being in a situation where i am
these things are very very complicated
good thing you look up early why you say
that
but yes it is true uh woke up early
today and i'm probably gonna go back to
sleep after that
text meeting
oh two hours concert is two hours
[Music]
two hours guys so that will
i ask that i asked if i can move the
meeting uh
let me let me get my phone real quick
and see if she actually replied
no
okay okay okay okay okay okay okay
okay i gotta reply okay it's all good
eh what i can hear voices
what oh wait i i muted this thing
[Music]
i hear something
alona
such a cute voice holy [\h__\h] ah
come on
cute such a soothing voice yeah
yes yes yes yes it is not okay to
uh uh uh you know screen
the concert somewhere else uh-huh
report any anything you see to
cover please thank you
hi hi the boss
[Music]
okay so she was asking if we got uh if
we're ready and we got a pen lots of the
right colors and all that okay
i have this thank you senpai
[Laughter]
okay okay she said please wait until
it's opening
hey look at my pen lights it's the
actual ones from
the concert the special ones yeah
the merch for this concert is so
freaking dope
the merch have you guys seen the merch
there's so
much like you see it now if you're
watching in concert
uh there's a t-shirt there's a muffler
towel there's a bag there's the acro pen
light
and there's much much more but they're
not showing it right now i wonder if
they're going to show it again
is that shovels no there's a kang bakshi
set of what
what is that in english and then a
pamphlet
and a tapestry a big one and an
acryl museum stand thingy
a metal charm set and a rubber band
and oh what was acrylic real keychains
as well
ice cream scoops now
[Music]
yo what else i think they had even more
maybe they'll show off this they're
showing the flowers dance i
i don't think i've ever seen this like
overseas before but in japan for
concerts
or like just store openings they would
like with people
other companies or like groups of fans
would send
uh like big big big flower stands uh
like you see here on the side the ones
on the side are mostly accurate
oh they're much bigger though they're
like bigger than
a human most of the time and
so yeah that that normally um uh is what
people send to congratulate people for
openings of
of restaurants or or concerts yeah
i think that's a really cute cute kind
of uh
tradition
okay i'm not gonna play my pgm anymore
[Music]
thank you guys i had this uh last last
minute
thought yesterday in the night before i
fell asleep
of uh getting pen lights for this thank
you for
a bunch of people reacted and made
something thank you
sorry i'm just using this one for today
but
start singing along with the bgm in the
stream so we can now
okay
wait um
[Laughter]
[Music]
da
oh
[Laughter]
m i think that was pretty helpful
i will do it again we'll do it again
no wait what was the melody again
now
it's starting in four minutes
a point on the screen says okay now
now
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh man if i was so sad when i heard that
this is not happening in life
fubu crucible was also really really sad
she she wrote on twitter that she cried
a lot i mean
that that is not like in an actual
concert hall
like i mean with audience with audience
that is the thing that was originally
planned but it's not happening
i know
[Music]
what can
we'll get there one day i'm sure of it
no
i'm saying now every time the screen
changes so you guys know how much delay
there is
[Music]
now
perfectly synced for me no it's high
five yeah
oh my god
[Music]
yeah yeah it's god talking to us
kamisamaktan
yeah let's go she told us to have fun
together
everyone who's watching the stream
it's opening now yeah
oh sorry i didn't know they were gonna
say stanton
third anniversary live from first
peak
where are you at i i
i i i i
hate
[Music]
already my antennae
[Applause]
yay
oh
[Music]
classic what a classic sight
i
i can tell nice voice
day by day cute
dun dun dun dun dun dun
so cute
[Music]
bye
foreign
[Music]
ah
oh
[Music]
i
foreign
what a great start to a great concert
oh next song already
what what is it oh wait only three oh
something
ah hat track
senpai
[Music]
i
oh fubuki senpai's voice is a bit
different from usual
dun dun
[Music]
my
face so cute
[Music]
singing a very low voice i i i
okay
i don't recognize the voice quicker
got it the guns
[Music]
i
oh
[Music]
but
la
[Music]
oh
that was a very different fubuki senpai
oh see i knew they were going to sing
bloom songs
awesome because i love them all so much
tsuki
[Music]
oh
oh this is kind of fitting for a
hatchimal it scares me
oh
very angry song
it does sound like hatama
tea she's rapping
wow she nailed it
kelly real quiet
kelly can do the same if not if not even
more
[Music]
hi
interesting song
don't fight girls don't fight
no kenka's united
hey
this was a cover song right i mean i'm
not cover as in
cover hello live but it's a it's a cover
right it's not an original
right
oh
yeah it's a vocaloid song right i think
it's the first time i actually heard it
i knew if it's like i heard of the title
before but i didn't know the actual song
ever
yeah first generation
yay
[Music]
they're gonna do self-introductions
i
oh yes he wants to send lots of passion
and smiles to you guys for the screen
she wants to be an idol today with
everyone
please enjoy
you want to make the best memories today
with you guys
she says uh in charge of say-so-ness in
her
life
oh she wants to be more safer than
everyone else today
oh
[Music]
she spoke so fast but i think she said
that she wants to send lots of smiles
together with the first generation
the the free part will end after this
emcee apparently
go get you tickets she says if you if
you're watching the free version go get
your tickets
or down there down there not not yeah i
do have the
ticket link actually in my description
they're talking about the songs that
they sung now
with humanitarian faced and they were
very nervous
they practiced a lot of uh choreography
for this and there were a lot of uh
formations because they only performed
the five people
oh call on response
she's asking if you guys have your pen
lines
mine actually looks past the blue the
lights are just i think not on
on this one
[Music]
sorry i can't to change the lights in my
van light
mommy's little point sorry no light
green
she says her color is light green but i
can't change it
this is good enough i am i have uh
colors for everyone in my heart
okay okay you're ready guys
[Music]
yellow change your pen light to yellow
so
[Music]
she wants to be she wants to be called a
genius
she wants us to say she say so after she
uh
asks what she is
[Music]
[Laughter]
i mean god has to be safer
if god doesn't say so then what what
what
it's the moody god
beautiful
she's gonna do her calling response you
know what's coming
she doesn't remember herself
[Music]
okay when i go back to singing now but
who's to sing in the next song
oh oh oh
solo
the free portion is over guys bye bye
free people
get you tickets get your tickets guys
first gen is so high pitched they really
are
[Music]
yata
wow
baby tell me what is wrong don't you
ever let me go
hi i am good i am still looking for
proof
am i good enough for you don't you tell
me what's my rule
coming on the right we are going
surprise
you and me are you ready for the fight
all right all right
lyrics
this is who i am
big red heart big red heart
big red heart
red heart big red heart mama big red
heart
i i i i i
i i i i
thank you for coming along on this
journey of my own
this is me i am falling but i'm strong
don't you ever let me go
i am falling from the sky
all right all right let's [\h__\h] go
it's instant sense
hi hi hi hi
oh
stay so idle
big red hot big red hot
big and hard
big red
hey
so adorable i'm glad we saw
ceso idol hatto senpai
yeah oh very senpai is next whoo
what is she going to sing
um
what is this song
i heard it wait is this
on it
is this like uh
ah
[Music]
that's a covering
well she has such a soft voice
i think this is quite a famous song
i'm falling in love right now coisto
cute
i'm in love
she's so cute
we're singing is so good
nice camerawork
uh
mean that's just super say-so come on
[Music]
that little jump
that was so adorable
okay let me take off my cardigan there
we go
is
see connie wait that's the bird from
hirotodi
on the screen that's the hinata
just kidding it's not the same
[Music]
[Laughter]
oh she's using a low voice a lot in this
concern
[Music]
why
[Laughter]
[Music]
hmm
foreign
are you playing with one hand
well this is for looking senpai okay
it's
a king okay football
[Music]
i
foreign
[Music]
yay
i love you i love you i love you
great guitar playing wow wow wow amazing
they're making fun of her because she
wasn't playing
what what else what a
a low weight guitar
oh she said that is not really
a song from the first generation but
it's the first song that they sang
together
oh yeah normally they don't do that much
do they the formation and
my changing positions
like if you check the other concerts
indeed they mostly stayed like in
in one place they did choreography maybe
but they stayed in one place
now they're talking about the songs they
stay sang uh it's going a bit fast
but they're talking about
oh
she says that uh since her debut
often like like was acting as she was
gonna put up a fight against
matsuri senpai so the song was very
fitting
how are you
oh my god there's so many people talking
at once
well well they're uh praising matthew's
empire for doing so well because she
says it was very difficult that song
red hat
yeah they say that you get brainwashed
by this song it is true it is true
oh oh foot broke
she always loved this song
the one that she's saying she's on a
coin
she wanted the love to come across to
you guys
and hopefully it worked
air guitar kitsune
no more
oh oh the original artist
uh she actually
uh had a guitar in the music video as
well but she
she was carrying it but never actually
played it so that was kind of a
reference to that i guess
oh
oh apparently she made a a promise to
her viewers that she's gonna sing
sorry days on uh in the in the concert
and even though she thought about doing
her own original song safe on father
originally but yeah
it was a promise to her viewers
or something something arrived
oh i under the flower stance
hmm
well at least then they don't uh they
don't ever
die normally it's real flowers but i
think because
this is all digital now they mean a
digital version
and then at the top it all says uh who
who are
the people who sent the flower stands
somewhere from like single people and
someone from like groups of people
oh who the hell is facial land
[Music]
oh oh oh i'm getting dizzy now how many
rounds did we make
man got my luck fixed down
overseas nikki thank you
sneaky
they're [\h__\h] you guys
no
oh they're gonna talk about the stage
there are indeed
a lot of elements from their like icons
and stuff
in the stage
oh the first gen actually gave uh
like ideas on how they want the stage to
look like so they made it together
ah they wanted it to look like a
envelope kind of
from first was an idea from aki senpai
wow that angle aki senpai aki senpai
[Music]
kakuroga
first row view yeah
oh oh
oh they are recommending the pump
pamphlet pamphlet what's it in english
the little booklet for the concert
they want you to look at it i'm not sure
what they're referencing to the
they want you to look at the booklet
oh it's gonna be a treasure they say
book it sold out three days ago oh no
oh oh
oh they're saying maybe that specific
song is going to be sung
soon i'm also getting really hungry oh
my god i didn't eat breakfast as a
[Music]
question
they're going to look back on the past
three years now with some video footage
this is gonna make me cry is it it's
gonna be very emotional
ah oh my god
that is so old they were still wearing
swimsuits back then
me is
oh
that's really old
oh that was before okay senpai's 3d was
announced so in the back she was like
holding her 2d
um stand and waving it around
she wants to show off their swimsuits
again oh
that would be nice sam
oh let's recent
cute
halloween today according to medicine
funny
kiana swimsuit when uh just check out
twitter
it has even been cosplayed and
at the inaudible
ah this was the the revival um stream
of her after her little break and she
couldn't do it in the year before so
that's why the stream was very special
to her
they just realized that the colors uh
are different than where they're
standing
no problem no brown orange and yellow
very similar colors
i need to see
what's her moment a special moment
oh
isn't that also super old super
nostalgic
this is like two weeks after her debut
no
no the song was uh released two weeks
after her debut and this was in her 3dw
oh yeah yeah we're talking about this in
hall talk
her story of the struggles in the first
year
when she was in the hospital
ah yoga
oh the archive is back apparently it was
gone for a while but that archive of
that
pretty uh debut is back
yeah unprivated now if you want to see
it
ah that is also somewhat recent
oh yeah
oh from her birthday stream
oh those two are so adorable together
[Music]
um
she said she loves luna and also
normally she doesn't really get presents
like
presented her directly into her hands so
this was very special to her
ah what is she gonna show us ah
she says that there wasn't really many
emotional moments so she went for this
one from her birthday
this year for her birthday she wants to
do 3d
because she couldn't do it last time
monster survey is criticizing her for
choosing that as as
for choosing that as her three-year best
memory
she explained that this is so special to
her because at the very end whatever
somebody called and then they got
for the first time in a long time they
were able to talk and got closer again
they're calling that certain knitter
because she didn't show that exact
moment though
but another moment because she was
feeling embarrassed about it
oh
she said that there was this stream that
they did together with the first gen
and she was thinking of showing that
moment but it already showed up in the
in the opening so she was like whatever
is very difficult to choose a memory
from those for years because so many
things happened
oh the right side has eaten bugs before
the left side hasn't
uh let's eat some good food yeah i agree
i would be on the left side
that's a great similarity to have
yeah you could say
maybe the right side is the super brave
side and the left one
we're going to the next song
only three oh the blondes the blondes
are singing to us
kimbap
i was i was thinking there's a lot of
bombs on the first generation
oh
that's a cover um
i
dance moves
cute
oh i barely heard this song before but
it's really cute
oh cute
[Music]
oh my god they're so adorable
i mean if you call this if you don't
call this an idol then what is an idol
[Music]
hawaii
cute
[Music]
i love that song
oh
[Music]
um
hmm
yes i will choose you
i love his singing voice so much
it's so beautiful
and i think for her original song she
did the choreographies herself
as far as i know
oh
[Music]
um
aah
yo my hearing
[Music]
oh
god and king
middle stage y'all
who knows
godfriend
silent siren oh
i was a quite a fan of silent siren when
uh the group was first
created
yeah actually i bought their album back
in the day
oh it's that old girl's groove right the
old girl's band
silent
[Music]
i
usual cute voice
hi hi hi oh hi
hi hi hi hi
i am i i i
need to catch up on silent siren songs
it seems
i've been missing out on stuff why
aren't you even still active
oh aki was in public somebody's house
during her karaoke stream oh
that's cute
matsuri senpai's eyes just pierced for
your height
i just realized the others have the
similarity that their
hair is all blonde but those two have
similarity that
their eyes are uh green
green greenish they have a similar eye
color
like green turquoise
turquoise i gang
just realized thanks to those close-ups
i i
i i i i
oh
oh never heard that song before but it
was beautiful
very fitting for there uh do it
they teleported back in there
i want those teleporting skills as well
can i teleport in there
in time huh
oh the idea to sing julie never those
three
came from medicine by she wanted to sing
that song
i tried really hard to do in the
practice
to learn that choreo
i'm five seconds ahead of you
interesting
ah that's because probably because you
have don't have low latency mode on try
turning that on
in in the stream in the concert
here
she was nervous to sing that song after
tuning them
uh remember the choreography already
everyone does a family
oh she's asking the other girls to sing
it as well at some point
maybe i should sing it in a karaoke
stream
[Music]
um
oh fubuki senpai wanted to sing kakume
with matsuri senpai
she likes the lyrics
oh
oh she says that the lyrics fit the
whole theme very well
um
oh
to sing a certain line in that song
because it fits so well because senpai
in the beginning of her
activities didn't really know uh
what to do and how how to what kind of
streamer she wants to be
hey we need to bring martini stanford
onto hollow talk
[Music]
let's finish up the first gen soon shall
we
the set must be completed yes full
collection
they're freaking you guys right now yeah
nikki i'm knocking
no wife a friend only oh man don't break
my heart now
at least today let me dream
ah stay talking about
uh the horogram could have
watched it the recent one
they're gonna recreate it
uh right here i actually didn't watch
that one sorry
they're on the wrong position again
she said for that day she was wife oh
man why not today
[Music]
why
okay okay okay they're doing it now
ah
panic panic
i like how fubu senpai just kind of uh
covered and censored uh medicine by his
cleavage
because she's standing in the middle
oh
mama
they're going crazy
wow i mean that was very very fast so i
don't blame them
how many points would we give them for
that
eight out of ten
four thousand thousand ten out of the
ten i mean yeah since we have that emote
we have to give them ten out of ten
oh they're shuffling the scripts now oh
no
oh
oh they're changing the switching rules
now and trying it again because that was
too easy
i like the whole idea of doing this this
is cute
this will be horrible
and whatever that
ah
they lost track
i completely lost track
but nice cleavage cover for boogie
senpai
oh who's speaking handle who's doing
anton's voice
um
[Music]
die-hard script
um 10 out of 10
entertainment factor 10 out of 10 10 10
out of 10.
you did your best for the effort
out of ten
sorry guys i'm by the way so tired
my face is so tired i need a nap
after this and food
oh it's announcement time
oh letter sets
did you not already have enough
merchandise
well guys if you're a fan of the first
gen of any of those members you can use
those letter sets to write fan letters
to them
[Music]
okay
so cute i love leather sets never write
letters but i always buy letter sets
stationary
oh yeah they just mentioned the fan
letter
you can't write fan letters
where's my kia leather set make it
yourself
it's a super super luxury set guys go
get it
starting from today after this concert i
guess
online available online but pro maybe
only in japan
oh oh
wonderful hobby right for you what
from good smell company and max factory
are going to be
uh on display tomorrow
until 6th of june oh
online and in real life
whole life figurines woohoo
oh they're gonna show it a little bit
you said that
wait those are uh what do you call those
there were the nendoroids is this
dandelion
[Music]
cute oh my god
oh my god that the hatto senpai one so
cute
oh bunch of new other figures will also
be there on display
no matter okay no definitely but they
just have to
they're still creating them i guess or
it's still secret
oh you can't reserve them on good smile
company website
oh i want them they're cute
and android of all
oh
what
ah
oh key holders and pillows and all that
with this kind of illustration
oh not only first gen but also other
members
oh look forward to it
so much merchandise holy moly
solo song
what is she gonna sing
bye bye
there you go
i love that song
mata
[Music]
i love this song
love honey wigs i love honey wigs
oh very fitting the lyrics
[Music]
oh
foreign
[Music]
yakuza
it's telling you to not let you get ice
off of it
my turkey hi my turkey hi my
dirty hey
oh
[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
i
want to sing that song in my cut okay
what's next
[Music]
hey
foreign
[Music]
3dw me and gouda let's do it
i can see it i like this this is cute
oh they're going to come to the front
stage i always wanted to do something
like that
walk from the main stage to the to the
front
imaginary people in the audience at
those pen lights with no faces and no
hands and no bodies
[Music]
why you do them like that
pump
[Music]
this is such a perfect song to say thank
you to your audience
so great choice
[Music]
oh i love the song
i love it ah
they did a great job i like how they
walked up to that middle stage and then
it was even raised all the way up nice
whoo it was great
foreign
oh
she hopes that you guys felt some kind
of improvement because she sang that
song before
in a concert so hopefully she
improved in your eyes and if you're if
you're a new viewer that she hopes that
you guys think ah she's an idol after
all
of course i need to call
hmm she thinks she made no mistakes
in that i could of a performance
they did a great job at the stage the
people who made it
good job i like it i think this is the
first time that they have this kind of
stage
where without with a catwalk
and a middle stage i think that's the
first time
oh letter time guys we're gonna read
some letters with
uh their thanks to you guys your
gratitude
oh first is hatto senpai
she's surprised she wrote a lot she
doesn't remember
is this did someone else write a letter
thank you for coming to this concert
she is embarrassed to write letters so
don't be
don't get excited about it
she's already starting to cry
i yeah was very surprised
oh in the beginning she wasn't sure
like what kind of character she she is
or wants to be
but now everything uh grew so big
it is so overwhelming and she's able to
perform here
she says that not only her life but also
she herself has evolved and improved a
lot in those four years
and she wanted everyone to see that
improvement so she did her very best
please get a lot of the energy from her
oh she wants you guys to feel like
because hatsuma is doing her face i will
do my best as well
she'll do her best to evolve even more
congratulations on a little
three year anniversary
oh but she wants to go on until 10 year
anniversary
until then she wants to be the best
heart of mine in the world she's already
the best out of my little cause she's
the only heart around the world
oh follow me
hmm that was her filled with a love
letter to you guys
[Music]
cute
gonna be emotional
thank you for bringing me to this
beautiful view
please it's very special to her that she
was able to meet you all
oh no no she had problems with her
confidence because of like
hater stuff and [\h__\h]
i mean there were yeah a lot of
struggles a lot of tough times for her
whenever she streams she gets a lot of
love from you guys and happiness
she really thinks that she wants to
spend a lot of time with you
in the next year she wants to try to do
more things
that yeah just anything that she wants
to do
in hopes that you guys support her and
no matter if you're a new veteran or an
old fan
and and and
and she'll continue to send lots of love
and power and happiness to you guys
okay that was a horrible translation but
there you go
you got the rough idea of it okay
[Music]
such a fighter i need somebody such a
fighter
not
hi friends
thank you for always watching my streams
in the beginning she thought being an
idol was just a dream
she joined her life because she wanted
friends and and she was just a nerd but
now she has so many fans and
friends
just thanking the other members for
always being by her side
let's continue to be friends and she
says so so happy too
that she joined her life in in the first
place
she said that all our viewers are her
very important friends because they've
seen her
her bad signs and her good signs
she says that it won't change that will
be friends nothing
nothing more than that but she hopes
that continues
and you'll you'll support her even
though
yeah your friends don't
she might be very shy and embarrassed
but she loves everyone who's
listening to her letter right now
oh man
i'm not gonna translate that is too fast
her other members
oh man
[Music]
yeah oh
i don't want to translate anymore it's
too sad
[Music]
thank you for always supporting me
my dream came true and i'm really
enjoying this moment where i can perform
with
my gen mates
she says it's uh thanks to you guys that
this
was made possible
this is a big treasure to me
oh
oh man stop she practiced so hard for
this day and she finally came to this
day
she says she might cry alone and is a
bit weak but she
thanks everyone for their support
and today is a very special day i love
you
oh
in the beginning she wasn't the first
generation member but then it was
decided that she would join and
she was very nervous about that
and she always wanted to make have a
concert with the first gen
so she's really glad that it happened
oh when i give them a hug
okay last letter martially senpai
uh
thank you always
thanks to you guys this concert was made
up
thank you for always supporting me even
though i wasn't sure about my own
character whether or not i'm a joke a
meme character or a cute character
please continue supporting me in the
future as well i love you
next she wants to do a solo concert
and she's gonna make it happen so please
follow me
i don't know in which person i should
translate this stuff i keep on changing
is she spanking her genmates
oh i thought about quitting
many many times
but at those times fubuki senpai was
trying to hire
so hard to to go on with whole life
and and you always show blah i can't
translate this
there's no break to put in translations
well thanks to her genuinely she was
able to continue even though she thought
about quitting so often
she loves all the other whole life
members as well but her gen mates are
very special to her let's do our best to
give her a vital
i'm just thanking the staff as well
thank you for working hard in the
background
she hopes that um even though maybe they
weren't able to put it into words that
well
she hopes that that the feeling of them
working so hard towards their goals came
across to you guys
if you're not giving me she says this is
the last song but if you're not giving
gonna give me an
encoder i'm gonna be mad
next song is very special to them
no she says there is no encore after
this
that it must be plus magic seasons
l-e-a-o
now the one when uh the blue had an
encore
i think the others didn't
[Music]
oh
actually kind of reminds me of hito in
audition huh
[Music]
foreign
hey
[Music]
um
carry on
i mean i love all the generations so
that's a lie i love them all
but
uh
[Music]
hmm
wow
let's go
tail is so fluffy and so cute
i want to touch it
[Music]
my fireworks
oh
[Music]
oh man that's that's sad i want some
uncle
come on come on really was she serious
i guess so oh no
oh
to be continued
oh she says it's over
they're advertising merch again
and please use the hashtag
screenshots are okay
go ahead and post their screenshots on
twitter with the hashtag
[Music]
oh that was really really really good
great concert
you
[Music]
gonna put down my pen lines because i
guess it's over
oh ah
it's really really cool that they were
able to do
a first-gen only concert because you
know christian has
been around for such a long time
i personally haven't been around
uh in the very beginning when first gen
first popped up but fukuki sampler was
the reason
why i found her life and
especially after doing whole talk with
most of the girls in here
i feel like uh
they yeah i kind of i know about a lot
of the struggles that they've been
through
by getting to know them and so it's very
emotional
very special um
to watch this and and to see them
together like this performing together
and just becoming one
as and one whole unit as first gen
it's very special
i hope they can do more stuff like this
with the first gen or even like other
generations
like per generation having having a
concert for each generation that would
be cool too
but uh it's just the first generation
just really deserves it
especially like first gen and zero
gender really
created whole life and made it to what
it is today
halloween concert
hopefully one day we can make that
happen too yeah um
that would be lovely i would i would
love to do that but you know it's just
very difficult because we're all over
the world
so that's something for the for the long
very distant future
thanks for translating thank you for
listening guys i hope it was helpful
a little bit it was a bit difficult as
usual because
they don't take breaks uh to let me
translate
they don't put in any rake cell it's
hard to uh
put in translations because while i'm
translating they're talking something
new
and i miss out on that usually
so yeah it was just a rough translation
and but i hope it helped i mean well
mostly the gist was the gist of it came
across i think yeah
and sorry for being a bit tired of it
low energy it was still great even
though i was a bit low energy
attention
um
thank you for watching together with me
yay if you missed some part of it
there should be an archive available
uh you should be able to watch it later
on as well
um yeah my archive will stay up
of course as well and tomorrow is
hollow talk
and uh after taking a little nap and and
after talking to my tax person
i will work on the questions thank you
everyone who asked questions don't ask
them anymore it's uh
i'm not gonna check them anymore i'm
going to compile them
put them into graphics and then i'll see
you tomorrow for her talk yeah
tax person no no but she could probably
do it
um
we will ask even more no it's useless
don't do it don't do it
oh archive available until until 28th of
uh
june okay that's one month huh one month
oh yeah enough time to watch it
afterwards
when exactly is the marathon uh i'll
upload the schedule
maybe today or tomorrow i'll think about
it you'll see it soon
[Music]
that time was just roughly an estimate
i'm not sure
i'm not sure maybe 2 p.m my time
something around that
we may start around that time
but just wait for the schedule straight
for the schedule
all right then no super chat raining
today i'm sorry sorry sorry sorry sorry
uh i'll leave you guys there and thank
you for watching hope you enjoyed it
that was an amazing concept
first generation cycle
[Music]
please continue to support hello live
thank you guys you're amazing
that's my let's make many many more
amazing memories of whole life let's get
whole life bigger and bigger so that one
day
everyone can also be on a real stage
again not only virtual
and not only online live stream it's
thank you for your support hold on
forever
[Music]
bye
thank you
[Music]
you