[Music]
passing by the mil your
Roes I could them
F the reason why
who I am you couldn't know stuck in the
ruins my
disillusion in between the Dual
reality my own
desire Kiss Me To
You O moving faster than the light can
I'm in the
absence alone the king back then I lose
my way I can see the day when I can
reach you again then can I let
go I can hear your voice leading me
through the boy fade
away to the
great i t I'm walking by the lives the
FL before my eyes along cuz silence defy
still I'm reaching out to you connect
sacrifice the life I tell myself so I'll
survive one day eventually the light it
will lead me back to you see
[Music]
me I am the
Wonder I am the Wonder
around
faith is gone the well is
try no more
believing just to
seeing ooh feel the daylight on the edge
but I can't feel the heat fall back into
theend and I lose my way I can see the
day when I can reach you again then can
I let
go I can hear your voice leading me
through the bo F
away to the
Grave turn I'm walking by the Liv the FL
before my eyesone the silence happening
still I'm reaching out to you con saice
the life I for so I'll survive one day
eventually the life it will lead me back
till you see
me da da
oo I am the Wonder
around
[Music]
o one
around
[Music]
ah