foreign
[Music]
questions
foreign
[Music]
thank you
questions
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
hello
can you hear me can you hear the PGM
oh
Chihuahua is back
let me pour some tea I'm prepared it's
like it's like back in the day when I
was [\h__\h] sick and streaming
I'm I prepared myself a huge jog again
a monstrous jug
of tea
ah no it's not my snot is okay
um
um my phlegm is honestly uh pathetic
I've been like coughing up on a choking
up some flag but it's really just
pathetic nothing compared to what it
once was
uh which is a good thing I guess but
it's a bit more difficult to cough up
something that's pathetic
than something that's like
big
monstrous and
thick
uh
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh my God we got another like
situational Super Chat you should
honestly I should hire you to write like
my voice pack situation Scripts
would you be up for that the pay is
exposure just kidding
um
[Music]
okay let's see I've I've just realized I
haven't played
Minecraft
since I got my PC upgrade so let's hope
this goes well but I just realized you
guys are hearing the bgm much more quiet
than the actual game audio
and I know you don't see it yeah
maybe around here
oh wait a second
wait a second what did I do did I
nothing's going wrong everything's going
right everything's cool everything's
going according to keikaku
um maybe wait two more seconds
because Minecraft launcher did I open
the wrong Minecraft launcher
there's like a gray one and a green one
I'll put the gray one maybe that's why
all right
translators notes means plan let me open
the green one let's see if that fixes my
problem
[Music]
it both said Java though
and it also had like all my I don't know
it seemed connected with you know the
thing
uh
uh it says multiplayer disabled what
happened
[Music]
the both brings me to the same thing so
I'm guessing that the launchers are
whatever
uh what
I was just playing with the settings
the graphic settings that didn't change
anything I'm logged in ah
maybe this
no that's my Mojang account I need the
Microsoft account right
I think I know maybe what what why uh
yeah I know but they merged them ages
ago no when I clicked on the other
account it brought me back to the
Microsoft Account wait I'm logged in
what's the issue did I get banned well
how would I get banned
uh
uh let me I mean
I'm on the chat Java Edition right not
Windows Edition
I didn't do anything to get banned
wait
how would I know that I got bad I mean I
can't get banned from online multiplayer
in general right like over where I can
get banned from a server but maybe not
from
like you know the whole function
right
um
let's see
okay
no no no no no no no
the gray no I tried both the green and
the gray one both leads me to
[Music]
um
uh making me nervous
um my croissoft
okay well
well my my Microsoft account that's what
it is right that one's working
um
no I want to play Minecraft let me play
Minecraft
Ian curse uh it's been a while I'm so
happy to see you again Ian curse
online online
please check your Microsoft account
settings what could I have I mean I did
play around with my account settings
recently
but what could I have changed that uh
keeps me from playing let me go my
um mine Minecraft
Microsoft
multiplayer disabled
how to fix multiplayer is disabled in
Minecraft
the protection settings present and yeah
I did change some of that probably
uh edit profile info change the date of
birth year to 2000. I'm
where
look at her profile
I did I did profile
info here yeah but what if it's anyway
already that's not the issue
step two living the Microsoft Family
Group go to family Microsoft leave the
family group
eh we got another raid can you help me
fix Minecraft
uh I'm the only one in my family how can
I what if I remove myself from the
family then there's no more family is
there
doesn't seem like the issue allow
multiplayer on Xbox One
why why Xbox
what
seems like a lot of [\h__\h]
none of this none of this makes sense to
me
turn off
you're joking right wait none of these
Solutions make sense
how to fix multiplier let's let's watch
a video
here if your Minecraft multiplayer being
disabled do you hear that
I'm gonna show you how
fix it
I will not subscribe to your channel I
will not leave a like just start
quit Minecraft okay I'm quitting
Minecraft I'm never playing Minecraft
again though
okay
Microsoft
yeah yeah it makes sense a privacy not
privacy apparently I I
get to the point
mm-hmm
uh-huh Microsoft yeah I mean I'm I think
I'm in my Microsoft account yeah
my info
yeah that's why I am
I am over
I'm over of course I'm my internet is on
otherwise I wouldn't be streaming
why is the Xbox profile even relevant
but okay I'm going to the Xbox profile
uh
oh yeah okay privacy settings here too
uh-huh uh-huh
that's doing react content
what's wrong with that
oh yeah I I did mess around with that
recently
middle option
oh no I do allow that wait
ah
live
I just kind of
um you know blocked a lot of things to
make sure the account is really private
but I did block
um
me being able to participate in
multiplayer games
on Xbox Live but yeah okay
hold on I'm
saying thank you for waiting
oops I was a little bit too careful
preventing myself from playing with
others forever lonely what does it
matter anyway because I'll be alone on
the en server anyway won't I never said
will you join me on the en server or
will you also join the Japan server only
I mean it's connected but you know
nobody is building anymore somebody
wrote this on to me on on Twitter and it
just was like so straightforward it's
true but it was so straightforward like
I'm happy you're still building on the
en server because you're basically the
only one everybody else even the new
members are are all gonna be building on
the Japan server only and I'm like
that's so clearly awaited multiplayer is
still disabled did I properly save it
I think I did
ah let me try again
oh
this is fun
emotional damage emotion emotional
damage
emotional damage I don't know
okay here come on come on come on
come on come back go Minecraft come to
Mommy you can do it
did Never Say Something by the way uh to
my question
Mommy
tell me more British guy
okay I probably need to make changes on
my other privacy thing as well
um
uh
we couldn't load your settings try again
later what what what what what
my normal privacy settings they can't
load
eh it says
it can't load the settings please try
again later
it can only load the Xbox privacy
settings
try running as admin
I did restart the game client
ah why
[Music]
uh
[\h__\h] annoying man
I'm telling you [\h__\h] annoying
um
is she raising she wants me to teach her
Minecraft
did you never play Minecraft before ah
but Minecraft's on your Xbox
I haven't played you'll need to teach me
okay I will influence her to stay with
me
restart
ing unnecessary
Mamma Mia
um
how about
I don't know what to do I don't know
what else was I feel like that was the
solution
ah jenma is trying to send me Solutions
[Music]
why must every one of these [\h__\h]
articles lead with an introduction to
Minecraft Minecraft is one of the most
popular sandbox games with over 126
million users across the world due to
the game's prominence complications are
expected to arise yeah okay you may
create your own Universe no one gives a
[\h__\h]
no one gives a [\h__\h] I hate it
uh changing account age yep leaving
Microsoft Family group I'm the only one
allow multiple and I did connect to a
test server to ensure well that doesn't
work because I can't even get to that
ensure that the right account
um
I think it's the radical yeah it is
they lengthen the articles for ads yeah
I can I can imagine that
it's not Minecraft for Windows right
it's travel right yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah
um well you know what I think
I think this should the no that's right
that account is right
[Music]
my PC is plugged in
uh what about if I start without shakers
does that matter
does that matter let me see
but all the other things I already kind
of did I think make an expose account if
you needed so that the Online safety I
did that okay I know it's not working
[Music]
um
what the [\h__\h]
should I really restart my PC I don't
wanna I don't wanna that doesn't seem
like a thing I need to do
play mine I want to play Minecraft
Minecraft
I'll try to find more solutions
Minecraft seven multiple scissors and
then I have to
Minecraft players
[Music]
you may as well do it to roll it out
okay style NADA everybody's wait for me
otherwise
[Music]
what about here
let's change something here and
I don't think so okay yeah let's hope
um
hello
that was fast yeah
speed PC I guess we're back
a doll
um I'm scared guys I'm scared to check
Minecraft launcher gray or green what do
you want let's go with gray it doesn't
seem to matter they're the same
um
I'm so scared please hold me
please hold me
I'm scared
play
waiting on install why is it always like
installing that's also something I don't
know but starting
and
drum roll
um uh drum roll no
it's not no no no
um
I I also knew it wasn't gonna work
[\h__\h] restarting PC but yeah all
solutions are yeah
um Let me let me see let me double check
if I changed all of the privacy
settings microsoft.com
[Music]
yeah
and Yahoo
um
that's why I never change a running
system for real for real
okay
where was it again
[Music]
um
no it's not induction shoots it's in my
info
uh edit edit what
[\h__\h] I forgot where it was
do you guys want some music
we can also do I do originally I wanted
to do a tattoo done because I have so
many stories to tell
I might as well just do not Sudan but I
don't like the way the stream started in
that case
also I want to play Minecraft
[Music]
let me just try to find the thing again
because I'm I'm blind now
okay I can't
uh
you want to see Minecraft too right I
know
me too
uh okay
profile
no
that's a family I don't have that right
[Music]
um
no
okay
[Music]
um
okay okay okay okay okay uh
yeah maybe again
[Music]
which settings
seem like
they should they are necessary
um
they don't none of this seems necessary
[Music]
like shelling the profiles
um
[Music]
it says nothing about multiplayer but
let me do
um
what
ah
age restriction no I set it to
over 18 of course now it says again we
can't load your settings what the [\h__\h]
Microsoft
I saved something and now it like
refreshed and says we can't load your
settings please try again later what the
[\h__\h]
[Music]
um
okay
it makes me really sad but we're gonna
do that
I guess because I am
I'm feeling pressured
and let me change the title
so that people don't come in here like
they got baited
but stay because I got interesting
stories this was what this whole stream
was gonna be about anyway about my
stories
a story
time
I just gotta change the thumbnail later
bamboozle yeah I'll I'll try to fix it
later I guess
uh
[Music]
okay
moving to here maybe
isn't it lovely this place
they made this background for us to use
so sweet
you go here chat make yourself
comfortable
and here's some
chill music
out of a straight out of a jrpg
new background yeah not not only for me
like you probably saw other members
using it because it's like a
anybody can use it kind of thing very
nice they got like some foods and drinks
as assets as well
and there's a day version and there's a
night version
[Music]
the gym has Kingdom heartsfield well
maybe because you play Kingdom Hearts
for me it has a Tales of Symphonia feel
by the way let's get started right away
with it um because you guys probably
want to hear like my thoughts and
whatever about the New Gen
Bijou likes tails off games and we
talked a little bit about games and she
uh said that
um her favorite is Tales of Symphonia it
was her first one and and and and it was
ever since her favorite one and I was
like oh my God Taste of Symphonia is
maybe not my favorite one but it was
also my first one and and ever since I
started it like it was the the
kickstarter for me to get into
um
to get into
a tails off as a whole yeah so we talked
a little bit about tails off games and
and and and and
New Gen let's make a topic here
I'll make new gen
e
[Music]
wonderful okay fine are you guys okay
with this
are you guys okay with it as she asked
me about Tales of her eyes
yeah she's like she was asking me if if
I think she asked me if it was a good
game
and and how was it I was like in the
voice chat remember last time I talked
about the New Gen after it got announced
and I was like I haven't really gotten
time to talk to them much besides maybe
nerissa because I have been busy and
time zones and I was like in Japan
London this and that
uh and yeah so after that stream where I
complained about that immediately after
I was riding with narissa and Marissa is
like oh actually they're all in the call
right now and I'm like oh can you ask
them if they want to like talk to me
she's like okay I'll go I'll go ask him
ask him so nerissa helped me
to get them all in the room with me
um
yeah they were like I think on call on a
different server and then they came over
to me and we chit chatted for a while
even though like that that was before
the karaoke stream and I was I just
really wanted to take the chance to talk
because that was the last chance to
really talk before their debut so uh I
was really excited and it may have
contributed a little bit to my throat
being even more strained but I say
that's worth it right
[Music]
yeah so I asked them a lot of questions
that I had on my mind and and they asked
me some questions so one question was
like about
um how okay what how do you stream like
long games
um such as jrpg games and so on and and
I didn't really know what they mean with
how there's many ways to answer this
question
um but like I said I said I think it's
good to have at least one like series of
a longer game running doesn't have to be
a jrpg or so let's just say like
generally like whatever Dark Souls Zelda
game whatever uh GTA could be anything I
said it's nice to have one like running
for like you know every week maybe once
or twice because I know I know like all
those like short one-off games are fun
and all but uh if you if I would have
done that for like three years straight
with the pace that I'm streaming in
then by now I I wouldn't have any like
games and good games good short one-off
games anymore left yeah I waited ages
with certain games just because I was
like keeping them in my stockpile for
times where I need a filler game you
know
yeah so yeah I said it's good to have
like one series running uh and I also
said I don't recommend like spamming it
if you have like a series like Zelda
whatever don't don't fill the whole week
with it
maybe just one or two days yeah maximum
it's my recommendation but in the end
you can do it how you want
um
and then I think we talked you know a
little bit the whole time like everybody
was in there like me and the Advent
girls
but we talked about all kinds of topics
and a little bit about Taylor Swift
games and then and then bizu and me uh
we talked a little bit about Zelda games
and I think
we talked about Zelda games and and and
uh I think
um
the twins said they want to play Ocarina
of Time they said oh me too me too and
that is that that one's nice because now
you can play a Nintendo on Nintendo
online easily and and I said no but we
want to play it like on the OG because
we can and I'm like yeah then why not
what the hell no let's go
um and and and then Bijou I think Bijou
said uh that her favorite is Wind Waker
and I was so [\h__\h] happy because my
favorite is Wind Waker too even though
you know like at the time when it got
released it didn't get much
um like love but uh I feel like nowadays
it's getting more love than it did back
then like people look back on it and
they're like it wasn't so bad it was
pretty good it was cute it doesn't
deserve so much hate right yeah so we
like the same Zelda game we like the
same Tales of games and uh there was one
more thing
what was it
I was never like game that way
I think bonded about
you know like the topic of Fire Emblem
came up and she was like asking about
playing Fire Emblem engaged because she
played fine blend games before
and uh she was thinking about maybe
playing Fire Emblem engage and I gave
her my honest opinion and if I said I
love fire playing free houses and then I
said I told her my honest opinion about
engage and I will not say what it was
but uh shiori chimed in to agree with me
um
but I I also told her like because of
that
um what because of what I said about
engage I said because she's planning to
play or like already started to play
totk I told her in connection with that
that with these long seriouses in order
to not
um have them overstay their welcome what
I recommend is when you can try to do
side stuff when it's like really long
games try to do side stuff off screen I
told you that for me the balance worked
out perfectly
for
um
for totk like I think all my viewers at
the end of tfdk were like yeah this was
perfect like the length of the
playthrough and the way you the pacing
the way you like did some things off
screen everything was like perfect
so I said
maybe consider that if you want to play
for the whole game
maybe consider
doing some stuff like I feel like it
doesn't work for every game for tutk it
was like really easy
um
for engage I felt like
uh we were rushing for the main story
anyway
and there wasn't really any side stuff
that
I mean
you could do like
you know training maps I guess but
it didn't it's not the same right so
yeah we rushed through the game and
still yeah you know
tltk was peaked that's a teotic hair was
so good such a great experience so uh I
hope she will enjoy it yeah so like we
really like the same games a lot me and
Bijou
[Music]
that made me quite happy and uh she
seemed interested in streaming Tales of
arise
I told her oh I I finished that one
already on stream because I was
Ambassador
um I have some facial official
Ambassador let's go I'm actually really
do it but she was like considering it
and and Fire Emblem so I'm I'm excited
that maybe I won't be the only jrpg
streamer anymore
um ambassador
ambassador
[Music]
she mentioned like 10 different game
series she wants to play on her stream
now I wonder if she mentioned
accidentally here if she's aware of
Atelier because
uh I played Atelier on my stream a few
times and I mean it's uh it's a very
chill like I think it's a good stream
game honestly on its own because it's
kind of chill there's a lot of like
creating like crafting things and
running around and foraging and
collecting things in theory I think it's
a good stream game and it's kind of cute
like visually it's very cute and you
know if she likes jrpgs and stuff then
you know you know you know
[Music]
chill with good views oh what the
background or the front
can't be monetized oh well I mean it
doesn't doesn't
it's not necessary to always monetize
every single stream yeah
I mean honestly for me it's a little bit
of a relief that I can't monetize GTA
because uh I I needed to catch up on
things
and why why not you know you guys can
always like wait until the next stream
to send a Super Chat and and honestly I
mean I don't really know because I don't
really pay attention to it but I think
like besides super chats
uh like ad income from monetization from
videos
I think is like like barely worth
mentioning
so I feel like that doesn't really
it doesn't really matter
it's it's really just super chatos
yeah ad income is pennies like that
that's what uh I I have in my head you
know
Nathan please Nathan Nathan
Nathan Nathan Nathan Nathan
Nathan
I feel like somebody recently was called
in my surroundings
[Music]
but I'm gonna try and remember who
I think you broke
no I'm okay I'm okay I'm okay
maybe maybe
anyway oh [\h__\h] did you hear that
crispiness my throat
um like I I can talk for a little while
I was actually happy that was gonna be
Minecraft and not that's it on not a
full-on that's done because
um
I I noticed that if if it's like a game
that I'm talking over
then there's still like some little
breaks in between talking uh and it's
not too too rough on my throat but for
that too
I'm like I have nowhere to go so it's
gonna be a bit more rough on my throat
that's the problem
oh
[Music]
but I'm I'm drinking tea to support me
support character T
um okay uh so wait can I say something
else about uh oh hey
um
[Music]
what do you want to know what do you
want to hear
um
I'm planning uh something I'm planning a
collab with uh all of them
um
working on that mm-hmm
and thoughts on the twins I already said
before that it was genius after uh that
that was before the debut now after the
debut I don't know what else I can say
it's still genius
um
I think
me and the twins have
many things to connect and talk about
um
and they are cute and they're gonna be
really successful and they're gonna do
really well
and uh uh they're cute
twins remind me of debio Kiara why
why why because of the Japanese speaking
is your impression change at all after
the debuts
cutie changed a bit for me yeah
I I mean I didn't like talk that much of
shielding in the first place like on
that call she was just like typing in
chat instead of like talking
so that was another like
I guess like a reason why I didn't hear
her that much
[Music]
um
but I was a bit
um surprised with her
what the hell to describe it her
sultriness and character maybe I don't
know hmm
uh is that do you understand what I mean
like she wasn't sultry towards me
of course not
um
[\h__\h] my chat stopped moving here come on
I also stopped an OBS for a moment
sultry I mean sultry seeing u s s u l t
r y
I don't know what that word means
why do I know
foreign
oh yeah her playing piano that was
really cool like I really like like you
know piano playing people
and um that's really like nice I hope
she does it a lot she should do a piano
playing collab of Luna no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no
[Music]
yeah but she seems to be going for quite
the niche in like streaming topics so
far she hasn't played a single game
right and I think that's cool like
hopefully we'll see her play some games
but
um
I think it's nice to have a niche like
not everybody has to do it the same way
not everybody has to play games so uh
hell yeah let's go
hmm
and I've been talking more and more with
that we've been talking about
is there a debut I think it was in her
Debbie before in the Stream after she
said
um her adult Master oh she's
chicken young and I'm like wait did I
just hear that correctly
because those are exactly my two
favorite I almost remembers too I'm like
what the [\h__\h]
I'm like what the [\h__\h] we kept on
agreeing like I I hit a rap about you
know confirming this for me and we kept
on agreeing on like taste in ah she's
still watching that girl can we can you
call and talk to me already
[Music]
why why it's gotta be like this yeah but
you're mad your taste why is it so in
sync with me
why why
what the [\h__\h] like we have I said we
have the same taste in women
[Laughter]
and I honestly I feel like she said she
like uh likes uh fauna the most in
Council right I was like thinking if I
was uh you know not in myth and I was
just like watching as a fan if I
continue to watch as a fan who would I
have liked in uh whole life English as a
view because I feel like the experience
is different as a viewer
I don't know if it would have been like
if my ocean would have been funner but
I can see like why she would like kiwawa
and fauna you know
I can see it like I feel like she's not
the only one
um
it's not the only okay yeah oh yeah I
would definitely be watching amen
yeah
I guess that's where our difference but
that's why are we different there
I would be watching Amaya
and conservice I I wonder
like I would definitely choose uh
according to what they play on stream
like what games
[Music]
do they play games and I I'm so
interested in I'm actually don't know
and I mean
I mean of course also personally so game
choice and personality I don't know I
don't know
I don't know
Amma is a safe bet though
[Music]
they played PP game yeah that's
something I don't want to see
[Laughter]
um
yeah they played some RPG games though
so that's that's pretty nice
it's hard to imagine you just being a
viewer right but I once was just like
you guys I was watching pecora mostly
I was watching her archives like daily I
never watched her life for some reason
because I was like the moment like when
I really was getting into her she was
already pretty established and she had
like so many streams and I of course
mostly enjoyed her Minecraft streams but
like when I watched all the recent ones
I went all the way back to I scrolled
all the way to the beginning of her
archives and I started there and I
started working myself up like you know
with uh Minecraft but also with other
streams that she did
I just went back for to the very
beginning and you know went through all
the archives
foreign
and I really enjoyed her death stranding
playthrough
I don't know I don't know what it is
about it I liked her taking care of a
baby
[Music]
I was a bit terrified but her walking I
don't know her walking
her walking
uh it's a weird game yeah
it's a weird game she did play Dev
stranding yeah
[Music]
you get it you get it nice
nice why is it so hot oh my God the tea
the thing
YouTube
[Music]
I had a I had a uterus joke today
in my mind
too bad I forgot it you guys must suffer
because of my lack of memory
uh I'm so sorry I know you would have
liked to hear my YouTubers too
[Music]
oh man why
uh
Fire Emblem hop map
I'm still tourists
hmm
yeah
ah yeah yeah
what else did I talk of nurse about
we talked about
possible
possible future
song cover idea
literally cannot hold back
planning things with her
yeah but I mean future like probably not
within this year
it's never sound kind of busy it seems
like she got things planned out oh who
knows who knows
well we talked about I don't meister and
Toho songs and this and that
how does it feel to have a cool heart
that loves you so much
can I say this
um I was janma
I was genma no I
I was I was
I put janma into a boiling water
um cooking pot and I asked her janma
tell me tell me about the new gen please
and she said no and I'm like please
please tell me tell me she's like no and
I'm like please tell me she's like no
I'm like okay
um
laughs
and uh
I don't know there was like I just
randomly I think I just randomly said
without any expectations that I wish I
wish someday somebody would join who
would maybe like me
[Music]
oh 10 minutes typing okay
and and she didn't say anything but she
said
um well she like she like kind of like
Smiles like sassy in a sassy way and I'm
like
[Music]
she said yeah maybe maybe there's
somebody who likes you specifically but
she said nothing else and I'm like and
the whole time she really didn't tell me
but I was like forever guessing who
could it be
[Music]
and I was so excited when we were like
introduced to each other finally
um
I was so happy
yeah I was so proud and then she even
turns out to be a burp like what the
hell
wanna one of coins you dunk
in very sad She's Mine hands off
everybody
you hear me
hands up She's Mine everybody she's my
verb okay she's my intern she's gonna be
working for me okay hands off we got a
contract okay
noted yeah you better note it write it
down write it down make it clear for
everybody She's Mine
it feels so good to be liked
like you know I I I I joined whole live
uh
fangirling of a pecula senpai so you
know
and ever since
I joined you know people you know
usually they're like ah my favorite is
Molly and my favorite is Corona my
favorite is Koda my favorite is nedisa
and so on and I was like oh well I mean
I understand you know not none it's it's
quite difficult to be someone's favorite
and then they gotta make it in here so I
didn't expect it this is crazy
I will treat her well
I will treat her well I will I will
bathe her I will feed her I will dress
her I will hold her hand and walk her
[Music]
um
I'm sure she will enjoy it no actually
okay maybe no bathing unless no it's no
it's been as long I don't have to be
naked um
as long as I don't have to be naked
she's my baby bird yeah but she's so big
she's such a big she she's drank too
much milk
she's such a big burb
she's a big big burp in a big big world
it's not I don't I don't know the lyrics
anymore so I can change them
yay
[Music]
thank you but wait no if I bathe you
like look at mothers bathing their
children they're not doing it in a
swimsuit nerissa don't guest like me
they're usually normally clothed when
they're bathed their babies
[Music]
you know change my my whole idea of the
world
uh no no no no they're not in the swim
Ming they bathe their baby
[Music]
got a sister
no
um
I don't know what to say about that
Cobble
oh
just
[Music]
just kidding I love you but
no it's it's not a new mommy no
[Music]
we're a difficult situation very very
difficult situation
it's it's it's complicated
so apparently she's the tallest now
so I saw a fan art of us me and nerissa
and the the size difference is already
very uh threatening no very interesting
just kind of look it's gonna look very
weird
if we're ever in 3D standing next to
each other how tall is Elena because
Lynn is quite a bit taller thing too but
still looked okay when I was in her 3D
showcase
um
172. oh that's not that much smaller
than Arizona
oh
that's not so bad
[Music]
three centimeters could make up a lot
Kiara finally gets to be the small one
I guess so
and I'm small now
I'm pretty telling myself yeah like my
my size is not so small to begin with so
[Music]
um
I'm smart but it's gonna look very funny
yeah like if Marissa and Bijou for
example stand next to each other on
Alyssa and gura
um
that's gonna look
weird
are the horns counted oh good question I
would say yes because like generally
these things they count the shoes
so they probably also count
the head stuff but I don't know you
gotta ask her I guess
um
oh they don't count the horns horns
aren't okay okay okay okay
oh even though it's something you can't
take off even though it's part of your
body honestly I would I would count
horns into your size more than I would
count shoes because shoes you can take
off
but horns you can't you know what I mean
that's like part of your body at this
point
right logic
kiwawa and her logic we must be bad
um
can't be too logical
[Music]
I don't speak
Marissa you gotta learn centimeters for
me can you do that for me so that we can
have you know more fluent smooth
conversations with with each other in
the future can you learn centimeters
please and meters
like generally whole life is a Japanese
company so they do centimeters anyway in
like official size uh you know sizings
and everything they do they you have to
learn it anyway it's better for you to
learn it um
[Music]
I thought it was 175. Oh you mean you
mean with horns in 180 or [\h__\h]
oh [\h__\h] because that's what you see on
screen if you're in 3D so we have to
consider that
sorry couldn't hear you over the freedom
you mean defeat them
[Music]
you and your fetishes Americans
that's this
[Music]
so funny these days because I went to a
comedy uh Club in London for the first
time in my life I went to a comedy club
in general and you know my life has
changed but I was I was funny before
that like the moment I entered the UK I
was so funny
sorry that's that's honey that's honey
okay it's a honey bottle
a very funny sounding honey bottle
it's pretty much empty
yeah it's like an empty ketchup bottle
um come
but yeah
um
I made so many funny jokes
me and the rmt were playing cards on the
bed to just you know take it easy for a
little bit because I was sick and she
mixes the cards right and then
apparently this is what you do after
you're done mixing the cards you put
them on the table and then the other one
like picks up half of it or so puts it
to the side and then the mixer puts it
on top again you know what I mean
shuffling
yeah cutting the deck
trimming the deck cutting the deck I
want to play it let's play this fire
um
and so uh in German we say or she said
hip up
which could be directly translated to
pick up
um so she puts it down and she says hip
up so just like pick up the cards and I
I'm very funny so I pick up half of the
deck and I put it towards my ear and I'm
like
[Music]
oh
and she's like haha very funny and then
next round she does the shuffling again
and she's like pick up and I'm like um
what do I do now I'm thinking in my head
and I pick up
but instead of picking up the deck I
move over to the hotel rooms telephone
that's next to the bed and I pick up the
hotel phone and I'm like must you want
to see
I'm continuing my joke
and I tried in various ways to uh you
know continue my joke eventually I had
to give up because I couldn't think of
any more variations
I'm so funny
so funny
oh I'm so funny
and then one time
um
we were preparing to get out and you
know on the first day of our London trip
my throat was strained but on the second
day I think is when
um like my nose started running a lot
and so I was like blowing my nose I was
sneezing so much I was sneezing like a
million times a day so I take it back I
think the other day I said sneezing
doesn't indicate that you're uh sick but
okay I mean yes I was right with like it
generally doesn't indicated but I was
sneezing so much yeah so I asked
um to
I was in a funny mood I I I asked rmt
when we were preparing to get out I was
like rmt did you buy any chance pack
[Music]
a leash
and she's like what why the [\h__\h] would I
do that and I'm like because my nose is
running I wanna leash it
so it doesn't run away
and she she actually laughed at that one
I think I think she did
no I'm so funny you stop please I'm so
funny
[Music]
oh yeah it was so funny that I had to
tweet it out I even tweeted it yeah
a little bit like adjusted but
I tweeted my friend sounds very polite
come from I was just so proud of my joke
I had to write it down on Twitter
um
magic good one thank you
we have to change the topic because I'm
not talking about the New Gen anymore
should we continue talking about London
uh because I talked about the first day
in my previous stream we talked about
uh the whole ordeal of getting to the UK
and uh going to the Lord of the Rings
Musical on its opening day which was
really fun really great yeah
so the second day uh let me remember
what did we do on the second day
I think on the second day we did the the
borough Market basically like I I was
kind of in charge of deciding what to do
because uh rnt she like has been to
London a few times before and she was
kind of like whatever anything's fine
and like okay
oh but we started out like uh in the
morning and we had breakfast and the
breakfast was amazing
this is important because in the
following days breakfast was [\h__\h]
but it really got my hopes up we arrived
like half an hour before the breakfast
would close
[Music]
don't you love my honesty
ah
and it was kind of busy you know but I
generally don't mind because I'm I I
just take when I go to a breakfast
buffet I just immediately take
everything that I want and then I don't
go to to the breakfast a million times
like to the buffet I just take what I
want and then that's it then I'm fine
um
I'm glad you guys like it thank you
thank you thank you
um yeah so we're at the breakfast buffet
we're getting seated uh pretty quickly
this is also important because yeah
we've got to seated immediately
um this was did I already tell you which
hotel I did right the Waldorf in the
middle of London the Battle of Astoria a
story if I didn't say so Japanese a lot
of Astoria
very fancy hotel
supposedly
um and I had really really good
experience in a bottle of Hotel before
for breakfast long time ago in Berlin so
I was like looking forward to that yeah
so we get seated and it's kind of busy
but you know no problem but the like
there's a like a server a waiter who
comes up to us asks like do you want any
tea or coffee and I'm like yeah this and
that and like I asked about the menu
because besides the breakfast buffet I
have a menu
um that's it has like like you know
omelettes
uh eggs benedict Etc but the thing is
half of this menu
has an extra charge which it's kind of
lean like you're already paying so much
for breakfast buffet and these extra
charge items are not even that like
crazy special in my opinion
it's pretty lame right so seven pounds
it's not like crazy expensive it's not
like a full price of a meal but they
definitely are charging extra
so half of it is extra and I wanted the
French toast which was on the extra
charge stuff and I am stingy as [\h__\h] so
I didn't really want to pay it I asked
even though I knew what it meant I asked
the waiter like tell
um this like this is free right like
this here and and he explains yeah so
the left side is free and the right side
is you know chargeable but
you can if you want you can have
anything uh for free that's fine because
it's really busy right now is what he
said
and I'm like I mean
in in his book we got seated immediately
I didn't really feel like you know I
didn't feel stressed out or bothered by
it but the business in that moment but
he was so nice so I'm like oh thank you
so much okie dokie then I'll take the
French toast and my friend takes the
eggs benedict
so
that's really nice customer service
right so sweet
um I got another thing uh like some egg
stuff also like a Savory thing as well
a while later he comes back with food
and it's amazing it's really good I did
not I didn't even take anything from the
breakfast buffet in the end because it
was kind of mid anyway
um
so uh yeah that was great had a good
breakfast and then the following days
I'll just skip over because this is a
connected topic
we had two more breakfasts okay
so the following day I'm excited it's
about like around the same time
we go to the breakfast around the same
time because it was fine the previous
day and I'm excited I'm like oh yeah
let's get some more stuff maybe because
we go at the same time and we'll be busy
again and maybe we'll get the stuff free
again if not that's fine too because
there were like
um Pancakes on the free menu so I'll
just take that so we walk over to the
breakfast buffet uh to the restaurant
and there's a huge line
there's a huge line
uh for people to be seated and it's like
half an hour before the end of the
breakfast time
yeah so we're like yeah okay well let's
see what happens and they take ages
to seat people but now it's really busy
but there's like I see people running I
did breakfast buffet service in hotels
before uh as a job for like months okay
so like I've experienced it on busy days
I understand it but you know
it was there was so much going on inside
like uh there were so many staff running
around inside okay but there was only
one staff in charge of sitting the
people she kept on like coming back and
forth uh to the seats and back to us
Tuesday's been to us but in between she
would also bring them like the menu and
the coffee and this and that like you
know the first items which I feel like
somebody else could have handled and the
whole time she was walking like so
slowly
like like it doesn't even like bother
her that there's a huge line of people
waiting 30 minutes before the breakfast
ends eventually 20 minutes before the
breakfast ends and eventually 15 minutes
before and then so on
um
yeah it didn't seem very in that very
efficient from our point of view from
people who worked in hotels before
like really slow just really really slow
and sitting people could have been done
by maybe another staff too you don't
have to be like extra extra trained for
this job in my opinion
um
yeah and the the guy from like the
previous day wasn't there on that day
either
eventually we finally get seated
it just took ages
and uh
they don't however they don't bring us
or ask us for the coffee so we have to
ask for it they don't bring us Cutlery
so we have to ask for it normally the
whole it's a [\h__\h] Waldorf the table
should already be set as it is for
others but it always wasn't set so I
asked for cutlery they bring Cutlery
then they ask for menu then they bring
the menu normally all of this is already
on the table
yeah but actually I asked for cutlery
she says yes okay and doesn't come back
I waited for like six seven minutes so I
asked again then we get it
um that happened a few times with a few
things
yeah
so you know the service was pretty bad
on that day and the the staff was like
just like operating way less efficiently
than on the previous day
we were like what's going on today
what's what's happening but we're like
okay I guess we're not getting the the
compliment even though like this would
be the day where we're actually
um experiencing the effects of the
business this would be the time where
maybe they could Comp US the free
breakfast you know and then the extra
items this time it would make sense but
no but nothing was offered so we're just
gonna go with some free stuff
um
and the free stuff was calamid compared
to the extra charge stuff it was really
mid
um
yeah
yeah no that there were plenty of stuff
planning and everybody was walking
slowly I tell you everybody was walking
so slowly I've worked in FNB and when
it's [\h__\h] busy everybody walks really
fast
but they all walked so slowly
um
yeah so we're like okay this time
breakfast was kind of disappointing but
hopefully next time next day it will be
better
uh the next day I I'm feeling like you
know eating something Savory I just
wanted scrambled eggs but I know from
experience
[Music]
that pretty much every Hotel
chain at least unless it's like I don't
know maybe a fancy Buffet uh but but not
a fancy
uh what's the word I know even this
fancy hotel
they all use
the fake eggs that come like as a
mixture from the package you know you
guys know that we talked about it before
on my stream
the scrambled eggs that are in the
Chevy's
are you know have you ever wondered why
they taste kind of bad why they don't
taste like real fresh scramblies and why
they all like have like completely
perfect one color color
like they're completely
perfectly one color right
because it comes all out of a a paper
package it's a mixed already mixed
mixture with barely any egg inside uh
yeah so
I mean there may be some egg but it
really it tastes it's just not good
right so if they were able to make like
on the menu on the free menu even you
can order an omelette and I tried that
on the previous day and The Omelette was
fine The Omelette was good
um
so
it's not on the menu but what I've done
in other Hotel breakfasts is like ask
for a fresh scrambled eggs and it's
really not an issue you know if they can
make you an omelette or like eggs
benedict they can make you
fresh scrambled eggs
with frail eggs because they're using
the real eggs for The Omelette too
um stay with me guys
I've had this before like even in a in a
Hilton which is like below the Waldorf
in status in like quality and stars and
all that but they belong together
they're in the same like big company you
know
yeah
so I've done this before
[Music]
um so I asked I ask I say hi so I I've
tried the eggs in the Chevy I actually
really did I gave it another chance even
though I know what was expecting me I
say I tried it you know I I know I know
I work in hotel I know why it tastes off
and I know so could you please maybe
make me uh like fresh scrambled eggs
that's all I want you know just fresh
scrambled eggs maybe top of some chives
or whatever
that's all I want
and uh
he looks at me and he's like um
we we have scrambled eggs over there
they're fresh and I'm like
um
well maybe fresh out of the package out
of the oven sure
um but you know what I mean with fresh
is like you know crack the eggs open
like click and then mix it and then pour
it and then the frying pan you know
let's just make it separately with like
real fresh eggs that's what I mean and
he's like
um like he was really resisting it the
waiter was really resisting it uh
and eventually he also said that like he
thinks that if he brings this to the
kitchen they will just like bring me the
same thing and I'm like let's give it a
try Okay because like I've experienced
this it can work it can work
um
listen you know please could you
could you try because I I um you know
he's like okay I will order it for you
so he disappears I also ordered
um
[Music]
I think yeah I also ordered French toast
I think
yeah I did I did order french toast
because I wanted something good
but I kind of wanted to eat it at the
same time the French toast rise no
problem it it was okay I ate it
happening
and then
key aren't
but you know I I just speaking to
speaking out of experience you know I
know what they can do
so I expect a little bit more and it was
expensive too
so my French toast arrives the scrambled
eggs don't I finished my my French toast
slowly and by the time I finished my
friend shows the scrambled eggs are
still not there so the waiter eventually
he looks over and he's like did you get
your scrambled eggs I'm like no I didn't
and he's like okay sorry I'll check
and and he said he did he did put it in
he did put the order in
he goes back he disappears
I wait I wait I wait like 10 minutes
later he comes back again he's like
asking did you get it now I'm like no no
I'm gonna so
uh he's like ah [\h__\h]
he goes back he doesn't say [\h__\h] but you
know he was getting like kind of
frustrated towards like his own staff I
guess
yeah so
he goes there eventually now this like
third time he finally comes back with
something
and
normally
I I feel like I have to draw this
I feel like I have to draw this
[Music]
[Laughter]
I can't hmm
ATA
[Music]
I just I just can't
you're sure
thank you
hello
so
yes I may have been a Karen during this
whole ordeal no but I was still
I was like laughing and I was like you
know trying to be nice and just like I
was just you know trying to make them
unleash their full potential so normally
like when I order french toast
it comes on a big plate it comes nicely
served with some stuff and
you know okay that looks like a face but
you know it's like they they serve it
nicely then I I ordered other things too
like you know and it's always like
served on a big plate maybe The Omelette
was like this and
um what they have I mean sure there was
like some stuff like some herbs blue you
know nicely yeah so the eggs come
the eggs arrive in a bowl that's
size Wise It's like about this size so
it's really a tiny Bowl
it's not on top of a plate or anything
either it's just the bowl
and it's just
the eggs no no chives nothing nothing so
it's just like really really without any
love it's just like this they just like
slammed the eggs into the bowler like
whatever like I can literally imagine in
my head the kitchen person who prepared
this was like
the [\h__\h] you really want me to make this
stupid scrambled eggs they're they're
out in the buffet are you serious this
lady this [\h__\h] Karen should just get
it from the buffet I'm not gonna make
scrambled it is I don't have time but
why would I why would I make this this
is just okay [\h__\h] it you really want me
to make it okay let me just take the
scrambled eggs that we always make
because that's what they did and put it
in this bowl here take it I'm not gonna
make this pretty looking
and then he observes it to me and I look
at I look at the eggs I look at him and
I'm like and RM teals it looks with my
egg and we're both like
because on first glance you can
immediately see it's the same texture
it's the same color it's the same [\h__\h]
that's in the Chevy
and so I look at him and I'm like are
you sure this isn't just like you know
the same
and he's like you know it's it's they
said it's fresh it's freshly made
freshly
and I'm like okay
so he leaves and I I go I walk over to
the to the Chevy the like big silver
thing and I take a spoon out of the
because I knew already but I wanted like
Clear Proof uh I take a spoon out of the
eggs there and I bring it to my table
and I put it next to the eggs and I I
see it's the same stuff
so uh I'm like whatever doesn't matter
um I was like I'm not gonna
I give up I said I give up
and then eventually he comes back you
know it's already calmed down the buffet
like it's like closing slowly and and
people are leaving it's really calm at
this point he comes back and he's like
like he's really nice actually he's like
smiling he's like you didn't like it did
you and I'm like yeah I mean it's the
same you know and he's like oh I'm I'm
sorry should we make anything else for
you and I'm like well I don't know like
it's just gonna be the same right
so it's okay and he's like I'm sorry
you're disappointed I want you know
let's do something do you maybe want egg
whites uh scrambled eggs and I'm like eh
egg white scrambled eggs
I mean
hmm
I I never heard of egg white scrambled
eggs before and I never tried it before
but in my head I just wanted to try it I
considered trying it because
you couldn't make it out of the same
package right
they don't have I I don't think they
have something like that prepared like a
package of egg white like finished
liquid scrambled eggs
um you would have to crack the eggs and
separate the but if they can do that why
not just make me you know normal
scrambled eggs but whatever let's say we
force them to do this
so I was like hmm
okay
let's try it I didn't know what to
expect but
um
I think I took a picture of this
[Music]
Santos
[Laughter]
[Music]
eventually this arrives
it's like it looks like it looks like
it looks like it looks like I don't know
it looks like
[Music]
yeah it looks like anything but eggs I
don't know if this is normal I've never
tried making but maybe this is what it
looks like when you make scrambled eggs
with egg white only
um
like like he serves this to me again in
a uh uh love less Bowl you know nothing
just this like ridiculous compared to
the other things they serve
um it's like a freaking five-star hotel
okay
we're paying for free nights we're
paying uh like 800 pounds 800 bucks 800
900 bucks
this is what I get and I look at I look
at it I look at him and I'm like okay so
give it a try
[Music]
oh
I'm so sorry I said it I said it he was
still standing there I said
laughingly because it was so
entertaining to me I said wow this is
disgusting
[Music]
this is disgusting and he's really
laughing I was so amazing
it's awful no the waiter is
oh is that his fault it's it's the
kitchen that doesn't give a [\h__\h] I'm
sorry
ah
so I'm like it's okay like he's still
trying to find a solution I'm like it's
okay it's like it doesn't matter it's
okay it honestly tastes like it came out
of back of a package too but I have to
try it out at home like it has the same
texture and like
uh consistency or whatever uh as the
other ones but
[Music]
ah so we gave up and
um
I I was just amused and fascinated yeah
I I don't know
they spent a lot of time supporting
white and yellow powder it's so paleo it
comes in I'm telling you like in these
Tetra packs
um
[Music]
you can get egg whites in a carton but I
wonder if they would have had that
prepared because I worked in these kind
of hotels before and they don't have
this like in stock egg whites maybe
maybe that Waldorf does I guess
but yeah
it's pretty disgusting
it was so disappointing because the
first breakfast day was amazing and then
the following two days oh on the second
day we also had to wait endlessly to get
seated uh we were seated like five
minutes before the uh breakfast ended we
waited like 25 minutes to get seated
which is
ridiculous
for breakfast
they were there were plenty of seats
yeah there were plenty of seats I saw it
it wasn't like a lack of seats we didn't
have to wait for others to finish their
breakfast and you know open up the
tables no
[Music]
yeah
uh oh yeah I think
in the end they uh let us have the
french toast for free on the last day
because I think the other staff they
like heard about
[Music]
my lack of satisfaction
[Laughter]
well thanks for the seven pounds
[Music]
what a deal
um
[Music]
I just don't
just don't get it because they can make
an omelette you know what do they do for
an omelette they make this with fresh
eggs and like I taste it you can taste
the difference they made it with fresh
eggs why can they not make [\h__\h]
scrambled eggs
so
stuck I was like I I I had to find
the real scrambled eggs
um
[Music]
when I worked in um in a breakfast
buffet before uh for a hotel it was like
definitely way cheaper than this hotel
like
less than half the price and
for a night and we didn't even have like
a like a menu
but
uh sometimes they would ask can you make
us an omelette can you make us fresh
scrambled eggs Etc
because we also used the Tetra packs the
cartons
and even though we didn't have them on
the menu and even though we didn't get
paid any tips or anything extra
we still would make it in our kitchen
like
yeah we would still cook it even though
this was not like necessary for us it
wasn't on the menu it wasn't something
that we had to do but would still make
it
um
yeah
I would still make it even though I was
like really young
and I wasn't the Cook or anything but I
tried my best to like throw something
together like it's just breakfast like
you know it's just an omelette anyone
can make it I mean maybe a Michelin star
Chef would make better omelette than me
but yeah I would personally make it and
my other kitchen breakfast kitchen stuff
because they're different than the other
kitchen stuff they would also make it
yeah
no
we could say no we would say no that's
not on the menu and we didn't even get
tipped for that [\h__\h] hmm
wow
uh okay and then there was wobbly water
after the breakfast on the second day I
I the reason
won't pull on the pictures
looked good if you look up
I will not show it but if you look up
Waldorf let me look it up too
wild wild dorf London pool
bad nice um it looks beautiful wow
hahaha
oh my God the promotional images
are such a ripoff
[Music]
we booked it because of this I literally
chose it because of this because I
wanted to keep up my swimming reps
um
so I was excited to go here I was
excited I was an indoor pool because uh
you know it won't be cold or whatever
[Music]
laughing and honestly rmt was spooked
out too we go you know we put on our
bathing robes and we go down it's like
in the underground of the hotel okay we
go down and it's like we follow like a
corridor that's like
weird dark and long and outdated as [\h__\h]
and we finally reached like a like it's
not really clearly indicated so we
weren't sure like is this the place but
we reached like some kind of like
fitness center that's huge the fitness
center is huge there's like a million uh
things to train with but like only two
people using it
um but it's like weird it's not like a
normal Hotel fitness center it's like we
both said this is like weirdly huge and
then we go to the reception we say okay
we want to use the pool she says okay
you gotta go here you gotta sign this
and this and that here's the towel you
gotta go this way and we're like okay
so we follow the corridor and it just
gets weirder and weirder it looks like
it's from the 80s or something and
hasn't been renovated since
uh and it's like a million a million
lockers
I swear it's like weird amount of
lockers and they're all like really
[\h__\h] retro
the floors are like bumpy the walls are
dirty it's it's weird it smells weird
yeah it's like back rooms and finally we
reached the pool and until there it was
already like we were like what the [\h__\h]
is this
so we entered a pool and it's like dark
and it's
loud weirdly loud Acoustics and the
wallpapers are all like ripping off
falling off there's a lot of
um uh what's it called when
uh it's like when food goes bad
[Music]
um
mold yeah there's a lot of mold the
saunas are both that working uh but like
the weirdest thing is like almost all of
the wallpapers are ripping off the
towels they gave me had a hole and many
dirty spots like dark spots
I think it was really like what the [\h__\h]
this is a five-star hotel what's going
on I'm like okay well
[Music]
this is not looking like it was
presented on the pictures but let me try
out the water let me swim I have to swim
this is what I came for hmm
it was really really moldy and Flaky the
wallpapers were go going off everywhere
it was so weird so I go into the water
and here's the thing
you will not understand
[Music]
this wildly
it makes no sense
what does it mean well
like I would stand in the water and even
though it shouldn't be moving it's
moving but there was no wave machine or
anything in in hindsight like somebody
tried to explain to me what could be the
reasoning because like shallow and small
so like the water goes back and forth
and like it creates some kind of I
thought that's what it what it was maybe
like the physical at the physics of it
may be created like a lot of waves and I
would start swimming and it would create
way more waves than it would in other
pools
there's no wind there's no wave machine
there's nothing there there's not like a
million people swimming in this only me
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's so weird it's so weird
and it was annoying me because it
actually made it more difficult for me
to swim in it literally felt like I was
swimming in the ocean
yeah because it was so wavy and wobbly
and it made my hair so wet I was trying
my best to like stay over water because
I my I didn't want to get my hair wet
but I got my hair so wet way weather
that in other pools
by just swimming normally and
so
um
I had to an ocean
[Laughter]
I'm telling you I'm a water scientist I
know for a fact that was watered down
water why does that mean
ew everything was so ill like after a
few laps
I think this is why
um my my advice my triceps uh hurt for
days after
because I made an extras like big effort
to stay over the water because of the
strong waves
so I had to use way more muscle power
non-existent muscle power
um you know what I mean
it needed more effort for me than usual
to stay over the water that's why my
triceps I never heard before when I was
swimming and I didn't swim that many
laps either eventually I go out of the
water and like rmt let's leave and never
come back and she's like yeah this is
[\h__\h] creepy like even she would agree
even she would agree like she didn't
want to be there
she said also it was creepy everything
was dirty everything was moldy and the
wallpapers were like falling off
everywhere everywhere
everywhere
[Music]
creepy so in the following days I didn't
go back because it was weird but I asked
um like the following day I asked if the
sauna was like working now because it
wasn't working the previous day and I
called the reception for it
and receptionist said sorry uh I can't
tell you because the pool at the fitness
center their third party owned and
I can't tell you I don't have any info I
can't like you know and I'm like can you
not like connect me to their like phone
and I ask
and and she says no I can't connect you
and I'm like
and I said she said well if you want I
can run down there and ask them
and then call you back and I'm like eh
it's but it's so it's so far like from
where you are like it takes a while to
get there like why would you run down
there just just ask maybe can you call
them and she's like no there's no we
can't call them I'm like there's there's
one like button on the phone that says
um
it said something that could have maybe
meant this is for fitness and pool but
it wasn't very clear so I asked is this
for the for that area can I call that
she said you can try but I don't know
what it's for that button
you can try though I'm like okay let me
try so I hang up and I call it and no
nothing it doesn't work so I call the
reception back I'm like sorry it doesn't
work I tried uh can you like get me the
info she uh it's like yeah no problem
and she runs to the
she runs there and later calls me back
and she says sorry the sauna isn't
working and I'm like okay
[Laughter]
uh more like confused about the
breakfast like there were several things
that were just weird in this hotel
right
yeah
but now I understand her saying that it
was third party makes me understand uh
why the pool wasn't such a awful
condition but I would think that wild
earth when they like use this for their
own property that they the third party
owned
pool still has to keep up like certain
minimum requirements especially if it's
about hygiene
they certainly have some kind of
contract there
it has to be
[Music]
yeah and it's listed as part of their
hotel in the in the on the website they
say they have a pool so
it's their pool
supposedly
but it's first party so if you guys
don't want to stay in the hotel but you
want to see this haunted pool please go
there please if there's anyone anywhere
in London is there anyone in London I
beg you so that I don't sound crazy
please go there
and
[Music]
make me sound less crazy
[Laughter]
[Music]
no I didn't leave any review like the
whole time I was like saying to rmt I
kind of flown on like like in a friendly
way give them feedback I don't want to
complain I don't want any like any
compensation I just want to tell them
that their service is inefficient and
that their pool is haunted that's all I
just want to tell them
laughs
but I didn't and then because arm team
was like
[Music]
yeah I just yeah I just wanted to give
them constructive criticism but I know
I'm not doing it for rmt's sake because
we we booked it with her membership and
uh
you know
that I beg you guys anybody in London
please go there there's like you can go
there without booking the hotel
apparently so
got it please I don't want to be the
crazy one
please go to the haunted pool
s
[Music]
foreign
I have to go swim again I'll I'll try to
now that I'm also healthy relatively
healthy again I'll try to start
restarting my swimming reps
six hours away from London if you still
have
still have the next couple of years
just go there please
my lifeguard training never Incorporated
Supernatural Waters
then that means you'll die I guess if
you go there I'm sorry
[Music]
yeah the the pools here in Austria are
not haunted and they're not moldy so I'm
I'm excited
oh man I'm so I'm sorry that I maybe
gave you guys a carrot impression now
but honestly I've seen Karen's complain
to me in hotels I've worked in hotels
and I'm not like that I didn't even end
up complaining the only thing I tried is
to get normal scrambled eggs is that too
much
huh
yeah
[Music]
it's not even unusual I had so many
people like
um try to get like omelettes and [\h__\h]
from me before
wow so um the hotel yeah wasn't so great
but thankfully we stayed out of the
hotel most of the time yeah and explored
so uh what do we do on that day and we
went to burn market and I posted a lot
of pictures right I posted so many
pictures
um the plan for that day
was the borough market and then
maybe M Ms but we moved out to the next
day
and uh uh the
what's it called uh I booked dinner for
on that
um goddammit I'm forgetting everything
that tall Place yeah Sky garden thank
you Sky Garden you guys told me about
Sky Garden you recommended me Sky Garden
so I'm like okay let me try to book a
restaurant there
um for dinner and oh yeah because we
went to
the the ferris wheel and we rejected it
we went there and we left and we went
back to the hotel to get ready and then
go for dinner
um
yeah but first the Burma Market uh I was
really fascinated by it
and rmt was like saying that you know we
have stuff like this in Austria oh and
I'm like yeah really but like this like
this
[Music]
you guys probably saw the pictures on my
Twitter
it was incredibly crowded though and I
would say that 99 of the people were
tourists I I everybody seemed like a
tourist which is fine but like which
makes me wonder do any londoners even go
to this Market
okay let me show you
um
let me show you all the pictures
[Music]
it's like a big big Market uh many many
shops that sell all kinds of things and
you would say like you would see that
it's kind of like
split into several areas like some areas
would serve you like lots of cheese and
not serve you like sell you lots of
cheese some areas would be more about
like sausages and meat some area would
be about Seafood
yeah you know
um and one area was about like uh fruit
and all that uh this was just a pretty
picture I took with my with my three
times portray Zoom which is was really
pretty in full size if you look at it in
full size
uh just an impression when we entered
the market there were lots of
strawberries I got some strawberries
because the breakfast had like
strawberry on the French toast and it
tasted so good I think that's where I
decided I want to eat strawberries
um and uh these were okay but they were
all screaming so much it scared me like
some guy was like standing there and
like he would like Scream the like first
first half of his very short sentence
like really like
um
and it was so scary like I literally
couldn't hear what exactly he was saying
anyway so it wasn't really efficient
the markets Market promotion jump scare
[Music]
but it was really fast like this Mark
this one was popular but it moved really
fast so it was really easy
um to get some strawberries
and and then I we didn't eat this but it
was fascinating they had like this huge
frying pans where they were cooking a
mushroom Rosado if only I was a mushroom
fan this looks so delicious on the right
side they had like kind of like
decorational mushrooms going on
um
that this was really popular it had a
huge line and then another one that was
like doing Seafood
I don't know if I
put the picture
do I have a picture but and there was
another one like this that was doing
Seafood risotto too I think yeah
um
it was like it was on a weekday so I
thought it wouldn't be so crowded but it
was kind of late that the time that we
went so maybe that's why I was more
crowded
um
yeah uh yeah we had some food this and
that what did we have I had we had some
like sausage which ended up being from
literally South try to to roll Tyrone to
to roll uh and the lady was like
speaking German to us she noticed that
we were speaking German yeah so I'm like
oh Dad this is not even like really from
here this is literally from
um
my my rmt she had a
scallops I guess was that scallops whoa
sheesh and and
what else do we have I don't know I
don't remember
crack I'm sorry I'm sorry
[Music]
just goes straight through your uh
throat I guess I don't know it looks
disgusting I didn't even try it smells
very oceany
[Music]
I'm okay I'm okay I'm okay
eventually she got a coffee too oh and
we got fish and chips and I have to say
this time
oh I also had a donut but this time the
fish and chips uh even though I wasn't
really like I was kind of full I didn't
want to eat anymore but rmt ordered fish
and chips and it was like quite a huge
portion I'm like what are you doing rmt
this is huge and she's like you have to
help me I'm like
I'll see because like last time I ate
fish and chips in uh the UK it was like
not that like good it was like boring a
little bit after I feel like At first
okay it tastes good but there's like
just like not much like Flavor variety
you know what I mean so maybe a few
bites is fine but then eating a whole
like big serving of that I don't know
but we sat down to eat it uh eventually
I started helping her and I'm like wait
this is actually good
it's actually good also she got like
there were different choices of fish
that you could choose and she got caught
which was one of the better ones but not
the best one so somewhere in the middle
that's actually good and I enjoyed it
and even though I was already full I was
like I ate up all of her leftovers which
was quite a bit
and I didn't get sick of it this time
but I think it's also the amount that I
ate it wasn't the full serving so I
couldn't get sick of the flavor but it
was like really yummy
yeah type of fish makes a difference too
hmm I see I see yeah this one was really
fine this this one was yummy I'll call
this default they had cheaper ones
though but yeah maybe Cod was like the
recommended one that's why it's like the
middle option
yeah chips fries on the side they were
also really yummy
um
so yeah
haddock
it sounds so weird I don't know what
that is
Not Call of Duty no
in Brighton it was quite a vibe to eat
it at a beach I can imagine yeah like
eating it in a different location also
makes you know a big difference yeah
but even though I was already filled up
on food
I enjoyed this at the very end so that
says a lot in my opinion also a lot of
the time we were like taking these big
double decker buses I was enjoying
taking the buses I don't think we used
to tube a single time
we use that train to get into the city
center from the airport but we never
took the tube we always took the buses
because the buses were able to take us
everywhere honestly and I preferred it
anyway
um
it was it was fun it's it's just like I
it's intimidating the buses are so huge
it's kind of scary the fact that they
have a second floor is like terrifying
for me
but I would always get up on the second
floor
because like when do you get to be on
the second floor there's like a
sightseeing bus to me normally here like
we use a lot of buses in Austria and
they're like more on the lengthy side we
have like really long buses that have
like this weird thing in the middle that
extends them and can make them like make
curves and all that and we even have USB
slots in the in the buses and it's like
really nice we have really nice buses
good bus culture but we don't have
double deckers only for all exciting
buses
Berlin has a lot of double Legos really
I don't remember that
I didn't leave you in the cold again
yeah that was the problem in my first
trip to London because
um I think it was because our our the
difference was that our hotel this time
was very Central so the buses would stop
anyway everywhere all the time where we
were going and where we would go
um and back then our hotel was a little
bit outside of the city center and so we
were waiting at stations that weren't
used much
yeah
they ignored us so much oh my God
ah speaking of buses
[Music]
ah look at this
good I would like this I'm sure
[Music]
Peppa Pig boss
egg if there's an affinity I was
seriously like rmt should we go to the
Peppa Pig afternoon tea
[Music]
but we already had reserved afternoon
tea for the next day in our hotel uh
which was quite fancy but really
extremely expensive like ridiculously
expensive we were shocked
yeah
um
Peppa Pig playful confirm I don't think
so what is that game even about
send it to her I should I was thinking
of her when I took the picture I was
like yummy Peppa Pig Buzz wait I need to
take a picture of this
I don't even like I don't have any
connection with Peppa Pig I was just
like oh Gouda
my friend got his fish Stoned by a
seagull and he didn't have to pay it
anymore
what do you mean he didn't have to pay
it anymore
because uh it got stolen before he even
paid and they saw it the shop owners or
so wow that's that's nice
seagull
seagull you little [\h__\h] the day when
the seagull YouTuber joined his whole
life and wants to join horotoni I'm
going to
protect everybody from those evil evil
Birds
seagulls or evil imagine imagine
a [\h__\h] seagull
oh man
[Music]
singles seagulls must never be allowed
to join whole life never
okay so then we went to
um in the evening we went to a
restaurant that I reserved so at the at
the what's it called again Sky Garden
there's free restaurants
one is like kind of mixed possibly UK
food
one is Italian and one was just a bar I
think
and
um
and I thought well honestly I'm I'm oh
well there may have been one more so I
tried first I tried booking like the the
main one it seems like the main
restaurant I tried booking it but they
didn't have any availability so I look
at the next one which was the Italian
one and I
I'm like
okay this one I can book I book it for
like normal evening time for us two
people and it works
so we're excited
and we go we go there and
everybody I'm telling you now
just so you know if you want to go to
dying in the sky garden with a beautiful
beautiful view over London
all the restaurants all the bars are up
there at the top in Sky Garden
the one I booked the Italian one
[Music]
except that one that one is in the
building next door
on the ground floor
and it wasn't fancy I thought it was
gonna be fancy So I dressed up fancily
[Music]
um I got baited by the sky Garden
I thought it was gonna be fancy
let's run some too fancy and it wasn't
even it didn't even have a nice view and
it didn't even have a guarantee on the
website it said like there's no
guarantee like you're not automatically
getting entry to the sky garden with
this restaurant so I'm like hmm that
might be a problem because I saw it like
after when it was already too late
I already booked it
but they were very nice they like
offered us immediately without us even
asking to give us access to the sky
Garden after our dinner if we want to
and we're like oh really can we go
they're like yeah no problem uh actually
rmt forgot her uh like license uh no
license but like passport or whatever to
her ID to show because that was one of
the requirements if you want to go up
there's like a airport security
basically they check they scan your bags
and everything and you have to show your
ID and she was like that's a bit of a
problem if you don't have yours but she
said I have a picture of it maybe that
works and she's like yeah you can try I
guess
yeah so we tried but the cool thing was
food was fine by the way it was yummy
but big portion
um but not fancy but it was yummy it was
really yummy
um so we we walk over to the next
building and we walk in and the lady
that first like uh seated us and
explained everything to us
in the restaurant was now in that
building in the entrance which I think
may have helped us get in without even
showing our ID
I had my ID yeah but in the end we
didn't have to show it so we proceeded
next to the security check and in the
security check I thought maybe here we
have to show our ID but they didn't ask
for the ID either
so they just checked the bags and that
was it uh and then we got up to the very
top floor
I think it had a little bit more than 30
floors maybe I don't know 47 or
something 48.
um
and yeah it was so busy and I
immediately was like ah okay that's
where the party is going there was loud
live music there was a huge part there
were millions of people everybody was
like kind of cool people like you know
like fancy cool people people
extroverted people
who go outside
many adults no children and they were
chilling at the bar it was already dark
so you know everybody was kind of like
in a bar partying drinking mood and I
saw people were also in the restaurant
up there dining nicely
but
you can still like go up there and you
can go through the sky Garden there and
um it's like a lot of stairs you go up
and you look around and yeah this is why
I took the picture
um but yeah we looked around and we're
like okay yeah that was nice but there
was like two cute girls
um they were you know relatively young
maybe around my age and they asked rmt
to take a picture of them
so they start posing against the window
although you can't really get that close
to the window oh there's like a big
fence you know and a wall and all that
but they start posing against it and I
am to start taking a picture and I sneak
over uh on the phone and I look at her
Framing and positioning and everything
and I'm like
um
kind of can do better so RNG is like
yeah you probably can so she gives me
the phone and I start taking the
pictures and I get like really into it I
go like from different angles and I also
say like cheese cheese cheese so they
know when the picture is happening you
know you need that that's really helpful
when you say when it's happening please
do that everybody
and I go like down I go up I go side I
go here in here and I take so many
pictures so they have a lot of choices
you know
and and they're like really happy so at
the end they take a quick look at the
pictures and they're like oh they're
really good and they ask me
[Music]
they ask me are you a photographer
they asked me seriously
are you a photographer I'm like no I
just know what looks good because you
know you know you just know when you
know you know it's like an experience
yeah it's just like you gotta get a
feeling for it so many times when I ask
people here okay
let me tell you something
all right
um here everybody if you ever you know
have like somebody asking you to take a
picture either a stranger or a
girlfriend or boyfriend I don't know or
or your sister or whoever
um
[Music]
could be anyone let me show you so this
happens to me a lot when I ask someone
to take a picture for me often so this
is like let's say it's a let's say it's
a not a
[Music]
let's say it's like this this long frame
Okay so
it sometimes it depends but you know
what often happens is there's like a
scenery yeah and then they take it like
this
foreign
often too much of the upper of the lower
body even though I say upper body only
then I'm like not centered sometimes
it's nice to be off center but most of
the time you want to be centered
um especially for just like simple picks
like this and then too much
too much of the background up here
there's like I'm so small I'm so small
on the picture okay so what you really
want I'll tell you what I want what I
really really want so tell me what you
want what you really want I wanna I
wanna I wanna I wanna I just wanna
you know do something like this
[Music]
you know that's all I want
it's it's that difficult yeah
so yeah or if you take a full body if
you take a full body
because sometimes I want the full body
you can help the model if the model
doesn't know what they're doing by
telling them the following thing even if
even if phone has a like a wide angle
option or even without the wide angle
you can do this but often they will just
like you know pose with straight legs
like this
instead tell them to extend one of their
legs to the front it will look so much
better and yeah just
um maybe go a little bit like lower
angle like take it a little bit like
upwards only a little bit not crazy you
don't even have to go on knees but
sometimes I'll do a tube
um
and you can try to take it from the side
sometimes if you want a little bit of a
cuter effect you can also take a little
bit from from above but no need to
always take it from like straight from
the front and yeah and generally again
like
let's say we're taking a full body
picture
uh ideally you want for like if it's for
Instagram or whatever the girl will
usually like it's more aesthetically
pleasing if the body fills out most of
the picture sure you can cut it
afterwards but if you first start taking
the picture
like this
you will cut so much of the picture that
you know like it will it might be kind
of blurry because the person is already
so small
that when you cut it
and frame it better the quality is often
really bad you know at that point and
the it might not be like focused well it
might not you know show all the details
and you know I don't like cropping too
much you know
yeah
so this is this is good this is bad
this is bad this is good
are you a photo
honestly I I get told like I take good
pictures often
like you guys also told me on Twitter
when I was uploading the picture the
pictures from the borough market like
sometimes I don't try to make a perfect
picture but sometimes sometimes I do put
a little bit more effort in I did put a
bit more effort into the better Market
photos
um
yeah
yeah I think it's like just like over
the time this is like the same with like
drawing in my opinion when you draw or
when you take pictures for a long time
you will get like a better understanding
of what's aesthetically pleasing to the
eye
um yeah and it just comes naturally then
like I feel like
when you've never taken the picture
you've never drawn before
you don't notice a lot of these things
[Music]
um
and then when you do you know like what
looks best
the composition composition is so
important
and also like the lightning like when
you take a selfie for example like
before you take the picture turn around
like
180 I think not 360 right
turn around one full turn slowly while
holding up the phone and looking at
yourself
and see where the light is best
that's what I always do
um
often it's not about the background uh
it's more about the lightning of your
face
yeah and like don't take it against the
or often it's better to take it in a
shadow area like if you if you're
outside uh you take it like let's say
you take it in the in the open field
where the sun is blazing uh it will look
so bad walk over to the shadowed area
where there's like a roof and it
suddenly will look amazing
mm-hmm
oh my God I want to school you guys on
how to take uh selfies like the angle of
selfies
so many people just don't know how to do
it
[Music]
I always have to teach people like
anybody like anybody who's not
experienced with taking selfies I have
to teach them because like it's just so
bad
so bad but it's hard to explain without
like being able to like show you guys in
person with a phone with me standing
next to you you know
um
but yeah
it's basically like
you you see yourself on the frame
so often people will have themselves
they hold it like like so that their
face is on the corner of the picture
the only thing you have to do is angle
like pull put your finger control the
phone angle with your finger angle it a
little bit like towards yourself
and maybe put the like phone if you're
tall then this might happen like
naturally but put the phone like above
yourself
like the let's say let's say your face
is here then instead of going straight
you put your arm up
and and the phone instead of instead of
straight you have the phone like a
little bit like this you know what I
mean
no yes
Lance at a slant uh-huh
at an angle
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
yeah try to put yourself in the center
like some people just I don't know how
you don't see it but you'll be at the
corner just put yourself more put the
arm more towards this way
towards that way yeah and and when
people take group selfies even with one
person extra or a group more people
here's my life hack do not stand in the
middle you will have the hardest time
capturing a picture I when I was whoa
when I was watching the official stream
the swimsuit one
I was I was screaming it at my monitor
um
they were doing their best but they if I
was there I would have won the selfie
game I'm telling you because if you if
you're in the middle let's say you use
your right arm to take a selfie I think
I yeah my selfie arm is the right arm so
you're here let's say you have five more
people to join but by you using your
right arm and standing in the middle
you're already usually what happens is
that you already like you already like
kind of on the side you're not even
proper in the middle but people will
like have a hard time like finding a
space so what you gotta do
[Music]
um stand on the very side stand on the
side use um let's say you have the right
arm as your uh phone
selfie arm stand on the right side if
your selfie arm is the left arm then
stand on the left side of the group like
this is you
and
and this is uh everybody else in the
line or somebody could also be here like
um crouching
and then you hold the arm
actually upwards
um
upwards
[Music]
and then what will happen is
you have somebody here you have somebody
here you have somebody here everybody
fills in the picture nicely
this is how I always take the best
selfies with my friends by always
standing on the side like somebody for
example somebody will ask me let's take
a picture I'm like yeah yeah they like
gather around me like on my left side on
my right side I'm like no no no no no
and I I go to the I go to the very end
of the like line of people and then just
take it you know like that or if if
they're taking the picture I'm like what
is I asked them like what is your selfie
arm like what what arm are you naturally
taking the picture with and I tell them
oh oh is your left arm then stand on the
left side
I could I
class I could I could class on this
yeah professional influencer
mm-hmm
a selfie uh like phone uh tripod thingy
helps a lot by the way I forgot what
they're called
I know they're obnoxious and they look
stupid but they help so much to capture
a bigger group selfie
selfie stick yes
the Boomer comes out because I forgot
what it's called
ah
question
and it's nice because with the selfie
stick you can capture more of the bodies
too like usually the problem is like
there's not much space to fit in a lot
of people if you just have a normal
phone that doesn't even have like a wide
lens for the selfie mode a lot of phones
don't have that
so there's there's no space yeah they're
banned in so many venues also in like
Disneyland in Japan
[Music]
foreign
I will even use them for solo selfies I
mean not right not really nowadays but I
used to I used to use selfie sticks a
lot for solo selfies because it just
captures so much more of the body and it
just looks better
[Music]
yeah okay okay okay sorry we we went
like some other place here
[Music]
it's actually like useful information
right
and I just wanted to flex because the
girls literally asked me if I'm a
photographer because I was so good at
taking them some Instagram of course
like with professional photography it's
a little bit different like what people
desire
compared to um
compared to like just Instagram whatever
Twitter photography places you know
social photography I guess is what I
could call it
um different different things are
desired there and more different like
things come with it if you do
professional photography but you know
you know
hmm
yeah
um this could be right everyone even
interesting I totally up for a
photography masterclass yeah but I I
couldn't really do that because I'm not
like I don't know [\h__\h] about real
photography I mean no I really don't
I just know it looks good on a picture
I'm I'm a pro at composition
evening from the UK Canada hey hey are
you in London please go to the pool in
Waldorf Astoria in London and and
confirm for me that I'm not the only one
who thinks that the pool is haunted and
cursed
you're as good thank you because nobody
else wants to do it why the [\h__\h] does
nobody else want to do it
um
honestly there were so many other hotels
like Hilton Hotels that we could have
chosen that had pools but we just went
for the Wildlife because I was like I
want to treat myself in hindsight I feel
like we would have had generally much
better experience in the less expensive
Hilton than we did in the world of
um
oh
also like I had trouble sleeping uh
sometimes because like early in the
morning at like seven six seven eight
A.M
the doors like for some reason I heard
I heard so many doors slamming and
stomping and [\h__\h] and I was wondering
like what the [\h__\h] is that is that like
people checking out but
later on we noticed that across our room
straight across our room was like the
housekeeping
um
back room like storage room
and they would start preparing
everything by for like a full hour like
going in and out and closing the door
really loudly several times
and I I really couldn't sleep because of
that it was so loud the walls seemed so
thin it was straight across my mouth it
was so so like acoustically the whole
building is not ideal hmm
yeah oh oh sometimes we are watching TV
and it's just like
at evening we would watch TV together
the UK TV and I at home I haven't
watched normal TV for the longest time
just because I don't have a connection
to normal TV stations
um
[Music]
and uh I was shocked we were shocked we
were amused and shocked I was happy that
we found uh Kitchen Nightmares running
on the TV so we were watching a little
bit of Gordon Ramsay's Kitchen
Nightmares so uk-ish oh my God amazing
and then besides that like there was I
think it was love Island running and we
were like zipping through the programs
and nothing was looking interesting and
then we were we saw love Island and we
were like it was like in the middle of
like a
elimination process I think like we
didn't know at first what this was about
how it works but like related we
understood that basically there's like
couples they get like forced to be
together with and like mixed and mingled
and eventually I guess you you you stick
with someone and then they eliminate
each other depending on what these
couples think like which couples are
good like they decide which couples
actually work well with each other and
if they don't if everybody agrees that
one couple doesn't work well they get
kicked out I guess
if I understand but it was in the middle
of that process of them deciding and and
we just were zipping through but like it
was so dramatic so we kind of stopped
like there was this like really dramatic
music and everybody like they were
cutting the camera angles to like all
the dramatic faces like they were all
like looking like so serious and
everything was so dramatic and it was
like
[Music]
the person I want to kick out is
it took like it took 30 minutes the
whole process took 30 minutes I'm like
why is this so dramatic this is so
ridiculous this show is so ridiculous oh
my God TV TV nowadays
it was so bad and it was like so
difficult to find something good on the
TV
eventually I stopped at the Muppets I
found uh at some point I found like the
Muppets
like I think it was a movie I've never
watched Muppets before
but that was the best thing I could find
it was actually kind of cute
yeah
yeah like a frog and then I realized oh
my god pomu really sounds like Kermit
the Frog when she tries
she really does
I never really watched Muppets before
this was the first time I know I didn't
know piggy like gets like
together with Kermit wow wow
[Music]
who's a movie it didn't feel like a like
a series because like the plot was
something like they make they want to
make a movie and then Kermit gets lost
and gets in an accident and gets into
like he forgets all his memories
uh and they search for him and they
panic
and finally they find him eventually but
it was really cute
let's watch Muppets Christmas this year
oh
I'm open for it it was really cute
rmt didn't agree rmt thinks Muppets are
creepy
oh maybe it's my person Take Manhattan I
don't know also on the plane on the
plane ride to I think to Japan I watched
the Mr Bean movie I wanted to tell you
guys that
I watched the Mr Bean movie because
the only interesting looking thing at
this point
[Music]
me personally
it was so cute
I really like the Mr Bean movie
[Music]
I haven't watched Mr Bean since I was a
child
the one uh where
um there's like a movie festival
where he travels and there's this kid he
he causes the kids to like lose his
father
and yeah they first like in France yeah
France
the holiday one it was so funny it was
so cute
[Music]
I love them like the moment when he got
the seafood platter and it was like you
disgusting because that would be me
struggled with like like consuming the
food and just threw it into the ladies
handbag so funny oh my God the oysters
yeah
[Music]
uh my tea is too hot
you have to watch the first film too
well maybe I will
maybe I will
like when I was younger when I was a
child I thought Mr Bean like the program
was kind of creepy I didn't like the
show
but now as an adult I enjoy it
I like I like it as an adult I probably
also would have thought that the Muppets
were creepy but now as an adult I like
it what is this about because I feel
like these shows are more like made for
like kids
don't you think or is Miss is Mr Bean
not supposed to be for kids I feel like
it was supposed to be for kids
yeah I don't know it was kind of like
scared to me
because yeah I don't know
weird things were happening on these
shows
for everyone yeah for everyone what kind
of aimed that kids if that was like what
I thought it was but maybe not
um
wait let me check my notes was there
something else about London I'm sure
there was because I was like mostly the
second day
ah yeah there's more
yeah the ferris wheel was insanely
expensive what did I say how expensive
it was like 30 or 40.
bucks or so
or something 45 pounds how much is that
in USD
it's just a [\h__\h] ferris wheel
insane
I was thinking they want you to buy it
in a package
[Music]
there were packages but even the
packages like a lot of them don't didn't
seem worth it
holy [\h__\h]
[Music]
okay the uh I guess that was already the
last day
today
[Music]
one funny thing this is really random
but in the in the I think it was in the
Italian restaurant maybe they asked us
after the main food
would you like some puddings and we're
like what
puddings puddings and they're like yeah
puddings I'm like
no I think it was at the a Lord of the
Rings
uh yeah I was at the Lord of the Rings
um restaurant
like what
no but they meant dessert
somebody said sausage I thought so too
first
but no it's it's a dessert they mean
dessert
um I was like do you like I asked
pudding and they should I think they
noticed we were foreigners and still
they just replied before yeah puddings
like could you not say dessert so I'm
like do you mean do you mean does it
hurt he's like yeah ah yes please give
us some pudding
um
yeah that sounds interesting let's skip
that
I just wanted to say I had blue blue
color over my all over my hands and lips
because I touched the stamp on the
tickets that was freshly stamped
rmt was like you you got blue all over
you I was blue
I didn't skip it I told you in the end
okay uh
let me tell you about the
Museum I guess
uh just like telling you things randomly
now I guess
[Music]
I found
in the museum
and we went and we went to the British
museum because people recommended it
because it was big and free of charge
you can go in without paying anything
they kind of like push you like like in
many places they're like there's like
big banners of people saying five pounds
please donation please but it's free
I found Hollow burbs
this was in the British museum
um
but that's just like one small thing
honestly there were many more big huge
impressive things this was just like
kind of random I was like oh Birds
um but the problem was this place is
huge like literally like it's like where
the [\h__\h] do we go
uh what should we do and
um I I kind of made me and uh rmt by uh
the app
now I recommend instead of donating five
pounds if you're gonna donate don't get
don't donate five pounds because for
five pounds you can download uh or
purchase the uh museums app
and listen to audio guides
all over the museum
and it's five pounds and basically at
this point it's free for them so it's
basically a donation
it supports the museum yeah
um this the structure was huge billing
like the moment we arrived I was like
holy [\h__\h] it doesn't even come across
quite well on the picture but the thing
is huge like off to the sides like
outside of the picture it was also like
still much bigger
it's huge the the the the those like
those the the
things they were huge
and this is free actually fascinating
but the problem is because it's free
it's insanely crowded there's so many
people it it was kind of
tiring tiresome
Anonymous
it's huge
I never been to a museum that's this big
there's like a million different like
areas
so we were kind of like lost in
what to check out so I decided okay you
know what we're gonna I'm I'm personally
interested of course in European history
let I want to see if there's something
like tutors related that I can find
um so we went looking for that so we
went and we didn't check out the whole
museum I feel like you can go back to
this Museum like 10 times
or 20 times and still find new things
really if somebody went there before
you would agree I think
it wears one out physically and mentally
so big yeah
um
it's massive yeah
my parents also only saw one portion
okay so then I don't have to feel like
bad about it like after a while like the
problem is not only the size but like
even if even when we only chose like a a
small amount
of the museum to look at even the small
amount was overwhelming like
the placement of things
it's just like it's like it's like their
[\h__\h] storage room it's like UK's
[\h__\h] storage room
like they rented out like a big haul to
store all the things they stole
and they don't know what to do with it
so they placed it all like
in your face
it's huge there's so many things and
everything has like text with
explanations but it's like too much it's
like overwhelming information in my
brain I couldn't take it honestly that's
why I got the audio guide to at least
like talk to me instead of me having to
read it because it's just too [\h__\h]
much
sorry overload yeah
um
awesome
[Music]
so I was listening to the audio guide
that was interesting like they told some
nice stories but like I could I could
like go back here a hundred times and
still hear something new
I it's honestly somewhat of a criticism
I think it's better to have it be
smaller and maybe charge some money so
that there's less people two
um
it's just too much
too much
foreign
[Music]
I I never went inside the Louvre
yeah too much too much history
um I would go back because it's
impressive
I would go back if I ever am in London
again and need something to do
um
yeah
everyone can experience it and not only
the rich program this was set up like 20
you know what
what wow whoa
wow you built that what blocked you made
in Minecraft
but you also go back to the hotel no
never
not worth it
this is so sad I'm so sorry
[Music]
so sorry
went to London three times three times I
visited the British museum still think I
haven't seen it of course you haven't no
you haven't impossible
Comedy Club you want to hear about the
comedy club
wait after the museum we went uh I
wanted to go this is so random but I
couldn't think of anything else so I
wanted to go to the m M's uh world
in London there's the m m store that is
kind of like an experience
and they clap for you which is nice and
it's really big it looks fancy
so I want to go there so we went up we
made our way there and afterwards we
were we were gonna go for like late
lunch
yeah in Piccadilly Circus
we arrived
and I think we're passing through like
China China Town yeah
while we're at it which was kind of cool
it looked pretty nice we didn't really
stop by anything
um but it looks really cool look
look at all these cute decorations
it's pretty big
lots of different
um
stores restaurants shops
really busy too this is like a reason
why I don't think I'm out I want to go
back to London
um it was just
too many people I've been to Tokyo
and I've been to L.A
although I didn't see much of LA but
still I've been to Berlin I've been to
Paris been to Rome
and
there's something about London
that's just
mentally tiring
the amount of people I feel like other
places like Rome Paris Etc also had a
[\h__\h] ton of people
but London
it's just
I understand now when people say what to
do in London leave
it's it's I don't know what it is
but it's too much
it's just too much it's unfortunate
because it could be so beautiful but the
amount of people is
disgustingly too much
[Music]
[Laughter]
great
um
it's way too way too crowded way too
busy
I'm busy in a weird way
[Music]
I felt like that when I went to Holiday
yeah
I agree I feel the same in Harajuku and
hot the fingers Harajuku is just one
small area in Tokyo now London for me
felt like
like Harajuku 24 7 anywhere I go
at least in the city center which is Big
the city center is big
no that's a good way to compare it
the best thing to do in how to quiz
leave the best thing to do in Harajuku
is go there on a weekday in the early
morning or go there even better on a
weekday when it rains
in the morning like in the before noon
um
that I've experienced is uh okay can be
okay
can be totally fine actually
um so we go to uh
Piccadilly Circus I guess it's called
and we arrive at the M M's world and
there's a huge line I'm like why
I didn't expect a huge line and I look
at rmt she looks at me and we're both
like yeah we're we're not like that
interested that we would wait in line
it's not that important to us so we gave
up on it so we walk over to the Lego uh
there's a like right across there's a
Lego uh thingy I don't care much about
Lego either but we were like how about
we go in there because that looks
impressive too and The Lego Store also
has a huge line and we're like um okay
no and then there's a there's
um one store that's like tea
some tea brand and that one didn't have
a line so it went inside that one and we
were shocked at how expensive the tea is
we were like [\h__\h] hell no I'm not buying
anything and we left the store and then
we uh went into a store that said
American candy that I've seen several
times throughout London
uh placed in all kinds of places
and I wasn't interested because I
thought I don't like American candy but
I went inside and it was way more than
just American candy why is it called
American candy
there's Japanese candy there's European
candy there's like every candy in there
the way it's advertised with American
candy
not good not good it was everything
[Music]
ah marketing
hmm
[Music]
yeah they had anything which was
actually kind of interesting I almost
bought a Dr Pepper because they had so
many different Dr Peppers that was
interested in that
but you know eventually we left that
square and went to dinner because it
wasn't really
um you know anything to see and when we
were walking we saw like several like
street performers
and
the first one we see is like a Japanese
no
here and he already he was still like
explaining things but he already had no
I guess he already started and was
explaining the next thing but he already
had like a huge circle a huge crowd of
people and he had a microphone and there
were like speakers and he would like say
he would speak in English but a very
strong Japanese accent and I feel like I
understand it because I speak Japanese
so I also ex I also understand very
strong uh Japanese accent you know if
you guys everybody here who speaks no
Japanese
do you understand mikoji's English for
example or anybody any Japanese member
except like the ones who are good at
English do you understand their English
sometimes kinda sometimes kind of yeah
so there's sometimes what you understand
what they're saying and sometimes maybe
not so this was how it was
it was literally speaking in in Katakana
but I was like it's Jeff
um
and what did they say I don't know stuff
like uh dangerous
danger very very dangerous
not go over or buy a line you know very
very dangerous
yeah
did you chat to him no no no no but he
took so much time to set up that we were
like okay let's get going we didn't even
watch him actually doing the thing
but he had a lot of people around him
very popular guy and we walked a little
bit more and we found someone singing
some dude ah he was from some European
Northern Scandinavian country he was
singing
[Music]
and playing his acoustic guitar and it
was so beautiful I love to sing and it
was so good
so I actually stopped and watched him
for a little bit
I sang along quietly it was so nice
yeah so good it was really good I took a
video maybe I'll upload it on on Twitter
he'll get some some exposure
yeah because I I made sure to film the
name as well
so that there's credit
[Music]
credits where credit is due
and then so I have a friend in London
she's not a Londoner but she lives in
London and last time when I was in
London I also met her
and and just for like a little cafe and
last time the thing is we were also
there with rmt uh but this time I didn't
want to like you know have rmt wait
somewhere just so that I can meet her
um so I said sorry no meeting but I
asked her for recommendations for
restaurants
um
and she gave me a lot of recommendations
and I chose to go to an Indian
restaurant
and this was interesting and this
restaurant I actually recommend to
everybody who goes to London
uh let me look up the name again
um it was really good it was huge it was
actually like like an experience to be
in there to walk in there and to sit in
there because it was crazy like yes you
know
I don't know how you say it uh yeah
that's how like good it is it had insane
reviews like everybody loves it and and
it's huge this thing is huge and it felt
like a kind of like I don't know like a
salon
like the inside it didn't even feel so
Indian to me the uh inside but I don't
know it was like weird and the whole
atmosphere is weird but so interesting
and there's like a million staff like
one thing they're not lacking is Staff
but they're not liking anything honestly
it's crazy
um
yeah they had so many stats like
everybody was running around
I feel like they have one staff per
customer group
and so many kitchen it was kind of like
an open kitchen you can see them cooking
and and and
there's so many kitchen Cooks as well
sounds like an established Place hell
yeah like there's it looks like like
there were so many like Indian people
there too eating there so you can like
feel like oh there's a lot of like local
Indians eating there because it's really
[\h__\h] good but also a lot of like
tourists and a lot of like local looking
non-indian people
it was like really really cool like I
was like what the [\h__\h] is going on so we
were seated by some really really nice
guy like I had some nice guy was our
waiter and he was so nice like I I don't
understand
this is so much better than the
breakfast I had
and so the the table is kind of small
okay but the menu is like a newspaper
thingy and it had like a million menu
items honestly like according to Gordon
Ramsay this is actually not good you
should keep your menu small but okay
they had lots of variety
and
um the thing is I don't I I never eat
Indian food and if I eat it I'm a basic
[\h__\h] I eat butter chicken curry
because I can't eat spicy food and I
don't know what all the other things is
that are so I go for the most basic
thing but the chicken curry I love
butter chicken curry
um
[Music]
yeah uh honestly the amount of stuff is
so crazy that when one staff member was
I was still like waiting to get seated
outside of the restaurant and one staff
member would walk towards the entrance
and wanted to get in and they're like
who are you like you know because they
thought it was a guest at first so she's
like I work here and I'm like oh okay
like there's so many
people that work there's so many staff
that they don't even know each other you
know
crazy
[Music]
yeah so we were like looking at the menu
we're like ah yeah what is all of this
like no idea what all of this is so I
asked kindly I asked the the waiter can
you like like recommend me things and
can you tell me what's spicy and so on
and and and and so he explains
everything he recommends me so much uh
it gives me really good recommendations
depending on what I'm looking for like
something more like Saucy that I want to
eat with naan bread I really wanted to
eat naan bread
um
yeah and so he he recommends us a good
combination uh I don't think I remember
what it was called yabe maybe maybe
there's anybody who's really good of
Indian Cuisine who can tell me what this
was but it was their house
[Music]
um special
thingy it's kind of a salad uh
does anyone know what this is it was so
colorful yes yes
yeah yeah
um it has like uh I think those were
like potato thingies and uh I don't even
know
but there was like sour cream and like
some I don't know it's surprisingly even
though I said I don't like spicy food I
can't eat it I said this one should be
fine
um it was spicy I'm telling you I was
suffering but it was so good oh it had
like Granite Apple grenade apple seeds
definitely not Grenada what was it again
uh pommu grenade pomegranate
uh
um I'm so excited to tell you stories
guys I'm so excited
[Music]
sufficient suffering yes
the pomegranate it had pomegranate in it
was like a fruity spicy hot refreshing
not hot as in temperature but it's hot
spicy
it was so good that I had to eat it
because it was so good but it was really
spicy even RT who's good with spiciness
she said yes you are right this is spicy
not like crazy spicy like JMT would have
no problem with it but rmt was also
saying oh I'm spicy I need to try this
it's like one of the recommended menu
items um so we had this and and then and
then and then
uh it was difficult to take pictures
because the table was so small and
everything was like squeezed
I think I can show rmt hands right like
who the [\h__\h] like it's just a normal
human hand
it's not even it's not it should be fine
but here's the here's the um we got
bothered
garlic number he was like okay do you
want the normal naan bread or do you
want the the garlic one that really like
garlic of course and then he's like do
you want it buttered and me and rmt are
like I don't know do we want it buttered
I don't know and we're like I asked him
what what should we do do we want it but
he's like yes yes you should it was so
good
non-bread Mommy So Gone why is it so
um
and then wow wow oh my God so it's bread
it's the rice good serving of rice here
we finished that that yummy stuff it's
like a it's like a freaking rainbow it's
beautiful
um and and here's the oh oh this was a
special Curry it was like also a special
thing on their menu
um
I think it was like
normally it's not like this it's a
uh not beans what do you call it again
um
the small
lentil yeah lentils black lentils
something something special thing it was
something special uh quite a bit it
looks it doesn't look like so much but
it was quite a big serving and so we
would eat it with the rice and the other
thing it was really like a strong flavor
and I'm so happy I didn't go for the
most basic [\h__\h] thing but went with
this like this recommendations because
they were really good and really special
and and something I never ate before
yeah and this one wasn't spicy it was
really mostly the salad mmm
yeah
hey that's so yummy I need to go to the
idle meeting right now because I'm
really
one reason I'm talking so fast is
because I'm feeling like having an idle
meaning but anyways
[Music]
I really recommended this stuff was so
nice everything was served really fast
the food was really good it was a really
interesting restaurant to be in this
room
d-i-s-h-o-o-m big recommend
just go no
it's so good can you guys please go here
and tell them you came from a YouTuber
called Kiara
who really enjoyed this restaurant thank
you please go it's so good I I I'm you
know see I may I may criticize a really
[\h__\h] expensive hotel for like
lacking quality yeah and not doing basic
things but then I talk really well about
the things that are honestly good I'm
just being an honest uh authentic person
travel uh tester
The Duality no I'm just honest it's not
Duality I'm just honest yeah I'm telling
you this was amazing I don't even eat
like Indian food ever and I'm so glad I
chose this one because uh it was an
experience I'm I want to go again
I wanna eat more of these Indian foods
thank God they had some stuff that was
like not too spicy this was this was
kind of spicy it was a little bit
suffering but it was really good
yeah let them know I recommended them
please do
um
they probably will have no idea who
you're talking about and and don't care
but
no wonder it has so many crazy good
recommendations uh reviews on Google
[Music]
I love your brutal and fair honesty
thank you
again you guys I want you guys to go to
this restaurant I don't want you guys to
go except for testing the pool and
proving that it's haunted but I don't
wanna like I don't want to advertise
things and then you guys go there and
you're disappointed because I lied to
you
um
hmm
Kiara sends you her regards yeah also go
to the Lord of the Rings musical please
and tell them the Austrian girl sent you
go there if you feel the drinks please
go to oh
remember narissa likes rings of power
another reason why this woman is made
for me
they did such a good job hiring her
I think it's such a good job
I love her
I need to watch the new season with her
when it comes out nerissa you're not
listening anymore are you
gotta tell her
when the new ROP season comes out
let's do a watch along together LOL
we didn't watch along for the last
episode right
maybe just for the last episode of
course okay but honestly I I
don't expect much from the next season
because they like canceled the show
right so they're probably gonna try to
squeeze everything into the last season
or it's gonna be like kind of like a
cliffhanger cut off or whatever so I can
imagine it might not be so good
um
yeah I heard it was canceled like
they're doing they're doing the coming
season but they're not doing anything
more that's what I heard
[Music]
thank God don't say that
I don't think it was originally planned
to be only two seasons because they they
like kind of built up in the first
season for like so many things story
arcs
they introduced so many like different
people and their stories and you can't
do that in two yeah right see they plan
Five Seasons it's not canceled
huh well what I read is they're not
doing more than two
[Music]
are they doing
fine
[Music]
Marissa what you just wrote to me
who the [\h__\h] was hellbrand again
let me look it up I forgot
[Music]
oh yeah yeah I mean yeah he's good
looking
I'm uh
[Music]
do I already know that guys did you
spoiler me just now in the chat did I
already know that
I didn't mean who as in like who I meant
as an
uh what he looks like I knew that okay
okay it seemed like familiar information
but hmm
they did okay okay okay okay
no but collateral is so cute
Marissa I don't even understand how you
can be talking about how brand here and
not about galatriel
like what the [\h__\h]
like she wrote to me on Discord
I can't even say it
and if I can say it
how
a collateria I do love her okay
[Music]
she's so pretty
yeah okay I think I can say it she said
I'm excited as long as hell brand stays
hot
[Laughter]
I'm like who
see my memory um my memory kind of
deletes male characters
I only remember female characters
no okay not completely but
because she's so cute
gosh I really need to to an island
meeting but ah this was so good I want
to go back this is the only reason why I
would go back to London
this is how good I rate this restaurant
so good it's the only reason I would go
back to London
[Music]
honestly next time if I go to the UK I'm
not going to London I'm going to other
places
I'm gonna go to nicer places people did
tell me like when I arrived like don't
go don't don't leave London go here go
here go here I'm like I don't know kind
of far
[Music]
um
or Scottish highlight I would love to go
to Scottish or Highlands Scottish
Highlands yeah
sounds lovely sounds lovely
[Music]
oh no we also went to the wizard shop at
that Piccadilly Circus right there was
also a wizard shop
that like Wizardry something something
uh that advertises as having Harry
Potter stuff Game of Thrones stuff and
one more thing and I was like hoping to
see some Game of Thrones stuff but I
went inside and I swear 90 of the
merchandise they were selling was Harry
Potter
there was like
only like free items of Game of Thrones
things
which were like cups and that was it
so I didn't buy anything that was kind
of sad I was hoping they would have more
stuff
yeah
um
[Music]
should I say this
no I don't say it because it's kind of
weird that's what I'm saying
[Music]
okay let me tell you one more thing uh
we're almost done with the UK a little
the London topics Hallelujah
so as you may know
we went to fangster recommendation from
one person specifically uh I don't know
if you're here in the chat are you here
in the chat I I don't remember the name
right now
um
yeah to The Comedy Store who's the
person who recommended it to me because
I want to say big big [\h__\h] thank you
that was genius idea
um so somebody said how about you go to
watch some stand-up comedy and I'm like
um but where do I go like what what kind
of place would I go for that and that
person recommended I got one guide in
the best possible way a person
recommended The Comedy Store which
apparently is a really really popular
place
for stand-up comedy and
I didn't know how popular it was
beforehand
but so I would look on the website like
what's available and so every night they
have like different specials most of the
time it's like stand-up comedy uh
specials of different people doing their
sets it seems like uh not always stand
up though but most of the time it seems
like they have stand-up stuff
so
I chose this one night that seemed uh
perfect for us the day I think it was
the day before we left
um and when booking the seats it gave us
an option to also have like a
combination of a ticket with dinner like
one main food like a pizza or something
else and two drinks so nice ticket
combination and also you could choose to
have premium seats for only a few pounds
more like really just a few like four or
five pounds more that was like why not
like I don't know how bad the non-premen
seats are but why not so we added that
so we had the dinner we had the drinks
we had the premium seats uh now we go to
The Comedy Store we walk over it was
like in walking distance from our hotel
so it was a nice walk a bit scary but it
was nice
um
and happy birthday
yeah and I already had this feeling when
I was walking over there that like it
might be really busy it might be better
for us to be there earlier but we kind
of just went there so that we would be
on time for the opening time you could
enter earlier
um it would open at 8pm and it would
start for real at 8 30 pm
and we arrived like at 8pm basically and
I already had like this bad feeling in
my guts and that was right I was right
with my bad feeling we should have been
there earlier I don't know if this was a
usual night there was apparently one guy
performing there that was exceptionally
famous
who I had no idea who he was
but it might have been because of him or
it's really always this famous uh this
popular I don't know
so uh we get there I show them my ticket
and then there's like a guy who says
okay wait for the next like there's a
guy coming who will show you to the
seats uh they give us like premium with
wrist bands which are just made out of
paper but it shows that we belong to the
premium area
and we're like oh
so he brings us to an area that has this
View
which isn't so premium it was really
crowded everybody was basically already
uh they were like
it's hard for me to tell but maybe like
200 people there I don't know
we were very very much on the side
uh and it was pretty far back it doesn't
even look that far back here but I feel
like it was pretty far back it was
really dark it was a small space
we had like a little bit of a like kind
of like a table that was attached to a
fence
um it's okay though like I don't know
it's okay at least like you get assigned
a seat because like if we came this late
without premium tickets we may have had
issues finding a seat because it was
already like so full
um but we were seated there and when we
when they brought us there they were
like uh like four or five people it was
a roll of like maybe eight or ten seats
and half of it was already filled up by
some people and the guy that brought us
there seemed to have a general idea of
like uh who he is already seated because
he was like what are you guys doing here
you're not supposed to sit here and he
kicks them out because they don't have a
premium ticket and they're like so they
leave and the whole row is empty now
like eight or ten seats it's really dark
it's hard to see but they're all empty
and me and rmt are like okay should we
sit in the very inside uh
this is this is important all of this is
important guys listen listen
[Music]
yeah so the seeds
there's like a like little table doesn't
even fit a a plate properly but okay so
these are the seats
one two three four five six seven let's
say eight that seems about right
um and we're like okay on the very end
of it there's no like exit to walk out
so should we like go in the very end or
or where but we're like well we still
have to go get food so let's get food
first so um rmt puts down her jacket
over both of these seats spreads it out
but because it's so dark it's hard to
see
but still there's something there now so
we claim the seats we go over to the
food counter and it takes a while it
takes like about 15 20 minutes for us to
get our food and our drinks and this
whole time the MC is like doing like a
warm-up this is the MC like you're not
allowed to take pictures generally but
the MC I think was fine the other ones
you weren't allowed to take pictures of
[Music]
um German move you think so
good holders and it's
it's like they don't sell more premium
tickets than they have
but it seems like sold out
so we come back and there is these two
seats are still open but there's people
someone sitting here someone sitting no
I think it was still empty but they were
about to sit down and then there were
three ladies here
okay
uh okay now the I guess maybe four
because there were only two seats left
here at the end and so we're like um
okay let's sit down
very full now
and they they were like all really nice
girls and they like look over to me and
they're like it's really loud it's
really hard to hear them you know
because everybody's blah blah blah blah
blah it's really [\h__\h] loud and they
talk in an accent too so it's hard to
hear from me but they're like
um like
they're kind of like checking if we're
really supposed to be here and I don't
want to be like uh yeah we were here
first you know but I I don't want to be
like that and I didn't say it because it
like kind of gives like a weird maybe
[\h__\h] impression but we were here first
before all of these people were here we
were just getting food and we put a
jacket down but they didn't see it
because they then said that their two
friends male friends are still coming
and they were supposed to sit on our
seats uh but all of this was probably
happening while we were gone taking our
food uh
and I'm like hmm and they were like
where you seated here by the guy and
we're like yeah he brought us here and
so we sat down here we put our jacket
down but a lot of this information was
kind of I think lost also in the
loudness of the room
um yeah I knew one of us should have
stayed I was gonna say it to Auntie but
yeah we went together
ah because it's hard to carry everything
um
and yeah they were like kind of like you
know we were figuring out like where
they wanted to know if we were not
supposed to be here but we were here
before them but I couldn't really say it
so clearly and I was like kind of
stressed I just wanted to because the
show was about to start uh and then it
did start they were like okay let's let
the guy figure it the guys figure it out
they say that and we're like okay I'm
fine
so we're sitting here starting to eat
our pizza ah wait we're sitting down and
I have a drink right
one out of two drinks and a guy
he's like going here okay a guy passes
by he has a jacket and a bag on his butt
and he like and it he's like I need to
go through for all of these seats and
it's really really barely any space
there
and he walks and and I'm looking I'm
seeing this this is dangerous can he be
careful and I'm like
and he doesn't give a [\h__\h] he just like
happily walks over there like kind of
moving everything on his way like his
jacket touches the pizza of my friends
and then he like he walks by me and his
jacket moves my plate and my my my cup
and everything moves it move it and I'm
like
and he doesn't hear it it's just like
he's ignoring everything around him and
he bumps over my drink it spills all
over here
and uh in front of here are people
sitting that are leaning onto this whole
ledge so I'm surprised they didn't
notice but uh it must have spilled over
to their side as well
and he even after he spells it he
doesn't notice he keeps on walking and
I'm like well great uh that's my drink
spilled completely cool I say it and
this girl she's actually a homegirl
she's nice she notices and she like
tells her she tells her she tells her
she tells him like dude you just spilled
her drink completely and didn't give a
[\h__\h] and he looks over to me and he's
like I'll buy you a new one and I'm like
yeah no whatever thanks it's fine
because I already I have a second one
anyway okay
[Laughter]
space and you pay no attention to your
surroundings it's like what the [\h__\h]
um
Jack kind of pissed off right like first
of all like it's stressing me out that
there's so many people I think I have an
issue with so many people being in one
space it stresses me out and throughout
the whole London trip
and it's loud it's dark and stressful
the people these girls are disgusting
with me I have to like be the the
messenger
um I have to like kind of defend our
seats and and then and then the guy the
seater comes over
and he's like you know trying to figure
out what's going on and he sees us and
you obviously should remember us and he
does seem to remember us and he seated
us there and he's like what do we do
what do we do but the show is like
starting at this point the show is
starting and they told us that MC told
us don't talk to your neighbor while the
you know show is going on because it
annoys the comedians it it distracts
everybody around you and I'm like yeah I
understand that I don't want to do that
either because that's awkward
[Music]
um I don't want to do that I don't want
to be talking during the show but now
this whole like thing is like
going on the the big guy he's like okay
I want to be doing that the guys came
back too by the way they were like what
are you doing in our spots and I'm like
I don't know I'm just I've been right
here first but I couldn't say it nobody
heard me anyway and I was feeling like
really socially nervous for some reason
in this one I don't know I couldn't like
I uh I couldn't really articulate myself
either
um I was like getting really really
Kappa Koto really English
ESL you know and and everybody's
stressing me out you know and I'm trying
to not cry
and then eventually you know he's like
he's like okay let me check something
and he walks away and then he comes back
again he's like okay can you guys maybe
sit somewhere else and we're like yeah I
mean they're fine I mean we were her
first rmt says it too rmt says it's a
guy like we were hit first but yeah okay
I mean
you know I guess so whatever and he goes
back no somewhere again he tries to find
different seats for us that we're still
premium that were empty somewhere here
we're trying to enjoy the show but first
he was kind of like yeah whatever you
can stay seated so we were just you know
we thought we were fine but then
eventually he does come back to tell us
and the whole time I also like she keeps
on asking me what's going on I'm like oh
it seems like we're fine we're staying
here and then he comes back later and
says no come with us you please come
with us and then like sorry I guess
we're not staying here the whole ordeal
was so annoying and distracting
the whole situation we we looked like me
and Auntie looked like we stole the
seats not only to these girls but even
more to the other people surrounding us
behind us
uh looking at the situation
like but we didn't but everybody it
seemed like we stole the seats and we're
really like being annoying foreigners
that don't know where we're supposed to
be sitting and we're in the wrong place
um
us
annoying it ruined my mood for the
beginning then we moved over we had to
take our pizza we had to take our drinks
it was so crowded it was difficult to
maneuver uh yeah and I already had my
own
build and we walk over to the new seat
we have to walk through another line of
people like this but I was very careful
to not spill anyone's drink you know
and
honestly the new seat I took this
picture during the break so people are
kind of scattered but the new seat was
better so the seat was fine the seat now
was kind of Central and we were in front
of the AmEx ticket holders VIP seats
apparently if you have an AMEX card you
get a VIP seat and they didn't even know
about it themselves these people it's
just not like automatic but yeah we kind
of got a better seat
but coming here was annoying and it
wasn't removed in the middle of
somebody's Act
kind of disrupting everything I don't
want to be the kind of person to disrupt
everybody I don't want to walk in front
of people uh while they're watching a
show I don't know
that's so bad
[Music]
I felt so okay why
um
yeah and so I was I sat down I was
trying to enjoy the show the and the
like I missed half of this guy's act he
got like 10 minutes I missed half of it
I was trying to get back into it but
honestly my mood was like hmm
so I couldn't enjoy the first person's
Act I tried to enjoy it afterwards and I
did eventually I I was able to
flip the switch on my head and enjoy the
rest a lot of the comedians made like PP
Joseph
very uh sexual jokes
um they were like I feel like in the
first half at least most of the first
half was those kind of jokes it wasn't
that funny in general not for me
um
um but a lot of them made jokes about
the the AmEx ticket holders
he hates you in this room because you
got the special tables and you didn't
even know because they're like did you
know that you're getting the same
they're like they picked one person from
the VIP tables and she's like no I
didn't know
it's like ah everybody hates you in this
room it's only because you got an AMEX
card
I'm like oh maybe I should get an AMEX
yeah the crowd work was fun I really
like the MC because he would always talk
to the the people
um that was fun
um
some jokes were pretty yummy because uh
[Music]
um yeah oh the last guy though was my
favorite that before the last guy I
think was the famous guy
that everybody was like really excited
for but I have no idea who he is I
looked him up on Twitter and he does
have like three million followers or so
um
I didn't know him
[Music]
um
yeah John Bishop I think that was him
yeah
right look it up
do you guys know him I feel like he does
seem to be well known
in certain places yes John Bishop
you know him yeah he was there I feel
like it may have been
no no it wasn't a secret
no English comedian presenter actor and
former footballer oh yeah he did talk a
little bit about football
he talked about oh my God I don't know
if the story is real he told the story
he he said
back before he was a comedian in his
football times
uh there was this one time where they
took a group picture and he was bored he
was really young and he was bored and
he took out his pee pee in the photo
and you could see it in the photo but
nobody noticed and it was put up as like
an honorable memorable special photo
somewhere uh for like years and years
and years like 20 years or so and nobody
ever noticed
that's what he like talked about
okay
the whole time I was like like this
everybody was laughing and I'm just like
is this story real did he really do that
like what
yeah uh so his I didn't even enjoy his
uh
skit that much I don't know
the one I enjoyed the most was uh
um
oh dear I don't want to say anything
wrong but I think there was like was it
I'm already losing my memory you know
but I think there was like ah
yeah I think it was an Indian guy
because he made kind of like jokes like
they were related to his culture
um and and the the Indian people next to
me were laughing so much especially uh
for him
there was a woman but I was really
rooting for her but she wasn't so funny
and she had this one moment I felt so
bad for her because oh I could totally
imagine what she's feeling
um there's like she was like telling
this joke and and she was trying to
think of one specific word and she's
like she's like literally like you can
see it she's panicking like she doesn't
remember it and she's like saying it out
loud like oh I can't believe that out of
all days today I can't think of it oh no
oh no and it takes her quite a while and
the whole audience is just quiet and
she's like ah and I feel so bad I feel
but I'm like rooting for her like come
out there and she finally thought of it
eventually
yeah
I didn't do a set maybe I should have
yeah but um she was okay she at least
didn't make so many PP jokes
yeah
um no I didn't feel secondhand
embarrassment I just felt uh like
worried worried because you know that
can be very very stressful
um
and then
the oh yeah the guy the the Indian guy
he was funny because he made a lot of
like
um jokes that felt relatable about
traveling and immigration so
uh yeah like something about his like
girlfriends uh
uh I I had they were watching a like TV
show a movie and there's like
um this girl
I guess she has to leave the country or
so and go over all the way to like
different continent and the guy's like
I'll go with you and she's like it's so
romantic the girlfriend is so romantic
and and she's she's asks him would you
do the same for me and he's like hell no
and everybody laughs like no something
like that roughly
[Music]
oh that might have been him
maybe you guys are looking up the the
performance of that night aren't you
ah yeah that's him that's him
I think so
it was Tim
no wait no wait there were two hey
[Music]
who was there on that day
I don't know anymore he was funny yeah
he was in task list I wasn't here I I
didn't watch did I no I did watch it I
did watch it
anymore it's been too long to really
remember everything
um I feel like there was one more guy
that told this story
um wasn't necessarily Nish Kumar
not sure
but then the last guy he was apparently
a newcomer and uh he started comedy with
16 I think and he was like
over 18. and he was 21 yeah I think it
started with 18 and now he was 21. and
he was telling a lot of MILF jokes but I
don't know
he was so funny to me he was the
funniest to me I was actually laughing
uh at his set
yeah and even though he was a newcomer
apparently he was like already doing so
well he was like opening for big shows
let's see what was his name I think
I think I know
uh
[Music]
I were late but it was just really funny
does somebody know his name that's
important he was actually good
um
if you guys can tell me let me see
I need to
[Music]
you guys don't know this one
I feel like I even
mentioned him in the Tweet Maybe
did I
Tom Lucy thanks Tom Lucy
he was really good and apparently he was
opening for big shows yeah
um what did he joke about
MILFs and oh ah I learned this new word
um auntie and me talked about it after
after the set we were like what did that
mean we didn't understand it
[Music]
um
what was it again ah
um he he described himself as this and
said like uh like he's like everybody no
he is dead he he identifies as this
um I think
um when I looked it up it was uh
described as somebody who isn't gay but
people think he's gay
because of like the way they present
themselves
ah
no not metrosexual he had like a special
word for it
flamboyant now that was suspect
not metrosexual not that other word that
sounds offensive
it was a short word
foreign
maybe I can do I see it in my Google
history
[Music]
it was Camp I think that was it he kept
on saying his camp camp and I'm like
what does that mean when he was making
jokes about that too
um
oh it might be kind of British
did you guys learn a new word too
Camp is a British comedy staple he
really like yeah I I I I get it
I agree hmm
new usage for me
somebody
can't be something else and well I mean
a camp let's go camping or you mean
something else besides that
[Music]
never heard it used like that
it's everybody
knows about it it seems in England
let's go camping yeah
anyway so yeah by the end of the show I
I was you know happy I enjoyed it
um
I felt like I want to go there again
that was like my highlight this and the
Indian restaurant were my highlights of
the trip oh and of course the Lord of
the Rings musical the reason why I went
there in the first place
um yeah
um
next time I want to get a VIP table but
apparently
you only get it if you have an AMEX card
how was the flight back ah
oh oh
bad oh bad oh so interesting on its own
that was like it's worth its own [\h__\h]
tangent let me go like really quickly to
idle meeting and then I'll tell you
because that was wow okay BRB
oh
[Music]
foreign
thank you
donkey monkey
[Music]
s
they've been sleeping all this time in
the same spot they have a current
favorite spot
oh
hello let me like really quickly recap
in Japanese too
um
[Music]
foreign
so oh yeah so I did just remember while
I was talking about it many many many
years ago maybe like 10 years ago in
Japan I went to uh like comedy thing in
Osaka Osaka is like the city of comedy
in Japan
but I don't even
remember that it was it was so Random
I didn't even understand much of it
[Music]
um
I would go again though that would be
interesting I wouldn't mind going again
um
yes okay so
London this is
that was uh that was The Comedy Store I
want to go again
but as I said I don't want to go back to
London that's my problem
[Music]
um
so on the last day we checked out at
like 12 right after oh wait I didn't I
didn't talk about the afternoon tea but
I'll just talk about the afternoon over
time uh or maybe afterwards after all
it's the afternoon tea after tea
so the flight we checked out at 12 and
the flight was gonna be a little bit
late so
I think oh I tried to squeeze in
something
what was it Aya I think
the afternoon tea
that's one of the things I think we did
at the end and then
going Aya going to the m m shop maybe
and the museum no no wait absentee was
the day before and on the last day after
checking out I think we went to the
museum and the m m stuff all of that
that happened on the last day and the
Indian restaurant that happened on the
last day all before our flight because
it was relatively late in the afternoon
I think it was supposed to take off at
like
sometime between 7 pm and 8pm
[Music]
and
we've already checked in online uh blue
blood blue after the Indian restaurant
we were like you know just trying to
waste time so we did everything slowly
but we still had a lot of time after the
Indian restaurant we go back to our
hotel to pick up our luggage
and make our way quite early to the uh
to the airport
but the moment we arrived in the hotel
and rmt checks her app
because apparently this only shows up if
you have the app they don't send you an
email
nothing you have to check the app you go
don't get a notification it says our
flight has been delayed by around two
hours
and we're like
ah this is one of the home
oh man what do we do we have two more
hours what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
so we decided to just you know waste our
time away by sitting in the cafe and you
know hanging watching on stuff on our
phone and so on
we waited and waited but during this
time they kept on updating the flight
time it kept on changing like back and
forth back and forth earlier later
earlier later
um but you know
if if
like if we would have went at that time
we would have been uh like four to five
hours early for the flight eventually
like more like five hours because they
didn't even start at the final delay
time they needed even more time it would
have been way too early so obviously you
don't go there that early right
we just waited until a more appropriate
time
because the airport is not a nice place
to be
uh finally it was like a normal time so
we made our way to the airport and we
would have still been there like one and
a half to two hours early
um
and which is plenty
and then in the air in the in the train
uh you know we find some information
that implies
that even if it's delayed by whatever
many hours you have to be there
to check in
at the original time
like originally intended
check-in time
and we were like what
[\h__\h] what do you mean like even if it
gets delayed for seven hours you're
supposed to be there seven hours like
nine hours in total then early and wait
for nine hours in the [\h__\h] airport by
that logic that's what you're saying huh
and and then we we try to find more
information I didn't find any like cases
where this happened before on Google but
I did find like some some like something
was written there like at to check in
and we were already online checked in
we're not giving any
um luggage up so maybe maybe that's
different you know and I I then try to
call because we're already on the way
but at this point we would be too late
we would arrive at the time when the
gate would have originally closed
so I tried to call the hotline for this
Airline
and I eventually reach it and I asked
them you know I just read this is this
okay are we gonna be fine and there's
they they say on the
you're okay you're gonna be fine uh
it's it's it's you know it works you'll
you'll be able to you know get in
normally
so I'm like okay hopefully that's right
she seemed really nice she doesn't seem
like she just wanted to hang up on me
immediately
um
so arrive arrive we arrive at the
airport
um we're very early in theory but we
hurry the [\h__\h] up anyway because I'm
very concerned at this point
uh we make a way immediately to the
security check
and
[Music]
we get to the gate right before the
security check where you put your ticket
on
and
we touch it try to read the code and it
says beep
flights left or whatever
uh can't it won't let us enter I mean
like
oh no oh no
and we're like What do we do and we're
like uh walking up to a staff that was
right there talking to someone else and
like waiting for them to be done
to let us in by the way we checked there
would be no more flights back to Austria
at this evening so it would have been
kind of [\h__\h] and we wait for the staff
to ask them
and while we're waiting for the staff
another staff comes up really tiny lady
a tiny but grumpy looking lady
um who's
uh being followed by two more tourists
a couple and
she's like asking us kind of in a grumpy
way if we're also for the Austria flight
here
and we're like yeah
um and she's like really angry she seems
to have already had a lengthy discussion
and fight with the other two they told
me the girl was really upset like she
was like this lady screamed at me she
wouldn't let me bored blee blah blue and
the the lady like to us you didn't say
much because I guess she already fought
plenty with the the other couple
um but she said like you're supposed to
be there at the original time you're too
late you too late and I'm like what do
you mean we're too late the flight is
too late
what do you mean this makes no sense but
we're like kind of doing PN eyes and
like please let us in and she's like
probably only because the other couple
already like you know fought for it
they're like opening it up for us but
they would normally not have a sled
board our flight she was pissed off that
lady was pissed off and she wasn't even
from the airline she was from the
airport
but she was really pissed she was like
really angry like this is your father
why are you ladies
and I can totally relate to the girl
from the couple she really seemed very
upset
um to be yelled at from the lady
uh I can imagine like if I was in her
situation I would have cried
uh yeah apparently some [\h__\h] happened
some [\h__\h] went down before we
um got there and everybody you know
gathered there
so they led us through
and then I'm like thinking to myself
okay the only reason
they could be so angry and stressful
about this
and they the only reason why they would
want us to be there at the original time
is if they would like already have like
they said she said wait like annually we
were waiting for you we're all just
waiting for you and I'm like what are
you okay that sounds like they're
already like seated in the plane and are
just gonna wait two hours inside the
plane otherwise nobody is waiting for us
right
like how right so we we walk in we walk
through the endless duty-free shops
stress stress through and then we go to
the gate to the screen that shows the
gates
it says
it says no gate yet
the gates will be shown in from that
time it was like an hour later or over
an hour later
you [\h__\h] are you [\h__\h] kidding me
I swear to go who's waiting for us this
is not about us later on of course we
found out that the plane was late
because the the flight from before that
the plane was used for was late as well
[\h__\h] is she on about it
security lady [\h__\h]
yeah they stressed like for for us it
wasn't even that bad but that other
couple was like shat on so much by that
lady
for nothing
we go in there and we still have so much
time until even the gate is being shown
they don't even know where they're
putting the plane and they're like they
ended up even still delaying it a little
bit more uh even after the game was
designed decided because apparently the
the airplane was too dirty and the
previous Airline didn't clean it left it
with all trash all over
uh so it took forever and our original
arrival time
ended up now being like three hours
later
past midnight we arrived at like one
past midnight 1 45 or so
so [\h__\h] late that the trains were
gone and we had to take a really really
expensive Uber
the trains were all dead
and obviously like the all the Ubers
were like spiking their prices double
the amount than they usually are
um
had a similar issue when leaving La
I mean I know that these places they
have their rules like airports have
strict rules for their this and that but
this just this rule doesn't make any
sense to me and the lady on the phone
told me I'll be fine oh well
um
oh rmt tried to you know get
reimbursement but on that site that
would tell her if she gets reimbursement
or not after putting all the info it
said you're not getting any
reimbursement but I told her to still
try maybe contact the airline directly
um but anyway so it was really late I
was so tired I was so tired
and the thing is on the airplane
something funny happens
um
that kept me awake because it was
entertaining
thankfully uh so I unfortunately got a
middle seat
um because there was nothing else unless
I paid money and I'm like hell no
um
I get middle seat
so you know everybody must have
experienced this before you know how it
is when you
um
you're very tired but you're sitting in
a car or train or an airplane
and it's small you can't lean on
anything
because every position is [\h__\h] and
you're falling asleep though and you're
like constantly like going like this
wait
right you keep on like waking up because
you're like going like this right and
then like
like a zombie right so the guy who's
sitting next to me was a really tall guy
on the left side to the window and he
was having this issue and I was like
feeling kind of bad for him because this
was like I think like a two hour flight
or so and he was what what only
and he was just suffering he could not
sleep and this was like in the beginning
of the flight and every few uh
I would say every 10 seconds this would
happen like this
every every 10 seconds and yeah
zombie oh okay
he was suffering and this went on for a
while like maybe 15 minutes or so I was
really tired too but I was trying to
stay awake because middle seat has
absolutely no chance in relaxing and I
was watching
um some stuff that I downloaded on my
phone at least I was trying yeah I felt
bad for him he seemed so [\h__\h] tired
and planes make you even more tired I
feel like than you actually are
yeah I'm landlocked
and I know that feeling I've experienced
it many times he couldn't he's too big
so he can't really use anything so some
people try to use the the the table to
like lean down and put their arms on the
table on their head but he couldn't do
that like he was legit way too tall
he tried leaning forward against but
nothing worked for him
[Music]
so
at some point
he wakes up and he's like [\h__\h] this I'm
done he looks over to me in my
um other the the aisle person he's like
sorry can I can I get through
just like with his hands he didn't say
anything
and he's kind of like smiling he looks
by the way normal he doesn't look drunk
or he doesn't look sick he's just really
[\h__\h] tired
so he leaves he goes through and I'm
like okay he was I guess he's going to
the toilet but honestly what I'm really
thinking is after like witnessing all
his suffering I'm thinking he's gonna
try to sleep in the toilet because it's
way more spacious
at least for a little while I I feel
like that's what he's trying to do
because he seemed suddenly so determined
you know what I mean
from all that suffering and I feel like
that's I I could read his mind like I
think that's what he was trying to do
oh gregorock you don't even know what's
about to happen
seated in the middle of the plane
and
let's say
this is our row
and there they just started doing
service at the very front of the plane
he goes that way to the toilet
he walks and I watch him and he's really
tall but he's just getting smaller and
smaller and smaller
and then disappears and I bend over and
I'm like what what happened and I see
him like in a position that looks like
he's like tying his shoes or something
because he's like kind of crouched but
then I watch him as he and this dude
that's sitting here is watching him too
as he completely lies down
he just slowly completely
lies down like this
on in the middle of the airplane on the
aisle I've never seen this before
and I feel like because he couldn't go
through
to the toilet that's why he gave up he
this is how [\h__\h] tired he is he just
lays down here because he gives up
because he can't go through the toilet
because they're doing service
and the guy who just like looks at him
like really confuses like an older guy
he's like Swift this guy but he doesn't
immediately like try to talk to him or
Pat him no and like a lot of people are
like watching this and like really
confused
uh
and I'm just like worried like oh but I
feel like I understand what's going on
you know because I'm sitting next to him
I'm like I'm like yeah but the cabin
attendant surely must notice it right
but they're so focused on their stupid
service they don't see it it's true one
is facing this way and one is facing
that way but they don't see it
and they they continue on for a while
they go to the next row they go to the
next row eventually this guy gets up and
tells them and she looks back and she
sees it I'm like okay uh
but
I think they continued even after being
told a little bit more until they got
really to this point and then they
talked to him and they they let him pass
and he goes into the toilet
[Music]
and then I'm like hmm let's see how long
it takes them to get out
and he doesn't he doesn't get out of the
toilet for a long time
[Music]
somebody else makes it to the toilet and
is like waiting in front of it because
they want to go to the toilet but it's
taking so much time and thinking yeah he
fell asleep in the toilet
yeah and me and my aisle partner she's
just like also very confused like what's
going on
yeah
it's fine you're sleepy I feel really
bad for you you just sleep in the toilet
do it
[Music]
um
yeah yeah I think it should have had a
toilet in the back too but this lady
then probably didn't realize how long it
would take for him to come out so she
waited in the front eventually uh one
lady they're still doing their aisle
service they're very slow
um one of the cabin attendants that's on
the like on on this side of the uh like
cabbie thingy she goes back to the front
to get something like some drink or
whatever for the passenger and then the
lady that's waiting for the toilet like
kind of says something to her probably
like I was I don't know I think
someone's stuck in there with a
um so she like the cabin attendant like
knocks on the door
and I'm paying attention to all of this
because this is keeping me awake this is
like riveting for me so I'm I'm thriving
on this this is the only thing that's
keeping me awake and I'm just curious
what's going on
so he opens the door and he kind of like
bends outside of it like
foreign holds the door open and he's
like you know
just like going like half and he's
smiling he looks normal and the lady
the lady is like
dude what's up
I don't know what they were talking
about but
[Music]
I know about you but I would be
embarrassed to admit that I was so tired
that I tried sleeping on the toilet
so I would probably do the same Maybe
but it seems like he conveyed that he
was feeling sick and he needs to toilet
for a little bit afterwards I talked to
this lady when she came to do service
for our row and I asked her what's up
what did he say because he's supposed to
be sitting next to me is he okay and she
said oh yeah he threw up like she didn't
see it but he he said he threw up and
he's cleaning it
um and like because you know so he's
staying in there right now to clean it
up
um
so
[Music]
um
now you could think yeah maybe he was
really sick to me I still think he was
just really [\h__\h] tired but who knows
who knows honestly they could be copy of
course but I doubt it
he didn't know he didn't seem drunk I
would have smelled it I have a very
sensitive nose
for alcohol
so it still takes him ages to get out
there like if you clean something I
don't think it takes that long
[Music]
but she gave him like a Coca-Cola and he
stayed in the toilet for a while with
the Coca-Cola and everything and he got
some snack or sofa free all of this for
free normally it costs money but that's
nice that they're taking care of him and
she said that the cabin attendant said
like after he gets out he's closing the
toilet she's closing the toilet anyway
for everybody
um because I guess otherwise she would
have to clean it
yeah uh finally you have to like being
in the toilet for a total of half an
hour I think he comes back
and he's smiling and he's walking
normally and he's looking fine
and he comes over he sits in our seat in
a seat and I ask him like are you okay
[Music]
um his his face color looks fine he
doesn't look sick he doesn't smell this
especially I feel like when you throw up
you smell a little bit like throw like
vomit right maybe not if you cleaned
everything properly and
yes maybe brush your teeth but there
would have been no way for him to brush
his teeth you will smell right I'm I'm
so sure he didn't smell a tiny bit
he looked fine he smelled fine so I
still don't believe it
but yeah he tells me the same thing he
tells me like oh yeah yeah I'm fine a
blood low blood sugar you know
I'm like
okay and he's like I'm fine they're like
you know I'm drinking this Coca-Cola so
oh
I'm feeling good
I'm like okay
so I just bother my I I just mind my own
business and watch my phone [\h__\h] and I
noticed after he's done with his
Coca-Cola he's falling asleep again but
this time he's not like
he's more calm but he definitely fell
asleep immediately proving that he was
tired all along
I don't know it could be of course it
could be like you know but for me I
really just thought he was so [\h__\h]
tired and I oh yeah but who knows
ah
it's so weird I never saw something like
this before like lying down in the
middle of the plane
and they did
it fast
the cabin attendance they just did not
yeah for the longest time what's going
on man
[Music]
uh
yeah maybe it maybe it was a like a
health thing I don't know I'm giving him
the benefit of the doubt
hmm
they've seen it all
they chose to not perceive
it's so surreal yeah it's crazy
everybody in the plane was curious about
what's going on and I was like in the
best seat
I had the the VIP seat I may not have
had the VMP seat in The Comedy Store but
I had the PC here
I know I found out everything firsthand
best scene I had the AmEx scenes and
this is what kept me awake so I
appreciate it
and
I'm sorry for him though like he seemed
like a nice guy and you know he was
suffering so
I'm glad he felt better afterwards yeah
oh I'm exhausted too now from like my
face hurts
my face hurts
that sounds exactly like dangerously low
blood sugar but keep Coke around because
okay or maybe I never experienced
something like that so I couldn't judge
just from watching them makes me want to
lie down until my sugar goes up yeah
okay I'm sorry I never I never like I
don't think I have any friends who
experience that
[Music]
hey Coca-Cola is like [\h__\h] magical if
it can like heal you from such a
situation
it honestly should be sold in in
pharmacies
like people also here recommend
Coca-Cola when you feel sick when you
like sick in your stomach
magical drink people people hate on
Coca-Cola for having like million pounds
of sugar in it but
it's magical you know it can even unclog
your clogged up clogs
[Music]
I don't know maybe it can
yum
yes what you said big reason why they
give you a Coca-Cola after donating
blood aha yeah they they do do that
um
additionally stomach medicine oh wow
that's why it has such a color medicine
always has the scariest color I'm just
kidding that's probably not why but you
know what I'm just joking
[Music]
Mamacita
every time I talk about Coca-Cola these
days I keep on singing the new jeans
Coca-Cola sponsor song
it's a it's a K-Pop group that's really
popular now that got like did they just
they just celebrated their first year
anniversary and they had the craziest
like tie ups so far
um
and there they had McDonald's they had
Coca-Cola they had a lot of like huge
fashion brands
crazy [\h__\h] they sang a Coca-Cola theme
song
they're so young too like oh my God
they're like 15 16. they're gonna be
the [\h__\h] there's dude
it's probably becoming the richest
teenagers in Korea
um
it's insane holy [\h__\h] like I feel like
if you get rich so young they they seem
like so like down to earth and innocent
in the beginning and I mean they still
probably are hopefully but I feel like
this can mess you up
if you if you like grow up with this all
this crazy success
and all this money I'm not kind of
concerned about them
it's gonna mess them up I think
new things anymore
foreign
[Music]
but
I know
yeah there are child celebrities that
turned out well like Radcliffe
no but still I don't know
I hope they stayed a nice cute innocent
sweet girls that they are now I love
them like honestly ever since Betty's
cobal
my Oshi Idol group
uh after they graduated and all my other
like favorite Idols that were like
second best after they all graduated I
never really felt like really interested
in an idol group before and again
um like always only like superficially
I would just listen to the music but I
didn't care about them
but
I'm I'm like watching a lot of new jeans
content
and I really like their personal attires
and they're so cute like I'm caring more
about them than about
others and I I don't only listen to
their music so
um
I I feel like I'm
getting pretty deep into it
yeah
I think you're telling us about Nina I
still have Nina tangents I didn't tell
any
um but they will come maybe in maybe in
the next stream I have a headache and
I'm feeling
I won't go on forever
already it's like almost four hours
this is a really long that's done
specialized stream
drink some coke
feel sick drink some Coke have a
headache drink some Coke have a
toothache drink some coke
[Music]
oh yeah and then um I think we can
finish up the London tangents if I tell
you about the afternoon tea so I saw the
hotel had afternoon tea I didn't see the
price
we just booked it not knowing the price
Mamma Mia
I forgot was it like
I have to look it up again because it
was like surreal
[Music]
it was like a Beauty and the Beast Be
Our Guest afternoon team
uh okay it's 76.
[Music]
76 dollars
yeah we were I mean you know uh we were
shocked when we got to feel like what
what
oh my God we're like What did we get
ourselves into
um
so let me show you what you get for 76
US dollars
there was a harp player playing
partially Beauty and the Beast she was
she was playing B August uh as an intro
and some other stuff
which was nice
I guess
let me show you
I took a picture of an empty table to
give you the general like atmosphere
it's quite nice I mean there's like
yeah just normally normal table with
like a our table didn't even have the
rose but it had the the rose shaped
um
uh tablecloths whatever
yeah I I I know a lot of like I used to
know a lot of napkin folding techniques
but I didn't know this one this one
looked nice especially in red
and then
let me show you this this was also the
same place as where you had breakfast
it's really pretty
the interior is really pretty in the
architecture
so
I mean yeah life harp music quite nice I
guess
okay but here comes the food
pounds and dollars I already converted
it
this is it
I mean you can get some extra sandwiches
like from the same ones they they do
offer you more if you want more
wait wait there's more wait there's more
wait wait wait wait wait wait but the
taste let me tell you
uh especially the
um bottom left one and the middle left
one
tasted like anything like even
especially the bottom left one was
basically just a little bit of cream
cheese with a little bit of tomato
that's it like oh so wow 76 US dollars
worth uh and then
um the top one was nice it was like
tomato with basil uh pesto whatever
and the smaller ones on the right side
uh were interesting
um
was basically like Schwartz boat
and like something on top and the the
middle one was a bellini like a mini
pancake right with a uh
a shrimp and the the bottom one was I
think like some pear or apple yeah I
think pear stuff on like a little bit of
bread but the bread on the left side
like all of the bread was like kind of
like described on the menu as where they
got it from and so on
honestly
it was just it was just like toast bread
any kind of special but it just they had
the texture and the flavor of normal
toast bread
just any kind of bread
should have gone from Peppa Pig yeah
that's what I was saying and then this
was like this was the Savory stuff then
then comes the the sweet stuff but
before that they did like
they did like a little bit of like
special match they were like hi do you
want some magic like the waiter comes
over and gives you some magic because of
this Beauty and the Beast themed
um
[Music]
like they did something
magical they put this like funny Beauty
and the Beast cup and poured something
in and then it was like foaming
the whole time was I was like wow so
good I was genuinely fascinated
magic is expensive
[Music]
and then
here comes the sweet stuff
[Music]
it was probably dry ice now that you say
it yeah that's most likely it
um scones four scones
uh two with raisins two normal ones
get some jam and so on and free
ah actually five four I guess because
the middle one is also a cake the clock
is a cake too
[Music]
yeah free plus one that you share little
cakes like one macaron one macaron
one little cupcake thing and one little
cake thing
and the middle thing is like a chocolate
cake that was like kind of on like
chocolate cookie with chocolate cream
this and that
quite nice that taste was really good
was really a strong chocolate flavor it
was good the little cake was yummy the
cupcake was meh the macaron was okay but
small and I I'm not a big scone fan so
rmt loved the scones and kind of uh
skipped the top uh floor though I was I
was eating the top ones she was eating
the scones no there was there was jam
and butter yeah
um
but I've had many many afternoon teas in
Japan in Tokyo
and and yeah
for this amount of money
per person
wow and you get endless tea like how
much tea however you want there's like a
choice of teas the teas were nice
I mean it's called afternoon tea so you
would hope so right
[Music]
it's so heavy I'm making myself tea now
for approximately one buck
[Music]
yeah the teas are really good
but what I I wouldn't have booked this
if I knew it was 76 pounds
box I keep using pounds I already
converted it
um
crazy right
[Music]
crazy
see the you see the the stains that was
from the magic left some stains on the
tablecloth
um
yeah
yeah once and never again yep yeah Magic
Sticks magic is dirty
should have just go to Patisserie
Valerie Valerie store
half the price for two people I don't
know about it did you recommend it to me
oh
this one's in the hotel so I felt like
it was comfortable to just go there and
also I thought you know wild off must
have great quality
I was shocked yeah the sandwiches were
just like any anything you get at the
supermarket
[Music]
I recommended a good place for afternoon
tea you did
oh man was it Peppa Pig
I wonder what the Peppa Pig afternoon
tea is like
I really wonder
between that the hotel water and the
comedy club man there's a lot of
disappointments in one visit
yeah it was really like I said this to
rmt like at the end when you know our
flight was delayed and we were at the
airport and we were like you know
greeted by the angry lady
I said I I mean you know overall we had
some fun experiences but don't you feel
like this trip was kind of cursed
so many weird things negative things
happen
like they're not like World endingly
negative
but I feel overall like we were just
cursed
right thank you for agreeing
here's quite something
[Music]
and then you know
the taxi at the end like we had no other
choice like
couldn't walk
there were no trains No Buses nothing we
were forced to pay a double the price
yeah
messed up [\h__\h]
oh my head hurts
[Music]
no but still
you know certain experiences like The
Comedy Store and the Musical made it
worth it
but in hindsight I wish I feel like we
made the trip longer than it needed to
be just because we thought well if we're
going all the way to fly over there we
better book a few more nights to make it
worthwhile
but in hindsight especially also because
I was sick and because I felt like I
would I have to stream and all that but
I was sick so I couldn't have streamed
but you know
um
I I wished it was shorter
just a short trip from Tuesday to Friday
Tuesday morning to Friday night
but it was longer than it needed to be
now you know for next time you can try
something different in England yeah I'll
go to a different city Maybe
[Music]
you got several days of content out of
it and you can use the money you made of
it to pay for the next trip
how much money did I make I wonder if it
even covers all this expensive [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] afternoon tea
and the hotel no but um it's not about
that but I I appreciate the the tangents
overall for me this is content yeah
I appreciate having things to talk about
[Music]
places I won't go la San Fran and now
London what's wrong with San Francisco
I think San Francisco is nice
I mean I haven't seen much but I went
once and I had a good image of it
everything
how is the cat Center
well I think she was fine like she
couldn't stay over so
that's a bit unfortunate but she did her
best
yeah she likes my cats a lot
[Music]
massive amount of crimes and expenses
for no reason
I feel like if I
would be in San Francisco either living
or as a tourist uh the ups and downs
would piss me off
can't it's such an unwalkable City don't
you think
so you can't walk it you have to have to
take taxi or whatever
city has ups and downs yeah but this one
has like literal ups and downs
[Music]
La was also terrible with that
it wasn't as noticeable to me as as San
Francisco
hmm
man talking about all these topics so
excitedly
I'm really tired out
[Music]
also it's so unfortunate that I got sick
literally on the day
we started our trip in the morning and
then by Friday when I came back I was
like
I feel like I was mostly healed
and then the next day I did the stream
the talking stream and the karaoke and I
strained my voice so much that I kind of
like backpedaled in a negative way
[Music]
I feel like I would have been
fine but I had to you know I had to do
the karaoke and I had to and it was
worth it because it was I didn't you
know there were many viewers so I was
happy to sing for so many people and I
was excited to talk to the Advent
members in between even though it
strained my throat even more and I was
excited to talk to you guys because you
know I stress myself out when I'm gone
for too long because it was too Japan
trips and where I couldn't stream much
and back to back and then and then and
then only one week in between where I
could stream normally and then back to
Japan and then I come back and I only
had one day one normal day and then I
went to London
um and then right after London I knew
that that Nina was coming and I it would
be like rude and so mean if I wouldn't
like spend some time with her you know
so I had to
um give her some time to
um so so
yeah and then I even get sick it makes
it even worse
I'm so sorry guys that this whole month
was like such a mess
an inconsistent mess I hate it I hate
like for a week or two it's fine but it
was the whole month and I feel so bad
I'm sorry
and then even in Japan like lots of
plants fell through I couldn't stream
as much as I wanted to in Japan either I
wanted to stream more but I couldn't
yeah
yeah but you know I'm back now and we're
gonna
we're gonna do everything normal yeah oh
my head hurts so much
um we're back we're back we're back and
what 66 hours even even though I was
gone for most of it
that sounds like plenty but
I guess because of the GTA streams that
I had in between the Japan trips
label and burps collabs if someone's
Toronto right like I had fun making
those off collapse happen
[Music]
I'm glad you enjoyed the stories they're
good stories aren't they
[Music]
so this week I don't know if you guys
saw the schedule I hope you did and with
the last little bit of my energy that I
have which is non-existent now
um
let me show you the
schedule I still need to upload the
artwork
um but we have
not Minecraft today I'm sorry maybe if I
can get it to work tomorrow maybe I'll
play Minecraft tomorrow because
everybody's warning me about pizza Tower
and it's making me insecure I just saw
like a little snippet of gameplay and I
thought it looks funny I guess
and the other members were so excited
about playing it so I was like well it
must be like good then right right
but everybody's warning me about it and
I was first thinking about Hotline Miami
2. but then I was like wait before I
play that
what about this new game
so maybe I'll change it to Minecraft
tomorrow if I figure out
how to get it running because it's not
like I'm really like like I really want
to play Pizza Tower it's just that I
felt like you know
uh
you know
just try the game first okay okay please
don't change it you want you guys want
to see it okay
I'll try okay
okay
let's try all right then and Members
Only
I don't know yet one it will be
maybe a movie watch along because I
don't think we had one recently
and I want to eat
the popcorn that I stucked stocked
stocked up up on because at the airport
I finally thought
the proper cool and the proper popcorn
what's it called I bought so much
uh and I ate it for the first time in
years and I was like hmm this is good
but it's not as good as I had it in my
memory
in an airplane
uh like 10 years ago or so and I was
like this is the best popcorn I've ever
eaten
I love this flavor and since then I
wanted to eat it again and now I bought
a six
packages but they're kind of small and I
already ate one as
pretty good still but the flavor is a
little bit weak could be a bit stronger
what's so good about it I really like
the the sweet and salty flavor it's the
I think the main one the yellow one
um thank you for the super chats
thank you thank you guys
[Music]
um
so I bought a lot of that and maybe we
can I can eat it while watching a movie
with you guys
if you guys are okay with it
and then do the atda let's go
more GTA
um I don't know maybe we'll finish it
are we do you guys think I could finish
it on the weekend
[Music]
I don't know how far I am
no idea no idea no I don't think so yet
okay I mean I don't mind maybe the next
weekend then
although next weekend I have some plans
we might have to do a GTA streams during
the week but I'll make it just one
instead then maybe maybe on Friday or so
because I think I got plans on the
weekend not streaming cleanse but you
know
um
[Music]
uh I think that's next week uh also yeah
next week there is like two things that
I have to get up like
[\h__\h] early for you guys probably saw
um I'm in the Pokemon unite tournament
S I am aware that it's not a real like
proper Pokemon game like the typical
ones I am aware
um
um yeah and and these kind of games are
not really my thing but
yeah I'm I'm trying it out because I was
uh kindly asked if I would like to
participate
and it's like wait what time was it the
calendar says
[Music]
um
where is it
calendar says
[Music]
might want to train maybe I can in a
stream before Oh 4 00 am I don't know if
it's really starting at 4am but it says
4 AM until 7 A.M for me
and then on Sunday next week at 6 00 a.m
to 9 00 a.m my time I have the Minecraft
ID sports festival
so
Shady times for me
I know a lot of the game really okay
yeah I'll I I wouldn't mind doing a
practice stream if I have the perms for
a practice stream
okay Pokemon Unite
let me just schedule it for the night
before
[Music]
uh and then I also want to do a
Minecraft practice stream they said they
said they're still gonna tell us
there there will be a practice uh day so
I will probably participate in that
depending on the time though
um if it's not like 5 a.m for me
fauna can train me
should I do it as a collab I feel like
maybe I should get into it on my own I
don't know
um I can ask her maybe if she's not like
already being asked by everybody else
oh okay
[Music]
um yeah Minecraft I want to do at least
one brand stream maybe two because I
don't want to suck I don't want to suck
for one game apparently am being put
into the same like like it's a duo with
Kaila against everybody else but I don't
wanna I don't want to disappoint Kaila
so once they put out the info on where
to practice and when to practice I will
be participating in that
[Music]
maybe me and Kyla can do a practice
stream together as well oh my God I
think there will be a lot of collapse
next week
let me ask for now
wanna
we haven't collabed one-on-one with fun
in a long time haven't we
[Music]
for the Pokemon unite thing
uh two
teach and train me a bit in a collabo
stream
[Music]
what time is it now in like American
time PSD CST EST
I would say around this time would be
good for you know collapse of Na girls
usually that's what I like to do
oh okay
[Music]
okay I asked her no regretting spaghetti
well
[Music]
or
evening or morning jst would work for me
then
[\h__\h] I forgot that oh yeah right
[Music]
um
can she even no I think you know because
for myth like when uh
like we don't don't they have like a
streaming setup
[Music]
we probably have a streaming setup I
think she's waking early in Japan yeah
have they they yeah okay okay then
she'll be able to help me normally I
guess
[Music]
she's doing morning gestures
is she trying to keep her normal
streaming times or what
[Music]
okay okay I don't know how busy she is
so who knows if we can set it up but
uh yeah damn I have absolutely no idea
what to expect the only thing I ever saw
of the game was like a trailer when it
was first announced I think and I was
like hmm no kind
I have no idea
just know it's a mobile game yeah
dude do I play it on my phone
do I have to stream it from my phone or
like an iPad or so or is it on the
computer
switch
ah okay well that's um more convenient
for me than to play on an iPad or phone
okay
wait so they use the usual
um online Nintendo online
okay
is that gonna work well
for a
uh they have their own service okay okay
okay
because I saw I first thought it's only
like Enid members but I saw Japanese
members are participating too
so
I hope it will be fine
[Music]
with like all these different continents
participating
what what's even like the system are we
gonna be one versus one and then go up
and then again this is just like a
normal bracket system probably right
yeah right they did tell me it's a team
game
the team decided
not enough anything did they say
something
ah
Japan versus ID versus Ian oh so farmer
isn't even against me okay so because I
was wondering if she's like playing
against me then she might not want to
help me
okay okay interesting en team oh
I think I saw Cali Iris fauna meet and
was it Bales or or Ina or
[Music]
yeah me
that'll be an opportunity to talk to Ami
the other day I was like in VC with
narissa just alone just us two
talking about specific things
suddenly Ahmed comes in she's like I
don't I just want to listen don't mind
me and she muted herself and she was
just listening and I'm like oh
okay I would never tell Amit to leave
still listening girl you love me too
much
I love you too
ah cute hey it's so surreal to me that
someone likes me
[Music]
how is that
why
what I mean I know you guys love me but
I mean like somebody in whole life
specifically liking me like as like you
know not just like oh I met her she's
nice I like her but like she likes likes
me
[Music]
she's been watching my streams she's got
my
she's got my birthday blanket she's got
my my plushie Bijou told me that she
like they met up and she brought her
plushie to sleep with it
cute
I love her
[Music]
Coop huh
long wow you must love me so much to
bring along a Plessy of me
[Applause]
y'all
see I'm I'm gonna be the best Senpai I
could ever be for her
I want to do like a little podcast with
Marissa
I just want something regular with
narissa
hey emotional support Plus
we should do something somewhat regular
do you want to join girls talk like at
least for one episode
of course you want to
wait
let's talk about cute girls
when girls talk you know girls talk was
supposed to be things girls talk about
but what about what about we make one
girl stock episode girls just talking
about girls like fawning over girls
[Music]
talk about cute things about girls
just a really gay episode
[Music]
just just girls talk
girls
stock
or maybe Ollie should be there too yeah
[Music]
reasons why certain girls are cute
pointing at their illustration this part
is cute this part is cute this part is
cute this part is cute because this and
this
[Music]
Golden Gate time that's still so surreal
to me
that's something some what was it like
some food some popcorn or some what was
that called Golden Gate time
[Music]
an ice cream layer right
laughs
I've had narissa was my quarter for less
than a week and if anything happens or I
would end everyone's in this room and
then myself
yeah can we hope for whole talk in the
near future oh I was just thinking about
it yeah I do want to pick up whole talk
again because yeah I've been so busy I
couldn't do anything
still gotta finish uh four fourth gen
right yeah Fortune
[Music]
nanola
never to sing
the song
um
[Music]
do you think but it's English I was
gonna say do you think I can request her
to sing it it will be quite a struggle
it would be asking quite a lot of her
I'm alive still breathing stop to hide
doesn't realize that to survive
[Music]
so good can I sing it again
can I sing it again
oh why is this song So Good
why is this song So Good
oh I need to tomorrow
record something because I'm kind of
like yabe
now that I was gone for so long I didn't
have time to record things but the
lyrics are done for all my songs and I
have to record a couple so I don't think
I have much time this week to record
because I I like have the whole weekend
with GTA
um
I'll try to record maybe tomorrow or the
day after tomorrow like at least one
song
for for the album
yes
foreign
[Music]
the instrumental
okay fine
it's just my head that hurts so much
right now
I can sing one song
and then I say goodbye
am I am I yeah bye on super chats guys
somebody's surely keeping track Amaya
bye can I read them tomorrow
am I yeah bye should I be worried
it can't be so bad I just called up a
while ago
[Music]
hmm
no don't make it worse
[Music]
are you listening do you know the song
it's so good you should know it because
your kfp
[Music]
I want to hear nerissa Sing it too
okay let me sit properly
come by come bye
time us
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm alive still breathing stop to hide
done grieving realize that to survive
someone's got to stand and fight and
I've tried to believe in only time stop
the bleeding I'm not waiting anymore I
know what I came here for
cause feelings are temporary with broken
hearts get the sky
High the darkness no longer
chasing and hunting and this time I'm
coming for blast
be the last one to laugh then you run
out of breath catching up
baby you don't even know me at all
still kicking Break The Rules rewrite
the system and my story wasn't done
strep and I have been rocked against
kept the court during the Witch and
you'll regret what you're missing and
I'll take it to the Grave that's the
pressure
[Music]
no longer scares me with me I'm chasing
and hunting and this time I'm coming for
blast
to be the last one to laugh when you run
out of breath catching up
you don't even know me at all
[Music]
good
Ness
[Applause]
be the last one to laugh then you run
out of breath catching on
I'm a fresh and a half baby you don't
even know me at all
[Music]
no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no
[Music]
I'm Raptor
[Laughter]
I love the song so much
what a bump
this movie is meowing and suffering in
the distance that little [\h__\h]
Raptor
wow
baby
I hate her so much
hate that little [\h__\h]
love her though I hate you I love you
what did nervous to say
let's Scrolls
oh can't find it
Let It Go
what'd you say that's my wife
laughs
forced marriage
it's okay I accept it
[Music]
why is my cat suffering
maybe I should check up on her but she's
you know she's always like this
I feel bad
I feel so bad well well well
four and a half hours
of chitty chatty
did you guys enjoy
the tangents
I'm sorry we couldn't play Minecraft
yeah
well you're lucky because finally the
London
tangents are done
thank god
let's leave London forever behind
as it's supposed to be
what she's meowing like crazy
oh
you missed me
oh thank you great Minecraft
[Music]
but at least I could focus on the
tangents probably a good thing
because I
otherwise I'm like really scattered when
I tell my tensions and it's difficult to
uh to um
to show pictures if I was playing
Minecraft
Raiders
welcome
who's writing me this song I heard that
the twins rated me in the waiting room
thank you twins is this gonna happen
more often now because that was at their
Morning Show right
so this is am I finally gonna be raided
by people maybe by the Twins when they
do an early stream
is this gonna be a thing
oh my God
yeah we're completely out of uh chicken
nuggets now that uh so many
people visited kfp at once
they seem to be big dogs not small dogs
they're not Chihuahuas after all so I
like big dogs honestly
I prefer big doggos over small doggos
very much
short stream always 30 minutes right
yeah I heard I heard they told me that
was their plan
um
nice in smart of them to have something
like regular going on
always good to have some regular program
going on
and it shows me that they're open to
being awake early in the morning for
them
which
shows me they're really willing to be
open awake at any time
so I'm gonna write that down
for the future
they showcased dog was in their stream
on the podcast
what if I send them cat pictures and
just say their dogs believe me believe
me
Ducks can't really tell can they they're
excited about any animal
they're like
about anything so I'll just send them
cat pictures
and hope they feature my cats
they have no idea
they don't know
no they like cats I know I know they
love cats hmm
but will they show cats
[Music]
I want to see
I want to see cats but also
um I wouldn't mind looking at some
doggos if it's like a Samoyed or Corgi
Bots Show us the Corgi butts please
[Music]
ah so yeah I've been gone but honestly
if you think about it maybe it was good
because you guys could like check out
the newbies
without being forced
to watch me
by principle
yeah so did you check out the newbies
huh
did you check him out
the newcomers
and in that voice okay yeah
pretty cool
catching up on their debuts there is
something
coincidence me too
um
Bijou funny really
is she funny what did she say is she
funnier than me nobody can be funnier
than comedian Wawa hmm
hmm
there is a new Orchid Blitz
all right
don't say that to my face
[Music]
issue is a Leroy Jenkins
what
[Music]
statement
Egypt has a similar sense of humor to
Guru or I can see that I can imagine
maybe it's a thing with small people
they have the same sense of humor I yeah
I really like the whole Rock thing and
the pickaxe kind of got a you know it's
like it's like you're doing archeology
you have to first
like
you have to face them like and uncover
Her Like She's a
when you when you call it like an old
old
mummy
[Laughter]
yeah
and you go
and out comes a fossil yeah she's a
fossil
um
I love it
[Music]
oh
don't I have a huge uh Minecraft pickaxe
that can turn into a sword too but
I have Minecraft pickaxe version is
right like a huge one like a big like
human sized one
and I was like what the [\h__\h] do I do
with this
maybe if I ever meet her
I'll give it to her
present
I do I do have it
uh I don't know when I will ever meet
her when when will be the first time but
I hopefully will not remind me guys
please remind me
when the day comes I will mine her yeah
didn't you give it to Mama Tony I don't
think so I think I gave her maybe
something else wrong
cruel well well she's a cool high
she has to go through certain trials you
know
could there be a hollow Advent calendar
decision I think so I've been talking
with management about it
[Music]
um
so this time I'll get the support from
them but I said I'm very very open to
helping them uh
control everybody
like getting their [\h__\h] done
but this time we can plan everything way
more early
so yeah and Advent I thought it was
really funny Advent will be taking part
in the Advent calendar
yeah if Advent never releases an advent
calendar merch
[Music]
then what the [\h__\h] are you doing riot
but they have to release it early enough
so that you guys could actually receive
it before Advent is happening
[Music]
ah anyway I think we talked enough did
we
Dilly Dilly
[Music]
no
are you guys we see each other tomorrow
for a pizza Tower I guess
um
yeah I actually cooked yesterday it was
weird because hello fresh I got the box
and I remembered that I chose recipes
but I opened the box and you know before
opening all the packages they're all
like packaged separately I opened the
recipes
uh it's like an envelope and I open the
recipes and it's like all different
recipes I'm like what did I choose this
I don't think so and I'm like I guess
whatever they sent me the wrong ones but
I'll cook it I guess so I checked
usually and there's like on the recipes
there's numbers and then you check the
bags they have numbers on them too
so I'd look for the number on the bags
and they didn't have it I'm like what's
going on and turns out they sent me the
right ingredients but they sent me the
wrong printed out recipes but I could
um
open the recipe on the hellofresh like
app so no problem
but it happened to me before where they
sent me the wrong ingredients too
yeah but this time it's not so bad
because I yeah I could just
you say farewell to your Koreans and say
it was kind
[Music]
of kind of more like wow thank you so
much I did I did try to do that but yeah
she just left on time she said oh yeah
just uh you know if you want you can
book me again and yeah thank you you
were a good student you should continue
I'm like thank you so much and I I don't
know it was just like so
and she was gone she's a normal goodbye
and I'm like
we spent so many so much time together
and we talked about private things too
today she even showed me pictures of her
children and her husband
she asked me because it was related to
the topic that we were learning I
learned a word for taking after someone
and she asked me if her kids take after
her and I'm like no not really huh and
she's like yeah I don't think so either
is that all I meant to you so my job
here is done
no she was really nice and
um yeah I I do think I want to book more
lessons
but
um
for now like honestly it's been really
difficult to squeeze the lessons into my
schedules
it's not just a lesson because it's also
like studying in my free time to keep up
with the lessons
and I think for now I just want like a
few two or three months without that
pressure and obligation and but I will
do like Korean study streams to not
forget everything I learned and paid a
lot of money to learn for
[Music]
yeah okay my head hurts um my eyes are
tired I can't
foreign
[Music]
I don't know uh because normally like
I'm like always like not really like you
know
involved like I don't get rated so you
um but uh like recently for the for the
karaoke uh
uh relay
uh I asked nobody was gonna do this but
I asked the staff like in openly in the
like Discord Channel I was like hey
since this is a relay are we gonna be
doing like you know
um uh
what's it called
redirecting and the staff was like oh
yeah you know what yes everybody please
set your redirecting and suddenly
everybody was like Hey Senpai you don't
have your redirecting thingy on can you
turn it on and everybody turns it on you
know they're all like communicating with
each other suddenly like oh hey I did it
for you can you do it for me can you
turn it on can you turn it on yours is
also turned off can you turn it on and
hey I set the redirecting for you yeah
yeah yeah
they were not going to do it otherwise
[Music]
I got the ball rolling yeah so now
everybody turned it on at least
everybody who was like in the relay
um I think like a lot of them didn't
didn't even realize that this function
existed until now because they don't
really know twitch a lot of them I think
so I think they probably also didn't
know that it exists for YouTube now too
um
I told Ina to turn it on for the relay
and then she turned it on last like she
turned it on while I was already
streaming so I set it last minute when I
already like ended the stream on obs
ended up not raining me though
but the viewers still came over I think
because I saw a lot of Japanese people
in the chat
but I think like most other Japanese
members ended up raiding each other so
that was nice to see
um
I was nice to see yeah she was kind of
like you know things were not going well
she had the Ian curse that I had today
with Minecraft
[Music]
so I think tomorrow hopefully everything
should go well I'll see you tomorrow for
pizza maybe I'll eat pineapple pizza
while I'm at it
yeah now I'll eat my food from yesterday
yeah
what's Ina streaming
we can write you know what is she
streaming
[Music]
she's drawing is she drawing the new
members
assumes she's starting the new members
[Music]
nice and okay I'm really exhausted thank
you for watching and listening to my
crazy tangents
and I think
my final message is
once you arrive in London
leave
and don't go to the wildlife Hotel
unless you're checking out the pool
please check out the pool
check out the pool I'm not crazy the
pool was wobbly as [\h__\h]
that's German we say I'll be dancing bye
bye
[Music]
thank you