[Music]
for
n
[Music]
hello
H here
[Music]
I wa why am I so
framy I'm kind of lagging a little bit
wait both lagging is it is it a pain it
wasn't it wasn't this before
eh it was fine before it was fine before
before wait what happened it do be like
that sometimes I think I had that with
other games
before yeah I'm not sure why you tapped
into the game or out of the game I'm
tapped into the game but like before
stream started our models was moving
from um maybe cap the frame rate I don't
know if you can cap the frame rate in
this game usually when the model lags
it's the graphic car going oh my God
there's a lot of stuff going on yeah the
the F the FR is
is
C oh maybe maybe it's just four of us
together vn's on that's usually what if
I turn it off turn it off turn it off
vyn is
evil really vyn usually helps depends oh
well yeah sometimes it's better to turn
it off sometimes better to turn it on
I've made both experiences well the game
the game itself isn't lagging it's just
us
it's time for
pngs it's time for pngs but it was weird
before stream start it was working fine
yeah really ly fora too um for me the
game is a little bit laggy but the model
is fine I think my PC oh I'm the
opposite the the game is fine the models
are laggy oh oh I mean that's better you
don't want to see a laggy game
um I
probably PNG should be finding yeah yeah
it might be it might be the the room
together that could be it you can do the
Discord light up thing if you have it
ready oh wait I tabed it wait it's The
tabing that changes things
often depending on where oh we're fine I
if I tab into
let me move our thing it's fine but if I
tap into the game it's not
[Music]
fine I instead of
tapping
like I don't know if it works cuz
sometimes I don't tab I just click off
of the screen and it's fine I don't know
if that helps okay let me see I
thought I mine is fine now I after all
tabing back and forth okay may maybe I
should rap all tab back and
for what if you window mod right now
orre what what um input capture are you
using
for
capture try full screening the game
maybe oh yeah maybe I can un full screen
the game uh where is
that oh it's already
borderless mine is
windowed okay mine is windowed now maybe
if
I maybe if I try full screen yeah TR let
try full
screen if I can become PNG that's
totally fine
too I had this with some games too but
it's been a while so I don't really
remember any
solution but while we're fixing this
maybe we can talk about our character
choices which has
which what was my character called again
uh uh Fair's it called again Fair fairy
the furry yeah Fair the F the furry the
furry she's the
furry yeah for most of the game I think
I used a different character but then
later in the game I switched to fairy so
that we have more variety as well
remember how to play here but I'll I'll
support you with my ghosts I think my
Whip and my ghost you can watch me Whip
and you can watch me neigh neigh
yay the
whip oh I changed the color so it looks
a little bit more orange thank you bi
for teaching me how to do it yeah is her
is this her original skin is it is is
she
pink no she's blue oh she's blue
okay she's blue actually I just realized
bi
boo are you like the ideal version of
yourself like like small but big boobies
yes this is n is what I aspire to become
one day that's why I play her totally
cool Nan with katana yes she is
everything I want to
be what you see when you look into the
mirror now that now that I think about
it yeah I'm sure it'll happen B I'm sure
thank you thank you for believing in me
one day one day I totally see it like
the hair color totally sells
it the hairstyle is like um the the the
infamous anime mom m w
isn't that isn't that like the one the
one ponytail over yeah I that that's the
one ponytail but I guess the hair
covering one eye the covering one eye
kind of
[Music]
thing okay then what's Zeta playing
Nota but you want to switch the
character um maybe after this after we
figure out what kind of team comp we
want but um my team is full blonde team
so I go with da Zeta kostro and Char
charot is that her name I mean I mean
charot but sometimes I would play kago
but not Zeta I don't know Z Zeta Zeta is
not Zing for me I don't know she's too
she's too she's a little bit too
complicated
[Music]
okay and Thena is tiny as hell tin y
cute it's my M your crown your crown is
like as tall as your shoes from your
default
outfit okay my default outfits shoes are
that
big it feels like
that see but I'm potato but to balance
the power level of the party I won't be
playing potato today oh yeah something
else the potato potato you're too high
level so
cute who is this who's that play a uh
aista aista aista aista aista yeah
aista aino vanilla a barista yeah wait
his name is actually a Barista sand
phone sandone
sand Sandy oh
Sandy sand
alen where sand alen alen is his name is
it alen sand Mr Alam sand he also so
edgy he's wearing high heels he is edgy
he so to be why' you call him a barista
what's the
[Music]
lore it's a long story oh
oh he doesn't look like he would be a
barista to be honest I know he just came
out like two days ago so I was like you
know
what oh nice
sword
flexing okay nice hey what level is that
character uh
76 the same
level
oh oh yeah oh 76 oh I heard 36 76 yeah
we have a little bit of a power Gap
uh Zeta and me are like around 40 and
biu and Ena are like 70 but does it
matter does it get adjusted like when we
play together I don't know how it works
but when I when I play randoms before
they kill things in like 2 seconds but I
don't think I have the gear to like kill
things in two seconds so I think it's
fine well Gaba will be strong yeah we'll
be fine it's it's it's fair right we got
like two four tiers and then two seven
tiers should be fine carry us yeah I'll
do my best I don't remember how to play
I have no idea how to play J but we'll
be fine I don't know the buttons anymore
oh but um me and zaa have not played the
epilogue yet but so it seems like we're
starting with the epilogue group quests
or so yeah okay is that okay that one we
can play together you guys accept the
quests
uh undertake Quest
uh wait no okay I think I might actually
have to revert to PNG let me just check
real fast
okay is there right quest uh uh can I
click oh I can make a
request uh how do I know I have a lot of
quests how do I know which one is the
right one um there should be ones where
it has like a mark well if you want to
progress the story you can do anything
with the Mark or can do any Quest that
you haven't
done it's definitely the four people cuz
me alone is fine so I'm going to have to
revert you guys the pngs okay okay no
problem no
problem people's gone is there to see
whether the quests are Solo or grip
quests everything thing is a group Quest
I think or it can be done in group okay
it's only when there's like a
story um Whatchamacallit well actually
you I don't think you'll see the story
quest in couldn't be that the group some
of these quests are from before I
finished the game so it's like yeah as
long as I think you hit like the highest
level difficulty oh it should
be okay should be fine
uh cuz I have like 10 quests or so yeah
you'll get a lot of new quests just go
through one by one okay okay you can you
guys will help me do my homework I
suppose then I'll just start from the
top okay
okay let's go normal survival quest it
says spare the rod spoil the valley
defeat as many foes as
possible uh in some snowy
[Music]
region snow undertake Quest We Are The
Undertaker mat depart for Quest of
current party
okay okay let me press ready okay ready
ready ready I'm going to play Ki for the
heel okay okay thank you for your
service let's go I will not be support
at
all I'm playing supp Just for this just
for this time oh I I think I have a heal
too if you guys need me yay double heels
oh on the controller which buttons are
the attack buttons like top or left or
right uh square square is attack
okay it's been a
while yeah it has been a while focus on
on a like
a to focus on one
character I think there
was okay I'm doing fine even without I
guess her what it
called
[Music]
is what's this
grab oh yeah you can throw that at
enemies oh you can throw the bomb that's
cute oh there's money
money where Money
Money free money we got to share it we
got to put it into a shareed account cuz
we're playing
together is that how it works everyone
do we have to share the
wordss have to share okay if you're
asking seriously I don't
know yeah that's actually question who
gets the reward maybe all of us yeah
everyone does but like not shared just
like everybody gets the yeah the same
amount okay that means that means in
times like this you can do
less and still get the same
robot yeah you can just look
pretty do
nothing it's so it's so shiny I can't
see let's go okay I'm starting to slowly
remember how to
play I'm starting
starting to remember the bottom at the
end of the game that tells you who did
the most
damage uhoh I don't want to see it I
like the bombs they're
cute yo this is really a lot you know
how to
P wait are we done yet oh no we got all
the
there's
more the game down sound protect me
protect me I don't even I don't know I
don't know where you
are it's so it's so it's so shiny I
don't know where everyone
is
okay I'm back in Action welcome back oh
these ones all the Slime I like them
oh I just now remember that with fairy
you don't button mesh but you continue
press the same button ooh like you you
press it down for several seconds I just
remembered where are the bad guys there
they are oh that's actually why I don't
play Zeta that much she has like she
needs like order and like structure in
her Combos and I'm like no I just want a
Button Mash
I get
[Music]
it
level you guys are you guys are you guys
are so strong there's no chance for me
to heal yeah these wave clear quests are
really good for levels
oh wow I'm
grinding I feel like we're playing an
mmpg together right now I love
this oh I'm in bubble I'm in the bubble
what's bubble bubble where where I'm out
of the
bubble bubble bubble bubble take this
bomb stupid
eyeballs 10 seconds remaining oh I
forgot I had
skills I found the skills
nice up times up nice ni too
late o oh I would have wanted to see
everyone's uh what is it called the the
the old the sky bound thingy oh we got
to find a boss yeah maybe on a harder
boss we can don't remember how to do
alt it's like left stick right stick you
click both I think oh
okay oh that's
manageable oh oh
caming
expert D
[Music]
damn
weakness I smell weakness what does that
mean imagine the smell
imagine what does weakness smell like
sweat I guess salt or blood cuz they're
dead Rotting Flesh decompos okay we got
s++ beautiful nice are you done
reviewing Quest results yes returning to
town yes nice nice we cleared that one
easy I already C off the character
voices cuz you guys sound so much like
anime say
you says I want
to just want
okay next we're going to defeat a
griffin it's a boss
fight
the uh clear I haven't
seen okay ready Ready's
go changed into tiny potato oh potato
potato potato my favorite potato favato
ready okay okay here we go
again party of girls that her crown is
made out of
waffles waffles you kind of look like
waffles
delicious okay I'm sure it's real gold
no not
waffles oh it's fying oh oh okay okay
okay okay I remember now got
invincibility let's go
come here get out of the I have G
yeah wait we're not playing Monster
Hunter someone get him down wo wo w w w
w wo
wo is that his
HP
yeah oh he
L an old I don't know
wait what I don't know if this is normal
I didn't even do any
damage
not it's okay we got the rewards make
sure you get the rewards yeah easy that
was so easy I did nothing but breathe
the whole
time yeah I don't think I even got a
single hit
in y y y we'll be done in no time with
all the quests like
this nice do you guys skip cutcenes or
do you no I always like to watch the
anime girls being cute me too I never
ski cut scene o Ena Ena literally killed
her by
herself we didn't do anything me and
Z let's go we were
we were chearing her on that's good I
kept on jumping and couldn't hit
[Music]
him yeah g Griffin is a little Annoying
participation
reward yeah you still get you still get
participation rewards it's
fine let's blame it on the you know on
the fact that you girls are really high
leveled so exactly we couldn't do
anything it was it was level 20 you guys
are technically overlevel too poor
Griffin that is
true H I won by doing absolutely
nothing okay take take that
win we need those winds to balance out
the L's how did the Griffin smell like
Ina did you smell
weakness I I did not smell weakness it
it it was not part of my my
MVP it didn't smell
weakness okay we're going to do another
boss okay don't know what level this one
is but it's a furry cane F fur oh that's
that's one of the story bosses a fury
cane okay don't worry I I always think
it's Fury cane
too fur can which one was
this it's the the Wind Horse looking
thing yeah
it turn into a lady or something like
that yeah the green looking one I I
think I it's been month for
me I don't remember wind Primal okay oh
no it's this
one
yeah furrie furry cane fur fur furrie
sounds more like hurricane so I think it
should be furri canane not Fury cane
wow
what just got started what is he dead is
he is this stage two no he's dead oh
stage two okay no it's
dead we get to some more difficult
quests eventually yeah you you just need
to unlock a higher level what iall it
difficulty yeah be f one hit 50 % HP
gone no
wow well I can check that one off my
list let's go let's go cleared in under
two
minutes let's go suddenly hurricane is
much easier than I
remember yeah when I was playing like
without a party I thought those goals
like finished under 2 minutes were like
impossible be eat this time yay
yay yeah but seems like going with a
party is the way to clear those side
goals clear with minutes
[Music]
nice okay another
s++
s+ returning to
town you got a crewmate card a new
Alley's waiting for you at the nicknack
sh oh yeah you can pick a new a new team
member now yeah yeah I don't want to I'm
happy with this team I'm not going to
replace you guys either he's
loyal okay next is Rea done did it
defeat as many foes as possible oh those
won't last like 8
seconds yeah this should be AIT long you
like a a story class that unlocks cuz I
know like you have to do you have to
like watch a cut scene really fast and
then it'll
unlock the End Game Quest so you might
want to go watch that cut scene real
fast and then new Quest should open up
to you I don't know what it says to your
top top uh right of your screen does it
say anything
no oh it doesn't say anything why would
it say something
there cuz it says it says something for
me oh well let's check after this Quest
I'll check properly
okay how do I yeah level
later en know you ready oh yeah yeah
yeah I mean if
anything I can probably put up a little
horror Quest too oh yeah I do
that it just won't progress your story
that's
all I don't mind spoiling
go go go go go go go no it's it's just
like harder versions of the quest you
already did
mm okay o oh let's
[Music]
go it's so
cute oh
why you so they look
so the male
voice
to no the bom they look so
goofy oh snack is no match for
us
oh I remember I I feel kind of badel a
lot to
Lev oh there's
more Overkill
Overkill
die
Overkill no problem not that I needed it
but I appreciate it feels good it's like
going to The
Spar exactly I healed you guys at full
health am I doing
nice
yes I'm poisoned please help me you are
oh no are you dying I'm dying you're
you're you lost 1% of Health I'll heal
you thank you that that can't happen
give her something to do give the Healer
something to
do no why you died in front of me
for
bye yeah give me that
money one
more
oh I love the surfing in the sand yeah
it's so nice I wonder if you can
actually do that IRL like just I I think
so there's like SL sledding with the or
skiing in the Whatchamacallit in
sand like sand sailing where like you
get on like a little like boat sort of
thing and you can Sail on the sand oh no
let's heal let's heal thank you
important
2% let's
go the
bomb they die with one hit from the
bomb yeah the bomb's pretty strong yeah
the bomb one minute
remaining is this called horny Birds
does that what I feel
horny might be wrong
oh the BFF is good what it
fantas 30 seconds 30 seconds eat this
ball okay it's horn bird not horny bird
okay very
close pretty much same
thing wait do oh
okay and they're gone how do you slide
so fast over to the enemies over there
the by the time me arrive they're like
dead already I have a gap
closer oh it's like endless until the
time ends huh
yeah
Overkill yay so many
Overkill yippe
y we did so
well you're doing great
easy wait when I skip the cut scene does
it skip it for you too no everyone has
to skip it for it to skip I think oh
okay I didn't skip S I
skip not look at look at her um what is
it executioner but
healer The Duality
I'm a devil to my to the enemies but
Angel to my friends you know I'll be
angle devil
exactly okay I'll see if I you mean the
cutcenes
uh wait where were is it tell you to do
anything if not that's okay we can have
Ena post a hard request what those again
in the in L's or where
no I want to
try what everyone's power levels at
where do you see that power levels uh if
you go into your menu where you see like
the stuff uhhuh under your character
uh-huh under your HP
782 oh I see it now never mind okay
3,000 3
3,000 let's
see uh something with around
3,000
[Music]
3,000 okay I can I can post something
okay okay bio show me
your show me a good
po oh
uh yeah wow
oh
wow how how do I accept do that again
there do that
again you see
it is there a difference in what it
looks like so I know it's your
quest
uh yeah how do I see your quest
I thought I posted it hold on do you
know the name of the quest so uh I don't
think oh actually
maybe I requested it but I don't think
you have it unlocked maybe you can't see
it uh now oh but I didn't even see it I
should at least have seen it right
probably I don't know how this
works but you're around do you have hard
modat unlocked I only have easy and
normal no what people oh people a do
I only the leader can start yes I do
have hard mode unlocked oh oh wait I
found there like a separate menu I think
I found it oh okay instead of undertake
Quest it's under Quest details at the
bottom okay we can do
this okay let's
go okay oh my job requirement on you
don't have it unlocked I hav it unlocked
it oh yeah okay it also says I'm not
their
requirements what requirement is that is
that the um what is it called I'm
walking hard mode so it's probably after
your after the story
M okay how about how about this
one
oh wait did it let me switch that out I
think I can saga
continues oh I have to now switched oh
there we go okay okay this one works oh
it works
yeah y
so is this a quest you did before
or you know this is it's it's a new one
you unlock in the normal I
think oh it's this guy uhuh the MMA guy
oh this oh I remember this one that was
always fun jumping around the
platforms I remember the platforms right
yeah it's
fun ouch ouch ouch ouch ouch hot hot hot
hot I remember falling off the platform
so many
[Applause]
times what
what wa it's over
it's
over you to chill for this magma boss I
smell I
can change my
weapon your weapon
overow I don't
know should I change to a weaker
character
maybe is there a character you always
wanted to try that you haven't tried yet
yeah maybe I'll
characters we'll see we'll
see oh I I actually didn't notice that
until now but you have a dog following
you
around yeah it's the ghost
yeah I thought it was like a special
ghost animals it's not just one it's
free it's free
mhm they're cute they're my pets I'm My
Own four people party
[Music]
okay okay so do we want to try another
like Ena Quest
or yeah I mean if you have to do for the
epilog again to unlock hard mode I don't
remember how do
we it's like I don't think you'll see it
while you're in the um what you call it
like a party online party a
oh but I do also have a saga continuous
Quest like the fire one we just did I
have the ice
one we can do that we can do that okay
think it's the hardest quest I have
available have you um so after the
credit roles for the main story have you
not like done anything
afterward
uh uh w remind me if I'm wrong but I I I
don't think I did anything I think did I
I don't think I did yeah after after the
credits rule you have to like talk to
the guy at his house or something and
it'll give you like more quests I
believe uh which
guy the glasses dude right well the
glass the the fix dude I think yeah Rand
Rolland the the fixed dude yeah fix it
fix it guy fix it fix it dude again
someone lead me
there didn't he die I'm so okay what
what he didn't die die he got Stu gone
for a bit okay he he got Shadow realmed
yeah a shadow
real people I'm following you you're
you're bringing me to the guy right
wasn't this the spot what are you you
mean spoilers it's not spoilers I
haven't even gone to the
epilog oh Zeta did you do anything
after seeing the credits nope oh I I uh
I did nothing but I didn't accept any
other question yeah
okay well what what we can do if we want
to have them unlock the hard Quest is uh
Zeta and waa
quickly go watch the cut scenes and
single player me and Ena can do like a a
hard Quest while you guys are doing that
and then we can reconvene and do the
harder Quest together sounds good yeah
okay so uh how do we cancel this
matchmaking I'll cancel my lady
status
uh okay but then okay we all leave each
other uh I guess you're going to make
your own hardcore hard mode party on
your
own okay leave session it shouldn't take
too long to unlock the epock stuff you
just have to go through the story stuff
really quickly so you two can do that I
think like in a couple minutes I believe
it didn't take too long for me okay and
then you can meet us back here and then
yeah it does say speak with ID yeah mine
too mine too I'm exactly the same okay
okay we're playing together even though
we're solo okay it's a race just see
which finishes this hard all
right oh your weapon is so
GL special
weapons um don't worry I'm reading all
the question you probably choose the
hardest one for you
this me
Grand to see back
again oh it's the same fire guy but I
think it's harder level
let's oh I guess I'm the host
huh he might not come back it has joined
my
party J are you actually reading
everything oh I'm actually
reading wow I can to be honest I can
read faster than this but I don't want I
don't think my chat can read this fast
so I'm picking it slow can wow no no I
have high speed no I have high speed
ability it comes with being an agent not
underestimating anyone
but I can't remember how to play your
what's your words per minute or
whatever oh I haven't I I don't know do
you test it out I guess a reading test
too I think there's a reading test or
something but is there do they also test
if you actually understood what you read
pretty sure it comes with it like
reading speed and then
understanding we should do that as a
collab
stream reading leing a
charge uh okay so is this part of what I
have to do I'm playing yes you have to
do the you have to do the RP you have
the RP as to do and then you should s
I'm blocking the people no where are you
people I all what what happened how did
I
[Music]
do fine fine I'm
fine H me and Z leave you and you girls
are lost a lost
cause D maybe you need us after all
we're fine I'm back we miss you oh yeah
we missed you oh no the boss
is killing us oh no oh we're dying what
am I going to do you'll have to learn
how to handle these bosses on your own
at some point it's what roll on we can't
always help you out me and Zetta yeah
please carry
us my back hurts from all that
carrying B's back it's not because of
[Music]
wait you joined my party why is there a
dash button uh right trigger wasn't it
oh well it was Dodge at least oh yeah
that was
dodging Kara did it join your party yet
yeah I'm already doing the fight what I
skipped you ski through
everything yeah
no I'm going to
fast you know I'm not streaming so I can
do what I want yeah can you get left sck
click the left stick apparently left
stick you must play it I forgot about
that same nice isn't it a lizard man oh
he did
did I remember now okay okay
search for the stolen goods why thanks
for
the
wow it becomes Dragon did it we did
it oh my
God I forgot level 100 Grand why is he
level how how does how do I make him
turn into a laser again
uh I don't know how it happened but
maybe I think you have to charge why oh
oh right why okay I think maybe that's
how it happens okay I smell
weakness she smelled it she SM it's so
over she smell it so
stinky so stinky
it smelled like marshmallow it smelled
like s'mores in the
fire that's actually good delicious I've
never had a s'more before you have
nether we don't really have s'more
culture in
Austria it's not a thing I gu it's a
very amican thing I don't see s'mores
anywhere outside
of mirac I want to try it though
although I'm not a big marshmallow s but
I like cookies and chocolate that's what
in there
right yeah it's what is it
gram gr cracker gram
cracker marshmallow toasted marshmallow
and then chocolate no now I'm
hungry did the have you had a
that before
that s'mores the thing s'mores yeah no I
haven't had
smores okay but hold on s'mores is the
so s'mores is like marshmallow that you
throw in fire on a steti you don't throw
and then yeah you you you toast it you
toast you and then and then once it kind
of melted a bit you squish it between
two pieces of crackers is that s'mores
yeah the great
crackers
oh I feel like I made one without the
fire that doesn't
[Music]
count there's so many go
they
are okay I'm okay I got a gun did you
see
that again when everybody's blue what
happens press
B oh no that was different that gave me
a press both sticks uh prop oh L time
you press
B should be glowing on your menu your
face so goofy oh wow it's
over ah I was thr off
unbelievable
unbelievable o oh
oh there's a
witch a witch a witch
Goblin I'm going to get people no how
could you do that to people
okay destroyed one of leg going to hit
me from
here people
no did you read Lord of the
Rings I didn't read it but um you I'm a
big fan of the all the movies and I even
went to a Lord of the Rings musical in
England last year no
way yeah it was really cool cuz it was
like on the countryside of like some
London and it was really cozy and and
they were so amazing they played so many
instruments that really beautiful that's
so nice are they known for their music
[Music]
though fo there's a black griffin what
is
this did that why did you ask oh no cuz
like we were talking about goblins and
witches and I suddenly thought of Lord
of the Rings and then I suddenly thought
of you so cuz like cuz like I bought
like a
book but then I also like I was like
considering if I should start with the
movie or the
book but then I bought like four of the
books but then I haven't read any cuz I
wanted to but then I'll cut I kind of
got lost The Hobbit before yeah I I lo I
I was already lost in The Hobbit
one oh you finished it because I wanted
to do a book club where we reach a
hobbit you can join it if you want so I
want
to
I did you sign up because I I asked
before I did I reacted I reacted with
Okay okay then you're in anyway
y I want
join
okay everybody who wants to join shall
join and if we're done with the Hobbit
we can start reading the LA
during okay and maybe we'll figure out
all the issues you had with it like why
you're confused about it okay we can do
that y i remember I remember being the
hit in school I didn't understand
anything in school wow yeah I think I
read it in school too but I think I
scammed through it because I really
don't remember anything oh my God it is
about to
die what if I die can they revive
me wait I have heal items I forgot inol
I died what did I read
inol no we could have one face it it's
okay who's healing me it's not dang it I
thought we were stronger than this
honestly z z why why you not Reviving me
hurry
up this Zeta is so slow Zeta also
struggling yeah this that I
struggling thank
you w
did you did you beat the bird no not yet
I'm like at
47 bu I did it
first already I finished it first and
without skiing the cut
scene
what
how I
don't I don't know
damn
girl okay here we go this is
it you should be thinking it i' make a
great
[Music]
mix
explosion stop stop the coffee pasta
are you motivated people I'm so
motivated right now
wow give me that
money level up I must keep getting
stronger this isn't even her final
form oh go watch
watcham to see how they're doing well
I'm not streaming but I'm suffering
right now oh I I guess I guess uh Cara
is in a different level huh
uhhuh did you unlock the
question huh what did you
say did you unlock the stuff oh not yet
I'm still in a cut
scene oh yeah keep on watching that cut
scene
okay I'm not going to skip I'm not going
to skip don't skip I won't skip skip
ad skip skip ad if you skip ad you skip
it skip it no don't do it to
him oh my God this is obliterating
me I okay okay I did it he's dead
actually I think I think since they're
done we can wait now yeah
yeah
okay let's
go vamos Amigos
[Music]
are you yes
yes I do that so often
[Music]
I can't help it like I always want to do
it it's from that one Clipper yeah
the you have to do it a little bit more
like whispery I
[Music]
guess oh I got him I'm in chapter zero I
think oh me too me too okay okay okay
okay okay okay okay this is good you
should be able to do stuff now I think I
think I can do stuff now
go wait crew mate I have to read the
Journal of Roland oh no I
skipped you could but yeah for fix it
guys you may now join online quests of
the following difficulty hard very hard
extreme yay okay let's
go hold on where's the I don't know who
to get for my new crew
mate um
where oh I want to choose a new one too
nor was it in the knickknack Shack or
where was that again yeah the knickknack
oh yeah I think I can get someone too
the parrot
kid crewmate card trans
unbelievable oh do you have to pay money
for these
dudes I think you can unlock it oh by
playing the game too maybe I got the
see what the hell oh this lady is cute
the one with the bow is that a bow
yeah oh she
cute I want Twan but I cannot have
Twan the new just like the
sand yeah I'm looking at twen TW looks
so good
yeah but I cannot has okay
I accept my
fate your how I have all the cute girls
unlocked but I have I have not unlocked
any of the
dudes I want to add another blonde to my
team but I don't know who my options are
limited maybe you can make them blonde
in the color change oh the skin oh
[Music]
none of these dudes interest
me H okay uh if we make a group again
you guys already have an existing group
do you want to invite
us um I think can yeah I can go for
it oh wait I have to change party
first party
okay I sent
invite does it just show up in the
screen in the middle or you should get a
steam invite oh send a steam invite I
think so well that's how that's how we
got in last time oh okay I did get a
steam invite okay
okay all
righty is the password the same as
before yeah it's the same room okay let
me
join you we're coming back the noobs are
coming
back welcome back we're here to balance
things please
carry we'll carry you don't
worry oh do I have I have to censor the
screen you have funny hair
Ena thanks it's like you have three or
four a oh
yeah it's the antennas did you wake up
like that no I I put on moose or
whatever you invite
me I I thought I
did uh let me do it again
okay did you get it no
let me double
check
um I don't think
so oh I don't think we're friends
St not
[Music]
friends her yeah you can invite her okay
it's okay I'll I'll use this chance to
add her on Steam okay you have been
invited please join us again Zeda all
right
do you know the gro characters are
actually pretty short like naraya the
one I'm playing is actually shorter than
me she's like 130 something huh
yeah how short this
potato okay so the EPO quests are the
ones that Roland or whoever suggested I
suppose yeah and then okay I think I see
that they are marked yeah the the marked
on do those okay then I'll put it as a
request into the requests oh it would
have been better if you were your host
huh uh okay I
requested I think me and Zeta will need
the same ones so I think it's count for
both of you
mm let's go ready
ready
ready oh oopsie ready ready ready
ready OA you
changed still the same oh yeah wait did
I change no I I I thought you did but
now you didn't you're cute as Calo
stro I'll change after
this variety o what's this this music is
really good
[Music]
where oh is this one way we shoot the
shoot with the
[Music]
Cannons oh it's the cannon
thing there's not nothing here yeah I
don't quite the challenge I I'd rather
just beat stuff up same on one side and
there's two cannons there then walking
around we're just chilling we're just
chilling so much for us carrying the
other you guys you guys can do the
Cannons no it's you go okay here here
I'm lazy someone else use the cannon I'm
just going to run around and look all
right I'll try oh I a
oh
aim oh they're already coming to the
ship well more things to do yeah
oh
more yeah shoot them shooting
them the horny birds are
coming okay take them
down I don't think they are quite
birds are they
dinosaur ouch ouch ouch something is oh
I I like What's blocking my vision oh
something's on top of
[Music]
me no poor little
one little
one wow nice link attack nice this is a
bit more of a challenge at least than
the other ones I think aing the aiming
this cannon is the
challenge
mhm oh oh it's happening again yeah
there's more in the sky shoot them down
go get him no they're already
here
damn those poor little thing
go go go
[Music]
go wow level
up
[Music]
who I love attacking nothing
ooh I love shooting at nothing oh we
didn't do the clear within three minutes
go no oh we
suck
damn go get him
guys doing the ground
work do the
SP ouch
link
ATT
nice oh it's
done
[Music]
y ah minutes is still possible the goals
don't look so good we
suck I need to do charged shots oh
I mostly did the pew pew pew
mm oh well this is fine oh this is this
is
good hey hey hey hey hey hey
Ro missing a couple of light who what's
going
on
what what does this mean
[Laughter]
I'll get him next
time whoa whoa what how does what no no
I don't want to repeat the quest no oh
wait oh yeah okay okay unless unless you
want to do it in 3 minutes no boss I
want boss oh okay I want violence okay
we'll give you
violence yes thank you
you've acqu
curio okay you should check if that
Quest the first I think it was the first
one on my list is it gone for you now
okay let me
check first one on the list I mean I
guess now you would have a different one
as the first one on the
list uh um veteran Sky fair is it
oh yeah yeah it's gone rule the skies oh
okay
yeah doesn't have the mark anymore so
the next one would be the juice of
jealousy do you have that one too oh my
next one is uning the troops but I have
the juice of jealousy as well oh but
does the the other one that you
mentioned have the mark Cuz only juice
of jealousy has the mark for me I'm not
sure if that is even the right Mark that
we should be looking out for though it's
like a orange oh yeah yeah it's it has
the mark for me okay what does it mean
the Mark I think it says that those are
the pre the EP those are the story
epilog Quest that used to progress
through the
epilog but it still says I only finished
two out of eight jobs yeah more lock
down the line yeah I'm I'm at six out of
eight right now oh
okay but it was two out of eight before
the fight that we just had and now it's
still to out of eight yeah it comes in
waves you have to do Wes Quest so this
wave is the second wave of quest oh it's
not like eight quests you got to do it's
like a whole bunch of them oh
okay damn that's a lot
y oh oh here we go
bad guy
please there's something satisfying
about beating up
goblins dang
it okay
shiny money money money
[Music]
M no one wants to get my AOE bubble I'm
sad what is that the heel no my Ali
slashy slashy attack no one wants to die
yeah they're kind of scattered all over
ouch come
here
L
nice no what are they fighting oh
no ooh nice nice heal
for y
l byebye
[Music]
I miss the
link Zelda will be disappointed in
you get the joke I get
it
ouch
ouch why oh okay I'm not resistant to
fire
no I didn't get the don't get inflicted
with burn more than four times
achievement oh I also didn't get it oh
no I also didn't get it across all of us
so
burn I need heal I need heal I'm in
healing sorry I don't have heal I'm
potato now
oh
[Music]
nice did you watch what I did
or did you see this attacking I saw I
saw so
cute wait I'm not at 100% I'm at 100% I
think if one of us uses it you'll be
100% let's go go I'll use it to go
woo I can't see it's too
flashy oh I couldn't use
mine
ouch wa I need a big thing to use it
on what is a big
[Music]
thing oh wait 30 seconds me I'll just
use it ah yeah where's the enemy where's
the enemy
yeah no I'm not at 100% anymore
no please come
on more
good good 10 seconds you have 10 seconds
to use it okay go go go go this one
[Music]
wow the slow
motion please give me some titles
please I want some titles to flex okay
let's see the
titles oh yeah how do you put on the
titles in when you're in the lava
NOA I think you have to go to your Co-op
settings maybe not
sure oh you can point them
as oh
[Music]
nice oh wow I'm the link starter proud
of you thank you link starter I start
collabs I start links I start everything
bio always has the no healing
needed I don't need healing I just kill
things way too fast
yeah oh yeah I start fires I start links
start a fire
today fire fire like the
fire fire fire pants on fire fire fire
fire fire I'll request protect the rep
it's also a boss fight y boss fight
okay I've been waiting for a boss
fight what oh CP is also always in a
boss fight cuz they're always fighting
me
wait who win fighting about their salary
and about their
their union rights or whatever
you give them
salary you give them union rights no
that's what that's what they're fighting
such a good boss you even gave them
salary well salary salary is like there
is salary but the salary is the other
way around like they pay me so Oh I
thought you were going to say salary as
in like the vegetabl that's that's to me
I give I give mine the salary with the
vegetable always cuz I can't eat them so
you can't you can't tell people that
you're paying your kfp then we all got
to start paying and I don't want to do
that don't worry about it but maybe from
now on when they ask for salary I should
just give them the vegetable yeah yeah
maybe then they'll shut up about
it salary is good you care about their
health and wellbeing
prefer other
vegetables okay who here has watched The
Fallout show I haven't but I want to see
I heard it's really good please watch it
it is so good it made me start playing
the game
oo and the protagonist she's so cute she
has like really poppy big eyes that pop
out of her skull what I know she just
her eyes are really
big she's so pretty no stop targeting
me why why why why
why
nice I it takes a long time for me to go
there
I love l oh
yeah oh okay
nice oh my god oh
nice that was a good one
mhm
explode yes I my treasure
money I'm going to do the money first
[Music]
loot goblins you for
Goins it's shed you have to
wor I want a
receip let's see the titles titles
titles the most important
part
totally ah
no titles why why I got all the titles
you can't see on my screen but I got no
healing needs specialist and Lord of
crits yeah I smell weakness that's
all smells weakness that's smelling
weakness
now weakness okay but what do we learn
from this titles don't matter tit
no they don't matter most important yes
people you try hard no no no no they
don't
matter they don't matter they really
don't yeah they don't don't
wor next one is in delts of lives or
[Music]
so it it's Dragon power is pulsating
oh Dragon power
W Ina looks so cool with her big Cape oh
thank you like from behind all all hide
inside the cape yeah like a
[Music]
blanket okay
ready here we go
again we're all we're all inside her
Cape
connecting T did you ready up yeah I
ready up yeah it's just the server I
think just connecting oh
dear uh cuz nothing's happening for me I
see I see oh it says connecting on my
side but I don't know what yeah it say
connecting okay yeah it it go while okay
issue I was sliding it was probably yeah
sliding around yeah like not
moving
lag
oh oh hello it's a hor Oh I thought it
was a
horse a horse a horse was I saw the
looks like a in my defense the back of
the hair does like a horse hair horse
hair link
[Music]
that oh yeah oh yeah oh yeah this is
going to be done you
[Music]
know this poor this poor
Goblin wow that felt good we were going
on felt that felt
satisfying money
money go you have to
rush loot
Goblin the middle box looks better than
the
others yeah that's why I want to open
it got the titles don't
matter oh you're saying
already I have don't
matter about what's coming oh I'm scaped
let's go see my gun was right it doesn't
matter it doesn't matter especially it
doesn't matter the most when you get
none it doesn't
[Music]
matter you're lucky that I am blocking
my title
oh you are blocking your titles on my
screen they can't see all I'm collecting
yeah
oopsie that's so fast where we can be
done with this so quickly mhm it get it
gets
harder trying to see what
character you want to switch again nope
maybe Z after this
maybe
finally oh if you switch I'll switch to
potato okay
okay uh after this
one yeah
okay I will I'll give Zeta a chance she
deserves a chance yeah
please I want to see Zeta you're the
only one with a shared name in this game
you got
to represent it
Z need AA
skin yes Zeta
skin
skin are we loading again yeah we're
loading yeah server
issue that's
okay we
are slow
server it'll be
fine Zeta and Zetta
collaboration Zeta and Zetta
collaboration there's jeta as well right
the main
character J yeah ga yeah that's why both
of them are in my party I'm
like I'm I feel so reassured with my
doel
gangers but the jeta one is written how
DJ T DJ e e t a i
think yeah g
ah
DJ
DJ DJ I thought I thought you were share
my
name I only share my name with the
hamster from
hamaro wait which you want to share your
name no I've never I've never met a
video game character named beu before
oh yeah
beu
beuu beu where where is beu
from it's French it means like jewelry
oh
yeah yeah oh okay maybe there's no game
characters but there's a shop there's a
shop chain in Austria that sells
accessories like Claire
it's called
Brig
cute it's it's nice it's like more
mature than uh
Claire's oh mature you're so
mature
it's mhm that's why that's why I'm bibo
because I don't feel mature enough for
my
name no be is totally the type that
would shop in Claire's not in
[Music]
Claire but no no I also sometimes go to
Claire's still
sometimes I got my ears pierced and C me
too me too oh okay good okay I'm not the
only one nice I was I was very old when
I did that so does does Claire's use gun
or
needle they use
oh interesting but I never got my ears
pierced as a child mhm and so I Did It
For the First Time as an adult and I
felt so awkward and that Claire's at
least it was pretty
empty and I was so terrified even though
it's not a big deal like some some
parents let their make their like two
year olds or so uh Pierce their ears
right right I don't know to have no yeah
some some par like here like some people
get their ears chis has like a baby so I
guess they don't remember it yeah
they're like feel the pain now so you
don't feel it later it's not happening
what should we
do I don't know I'm stuck I can't move
me
either I also I can't cancel my ready
stat status either I feel like an NPC
the NPCs are like walking around me and
I'm like I can't even move am I still
sliding around you yeah I I still see
you're able to move yeah you're able to
move like you're supposed to be able to
move when you're ready
up no that's just because it's taking so
much time I'm I'm ready up I'm
chilling I'm waiting for
you it shows me that is not ready up but
I'm sure you are
ma'am where where even is Zeda I don't
see oh I'm here near the um the quest
the quest table you can't you probably
can't see me okay I indeed cannot see
you wait really I'm gone yeah maybe
that's the problem I don't know what I
think I think you should rejoin cuz yeah
I think it's you because you can move
yeah you're able to move when you're
ready to but I was able to move before
too and we still got in but it's just I
guess not working this
time wow okay how do I how how do I how
do I you're not allowed to
move but I can't uh do anything though I
just I can move just just exit the game
like entirely what alt alt
f4 no oh she's gone okay oh okay I can
move we can move now I can move
now actually all de for was the
solution but now she's
gone it was W connection come
back come back soon please we'll wait
for you come back to
us oh she's being a sunary we need our I
mean we can go without
you I'm sure that's what you would
like you promised that you were going to
carry us what happened to your
[Music]
promise you you know the real carriers
are
elsewhere
Ino I'm swapping to potato I don't know
what you're talking about okay okay I'm
I'm swapping to something else
then swapping to potato swapping to am
potato am
potato
potato is
potato you have a level 69
nice did you stop there on purpose no I
didn't she's in my party so she
naturally levels with me it's not like
you had all planned out
yeah are you sure you want to keep
leveling up people you could have it
stop there oh that's true maybe I should
just swap
I'm back and I'm ready
up I'm ready as well
okay okay there we go there we go play
her potato how do I play potato d i jump
right you jump that's how you play
potato just keep hitting attack button
yeah just just
keep just keep pressing
X oh this the coin collecting
one what's this W where
[Applause]
[Music]
where wait am I
alone ouch just everyone spread out and
collect coins around the map okay okay
is all
ouch
oh oh yeah she has that thing ooh nice
that's the first time I ever saw a quest
like that the
coins yeah I think
or yeah I don't think I ever had a coin
Quest like
this I I don't remember I have really
bad slimes oh yeah now now the slimes
appear now that we have all the
coins uh where are they though oh I see
you can go to the center and then they
should oh my coin no you took my
coin it's up at the top how do you
reach I'll take this can someone shoot
that thing down oh I see
it bring it
down he's destroying the
structure
oh oh what is that a kettle oh it's a
kettle bring it down
I am too
short hold on I could down
maybe no no that oh I can't I don't have
like any ability to get up
there did she have like a jump
thing I think I un equip
it oh oh I have a raining a raining
meteor that's
good but how what are you supposed to do
here
jump jump but we all can't that
[Music]
high sworn I had like a jumping attack
thing I got this is your M how do I do
how do I play
her I don't remember the name of the
skills I just remember muscle
memory oh yeah she has a rushing rushing
attack there's one over here that is
less on a
for please on the way lowest
spot I think you just well cuz I have my
controller set so that it keeps pressing
the button so you have to keep pressing
it until she goes like super fast and
attacking if you
[Music]
know you can just keep doing that it's a
basic thing
okay
[Music]
okay okay okay nice ni is there another
one that we can reach
easier
o well say something if you find another
one of those slimes oh I found another
one it's small
okay oh only we need to defeat King
slimes King Slime
coming but coins is also
important
true like three of us literally tried
for one minute to reach the the thing on
top of the stru
yeah I was that one
cattle I could get 150 coins coins it's
okay we killed it you almost
died oh I think oh maybe maybe next time
we could split the job one person go
coin hunting yeah Ena was continuously
coin hunting I think while we were
fighting there maybe two people oh I was
figuring out how to play so I was
useless
H we can try it again should
we long distance
Runner I was running over oh
yes should we try it again yeah it's
okay we can do a boss oh okay maybe
another
boss okay yeah let's do a new
boss BOS BOS
I want to fight stuff with my
[Music]
potato I want to fight creatures that
are
alive next one is indeed a boss fight
[Music]
yay oh where oh there you
are ladies small
potato potato in a fire
why potato potato
potato potato
potato potato tomato
tomato tomato I hate
Tomatoes I also hate Tomatoes let's
go cook cooked tomatoes are fine but
like ra Tomatoes no I love raw Tomatoes
especially cherry tomatoes no cooked or
raw it's horrible what about like uh
like raw tomatoes with mozzarella and
Balsam
vinegar no maybe when I'll eat it I'm
sorry Italians I'm Sor I'll eat it in
afterlife
damn it's so refreshing though it's
really nice to eat in summer
it's like kind of like it has like a
combination of like
sourness but
bitterness sweet sweet potatoes sweet
tomatoes like cherry tomatoes do you
like
those the small
ones not
really like even if it's sweet because
if if if I wanted sweet things I would
eat sweet things but not tomatoes
there's better sweet things than
tomatoes I don't think tomatoes are
quite
sweet no people where are you okay I'm
okay wait do we have a Healer right now
no no I mean Ena can heal
right hold on hold on hold on how do I
how do I what is it called how do I uh
revive thank you how do I oh I keep I
have to unlock I used an item to
revive oh everyone's their own healer I
guess so yeah be
careful this one's
strong
yeah oh wow wow wow wow wow wow no not
today
caught in the FR Bight no we're all
split up grateful oh oh it rolls into a
ball that's
unfair ouch OU
okay that is so
unfair can someone revive me okay coming
oh bi's
closer she
revive thank you
what they did
that oh nice oh nice
[Applause]
what we only have
60%
64% can I can I
all
o
go go pets
go watch
me oh first time I'm seeing this off
[Music]
okay
o
finally powerful
first we did
it go full Button Mash let's go let's go
let's go
dark pile them yes oh yeah what is this
moment do you have also everything blue
he he's slow down so you can use skills
and not worry about it cuz he's okay
nice okay okay bye
[Music]
bye I got out okay good
ooh
no hold on coming coming coming coming
coming coming coming thank
youa how does it feel to play ASA oh
it's
nerve-wracking CU like I'm like I have
to count the combos like one
two well how far does it go the the
counting ouch I think till three but
it's it's it's it's taking all of my
energy to count till
four wo
wo
no hold on a title for dying so often
hold
on and you're going to get I got you I
got you so
often oh
man it's okay I'll take the L's if that
means that we'll win in the end
sacrificing for the
team yes so
Noble taking one for the
team thank you for your service
oh no oh no oh no no no oh no oh no
careful
careful oh no don't worry revive revive
revive
[Applause]
revive no we both
[Music]
die okay okay I had the potion left
that's good oh what's happening oh no no
no wait okay okay okay okay we can't die
it's okay dead we can do it we can't die
no that's crazy wait I have to quickly
push the button
no
no so close our first failed
Quest we got to repeat it we got to that
was fun though that was crazy yeah that
was fun I'm bringing I'm bringing back
out okay okay I'll
try I'll I'll do kago for that extra
heel okay then we have to like get out
of this once right yeah okay okay okay
bring this bring the strong characters
yeah bringing back the strong
characters yum B she can stay at level
69 that one absolutely obliterated
us
she
she but I've already gained like 20
levels since we started same you level
pretty fast yeah yeah you're at 60
now mine keeps changing the character so
it's like 50 50 50 all like equally
spread out that's good you're leveling
everybody yeah give giving everybody a
chance yeah one thing I haven't
considered is I leveled like 20 levels
but do I need like better equipment
where do I get it I Haven you can go
into your masteries and level up your
like stats oh um to get better stats and
then you can also buy weapons at this
guy oh up the weapons too yeah oh I
can't I guess I can't do it now we can
do it after this Quest H oh wait if I
just unready for a moment I can oh yeah
you can do that
too oh I think I'll unready as well hold
on
up oh more weapons are available I have
so many books this is
good I don't have Earth orb I don't have
Earth orb where do I get Earth or if you
don't have items go to this the little
dude
par yeah the parot dude go to treasure
treat and maybe it's selling it in the
Treasure trade okay Earth orb where are
you Earth
orb how much do you need oh there's
definitely Earth orbs
yeah okay got
one and
[Music]
then going back
to
[Music]
like damn this one's so
cool I will ref I'll do my masteries for
now
instead I'll just do
everything got to get stronger more
power yes
wow I
am what is it called um leveling up for
a bit wait for me okay I'm leveling up
to just let me know when you're ready
okay
um oh this one's czy good but
should I upgrade or not I like this one
better s i r this
S I run
[Music]
this
okay oh there's so much I can do no
wonder I was so weak
SAR is better H I guess
[Music]
SAR
SAR okay SAR hold on we need or more
Earth
orb oh okay I'm I ran out of points
let's go okay Earth or Earth or
orb one
more I am so torn between two
[Music]
swords get the one that looks cooler h
both of them looks cool I am so
torn upgrade web as should you normally
go for upgrading
existing weapons you know what s looks
cool so you're going to need to upgrade
all the weapons eventually because um in
your Mastery page each weapon gives you
bonus stats so the more weapons you have
upgraded the more stats you can get um
yeah looks better so do all of them okay
well I don't have dragon scale but if
you're worried about stats crit is
always good
mhm okay I'll make new
[Music]
weapon hello Ina's
tall okay I think I am ready I love some
some materials a bit for
later hey hi hi
hi wait one second uh
okay okay enhance
success
okay
oh okay
[Music]
on I
think that that should be
good oh I can add one more
sigil attack power I like I bought a new
gold sword it looks cooler but the stats
are
lower
ready I'm also ready
[Music]
ready let's go
second try at same Quest right yeah yeah
yep
okay this time we'll get
him Are we more confident yes I brought
out the
main the main okay that should be easy
then I'll bring the heal this time
[Music]
and buff so I have a buff that Buffs all
allies way faster than before
yeah oh
wait wait why am I attacking a wall stop
ow
ouch ouch
ouch I'm
frozen hold on hold on hold on W he
thank oh yeah right thank you wait the
heal's gone okay hold on hold on
[Music]
nice oh nice this is much
faster it's night and
[Music]
day oh okay you fell off
there for real you yeah yeah I fell down
the map but I'm fine
I thought there's an invisible wall over
there no no I fell off the cliff now I
kind of want to try falling down
too it actually does nothing I don't
know if you lose like certain stuff like
definitely on my health let's
go oh he's
[Music]
dead so easy
wow that was so different yeah that
was main character and
energy money much
better
oh but I like to pretend that me and
Zeta upgrading our characters also
helped a little really it's like it's
the little attacks you know it adds up
yeah a little bit Yeah it adds up into
big numbers yeah
what what do we have oh I got titles we
all got
titles we all got titles titles I
finally got support
Master
wow you were supporting me like a
master nice the Wai support
okay s++ exactly what we deserve yeah do
we have more boss for B
boo
maybe I got a crewmate card thanks but I
don't have anybody that I
want drum I'm not interested in guys
we're going to fight another Griffin and
apparently we're going to turn him into
our dinner
drumsticks yummy what's more delicious
griffins or kfp kfp of course all the
way of course yeah Griffins are not
supposed to be eaten anyway Griffins are
supposed to be flown
ridden what do kfps taste like since
what do kfps taste like it's just
chicken it's fried chicken but it's the
best fried chicken you can get out there
but also
actually because of our name you might
think we focus a lot on on fried chicken
but it's actually more the burgers we we
prefer to do
burgers burgers burgers but IDE e
chicken
burgers cuz I don't even like like fried
chicken buckets like just just a chicken
I don't like that that much I want more
variety tea and that's what a burger
gives you with the lettuce and the
Tomato perhaps have you ever considered
sauce kfp maybe that'll give you the
variety if you like add sauce kfp sauce
oh sauce we have many many sauces we
have Yago uh
sauce Burg no I have we have a lot of
sauces I I wrote a menu like three years
ago actually oh like a legit menu oh
that's so nice do you have a
drink oh Many Many Drinks all the
drinks
chicken chicken I recommend Dr Pepper Dr
Pepper I don't like Dr Pepper
what yeah I don't like cherry flavored
stuff oh but it's not really cherry
flavor it does taste like cherry flavor
yeah but then there's a Dr Pepper cherry
flavor specifically as well
so but I think I I get what you mean it
has like a an interesting hidden laor
pet how do we get to come down I do we
wait oh it does come down it's attacking
en get there
taunt
him taunt
him you
smell like weakness yeah I can smell
your
weakness let's heal
what
[Music]
a not
tornado but I didn't and I died close to
Z yeah hold on hold on hold
on hold
on revive thanks oh did you revive
yourself yeah oh yeah you can revive
Yourself by mashing like Yeah by mashing
button
oh I used the item before Oh knce
[Music]
break
nice are you muted no oh okay
okay does somebody have a stand
a
stand what do you mean like a JoJo stand
like I see like a big guy in armored or
something oh I I stand uh no I mean in
the game or yeah oh yeah in the game
yeah yeah Oh I thought I was like do you
have a stand it's en en it is yeah
oh oh it's a JoJo St
it is
a no it's a it's a summoned big
dude okay I still don't know what you're
talking about don't worry about it I
smell
weakness it was worth weakness leveling
up I got the queat en
are is your head okay like do do you
want to rest or for a bit before I could
probably do like like one or two more
okay okay don't push yourself yeah don't
push yourself we can like end it when
you're not I think this wave for me and
Zeta we we only have maybe one more
Quest or so left okay for this wave of
quests let me
check I am not going to read the
notes me neither
reading you can read oh yeah it's just
one left defeat
laon sounds
[Music]
fancy have you been to France before
that name you kind of got to go oh I
guess I do kind of got to go
huh if you want to go I'm close by I can
go with you I've been to uh Paris a few
times I want to go I've never been to
Europe before hey yo come
over I hear it's nice though it's
beautiful there's so much like variety
Europe is very versatile you know we
have have so many things to offer so
much
beauty Beauty one of the beauties of
Europe is me by the
[Music]
way so come to
Austria you know you're selling it
pretty well
right another one of the Beauties is my
cats oh they would also like to more
members more Holo members come on cute
cute
forgot to I want to see if every Hollow
member's
cat yeah there's like I feel like
there's way more cat owners than dog
owners way more by far which is like
really an unusual raaco I think like if
you just like walk around in the world
in an IRL world and ask people do we
have a dog or a cat then it's more
balanced but within Holo it's so
unbalanced we all love cats
oh Bon cats
special I love cats I love cats
[Music]
too
whoa is he also going to be so strong
why is he he's shooting laser
beam because he can all I hate it when
all you can do is fly fly fly you have
nothing else to
do
o oh this okay I guess we still so he
also went down nice
yay okay we we finished the first wave
of quests it
seems F think you have a boss in between
I think you just move I forget I think
there is it's like
the some sort of dragon can we help with
it not sure I think it was
solo not sure it might be
cool I don't remember it's been a
while got waited by
K oh hi
[Music]
K Carrie wa doesn't know what a stand
is I thought what do you mean something
within the game so
but I mean I've heard of Jojo never
watched it though but I know some of the
poseses
mhm I wanted to do a JoJo watch
along yeah I wanted to continue
it I haven't I'm only in part two but
the stand thing doesn't happen until
later I think uhhuh okay okay what the
thing that defines the show seemingly
only happens
later what what it starts in part three
yeah part
three oh okay well well well oh yeah now
it says finish the jobs four out of
eight
nice oh there's a rank up Quest button
ah yeah it says defeat the Ancient
Dragon but I think it's probably oh is
it by yourself I was able to make the
request oh okay let's do that and then
we can
yeah we can do it
together I can get carried
through
hooray I got to know Dojo because of the
what is it
[Music]
[Laughter]
called they just repeat a lot of words
and oh yeah that
[Music]
one what the [\h__\h]
is he uses his tongue Andes
a is that an attack no it's a it's a
oppose a stand yeah it's a pose I
[Music]
guess when I hear
y i i I'm like imagining Ena but with a
roast in her
mouth I feel like it's something she was
saying with
with you know my
inner ouch one fire
wait
yeah
[Music]
OU what the did he just give birth what
is there's a little
one uhoh we're so
small keep on dodging keep on dodging
[Music]
uhoh it's raining
Su the dragon has
descended I can
feel ah don't move away
the link ouch you missed
it okay there's so many there's so
[Music]
many
goodan log to YouTube
good morning oh we got four treasure
chests this
timean
[Music]
yes I studed TI bit for like really yeah
for like 3 weeks Max oh three
[Laughter]
weeks oh yeah how was your tie trip it
was so hot peopleo I died it's hot I
died but it was it was nice I had some
good food and I saw a a beautiful Temple
it was amazing it was incredible but it
was too
hot and I hot do you know people do you
know about those
inhalers what the like inhalers yeah
Thai
inhalers it's like a popular souvenir uh
and like everybody uses it small
inhalers that smell like
herbs come on you got to know it no you
sniff sniff small
inhaler oh I got a little yapping scene
well I know Ty people like smelling
things we
always always getting like
smelling like having like the spice like
bag where you like smell it and sniff
sniff yeah yeah yeah they're like in the
little container though like really
small container portable little inhaler
oh I think I know what you're talking
about yeah and it has like holes in it
right or something yeah it has a cap
that I I can and I got so many of those
and I like gifted some to my my mom and
my friends but they smell really nice
and then I got a lot of tie
pants I'm wearing tie pants right now oh
yeah tie pants are like comfortable
right I don't wear pants so I don't own
tie pants but I they're so
comfortable and then for the first time
ever like I did thae massage uh overseas
right outside of Thailand but now I had
a thae massage in Thailand whoa was it
better it was uh I I mean I had Good
Time Massages outside of Thailand but
this one was really good and uh it was
like an older Thai lady that did it and
she kept on she didn't speak English at
all but she kept on laughing at My
Pain
a well pain and massages are good right
means like it's getting out all the
stuff I love I totally love it I need I
need the pain she was good good lady
kind of like the mom type of
lady yeah I was good did she step on you
she I think she did
yeah and I
died that was good stuff I wish you
could have taught me a little bit you
know before but the times didn't match
up yeah the timing
was bad but maybe another time sometime
you can teach me
um if you say nadak to
somebody they'll like it that's cute
like wa n
[Music]
or cute it means
cute it literally translates to face
love oh face love face love love your
face yeah love your face love your
neighbors
love I see thanks for the little little
uh tie lesson yeah you're
welcome okay so we we did quite a lot of
quests mhm and I think that's a good
point to stop right yeah and I feel
better thank
you yeah thank you everybody for coming
together at this weird time thank you
for making time girls no thank you as
well it's okay I'm awake anyway I am I
am also easily awake anyway at this
time yeah I'm glad we could find like uh
you know exactly four people for a full
team mhm yeah full team that's
awesome are you girls going to still
play this sometime or are you done with
it kind of I'm kind of done with it I'm
kind of curious as to like what's an end
game you know what's an end game a lot
of grinding
grinding grind blue grind blue
fantasy me personally I might play it
off stream but depends like if if you
guys want to play then I'll be happy to
have I to play at least um in
multiplayer I guess again M I have a lot
of games I want to play right now so I
don't think I have time for it solo but
you guys ever want to play again I am
down to play again same same same same
here yeah whenever whenever whenever
wherever and we level up so thank you so
much for helping out helping us with the
quests yeah it was fun yeah thank you
for helping me look
cool yeah you you look pretty cool yeah
thank you yeah you're cool now you're so
mature
wow you got your pro your strength sure
yeah short people can be cool n Only
proves that
okay M yeah M I agree why why why is it
getting quiet
no short people are are cool short Kings
short Queens yeah
exactly yeah thank you thank you
everybody for participating and uh I
don't know I don't Stream So This is not
I don't know okay you girls can say
goodbye properly yeah do you want to you
want to want to close it off does anyone
have
announcements no the announcement is
thank you
just thank you Advent announced 3D de
summer
y check it out we're all working really
hard for it um and really excited but
there's no date yet right just the
summer yeah just this summer is the
whole summer the whole summer yeah every
day 3D every day is advent day it could
be tomorrow who knows it's not tomorrow
spoiler but they're not going to be
ready at all times yeah you got to be
ready for it I'm so ready for it I'm
excited I'm very excited for it it feels
like it happened so fast it feels like
admin just joined like one month ago but
in reality you've been around for like
half a year almost a year actually it's
going be a year in like a few months oh
what two months yeah time flies you've
been around for 9 months says Jad nine
months yeah N9 10 months or we debuted I
debuted July 31st I think I think what
July for July last year yeah yeah July
last year but we're almost back in July
exactly what what you just joined
yesterday don't lie to
me oh my god it feels like that doesn't
it this whole half year ever since we're
in 2024 flew by insulin it makes me so
mad it it's got to go slower it's
stressing me out yeah still just a baby
but not really we're growing
up time
FES well I don't have an announcement oh
I have a inac con um event meet GRE 15
June yay that's all anybody else if
there's none we can close and end it
right
here yeah yeah yeah yeah that's fine
okay thanks for watching thank you
everyone
a make sure to get some rest
[Music]
awesome good night everyone