[Music]
foreign
[Laughter]
[Music]
key
good morning i woke up early for this
announcement
good morning
[Music]
good morning good morning
wow i'm so surprised so many people are
already here thank you everyone
thank you hello how are you guys
[Music]
okay i'm glad you're happy thank you
guys for the super chat
oh i've had this uh i've had this
pre-chat open
for like what 14 hours so what
okay
i have it for 14 hours open so i think
um
there's a lot of nice uh messages from
you guys in the super chat i
think i will i will read at the end
probably
maybe we'll see anyway um medium too
loud
thank you thank you for letting me know
is this better
well maybe how about this is this better
okay okay thank you so everyone
uh we have all come here today uh
because there is um
a few things that i would like to tell
you uh but i want to
make sure that everyone uh stays
until all all i have to say has been
said
because some of you might think oh
that's it and we'll leave early
but i will keep the big thing
until the end okay
but there's other things don't worry i'm
not gonna make you wait forever until i
tell you anything at all i'm gonna
i'm gonna get started but um there's
something
there's a taste it's not only one tiny
thing okay
you know i don't have a simmers
okay so let's start with something that
you guys already partially know
uh
[Music]
if you've seen my schedule and if you
listened to what i've been talking about
recently
um i've been planning to make a talk
show
yes yes yes yes yes it's in my schedule
for uh saturday
but for many of you that is still friday
um it's going to happen this week for
the first time
and i prepared some things for that
and i want to tease you all with that a
little bit
to get you more excited
yeah that's the first thing i want to
show you later a little bit a little bit
later i'll announce the thing i really
want to announce
so stay stay with me stay with me
about the talk show i
have been prepared preparing some things
because i wanted this to be something
special i didn't want this to be
something like like a normal two-person
just talking to each other collab i
wanted it to be something special you
know
i wanted it to be legendary and i wanted
it to be my regular
special thing so first of all
i will announce to you
the name of the talk show because there
is actually a name
yes yes yes
[Music]
and with the name comes
a logo
a logo yeah i um
like that is the thing that i uh maybe
you guys remember if you've been
following
my twitter a while ago i
was asking on twitter for people who
could
possibly uh i could who i could
possibly commission for a logo for
something
secret that was not my fairy tale
reading
i think that's what i asked on twitter
and then i got a bunch of
amazing people writing to me sending me
their samples
and i commissioned someone to make a
logo to make this
even more my thing you know it has it
has to be
my thing things have to be made well
done so
logo and name announcement in
five count with me
four three
two oh wow
[Music]
damn
thank you do you like it by the way this
is made by
a spirits snare a spirit snare spirit's
there
look at it it has my image colors
amazing kind of hyped it and uh i was i
wanted it to
be like kind of modern and so that's
what we're going for but it was kind of
like
maybe a little a little bit i don't know
how to pronounce how to
describe it but yeah i had some choices
it was really hard to choose
the right logo
gotta drink my tea to stay calm everyone
don't panic yet
there's there's more there's more there
is more
so as you maybe heard uh
in the collab with anna yesterday
amir uh is also helping me with
something
regarding this um
you might know uh well let's keep it
there
you might know that ame is pretty good
with like
making videos
[Music]
but she's also so talented so i asked
her if she would
be alright with making something for me
because i did not only
i did not only uh commission
a logo i went
beyond that and i commissioned with
the the person who made the track that's
playing right now in the background i
also commissioned
one more original like track for the
talk show for the talking session
but i also commissioned an
intro track so i got two new tracks just
for the talk show
um
[Music]
so i'm not going to play you the general
bgm which is by the way very
jazzy and very smooth and very very laid
back
it has like the thing that goes
okay i don't know i don't know
even how to mimic that instrument
what's it called again the typical jazzy
thing that goes like
no no okay that's definitely not yes
it's sex
sex
so the general medium i will not play it
yet for you you have to wait until the
until the actual talk show but
amelia okay she didn't finish it yet uh
which totally fine
but i was i still want to show you the
preview
that she's working on right now of the
intro because she's making an intro for
me
ami thank you so much
so amelia
yes yes yes and by the way for the
people are still coming in this is not
the big announcement
wait a little bit uh it's it's it's uh
coming soon
this is not the big announcement so this
is not
keep in mind this is not finished but i
want to hype you up so let's watch it
shall we watch it do you want to watch
it
it's a preview it's just a preview and
you will get a little taste
of my intro music which is so jazzy i
love it
again
intro music starting
in five an intro into another intro
music into video preview
interview starting in together five
four three
two wow
[Music]
there you go that was a small small
small taste of it
mother mother of your mother
it's still being worked on by amelia
thank you so much amelia thank you
but do you like did you hear that that
was not the whole track but did you like
the bgm the the intro track
it goes like that
[Music]
it's so good um i i
i was like uh the the person who made my
current video
i i told him i want something very jazzy
i gotta turn my own video up again all
right
yeah i told him i want something jazzy
baby jazzy
yeah and with jess with jazz of course
comes the sex
okay we're getting closer to the real
announcement
but before that um i want to show you
one more thing
oh which also kind of reveals something
else from my talk show
because i prepared even more
for the suction
so you guys know that my first guest
you guys know this my first guest will
be hosho marine
you guys know this i made i already made
the thumpnail
and i want to show it to you because it
looks cute and because there's something
else there
that is a little
teaser so let me show you
let's see if you notice something
is
and if you look at the background
look look how cute we are looking at
each other but if you look at the
background
what is that what is that it's an
original background that looks
[Music]
i i commissioned two vgn tracks a logo
and a background and amelia is making a
video for me
i am well prepared my friends i am all
in for this i
am super excited hopefully you are as
well hi
[Music]
do you like it it has like the color
vibes
um of that background uh
kinda overlap a little bit with marin
senpai's
uh color theme but oh well
that's a coincidence um
yeah i wanna i wanna uh point out
that um in the background uh i
specifically asked
for a sunset uh because
you know my hair looks like a sunset
um so i wanted a sunset in the
background with the skyline
looks good right and there's red if you
if you look closely
you can also see there's like feathers
uh
phoenix feathers in the background it's
uh i know so you call
that's that and with that the whole
uh holo talk announcements
are over i think that's all i wanted to
say
ah yeah one more thing one more thing um
in five minutes i'll tell you the real
announcement oh my god i'm so excited
um one more thing so uh i told you
before that this is going to be not just
a normal like
collab where we talk to each other i
want to
basically the whole concept let me tell
you again for the people who don't know
the whole concept
is basically i know that many of the
overseas fans
got interested in hollow life because of
clips and stuff
translated clips or not translated clips
but i think
many of you even though you like the
japanese talents very much
you probably don't really know if you
don't speak fluent japanese you probably
don't know that much about them
at all you think you you watch some
clips but you don't you probably don't
know that much about them right
you want to know you want to have more
deep knowledge but this is usually not
something that
is really um laid open in these clips
you know
especially if there's like lots of
non-translated clips
you will never really know what they're
truly saying so
using my talents i am going to be asking
them some really deep stuff you know
some really deep questions about their
activities about their life
about how they're feeling for example
for money and senpai we can talk about
the process
of making her songs etc stuff like that
i want some deep talk
and we're gonna do this in japanese but
i will be live
translating her answers to english yeah
so that the english bros can
find out more about their favorite idols
that's that's how it how it's going to
be
[Music]
honestly
so for this um uh
i want you guys help i want your help
after the stream i'm going to be making
a community post
on my channel where i ask you guys for
some deep questions okay i don't want
joke questions
i don't care about joke questions we
don't want to know what her
what what what her favorite food is or
if she's still horny
we don't want to know that i mean
we do care a little bit about her
horniness but this is not about that
okay this is not about that so i will be
asking on my community
um post for some good deep
questions that you've always wanted to
know i want you guys to give this
a big thank uh what like
something special that you wanted to
know think about it
[Music]
yes yes yes yes i'll be asking the big
brain
questions the things you've always been
wondering are just things that make
gives you deeper knowledge of these
cute items so for
american viewers this is happening on
friday
late night and for me this uh for
japanese viewers this is happening on
saturday
um early noon
toyota
foreign where to start
where to start where to start i've been
teasing this
for a long time
[Music]
i've been teasing this for a long time
and
um because of these teachers some people
have been
trying to figure out what it could be
and i have to say
um most of you are wrong
so
maybe you guys remember one time
i said i am
did i say that i wonder i feel like i
said this before
that i am preparing
something for thanksgiving thanksgiving
is
next week
well well well let me tell you it is
not it is not a collaboration with kelly
no we are indeed working on something
that she
uh accidentally said in her stream
she did um
accidentally well like she didn't know
that it was something that she shouldn't
say
she did say that we're working on
something on the side but that is not it
that is not it is
this particular thing that i'm
preparing for thanksgiving
is something that was on my goal
list on my debut stream
um
[Music]
presents to you
her first original song
[Music]
don't leave yet there's much more i will
apple
oh i will i will not just leave you like
that i you know i'm the type of person
who likes to tease as many things as
possible
yes actually since them since the
beginning my plan was and since i said
in my debut stream it was on my goal
list i said
i want to make uh
original music as well and you know
callie has been
uh releasing all those bangers and i've
been listening to them and i was like
i can't wait anymore i can't wait
anymore i want to make music too
thank you oh thanks for the super chat
but there's still more there's still
more yeah i've been i've been
i was like i cannot i cannot hold my
back myself back anymore i want an
original song
so i um took it upon myself
i chose
someone to make a song for me by myself
and i asked him would you like to
work together on a song
and uh he uh
gladly accepted but um
we we did not have much time because i
said that about a month ago
and um he was a bit busy with other
stuff
um
why are you guys coming up with such
unbelievable names
what what what kind of genre are you
guys expecting
[Music]
i think okay let's be real it's
obviously not gonna be rap but what do
you actually
expect from me what kind of genre i
think many of you
would um expect something
cute something poppy
something cute wow we'll see about that
um but other than that i i already
want to show to you
the jacket design the promotional
illustration
and i want to show to you the title
as well
do you want to see it do you want to see
it of course you want to see it
do you want to see it
i am i was like if i want
for my first single i definitely want my
papa
to make an illustration for this
so i asked my papa to do it
there you
illustration five
four three two
[Music]
one
and the title is hinotori
in romaji in uh in our letters uh on
purpose not in
japanese letters
[Music]
he totally means firebird in japanese
but i went for the i thought it was
fancy to have it in
japanese but not firebird in english you
know
thank you so much papa for making the
illustration thank you for the super
chats
but wait there's more but wait
there is more
there's still more there's still two
more things so don't leave
us
doesn't this look amazing oh yeah so
release is 26 november which is uh
thanksgiving
and um since i wanted since mostly
america and canada uh um
you know celebrate thanksgiving
it had to be at least thanksgiving in
their time zone
so the actual release uh
will be for japan will be quite late uh
in the end
in the late night it will it will be 26
but um
for you guys it will be i think
thanksgiving morning
for the american and canadian viewers it
will be thanksgiving morning
so you wake up and you listen to this
there is more there uh actually no one
more thing
um i am i asked
kelly to make a music video for me
and she's working on it right now
[Music]
yeah cali is making a music video
and for the music video i also um
commissioned some extra art not from
fuke papa
not from my papa because i wanted a few
more pieces and i uh
that that had to happen quickly
[Music]
do you guys know i for thanksgiving you
know i don't celebrate thanksgiving but
i
felt like i might be in danger thank you
guys for the super chat
i felt like i might be in danger for
thanksgiving because people do think
even though i'm obviously a phoenix
people think i'm a chicken or a turkey
or whatever so
i was like okay i gotta do something to
get their minds off of eating me
i need to i need to distract them with
something and i also
need to let them know that i am indeed
a phoenix that's why the song is all
about
me as a phoenix and um
how how how strong i am and how how life
there might be struggles but i keep on
fighting until the end
you know that's what the song is
basically about it's a very strong song
and with this you might forget that uh
what you think about me
and you might realize oh she's a phoenix
i cannot eat her on thanksgiving
and that way i will be safe from all the
dangers
[Laughter]
[Music]
america
there is a few more things please stay
stay with me stay with me there is a few
more things
so cali is making the music video right
do you um ah let's start with the other
thing okay
uh besides that besides me uploading the
song
on youtube on thanksgiving with the
music video
um it will also be on all kinds of
music services thank you guys for the
super chat thank you
look forward to your thanksgiving now
maybe actually yeah maybe you can spend
it with your family
because of reasons but you will be able
to
listen to this song it's my present to
you for thanksgiving
yeah it will be on spotify itunes amazon
music
etc eventually it will not make it in
time for the 26th
i think but eventually soon after
it will be on those music services but
but
now here's here's something special
for the people who really really really
love
kiara and really want to support kiara
now i don't have a graphic for this yet
to announce it properly
[Music]
on both i will release my first voice
a voice back i think maybe i think
there's many
new fans who don't know yet thank you
for the super chats thank you
i think there's many people who don't
know yet what a voice pack is it's
basically like
um like
well yeah it's just a voice of me a
special voice
but i wrote i wrote a little script and
i thought of uh
something between us me and my kfp
employees and i i
recorded it at studio yeah
and the voice pack will include a thank
you message
uh the script the so it's quite quite a
long
several minutes of a voice of me talking
to you
there uh yeah that's that and the
instrumental version of the song
because uh due to business reasons
we since we want to sell the song on
uh spotify itunes etc we cannot include
the actual song
in the voice pack but you will get the
instrumental version as an
extra hi boys
um
that was um an interesting experience
but i'll talk about
all these things in my uh
yeah that's the other thing i'm doing uh
i'm doing uh of course like a release
party like cali usually does
uh for we're gonna watch the music video
and right after that
i will stream and we talk about
everything together
on the 26th so yeah that's that
uh so release on youtube 26th
voice pack also release 26th
and then later on spotify itunes amazon
music but wait
there is more mada
i see already people are leaving but
there is still more
yolas the last thing
but wait there is
see that that is the reason why i had to
stream
uh for this announcement because there's
so much i want to tell you and so much i
want to show you
there's more obviously you know i'm a
very excited person i like to share as
much as possible with you
so
would you like would you like a little
sneak peek of the socks would you like
to listen a little bit to it
[Music]
of course you do of course you want to
listen to it of course why would you say
no
yes it is
an amazing song so i cannot hold myself
back
i will let you listen to the chorus only
oh my god only the chorus
uh so please enjoy
one second
okay
are you guys ready for this
i hope that i hope the audio will not be
too loud
but should be fine
the chorus only
are you ready count down with me
five so many countdowns today
four three
two one
[Music]
um
[Applause]
[Music]
isn't not amazing i swear it's
damn damaged
i know listening to only those few
seconds it's kind of hard to judge
but it's a really really cool cool cool
very cool um very cool song
with lots of igetai yum yum yum yum yum
yum yum
i know some people say it's like an
anime opening
yeah pretty badass right
i didn't want a cute song eventually
maybe one day i want a cute song as well
but for this one i was like i want
something
really really really cool do you wanna
was that too short to i feel like you
you would like forget it right away do
you wanna listen to it one more time
to like really get to get like
understand
how how how it is do you want to listen
to it one more time
okay let's listen to it together one
more one more
one more one more
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
yay okay that's the last lesson i give
for you
yay
so many of you many of you thought this
is gonna be an announcement about the
collaboration
or it's gonna be 3d honestly that's too
early i'm sorry but
friday is a little bit too early
or like it's gonna be the collab some
with cali which was already uh
like teased a little bit there will be
there will be something like that as
well but no
it is my own solo original song
yeah oh i'm so i'm so excited like
uh i'm so happy to be able to
you know release my own music
for you guys i'm so happy i can also
share it with so many people i've been
really looking forward to this
and uh recording it was a lot of fun
yeah um
the the the chorus was mostly
japanese to song the song is mostly
japanese but i did add
quite some english lyrics to it i
i wrote lyrics um by myself partially
the japanese lyrics are written by
someone else but
the english lyrics i wrote myself there
is no
english version but there is quite some
english in it
yeah you will of course when i release
the
video there will be subtitles uh the
english translation as well
i should turn on my music again
[Music]
about you know being strong about
standing up again about
fighting about reviving until finding my
about fighting finding my destiny
all those kinds of things i'm so excited
okay after this i will upload that
graphic on my twitter as well
did you guys expect a song like this
from me
because i really thought that people
would think it's more like a poppy cute
song if anything
smell like something adorable
but i wanted to show you how how badass
uh kiara can be you did expect something
like this
really really
[Music]
foreign i'm so excited that's why
uh the last few days and weeks i kept on
teasing you guys telling you
there's something amazing coming up i
can't wait to tell you
there's something amazing i told you
like almost every
stream the past week i told you in like
pretty much every stream
yeah i just couldn't hold it back and
some of you didn't take it seriously
some of you were like oh yeah
announcement whatever but this
this is much more than just an
announcement
it is the start of an era
the talk show with my own original song
talk show starting this week so
stay tuned look forward to it
[Music]
my body was not ready for that much time
thank you guys for the super chats thank
you superchat
yeah i'm excited you're excited we're
all happy
thank you all for coming today to watch
this announcement stream
um i think i will um read the super
chats
in the next stream and i i'm going to
do a gorilla stream in about
12 hours
[Music]
scheduling
i will reserve it after
this stream it will be a spontaneous
stream that was not on my schedule we
will be playing among us together
[Music]
among us yeah i think probably something
around 11
p.m my time which is like in 12 hours
thank you guys for the super chat
[Music]
the super chat i will read in the among
us stream
so i will reserve that stream afterwards
[Music]
hey that was it from kiara all the
announcements
and please everyone please welcome
to the holotalk first edition
with joshua malinka
[Music]
we say in german the usual
greeting
[Music]
thank you for coming everyone thank you
so much for
hyping everything up with me i'm looking
forward to
you hearing the song soon and showing
you
everything in the in the whole talk show
thank you guys i love you
finally finally i could say it all out
loud finally
finally it's all out ah what a relief
what a relief i'm so excited
yay bye bye
see you see you in 12 hours for a manga
stream
bye-bye
[Music]
i'm not laughing shut up
bye bye