[Music]
Thank you very much.
Well, the music garden has started tonight. I
haven't finished it yet, but it's
getting hot, so I've
been thinking about going there a little bit.  I
got my hair cut, right? Come to think of it, I haven't had my hair cut
quite a while ago.
It's my birthday. It's a
happy birthday. I
haven't brushed my teeth, but I got my hair cut.
First, I'd like to introduce today's guest.  [
Music]
[Applause]
[Music]
Tonight we will be bringing you another gorgeous guest,
Music Garden.It seems that tonight's popular
overseas groups will also be connected via broadcast.You ca
n't miss it until the end.Yes, this is it.High
Price LukeThank you for being a regular customer.Thank you very much for
today.  I think it's the first time,
but
thank you very much. Thank you
very much. I've appeared 61 times, so from now on, I'll be doing it 62 times, 63 times, and every time. Yes, yes, I'd appreciate your continued support.
Thank you.  Well then, let's start the music garden.
[Music]
[Applause] The
first guest is High Price Louis.
Thank you very much. It's my
birthday, thankfully it's my birthday.
Thank you very much.
This information I received recently is a nightmare.  It's
like I wake up
after watching a movie, and for example,
when I'm recording an M movie, there's no one there, or when the
curtain goes up on a live performance, there's no one there.I have
nightmares like that, and I wake up and
cry.I'm the
manager.
Is that what it's like to call someone? Mr. Manager,
that's not that hard. You call me after you wake up. You call me and say
ok, okay. She
sleeps like a mother. Do you
have nightmares? I haven't had them lately.
Shirakami-kun, I dream that I don't remember anything famous.
Of course I dream.
[Music] The most
famous thing I had recently was that I was in the mountains,
picking mushrooms that I
don't understand.  I
think so. Let's go back later and make some adjustments. Okay,
that's it. Rui Takamine will
perform the very popular cover song Loveka.
Please stand by.
Thank you.
[Applause] You do
n't remember your dreams.  I'm
not sleeping soundly, but that's a good thing.
Well, it's popular among young people.
It's listed on Wikipedia. I wonder
how many times this has happened. I'll
check with my manager later.
Okay, let's check it out. Now, let's get
ready.  Now that we're done, let's
go.Then
let's go and love Rui Takamine. [Music] [Applause] [Music] Will the uncivilized feelings change? [Music] If it's sweet, then it's too sweet. For lies and elaborate love, no, no, no.  Or should I start writing?
The art that was waiting within reach
[Music]
Surrounded by a scary level of evolution My
wishes are
launched and delivered in a whisper
Even so, the light is
already about half of it The
unexplored
feelings will change
[Music]
La la la la la man capi? It's a
love affair that's full of lies
No matter what, I don't want to start writing it down It
must be painful waiting at a distance I can't reach Is it a
bug bug bug I've
fallen
If we meet at a distance where we can reach and it'll be surprising
[Music]  ] La la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la la  It seems like they didn't have enough
microphones, so I didn't have mine. I looked around and saw that everyone was full of animals, which was nice. There were people with dogs and sushi ram cong cong leg. It seems like the
ingredients are good. Do you
eat sheep? It's
delicious, isn't it
?  You'll be
performing your songs, right? Yes, I was
a little concerned about how delicious everyone looked,
but I hope everyone in front of the screen
will be excited as well.
Yes, please stand by, please.
[Applause]  I
think it's surprisingly good.The best caste-like food you can eat there is the lamb.I think it's delicious.The ramsam
is delicious.Would you like to
go out for some food after this?
Okay, then.  Let's
have a week at Shoinu Takashi Shiram
[Applause]
[Music]
From tomorrow onwards, we'll
pass the tickets, Kinro, let's cherish the days of our dreams. Let's go to another one,
pass the tickets, and enjoy our daily lives. We'll only
go if we live. Yeah, let's go.  We've just started
thinking longingly about each day, and we're
getting used to the practice.Always remember the smile you put on.Look
at the plans for tomorrow night, which are quite important.So let's
think about it all on Friday.Let's break down the wall with freedom,
pull it out, and our hearts are cloudy.
Ha, if I give up on my heart that passes by, then I'll take it easy. There's still sun and moon from tomorrow. Let's
turn around and cherish the days of our dreams. Starting
tomorrow, let's
live and enjoy each day.
[Music]
What should we do now?  I don't have anything to do, so I'm
toast. I sleep four hours a
day, put all my energy into it every day, and grow up to become an adult.
When 35 episodes have passed, what kind of cool-looking adults will we look like?  Our
hearts are cloudy. We love each other. It's
okay to take it slow, don't stop. Someday we'll be free. We'll
definitely be together
again tomorrow. It's Sunday. Let's cherish the
days of our dreams. Starting
tomorrow, we'll find them again. Hey,
enjoy each day and live.  Please
[Music]
These repeating days have no place to go, and these feelings
go round and round, spinning around in a dizzying pace.
Let's move on from tomorrow, cherishing the days of our dreams.
As long as we want to live and enjoy each day, tomorrow
is another day.
Let's cherish the days of our dreams
[Music]
[Applause]
[Music] I
think I flew high, but even if it starts raining again,
I'll
protect you, so fly ahead, I
don't know what's waiting for you in the future, I
believe.  I'll go anywhere with you.
Next up is the three members of SSS.
Thank you very much. It looks like it's going to be your first
appearance.
What does SSS mean? It
comes from the initials, and we're sexy
sensitive warriors.
Do they have any sexy episodes?
No, that's right.
When we collaborated on Chocolat, the
three of us played around at Chocolat's house. I'm
really sorry, but it's
too much to say here.
[Laughs] I see.
Well, that's Marin-san.  Ha,
Marin-san too,
that day I was allowed to do something from an erotic book,
but I did something that I can't say,
so I won't go into
details on this show.I brought it with me.
[Music] Do
you want to do it?I'm fine with it.
After you listen to the song, Pol-
san will make a decision, so tonight you'll be able to
perform a sexy song.That
's right.It's a song that's perfect for us, who are really sexy,
so you guys are watching.  I want to make this a melt-in-
the-mouth affair. If I do say so myself, I'll say it's sexy, but it's amazing. I'm a warrior. This is because of the Reiwa era. So, please, yes, please. [Music] [Applause] The player on the phone is great.  Well, I
guess Reiwa might not be so bad. Well
then, let's go to SSS in all its grandeur.
[Applause]
[Music]
[Music] My
nerves are already
drowning in eating everything, so I'll take my heart and
push it in my mouth.  It seems possible
[Music]
Not
[Music] I
don't need everything I don't need everything I have a calm
ambition
Satisfaction is not there I can see
it It's up to you to do what you want I
won't do anything I'll do as long as I'm happy than anyone else
Look, in this world  No.
[Music] It's
not the time to be small.
[Music] I
wanted it. Does it feel good
?
[Music]
[Applause]
Yes, next we'll split the bill. Thank you.  You
shared a cream puff with me.I
wonder
if it's okay to spoil me.I wonder if that's the key to maintaining a good relationship.But we
meet almost every week.I
don't really say anything about it.
But I thought we got along well after all.Okay, I'll
ask you to stand by for today's amazing cooperativeness and trainability.Thank you very much.
[Music]
[Applause]
I think the female executives in Tokyo are a bit too strong.  Well,
since the relationship between subordinates and subordinates ends, I
wonder who is actually superior.In
terms of power, the demon is the better, but
Ayame-san is still a little
young, so she is still a cream puff.  I'm in a
good mood, don't you think? Well
then, let's go. I'm sure there are many people who wanted to listen to this song with these two.
Turing love with a demonic feeling Ah
[Music] I
don't understand the weather of love
[Music]
Time  Evidence
Today I want to prove the course. What is this invisible impossibility? No
matter how
many times I turn around or bump into something,
this Mario of the organization is a condition of use.
[Music] I
thought it was something like that.  But I can't find the coordinates or the stars,
and it's
not even listed in the tourist materials, so I'm
looking for this feeling that happens in a three-dimensional world, and I'm
shaking without a goal. [
Music] [
Applause]
[Music] The
baby motion is to look at the other person and
show off your innocent breasts.  The higher it gets, the more the lighting
seems to change.
If it's like the biggest war right now,
[music]
[applause]
[  [Applause]
[Music]
[Applause]
Next up are the two analogists.
Thank you very much. I think there will be a lot of attention on what the two analogists will sing today. Thank
you very much.
Did you know that today I will be singing Bug?
Yes, when I thought that I wanted to try my best
at singing, I ended up thinking that I really admired Mizuo from the same agency as a senpai,
and even more so, if we could sing together.  I wanted to
sing a cool song with you,
so I invited you with a bug.
Thank you.
[Music] I
guess it's a big difference from before.
Recently, I've had some warm episodes with my juniors, like Comet, who is a
senior and a junior.  That
's sudden.
[Music]
In the warm episode,
there's a chorus that describes this bug, and you
almost captured it.
Where I was at the end of trading, I'm going to
take it.
Thank you.
[Laughter]
Please.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
[Applause]
Hey, you appeared again this time. It
seems like it's going to be a
warm episode. I wonder if we have any warm episodes.
Ah, the venue and the lights are pretty warm right now. It's
warm. This is the 61st time.
61  It's the third time, let's go.
Let's go. Let's go.
Bug by analogy.
[Music] [Music] [Music] [
Music] [
Music]
[Music]
[Music] No no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no [music]
]
[Music] See
you all again! We'll be introducing the High Price Louis Birthday Commemoration
2023 goods. It'll go
on sale from 10pm after this, so be sure to check it out. We've
prepared 4 types of goods this time.
Random
canvas art.  There are
4 types of magnetic coaster ice cubes.Of
course,
there is a bonus for purchasing the full set.The limited edition
comes with a bonus voice for eating omelet rice together, and a postcard with my foil-stamped message and autograph.
Quantities are limited, but we've prepared a lot
of them, so we'd be happy if everyone who liked them, and even those who didn't like them, could get their hands on them.In the regular version, the handwritten autograph part says "I want to know."Now, let's take a look at each item one by one.  Let's
start with canvas art. An
illustration of someone loving omelet rice drawn by Mr. Kuchiko. Is
n't this really cute? It's also
stylish. I think the color will blend in with your room.
Let's hang it up in your room and
eat together. Next up, click here.
Random
magnet  One of the 4 types
of magnets with cute cute illustrations drawn by Mr. Tumi
will be delivered to you at random.When you think of magnets, you definitely
want to put them in your refrigerator.All 4 types are
cute, so if you like, please complete the set.By
the way, I'm drooling.  I
especially like the sloppy one. Next up is the Chan-chan
coaster. When you put a drink in it, water drops get on it, which
bothers you. This coaster is recommended for those times. It's made of
metal and cork material, so it has a solid feel, making it a
coaster that can be used as a decoration for everyday use.
After all, I
want to place a glass of a cold drink here and make a drink.
So, I
need ice for the gate drink. Lastly, I
will introduce ice cubes.
Wash and repeat my ice cubes with various motifs.  The
good thing about Ice Cube is that it can be used.I
wonder who has the Kasako panel.That's
why the
ruler of New Japan Pro Wrestling is Great.Even though
this world took the trouble to personally introduce Gucci, it's
sure to be a
perfect match.  Aim for the complete list and go home.
Hey, you high price from there. This guy is
good at pro-wrestling. Besides, it's his
birthday, right?
This is Yokarou's birthday present.
Hey,
princess, happy
birthday.
Next up is this week's pick-up artist
section.  A group that is currently attracting a lot of attention from overseas will
be performing live.
Foreignartists I'm
looking forward to this. I'm looking forward to it
. We're connected,
so let's connect right away.
[Music]
Everyone is cute. There are a lot of them, but that's what I said earlier.  Some
people were here all the way. I
went early.
Hey, isn't this the usual Louis who was in the studio before the station? It's hard to
hear. It's
hard to hear. It seems like the reception is a little
bad.
So, once again, everyone at Holo Tori
[Music]
Thank you in advance.  It
seems better not to mention it for a moment, so let's introduce Holotori.
Let's see what kind of group we are. We
have summarized it on VTR, so please take a look.
This week's pick-up artist,
Holotori JP
iden. A global idol unit that transcends the national flag.
Follow members are
Peacock Favoria Rayme from ID Takanashi Phoenix from en
[Music]
Side
JP to Takataka Email
[Music]
Subaru
Ozora A group that is currently attracting attention who can speak other languages ​​and is made up of core birds We will
perform tonight with these unique girls.
What they do is express their brightness The
theme of Nikkori Research Team and the world of this world There are
many Hololive songs by Econina and Shota Horie, who are indispensable in the music scene.A
dream collaboration song between two famous artists who have worked on it.It's
amazing.  Along with the song, Holotori will spread its wings around the world.
No, I'm looking forward to the bath-taking performance that is currently attracting attention. Yes, I
think we can look forward to this.
By the way, do you have any favorites? No,
everyone had a fresh feel and
was really cute, but
that's not the case.  However,
with Treat Box, that's already the case.I'm
sorry for that, but the meaning
is a little different.Group:
Nowadays, Mr. Hako and everyone else remember it, too.Thank
you.It looks
like everything is ready, so let's go.
Let's play Orotori and continue with the 2 theme world songs of Nikkori Research Team
[Applause]
[Music]
Today too
Collection
[Music]
Smiles around the world
Anyway,
I'm
not saying that. Let's leave for now. Wait a minute, wait a
minute, let's
begin.  First of all, I
forgot to change my clothes as a master.I
have a mobile battery.Of course, it's
off, and I'm here, so it's
not normal.Who are you talking about?It's going to be impossible for us.It's so
crunchy [
Music]
[Music]
My heart swelled even more when I touched it.
[Applause]
[Music] I've
been looking for a
place where I can say it's special. Why did
you choose me? You took off
because you're amazing.
[Music] I
feel like I can't lose, no matter
what.  Your voice was still ringing inside me
[Music] I'm
scared, I'm nothing, but I wonder if I can do it
[Music]
But what's the point? Don't sing the song with a face on your face
That's not it, just jump in.  Let's
go to our world. I wonder if we'll be
able to meet the world's feelings. I
want to sing, I want
to dance. I want to laugh as much as I want to say. We can get lost in
our nameless world.
That's why we're
changing.
As we wish, now we're
looking forward to it. I want to drink in your future.  I'll sing
it. [Music] I hope you don't think twice as I embrace you and go to the world that I want to see. [Music] Thank you to all the chickens. I'll keep an eye on your future activities. That's right, this is Music
Garden.  However, there were only two songs left. It
felt like it was about 8 hours long, but it was only about an hour long
. It
was perfect. The next two
songs are the same as before.  I
created a song called Sekai yo Sekai that everyone performed.I didn't create the world,
but it's a song based on the world I mentioned earlier.It's a
new song written by Teko Nina and another song by Shota Kawahorie.  That's
right.Thank you very much.That's why I was told that the
two songs have a strong message.I'm
surprised.Now
then, let's move on.Deconina-san's newly
written station.Idiot
Baka.First
song written by Shota Horie.
Cry two songs in a row, please
[Applause] It's
enough, you've turned around, put on a cool look, and it's not cool. I'm tired of things like that. Leave me alone. I don't want to know. It's
okay. I can't
hear you. I can't be jealous. I can't be jealous.  I'm tired of them telling me to cover my ears.No
one's
looking in on me.So
leave me alone
and let the annoying idiots crawl at me.They say they're waiting for me to leave me alone.They say I'm actually frightened, that I'm just a
weakling who just barks.
[Music]  ]
Yes, yes, always just a calm fishing guy, etc.
I laugh with my walls up and
don't come any closer. It
's scary. It's
okay. You're still angry. Just leave me
alone. Even if I look away as if there's no future in my life, I'll still come after you.  It's
okay, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, that's
not okay.
If
you don't like it, then that's not okay. No one will look at me, so I wish I could just keep my mouth shut
and say that all the things I don't like are okay. I wish I could
think that.
No, stop!
That's always my goal. Kill what I want to say again,
then forget about it. I'm just barking
at the idiots who are just making fun of rumors. I
'm waiting for something to happen again. I'm actually
scared. I'm
just barking.  I was a weakling
[Music]
Yes,
I'm being used to it, but I laugh with my walls up. Don't come any closer. You're just being lazy.
There's nothing I can do about these words. I can't help but put up with the
wall today.  Laughing with a smile on my face, I was told not to come any closer.
[Music]
[Music] Even if
someone didn't crack
me, I hate it even more. My
imagination
blocks my vision, and I
write down the reason why I'm miserable.  There
was a black shadow on the other side of the classrooms,
looking at me without saying a word.I
cried because I wanted to be saved by you.I
couldn't stop the voice,
thousands of times.Even
there, there was
hope. [Music]
I was the only one who wanted to forgive the ugly light wrapped in the darkness of despair.I
put on a balloon and
opened my eyes.
[Music]I
wonder if this is the last time.I don't want to die.I do
n't want to die.[
Music]
I'll fill in the answers that I can't solve.  "It's funny anyway," I
heard faintly from across the window.It was
just a prayer-like movement.I
don't know the words that can save you, but I
called out to you, saying, ``I'm lonely.'' [
Music]
[Applause]
[Music]
[Applause] I
almost died last time and again, clothed in the night of hope and despair, and once again, a thousand times, I'll take my breath to you. When I fell in love with the light on the other side of the window, I couldn't let it end.  Let's
make a song, let's
be together, let's
be together
[Music]
You, the living one,
follow me The
other side of the window, I
'm not a band, I'm a dead person, too.
Today, I'm smiling with my walls up. I can't get any closer. I've
turned around.  It's
not good to be cool. Don't get tired of things like that.
Leave me alone. I don't want to die.
[Music] We've had
fun delivering Music
Garden. It's almost
time for the ending. How are you doing today, Pol?
Well, I really had a lot of fun today. It
feels like I spent an hour.
No, it doesn't feel like an hour.
[Music] I wasn't
really busy. What do you
mean? I've been doing a lot of alter egos, but I'm an alter ego.  I was
very happy to be able to perform with various artists.Thank
you very much.Congratulations on the sale of
High Price Birthday today.Thank
you.Today
after Neko, there will
be NCC streaming exclusively for members, so I
think I'll give it a try.  I think that's what
I posted earlier, but I
think I'll put out a few things like that.
Please come and see it. I'd like to
ask all the guests for their thoughts.
Let's start with Inutaka Assislam.
Yay,
yay, happy birthday, yay,
thank you very much.
[Music]
Thank you.
Next, Ayame-san. How
was it? Hello, Rei-chan.
Thank you for your happy birthday. I'm glad we
could sing together.
Thank you for inviting me.
Yes.  Thank you very much.
Well, time flies, but
that's all for tonight's Music Garden.
Thank you very much. Goodbye
[Applause]
[Music]