[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]
just a second
foreign
we're here
today are you guys ready sorry for the
wait but we are here and ready to
have no fear
Clubhouse games World worldwide games
for Club
let's go I'm here they're here
welcome are you guys ready for the
totsumachi of the century
get ready
to play some games
however I do need a little sensor image
to come up
um in the meantime
just in case so for example if
somebody's trying to enter
and then I need to like put in a new
code or something like that which
hopefully shouldn't happen
um but this is the only one I have so it
doesn't mean per se that there's
something like lewd that's gonna come up
on the stream it's just you know
covering the game right and I think it
still has a hotkey no it doesn't
no it does not that's fine don't need it
don't need it
LOL I know it seems lewd but there's
nothing lewd going on I can assure you
okay
the hotkey is cold uh
no reason
just for fun
anyway
uh I should probably get in the totesuit
looks like you're in another voice
Channel yeah I get it
I know
well let's see when friends join I see
that there's somebody here waiting
actually as a matter of fact
there's somebody waiting
oh
it looks like there is a bit of a
schedule
nice
cool one sec
can we
and we
okay let me
she doesn't seem to realize I'm here so
I'm gonna
hi foreign
she doesn't seem to realize I'm here
that's okay I wonder if I can invite her
tap tap yeah hello
oh she says
oh oh
who's that oh okay maybe we should stop
making these noises
who's that Pokemon hey it's Iris it's
Iris
hi Cali
Chris are we gonna play a game together
yes let us play Clubhouse and decide who
is the best gamer out of
the two of us
don't play I guess alrighty yeah okay
let's do it wait uh am I allowed uh I
think chats I turned you down
it's fine don't worry about it oh it's
the online play uh Yago is watching it
doesn't mean that is a friend right on
switch yes okay indeed let me create a
Lobby then waiting for someone to join
oh I have to wait for you to join that's
weird wait wait so is there a rumor or
something already yeah I did like play
with friends
let me let me see if I can find see if
you can join
I've just got searching for lumpies oh I
see it okay
pull it down a little I have the sound
settings up extra high because we were
playing
uh with some quiet folk uh a little
earlier all right let's go confirm
hey Donkey Kong icon yeah DK is from a
fave no particular reason I just think
he's cool you know what do we play I
wonder what do you want to play
um honestly anything as long as I know
the rules I I haven't played uh
clubhouse in like
over over a year oh it's been a hot
minute yeah no car let's see is there
anything you want to play okay let's see
let's play uh no darts is a disaster
waiting to happen you played some Wii
sports today right yes I did okay let's
play toy tennis toy tennis oh is this
like kind of like the toy football but
I've never played this one before
similar
let's see it I think yeah you're just
gonna have to go back and forth it's
it's kind of like a
like one of those games that like your
grandparents own or something like that
and they have it in the den and it's
just like a weird like
like soccer game or like
maybe you don't know what that is
go me alrighty then wait what are the
buttons what is the name of the game
hold on how to play
can you just show all right Basics you
guys know what what I'm talking about
right where like you you spin the soccer
players and there's a ball yeah yeah I
know what you're talking about that one
spin them around that one I don't know
what that's called either but yeah yeah
foosball yes it is yeah kind of reminds
me of Foosball okay technical terms all
right cool but what is what are the
controls hey I don't know them either so
I don't know maybe we're both we're both
beginners then yeah we're both beginners
so we're on an even playing field okay
let's play huh two games for now yeah
two game match
okay let's go
bring it okay bring it no I'm I'm I'm
the Superior Color I'm red okay okay I
mean I agree but oh it's gonna tell me
okay left swing right swing right swing
okay that's easy remember okay okay
yeah just a little warm-up because
you're oh yeah it's because you're too
strong because you're too strong exactly
can I go four two oh I think so
um yeah I think you can
what no I got stuck no well I'm never
going forward again okay
yeah
hey
tennis
what was that a grand slam is what it
was I didn't know you could use that
yeah
little Spike make it easy yeah
no
piece is not not what let's go all right
peace was never an option I get it
it's never an option Deuce is wild baby
uh
we're gaming
no I don't know how I did that I think
it was like a perfect battery I think
it's the perfect Parry Advantage server
basically a perfect Parry I guess it's
timing yeah it has to be timing
It's gotta be well
the speed is real ah neck and neck so I
gotta get you twice in a row I see
oh really yeah I don't really know if
that like
means anything in particular but no
you have won this one but you won't get
the next one oh it's okay it's best out
of three gotcha see
what's two matches
I can Parry
oops I can Parry
okay bring it
that was just it
okay short handicap ah
go blue guy go be good what's up what
oh
gosh I hope no neighbors are listening
I hope no neighbors are listening to the
sound listening to what what well
there's nothing there's nothing sus
about us playing
little monkey noises
that might be us okay maybe a little I
agree no neighbors okay well that timing
was a little too good and I applaud you
for it but that's the last of that hey
you you hit it up you hit the ball up
that's what happens when you do that
oops
oh no
no hurry okay yeah okay not bad at the
worst
okay this one goes to more Irene uh all
right best two out of three let's go
party okay
we can do it
I'm diving
believe in yourself
I'm losing hope
don't lose hope you can't lose yourself
don't lose sight of yourself Iris why
are you suddenly so good at this uh
practice because we've been doing it for
a little bit hey I've been practicing
Justice
maybe
well there's that I guess
[Laughter]
do you want to play some
um I don't want to say toy curling air
hockey air hockey is the one oh air
hockey yes that is classic classic air
hockey I used to like almost dislocate
my arm playing air hockey that's how
rough it goes okay let's go
oh yeah this is pretty like simple but I
think that you can like bash the puck
which is important I feel like it's
really common to like accidentally like
push the Poke into your own goals
I tend to do that very often
um
we need no explanation we're just gonna
play air hockey Iris so competitive
let's go play 10 point match 10 point
match
that's the way to do it let's go
[Music]
red why do you get the good color
[Applause]
being a prank a bongo let's see I told
you it's very common I'm trying not to
be rude and toxic because karma's a hoe
in this game okay oh no oh yeah no Karma
there's no such thing as karma no
Karma's totally real I felt it in Mario
it was intense no still did you know win
by a landslide Yeah by a lot by a whole
lot
but that was apparently the first time
that she'd ever done that well
yeah
so Iris how was your day it's been it's
been great again with the neighbors I
don't want them to hear the noises it's
okay you're not it's not on speaker
right you're using headphones right I
mean I I am but you can never be too
careful you can never be too careful oh
Cali be more easy on me
you're getting it twisted you're gonna
make me not focus
that's the whole that's the plan whoa
CCC look what you've done oh my gosh
getting a workout in
yeah with our fingers
stop that
oh what did I say I literally oh wait
what the [\h__\h] was that [\h__\h] star
boy okay
neck and neck
come on just just don't know stop
stop you're getting your home get in
your home Puck you love your home no no
that's no no your home is that way your
home is that way Mori loves air hockey
match points inside the match
but will it I'm gonna play it safe
please oh yeah play it safe extra safe
goalie mode extra safe
well good games I don't feel like being
mean after that
we can play a different game you get to
choose choose which game you want to
play I want to play I want to play
Connect Four okay Connect Four is a good
game also weirdly my arm is like behind
my chair I have it like why it's like my
left arm that has like the analog stick
it's like a really chill position I'm
like leaning back and like my arm is
draped over my chair and I'm just oh
that sounds comfortable yeah nice and
cozy I gotta get an urban military too
you do I bet you'd really really get a
lot of use out of it because I know you
like to stream for long times too maybe
not like Marathon streams but long
streams so you basically just you lean
back on the back rest straight the whole
time right pretty much you can but I
mean it's just it's like very
ergonomical
ergonomic yeah yes we know we know how
to play we know how to play this game
wait why'd I back out of it let me try
and Skip Skip okay we don't need your
explanation play the game
here we go off to the races
we're gonna play Mind Games mind games
with each other I'm ready well I'm first
okay okay all right so you know the
strats
yes
what if I was just right there though
I just kind of popped over here
very clever okay that's pretty clever oh
really yeah a little clever yeah you get
where I'm going I can kind of see it I
kind of get it but you know
um I just kind of work on this over here
hmm
I do see what you're trying to do
oh no you see nothing I'm I'm playing
like four 4G chess right now are you are
you because there's a final goal that
I'm aiming for that you will never
well you're gonna need to do something
about this
I'm gonna need to do something if you
didn't say anything maybe I wouldn't
have noticed that there was nothing you
were looking you were really really
looking
okay I'm gonna be blind
yeah right yeah I was so blind you're
gonna have to make a move make a move
what are we doing um
[Music]
oh Cali oh Callie hey Callie son of a
[\h__\h]
she knew what she was doing there
that's a perfect Connect Four game right
there because you got to go first
this is this is where all my brain cells
went to connect four oh yeah 40 chests
here one more one more one more Connect
Four Oogie bring it in there
look what you've done I want to rematch
me how does that go she's a skill issue
all right
no you can go ahead and start first yay
let me show you what I'm thinking oh the
corner getting a little frisky oh frisky
I see let me copy you then oh yeah is
that what we're doing what a weird
unhinged game
stay away
hmm
come down here nope
not not in this lifetime
we good
maybe good here
I don't know we good here
what are we gonna do
okay of course we put it over there of
course of course where else where else
would we put it yeah
oh wait oh
yeah
um
yes yes
this is looking like a mess I know it
looks so bad I've had so many Connect
Four games where it ends up a tie
hey that can really happen yeah where
you fill up the whole board nobody gets
to connect four
[Music]
um
um seems fake but I guess oh no with my
sister it happens very often wait
what's [\h__\h]
huh no
instead of one
where I just where I just dropped the
red no wait really wait oh shoot oh [\h__\h]
you
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
I won't
[Music]
oh my God
um
don't think too hard Callie just feel it
maybe I do want to feel it I'm not also
blind maybe I did miss one oh well well
then we both blundered okay oh really
it's getting late
yes
you've been streaming for almost 12
hours it's been a hot minute
uh
no
mistakes were made I'm not going there
not on your list why would you not go
nowhere in your life you wanted to get a
four over there right oh wait let me uh
this is this is starting to feel like uh
depending on who takes who what turn is
what wait yeah no I get you
um just like that
[Music]
it's all blending in
it is
truly is
let's see
that's not Connect Four
[Music]
oh
where's it going no where would it be
going huh no what a [\h__\h] game what a
[\h__\h] dumb game well according to
Mike okay
let's go all right fine you're the
Connect Four Master but when it comes to
air hockey it's your boy I can tell you
yeah it is it is it really is one do you
want to try one more you want to play
air hockey one more time yeah I'm
honestly very very very
pistachioed at myself for own goaling
myself so all right all right y'all play
look you know what yeah let's do it I'm
not gonna get too cocky I'm gonna
because we can make it a point out of
five if if time is is yeah let's do it
yeah let's do five okay quick one just a
quick a quick question no you had to say
it what what does that mean just don't
worry about it okay
you know what you're doing Iris you know
what you're doing right now I seriously
don't like I've heard of that first
before I didn't damn it I know it's
slang
yeah yeah it is okay it's when you do
something real fast
drift oh [\h__\h] drifties I'm sorry drift
can you stop that
you have are you using joy-con like not
procon uh yeah yeah I'm using the the
ones that come with the switch uh yeah
those drift eventually yeah I can still
do it doesn't matter
oh my God
how was part two good I sang a lot no
dang it don't get distracted Mori
yep she's gonna win if you get
distracted you're supposed to
concentrate you're the opponent in front
of you right now
wait hold on
no let's get in there
yeah
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
Drifters come can I
I can still win
I don't know what I wish my
dad
just let me be good at this Iris just
let me be good okay
Cali it's Kelly amazing at air hockey
it's cool already thank you very much
thanks for playing with me that was a
fun time I had a good time as well yeah
I'm glad I was able to brush up on my
Connect Four Godly skills yeah those are
pretty good I will say you know what
yeah that was pretty sick
yes talk to you again soon laters
and there she go
there she go now I have to add somebody
I have to add this next person because I
actually don't
I don't have
I don't have her switch
account
her friend code
I believe
I got it all right so none of you are
allowed to add this person so of course
I can't let you see it
I cannot let you see
because it's a big old Secret
add a friend
search with a friend code
uh 4 20.
nine
three
there we go
the friend request has been sent
that sure it helps if you read it off as
you enter of course it does
makes it more fun makes it more
how do I say
exciting play with friends create a
Lobby
all right we're good
I'll tell her to come in now
okay
yeah
maybe some Japanese for this next part
get ready
okay nihongo okay
JP wakarimasu
foreign
it's not your girl
it is not
in case you're wondering
get ready
get down in the meantime
why don't you click that subscribe
button below
God it hurts it kills me
it kills me there's a new music video
coming out
pretty soon too actually as soon as the
the marathon is over
double this is
[Music]
my name is
foreign
[Music]
awesome bye yeah
yes yes you're like fine you're fine
wonderful me too
[Laughter]
welcome so this is
foreign
[Music]
thank you
um
okay
wait oh
Connect Four part two
became a show
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
three
foreign
[Music]
oh
no what
oh literally
okay
[Music]
bad eyes
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
so this is
okay
guys
[Music]
[Applause]
yeah let's go let's party yeah ready to
party
ready to party let's party okay here we
go
minifons
foreign
[Music]
look at that
um
[Music]
Renegade okay this
is
[Music]
I see I see foreign
um
thank you
not all at all
right
[Music]
yeah
oh I see I see okay
[Laughter]
corner
quarter boys
I thought
ah I see
I see okay
like this
uh like this
oh
um
[Music]
from it if you take hashiko
yeah so she
yeah
side
okay
damn it
here
only diagonal
laughs
okay okay
ah okay
Maybe
like this
okay
give me this
is
okay
this one
Hashi
oh no
corner corner
[Music]
present present Magica
you know
oh
no not in there why
[Music]
hmm
give me this one
up
yeah
give me this one
give me this
[Music]
is
so
[Laughter]
um
wow thank you so much
Choice okay
choice is dots and boxes dots and boxes
oh okay so this suit let's go come on
this one before Oh I don't think so okay
hi
all right
okay let's do it
okay
nice
[Music]
okay I see
thoughts and boxes
foreign
cocoa
okay
[Music]
give me this
okay
no you can't
um
hmm
give me this one
and give me this one
and you know what give me give a meme
[Music]
um
oh no
[Music]
okay we're friends
no no no
this is
of course
switch off
okay
one more time one more chance one more
chance let's do it okay
okay play okay
um
Pokemon
okay
hi
foreign
[Music]
that's right
no Cali Mercury
happy
okay be
e
boy oh
[Music]
foreign
hi
[Music]
look what is it
bye
I know yeah whatever night
[Music]
dangerous
I am
foreign
[Music]
oh
my God
hi
so this is nice
[Music]
so they got
foreign
okay
mom books
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh no
box
give me this one
give me this one let's go this way let's
go this way
no stop non-stopper yeah
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign yeah
it is
[Music]
bye Madison
so cute
we love genius vampire
who's that okay oh I hear your familiar
voice
who that
I'm sorry hello it's it's takanashi
kiwawa from an alternate universe the
takanashi Kiara from an alternate
universe she's here exactly that one how
do you know her crazy I I saw her in
Final Fantasy 16. oh yeah pretty crazy
it does fit into Final Fantasy 16
doesn't it especially the hair piece
straight like a final fantasy like logo
or something like that so I didn't start
playing it yet but I I do think visually
it fits yeah honestly perfect actually
actually perfect
that was so cool it fits you you're so
dressed up and you're just in your
pajama yeah because it's night time of
course I won't be sleeping but you know
oh God I was actually just telling the
story of our spa day with pictures on my
stream noise yeah it was fun yeah let me
tell you Kelly we have a problem huh I
recently deleted all my switch friends
no
so I don't think we're friends anymore
let me quickly send you
awesome I can add you no problem I've
got my sensor bar still here from the
last interesting stream I did yeah I
made sure to say it's the lowest res
jpeg possible okay here we go Okay add
friend don't worry no one you know why I
deleted all my friends why
I was trying to get
um
Uno to work on the switch why would
deleting all your friends help with that
because because for all the participants
which was for participants we didn't
show up for each other as particip
possible participants and we were shown
like others in our friends list but you
couldn't choose the other the ones you
actually wanted so we thought okay if we
delete everybody except us then it
surely will show us in Uno right it
didn't oh it was all for nothing
I sent you a friend request by the way
ah yeah
after three years of working in the same
company finally we will be friends let's
go
I see that you have over 110 hours in
tears of the Kingdom hell yeah I'm
finished though it was so good I wish I
could have spent more time in it ah as I
know it's a really good game
oh how are you doing by the way which
hour is this let's see uh if it's about
okay so we're almost at the 12 hour mark
hmm yeah so still that's still like
halfway from yeah
yeah
not not quite yet we're almost halfway
through though
um technically technically though I
streamed an hour before the start
um so I guess it's kind of like is it
halfway maybe not was it the the Calm
before the storm one yeah well I had
that as a super chat stream the night
before and then I had a membership
stream before the marathon stream are
you okay are you stupid
no why would you add one more hour
before the 24 hour stream and make it 25
hours Pow Wow with my members
this lady oh my god making it even more
difficult for herself
you'll be suffering at 23 hours and
you'll be like I wish I would have done
one less hour and wouldn't have done the
membership maybe maybe I'll try to pull
it together the spicy noodles will wake
me up I'm excited for spicy noodles oh
yeah
good luck with that I'm trying to find
the lobby right now should be in in a
moment okay oh yeah I found you take
your time
oh okay let's party
I pressed confirm ah unable to connect
to the oh wait do I not have no it
should be fine no it's a communication
error
we've been having a couple of those if
it shows me yours then I should have
internet right yeah let me try again
I'll try to put it back into the dock
and play via uh the capture card okay
come on let me in please Nintendo let us
play you've already scarred us enough
for Mario party
what if you make what if you make a
Lobby wonderful I'll try
yeah let me okay create let me
[Music]
I was telling the uh My Views that that
meat we ate at the Teppanyaki was like
now I know it even more seriously it's
my favorite the best the best uh vacuum
I've ever eaten right yeah every time yo
that wagyu just never fails I'll tell
you what no but like this one
specifically out of all the vacuums was
my favorite ever yeah nice marble maybe
it's like a personal choice but it was
so freaking juicy and soft and buttery
ah it melts in your mouth and all that
hell yeah so good delicious what tastes
like you're in yeah I'm in let's go
it's going
yeah
connections
what you want to play you can choose
what have you played so far I played uh
tennis air hockey connect four dots and
boxes and Renegade
mm-hmm so quite a few games but rent
what the [\h__\h] is Renegade yo it's a
weird one I think I won it by accident
it's like you turn on yeah I don't think
I fully understood it while playing
okay
I want to play Blackjack for someone who
knows it always [\h__\h] me over with this
game even better I mean oh well maybe
you'll get lucky this time you know how
to play this right of course I love this
game
okay I wonder if I remember I think um I
think the Yakuza times have put it so
deep in my blood oh yeah they've trained
you
yeah
let's go we gotta get 21 and if it's
over 21 then we're [\h__\h] right correct
okay so Kiara's right there and I'm
right here so let me I'm telling you
already the CPU will win yeah there will
always be a strong CPU and a CPU that
sucks
yeah so that's what is up Kiara's in
control
uh let me see do I wanna more is in
control I'll do 10 I'll do a casual
chill 10 for now uh-huh careful we're
careful I see oh
you don't see what I have do you know
you do I do
that I do but that's your question
let's go Dummies Wait do I stand or do I
hit I'd stand if I were you because hit
I get another car exactly yeah then
definitely uh let me hit hit me hit hit
me
yuck
and Kiara wins let's [\h__\h] go I should
have I should have just stood there the
house busted come on Maui
I really didn't think I was gonna okay
all right it's just the first round it
doesn't matter as long as we kill the
CPUs yeah exactly as long as the CPUs
suffer
we can't let the computers win one day
they'll take over humanity and that's
not good all right here we go
is that like a like a pretty sure it's a
Terminator reference oh you watched
Germany I never was germinated even
though I'm Austrian yeah I was about to
say what
confusion ah this kind of sucks
they've got a king
what's the possibility of them busting
[\h__\h]
right hit me
let's [\h__\h] go stand stand oh
oh you're standing with the CPU hand in
hand
are you kidding me
rigged rigged rigged rigged House Always
Wins House Always Wins it's rigged I'm
gonna lose it we should go to the casino
together we really should be your
favorite thing to play in the casino
the only card game that I understand
yeah I also don't get poker so that
would be a no for me it's 2 30 again
let's get it back
risky riskier maybe a little bit okay
I'm gonna stand for sure
[Music]
I will risk it for the biscuit yeah and
I'm [\h__\h] Buffet very close though uh
let's see how y'all stand on that don't
gamble guys don't gamble not great for
you yeah
please know what yeah I think I would
also like to play roulette in the casino
yeah roulette seems kind of fun seems
simple enough for my pee brain you won
you won because the dealer didn't get
21. yeah
dealers got rules they gotta fall too
why am I fourth now what the [\h__\h]
happened
I'm all in
good luck all in baby
90s Cali you can go negative in this
game yeah
you're crazy huh wait communication
error
players left are you kidding me we were
just getting into it the house just took
our money
and just kicked us out does he make a
new one okay I don't know something's
wrong today on the internet let me check
okay what internet are you using switch
you better be using the right internet
or I'm gonna be mad oh it might be me if
it went well for you with the others uh
did not go well for me with the others
so oh maybe it is hold on let me check
the network oh it's just Nintendo you
know how it is
yeah that is true I am indeed connected
to the right
Network all right well I'll just join
your lobby again we'll do it again we
will make it work
again let's choose a Lobby leave us to
you
just do it again
it's fine I'm in here come in here if
you think about it if you think about it
we just erased our debts you know all
good now
Brittany slate never happened exactly
never happened
I never lost any money in the casino
what do you mean number are you kidding
me why unable to connect to other
consoles
please try again I don't believe that I
believe that's a lie let me try again
hey no start ain't no start Arena start
in a start
a new start and a star Oh I thought
it's an anus star
okay wait hold on I'm playing I clicked
one of my favorite jerks jerks it's a
jerk yeah word play
is it German I love it so much no it's
English
I know it's from
um do you know uh
uh was it Arrested Development yeah yeah
uh wait was it
have you ever watched Arrested
Development no I think we maybe once I'm
pretty sure there's this guy I mean
they're all very interesting people but
there's this guy he's getting himself a
car he wants to start a new start but it
doesn't fit on his car plate license
plate a new start so he shortens it and
makes it into anal starts and
releases a song called and you start
right oh Jesus
[Music]
she didn't know
I keep on making fun of her with that
well now I'm gonna remember that forever
every time I hear that song
Someone edited the logo too
oh yeah yeah
okay
um let's not go back to the thing yeah
we got some time to only 15 minutes
we're gonna play Ludo okay yeah it's
sorry
hell yeah yeah that's sorry or trouble
or whatever it is
you know in German it's called The Game
title is called dudes don't be don't be
so angry oh really in German
it's kind of based very self-aware I dig
it
back over here we like to play it in
families oh yeah the family game you
play this with with uh Mama Tori
yeah no actually actually not much Mama
oh somebody said uh
uh sorry is a bit different apparently
really
we'll see so you you start at one piece
you want to get all of your pieces into
your into your holes oh into oh
the ones that are in your color
yeah we have to play with CPU ew yucky
for sure
uh but I think wait how was this like
actually it's been a while I think you
can like
ah once you Pat no once when you land on
someone's field maybe then you kick them
back into the starting position oh I see
that was this thing yeah gotcha
[\h__\h] my dad yeah yeah that's it
that's it so it's a lucky game
yeah you can choose which pieces you
move okay yeah
I get it Savage just be Savage okay
sounds good I can do that
animal this would also be a game that I
should buy in real life and then play in
hand came off collapse this is my new
thing you know sometimes came off
collabs I bring these kind of like board
games uh ideally like non-copyrighted
ones or like off-brand ones
understandable help me with myself
my
my oh what
the CPR the shitty
I know they suck they really are the
worst yeah what if I am hold on can I
not move one of these
game doesn't want to please move a piece
it's not letting me move one of these
pieces so
I guess I can't I guess you have to move
that one first
got it one
so lamb
of course it's just RNG
slowly moving slowly but surely all
right give me have you been like eating
any snacks while you're doing these yeah
protein bars energy packs you know oh
yeah that's that's all you'll be eating
in 24 hours sweat you know
foreign
yeah I like it I should treat myself
though after this stream is over get
something yum yum yeah you should what
are you thinking of oh you can roll
again but if you get six then you can
move one of yours out
okay I'm gonna get that blue guy
um yeah I don't know what I want though
maybe like a nice pasta
oh a nice posture he kicked the the
green one kicked the yellow one out and
this is the first in the road that I
rolled one
first time in a row oh yeah
uh-huh what a shame don't worry I won't
try and hurt you
yes don't roll don't roll it too
I'll be mad at you if you're old too
not just four one two three four ah I
bounced off of your head though
cocoon
okay
move away
yeah he's in control five let's go nice
finally moving but I still only have one
piece out there
one piece
I get it and I like Kiara so I'm not
gonna I'm not gonna jump on her head
you know when I was uh with Kelly uh out
the whole day on our spa day like at
least 10 people
when I noticed when I'm around from you
like everybody will talk to you about
your phone case like oh One Piece One
Piece
like three different people
at the restaurant too especially at the
restaurant they're like oh one piece and
then like the massage therapist was like
one piece like dang a lot of Japanese
people know one piece and the dessert
guy he was like really really like
interested he wanted to talk so much
yeah he wanted to talk about one piece
yeah like oh did you watch the movie How
many times did you watch the movie where
did you watch the movies like three
times
the new movies the whole time sitting
there having no idea about one piece
yeah it was kind of crazy it's always
it's the phone case and you know what
that's happened outside of just us like
hanging out as well
um like that's happened when I go
outside
if they talk to you so often in that
just one day I cannot imagine how many
times people talk to you about your
phone on the regular day basis if I go
outside a lot
oh my God a lot I think everyone in
Japan knows what
ever because aren't you getting annoyed
about it at this point no I think it's
cute okay I think this conversation
starting I'd say so
um if you don't know anything about one
piece
that's fine we have plenty of other
things to talk about anyway yes yes is
so true damn I've never noticed
something that creates such a reaction
as much as one piece I know right
it's like uncanny I know yeah really
weird nothing else will get so many
interested Japanese people I wonder
about it I don't wonder why because I
like it a lot but
it's like a national treasure for them I
guess I know right somebody in my chat
said one time Oda is The Treasure of
Japan
's pride and joy I was like that's kind
of cute
who is that Oda is the author of One
Piece okay
an eight-year-old
yeah he's he's the guy he's the dude
that that wrote one piece that writes
one it's not over
no
garbage
evil evil CPU I was about to say NPC I
need to escape from you please don't
jump on me
okay
thank God don't worry you're safe I
won't hurt you wait you're not drinking
energy drinks right yeah yeah I am
if you are okay if it's just today if
it's just today just for today yeah and
only when I'm tired so okay
yeah somebody gave me some tips from
their World of Warcraft days they said
here are the things that you need
they're like I played World of Warcraft
once for three days in a row they'd go
on like binges and they're like here's
what you need in order to survive you
need painkillers uh and then like these
other things ChapStick for your eyeballs
and [\h__\h] like that [\h__\h]
for none of your eyes start to burn they
said
yeah I'm well hydrated though don't
worry I got the straps
[Music]
don't use it on your eyeball I'll think
about it
I'll think about it damn
hcp I used to play like MMORPGs
overnight like for the whole night but I
I don't think I really had anything
so crazy like special
oh yeah like a strategy to survive it's
just like Cali
yours
I currently only have one it's cool
Canada I'm just unlucky don't worry
about it it's fun I know you didn't do
it on purpose
we're cool it's all cool
yeah some wizard tips so you liked World
of Warcraft didn't you I used that was
the first MMORPG I ever played and it
was because my family was all getting
into it so we played it as a family and
I was like I don't know maybe I was like
12 or so or 11. that's so cute
yeah I was too young honestly to play
World of Warcraft ah too young but you
did it anyway it was fun yeah I really
liked it and that kind of sent me down
the spiral of MMORPG addiction why
God yeah these guys are evil
what
what only be able to move the one that's
already in for now I think so oh my God
so you can get another one in there
that's rough buddy
wow
that is rough that's just rude yeah I
need a six I pass I I passed oh no
really that's a tough one wow
one or six
wow come on what a waste of time got
this
cheering for you six six yeah one okay
hey that's so good one is still good
right
that is still good the green is gonna
win no cap I hate that [\h__\h] greens
man oh I got someone else nice
oh me
oh cool
I'll take that let's freaking Go destroy
Grace
nice get them I wish I could hit that
yellow oh well all right the game is
telling me dude don't be so angry in
German how do you say it in German
y yeah
it was like baby speak
able babies
oh I got a number six but I can nice
only move this one
like on the starting spot oh my God
close takanashi you're cutting it close
again
I'm glad that wasn't a one or a four
yeah that that just passing by yeah
let's go oh you're in you're in your
first one yeah
hey let's go
uh I think if you're like close to your
goal and you like roll something that
like overshoots it like a six for
example then I don't think you can
actually get in yeah we do another round
yeah
that's also kind of that was so so bad
that's the worst thing I've ever heard
um
brutal game
but moving on nicely now let's go
we got five get in there okay piece
number two is there someone after me oh
yeah right there's some someone after me
yup I mean after this yeah oh good oh
yeah I can cut into drawing a bit yeah
nice
oh yeah
um I shall move the one that's further
okay I love it when it's us against the
NPCs
three letter words for non
non-consciousness having beings entities
it's easy to confuse okay I know that
doesn't make a lot of sense but they're
similar and they both have three letters
yeah wait it's not an NPC it's CPU oh
yeah confused Arena
there we go Blue
my turn
this one please
one oh why did you choose that one
because I wanted to get to the front
interesting chores
oh oh scary Hold On
move away lady wait a minute hold on
let's go yeah past losers let's go yeah
oh
maybe it's fun
playing from Beyond the I was about to
say beyond the grave but it's not dead
it's just playing from the Beyond I
guess
so nice
pretty close please please do not kick
anyone away oh I can get in yeah
[Music]
cool oh thank God okay yeah
okay okay
I'm not here to back seat you but your
guy is blocking the exit
for your for your last guy
I was just trying to get uh that one in
as fast as possible understandable how
about now we didn't nowhere now we're
gonna move on all right oh yeah I'm
gonna be head to head
I think green is gonna he got in that
bastard got in a piece of garbage
let's hope they never roll a six they
know you will be fine yeah
maybe maybe okay let's go
oh
yeah I'm such a nice person
I'm such a nice person
it shows you're no we're not on YouTube
[Music]
LOL you're in my way
thank you you better be grateful for
this day takanashi I am grateful be
grave
get her no chat no you'd understand
I'm so grateful I'm going to buy you a
bag of grapes next time grapes grateful
I get it little plant words you did
there
so good we've played wood places wow you
think English is your first language
it could be gold
we're making moves
did you see my new outfit animation yeah
I watched it that's the same person that
did that one fan animation that was
really cool
so sick yes so swaggy that was awesome I
love it's kind of like a weird thing to
pick out that I loved but I loved how
they used like 3D models and made them
look like like 3D that was cool I was
like whoa I mean I know it's 3D but like
that fits so well it's cool
efficiency yeah and then I love the
music that was with it too yeah yeah
actually I was like first I was thinking
of like voicing it and doing sound
effects and stuff but I also kind of
wanted background music so I was like
I don't know who to ask but I have this
one one fan who makes like Orchestra
stuff and all that I thought oh well
actually it might be perfect so nice he
created it according to the video
fittingly yeah that worked out perfect
yeah so I just gave up on voicing it
because I was like oh this is all really
nice I think it turned out fantastic
just the way it is hmm thank you love it
very I'm still thinking we should all
get together and voice the bad misbed
ending I want to
I want to do it wouldn't that be so cool
it would be let's do some voice acting
you know oh you know what that's one
thing one thing we could uh try to do
for anniversary oh nice idea
let's do that I like that it's sick I'll
bring it up I'll bring it up with Mazu
as well if it's okay yeah oh hell yeah
that would be fun spoilers no spoilers
what do you mean green green snorkeling
to get his last Soldier out how to
turntables
the day on stream I had a Miss speaking
moment I have so many of these recently
instead of oh how did
how the turntables the tables turn yeah
what I said was how the
how the turbo stained
turbo stain sounds like a different
language
[Laughter]
that's some Elite English right there I
tell you what couldn't even make that up
to me it still sounds like England
I mean yeah actually I get what you mean
to me it sounds oh no
but a piece of garbage now yellow is on
a war path
wow take him down I'll do my best but
you know they're slippery
or slippery give me one damn it no
that's so scary what if they get one
I'm so scared right now
are you kidding me he got the last one
out
oh God this is so scary
the last guy is there one in oh my God
no
[Music]
you can knock them out it'd be fine
[\h__\h] game it's a [\h__\h] game
this game is uh anxiety inducing so say
the least
it's going for you let's go I'm going to
get him hit him send them home
send them home
can we still turn this around yeah we
can we can turbo we can turbotain it
yeah I know we can
we can turbo tame it
all right let's go or
turbotain train no your piece of garbage
did he kick you back yeah the green one
did you know it's so rude so rigged
freaking bastard disgusting
disgusting
all of the turbo stain oh my God so
disgusting get him out
okay
I will yes send them home can I wait can
I piece of glass yeah yeah let's
freaking go
yes absolutely goated oh man
it's not over yet it's not over the good
thing is even if green is like red in
front of his goal he will have to roll a
one for example or a two like the
extract number oh my God it really be
like that that's crazy
hmm that seems like it'll take a long
time that's fine yeah it could
potentially that's fine well I guess
I'll just pass again
let's just pass again
[Music]
okay now that I'm past the greens goal
I'm less than dangerous I'm gonna catch
up with my last one nice idea
give me six yeah get him get him get
that piece of [\h__\h] yeah
let's go
sorry sorry oh my God I didn't mean to
throw you back
yeah you have one back in the home I'm
sorry oh oh I'm I'm wait I thought you
said why'd he get it
I thought you sent green back I did
what happened but then the green took
you out wait what I'm so confused how
did he says he immediately get a six he
got a six right yeah he got a six right
after yeah
disgusting disgusting CPU awesome cool I
can't
wow gross I hate that
the CPU is like nah CPU always wins
idiots
[Music]
come on
let's go
as long as we got each other I guess
that is true
that is true the house will always wins
yellow was on my spot but unfortunately
I didn't get a six ah God damn
keep it moving keep it moving mm-hmm
just going around the board until
somebody wins if we can kick green again
then yeah that would be amazing yellow
yellow is dangerous too yeah they're
both dangerous
gotta get him
keep them going around the board ah [\h__\h]
just uh just a one I saw
let's go
let's move
I believe
yeah
she's speeding officers come here come
here
God that is scary get him smack them
dinner is that a winner winner chicken
dinner Maury calliope
yay the CPU lost
let me continue playing
that kind of sucks they only care about
who gets who takes first I'm sorry
yay I guess yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah thanks koala that was fun indeed I
think it's already time for me to leave
right it is but I'll miss you
bye
[Music]
bye there she go
there
she goes there she goes again There She
Goes Again
Wawa
kiwawa kiwawa kiwawa
Chihuahua Chihuahua kiwawa
let's go
that was fun it was a good time
but we're not done yet
[Music]
but we're not done not yet
not yet we still have a little more to
go
still have a bit more
play with friends
and I'll wait for my next and last
friend for this block to come in
create a Lobby
I hope that Mata nihongo is okay
smiley face
no only English
shut up
yeah
yeah yeah
hello hello hello
my name is
foreign
you know
[Music]
Wing
um
foreign
[Music]
Duncan
all right
honey open
no
I use
okay yeah select game yes
[Music]
[Laughter]
a Japanese easy game okay
[Music]
yeah let's see
foreign
okay
[Music]
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no yeah
I'm here
[Music]
we can't you can't do that
[Laughter]
[Music]
RTA okay
okay let's play
Let's Play Come On
okay okay
[Music]
I want this one
yeah okay oh
okay
yep
[Music]
no no no
no yeah
[Music]
hi
I'm playing gomoku
[Laughter]
honey
uh you suck at games
yeah yeah
you suck suck
foreign
[Laughter]
guys
okay
okay okay
no no no no
no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no
it's me
[Music]
okay
nope
um
[Music]
oh
come on
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh you did it uh you can do it you did
it you did it yeah you did it you can do
it yeah
I can do it hey thank you thank you
senpai
[Music]
I want to play
um
air hockey air hockey
yeah
I like air hockey
yeah you like this
10 points
let's party no no no no no no no no no
no
don't tell me I'll touch you
yep no I'm here I'm here
one point okay one point yeah one point
okay
yeah
two points give me two no but
laughs
[Music]
three two three two let's go let's go
let's go
[Music]
yeah
yeah let's party
yeah let's party simple
[Music]
uh yes I'm welcome
and welcome here yeah no welcome here
yes that's right
[Laughter]
let's party
foreign
[Music]
yeah I'm a winner King Miko Senpai air
hockey winner King it's me yeah
okay what do you want to play
[Music]
mmm
boxing boxing oh
okay
yes nice choice thank you thank you
you're welcome now let's go okay okay
party
oh
no no no no no no
oh no
no no
no no no no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no no
what's this
okay okay I'll stop
one more one more okay yeah okay let's
try one more please okay no problem
let's go at least Punch Yeah
please give me Elite punch Elite punch
yeah let's go please show me
yeah Elite punch
okay please show me I want to see
three times
[Music]
babies
last game okay
[Music]
okay let's play
tennis
[Music]
yeah let's play tennis yeah
I like this game
it's so easy easy easy let's play yeah
two game match thank you thank you yeah
okay
foreign
no
come on here
One Piece One Piece
no no
okay okay
yes okay
okay
no sorry it's okay
[Laughter]
oh yeah
oh no
[Music]
oh God I don't know
[Laughter]
so this is soccer
foreign
hold on
go here
okay
come come here no
I'm close
come here
this way this way this way
this way
no no thank you
blue team let's go
come on
no blue team let's go let's party
party time no no no no gold
not even got tonight
no thank you
again please
[Laughter]
no
nope
no oh wrong way
oh
my God
you have to move
nope
let's go let's let's go let's move yup
no let's move
no guard for you nope
additional
stuff let me score yeah come on
wow I hate soccer
thank you you're welcome
you're welcome
wow
please give it a game
hello
yes you're funny yeah thank you I like
you yeah Mika's funny I like you
[Music]
yeah I like you
yeah thank you you're welcome see you
bye bye arigato
[Music]
senpai
look at school Papa
Mike peeking the mic clipping was so
good
all right let's play again Sunday
I really want to play again someday
well looks like that's it for Clubhouse
you guys
um let me hop out of here because I
gotta go prepare right for drawing
uh we're gonna draw now
um I'm gonna take a teeny tiny little
break little chill Break
um let's go hang out in the room let's
go hang out in my room guys
why is it daytime it should be night
time
um it should be night time
but it's not
let me let me move to the night room
hold on night time
basically the same advice corner has a
ton of questions so I think oh wow that
got really big
um okay
announcements let's calm down a little
bit there
oh my tummy is growling I think it's
time for some energy
I'm crying in my room
so obsessed with vitamins hmm
ah I have a lot of Discord messages
which makes me nervous
I hate that it's snack time
snack and chill time hour 12. coming up
on that halfway mark just one more hour
to go yeah if you want to be technical
about it I suppose that is true
let's see what do we got here
oh players left Maybe
there we go
things to look at for later
I guess
[Music]
okay
all right we're fine
all things I can look at later that's
good news 11 hours
I can't believe it wow I mean well
I've done a 12 hour stream before but I
don't know it's
24 hours is a long time you know
it's a long time
hey
here let me put my
switch away
because we're done with the switch
I'm not quite sleepy though I was a bit
sleepy before when I was playing
Clubhouse but uh playing with me Miko
Senpai woke me right up
oh
because
big voice
so cute big voice
she's funny she could wake the Dead
oh that was funny
that was funny
enter as a painter into the magical
drawing room
cool all right should be fine
three hours of drawing am I gonna be
okay
we might have to do some pretty
simplistic drawings here and there I
think
yeah
that's okay though simplistics hey
simple is good okay simple is good
you know
thank you
laughing laughing till I'm crying emoji
foreign okay
I'm gonna collab someday
so what's next well if you take a look
at the schedule which is not in this
dark room
if you take a look at the schedule
though we have drawing it's drawing time
we're gonna draw for a while
um
I believe that's
it
yeah so we've got drawing
this stream in and of itself is actually
not too long this one is going to be two
six hours ish yeah part four is the real
long one I think
the last long stretch so basically the
way that this next section works is
um we draw each other right so I will
draw you but you gotta draw me that's
the that's the payment
right
um
yep the price of a Mori drawing of you
is you gotta draw me
let me get my references pulled up
because I'm gonna need references of
everybody
that I'm drawing gotta pay the Mori toll
indeed
all right I guess we ought to enter
pretty soon gotta tap out no worries
thanks for hanging around as long as you
did
now let me set up this other room and
make sure that nothing you buy is
happening because we hate that
I guess I gotta turn off the switch if I
don't turn off the switch then the music
continues to play and it's not that I
hate the clubhouse music but
gotta go
so for background music
for background music
we're doing the whole alive mix
okay here we go
live Lo-Fi can't go wrong with it
am I right
Loop
good stuff
okay now let me see as for the next
screen
little window capture ooh scandalous
should be fine
window capture
and then
just do a brand new one window capture
two we'll call it
then we've got the room drawing room
I will go ahead and
top part out
no no no
[Music]
um
okay
whose window you peeking through Secret
I'm no stalker
excuse you
and then let's see ooh who's gonna be
first to join I see some people waiting
and I have not saved
I have not saved their images
you know this this stuff it takes a lot
of prep
it really does more so than I thought
but that's okay
it's fun save image
save here
gotta get everybody's pictures and
whatnot there's a lot to do
[Music]
okay I think I'm ready to go I'll go
ahead and hop into the call then
it's drawing Tatsu time
[Music]
we're in there oh I should jump in then
okay here I go
[Music]
for totsu
h
we shall wait they're in the waiting
room so
I'm here
at Renee
oh there there you are hello hello red
is here hi
hi welcome thank you so much for coming
to draw with me today
um
together oh sure together is fun I don't
mind if you guys want to draw together
with me
tell her to get in here hold on a second
because I have I have her PNG
all right there she is oh my god oh
Jesus jump scare
oh God what a jump scare I love it
though
look she's so big on the screen
hey everyone big old jump scare Ollie's
here
yay it's the two of us yeah two of us
are in here together
cool let me drag this down just a bit
nothing I'm not lowering anything it's
all good
everything's fine
it's everything else but yeah it's
perfect
it's uh the stream's been going good
thank you for asking it's uh I'm I'm not
feeling it yet but I'm pretty sure I'm
going to at the end of this so there's
that but it'll be worth it it'll be
worth it I know it
yeah we're doing drawings today of each
other
so I'm gonna draw you guys if you guys
draw me yes of course I would love to
draw you yeah Okay cool so awesome oh
sorry sorry no you're good go first
introduce yourselves oh my God I'm such
a dummy introduce yourselves well I'm
avalia Rainey from home ID generation 2
together with crazy Ally also from
Hawaii generation two
[Music]
let's go
BT dubs is are you guys using headphones
yeah
yeah but also let me tweak some settings
yeah cause apparently the sound is
leaking out from somewhere oh I think
it's me just a moment okay no worries
are you good how's now
uh I'll check one too all good oh nice
nice okay no problems all right I think
I'll go ahead and take the top part and
then you guys can have the bottom part
you wanna top us both or at the same
time you hush your mouth right now or
I'm gonna I'm gonna slap it off of you
I'm going to slap your mouth off of you
ollie I will do it you know my favorite
outfit of yours is the um the one that's
like that you wore in your concert the
one with like the um you know the
Snapback you know the yeah yeah
thank you so much I'm glad you like that
one I like that one too that if you
don't mind yeah sure go for it sounds
good I don't know do it do it is
oh my goodness I am lost do what you
gotta do like I'm [\h__\h] um I'm
borrowing a pen tablet oh no it's not
like my normal chocolate it's like I
just don't know how to use this oh I
think I know never mind
all good it's all good
um because we're growling
is like um
oh shoot
um wait I'm gonna erase Ali Ali Ali
where do you want to draw oh oh where do
you want to draw I don't know we can
split like maybe we can make a soft line
here we can erase it
yeah we can make like a self-sessed more
e Calliope oh wait what oh what does
that even mean I see what does that mean
leave it too rainy oh my God yeah
there's two of us so there's gonna be
two drawings and it's like
okay nice let's go
let's go I can't draw from like I can
draw characters facing the right left I
don't know oh yeah
oh okay oh my God is that thing that's
difficult for right-handed people people
usually like you know it's easier for
them yeah three quarters view is the
easiest I feel oh hell yeah yeah
three-quarter view nice
it's all right a try is all you need
because to be honest uh the whole idea
is that even if you only draw a stick
figure it's fine so true yeah what if I
draw you making the sheesh face
[Music]
oh my God I mean look it's all up to you
the world is zeroaster I'm like uh I'm
challenging myself today drawing with
this um
angle with uh or if you want to switch
tassels okay gonna try new things
um do you see like my tablet like making
like this random straight line I do I do
see I don't I don't know how to style
that I'm gonna I'm gonna delete oh my
God you could always just you know erase
it later yeah we could we could it's
just fine
yeah
this is fine I really oh my God okay I
don't know what's happening though right
strange are you using like a like an
iPad tablet or
um no it's like a like a Wacom tablet I
borrowed it from the studio
nice they gave it so it's like yeah
oh yeah I have no idea why this is
happening hey you know what it's a
fashion Choice it's uh yeah yeah it's
just it's a drawing guide that's all
that it is it's a drawing guide I know I
know or like little Picasso with it yeah
exactly let's go through no problem
looks great I think
looks fantastic so many ribbons on Ollie
or you know if you're if you don't want
to draw the ribbons you can always draw
me with
um really big breasts nope I'm good
actually I think I'll go ahead and uh
not do that
thanks for the suggestion yep I'm sure
I'm 100 sure
maybe next time Ollie maybe next time
next time you'll get them next time kid
you'll get them next time but the chat
Goes Wild
and the chat goes wild as expected
Sasuke
okay I need to erase this because it's
bothering me but also it's like how do I
stop it if the cat's going wild then
does that mean they're throwing
red Super Chat don't do it don't listen
to I'm about to go turn them off I'm
gonna go turn them off right now no
playing these games with me Ollie I'll
get you
he already did a true I did but I'll
really finish the job
really gonna finish the job
just so you know
cease
[\h__\h] God oh my God I see the lip biting
oh my God excuse me whoa hold on what
are we drawing
oh my God wait baby actually you know
what I'm gonna draw the same thing what
oh yeah
when did we decide that we were gonna
start drawing Callie ludes
maybe you said we could draw anything I
did while you're complaining now
oh my [\h__\h] God are you taking back
your words is that it are you so
cowardly that you're thinking back yes
oh my God yes I am I'm regretting my
decisions how about that
how about that boing boing Ollie please
uh maybe in another drawing stream
oh we had fun yeah yeah
we did yeah we did yep and also you
expanded your um you know karaoke song
Library you know so yeah next time
yeah I really did want to sing that song
just didn't have enough time to learn it
but uh good song
what is it
it's a very hype song you guys should
always like Sing It In karaoke yeah cool
I want to hear it at the club
[Music]
yeah I want to hear it at the club like
it's just
[Music]
boys
yeah
yeah that's what I want to hear oh yeah
yeah Ollie do you have ears
can't hear you because I don't think I
have it oh my god did they just fall off
I wonder because I don't see them on
your on your reference picture I do have
ears and under right ear I have like a
a tab oh my God it's like an opening can
tab oh
oh I see
hmm
struggling with this you're doing great
no like these random straight lines I
don't know how to turn them off very
Fushigi indeed but don't worry about it
I think it adds to the experience it's
abstract it's so true yeah I guess a
nice abstract one yeah how do I draw
um lip biting and
way I've never drawn lip biting Emoji
so this will be my first it's a good one
it's a classic yeah
classic
I feel like I need to make all it look
Wilder
oh
oh wild crazy wild and crazy crazy Ollie
mm-hmm yeah
[Music]
it'll never lose my mind though
oh you gotta learn the uh blinds as well
yeah
of course oh oh and uh the other one the
other one remember the the Baku new song
yeah there's another one the one that
you opened with Ollie that was the first
song you said
they wanna like I put like just the
three of us we can make like a cover of
it oh my God if it'll make you happy
yeah it'll make you smile Ollie
a trio cover anything to make you smile
best married
please say yes okay
oh send me the data
send me the data and I'll think about it
all right how about that
how about that then that's a deal let's
go immediately gonna work on the lyrics
distribution right after this yeah can
you imagine oh lordy
oh lordy
we need someone to draw the uh lose uh
no illustration use me illustrations for
the song yeah I guess so yeah of course
of course I see what you're gonna do
with you oh my god break this tablet
okay it's fine
oh my gosh
cute Ollie yay so cute how are you
Ollie Ollie is cute
Ollie is cute in the first place
Ollie is cute
drawing was it like you to Disney that's
right
that's correct I love to sex change so
true yeah girl I'm just cleaning up the
nozzle noise
nozzo no lines
I'm doing it right now let's go
why is the Eraser so small
it's literally the worst I was erasing I
was erasing and then the Eraser went
haywire and deleted the correct stuff no
oh my God you know what it's okay looks
good to me
thank you yeah appreciate it I think I'm
actually just gonna clean up the sketch
for this and that'll be good
clean up the sketch this is like really
scared of like um
missing it up the more Strokes I make
the higher chance it'll be like you know
but I getcha it's okay it's normal to be
nervous you'll be fine I'm sure of it
yeah
what's that it's just a chill just a fun
chill little cheeky drawing nothing to
worry too much about yeah just enjoying
ourselves and vibing just vibing what if
the people after this all want to draw
lip biting Cali I'll be mad
oh my gosh no no be yourself be yourself
Ollie you should be yourself
draw what you want to draw don't let me
just discourage you
tongue out then oh Jesus
awesome looking forward to it yeah
nice
[Music]
I'm listening to the ID theme song now
it just came on almost as if you guys
summoned it
[Music]
Ollie
yeah cute and then can't forget the fact
she's a zombie so obviously oh my God
the boing boing yeah
are you kidding me
bruh your sword is covering it up
perfectly on the stream
that means you can draw anything behind
it stop you stop that right now
I'll make you like do a blush oh my god
let's go oh my lordy oh lordy
[Music]
well since it's summer we'll make you a
little bit sweaty oh she's sweaty yeah
that's the reason why because it's
summer
of course
what other reason would there be what
other reason would there be
besides it being summer of course it's
summer
got my head on backwards and it's time
to [\h__\h] party
I do have my hat on backwards there
yeah perfect for summer
like the The Hand Emoji thing
oh my God not the head
[Music]
what the hell this is the most important
part what do you mean with this I mean
okay
yes but also what the hell
what is going on here
we're weren't we're celebrating and
having fun all right what are we
celebrating what are some things to
celebrate as of recently
um
the karaoke yeah no I was gonna I was
gonna say you guys is
forget
hey we just literally had rehearsal oh
my gosh oh
you guys you haven't done your collab
yet right
no okay it's gonna be on the 29th
I want to watch yay please do yeah I'm
going to I'm gonna do it here for the
ponytail the ponytail is actually this
way all right gotta be accurate
yeah that'll be accurate I'm so mad I'm
so mad with these straight lines no they
look beautiful oh thank you it's your
signature style now oh yes definitely
creating beautiful abstract pieces of
art yeah actually this the straight
lines look looking good yeah a beautiful
art piece
[Music]
it's not too late for wait no just
kidding you guys are in Japan never mind
I was about to be like it's not too late
for you guys for oh
you're here never mind we're here never
mind
slipped my mind for a moment
again
[Music]
so very good hold on yeah oh my God okay
looks nice
yeah
it's perfect for you
I'm gonna do a teacup drinking tea
holding teacup yeah yeah yeah as per the
usual is expected of you to hold a
teacup
yes thank you yeah very in character T
of course yeah nothing nothing weird
oh there's nothing weird that was just
like checking you know
you're out of here don't try you don't
trust me
curiosity okay gotcha I see
it
to give you like clothes or do you just
yes I want you to give me clothes Ollie
crazy Ollie I would like you to give me
clothes Ollie I drew the clothes already
don't you think that's too much clothes
in one drawing no oh my God you're right
because it's summer it'll be too hard
you too
I can see that
I can see that very clearly now
the sword works really well too God dang
oh my God yeah yeah
it's a perfect sensor bar
I love it I already got the first part
taken down the first part of the
the stream got taken down due to some
weird copyright issues that were not my
phone oh no yeah yeah with the karaoke
apparently apparently
um the songs that are okay to sing are
actually not okay to sing some of them
it'll get your stream blocked yeah
whoopsies indeed so so here we are now
um in this situation it is what it is
but if you get this dream band as well
and it looks like I never did a 24-hour
stream at all I'm gonna lose my [\h__\h]
mind
[Music]
[Laughter]
if you go a little lower and like put
like the clothing line like right at
where your sword is
you know they won't be you you you know
big thinking brainy
well see she's wearing clothes Riley and
you can see it on this canvas of course
they're very very very very low uh I
think I think it's nice
yeah wonderful it's great wonderful I
really like this outfit of yours as well
your twin Tails I love it yeah thanks I
really like twin Tails me too right
they're so cute everybody looks good in
Twin Tails I feel
so yeah everybody does
everybody we need fan art of everybody
in Twin Tales yeah gosh when is twin
tail day again you know how Japan has
all these like party uh days you know
there's a twin tail day yeah it is I
don't remember when I totally forget
which is a shame I want to remember
I wonder if it fits
oh
never mind I only remember like blocky
day only because it's like 11 and 11.
well yeah that's the easiest right
and then cats day like to February 22nd
yeah yeah
um cute yeah yeah I get it I get it now
yes there's like a
take your bra off day like it's like the
8th of August
take your bra off day yeah because if
you lay down the eights it'll look like
bras and boobs is that something you
just came up with yeah
wow
yeah I mean no no no no no 8th of August
is like Infinity booba because like the
number eight kind of look at the
infinity symbol oh my God
Uber's everywhere wow forever and ever
okay I respect it I do
thank you very much for respecting it
God
Renee I love this pendant that you have
on your default outfit oh thank you yeah
I love it you should sell it as merch
I'd buy it oh nice oh my God yeah yeah I
just think that's a good idea yes
it's kind of like you know not
translucent reflective I don't know it
just looks like um rock candy rock candy
yum yum yum yum I don't know I think I'm
just hungry I'm gonna eat your pendant
now
um
excelento oh nice
yeah I think it's like kind of done with
my wait I don't know should I color it I
don't know are you up to you
because I'm still kind of working I'm
almost done here I'm not gonna color I'm
just gonna do these basic like kind of
sketchy
sketchy ones so
I feel like I'm getting a little more
detailed the thread is than like I
thought I would but
Bellini's actually very nice model is
very very
it is
the deets
[Music]
Sparks is playing sorry oh
yeah stream Sparks do it or I'll find
where you live
YouTube
this box let the flame
[Music]
oh yeah we gotta draw tummy you have
your tummy out
tummy tummy
tummy time
oh my God what a lovely figure
I'm gonna color your hair I think this
little time sure whatever you want to do
okay
yeah
whatever you want to do
my first ever drawing of whatever this
is nice
nice wow you guys are artists too
cool
technically like an art collab yeah oh
my God you're right
I mean technically yeah
technically and actually
England actually so true yeah I need to
decide on the skin color
[Music]
go just leave a wipe but up to you I
guess just like a I just wanted to like
shade it a little bit
hmm okay maybe you have beautiful ruby
red eyes oh yeah I kind of they're all
right
beautiful they're okay
sheesh
[Music]
[Laughter]
what is that hand motion even mean
does anybody actually know
oh gang signs just don't know what it
even means
[Music]
it means sheesh
um
I'm not gonna say anything good job
never mind never mind oh checking your
pulse
inject into my veins
you got ice in your vans
okay
ice in my veins okay
is it raining pretty flat there no no
you just can't see
her arms are covering her chest
yeah
yeah that's all but believe believe me
they are they are abundant back there
you just can't see
believe in the going that believes in
you yeah
but it's there look if you want if you
want buba you got some all right so
Ollie made sure of that so
yeah I even included the line
yeah
yeah you sure did
you know be gentle with the with the
tablet you don't want to break it right
raining so true yeah
oh God what am I even looking at
cute
I think it's um yeah nice okay
put some shine in you guys eyes I think
I think this looks okay I think this
looks good
nice
yada
I would enlarge this if I could but I
can't
should I color I think I should call it
the Emoji yellow yeah so it's like like
the actual emoji
oh he's cooking something for real there
we go
damn let's go now we need Kalia Pizza
voice this sheesh yeah oh wait no you
mean that okay
um maybe someday
amazing
I'm embarrassed I am an embarrassed
person
you don't need to be embarrassed
but be gentle okay
yes gentle okay but be gentle
but
be gentle okay
there does that work
that works we'll take it thank you so
much swag no problem yay
everybody's looking good I drew much
smaller than I thought I would initially
but that's okay
I really like your lines there's like me
oh thanks yeah
oh thanks
thank you like the like the squirrels
are like you you know thank you I'm glad
that you like it big UPS I'll have to
take a screenshot no oh [\h__\h] I'm getting
sleepy hold on
do you want me to help you no no I'm
good but you know what yeah help me
what do we do
Oh I thought you were just gonna like
peek the mic or something what do you
want me to do that no you don't have to
hmm
just tell me to wake up in a loud voice
loud voice
oh Lord oh wake up
if you don't wake up now
it's a bad dream oh my God it's a bad
dream
you know like where you're like hanging
out with your friends and then like say
you're like your parents like call and
suddenly your friends like oh my God
like why are you taking off your fans oh
yeah it's the moaning sounds yeah yeah
like the mode sounds like oh my God like
don't drink the alcohol
bro pass me the
or whatever oh my God
yeah oh yeah I'm aware mm-hmm
yeah but are you awake now are you awake
enough now okay oh maybe that's great
it's probably fun do you want me to do
it again no I'm good
okay that's funny that was fast it's fun
too you got some art skills both of you
guys
damn I just enjoy drawing you very much
oh she's just being humble she's really
good at drawing no I think everybody in
this room is great at drawing
yeah lots of talented drawers in whole
life
talented drawers drawers but actually
yeah like a lot of people in whole life
they're like you know even though like
not everybody does a lot of drawing
streams a lot of people are actually
pretty good at drawing right
yeah that is so true
there's a lot of drawers in her life you
think there's a lot of closets but um
drawers
I see controllers
[Music]
it's kind of like that the Cali on the
right is talking to the Cali on the left
and like oh the be gentle okay and then
let's just like
[Laughter]
[Music]
it's um it's like a story you know it's
not it's not like two separate pictures
like I said we're drawing Celsius
that's okay right yeah
love yourself oh no yeah self love or
something love yourself something like
that yeah
see it's kind of like if you wanna you
know love others you have to love
yourself first true we're just like
putting putting this in the form of like
illustration you know yeah
perfect how long are we drawing by the
way
um I mean just until we're basically
done but I feel like I should probably
oh can I move this hold on move move the
specified area to another location
okay please select the range you know if
anybody wants to write self says Cali
fan fictions I'm not telling you to do
it I'm not telling you to do it but also
if anybody wants to you know make one of
the Cali Prego what
I'm sorry
oh you
you forget
an end you friend
you've forgotten you can log on oh I did
not know you could do that yeah what
looks like it okay select the layer of
movement
um all layers
and then wait oh [\h__\h] whoops
hold on it's a bit difficult to do
actually I'm trying to hold on
let me please let me move it
okay and then oh
bigger
oh
wow yeah
there's two of them please specify that
it should not be over the canvas
okay
um please specify that it shouldn't oh
okay I think I get it
mm-hmm
there we go
made it larger oh nice
yay friends my friends
pretty
attention please
and have tea time wait how you like tea
time right yeah I feel like having acne
tea
we've never had tea together before oh
that's so crazy to me because I love
doing tea parties with friends in Holo
yeah
when was it I don't remember I remember
I didn't go for tea but I'm here but
also like we should go to it you know
have a tea party when we can I want to
because I'm a big tea fanatic yes let's
go
yeah I like um especially when they have
like
like dessert plates and stuff like that
with like tiny desserts and sandwiches
and scones
I need stuff and something they have you
know things that look like sweets where
they're actually Savory you know like oh
Seafood papers yeah yeah oh I love those
yeah or like a salmon cheese sandwich
and whatever and it's like it's like got
like cute pink bread or something like
that yeah I love that yeah that's good
good taste good taste we gotta go
together
I know yeah the three of us and maybe we
can take you know the others as well of
course that would be great I welcome
everybody
sounds good let's do it
I'm down the only the only tea we've
been having is like the tea from the
vending machine in the supermarket
that is different it is different
but I think this this is done oh okay
I'm also I'm also done with mine I don't
want to risk it Ollie got pretty
detailed there I know
you guys did awesome thank you so much
thank you for letting us draw you yeah
of course yeah no always have a good
time whenever you guys are around so
I could hang out with you guys anytime
thank you so much
yeah I feel like wait I wonder how we
get rid of the drawings that are already
on here do we just like erase them or
like
I wonder it hurts to erase them but we
can maybe take a screenshot
a week you can actually save there's
like a saving option here there's like a
oh really now download all layers
yeah I found it
oh yes download all layers I already
saved it in case you need it okay thank
you so much I'll ask you for it later
yep okay awesome well then I guess right
here right now of hours yeah let's go
I'll do my best thanks a lot here let me
see if I can just delete do I have to
delete the whole thing it hurts
okay select all layers
okay so sad
so sad our memories it's okay oh hold on
a second all right that's all right it's
immortalized exactly
precisely
no worries exactly all good nothing to
worry about okay sheesh all layers okay
thanks again you guys I appreciate you
dropping by it was fun thank you Kelly
have fun will do I'll have a good time
pray don't die goodbye everybody
see you later
see ya
there they go
what on Earth
nice
let's go let me get rid of maybe this oh
a friend has entered
I see a senpai
I see a senpai in there a senpai flying
by
oh harama
foreign
let's see
[Music]
we've got maybe two wait part one and
two honor no part one is supposed to be
archived it's supposed to be but the
video got locked it got blocked
everywhere
and it's not my fault
it's not my fault I promise you it isn't
I was told those songs were okay and
they've always been okay and I've sang
them before
okay grabbing iPad oh
[Music]
uh
on it
wow oh
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
yes
oh my god wow
whatever
so this is
okay
okay so this is
foreign
yes
okay
this is
[Music]
yeah let's go
Elvis
since it is
[Music]
foreign
yes yeah like this yes yes like this
wow cute
[Music]
cute
um
I'm happy
foreign
thank you
thank you yeah
wow I know
[Laughter]
so this is
foreign
[Music]
yes
really really
[Music]
yes onigashimasu
wow
Sensei is Sensei is succubus
[Music]
wow
no I think succubus
yeah
foreign
[Music]
wow
okay
and devil ears
[Music]
yes yes yeah
beautiful ears
Mama sheet
so this is
[Music]
yeah okay
this hi
um
foreign
[Music]
sexy
not really
karaoke
got it
[Music]
yeah
okay
yo
good morning yes
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh my God no problem
tick
feel you this
you do this
yeah okay
[Applause]
[Music]
amazing
wow sticky
chocolate
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
yeah senses
[Music]
wow
cute
[Music]
foreign
I can't sleep please
I don't want to sleep yeah
yes because
nope yes nope I can't I can't
[Music]
Moss
um
foreign
of course yes
anytime
you're gonna
karaoke
yes
yo
yay
happy thank you Sensei yeah
okay cute Mark on Monday
yes yes
wow cute
and Roy
a lot
[Laughter]
yes
I like pickle
parama
it's
okay okay
call this
ah
okay
[Music]
yeah
yes cute wink okay
okay
no problem
hiroshio
[Laughter]
okay
um
[Music]
yes it is yeah like this
is
oh thank you
foreign
anything
thank you
wow I'm happy
I'm happy thank you sensei
[Music]
um
dakara
okay give me a guide please yeah okay
this guide
okay
yeah a guide line okay okay okay
[Music]
foreign
foreign foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
yay
yeah
of course yes
cute cute sensei
my cute sensei
yeah
[Music]
yay
it's good
[Laughter]
cute cute
yay
[Laughter]
hello
yeah
thank you
your bit
it is yes
I love you I love you too wow
[Laughter]
all right
Santo
[Music]
I know
yeah
all layers
yeah download okay
bye
[Applause]
peace
okay
[Music]
yay
that was fun
[Music]
cool
let me go ahead and it hurts to erase
this I don't want to but I'm going to I
have to
okay Mama I'll just have to finish it
some other time
Sensei is so cute
that was fun
I think we still have
we still have somebody else who's going
to enter in a moment here yata
who could it be
hello hi hi
[Music]
I'm excited I'm so excited I've never
drawn with you before oh yeah but never
I mean we kind of have met each other
like the other day right yeah we did in
person that was cool in person thank you
yeah Kelly actually give me a hug
yay
that was so fun hold on
sure sure yeah you were there you were
there when Ollie like threw me into the
wall right yeah I mean Ashley she kind
of threw you into the wall I was kind of
like
yup classic classic
all right well let me see okay we're
gonna draw um let's do the same as what
I just did with Sensei so like I'm gonna
draw a line down the middle okay hold on
a sec if if it will let me draw please
let me draw oh I'm on let her draw
please please I want to cook okay
here we go okay we're gonna cook
something uh-huh all right cool so you
take the right side and I will break it
up okay left side for me let's go let's
go okay
boy yeah layer layer let me just we only
have two layers in this man yeah I know
it's a little inconvenient it is I was I
always thought that during here as a
battle game because we actually we can
accidentally what's called again we can
accidentally erase each other's Arts so
yeah it's kind of yeah oh true actually
now that you mention it
let me get your reference image there
you are
um what should I do I'm also thinking
what should I draw
those would be good
all right
gotta think of something oh I sound a
little bit crunchy why is it let me let
me see might be internet yeah
yeah I know it's my connection I was
downloading a game sorry let me just
pause it it's okay it's okay no worries
okay it should be fine right now yeah if
I download the game yeah maybe it'll
just need a second to to chill out we'll
see
no worries oh yeah that works so is it
all right now guys you know yeah maybe
let's try let's go to um not this totsu
uh call because this has the lower
quality let's go to the main server
um on top there yeah because it's higher
quality there sure sure like me okay
let's go there
[Music]
though uh it does still sound kind of
strange I wonder why
let me just close
I
don't know
it's kind of worse here really it's more
oh my God it got worse like
um
[Music]
that's so weird
um
real quick okay
no problem
foreign
yeah must be hard using net for aliens
because I mean you're like above the
clouds and whatever
right and cell towers are like under the
clouds
I still don't know what pose is good
maybe I'll do a larger one this time too
yeah so I can just focus on like face oh
yeah is it okay right now oh
is it something better though uh I think
it's like the roboticness is gone
sometimes uh you cut out a little bit
but like for the most maybe it's okay
okay
better much better yeah much much okay
we'll go with this then that's the okay
let's just
help what's up
do you have ears oh yeah you do I I have
I have I don't have an animal ears
gotcha sadly sadly well maybe someday
you can always add more you know but I
could I could ask more yeah
I mean I can always ask in the future
yeah I mean what what ears would be good
I mean cat and dog's ears are already
there I could have liked one
um much
yeah something special like um a bear or
something or like a lion
I don't know I'm a bear lion uh let me
think what else what else is let me
think
um
small
hamster and um what do you got
wow oh
no I don't know what's going on where
what's going on
UFO Wi-Fi man evil
right now sorry guys Ah that's all right
don't worry too much about it it's okay
just using your alien voice it's fine
it still is so crazy to me that you know
so many languages
really into this thing girl girl group
yeah and I kind of like started learning
from there it sounds crazy though yeah I
feel like if you like something then
it's easier to learn like the language
involved with it for sure that's cool
but you learn so fast though I feel you
have like a language ability
to learn English faster but man I
couldn't deal with human like
[Music]
foreign
let's go back
but that's it
that's a
dang that was weird oh now you sound
okay
hello yeah you sound good
okay yeah I think this one's better yeah
much better that's so odd it must be
like a weird internet connection thing
um
I mean so Discord thing yeah wow we have
so many colors in your hair
paint
wow that's a lot of paint
how'd you do that
ah you know at one point at at one point
I kind of like tried to wash it all but
nah oh yeah
I kind of a gay problem that
understandable
there is a lot of it but you know what
it makes it look even cooler
oh yes it is it is it is I am proud of
my paint
painted hair yeah you should call it
painted hair yeah a bunch of different
colors I was I was thinking to myself
like I want to try and get some
different colors in my hair but it's
apparently pretty strict yeah it's a bit
stretchy it is it is but I I think you
can add like highlights or something
yeah or like inside my hair maybe like a
purple or something I don't know that
would be good I think purple or just
bright red would be really good for you
oh bright red would be pretty neat yeah
on the inside yeah and the red will be
pretty pretty neat Kiara was talking
about that today oh yeah she got like
some new colors stuff in her hair and
stuff like that but like it's still the
primary the main color still has to be
the same yeah the main color has to
business him like uh you can actually
just try to change your hair color to
blue or just something yeah
[Music]
yeah it will be confusing to the fans
and and as a someone who likes to draw I
mean that would be a little bit
confusing too yeah definitely yeah and
like new fans as well that are coming in
and are like wait is your hair supposed
to be this color or this color or this
color yeah it would be very confusing
very understandable indeed so so I won't
ask for too much but I I think like
having like one kind of different cool
thing for my hair would be kind of neat
I don't know yes it's kind of neat
actually yeah cute vanilla I mean I mean
I I really like your your pink color
thanks thank you
maybe you should add highlight
highlights yeah that'll be cool just
because like well pink actually it's not
the first color that I choose it's like
a color that I like right all right
yeah I don't hate the color pink it's
just not my favorite but it's grown on
me over time you know
I see
yeah so
you know
I'm fine with it
I know I know yeah pink pink
yeah Asia everything and red is really a
great color though yeah yeah I think
it's a good combination good combination
nice combination indeed yeah maybe I'll
do that plus I love red red is one of my
favorite colors of all time so oh my God
yes red is so cool
man I really love red yeah same yeah
like you know the Deep Red like a
combination between red and black and
gold yeah
red black and gold is really good that's
like the best combination it is it is
yeah I think you have a kimono that has
that kind of color scheme right yeah I
did I kind of like want to try to change
my image a little bit because before
that I always choose like a bright color
like white or blue light blue something
and kind of like hmm why don't we try
black and here it is nice well it looks
great I love your kimono design
did you like um do you have like any
input in like your clothes your clothing
design or do you just kind of say like
do whatever you want ah I actually uh
designed my own outfit oh yeah so I
could have like gave my mom and
um the manager like a really brief uh
sketch and I will just kind of like give
my mom the rest of it like just do
whatever you want cool
[Music]
yeah that's awesome here too because a
lot of members actually a lot of ID
members kind of doesn't really know how
to ex express what they kind of want
with the new hair and um what's it
called again and uh uh costume so I
probably often often um help them with
that
cool well
for like a free designs concept designs
yay cool that's so awesome it's nice to
be helpful in some way I want to be
helpful as well oh I'm a year older I'm
full enough yeah yeah I guess I always
feel like I could do more though but I
did yeah but we have we also have like
quite a few great drawers in EN I feel
so oh yeah yeah part of me is
a great drawer and he already draws good
too and there are a lot of like
everybody has like a pretty good basic
skill so I guess I'm just here kind of
like
eh I don't really need to to do anything
much else
it's really good too thank you
oh since when you draw I kind of like
haven't seen you draw in a while oh yeah
a lot of people say that uh I actually
like went to school for art a long time
ago oh really
really yeah yeah that was like what I
did that was my thing back in the day
but yeah I want it to be a comic artist
a long time ago
wow yeah but wow I could I could never
be a comic artist
oh my God so I know a little bit about
like I think I especially like writing
comic scripts so like someday I want to
write like script and then have somebody
better than me draw it because like I
think my drawing's fine but like I want
like a really good drawer to to drop my
future comic you know
um
yeah that's how I feel but
yeah personally that's just me
if you could draw a comic of yourself
right now in your free time though like
a four common things oh yeah that's a
good idea yeah I mean four color doesn't
really take a long time I think I think
wow I've never really thought to do that
before but that sounds like a good idea
I'd love to give it a try
ooh nice give it a try give it a try
yeah
everyone wants to get like free time I
mean do you have any free time do I have
free yeah do you do we have
chat knows already chat's like yeah the
chances of Mori having enough free time
to do that are extremely low but it's
nice to dream I guess
that's a drug maybe it's gonna be next
year maybe I don't know yeah exactly
precisely yeah I'm gonna throw it in
your free free little time yeah or free
time whatever little free time I have
I'll try I guess
we'll see
it's drawing
I really miss it
yeah I've been driving could take a lot
of time you know yeah yeah exactly you
have to be in the mood to draw it is I
feel like um I started liking drawing a
lot more after I stopped doing it as
like my future job I guess
yeah it is actually it is
there's a lot of pressure on me and I'm
glad that I kind of stopped
you know because it was it was making
drawing not fun for me anymore
so it is amazing it's really good if you
draw it on a base on hobby as a hobby
you ask him a work yeah a lot definitely
it was really stressing me out so I'm
kind of glad that it's just something I
do for fun now you know makes me like it
a lot more
it is it is like a lot more
I mean if you kind of like were um
drawing as a war you kind of like watch
Korean
um there's a lot of people's expectation
on you yeah yeah yeah they expect it to
be like super duper cool and good and it
kind of like
yeah yeah you think a lot about it you
think a lot about it and competition is
really really stiff and like I don't
feel like I can compete in today's art
world as like a professional but that's
just me
oh my God it is it is actually and then
and then you kind of like discovered
um
um people that who are a lot younger
than you but has a lot of skills than
you I was just like man so crazy right
yeah seriously he blows my mind
so I was gonna play uh see their
Instagram or something and they kind of
like a lot of people uh on Instagram
kind of like mention their ages I think
in their bio and I was like I would see
that's like 14. how
14 and 12. I'm actually gonna put this
here yeah seriously
like for real how
yeah for real for real for real for real
how for real I was gonna like what did I
do when I was 14 like I think I was just
kind of playing around the park or
something yeah I was just eating crayons
in school man like I don't remember oh
God yes
that's all I was doing I know I wasn't
thinking about my art future
[Music]
looks delicious in a way man yeah like
you're not wrong there are some really
tasty looking colors out there
can't be helped
so
it is
I mean at one time at one point you kind
of like Gotta Eat paint yeah exactly in
school you have to
yeah you have two guys
it's a part of growing up
it's a part of growing up you have to
explore the world guys
it's a must yeah
it tastes like crayons I don't know how
to describe it but it tastes like
crayons like those chemical sticky stuff
like candle wax yeah wax that's what it
is yeah wax yeah wax precisely yeah oh
so you have eaten crayons before
I I have accident accidentally and not
really accidentally I feel like um
I see well sometimes you just gotta know
there's some things in this world you
have to know for example and you could
have like know that crayons doesn't I
also call it tastes good and you know it
from there exactly yeah exactly and glue
yup gotta taste glue as well oh glue
yeah I got yup oh you know glue and
balloons you know uh those what's it
called again um helium balloons I know
it's not that balloon like where you you
have to kind of blow into it and then
what's called again
like liquid type balloon-ish
scoop what's it called again Chad Help
Me Maybe Jack knows maybe chat knows
like those type of liquid balloons that
you have to a bubble says bubbles not
balloon there's bubbles gotcha okay yeah
bubbles oh yeah man it tastes like soap
I know right when I would get inside the
bathtub I would like get some shampoo or
like soap and then put it on my lips and
try and blow bubbles and it would always
make my lips sting at the end of the
night yeah like yeah
everything's an experience I know that
that blue bubbles taste like bubbles
yeah like now you know
you know hey that that was uh and I know
what hell of an experience so why you
have to express a lot in your life guys
yeah just explore
experience is important
important very very important you gotta
leave the house every once in a while
right yeah I guess it kind of like light
the chat like they actually made the
edible bubbles really
there's an edible bubbles
really are you sure that sounds fake
that sounds fake can you actually eat
bubbles is there a such thing as an
edible bubbles
good question I wonder question though
yeah I mean really
it depends it depends on what it's made
of it's true I'm gonna be looking that
up afterwards not because I want to try
it but because you know I'm curious
because carrots is for experimenting and
for experience exactly for more life
experience and things to talk about on
stream yeah that's it
that's always what it's about more stuff
to talk about stream I was streaming for
Content I mean it will be really good
for a Content exactly yeah eating eating
bubbles oh yeah precisely eating bubbles
nice eating bubbles
could be good for you
this show it could be good you know
I mean if it's not forestry I think I
don't I don't think I'm gonna TR I'm
gonna try to eat a bubble just the
content right yeah this is for
intense guys but of course yeah yeah I
mean same with me and cat treats I'm not
gonna eat a cat treat on stream unless
it's you know or a off stream rather
yeah Kobo convinced me
oh okay how is it does it have any taste
at all
um I mean it was all right it's not
something I'd want to eat but you know
oh can we enjoy it
I mean it's edible though and of course
it's edible I think you can eat it so I
mean it's not bad I guess
[Music]
I suppose but again I wouldn't eat it
again
I mean yeah of course of course of
course I don't think you should eat it
again no forget that I don't think you
should eat it again oh my God absolutely
not no way on this planet Earth
unless it's on stream and unless Kobo
says it'll make me her favorite again
oh oh okay
okay all right if it's between me and if
it's between me and Kiara
and eating cat treats is what's gonna
make Kobo choose me I'm gonna eat cat
treats yeah I
that's worth it yeah maybe and it's
worth it
think I will I think I'll do it again
baby I'll do it again
I mean I'm gonna lie I think catchers
are edible at like like actually
actually edible because there aren't any
much like seasoning on it like it's just
like grains and stuff oh that is true
yeah they should make treats that are
edible for humans and cats and dogs
yeah wow I want them wow
yeah so I can share treats with my cats
oh and not feel ashamed
yeah not feel the same I I know it it's
good because I taste it so you you have
to you have
um to eat it or else
or else
I already taste it and see and it tastes
good good
not just okay
it tastes amazing if it kind of like
taste uh different brands I think that
would be a good one
a cat treat tasting stream yeah
myself so there's easily that a lot of I
don't it's kind of different from the
smell so I think the taste is different
too oh yeah
it's different though great content
ideas zofi
okay great idea I love it do it do it at
um moderately okay yeah moderately in
moderation of course in moderation of
course yes yes we don't we don't want
you to have a stomachache in the in this
BC schedule so yeah that would not be
careful that would not be good yeah
especially especially when the cats
could be enjoying the treats and then I
just steal them and then I get a tummy
ache what a waste what waste a waste
that would be all right there we go all
layers nice okay
making progress making progress making
progress making progress yay
e
drawn really fast tonight actually then
faster than I usually draw oh really
yeah oh that's nice nice nice nice nice
I guess talking to friends helps It Go
by a bit faster
it is actually I mean if you're kind of
drawing alone you kind of like have the
urge to kind of like do another thing
like maybe checking Twitter yeah true or
something
that's a good point definitely yeah
checking Twitter is become X right now
oh geez yeah my chat just told me about
that
that's awful I I hate it yeah really we
cannot we cannot say we we want to check
check the Twitter or we want to check
the ax like yeah everyone in chat is
gonna correct me if I say
I want to check Twitter you mean X
you're an X like we are I mean we're
kind of like tweeting so we're now
acting what yes
I've confused I hate it so much
you're like what what why they would
choose X they could have like choose
like more creative right names literally
could have been anything we already have
an X we have horokusu
I guess I'll just name I'll just name
Twitter after them yeah I mean yeah in
honor of pollock so yeah I go should sue
them name it after
where's my lawsuit you're gonna do it
wow pretty you're so fast
what the heck you wow
very fast drawer oh my gosh well I'm
almost done so I'll try and pick up the
pace a little bit
oh okay I kind of like still I don't
know if I should put a color on it or
not but I think I'm just gonna keep it
dark here yeah sure no problem whatever
you want to do is okay yeah okay yep
I'm even letting people draw stick
figures if they want
first yeah why not
why not everyone go from stick figures
yeah exactly that's it's a great it's a
it's the starting point for everybody
it is actually starting point for
everybody is in stick figures yeah no
shame at all no shame at all guys no
shame at all
yep
okay
see maybe some little eyelashes
[Music]
ooh pretty eyelashes eyelashes yeah
I look so I look so Moe
oh thanks
I feel like I'm a visual novel character
ooh I think you should make your own
game like official novel game like uh a
hall of following that would be good we
did that for um we did that for
Valentine's actually yeah I saw that it
was really fun it was fun I've had some
recent inspiration I guess to to do like
my own sort of like visual novel like
live visual novel with me and the
deadbeats so like I'd have them like
make decisions like
in polls like on the stream is what I'm
thinking of but I'm still kind of going
through Logistics I need to get some
stuff commissioned for it to make it
work but yes it is like you know um the
overlay like a game game overlay yeah
yeah exactly good yeah and then I and
then I want to get like some CGS made as
well so like if the chat makes the right
decision
um like they'll get to see some of the
CGS I don't know oh what is they doing
and then they don't get to see them and
it's a waste of my money
okay okay let me move this side down a
bit Yeah you must be careful
you must be careful and
yeah okay okay okay here we go okay nice
Glory Days oh geez oh shoot it won't be
lewd unless no I'm joking it won't be
I wouldn't be I mean won't let us anyway
so yeah
true that is true
yeah
let's see here's a little dot I always
just do dot noses gosh I need to draw
some actual notes
my nose is a DOT too
that is true actually looking at you now
yes your nose is a DOT
yeah not I mean dot is a good good good
news good news is adult no so
yeah
nice and it's easy though yeah exactly
yeah after kind of like see like those
uh like realism art tutorials uh for the
nose everything like
how like I don't know how to do about a
cow you're so good at it I don't get it
either
I don't get it either
the camera always start starts with
um what's it called again um with
likes this triangle shape ish thingy
yeah
and then we kind of like shade this here
and there here and then and then for La
there's a middle so you're kind of like
what can you can you repeat that please
no clue what they did it's like that one
meme of like how to draw an owl first
draw a circle next finish the elbow it's
literally oh my God that's what it
reminds me of
yeah oh alrighty I think I got the basic
oh nice yeah
cute though and then to be shoulder
those down here
yeah overalls cute overalls
ah thank you
complete my house
overalls
whoa
okay if you're not careful it'll become
a Squidward nose
actually look at the Squidward nose I
kind of like tried it before like once
and they're kind of like
yeah that's not it it looks like a
Squidward Squidward's nose let's go yes
good word
that's gonna be this big big nose like
this yeah like yeah
all right start one more
it's good Mister yeah
indeed indeed I love it it's good
perfect Squidward nose yeah let's go
let's go looking good there this is the
Squidward nose version
Oh looking good looking good let's go
yeah you're an artist like Squidward
[Laughter]
more handsomer um handsome Squidward
God no it's awesome now that's amazing
yeah now this is an art wow golden Brash
more like belongs in the trash
let's go
[Music]
let's go home
she's hot I know I am hot hey look at
you nothing new here
looking hot what did I do grew yourself
a Squidward nose
yeah guys if you want to be bolder and
handsomer and cooler you should have
yourself some um cardigan um
yeah it's available on stores right now
you should just probably grab it quick I
wonder if it actually is though like
what if
what if there actually is like a
Squidward cosplay you can buy
oh my God yes yeah I want a Squidward Mr
Squidward
it's a Squidward that could be good yeah
let's use this color okay nice okay
cool
cool cool
Mom I'm an artist
yeah looking great actually
this one great wow nice
wow that was fun
okay
oh my God Mom I'm an artist
finally my dream will come true
let's go
all right I'm gonna take off the nose
but screenshot it all right so let me
grab a screenshot guys screenshot guys I
want to preserve my oh wait let me just
save my cat yeah you can save the canvas
my own little layers don't know there's
okay cool cool cool cool cool nice
I did it already did guys thank you so
much yeah
wow it looks great a little shading on
the hair too so detailed
oh thank you you're fast
wow
Pete I am speed you're so Speedy I mean
as long as I don't color it and it's
Speedy yeah I guess so coloring takes a
while let me drink some more energy
drink
okay energy thing for today ah yeah only
one though I'm not letting myself drink
too many energy drinks it's bad for your
health not too many yeah it's really bad
for your heart actually kind of like
make your heart plump mm-hmm look more
faster yeah
yeah that's that is true I'll be careful
I'll also drink water
water
yeah everybody hydrated water guys
nice water
I can't believe I'm saying it but I'm
actually really looking forward to um
spicy noodles
oh really yeah I'm supposed to eat them
as like a challenge I guess but um
I'm supposed to be afraid of them
because they're ghost peppers in them
and whatever right
yeah I feel like you guys would be fine
you guys could probably eat the spicy
also probably fine but but not me
for her
ah so you don't really like spice or you
just kind of like cannot tolerate it or
actually I'm fine with spice I think I
actually have all of my out of all of my
friends that are not Indonesian
um I would say that I'm probably like
the highest tolerance
but
um but but everybody has a really low
tolerance so I mean like for example the
glass chips uh that Muno Senpai gave me
those were great I really liked them a
lot my I mean I was sweating but they
were good
I kept eating them right even though I
was dying it was like oh yes it is like
there's like this a really good spice
and then there's like a really really
like to get hurt yeah like yeah whatever
it depends on what kind of peppers yeah
I guess so wait everybody's saying that
they went through something like that
did she do the noodle challenge because
the noodles I gave her are the noodles
I'm eating
oh yeah yup it's the same ones I gave
her those
because I got a big pack of them but
they kind of like has this low tolerance
of spices she does are you sure she
likes it oh okay
oh okay I see
nice she did the Olga challenge yeah
yeah I gave them the noodles because
they were out of noodles so meanwhile
all I said you were the one who gave
them yeah yeah yeah because they didn't
come in in time so
yeah I gave some to Bae and Ollie and
Olga so that they could do their
challenge
and uh yeah
she just died
they then I'm gonna die if Bae died then
I'm going to die
meanwhile Ollie was just chilling it was
did Ollie have no problem
yeah we have actually uh my spicy
tolerant tolerance is um like
um around all these and in ID uh who
doesn't really have uh spicy colors
about rainy Riso and Muna so yeah I
actually like spies and can handle
splice that spicy that that good I think
wow
I mean yeah
I think oh no they used to love spicy
food but her tolerance has dropped a lot
since joining Hollow uh I see oh I can't
see I'm gonna need to go watch that
stream of bae eating the noodles oh God
yeah me too I want to see them
nervous well it'll be fine she's nervous
it'll be fine it'll be fine I mean if
you cannot just if you really cannot
either just uh abandon it like yeah your
your health is really really important
right now than the noodles so I do have
well I do have um some noodles that are
less spicy that don't have ghost peppers
in them they're just really hot Japanese
noodles but oh but I don't know I feel
like I want to do the ghost pepper
challenge because you know salamander
got a million views on YouTube and so
I'm like okay let's celebrate by eating
spicy noodles
that wasn't the deal more that's what
I'm saying that's what I'm saying yeah
but I think
JP stuff not really that spicy like I
mean uh you know it's spicy but it kind
of like hurt your mouth rather than the
good spicy you know a good type of
spiciness you know yeah I'm never really
a fan of Japanese spicy stuff because
you just kind of like hurt you like just
really hurts you without
I don't know without you enjoying it
yeah exactly well yeah there was a time
or what was it I had a friend um who
like grew ghost peppers
um just at her home like for fun and so
she brought a bunch of them to a
get-together that me and some friends
were having we were like oh yeah cool
this should be like fine
um if we just have a little bite and
then you know some of the others were
warning us like you really shouldn't do
that
I took the smallest teeniest tiniest
little crunch bite just a tiny nibble
like a mouse nibble
and I saw my friends like eat half
of the pepper
and I was I started hallucinating and I
fell on the ground and like tears in my
eyes and just looked up at the ceiling
and I wanted to scream that was rough
and then my friends ran away
you can guess where they ran away to
um yeah yeah
oh I didn't have to I didn't have to do
that
I didn't have to do that thankfully
because my little nibble wasn't enough
it was just enough to make me cry and
scream and it was bad but that was it
and like I started having a hard time
breathing I was like yeah
it was tough yeah guys you could
actually hallucinating if you could have
like
I don't know eat too much spices spicy
stuff yeah man
spicy
spiky I mean if if it's a good type of
spiciness it would be good like the
glass chips that you eat yeah those were
young I love that right it's spicy but
it's good but if you have like
is bad I didn't I was I was spicy stuff
but I cannot eat like Mala Mala spices
thing it could have like make your mouth
numb and your thumb I don't I don't I
don't really like that kind of spices
yeah the numb isn't isn't great I agree
yeah it's like this peppercorns things
yeah
Peppers
Brill I don't like that spiciness at all
yeah I feel ya it's like some spiciness
gets kind of Addicting to be honest like
there's something you like want to keep
eating it because it's like I don't know
what it is about it it's like the
hallucinations kind of feel nice I don't
know
but then it gets to a certain point of
too spicy where it's like nah bad
bad bad yeah
wow this looks so good the drawing's so
good oh thank you thank you thank you
for the cute drawing I love it it was
nice getting to chat with you as well it
is actually we haven't chatted in a
while it's been a really long time I
mean I know we saw we we saw each other
like our IRL but yeah it's all different
you know getting to collab and whatnot
so
thanks for collabing with me today
tonight yeah I'll try not to die I need
to stand up and stretch my back yeah
just don't die I want to play a lot of
games with you don't die yet okay I will
I promise okay uh okay I'm just gonna
say this uh should I be the one who will
upload this on Twitter or should or do
you want to upload this you can
certainly upload it if you'd like oh
yeah I will then yeah awesome thank you
you'll be take care of yourself okay
okay I will thank you catch you bye
there she go
love you Cali yopi
cute wow I'm happy
thank you you'll be
though it hurts to to delete everything
we must but I'll never forget
it's nice of her to save as well okay
all layers
[Music]
don't say no it's fine it's saved it's
saved
it saved everybody's saving theirs don't
you worry you'll see it again
you'll see it again
we still have one more person
left to draw with
one last drawing friend
oh boy I'll do my best go ahead and
separate the canvas ahead of time oh
oopsies
yay my favorite track is back
of this track
foreign
[Music]
how are you
I'm fine thank you
[Music]
bye hello hello
yes
wow no problem
thank you for coming
yes thank you dude I'm so very happy
yeah
no problem
together
yes drink together drop together here
foreign
yes yeah can you draw me please
let's go
home tonight
it's okay
um
foreign
pen
it's a long time no see
long time no see the snare oh
wow
yes recording
that's right live Embassy
[Music]
so live delivery hi shin
us
okay I'm awake yes I'm awake
yeah alarm thank you
[Music]
so many many many many sagio yes
yes
I have many many Vlogs today
[Music]
night night time
yeah let's go all night working
Easter
[Music]
talking and drawing of course
okay okay I see wonderful
voice
so so difficult
[Music]
is so very very hot yeah
I'm a Japanese but I'm not good
taking Japanese no no no no it's cute
yeah
this is
nice
throwing you are NADA
pajama pajama yes yes wonderful
I know let's see wonderful drawing yeah
wonderful drawing together
um
yes
so cute boys yeah
sexy cute voice so amazing I die
hey you died I died
I died okay okay I won't die for you I
promise foreign
[Music]
oh no nervous no problem
no problem Doki Doki tokidoki is
24 hours
[Music]
you love very strong
yeah I want to be strong thanks
good boy
um
[Music]
how to see
foreign
[Music]
yeah you're so very nice thank you I'm
so happy I did my best gambari mashta
yeah so cool and curious oh you're good
I'm happy
and happy thank you
yeah
[Music]
music so nice and cool and cute
foreign
[Music]
yeah big secret
surprise a surprise that's right yeah
it's a surprise
kimono
yes
okay
[Music]
yo
foreign
[Music]
it's true
foreign
[Music]
I know tummy I know stomach
yes yes
[Laughter]
[Music]
oh my God
skeleton yeah a little skeleton
foreign
it's nice yeah nice Echo because
chocolate Edge
dramatic dramatic
yes dramatic very nice
that's cool
tonight
yes
yes yes guess what oh my gosh thank you
thanks I like it
um
[Music]
thank you
happy
because
I refuse to this
it's a little Samurai
ah yes I am a Tom and I yeah that's
right secret society samurai
samurai yes
[Music]
wonderful
yes
you know
very strong
yeah and Katana Katana
yes yeah
let's go nice
like this
look at this
yay and big eyes
yes
big eyes
yeah
cute always say
jewelry eyes yes oh yeah
yeah
like diamond eyes
[Music]
yeah
I think so too
sorry
yeah you should
so he comes your snare
yes
wow
yes yes
I like it
yeah
let's go
how are you
cute
yay
[Music]
yeah let's get what's together once
again
[Music]
foreign
Idaho
yes thank you no problem
[Music]
sleeping yeah
yeah sleepy time long sleepy time
yeah I promise
um
hmm seven hours
seven hours yeah yeah nice
Hennessy healthy so Hiroshima
hello nice
so the more like this
guy bucket
mama
yes yeah
money today yep one time Takara no
problem
so everyone's so happy
yeah
yup
hey everyone so happy everyone
is
[Music]
drawing picture together me too
yay maybe uh my maybe this is my
happiest moment
yeah
the happiest moment
yeah yay
cute Samurai I did it
yeah I'm a very good story
yeah and cute
and cute
yeah
yeah cute and strong
yes let's see yep
[Music]
every time so
because yeah
so I'm very so happy of course anytime
it's truth
[Music]
yeah I don't lie
yeah
yes
[Music]
Maji Chuchu
yes yeah underneath
hi
[Music]
okay and the guy
hi
yes
foreign
yeah a little bit
it's like in there
ah just taking a design that got a
[Music]
um
[Laughter]
foreign
[Music]
I'm assuming
nice assuming yes yeah nice to me nice
hobby yeah
mm-hmm I think so too
yeah yeah
um
[Music]
hmm
thank you
sorry
yeah thank you for fan art always
thank you
foreign
[Music]
we're gonna dance
Kawaii
um
[Music]
yes
cute drawings so cute I'll save yes
thank you so much
[Music]
yeah let's do it anytime
foreign bye bye
[Music]
bye
goodbye
[Laughter]
Suki
uh
happy
yeah
saki no Suki
not the sake it's Suki
yo yo
saki's fine too though nothing wrong
with Saki
wow
see
I'm getting some cool stuff in my inbox
to share later that was really fun
drawing sesh I hope you guys had a good
time with it too
oh now moey gets to chill for a sec what
hour is Cali on now
um a lot
a lot
very very
how about that very very hour
uh let me go ahead and get rid of the
window capture here
and then for game capture we'll have it
right there but we're not doing jump
King just yet no no no
not yet because now it's chill time
more than average past halfway well
that's reassuring
no problem 13 and a half Etc
um
no no jumping yet chill a bit of chillax
time but my shoulders hurt a bit so I'm
gonna stand up and stretch him a little
hold on a sec
it's time for me to stand up and walk a
bit
oisha
oh wow that's um
that is
six Starbucks cuffs over there oh boy
and five empty bottles of picari sweats
I think the studio is due for a cleaning
yeah yeah it definitely is
I mean it doesn't nothing spoiled or
anything like that because I don't get
milk in my coffee but still not great to
look at
still not great to look at nothing's
moldy it's fine and they're almost all
drained
worse than the coffee down my throat
time to lay on the ground
I have no man on the ground
dude
[Music]
all fun
I want to get
somewhere
a massage my shoulders really deep
I could use that right now
honestly
no sleepy
no sleep I won't sleep I'm not gonna
sleep I'm still talking to you guys
don't worry I'm just I'm just gonna go
sit on the ground really quick don't
I'll keep talking I'll keep talking
I will continue to talk
just so you know I'm not asleep I'm just
on the ground
straightening out my back a little bit
there's no sleeping though not here I'm
not even tired yet
just hanging
the kitty cat seemed to be all good
oh
the babies my babies
ah
they had plenty of food in their bowls I
gave them their dinner and I gave them
some treats
I just know they're missing out on some
play time now but tomorrow I'll play
with them plenty yep I will play with
the kitty cats a lot
a whole lot lots of playing with the
babies
playing with the babies the baby cats
I'm still awake
I'm not sleeping
that's not what we do during a 24 hour
stream
we do not do that we don't
don't
I'm still mad about part one of the
stream being completely blocked
that's really annoying
but I'm gonna get it unblocked to mark
my words
and if I have to download it and edit
out the parts with copyrighted content
that it is what it is
but I will make sure that people get a
chance to see it
a lot of people wanted to watch it
but what can you do right what can you
do
nothing much really
no bones about it
okay let's just lean back in the chair
whoa Kyla
sending more power
yeah
thanks Kyla
we need the Mario Party sending more
power to Cali don't die Cali
I'll try not to
why is it blocked um because songs that
I'm literally allowed to sing were in it
yeah I don't know um it's weird
I don't totally get it but oh well
yeah
one sec ouch
all right let me lay back
[Music]
no problem it's blocked because
Wario
I doubt it
I doubt that
if you lie down you'll sleep nope no I
won't I just had to set my shoulders
right
think you're doing really great so far
keep it up we'll keep the train rolling
I have no fear that it will continue
rolling onward have my claims been just
have my disputes been figured out yet
please
no all right cool
I'm just saying that it really should
not be blocked
really shouldn't be
blocked
why
this train has no breaks
no breaks whatsoever
YouTube having a bunch of trouble chat
breaking a lot lately yeah I wonder why
that is actually that has been happening
a lot the chat breaking and whatnot
I'm certainly not the only person it
happens to though right
it's definitely multiple people that are
having the same issue
so
yeah a lot okay be a small Indie company
YouTube is a functioning website it's
what's happening
it's site-wide okay well I'm glad to
know that it's not just me you know
but did you at least get Mario Party to
work yep we got it to work we got to
work
yep I won't spoil who won fake spoilers
and chat
fake spoilers in chat
but anyway
no
problem
[Music]
um
sorry I'm reading some messages as well
hahaha
nice swag
just a lot going on
these days oh get out of the call get
out of the call no reason to be in the
call
what's up with you guys
I feel like for some people it's
morning time
at least in the states right
and then we'll keep trucking along until
it's night time for you guys
um
all right monster give me strength
3 30 a.m 1 35 p.m here
1 30 p.m here
gotcha
I see I see the later in the night that
it is I guess the more like towards
daytime it is in the states
not a hold on
we ended a bit earlier than
um was on the schedule which is honestly
I'm fine with that we'll just use it as
extra time to kick back and chat
you know
just some chill chatting laid back chat
you know ah where's my 24 hour stream
logo I mean I say logo it's not really a
logo it's more like a
what hold on
it's more like a uh
image that has the hashtag it's the
hashtag that's what it is
it's the hashtag
um it's not a logo it's the hashtag
thingy hashtag mori24
hey everybody if you're sitting here and
thinking to yourself what's up with Mori
is she gonna continue streaming the
answer is yes I will but you know the
truth of the matter is I actually stream
almost every single day if you're
missing out any of that what you could
do is click the Subscribe button below
below
if you click that subscribe button then
you'll get notified every time that I do
something which is kind of cool
um because I do a lot of things so
check it out
click subscribe and also leave a comment
and a like as well I like comments I
like reading through them
so yeah classic YouTuber moment skip ad
hit the Bell you don't need to hit the
Bell
it's that call to action it's that call
to action
and you're like supposed to do or
whatever I don't know but you know what
I'm trying to get better at like
just asking people for support instead
of just assuming that they're gonna
I guess
Maury 24 sounds like a news channel I'd
actually watch
yeah like a 60 Minutes thing or
something
anyway
be sure to hit join use your mom's
credit card to join tier three
don't
you kind of need to hit the Bell if you
want YouTube to actually send
notifications is that true
really hit the Bell please I have to
do it hit the Bell God doesn't say what
do you think should I hit the Bell
or is that Overkill
what do you think death sun say
he says he doesn't care
he says why are you asking me
I don't know a Sensei you're the one
that's supposed to be teaching me
well anyway more towards the end of the
stream I have like fun stuff to show you
guys you know
I have like
nope
a little special a little special
message
a special little artwork to celebrate
oh man so let me figure out what we're
gonna eat before the spicy noodles okay
avocado for sure
maybe some almond butter
if the milk at the ready
if you aren't asleep but I'm not going
to sleep
I'm not going to sleep I won't do it
I've pulled all-nighters before
hitting the Bell gets you alerts when
they actually work
describing is great if you can get
autoplay to cooperate with the tabs
seems technical sometimes I get
notifications for random subscriptions I
don't even have the Bell on for but
don't get notifications for the ones I
do have the Bell on I don't get YouTube
weird
why does YouTube have to go and make
things so complicated
oh well
you can't pull all-nighters anymore see
ya I kind of thought the same thing back
during the college days pulling
all-nighters was like no problem
but now it's like
I can't
no way but you know what for tonight
I'll make an exception
I mean it's already so very late into
the morning you know if if I think about
it okay hold on let's think about this
technically
I've played games until too late
okay
for example Final Fantasy VI which I
haven't gotten a chance to play again
in a long time
um but I was playing it and when I
started playing it I looked at the clock
and I was like okay
10 p.m I really can't play too much of
this
because then you know I have a stream I
have a stream in the morning it'll be 11
A.M and I won't get enough sleep
unless you know I properly right get the
right sleep I need and not play this too
long so I set an alarm for two hours
um to go to bed at midnight and then I
set the alarm and like I'm playing and
it just it goes off immediately why
because time just flies by and I don't
want to put it down because I'm at a
good part in the story I'm like okay
another hour
and then before I know it I just stopped
looking at the clock
I check it like maybe once every three
hours and I'm like ah three hours have
passed and then it's six a.m and I'm
like how did this happen to me I made my
mistakes
um I guess I should take some Tylenol
and try to go to bed and then I see the
sun rising outside
so my
my line of thinking
is if you really wanted enough and if
you try hard enough you should be able
to do it
you should be able to
but you need to do things that are fun
right
I don't know why I decided to play Jump
why jump king of all things
like do I want to stress myself out
maybe okay
perhaps the way I think about it is this
it would be too easy if I played a chill
game
okay we could just pop on Final Fantasy
16 and
four hours would fly
absolutely fly
like nothing we could
we could do that however
that is too easy
that is too easy and so we are doing
jumping goes to the babe now I don't
expect to Beat It
I don't but I'm gonna play like I do
okay Final Fantasy 16 would be an easy
hours yeah honestly I I start up Final
Fantasy 16. I look at the clock and like
10 hours are gone we haven't done a 10
hour Final Fantasy 16 stream but we
could theoretically I bet we could maybe
the next one next several ones be just
12 hour streams
just instantly time flies playing that
game I don't get it
I don't get it
so
honestly would be easier to play getting
over it for the golden pop
I mean I wanted though
50 times
I don't think I could do that in four
hours
pretend you're Clive jumping up to see
Jill
now there is an idea
I don't know Final Fantasy does that
though
especially this time the story and
characters are just so engaging
but don't worry we'll be right back into
it
um as for what the next couple streams I
have it I have planned are
um
a lot of it I kind of can't really it's
kind of hard for me to talk about right
now for various reasons but
um
on the 26th which is so basically what
will happen is I will finish this 24
hour stream right
um the first stream of yours that I saw
was eight minute jump Kings is coming
full circle yeah
nice
nostalgic
um
basically this stream will end at
something like
1 P.M
on the 25th well don't worry I'll get
lots of sleep and lots of good rest but
then the next day uh we stream again
um why I just have to you'll understand
I want to be there I want to watch the
countdown with you guys
and maybe do some drawer in
look exciting times okay I can't stop
can't stop when times are this exciting
but don't worry because after that I'm
taking a little vacation okay and I say
take a little vacation but I'm actually
I'm doing content on those days
it'll be fun though it's all fun stuff
it's all fun stuff can't stop won't stop
a relax-a-thon I don't know you'll see
you'll see what I mean
more than two days
um well I'm kind of
I just really want
I want to do a stream showing you guys
um diocom food
right like food at like a traditional
Japanese Inn and like use a hand Cam and
stuff like that I want to show it to you
guys
so and I figured why not just pair that
with like a vacation
you know
so yeah
that'll be neat I think that that'll be
chill see that's just fun you know
it's just me eating some real calm food
and like showing you guys the stuff and
the courses and stuff I'm gonna talk to
the place beforehand and like
make sure it's all good and whatnot so
yeah
Solo or off Club it'll just be me
it'll just be me because I want to go
and like find some peace somewhere you
know and like have like a real good rest
Japanese Ambassador yeah
Tokyo tourism Ambassador I gotta I have
to do those kinds of things I mean okay
it's not in the job description however
I want to impose it upon myself you know
that's how I feel
so you know some alone time
I'd like to stream it if I can honestly
but we'll see
we'll see how I go about it
I need to have a chat with the place I'm
I'm chilling at first
aren't you afraid of stalkers I've been
doing this a long time I know what I'm
doing
I know what I'm doing
there have also been a lot of times in
the past I've gotten pretty good at
faking people out
the fake outs are important too
just don't worry about it
I know what I'm doing
so
yeah this is my job the Jukes breaking
ankles
it's not my first rodeo
not my first rodeo so don't worry
I'll be fine
I have faith in you know that you know
what you do and just be safe out there
plus you can punch out most suckers okay
well
people here are small
that is true
and I do like punching
I do like a punch
I can't just punch most people I can
throw most people
the Scythe might give it away
I'll just make it real small and put it
in my pocket as per the usual
[Music]
yeah
because my size I can make it small too
little baby one little mini one
Ahmed or Cali stronger I think it's
that's a tough one
Amelia gave me a run for my money in the
arm wrestling competition
[Music]
but do you know
I don't but I know I have some moves
Amore's fists are rated E for everyone
for everyone's face
I'm healing is strong though I'll tell
you what
it's that buffson it's that buffsin uh
buff I guess
I own it more you're the strongest
Maybe
I do I there are muscles they
are our muscles
yeah that is true the Kiara altar looks
real tough though
I feel like
like in that outfit we could have a
really good fight together
she and I
I feel like we could like our battle
would be legendary
Kiara alter
she looks badass I know I remember why
don't you show me that outfit it was a
while ago it was like a couple months
ago actually I saw it for the first time
oh I saw the X oh it changed
[Music]
ah
foreign
I saw the X
that day you stop don't stop just go
your own way so don't be afraid
[Music]
keep up
and never be afraid
let go of the best
[Music]
like
looks like the logo of an important
gentleman club
oh lordy
I just wanted to go look at um
I don't think whoa what am I looking at
I didn't need to see that on my timeline
oh Twitter
where is
takanashi kiwawa
this is a Twitter
yeah new outfit lore video nice
yeah she looks so magical
already some good fan art coming out of
it
yeah recommendations for what to do in
London please
that's right yeah well I mention that
artists are so fast
I must still call it Twitter same
okay here we go here full outfit I'm
looking at it now
go on the Big Ben
oh nice
the the thighs in the middle are visible
very cool
and two two hairstyles cute blue nails
I just don't go full British
enjoy some of the food
hey this looks good though
so awesome yeah I know she's really
really happy about this one which
hairstyle do I like best let me see
oh that's really tough
in general I like the non-ponytail but
for the outfit I like the ponytail
like the the non ponytail one is like
super cute just like as as is and like
very spunky and I love it
however
the ponytail just works so well and the
blue in there man that's cool
ponytail is Peak RPG
ah man if I were to do like a second
color in my hair I wonder what would
work I feel like not a lot goes with
pink
you know
but hold on I need to actually you just
that just reminded me I need to do a
little message on a sec
to ask
because I already asked about like hair
color
got it
black
[Music]
yeah I feel like
I feel like
um that should be fine I mean a lot of
others have done that as well yeah
like streaks and like inner hair color
like crony with the blue and whatnot
must be okay and then you know Kiara's
got like blue as well the blue streaks
It's gotta be okay it's Gotta Be
I can't get over that hair clip though
it's so good
the hair clip that looks like a final
fantasy logo it looks like she's got a
piece of the mother crystal in her hair
so cool
so good nice nice nice nice nice nice
yeah I do wonder what the limit is I
mean of course there are people with
like multiple colors but what I mean is
like for new outfits and stuff like that
right
or for add-on hairstyles
yeah
because like obviously we can't
completely change our hair color so
yeah
good cue well I'm asking we'll see what
happens
we'll see if it's okay but I don't know
I don't know
I guess we'll find out
[Music]
I guess we will find out
yeah Kiara said you cannot change the
main color as it changes your image too
much but accents seem fine indeed
sense I want to try
I want to try
have you had lunch yet well it is the
dead of night so not quite lunch but I
have
some packs of energy
okay maybe I'll eat something real but
I mean I'm just also not very hungry you
know
with what outfit were you thinking of
having highlights my next one
my next one
I want a different hairstyle
and I want to give it accents
yep I've already I've already submitted
what I want so
but now seeing uh koala's outfit as well
I wonder if it would be cool to have
like some kind of like super Reaper for
them you know like not no longer
Apprentice of the Grim Reaper but like
the Grim Reaper you know
me moving up to be the Grim Reaper
especially yes some kind of like crazy
final form
super Reaper laughs
yeah I mean I already have I think I
have the most outfits in Ian right now
so let me just chill for a second I
think the new one it's very complicated
it's not it's not that it's very
complicated I put in a bit of a tall
order
um so it just it's gonna take
it's gonna take a bit of time isn't that
nezumori she wishes
yeah three this year just you know it
was a lot so
so let's let's chill a minute but
yeah I think um because it'll take a
while
um
the uh the so-called 2023 outfit might
be closer to the beginning of next year
but we'll see we'll see
now one of those outfits was a 1 million
uh wish
and I'm working on the second one right
now
I've kind of flip-flopped between a
bunch of stuff I obviously I can't
I can't uh tell you guys what it is I
wouldn't want to spoil it
right
mm-hmm
then you want to say you wanted to use
your second wish for the 3D model revamp
yes I did but
I'm not going to tell you quite how it's
going to be done I'm like not allowed to
talk about like the the stuff behind it
I guess the details the semantics
exactly how it's going to be changed Etc
but I think you guys will like it
I really think so
[Music]
so much stuff going on
I gotta get off Twitter there's just so
much stuff going on can't help but
scroll
okay don't tell us
keep it secret keep it safe
[Music]
you mean X I swear to God
I swear to God
Trader will do that to you get me out of
here
get me out of here
stop trying to make x a thing
I know you guys are just trying to rile
me up
what a weird why not the bird is the URL
Gonna Change please no
I can't I can't deal with that I can't
live with that
I beg please no
yes
maybe we will get some accents I don't
know it looks like it should be okay
maybe possibly potentially
oh oh come on baby don't be scared
let me retweet something
oh yeah thanks for the map whoa whoa
whoa whoa big memberships
50 gifted memberships jeez
thank you what the hell
thank you so much we're heading into
hour 15.
prettiest Blues
what a neat idea
nice gift gift a gift though thank you
kindly what a chad
everybody become Deadbeats or I'll kill
you and I'll force you to become a
deadbeat at that
give it up for hour 15 hour 15. well
this is officially the longest I've ever
streamed
officially so that's my new record
thank you very much Korean beat let's go
give it up for hour 15.
all right I need to sit up real straight
and then I'm gonna be massaging my
shoulders a bit
back to work
and back to lurking mode for me you're
doing great Cali Love The Clubhouse
gaming and drawing totsumachis thank you
Big Ups I'll try to keep it up keep up
the energy
we'll see
jump King woo
no I'm excited for it it needs to be a
challenge okay or else there's no point
I'm just gonna stretch a little bit
apology for bad English where were you
when Twitter die
I was at house eating Dorito when phone
ring Twitter is kill
no
what a shame
so only up that's cute
nope I've already made up my mind is
jumping
you will be playing jumping
proud of you champ
it was fun
according to Google the longest ever was
28 days LOL it means dream wise
I wonder hold on
wait but hold on there are like
sub-a-thons and stuff like that so I
don't know
longest stream ever
jump King the OG only up
now there's a dude that streamed for 634
days
it's the longest broadcast but I don't
know this person
yep
but they could have been like streaming
yeah like streaming music continuously
Lo-Fi music was like several years
stream technically I mean yeah that is
true
but it doesn't look like this person who
is this
somebody named GP
hustle who's more infuriating sucks a
bar bog man uh sucks bar because at
least bog man like
well hold on a second
annoying sucks a bar
likeable
uh most unlikable
bog man just because sucks who are kind
of like you know he
he's more interesting I think
stands for something you know
no they both say no
that is true
sucks a bar
well well well Detective
I wish that we could
I wish I really wanted to actually play
more uh games
um but sadly due to like rules and
restrictions and whatnot um I can only
play one game game per stream just
because of conflict of Ip Etc I'm not
allowed to have streams with multiple
games in them
anymore it's a new thing it's a newer
thing yeah so well well well Detective
sucks so far is worse because he hates
his lines but then he'll turn around and
say he loves them and be like haha
contradictions sure are funny
he's precociously enigmatic
yeah that's a word to describe sucksavar
who is saxabar you mean sexy bar
I need to I need to go back and say it
the right way
seems weird and silly unless you're
being sponsored yeah but
this is kind of how it is well well well
how intriguing pray tell
[Music]
sexy bars bit about the Assassins was
still my favorite thing in a way it was
pretty funny
to go from just chains of no to like a
monologue about like how they can try
and come and kill me they'll never catch
me alive
that was really funny
all right let me see hold on who did I
want to look I wanted to hold on a
second and I want to see I wanted to see
um
the yoga's channel
I want to see Bae eat these noodles
all right what do we got here
the Assassin Outburst floored me
pretty good
okay are they eating them let me let me
read the comments this is basically base
Suffering The Stream LMAO
really
you can watch the new leading on stream
I don't want to rebroadcast somebody
else's stream on my on my end but I'm
gonna listen a little bit
I'll hold an escape full screen
all right are they eating it yet
the rat just died stream on a stream now
I won't
let's see
um
[Music]
audio bleed
her react YouTuber now yada
I just want to see how hot these noodles
are okay you know what
instead here's what I'm gonna do
Google
and then ghost
how hot are ghost pepper noodles
one million it just says one million in
big letters
uh ghost peppers the spiciest instant
Ramen I think that this is yeah this is
the one that I have yup this is the one
I got
okay somebody made a blog post about it
diabok ghost pepper is the spiciest
instant ramen in the world real or not
okay so they got this noodles it's like
a gift it's a ghost pepper spicy chicken
dry black noodles in a cup thanks buddy
drink some milk before you eat this he
kindly cautioned alright so we're
ordering milk oh they say that if
jalapeno is spicy level 8 000
Scoville heat units ghost pepper is
spicy level 1 million
even jalapenos are like
I mean okay I can eat a jalapeno it's
like whatever I don't prefer to the cup
is peppered with intimidating words like
daring fear challenge flaming Madness
warning prey hard and risk
ghost pepper is a hybrid of capsicum
from Northeast India it is 400 times
hotter than tabasco's
what
it's bad but not that bad you say
jalapenos for babies it's pretty weak
for Scoville
uh let's see Guinness Book of World
Records crowned at the hottest chili in
the world in 2007 but it was dethroned
in 2011. the title of the hottest chili
in the world changes every few years
with ever hotter hybrids created so
there are just these these scientists
cooking like Mr White in his meth lab is
his lab
blah
cooking I'm sorry my brain is on
Breaking Bad excuse me just cooking
these new breeds
trying to create like a an instrument of
War
Jesus
don't let them cook
there's like one guy yeah the myth lab
that's what I meant to say there's like
one guy in the U.S all right so he opens
it up oh those really are just black
Peppers okay I eat raw chili peppers a
condiment since you were a child I see
felt a little intimidated left the cup
in the cabinet till today famish and
practicing social distancing finally
popped open the cup of ghost pepper
instant noodles
inside the cup there's a brick of dark
color instant ramen noodle a satchet of
sauce and also a disposable plastic fork
okay
University of New Mexico has a literal
lab dedicated to it
um
the instructions say add hot water and
let it soak for four minutes drain away
the water and squeeze in the sauce
there's about two tablespoons worth
I squeezed in everything
all of the day that's the way to do it
how was it flavor is a blend of robust
Savory spicy sweet I mean it sounds good
right the noodles were tender spongy
springy
typical of instant Ramen a subtle Taste
of wheat not much if any Grease
okay
the spiciness was at about level 8 out
of 10 for my palette the heat lingered
on the tongue and throat Rising
gradually to a 9 out of ten
towards the end I found myself breathing
just a bit quicker
panting a little with tongue sticking
out slightly trying to ventilate my
mouth to get some relief from the spicy
Heat
you won't feel the flavor after 20 to 30
seconds my eyes wetted a little they
were welling up on the verge of tearing
but did not as I was finishing the
noodles my salivary glands kicked in on
overdrive sending more saliva to my
mouth to try and dilute the heat oh my
God this dude ate all of the noodles
[Music]
I finished the noodles without bursting
the 10 out of 10 Red Line
drank a cup of room temperature water
and the spicy heat receded about 10 to
15 minutes later a stomach warmed a
little but there was no pain
don't don't tell us what happened
afterward we don't need to know
the madman spicy chicken Madness
wow
I see they still gave it a 5.5 out of
10.
[Music]
get him at Daiso for three bucks
why is this written like a fanfic it's
somebody's blog
it's just someone's blog
that's not the way it comes
the exact same way
yeah duh I don't I can't I don't know if
I can finish this like this guy but I
will eat them
I will eat them which noodle I missed it
it's called
ghost pepper
spicy chicken
and on the side there's like um
it's got like the Scoville units listed
gave birth to the sun yesterday
I'm not on a fan fiction website
Scoville heat unit for Peppers ghost
pepper is a million
orange habanero is at 350 000 Cayenne is
it 50 000. I like cayenne pepper
Cayenne Pepper's yummy so we just
multiply that by
20.
20 times the spiciness
#can or not challenge it says on the
side do you fear the ghost pepper take
the Dare and challenge other souls in
the depths of spiciness eat at your own
risk
milk and ice cream should help the burn
while I definitely also have ice cream
as well
spicy
thank you
confetti naika
mate
[Applause]
confetti here we go
oh
I'll do my best
do my best
soil
yariosai
hey JP Bros are you still awake a JP
Nikki
my eyes my bitrate
[Music]
still awake
[Laughter]
you do
um
foreign
[Music]
can you show the slippers I adore this
model okay
this sensei
[Music]
mm-hmm
my dad sends his slippers
I didn't really get to show off this
part
also you can see nothing
it's not see-through
it's not
for free for free
been listening to the stream all day
while at work it helped you pass the
time and helped keep you awake nice
nice
glad to hear it welcome anytime the
line's more visible than normal did it
get updated I don't think so
what line
I mean it's like a little tight around
that area but
I don't see like any
any pantsuit or anything
I don't think so I can't see
um
I don't know
I just don't know zoom in and show us
well
look there's nothing
it is firmly colored
are we gonna get another stream banned
please no
it's just a crease yeah exactly just a
crease no pants
no pants
I just wanted to prove I wanted to prove
it
that's all anyway
getting hyped for these noodles
give it a zoom you're welcome
now I've proved it it's just a crease
hmm
yup all it is is a crease
yep
a rare one guy w
ow surely
a favorite
okay a big stretch
oh
I'm not sleepy I'm not
um
Kiara
[Laughter]
Kiara responding to the T
to this the TK collab
oh yes our original song Together Dot
yup that's the one
that's the one uh the cats are really
going crazy out there what the kitty
cats doing
[Music]
Kiara was awesome early in the Stream
yeah she seems to be in good spirits I
love her new outfit so cool
I know she loves it too so
right
drink
slotted some cat ASMR
if I let the cats in here they will get
away they will get out of my arms and go
directly behind the computer and try and
tear the cords out
that's what they do that's what the
babies like to do that's their idea of
fun that's a game for them it's their
game
foreign
apply directly to cables apply cats
directly to cables
they can find the recorder
oh true
have them go in there and look around
oh fun aloud
[Music]
very aggressive
cats are like tasty cables
and get excused to replace the old
computer I am waiting for my PC case
I am waiting for it and it should fit
perfectly what are they doing
babies
stop messing around
oh boy okay
hold on
hold on a sec hold on a second let me go
get them
thank you
[Music]
foreign
okay we're good
ghost cat was being very
very bully to tutu
ghost cat was bullying tutu
so I have separated them and I've given
them treats
and now they will chill
they knocked many things over
yeah
yeah bullying No Bully No Bully
but I'm glad I'm glad I checked on them
so I could separate them
yeah because tutu she's so cute whenever
like she's been running away from from
ghost cats persistent quote unquote
attacks
no she's always very very Doki Doki you
know fast heart rate
so I'm letting them calm down for now
unrest a little bit
tutu doesn't fight back as well because
she's so small she's such a little girl
you know she tries she tries to but go
Scotty is a big boy so
but I have separated them and they are
taking a little time to calm down and
then I'll go ahead and let them back out
again
so if you go to her AC perch to escape
she like really picks and chooses when
she uses that so
so sometimes she runs up there but it
takes her a second to get up and she
actually doesn't go there as often
anymore I wonder if it's because she's
gotten bigger but yeah just a bit of
rough play yeah I'm just letting him
chill for a minute you know
it's been an exciting day with Mom not
in the house
or rather not in their vicinity right
they've been running around and doing as
they please and just non-stop running so
now we're gonna let him chill for a
little bit
it was it was cute when I was like
separating them putting them in there
putting them in their little homes their
little I said that they're small but
they're actually very big cages
um
I of course I give them treats because
you know I want I want them to know that
it's okay and
we're just going for a little chill
chill out time nap time in the cage just
for a minute if they're misbehaving
they're being naughty but I still give
them a treat right and I have these
treats that are kind of like tooth
brushing treats if that makes any sense
like when they eat them it like kind of
brushes their teeth for them it's hard
to explain but like they have to chew
them really hard and I think the treats
have like something that makes their
breath smell better
um and so I kind of break those up and I
give them
I give it to them and so I was getting
them out and then like I put ghost cat
away and then tutu sees me put ghost cat
away
um
she she sees me put him in there and
then she's like she's like going back
and forth between should I go get the
treat should I not she's gonna she's
gonna pick me up and put me put me for
my nap
so
put you in for the nap
but
yeah for a while actually the vet the
vet told me that
tutu is playing too much I guess
and that like she didn't know
she didn't know how to chill
and rest
and because I kind of didn't like how do
I say
I didn't like kind of the streets are
too strong
give her more opportunities to rest when
it's time to rest and whatnot you know
she she wasn't like growing properly
but that that's just what the vet said
the vet the vet told me that she was
playing too much and I need to keep her
in the cage more often
not necessarily more often but just
every once in a while like when it's
time for rest it's time for rest
it takes after mop
she likes to be up and at him all the
time
yeah so dude is just very restless but I
think that once they're fully adult cats
I won't need to do that at all anymore
it's just that while they're still
babies I kind of need to
let him have their rest time and then
their play time because when they are
out of out of the cages roaming about
they play like non-stop non-stop
non-stop even now
so but occasionally I catch glimpses of
them like sitting in various places and
I'm like okay maybe over time this will
get
this will get better
you know
oh wow big gift thank you very much
um
so you're saying you need to be put in a
cage to force you to sleep too
Maybe
I might need a cage
lock me in my room for a little bit and
I'll just play I'll play some Final
Fantasy VI and sleep
but they've got their water and their
food and their I give them some treats
because they're they're being good
babies Oh hopefully hopefully
I trust them to be good babies but
yeah I'm probably gonna get rid of the
cages in the next
couple months
because I think they'll be approximately
like a little over a year old
and so when things happen like um
like if there's like somebody that needs
to fix something in my house or
something like that
um I'll probably just put them in like a
room
I guess
yeah just put them in the room for the
for the time being or when I'm cooking
right because when I'm cooking
my stove has my stove uses fire
my stove uses fire and they love to get
near that and I don't like that so
yeah
yeah I have to uh probably put them in a
different room
but then that room will need to have
water and food and a litter box so yeah
they get really excited about the fire
they're so interested
so interested in it
so
cats they like the Heat
I gotta be careful and I'm always
checking the stove lock is on is the
stove lock on I'll check it like five
times a day I'll check it and then I'll
walk away and come back and check it
again
[Music]
looking for warmth
house is plenty warm it's Japanese
summer
but
yeah
oh shiny
the cat lost a few whiskers to a candle
when he was young yeah you gotta be
careful man I remember one time during
um a Thanksgiving dinner at Grandma
Reaper's place
cute little babies walking all over
walking around and I like I was looking
at like we were sitting down to eat
Thanksgiving dinner and I looked through
the corner of my eye
and I see one of the cats one of their
one of their fluffy kitty cats walking
towards like a candle that's like next
to the window
and I'm thinking to myself you're not
gonna go up to that are you and the cat
turns around and like the tail is right
over the flame and I jumped just in time
just literally just in time for it to so
like the fire the fire caught
fur and I jumped at exactly the right
time with a napkin and bet and batted it
out
and the poor Kitty ran away and from
that from that day on every Thanksgiving
dinner is fake candles
candles cats can be a little oblivious
oh thank God I was there God that was so
scary
I'll never forget that
poor baby
yeah so it was okay worried of the
rescue
Rory to the rescue
Slayer of humans but protector of
animals
so
yeah but she was okay she was okay she
was just a little I think that she was
more frightened of me like
hitting her with the with the
um cloth napkin I think that was what
what scared her it was really just like
I I kind of in a moment of desperation I
kind of like threw it onto like her tail
slash bottom half of her body
yeah I think that she was mostly kind of
scared of that but you know did what I
had to do
I did what I had to do even if she's a
little frightened of me from here on out
so
yeah
just a slight a slight twinge of bird
fur and I remember the grandma Reaper
like put her hand on her heart and was
like
it looked like she was about to pass out
yeah
I think I caught that not how Heroes
wear capes
oh geez an oven that was on and just
barely got backhanded away in time you
gotta what look I know that cats usually
land on their feet and they've got nine
lives and whatever
sometimes you should look out for the
cat
this one does I do wear a cape correct
correct I do
it's a hoodie cape
cloak even it's a cloak
not all heroes wear capes but some of
them wear cloaks
with monster teeth on them
yeah
like me
[Music]
protector of all kitty cats wood
I'm not sleepy
imagine if cats had opposable thumbs
that'd be terrifying for the world
I mean I think it'd be kind of Base to
be honest
I think that would be kind of cool
now where is my cellular device I
haven't checked that in a bit
[Music]
do
I'm a reading Mama Mori texts
reading Mama Mori texts I feel bad
because we haven't I haven't texted her
in a while I wonder if she even knows
that I'm streaming for 24 hours
hmm
[Music]
just scrolling through news
what do we have next on the schedule
long jump King time
long jump King
the pig long jump
I'll do my best
yeah
it'll be fun
I do want to see how far we get hey you
know what actually guys listen no shame
if we fall back down to the bog no shame
no shame
mm-hmm
go to sleep nope I refuse
I'm getting ahead of the shame yeah
[Music]
all right I'm finished updating myself
with news
so crazy how we can just look at a
cellular device
or like
Twitter for a second and just suddenly
you know like 50 new things that are
going on
oh I feel like I should hit it
oh
but no sleepy
what a world
I'm glad so many people are excited
about the TK song
it makes me happy
a lot of great things happening for the
holidays days
yeah
cool
the takanash Kiara song
I hope it'll I hope it'll um
I don't want to say live up to
expectations but I hope it'll be worth
the hype
lots of big news happening
do you plan on getting the figures of
yourself yeah I've ordered all the ones
that I can right Papa parade um
relax time I've also grabbed I believe
that I've pre-ordered the nendo I'm
pretty sure but anyway
excited to hear
ah
what was my shortest stream ever
[Music]
um oh I actually know what this is
it was rust
and I tried to play it in a place where
the internet was awful
or something like that
and it was about five minutes
the abandoned rust Street oh yeah the 4K
the 4K rust stream
uh it did not work and it broke my
internet for a day
yeah
that's what it was I was really mad
about that
I was like my internet's so good I can
stream in 4k and then I tried to play
Rust in 4k and then I couldn't stream
for the rest of the day
it was too
you cannot do this to me and it was an
experimental stream all right
that was something that had too much
faith and Tech yeah
had too much Faith in American internet
yeah I was in America at the time I'm
remember It's All Coming Back to Me Now
hmm
ASP [\h__\h] did not like that
six minutes long I see and it still
exists
I believe
wait did I private it I might have
privated it but I don't know
it is so bad in some areas for real
I must have privated it
I had to have
I was having a lot of problems with the
second base yeah it might be unlisted oh
yeah I think it was unlisted
yeah Japanese internet stability is no
joke it's it's much better than American
so
oh the rust one was six minutes the 4K
one was October and 13 minutes okay
those were separate streams
I'm getting it twisted in my head they
were separate they were separate okay I
remember now
different blunders
do you still have the second base I do
um
however I think that I'm going to
leave that at some point soon for
various
undisclosed reasons internet also being
one of them I can't properly work there
and like
I keep hearing
um
like especially Mama Mori is just like
no it's fine now I went today and you
know checked it out and it was all okay
but like
I don't know
but then whenever I go there and
whenever I try and stream right it
doesn't work so I think
um
I need to go somewhere else
there are a bunch of reasons but I'm
waiting until like the the you know the
lease is up the year is kind of done and
over with and then I mean hey I've got a
bunch of furniture and pretty much
already the the rooms are like designed
already so it just would be moving
living space
so
yeah good for casual Network use but
streaming is uh nah
nope
nope no good
oh
yeah that is definitely true you know
Mama Mori is like you know browsing the
internet checking emails and whatever
you know
but me I'm doing some different things
I'm downloading and uploading a
gazillion different huge files
streaming on top of that
it is a whole different Beast for real
yeah it's not quite as intensive
whatever she's up to
if only streaming was as simple as
checking emails yeah
it's a lot more fun
now Lean Back uh-huh lean back yeah time
to lean back
welcome new member welcome all my new
members we've gained a lot of new
members actually
sleep time uh nope don't pass out your
chair oh my eyes are wide awake
I mean wide open all right this is where
my speech is going to start failing
I can already tell my speech is gonna
start failing failing let's go
more members more Deadbeats we should
have another member's stream this month
get excited
more spriting and
MV drawing
I really gotta get to work on
I gotta get to work on that
now I have somebody who's gonna help me
make the video yata a very trusted
animator
um to do like typography and like the MV
editing and then I can focus on the
animation and art so
there's not much time left though so I
gotta get moving
Hi Maury Future Islands song is awesome
thank you for enjoying Future Islands
drink some Mountain Dew
no Mountain Dew only monster monster
pipeline punch
I can't wait to take the longest most
calming bath ever
and then
I'm gonna eat a tasty steak
because I can eat steak
interestingly enough the diet is like
yeah you want to eat steak do it
and the more like marbly the better the
more like fat that's in the steak it's
like yeah eat it don't sleep in the bath
okay I'll sleep before the bath how
about that
Mountain Dew Kickstart actually isn't
bad I've never heard of that is that
like a similar to an energy drink
yup all protein and fats diet A5 wagyu I
looked it up and that's that's expensive
though that is an expensive steak I
don't need to eat wagyu every day
I don't need that but you know what as a
celebration for streaming 24 hours you
know what maybe I will get a nice Wagyu
steak it's not like I'm eating that
every day but
after a 24-hour stream maybe it's
deserved
A5 is hella good you don't need to but
it's good
a reward for a long streams work
hmm
maybe I'll get a steak
yeah I'll do it
steak time
wag you no wag me if you aren't treating
yourself are you really taking care of
yourself good point
good point and I promised you guys that
after the 24 hour stream I would take
care of myself
so we'll do
um
just get sleep instead of staying bro
you make it sound so easy
well
steak and potatoes I can't eat potatoes
I know I'm starting to forget what
potatoes taste like and it hurts
ah especially golden brown potatoes mmm
with the skin
steak and eggs is good because eggs are
okay too
no mashed potatoes
no boiled potatoes no baked potatoes
no fries
not allowed
Bacon's good too though yeah which is
interesting because I was really never a
bacon person
like ever
but now it's like I kind of have to eat
bacon and I think I'm starting to kind
of like it a little bit you know bacon
and avocado all the time
on the grind
it's really encouraged me to like get
excited about cooking actually
um
I'm cooking all kinds of recipes now
because I mean I guess that's the thing
about about the keto diet right when you
do that stuff is like
you have to
you can't just order food anymore you
can't just go to the convenience store
you have to cook let her cook let me
cook
you you really have to cook so
but it's like it's like a fun hobby
you know
it's become like um
a Pastime for me
Avo bacon and smoked salmon on toast but
what kind of toast
you can have 50
yeah 50 grams of carbs is okay
so
you could have one fry with your steak
no no I need I need to save that carve
allowance for like
vegetables and the like
so
that cook is fun
isn't cooking a fun hobby
cooking's fun Hot Chip
Jessie we need to cook keto diet Jesse
medium carbs better cook
ing is like decorating an empty canvas
it's fun way to get creative with what
you want to do creativity is fun as long
as in the end you can you know you make
something that you're proud of maybe
it's not all that tasty but you know
da da
oh
[Music]
I started off just doing like low carb
which is nice but I want to be in that
ketosis you know
that's where you want to be
toast
it's a very strict diet
because if you go over the 50 you're
pretty boned
really don't want to go over that
really don't want to go over that fitty
pan soy kabutsu
[Music]
don't let the Sleep take you I won't
what's that uh it's carbs in Japanese
in an alternate universe Breaking Bad is
a culinary drama
if you're craving potatoes I've heard
you can use rutabagas as a low carb
substitute I've thought about trying
that when I got your debt when you got
your diabetes diagnosis let me look that
up
rutabaga
[Music]
how does that look oh
rutabaga or Swede
Swede is a root vegetable
let's see else for the name turnip
usually refers
to the relate oh okay other names
include turnip but however elsewhere the
name turnip usually refers to the
related white turnip
the species Brassica Naples
what a name originated as a hybrid
between the cabbage and the turnip
it looks kind of yummy low-key not gonna
lie how to cook rutabaga easy mashed
rutabagas mashed rutabaga with sour
cream and Dill that sounds good but what
is the tons toy cavatsu on it
creamy hearty and frugal
what is rutabaga sort of large turnip
The Taste is people's Maiden turn off is
it not good
um
not block notifications I don't need
that
you love rutabagas
you gotta make it right okay
let me check this parsnips are great
now never wait have I tried a parsnip I
don't think so
here this teaches you how to cook it
right
can you cook rutabaga with a skin on
unlike turnips rutabaga should not be
cooked with the skin so you have to
completely skin them
ooh rutabaga fries look good these low
carb fries are a godsend for those
following the keto lifestyle they're
also a healthy alternative when you're
craving fast food
rutabaga fries
now the question is where to find
rutabaga in Japan
wow
it says less carbs I wonder how many
less and then of course loaded with salt
because you need that sodium
listen to me
I sound like a
I sound like a freaking housewife or
something oh yes that's right yes low
carbs
you have to cook them right yes
like I'm talking with the ladies at the
Country Club
Jesus
diatoga just feels depressing I don't
know I kind of get excited about it
because it's like an activity I guess
cooking at least talking about cooking
for it
I do not have diabetes I do not I was
reading somebody else's message
let's see um
where to buy
rutabaga in
pan
Japanese vegetables
they have kabu which is turnips
wait uh maybe we might need to
substitute with turnips
anyway
that's something to look up another time
I will look it up properly another time
another time
oh man everybody's flipping about the X
everywhere I look
they hate it oh the people have spoken
they really don't like it
can I comment on the the teaser thing
that was posted no I'm literally not
allowed to
I asked
believe me I asked
so
oh well
guess we'll wait and see I just gotta
pass the time
[Music]
well Kiara already did well she wasn't
allowed to
I'm not going to get in trouble I don't
care who has said what I'm not going to
get in trouble
nice try chat I'm not gonna do the same
song and dance with the costumes and the
outfits and the Jesus
I don't risk it
you said quote unquote nothing
smartly circumvented it
uh
is this high tide it is
[Music]
she can just say it was the altar Kiara
not even for the biscuit
there goes my dad and he said it's okay
let's talk about
seems legit
what if I just ring up you go right now
oh my dad works the cover
I can't even have biscuits chat those
have carbs and true facts
my dad works recovery said it's fine
pulling you in like gravity something
something you are on your knees you
won't call you a go at 4am
laughs
you want to test me
I'll do it I'm no coward
because if I don't have your ghost phone
number
uh so I can't
and I doubt that you go is just
on Discord or something like that at 4am
no
hey Callie got my first P rank in Pizza
Tower yesterday congrats that that
probably takes a lot of work
nice hey congrats to you
he gets up early to run you think 4am
early it's about to be 4am
we're almost there
maybe I should retweet the teaser with
like a little comment on it like
like ooh or IDK
laughs
I wonder what it is
what could this be G
I don't know
I sound so done
yep
I wonder what it is
not about to be in breach of contract
not me
not I
don't
[Music]
dang
I will say though I will say
showing showing that
much stuff right there for that thing
[Music]
is it a choice
is a choice
[Music]
I am your girl on my private account I
give you permission to reveal whatever I
told you to chat so this net and all
that um
it showed a lot
I just feel like
I would have tried to keep it more
mysterious
but
oh well
the choice
I wonder if there's more
oh my God it's the man himself
remember Miss teaser video and Kiara's
scuffed Mike
I feel so bad about that
I am timeless
sorry Kiara
it wasn't I swear to God it had to have
been the way that it was set up because
that was a good mic
maybe the preamp was wrong
something was off there those were the
days I am death itself
[Music]
yeah no no fancy animations back in the
day but
I don't know man there was still I don't
know
I wouldn't trade it for the world
I legit I thought you
from the teaser no way
I am death itself we know that wait I'm
kind of mixing up the I am time I am
death itself hold on
no no no no no no no no
hang on I want to see this
do not play Connect the world
go back to the first video on the CH on
the channel
listen to it
the time is now voiced
oh my God
Jesus
welcome to the shark side
or the powers of depths join
come to the shark's side oh that's what
it was come to the shark side
[Laughter]
and death meets eternity
I am death itself
it doesn't sound a little ESL
great
God
oh I'm a Time
it's Elementary ain't it
oh lordy
it all sounded so different back then
all are invited to witness the myth
yeah look at those pngs floating across
the screen
ain't it not eating it I know missed
opportunity
hello live English
these little creepy laughs at the end
there
hold on say it say I am death itself one
more time
I am death itself
what is this
who is who is that lost young reap I
don't know who that is
ah time for the next stream
uh I don't know who that is
good times though good times
the self is very stressed
yeah a little known fact about that that
entire thing
um
there were a lot of spelling mistakes in
the original teaser
we had to really kind of kick and scream
to be like hey
it's not power of depths joints
what is this
the jfiku no I wasn't
it wasn't even JP that made it or rather
the JP side it was not
Focus ocean
stop Parker's ocean is Iconic
um all right off we go
yeah depth joints something like that
yeah in the beginning I was I was the
grip Reaper support
anyway good times good times
um I will be I will be back shortly
we're gonna play Jump King
and then go into the challenge part of
the stream get ready I'm energetic hey
let's go the grip
yeah grip around your throat as I
strangle you to death I'll see you soon
be be back in a moment in the next
stream bye
[Music]