[Music]
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
questions
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
Mickey
look
my ah my glasses are fixed you're
[Music]
um yay
cute right I know
oh
oh no now there's a new bug
no man whatever we'll ignore that
because I want to wear my glasses
that wasn't there before Eva hmm
oh wow
yeah besides that I think maybe we're
good
don't tell us yeah yeah yeah yeah don't
look
oh don't look how did you not see it was
pretty obvious oh well
[Laughter]
never mind
I will be
I will be I mean I guess if I take off
the oh
if I take off the
hair pins then there will be no bug with
the hairpins
unless
[Laughter]
yeah okay
okay no no hair pants then
easy solution
orange juice
[Music]
um
no no no no no no no
ripbot no it doesn't matter it's okay
it's okay
sorry guys I'm a bit tired but
um we're doing a cozy stream
[Music]
let me I think I'll use the bgms from
yesterday
those were pretty good
um
[Music]
let me throw them in there
wow
perfect
yo yo
same you just woke up oh hi yo good
morning
they weren't annoying that's good I mean
they're um they could be a little bit
repetitive but I have like five
different ones so
gotta go to work in an hour but I'll
listen background thank you
good evening from the UK hello oh my God
more more I need more European viewers
more
come here to Mommy come to Mommy come to
the European side
I want to have you guys
come here come here be mine greetings
from Greece oh I really I'm like so
close to booking a solo trip to Greece
man
oh I really want to go
because and I'm feeling like
but maybe it's it it should be fine
because if I look if I think back
if I think back to my trip with rmt of
course it's more fun with her but if I
think back like basically what we did I
can do that solo I thought you know I
would feel awkward like going to a
restaurant if in the evening alone and
all that but then I think back of the
places that we went to in hindsight I
don't think I would feel so awkward
about places like that being there alone
um wow Belgium Bulgaria what
are you guys like is there anybody here
who's like watching because they got to
know me through the neurosama collab
that's a good question
okay
oh
no don't lie to me you guys have badges
from long time ago
don't mind it was a serious question
kinda okay you I kind of believe
what's a Liars yeah
we got to know you through it though
so you did what
oh
no but this is my first key watch this
is your first Chihuahua's dream huh
I only know never because of you
oh
this is my first stream I'm a new
badges
God damn it I've never seen this chicken
before my yeah yeah yeah [\h__\h]
I don't even know what a YouTuber is I
thought this was Dr disrespect what was
that I think I heard that before maybe
what is that
who is that
pay no attention to the Phoenix badge
that's not helpful I am paying attention
to it
twitch streamer
oh first time
[Music]
hello I've been so up to you for years
now but never seen a stream before I
guess it's like a bot subscribe to you
instead of you doing it yourself it just
so happened right okay
asking questions is
is
yeah leading nowhere
uh why was I oh yeah
um
guys guys oh
[Music]
I have it's still muffins guys how long
after you bake a muffin yourself until
you shouldn't eat it anymore
this they tasted way better when they
were like fresh and still a bit warm of
course
they did they're okay now awake oh okay
okay yeah I mean they don't they don't
taste weird also but
they tasted so much better when they
were fresh but how am I supposed to eat
was in like one sitting huh
alone oh
yeah
impossible
you invite people over now I know but
I could bring it to them but
[Music]
um
it was so spontaneous you know
and part of me was thinking oh eating
all of this in two days would be no
problem at least six today and six
tomorrow I think I almost ate six in the
in the first day after I made them they
were so good
I thought I will I'll keep these all to
myself
gotta make it worthwhile then the
blueberries day
like give off so much color my muffins
are like blue and purple
[Music]
um
I don't refuse them ah if you freeze
them do you bake them again in the oven
or do you just let them sit in room
temperature for a while or so
Ollie hello
what
yeah yeah okay yeah yeah
that's how zombies enjoy muffins I guess
oh these are still good
um because I still have the including
the one I'm eating right now I still
have five
damn what the hell
um
should I put some of them in the freezer
like do you put them in like a plastic
box or do you wrap them and
foil or
um
[Music]
no they'll be gone soon enough yeah
probably I think by tomorrow they'll be
gone
I just I was gonna eat them for
breakfast today but then I decided to
eat my dinner leftovers instead which
are more Savory but I kind of felt like
some something Savory for once
[Music]
okay I will not freeze these ones but
maybe the next batch
I'll make chocolate ones next
[Music]
the frozen pizza was lame
oh
chocolate no not chocolate buns I was
saying chocolate ones um
oh yeah I could combine chocolate banana
muffins right
I want to try the banana muffins as well
you need like old bananas I have old
bananas all the time
and I don't even buy like a big bunch of
bananas no no
um
I buy like
free
and then I'm like um
I'll make sure to eat them all this time
that's why I only buy so little
um
but they go ripe immediately
and it's kind of even worse when you
um
when you put them into the fridge
I feel like
for some reason they ripe even faster in
the fridge
so putting them into the fridge makes
like helps not at all
buy them green yeah but what if I want I
buy them normally because I have a
craving for a banana
so I want to eat the eat it right away
but I should basically because I can
like pick it off of the different like
you know banana
packs so I should buy I guess two green
ones and one normal one the normal one
I'll eat that day
the green one hopefully edible by the
next day
um
foreign
dark and cold places
um
I even bought like one of those banana
hanging thingies
it doesn't happen oh
partially I feel like it made it even
worse than just laying it down
I [\h__\h] products we do not put but of
course not yeah I know that but you know
I thought maybe at home it should be
helpful
um
yeah bananas are difficult man
okay
next time I have a ripe banana I make
banana muffin
[Music]
okay last bite oh
um
what
was that
museum is destroying my brains as other
Brandy what
really
how this is not soap
not so brain cells destroying
no no I just finished one now I have
four muffins left
I'm the muffin man
everybody
so welcome back to my until yeah
[Music]
my
My Shabby but uh still cute
at the layer actually this is so cool to
have I mean it doesn't even have a
toilet
the whip we still in this game can get
higher than this ride in terms of like
living environment I think I think look
at ow maybe we can even go back to our
own Island
um
I thought this was possible haha
okay
well well well after I played this last
time I got kind of addicted right and
then I played I drew some stuff
but really only like a little bit to
grind like this cat
this originally this was like a NPC
drawn cat and they asked me to improve
it
and I was like uh-huh sure because it's
not the stream I didn't record effort
much into it but I think it turned out
cute
and I
uh the restaurant wanted like a
a little something like a advertisement
poster
and I think
my the way I kept it like simple the
Simplicity of it made it look actually
so good
I feel like it cuts off the beginning
um in these time lapse but
I started off it's a cheeseburger guys
it's a cheeseburger
I started off with like uh the
to make a Shadow before even sketching
anything I knew that I would put a plate
there
uh yeah put the shadow there isn't
doesn't that look so good and then yeah
I put the cheeseburger there
kind of missing the bird yeah but huh
it's a cheese and the burger uh bread
buns
yeah only cheese
no no meat
I thought that was pretty genius looks
really good simplistic uh oh I drew some
flowers but ignore those and ah the cat
was also
oh yeah yeah yeah
the cat
meow that's me that looks like me
but no it's chunkers the last thing you
see before you die
yeah cute
I think I posted this time lapse also
and then of course
I drew Ahmed and it took forever I spent
so much time with this
I think the line art that I did the
sketch
looked so pretty
and then I filled in the colors well
also on purpose getting rid of some of
the lines and just drawing over I just
had to remember where I had those lines
I've turned blue because I knew I was
gonna replace everything anyway
um
and I used some new tools for this like
the watercolor
um
oh and I had so many new palettes for
this I had the gray one the monochrome
one and some the the skin tone one
Etc yeah this took so long I was so
proud of this
um
almost didn't want to sell it and I felt
bad about selling it now because I feel
like later in the game when you have
even a better reputation they might pay
more for this just because you have a
better reputation but I feel like now I
got 2 000 out of it and that's like
pretty much I'm sure
like one of the best prices you can get
right now
[Music]
I don't know
um
yeah yeah these NPCs appreciate good art
bring in the big bucks yeah actually
there was just one we offered two
thousand and the others were all around
like 1 300 400 or so I was like nah no
no no no no come on somebody and I was
patient enough eventually somebody came
by to offer 2 000.
[Music]
but I feel like it would be even more
worth I'm just being kind of capped by
by the game right now by the progress
anyway I wish I wish there was a way of
seeing all the quests I have right now
um
because I don't remember
now it's been a couple days since I
played
guess we gotta ask everybody what I
already accepted did I accept something
for you
George Museum sign
I remember the time when artists
traveled did I really accept this as a
quest
no I don't think so no no no no
this is not a quest yet
honey
here is more like a colander Sparkle
what Sparkle spark will fix it easily
with some duct tape and putty
aha putty what
what am I gonna use that for
[Music]
I have hair long Punks on me Banky drama
a graffiti artist
uh do you want something okay thank you
like pen store Ben got all dope stuff
like spray cans and spray cans and stuff
okay I don't think he has a quest for me
I think I accepted like two or so maybe
upstairs
let me check the trash can
nice maybe it's from Banky again
spray cans and spray kids I went you oh
ah oh yeah right something like for a
flag I need to get information from
three certain people for the flag tell
again you need to hear Gabrielle's ideas
about the flag before making it
Gabrielle you need to listen to what
Harry has to say it's important for the
flutter design
and LOL LOL Gabrielle Harry and LOL
uh I feel like I talked to one of those
maybe but I'll I'll try let me see
you're Emily
I don't think
yeah currently she has nothing for her
the the cat was for her but I gave it to
someone else oh wait there's a fan
where's your fan
this fan has seen better days poor thing
completely dented in Russia but spark
can probably make a try again
um
what
a pepper nice free art materials let's
go
team the cave pillow yeah I wonder I
mean for this one this seems a little
bit special oh
it seems like I really have to you know
get everybody's ideas in first but what
I draw in the end probably doesn't
matter
probably
hi George
ah okay he has some things for me
repairs
ah no wait I don't need the broken shelf
yet no no no that's just uh what about
the other thing
a pothole oh wait this is a bug I think
because I already fixed a pothole but he
keeps asking me and even when I say pay
it doesn't deduct money though I don't
know why I even tried I was like did I
did I not pay it yet
um
do you have the game on your own yeah
yeah cause last time we we figured that
there is barely any bgm in the game
um
yeah this is a bug
I I don't think this is normal he keeps
on that because at one point the pothole
thing was gone from his dialogue but now
it's there again it's kind of weird
[Music]
because up there was the pothole
now after John we fixed it we fixed it
anyway look there's now my my
advertisements of the cheeseburgers
right there
yeah if you want something probably not
yeah because I just finished your quest
yeah
I didn't show you guys yet upstairs here
there is a Maggie does Maggie have
something for us
oh no
okay there's this little pretty Park
guys look it has a pond
it's nice oh you can change some stuff
in the radio but it's also very quiet
there's nice flowers and plants
Bull Street
wow wow I love how the birds keep on
flying around
oh I wonder if one day my art will be on
this thing
let's search again
okay this time nothing
Aya and here I can't go over yet because
I need six tools at least which do I
have it now
no but I think we're close I think I
have like five tools Maybe
yeah they really added so much
up here I can go but as you can see so
there's still areas and I still can't go
to
pretty impressive uh Gabrielle you are
one of the people I needed to talk to
flag
one of the bad Flags I don't think we've
ever had one that you could be proud of
oh you're making a new one could you
make it feel fresh something we're not
ashamed about
um
not really I mean I'd just like to be
able to pose in front of it without
shame
I can join the ceremony and my mother
would drag me there anyway
okay something fresh that's really not
very specific
okay
oh and I need to ask you too LOL
good one
Community flag it should be black
completely black oh black and fresh
who
and then black dark dark gray
okay
if you promise the flag that makes those
lovely people cry I'll surely be there
to watch
I promise I'll see you there
hey
black gray and fresh
I think the NPCs
like green
as fresh maybe like a light green
so if I mix like
maybe a black background with something
green on top of it or so oh Godfather no
no no we're not gonna drop fauna again
uh this is uh another funny buddy he's
blocking off another part straight I
think
I already talked to him he's really
weird though
there was one more person we need
something we need to ask and probably
that person also has something
contradicting to say
what are we looking for
what's up what was the last person
actually let's go to spark because he
can fix some things for us
uh the scrap
Wicked the pain from free battles is
going to be wild give me a second to
mount it
what oh those things were uh ah items
too
for that thought Quest oh
it froze paint an impressive Suite speed
of 2 84 kilometers per hour
we'll try it out whatever you can have
it I build stuff I don't use them so
this is another tool
a brand new power tool
maybe you should tell smell that you're
done she tends to worry over unfinished
business oh okay
what
what can we do with that
how did you do I'm done oh sweet I hope
Spock is happy and soon right I haven't
got to do that yet she'll need to wait
Paul wanted to help delivering stuff
flashing in someone to listen to his new
routine Maggie had some questions
regarding her school
do I need to remember this
yes I know I really need to learn to say
ah it's so hard no
yeah I mean no anyhow let me reward you
no another choice I I don't know what to
give you canvases or money buff
no can I say both let's leave it to
chance and again play Rock Paper
Scissors if you win I'll give you
canvases if you lose you'll get the
money
I guess both is fine
yeah okay
maybe I can get both if we get the same
pepper
keep on getting the same as him
nah try should mean I guess both man
um
I'm such a mind reader I understand
A.I apparently I wonder why
I guess
no it's not right I know ah okay I went
oh I can choose Maybe
I got canvases Okay small I want big
ones because I realized I can draw more
detailed on a big canvas because it's
basically like zooming in
which I can't do but I can just get a
bigger canvases yeah now
I was infected by noodle chanya she has
given me knowledge about AI
hope flash you guys are not the ones
either maybe the third person is behind
I think so
beautiful art
it needs to be beautiful go to Benjamin
let him just to paint ah
wait did I already paint something for
that
no but oh what is this sketch
wait
this one I got from the trash or they're
already coming I'm not selling anything
guys
cute
wait so flash once
Something Beautiful
and I need to bring it to George
no wait not you
hope
shouldn't accept these quests when I'm
not gonna do them right away
I'm supposed to react to it not deliver
an opinion it needs to be beautiful go
to Benjamin let him judge the painting
if it's beautiful come back to me
Benjamin Benjamin
I don't have something
yet
let's Draw Something Beautiful
how
how can we know it's beautiful
Benjamin
it wasn't Benjamin one of the Free
People I had to ask anyway about the
flag
look in the mirror
um Benjamin let's talk
ah yeah okay no he doesn't have the flag
thing um okay okay you want something
beautiful
I'll draw it show me when you're ready
then I'll be here all it needs to be is
beautiful okay I guess
that could be anything let me check your
tools really quick
I've so I bought the watercolor last
time I think after the stream it was
really disappointed because I I realized
oh man it's
um
it's it doesn't like go specifically
where you put your mouse no
it's like sprinkles it around that area
and that is very unfortunate
I think the sponge looks like you can
use it precisely and that would be more
useful
and I've oh my God I have so much money
I tried to not make too much money off
screen but I can't help it I need to
make sure
that
I
that I don't give away my paintings too
cheap
I thought it would turn out brilliantly
what do you mean
you're still digging for trash yeah I
I I still have like I don't know I feel
like I should save money you know
in in real life too
I'm still careful of like how much money
I spend
um
okay okay
then
I guess we'll use since this is a quest
thing let's just use a cheap
cheap something not a bad habit right
so what do we draw guys beautiful
um
[Music]
beautiful
we shouldn't draw the same people away
to her last time
oh I want to draw Ollie yeah
yeah I'm I'm I want to I want Ollie to
feel beautiful
where's my phone let me get a reference
that's a good idea
that is a really good idea
let's make only feel uh but again
actually
um I don't want to put so much effort
into paintings that I won't be selling
God damn it whatever it's for the sake
of the Stream
okay but let's not go too crazy on it
okay let's not go like crony levels
crazy on it like I did last time
I say now then I probably will anyway or
like at my levels I will I probably will
okay which version of her should we draw
should we draw
um
[Music]
I wanna draw her
with straight hair
but
I want to combine her straight hair with
with a
her like princess outfit you know which
one I mean
no not Olivia because Olivia
if we draw Olivia that would mean to
ollie that Ollie is not beautiful to me
even though she is
that would imply that I only find Olivia
beautiful
can't do such a thing
wait my
oh that's the new thing
oh that's cool it's random but um
that's cool like for a cool background
like a graffiti background
and surely
the punks will love it
should I just sell this
see what they think of it
here
I mean wait no we should spend at least
some more time with it because
um
I know they have a Time
uh a time a Time algorithm
[Music]
abstract coolness right it's abstract
it's fun it has um uh a cool new tool
how do I spend more time with this I
what if I'm what if I'm not actually
actively drawing I wonder if that still
counts as me spending time on it
hmm
I don't want to do anything else though
this looks good to me
Splatoon
I'm meta gaming
it needs more red
one do you know the AI is
I tell you that
yo this better not yeah it's all right
there you go that's too much man it was
better before
[Music]
um
looks like ketchup
God damn it can I name this
let's name it whatever even if it's just
a little bit of money I don't even need
that much money anyway what a weird Flex
um
what's it called what what was it gonna
I asked Platoon
Splatoon
let's sell Splatoon while we think about
what we're really gonna draw
um oh yeah and uh let me already get
skin
colors and I have so many different
colors
[Music]
I think that's good I think that's good
oh someone coming in but I don't think I
like it only the punks like this kind of
art I think
there's one to other the background I
did the background of a different tool I
don't know if they recognize that yeah
the old people they don't get it
I'll draw on paper
[Music]
what do you think Punk
I think they like it oh okay yeah that's
so cheap compared to how I think they
definitely recognize how much time I
spend on it because for Ahmed they would
give me like 2 000.
um I'll wait for another Punk
[Music]
but yeah better than nothing sure
basically I made money out of nothing
there George at least wants to support a
struggling entrepreneur how nice
still it was still a background
[Music]
ah what what Steve what the [\h__\h]
maybe that wasn't considered abstract
for the punks
yet
and I guess the the I think the chef has
his own algorithm it's different from
like George
the chef likes different things
um
[Music]
what okay
I got the the base for that painting
from the trash can
okay
um
[Music]
I'll be looking at the design from only
from her
from her from her what's it called I
don't even know what it's called what is
it called
make the background like bluish I think
[Music]
a reference sheet from the
cute princess outfit that one shocked me
so much when she revealed that I was
like what
[Music]
amazing amazing
okay I think the whole putting a blob
down
um
strategy worked pretty well because
otherwise
otherwise we have to be careful about
the lines
[Music]
okay let's start
let's begin
also I have six tools now we can go for
that new area I don't know what to draw
just
something simple I guess it's okay
[Music]
because it's so bright why is my my
tablet feels so bright to me today
at least these bright colors look so
bright surprise
[Music]
make up a new outfit now
oh by the way I wrote to Kaila I
apologize about the killing of
um well
her NPC
she said no problem no problem
no worries
wait wait she has a different skin she
ah wait for for Ollie I don't kind of
need my monochrome colors
[Music]
actually
skin color is gray like a I mean some
some are a little bit different but oh
it's actually gonna make it difficult
[Music]
is the the lighter one
um
the lighter one feels like it has a
little bit of a
Violet pink tone undertone but I don't
think we have that
I'll go with this one or nah
nah yeah okay I'll go with that one
okay
that would be the base
and then
like vampire skin is also closer to
white van Piana ah yeah yeah it's like
she has like makeup
all over
[Music]
again
this
this will be the basic shape basically
oh background looks like a pretty sky
oh yeah totally that's exactly what it
is
um do we have
fitting
hair color okay maybe not right now
it's like a hot pink almost red and I
have something between hot pink and red
and then a lighter pink I have to check
my pals I can probably just go with
these two where's guys
okay
and you know what
uh Zeta also messaged me
Santa also messaged me
what did she say
[Music]
that road to me
oh yeah she sent me a clip you know
and that says yeah I didn't expect Zeta
to be this kind of person
the perfect thumbnail
and she wrote in caps lock they're safe
I promise I love cats
[Music]
don't know about that
I broke her heart excuse me she broke my
heart
[Music]
I actually really like this technique it
works well
girl wants to get on girl talk Girls
Talk
um
but you know I I don't know on
um I think if you watched the the whole
stream
then I feel like you would you would get
it
but wait I kind of want to have her eyes
closed you know
oops I think like maybe in some clips
um this not this one but I think in some
clips maybe some some Kyla films maybe
like maybe took what I have been saying
a little bit too seriously I'm I'm sorry
about like in hindsight I also feel like
kind of bad about
um like
saying so much
yeah
um like roasting her so much
in hindsight I'm I'm sorry
it was a bit too much maybe
um I want to say sorry but
I think overall if you were watching the
stream you you kind of get
I mean
but I think no it wasn't all jokes but
the thing is like I was kind of
influenced by all the things I've heard
and like the clips and so on that I've
seen
which were always like giving me this
um image of Kaila that she's like
absolute
insanely crazy when it comes to building
things
and yeah my my image of her was like
over the roof like insane and yeah she's
I've I realized
um her Focus isn't much on building like
one huge insane building no he wants to
build I guess several many like
cool things
but it's not so much about yeah I mean
yeah it's definitely about the flex when
you look at the the
um
I need her her hair what does your hair
look like there
it's not so much about
um I don't know what's the best way to
describe it
oh
because I actually can see the The Raid
ah I don't have it on thank you for the
rain
uh anyway I don't know I I I I I I just
want to say like my image was probably
quite influenced that was problem number
one
[Music]
and
then again also uh the problem of
um
[Music]
yeah uh
I was I was also trying to cheer up
Ollie yeah but not only
not only but yeah I hope I Ollie
although I think that's also just a joke
on her side mostly I hope she felt
um you know
happy
[Music]
I think I kind of get where she's coming
from I think it's a joke but maybe like
somewhere
somewhere deep within she does kind of
maybe feeling like that too only a
little bit but mostly it's a joke but
then you know
I think I kind of maybe Loki get it so
maybe I can
cheer her up you know
so we're gonna have her like smile
I don't know I don't know like uh last
time I was like so warmed up now I don't
know
[Music]
um which colors to use I guess for her
it really should be
these monochrome colors
even for lips and stuff damn it
um
should be a little bit more dark but
whatever this works
yeah I hope nobody got really mad I'm
sorry if it came across as as mean I
didn't want to roast Kaila that much but
uh
I think she'll take it she'll take it
light-heartedly
looks cool
good
okay
does this look like Ollie yet
I think her
her skin color is very distinctive so
should be recognizable at least
[Music]
do you think you'll play more Minecraft
after the weather
hmm good question
I don't think I'll play as much as I
used to maybe maybe for a little while
maybe there will be a Minecraft influx
for a little while
but generally
[Music]
thank you hello
there's a pretty big update coming this
summer ah I heard about the cherry
blossom by all means yeah
let's try the sponge
oh the sponge is kind of big
[Music]
no
the smallest form of the sponge is also
so big ow man
[Music]
I had the watercolor also just goes see
it just goes wherever God damn it
difficult but whatever
there's a new type of bamboo wood coming
as well so I saw a picture of of the
like cherry blossom stuff and I'm
wondering I'm wondering
do you actually get like pink colored
wood out of it
that's gonna be like so cute
yeah I thought maybe it's an edit
that's that that's real amazing
[Music]
yeah that's pretty hype
pink wood let's go
maybe that was Sparky building desire
again
[Music]
no
what else comes with that something that
I can use for adventuring
what else comes with that update do we
know
[Music]
you can also make grafts and right
camels I can fried camels and where it
rafts for instead of a boat you mean
like a bigger flat boat basically or
what man I need to watch a trailer
oh
yeah I guess finding the new materials
if they're rapper
um rare then yeah that will be a
challenge
camels so they show up in the desert I
guess
that's nice that's cool
[Music]
technical
new Armor Designs oh
so if we made building too stressful for
you no not at all it's just like I find
it like you know when I build something
like like pixel art for example then
it's like a set design that I keep on
having to look at and it's like it it
takes what the [\h__\h] am I doing with this
ear
it takes so much like Focus
it takes too much focus and
[Music]
um
yeah
on stream I feel like that is
not very good for me
um
and if it's like you know freestyle like
building a house or something
yeah that's all right but still like
boring why would I build another house
when I already have a house you know
what I mean
I don't need another house and
oh yeah
[Music]
it just makes no sense to me
why would I do that
tons of new types of Armor Designs
coming
[Music]
everyone needs a summer Cottage
nah I don't storage but I don't need
storage either an unreal I mean only if
I start organizing things really well
uh
but um
okay let's do
God damn it I don't like these brushes
this is still not ideal
hmm
oh well I want to draw her hair do I
have any better
color for that maybe no
the Lush Forest ones also look too too
pink
I wonder if I can buy a new one
there was something red focused I think
I might have the money so let's go
maybe clean up Phoenix in a bit
no I think it's time to give up on
Phoenix tonight it's useless now it's
basically what
I mean by accident
it was cheap I guess no I wanted to look
at wait where do you get
where do you get the huh
where do you get the recipe is the color
recipes
[Music]
foreign
recipes in here
did I buy them all
huh
the punk
oh I guess so
okay
um anyway yeah I think until uh tears of
the kingdom comes out I might play a bit
more Minecraft
than usual
because we're gonna We want like shorter
games and stuff like that anyway
we have okay bye I'll buy them all
done you have no more
[Music]
one was pastel colors apparently and one
is romantic colors
[Music]
no I don't have plans for Crusader Kings
yeah spontaneous clevers yeah now now
don't get my hopes up
[Music]
hopes up what if
this is not gonna happen again
I hope so but hmm
[Music]
you know I was really a genius
when I chose my
my recipes for this week
I already forgot about it but when I
arrived I realized hey yo
I have free recipes for this week
one is finished in 10 minutes one is in
15 minutes and one is in 45 they're all
super short
I'm such genius so yesterday I was like
I don't want to cook but then I saw the
recipes are so short so I was like let's
go okay no problem then
no problem then
romantic oh yeah
yeah those are good colors I think
um
[Music]
I think that will help
okay
[Music]
45 35 normally most of the recipes are
are like 40 minutes they say they take
40 minutes but it feels like 50 to 1
hour often
um yeah but this time I was smart and I
got really quick ones so I whipped up
something really fast it was it was
nothing special that's why I didn't
upload a photo
well it's basically
[Music]
it was basically
like a grill panel yeah
just grilled
sausages and potatoes but the potatoes
were already pre-cooked
in a in a plastic thingy plastic bag so
I didn't even have to cook the potatoes
they were pre-cooked
and
yeah
and potatoes and I only had to cut the
onions and I had to cut the sausages and
then I had to make a salad the salad was
like the thing that took the most time
because I had to cut the cucumber in
very thin slices and I'm very bad at
that because I can't go like that
because I don't do the I don't do the
the thing
with uh
uh you know where you put your your hand
kind of into a fist on top of the
whatever you're chopping
I can't do that I don't know how to do
that the cat's ball yeah
[Music]
um
and I feel like for like cucumber salad
you want like really thin slices
but um
like they say you can either cut it with
your hand or you can use the
what's it called the cheese grinder
because it has one bigger compartment
for stuff like that and I tried that
before but it's really exhausting
somehow and it doesn't come out that
nice either so
I was like whatever I'm gonna cut it
normally this time so it takes a bit
more time but oh well
[Music]
okay I'm drawing in the hair roughly now
and then I'll draw lines around it
also she has several red tones in her
hair but I don't know if I can do all of
them
[Music]
and there's a there's a big
big uh black ribbon there but I am I'm
not gonna draw it I guess
because I'm mixing two outfits of hers
[Music]
a veggie mandolin to cut consistently
and quick
oh oh another reason why I can't cut it
like so well is because my knives are
really
um numb
um a mandolin what is that
I need to look that up but is that just
another like fun kitchen gadget
[Music]
or is it one that actually is really
useful dull oh yeah
I mean dull
[Music]
foreign
no I just talked about this like
recently I don't have a tool to sharpen
my knives no and they're ceramic anyway
ceramic so I don't think you can sharpen
them right
ceramic knives can you sharpen those
[Music]
you can really
oh yeah and the other colors I just
bought for fun I don't really need them
right now I think
[Music]
you gotta be careful they chip easily
need a wet stone
the [\h__\h] am I like in Minecraft or what
what a wet stone
feels like I'm in some game
you're telling me to get a wet stone
[\h__\h]
wet Stones do not exist in real life
[Music]
foreign
conspiracy theory
wait what they do I know but
to me
for me it's like
you know nothing I deal with normally
therefore it doesn't exist
[Music]
s
now
other red tones I still have this one
this is darker oh a little bit okay cool
because this part is darker
[Music]
yeah that's that's the only strand the
other things look like shadow
okay
um
[Music]
outlands normally I would do that only
in after the sketch but before the color
this feels wrong
[Music]
reminded of the time you went on a trip
with a friend
you said you say a tree and fought
Minecraft
expanding into real life
I haven't had that feeling in a long
time though because I haven't been
playing Minecraft I guess
I only get that when I'm like
playing one game too much too long too
often
but this hair actually goes over
[Music]
I had quite a [\h__\h]
and this one's kind of longer
too bad Ollie was only here in the
beginning she has no idea that I'm
drawing her right now
[Music]
it will be a good surprise yeah
it will be
okay
um
this strand kind of stands off from the
back
[Music]
and there's one here
I gotta figure out where all the lighter
strands are one is here
she's also still naked maybe I'll keep
her naked
no no
no not again kiwawa no I will put her
into clubs I said I will put her into
princess dress
[Music]
you must resist
stop throwing people naked just because
you're lazy
it's not an excuse
or is it
[Music]
yes I am like
you know
today I guess
cat ears and glasses
on a cute girl equals hanukawa
foreign
I just know what I know him I don't know
everything I just know what I know
is I think how you were translated
so genius oh
heavy on my on my walk home I weighed
down
people who don't know
[Music]
hanakama is one of the characters from
and she is so cute
and and and and
I think what was it she has a crash a
little bit I mean who doesn't
on the main character
the the boy the guy
[Music]
that's literally everyone like yeah
everybody does
but then there's like you know this
ongoing thing where some characters say
such a similar phrase but everybody says
it a little bit different like so she
says
what was it
um and then others say it like similarly
what were the other versions
somebody says like they they know
everything probably
somebody says that
[Music]
I need to re-watch man
is it worth watching definitely
I still stand by this tutus day I will
say it's the one of the best if not the
best anime for me
yeah I love oikura
even though she loves math and I hate
math
laughs
foreign
[Music]
pretty fast yeah the show is really fast
you need to be a fast reader
to be able to
keep up with the dialogue like I've even
I I think I used to pause it several
times while I was watching
there's a lot of like if he wants to
anime there's a lot of dialogue on the
screen that they're not even saying out
loud and I mean you don't I think at
least on your first watch through
you don't have to like read all of that
in my opinion
there's just too much like dialogue like
on the screen like as a graphic kind of
like
yeah like as if they're inserting manga
Pages basically
but they're not necessarily I mean
they're not meant to be read on the
first watch through because normally you
would watch it as a Japanese person you
would watch it on the TV when it's get
like getting like broadcasted on TV
right and then
you normally don't have a way of pausing
it at first so you're not supposed to do
that maybe on your second one if you get
really curious I would say
[Music]
yeah I'm drawing only
I don't feel so well today though man
I don't feel so well
also tomorrow I have a Korean lesson
um
I was like what the [\h__\h] when I realized
today is Wednesday already
how did the week
since last Thursday pass by is so
quickly how
I don't get it
makes no sense
[Music]
because I have to do homework I realized
that
I guess I'll do it tomorrow morning
when I wake up because today I probably
won't get to it
because the stream will be long
relatively unless I force myself to make
it shorter
foreign
which I would feel bad about
[Music]
but since I'm not feeling so well anyway
who knows how long I'll be going
no I didn't want to do homework so like
last minute but man this is suddenly it
was suddenly already Wednesday man I
don't get it
now I have to do it last minute
[Music]
foreign
I guess
it's weird because I feel like she never
until now explicitly said this will be
your homework but
um
like
she often left
me with some you know
printed papers said we haven't gone
through and I was like I guess we'll do
them next time
so I didn't really touch them
but
turns out her intention may have been
for me to do this as homework every time
she left it there but she never like
checked up on it like afterwards when
she would come again she wouldn't be
like oh okay so let me check your
homework you Wawa
she wasn't doing that so I always just
assumed
this wasn't homework it was just for
next time or so and then and then she
gives me homework like clearly this time
and I'm like oh it's the first time you
give me homework and she's like no no I
gave you homework before and I'm like
huh what then I didn't do it
then I guess I didn't do it
[Music]
I was so confused
but she also didn't check it so it
really was like passive homework
[Music]
so now that you said clearly
I feel like now I really should be doing
it
a little miscommunication
she wasn't clear on it it's not my fault
I think
[Music]
now I have to rush into homework it's
it's
quite a bit but I think it will be fun
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] why is that the problem
with
drawing is that sometimes you cover up
what you're drawing with your hands and
then you don't see
the balance now this one was way higher
than the other one what the hell
[Music]
which color did I use
that's fine okay this is so difficult
drawing only is so difficult because
[Music]
the shadings could also just look like
another different colored hair strand
same with the skin
but not if I make it very clear like so
yo this means someone
um what do you call these hotchkissed
did someone hot kiss
her face skin together
it was smart to draw her eyes closed
yeah
[\h__\h] oh
I thought it was hot because Hotchkiss
is the thing a staple right staple
staple
staple and I thought it was stapled
which
would be pretty brutal but
I probably didn't feel it
I'm assuming why am I doing this there
should be cloves on top of this
that's Hotchkiss
a gun
but like a staple gun or
what no it's what I feel like I heard
hot kiss in like a chaos song before
what that's a machine gun the [\h__\h] why
does it have such a cute name
yeah I know it from Japanese
[Music]
I'm right
was it a chaos though
why did they sing about a machine gun it
is a brand
floor ah
yo okay on made me think that the
stapler is called hot kiss
because Dave is singing about a
Hotchkiss like a stapler
because there is a stapler called hot
kiss
ah
um
[Music]
it's called oh in Korean too oh in
Korean they also call a stable
[Music]
ah
that's where I got that from
um
now it all makes sense
they all look the same on the palette
man what the hell
foreign
goddammit it's just like I'm playing I'm
doing an art stream it's not about it's
not about the money
right
I need an in-between
this is too dark
all right all right we're gonna use
gonna use this I [\h__\h] mess up
everything
see how it messes everything up I have
to fix it
[Music]
she looks like she's bloody
oh no
a Bloody Zombie is I guess not as weird
oh God
[\h__\h] it once
[Music]
it has its own life
foreign
[Music]
Ollie just Reborn
[\h__\h] which one is it there it is see
look way too similar on the palette man
on the icon
it's confusing
conflicting
[Music]
thank you
let me check the pastel colors that I
got like what do they look like
[Music]
um
nah
no no red tones for me but
they look really bright
[Music]
foreign
yeah even on the Romantic one there's
not so many Reds
shades
there's more like pink ones anyway oh
wait they look
nice
even some more skin tones
they look nice
but I don't know
[Music]
um
yeah no need for them I think
anyway let me look at her dress
she needs some pearls okay
pearls purse purse purse pearls Maybe
this will be useful for it
[Music]
okay well
two glasses came out thank you
the Nails Nails what are you talking
about
what are you talking about
no way to airbrush the darker tones
apparently for a blend I was I was
trying that but uh just
it goes everywhere man
[Music]
rude
made me want to try paint IRL me too
it has that effect on me too
I want to do that
traditional paintings room Actually I
don't even know by the way what to do
for the member stream this week
um I was thinking
one idea I had was trying one of those
um
what where what were those uh called the
stitchy ones the stitchy thingies that I
got
from the uh sponsorship that one
sponsorship remember
with a hand cam
I could try that
no not Star Wars we're done with that
yeah the embroidery
set I got this embroidery set
thinking maybe I could do that with my
with my new camera
[Music]
only smile looks wholesome really nice
don't worry there's still some blood on
her let me fix that
oopsie
[Music]
[Laughter]
we have to hide the evidence for our own
good
that looks weird oh well
[Music]
and I bought another the crayon right I
wonder what the crayon would do
if the crayon also is like
like low opacity hmm
[Music]
what the [\h__\h] what
don't they look all the same on the
palettes to you guys too but they're
quite different when you actually put
them
on the pepper
oh
[Music]
Lord lore Hotchkiss loreato
uh-huh
see the same black nine times right this
one
they're probably pretty different on
their own
hmm they're lit up somehow
I don't know which one is much
yeah whatever I don't care I don't care
I don't care
okay I don't care I don't care oh
I don't care um
[Music]
that's me
I'm just feeling like I have no energy
today man
plane crash sound oh no
oh no
well done here thank you
merci beaucoup
oh
I'm also feeling quite quite low energy
today I kind of feel the same oh no what
happened
we chickens we you chickens need some
more
vitamins and veggies and all that
you didn't don't shoot there guys don't
you dare don't shoot her
don't you dare make a big deal out of
this one
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
why am I putting so much effort into
this
stop just stop stop stop stop stop stop
stop just
finish this
don't put so much effort into everything
okay just
just leave it rough it's okay it's okay
it doesn't not it doesn't normally have
to be like so super intricate okay
there's a chance you will make
everything worse
if you continue trying to make
everything perfect okay
poetic isn't it
and if life doesn't give you the tools
for that anyway then you're just forcing
things that are impossible Maybe
I mean I did pretty well on the armor
yeah I pulled out all the big guns for
the Army one
but no
careful you have to be careful
[Music]
do you want to try and give her a blush
let's see ah
regret
I regret
grab regret
[Music]
that was
too much
what's the red color
more blood on her face I'm I'm just
going over with another spray can so
maybe
overall it won't be so bad
[Music]
okay
foreign
bird
[Music]
oh God I watched so many tier 2 videos
and did you guys see it I didn't even
tag to your zoo but on Twitter maybe for
ego searches so thanks for the raise up
a chat thank you
maybe fruit
uh ego search or other people tagging
him he replied
to one of my tweets talking about his
video the the cat one
[Music]
see
it was like a yo what [\h__\h]
I was like what that's so cool oh my God
what
and so I tried to
advertise a little bit oh yeah it was
like my new videos were better than my
old videos because I was watching his
older videos I guess
I said
um
I I offered an idea of
uh maybe making a video about Phoenix's
no not Phoenix's mythical beings
and he said oh I like Phoenix's good
idea I don't know like if if he meant it
really like he was considering it but
it sounded a little bit like it
a little bit but maybe I mean even if if
that is under consideration I will take
ages but I think it's a good idea
mythical
mythical beings
tier list
otherwise maybe I'll do it
and I offered my expertise because I
noticed in some of his videos
he gets like other big creators
uh sometimes when they actually have
something useful to say about something
uh he gets them to share
some information
sometimes
not always
I was like if you need if you need
Phoenix information
I can give
but I doubt that this is ever gonna
happen it really depends on
on how open that would be so weird to
have a YouTuber on tier Zoo's channel so
random that would be so weird
but if anyone can can make it happen
it's Mrs make everything happen aka me
I make things happen guys
bye you want to know life hack you want
to know the life hack of all time
how to make things happen
listen
free letters
a
s
k
ask
how do you do it kiwala oh I just I just
asked
I actually I just I just ask
um
yeah
sorry that might be kind of
disappointing
[Music]
incredible tell me more about this thing
you call asking
yeah I just asked
right
I know how to make this look like a
like a like a diamond
I'm trying
life changing
don't let you advance my dreams
looks like a ruby yeah I guess it's
supposed to be a ruby that's yeah that's
how I got the whole look your axes too
it just asked
that's that's all there is to it
[Music]
not quite
what I wanted to be like man
[Music]
I don't know I guess I guess from far
away it probably looks okay
that's okay
[\h__\h]
[Music]
I actually besides you know the stress
of having to do my homework for
uh the Korean lesson tomorrow
I also have a lot of um like recording
deadlines right now
whoa
um no it's not a wedding dress it's one
of her outfits
and yeah I already told like
told them for for two of the deadlines
that you know this is you giving me two
days or three days to record something
I've never heard before please I need
more time for this and they said okay no
problem but you know
no problem no problem
I said a tribe within this week though
and then there's some more things
not even my album though
lunchbox seems to be out of his mind
what did lunchbox say
why are you apologizing for him
oh yeah ask came through once again
sorry can you change the deadline for me
uh yeah actually yes we can
it just so happens that we are flexible
um
what
what ah
[Music]
um and the strategy doesn't work on
everything guys I'm sorry to disappoint
but it works on a lot of things like
really though
you you might be surprised
denied
[Music]
nope no no okay I think that will be
pretty much the extent of it because I
spent almost too much time on this
oh and then I don't even like it
I don't even like this one
I don't know
foreign
[Music]
when you like kind of just forced to go
with
the really rough [\h__\h] that you came up
with because there is no layers There Is
No undo
you just gotta hope that it comes out
decently
man struggle
actually tears do when I was watching
videos yesterday sent me on another like
Adventure to what was that channel again
that has a German name
um that explains like all kinds of
things that are never gonna happen
anyway and also some things just like
what what happens if the moon crashes
into the Earth for example
yeah yeah yeah
[Music]
sent me on another adventure because I
was wondering
is it possible and I didn't really get
my answer is it possible that we could
have another I'm just gonna ask you guys
could we have another big bang
like could a huge meteor as big as like
I don't know the Earth crashed into us
and destroy us
anytime soon like randomly wouldn't we
see that coming pretty far ahead
it's possible
but how
how far ahead would we know that
[Music]
that's not oh well I mean okay but it
would make a big bang probably
it would probably be pretty loud
okay that's what I mean
what 11 minutes what
what what
we would see it coming hundreds of years
in advance okay that's good that's good
oh God
oh you have stations that monitor yeah I
thought so I thought so
depends on the speed and the trajectory
of the object hmm
we would see it coming hundreds of views
in advance
okay okay okay good good I'm just
wondering if if that would be something
that could end my life you know
I just want to be sure
just uh no be aware of what what's there
is to end the Phoenix life
what possibilities there are
you want to know what ends you
possibly and you
eh I mean if a freaking meteor hits us
I don't think I would survive that
either no matter if I'm a phoenix
I don't trust myself on that regard
[Music]
foreign
yeah I'm done
it didn't turn out as cute as I wanted
it to
oh
gotta add some
some shiny stuff
[Music]
okay that's what all artists says
don't like it I don't like it but here
comes uh
only the Beautiful
it's like a tiger you know like
Alexander the Great or so
her clothes and no we're not selling it
although I would be interested in how
much they would pay for it let's see
I just want to see the price and then
we're gonna give it for the quest
oh I might be what if they offer me like
two thousand ah and should I just take
it and then instead of draw something
really quickly like that's something
that isn't even anything at all just a
flower
only only
what only showed up again
did someone tell you
you're here again another
oh
dad
the [\h__\h] was higher than my AME painting
wait Paul hey the thing is when you turn
them down here a lot of them just go
home
but I want to see what the others would
offer but that seems like already
incredible incredibly High [\h__\h]
ah yeah nobody Emily has money to pay
more than this
okay I'm selling it
I probably need the money for something
eventually that's just okay let's just
scribble something
I wasn't gonna
sell her I was gonna give her out for
Quest okay let's make something
beautiful really quick
um
beautiful right beautiful
I got it I got it
a garden holy bringing in the big bucks
it's because there were diamonds and
rubies on the painting I'm sure that
that is the reason
foreign
[Music]
something that was the quest right we
were supposed to draw something
beautiful and I said oh I'll draw Ollie
then
so okay
I think that was the original intention
which
[Music]
what is this going to be guys huh
what do you think
[Music]
it's me egg no it's a bit too round for
an egg
[Music]
it's it's a chicken it's going to be a
chicken
foreign
you guys because you guys are beautiful
[Music]
okay
how to draw you guys
[Music]
what do you guys look like show me your
faces
ah okay okay let me paint you like my
French girls
ah okay
huh
can you smile for me
thank you thank you
oh you got such beautiful eyes they're
so lifeless
love it
you're not dead are you
not yet at least
wonderful looking beautiful
oopsie
wrong brush
[Music]
oh gorgeous oh my oh my my gorgeous
wow I want to kiss that mouth
oh
cute
[Music]
oh my
God
I can't aren't you aren't you a little
cutie patootie look at you oh my God you
need to love yourself some more because
damn
I would love myself if I looked like
that
wow
oh my God
could not love you look at you oh my God
but I so the thing is I have this idea
[Music]
just gonna hide your privates because
you know
it's embarrassing isn't it
you're beautiful you're beautiful of
course but
um you know you're you're standing there
posing for a nude picture for me
and we gotta hide it a little bit
I'm sure you feel more comfortable now
too don't you don't you
there you go
don't blow it off we're gonna need a
bigger Leaf are you sure
foreign
[Music]
I still have to attach those legs to my
to my little chicken finger that's super
cute one you know the legs broke
the moment I like um unpacked it from
some bubble wrap I wonder if it like
broke inside the bubble wrap
I'm not sure
cute
wait I want to give you like some
low-key eyebrows
[Music]
I like that I like giving things
eyebrows like cats that don't have
actual eyebrows
it gives them so much personality
but like thick ones because they're cute
uh yeah I need to use hot glue to fix
you guys
I hope it won't hurt you guys too more
fluffy
oh my fluffy burp
[Music]
hope this doesn't tickle when I have my
brush around this area
does it tickle what
is cool
sorry I'm I'm done I'm done
[Laughter]
ah cute you look like an egg though
it's like an egg
um
the most beautiful
sorry Ollie
I mean look at this don't you agree
no one can top this
especially with those striking model
legs
and the body that could lay eggs
Rhymes no no don't sell it although I
would be interested in the price again
but no no no we will not sell this one
no no who who was this for
who was this for
Benjamin Maybe
no ah I'm supposed to have it uh rated
by Benjamin
is it beautiful
wow the colors yes
this is a beautiful painting is it for
sale or does it have a recipient
uh
uh what does that even mean
what am I supposed to press because
huh
[\h__\h] I don't know
what does that mean
s well she has been a bit more Jolly
lately oh ah okay it's the same thing
okay I hope she loves it haha I hope she
loves it
okay right so was it for when when I'll
go back to Emily because I I guess it
was from Emily
I'm so confused my short time memory I
already forgot everything you asked me
for except that it had to be beautiful
and wait what
no wait it had nothing to do with Emily
but LOL you you you
hope
she went down to the series didn't you
listen yeah I don't know did I listen I
may have listened but I may have also
forgotten okay let's see where it's okay
okay
all right the sewers I know where those
are
I'm coming
so long I painted something and I
decided to sell it because it was too
good to give it to you
but this is even better
this is even better
is it beautiful uh Ben loves it
show it to me here
all right uh-huh
um
no I feel nothing or do I ah
let's make it harder toss it in a fire
no
no but wait it's like it's like you know
like a feet you're this is the the
ritual to turn you guys into a phoenix
surely into the fire no
no
it's like I'm burning money
[Music]
what are you doing
you shocked me into feeling emotions I
hope Vlog can fix this there's nothing
more you can do for me
oh but they got a recipe
wait I feel like there's two outcomes to
this Quest I feel like this is like I
read this somewhere when I was trying to
figure out what the algorithm for this
game was and I think they mentioned this
Quest
um
I saved you guys I had to are you guys
okay
I'm gonna put you in ice water I'll stay
down here in the gutter for a while
maybe that helps
wait who was I supposed to give it to
now
what did they say
give it to
leave burned ow
oh
la la la la la la la la la la
no no I can't feel my legs
wait now I can still sell it though
right wait it still looks the same I
think wait
but they said go to someone to see if
you can fix it if you can save it it
looks normal ah cute it's so cute my
baby LOL
like this dude has a quest it seems I'll
go to him in a moment
oh
something super weird with hope I know
that you tried to help her but it didn't
work the other day I saw it was almost
as if one corner of her mouth twitched a
little and occasionally she burst into a
song She's a nihilist for God's sake and
I love like her or whatever oh I want
you with a couple of canvases that I
found if you can paint her a
supernihilistic painting what does that
mean when it reminds her of what's
important what makes her hope again
okay so do I keep my chicken
okay great the darker the better when
you're done delivered to Hope and we'll
see if it works what if I just have a
give her a black canvas
it probably should be more than that
nothing matters oh
so is that connected to an animation
annihilation
do people and they're late people
because they think nothing matters
no
yeah
something like that
yeah correct
kind of not that connected oh no I guess
no because no no because once you and
it's because once you annihilate them
there is nothing left
okay never mind it's not that deep
but it doesn't
it doesn't know I I take it as that
I would hang it up if I could but
they didn't talk about fixing my chicken
but hey he wants to buy it
nah
go away
no you cheap [\h__\h]
127 no I I prefer to like keep it in
that case
you little [\h__\h] we got a recipe by the
way
techno
sounds a lot right no you guys are way
more worth ah the punks are not gonna
pay much for that
they maybe don't like that there's a lot
of white in the picture okay a bit
better but now
you guys are Priceless that's right
get out of here punks
get out of here
[Music]
another Punk
playing a new palette yay
oh
that may have been useful for Ollie I
think maybe
interesting
Punk sorry auto Joseph doesn't [\h__\h] you
flash get out of here get out don't
don't you dare
insult my beautiful naked chicken
which canvas was I supposed to draw on
because they gave me one specific one
[Music]
I'll be able to get higher than that I
want to see what the old guys say about
it though
I wonder which canvas doesn't even
matter I'm gonna take this one
oh no no I think I bought this one
surely they just want a small one no are
these small canvases the ones I got from
the rock paper scissors
Spike 315 now
um
[\h__\h] I don't know which one to draw on
probably doesn't matter
but if it doesn't matter then I want to
paint on the small one
another Punk why are only punks coming
oh Benjamin's coming Benjamin thought
you guys were really pretty
[Music]
whoa smells let's go
finally now we're talking
I do wonder what Benjamin would pay but
I might just go with that now we're
clocking
[Laughter]
go with it
who the [\h__\h] is that
what is that never seen that one before
or is that Banky
who are you
suck Banky
yay oh whoa that's okay not quite near
unless
[Music]
they want it really black but I want to
add something
what do we do
what do we do for
just a quickie
um
supposed to be dark
a sad face
I feel like they might not like it
though it's no effort
annihilation
[Music]
okay he's dead
it's a great no it's supposed to be kind
of black but
it doesn't get much more black than this
it seems
okay
who was I giving this to
uh
hope
uh sewers right
you guys remember thank God
I am all lost
I'm lost hope
bucket there's a baguette sign there
what is what about the kuma song
I hope you like this
black yes
this is so dark I feel
[Music]
nihilistically nothing I might finally
be cured from the sickness actually I
really don't care go tell low thanks or
whatever it doesn't matter
yo low effort and high reward let's go
success indeed
um
[Music]
do we get something nice back or not
I did it what happened I mean whatever
but yeah what it worked well great
she'll be back as her old self in no
time the sun Joy can Smite even the most
devoted Nicholas nihilist whatever it
happened to me once and uh whatever so
uh the reward free canvas is on workout
okay now I have like plenty canvases
it wasn't for me okay sure
um actually
and I can unlock the upper area but
one sec let me do this one you wanted
something don't don't you
no oh okay
maybe it was my kinose
my imagination I thought he came out
running trying to give me a quest
all right
what about the flag though maybe the the
third person really is behind this
six tools yeah
look at the big boss coming with six
tools and all you must be high value you
should go see my mommy Brianna
I'm sure she'd love to work with you
all right I'm in guys I'm in oh there's
someone missing a fish
foreign
what
dinosaur Bobby Bobby
is a smart investment
good you found a new home seems like
getting evicted was just a kick you
needed huh your heart seems to really be
going down well around here I'm looking
forward to acquiring some for myself oh
yeah you seem like someone who would pay
me well
oh
[Music]
stop stop and that there's a cat cafe I
want to look at them but the angle now
kind of sucks
excuse me can I pass oh I can oh
dangerous
brianabull
wait what is this supposed to say try
our new bacon burger
ooh crab energy yo these are so good I
should draw something like that man
laughs
my people have told me you can make
something sell like hotcakes it seems so
first of all sorry for my wooden head
son stopping you
I was trying to keep him busy but it
almost cost me a business opportunity
counting your tools to see if you're
high value sounds like a child's idea
time is money and I always need more
money if you can make a coat of paint
that will make a great car the go-to
purchase I'll reward you handsomely eh
what
make it this what I'm really painting
the car
oh sheesh but that sounds fun
oh okay could I sell it
oh
[Music]
hey GTA GTA
is that a muscle car I don't think so
guys this is definitely not muscle car
but I kind of want a car like that
what
press f
oh
let me let me Munch a muffin
by the way
my head feels so weird today not like a
headache but it just feels
oh no stuffed
stuffy maybe I'm a puppet
what kfb
h
[Music]
Naruto
well this is really interesting
that is really new
full of blueberry muffins not yet I need
to become stuffed with blueberry muffins
[Music]
wow
I know okay I think
I didn't bring the colors I need but oh
well
now okay let's go home to paint that
much
[Music]
oh
I kind of want to do like a graffiti
cartoon
[Music]
ah
okay let me paint this car on my on my
aisle eel aisle what
no
[Music]
um
I'll take instead of monochrome
the skin color and we'll see we'll see
how that goes
easel that was
that okay
mm-hmm
[Music]
easel in German is donkey
wait I need my kfp logo
I want the cafe logo on the front
and then I want
um
Maybe
add Little Chihuahua somewhere
um
what do you mean frog raid hmm
oh it is kind of a frog
I love frogs I just today watched the
Frog Tail list of tearzoo
um
turns out frogs are overall pretty
[\h__\h] weak
who would have thought
that's why froggy Wawa will never be
able to take over
hey FB
okay F where's that I don't see my
keyboard there we go
kfp logo I got it
um
[Music]
ah
I got no proper yellow
[Music]
okay
I need a turquoise we don't have a
turquoise
[Music]
um
that's okay
[Music]
sorry I'm kind of eating something but
now I'm done I'm just trying to get more
energy because sometimes I have like no
energy today
yeah
um
this feels so inaccurate where I'm like
drawing it doesn't draw where I want to
draw
um
yeah it's so like somewhere else
okay big big round eyes
wait no
that's off center all right it has so we
like it
kfp logo
and now they have a little bow tie
a little spark in your eye
and then it should say kfp
making oh [\h__\h] I can't
making this card to an advertisement for
me and she won't even know it big
bamboozle oh
I should probably draw like from
straight front like this because wait
that looks so
that looks so different
so different I was bamboozled
looks like a melted blob
all right there's actually like a
little bit of a
blue background implemented in the logo
foreign
guys
that blue is wonderful wow
[Music]
okay that's that's enough for me now on
the side
we will draw
Something Like Me Maybe
um I mean a reference of me what do I
look like
what do we want to draw me as
just uh
[Music]
maybe in my normal uniform then because
this is uh this is the company car so it
should be
it should be my normal me
okay
[Music]
made kiwawa oh that would be cute too
foreign
but this will be scuffed okay I don't I
don't even I don't want this to be good
because it would look funny if it's
scuffed actually
um
I can't say
okay maybe maybe the blob uh
strategy strategy is not gonna work here
[\h__\h]
[Music]
I have to go way lower
okay
[Music]
but the handle hand away
I mean
what
hmm
[Music]
foreign
I swear it doesn't draw like where I
wanted to draw so
okay it will just be a scuffed car
scribbled but
it would seem as if I was um blindfolded
while doing this
yeah I have given up
oh my God
laughs
wow
we're back to garlic phone levels guys
one two three four five
[Laughter]
[Music]
ah
EE
cool cool
and wow me
nice I mean I would drive this car
would you not drive this car guys
I would I would where's my outfit though
uh
[Music]
and girl there you go
beautiful
yeah yeah that's totally me oh my God
doesn't it look like that
um
it reminds me of that really scuffed
anime art with those humongous eyes
which is kind of a meme
okay and here
let's draw froggy Wawa here
[Music]
yeah maybe is it the air or the planet
one yeah I think that's I think that's
what I'm talking about
but like it's just it's normally not
that bad I think but there's just this
one like image where it looks absolutely
cursed
um
funky wow is so cute
rocking Mama man the clips sometimes I
want to froggy wobble clips
they show up on my timeline and they're
just the cutest thing like what the [\h__\h]
the hands I really miss
having hands okay real talk
it's just great having hands like that
[Music]
um
is the collab was cute yeah but I didn't
even use VR then so I couldn't really
make the most of it
I wasted it
but once again here we have froggy Wawa
Supremacy because she looks better
than the kiwawa that I drew
when I learned how to aim for where I
actually want to draw
okay
[Music]
okay okay okay okay
froggy mwah
maybe race
oh wait she does have tiny little baby
hands
I'm gonna give her tiny little baby
foreign
little baby hands
wait oh my God help
oh [\h__\h] wait let me give it an outline
[Music]
there we go
yeah wait a little bitty booty booty
heads or and the rest of it
we'll have some
uh graffiti yeah which color it should
be orange but I don't have any good
oranges right now so I'll just you you
Wawa colors
featuring froggy wobble colors
collaboration
of the nation
in the station
with variation
there you go
not so bad
whoa coming for the wrap throne
[Music]
let's give it some eyes
it's a chicken in disguise
I cannot stop rhyming
because
we are combining
um the love
for art
and the love
for shark
now I said it now I have to draw it
[Music]
shark
random shark
you thought it was gonna be good huh all
right all right all right I get it I get
it
we shall have Gouda
make an appearance
foreign
form in her final form
[Music]
that smirk was not on purpose
uh that is supposed to be her hand
coming out of the shark suit
saying hi waving at you there we go
I don't wanna call a car
don't look at me
what a car
foreign
[Music]
stylish as [\h__\h] if you use this car to
get around town
everybody will be talking about you
everybody will be turning their heads of
course only because they think of it as
an amazing the most amazing car wait is
it gonna be like out here are they gonna
be showing it showcasing it
[Music]
huh
different from my usual lineup but
perhaps it's exactly the device
diversity we need I wonder if they
always give the same reactions team get
this to the marketing department at once
next time I blink there better be an
advertisement board of this cash cow for
you
and only man man cheap cheap they don't
know how much money I actually make with
my art
I trust you'll find it more than fair
good the marketing team is already done
I'm strongly surrounded by the best now
if you'll excuse me
resident where's my car where are you
gonna put my car
you will surely showcase it right
because they always showcase the the
things I do for them
cardboard Square noise
yeah I already have what 8.5 holy [\h__\h] I
feel like I've broken the metal oh no
there
needle
wait no the other sides were better why
is that no froggy what was that for
people with common sense
I agree
I agree I strongly agree with that
hello Belfort who are you you look uh
fancy are you selling
when remaining in the proletaria is an
issue of character not the suster
or to the potent form of investment as
long as you know what you're doing you
can achieve great returns and the kicker
it's all the tax write-off
uh-huh
is that all
yeah okay
[Music]
can I go in here no mm-hmm
okay let's go to the other store I guess
oh I guess we're still a little bit too
early here maybe he'll eventually give a
quest but not yet
fake Monopoly man
I can see it yeah the mustache and the
hat but there's another area up here
that you can eventually oh yeah it's a
museum actually yeah yeah
I need a masterpiece wait what I can
actually go in no
I can buy a ticket how much
how
I am a gate my job is to keep you
outside not to tell you how to get
inside don't you have any allies you can
ask
[Music]
can't visit the museum huh
okay okay okay okay
I
I wonder about the flag
oh wait Maggie wasn't you I have to ask
nah
let me ask the lady again because I
think I asked like two people or maybe I
asked all of them and I just don't know
about it yet it was supposed to supposed
to be dark and fresh I think
or black and fresh
but there should have been like a third
information
[Music]
nice
Margaret tell me about it that was it
again
you need to listen to what Harry has to
say it's important for the flight design
ah Harry is the only one I have left who
is Harry
[Music]
I heard you've got the commission to
design a community black young man
ah my wife has finally found her
vexilographer vexilu grandfather means
because I'm French on the Atlantic Ocean
if you ask me glorious Marine tradition
tradition must be at the Forefront of
the Vlog
oh
okay okay
my brother George would probably be
upset if you don't respect the art
history history of the town
uh okay of course I'll be there what
kind of husband won't show up for his
wife's moment of Glory you'll include
something awesome related to that yeah I
guess so ocean yeah okay
dark fresh and ocean
I don't know how
they're they are about it but okay
wait I'm not just supposed to draw on a
random canvas right she's gonna give me
a canvas I think
[Music]
yeah yeah
I got the information
[Music]
good you've talked to everyone and a
pretty solid idea of how to design it a
Recon the time to get to work here's the
flag please try to cover up Benjamin's
poor attempt uh the ceremony is about to
start I need to write my stupid speech
now good luck ah thank you
merci beaucoup
reported what do you mean pudding
how dare you
[Music]
it's a phoenix because
and they called oh my God it's really a
phoenix town
how can I get rid of the Phoenix no it's
perfect the way it is
I love this flag
I'm gonna turn it into something it's
not at all
what the hell is that it's a French
Phoenix flag I love it
[Music]
yeah they wanted it to be dark so I feel
like I should have started like with a
home okay wait
okay
let me see what we can do
well I guess we'll just get rid of the
you know flat colors in the back and
we'll just be a mainly Black Flag
[Music]
I love the Phoenix on there because it
fits so perfectly to me of course
of course
the city that I'm taking over is
literally
literally Phoenix then
2.0
okay
but they want like
some
something
that shows that they're you know all
about the ocean as well
[Music]
um
and they want something fresh I'm sorry
you gotta go for now at least
um
[Music]
oh
no
[Music]
um
trying to be creative now
foreign
[Music]
for a good flag is that it should be
easy to recognize even at the size of
your thumb
[Music]
I don't know I mean it being black and
like mostly black I think makes it very
recognizable
oh wait I have a good idea
mm-hmm
what the [\h__\h] is this what what the [\h__\h]
is this they're gonna be lucky what the
[\h__\h] what the [\h__\h] is this
what the [\h__\h]
[Music]
and I'll be like well you asked for it
you asked for this to happen
it's not my fault can't help it
I love this chicken woman so much
hi I mean you said chicken but besides
that I'm very flattered thank you
kfp colors are not dark yeah they
shouldn't be but they want it to be dark
um
punks they don't they don't get it
they don't get it
bad taste
black shouldn't be in a Stark
[Music]
um I wanna draw like not only I mean
normally a flag should really not have
like a portrait of a person on it but I
want to address something recognizable
on it
okay so far I think this has black
potential Maybe
[Music]
now I do want to add a phoenix
flying over
the this like dark ocean
I don't know what kind of perspective
this is but you know it's abstract
maybe the bird can be abstract as well
[Music]
yeah the top right is still kind of
empty so
probably there
all right
it Ocean looks like a feather very nice
I didn't realize oh yeah maybe it's the
Tail the Phoenix tale becoming part of
the ocean wow looks like the proposed
New Zealand designs what looks like this
what
there's like what is that a thing right
now Neil Zealand
uh flag proposals
what
oh [\h__\h] yeah
they're changing their flag
foreign
I'm gonna be honest yeah the Korean flag
looks like a you know Australian flag
sit the silver Fern flag hmm
but that's like what 2015 2016 have they
given up on it
seems like they gave up on it
maybe flag making it's my it's my secret
Talent maybe I designed the fern flag
for New Zealand hmm
all right let's I wanna find as a
reference like how to oh oh yeah like an
abstract icon style Phoenix
that would fit
um
yeah
yeah okay okay
[Music]
cool that's good
um
do I have the colors yeah I can make it
work
I will make it work
[Music]
hey they got what they gotta Lord of the
Rings fans until
I'm joking and you you're hinting at me
doing it what
what I'm confused
you're kidding oh
one of the flags they would choose was
Lord of the Rings related
have a little a little hint to a hobbit
house or oh the ring oh there should be
a ring on there
on their map
on their flag
[Music]
I'm making abstract boob
looks good I think maybe could have done
it a little bit more to the left
foreign
[Music]
just gonna add something
it's my hair
oh
Magnifique
looks cool looks like one of them fire
emblems
I am a fire emblem don't you remember
also of course it only makes sense
and now
I wanna I wanna we gotta clean it up but
I wanna test something
um
we will try this and then
okay oh that's a different black the
heck
the heck
when I used that one
okay
[Music]
sorry I'm not throwing as many like
um member portraits as I wanted to to
die
but I drew a beautiful naked chicken and
the Beautiful Ollie
don't worry I want to play more of this
game so we'll draw more in the future
clean look at that oh
foreign
[Music]
this way they're not losing their
Phoenix Sun identity isn't that
wonderful
dreams
[Music]
this is basically a samatory
flag
combining the ocean
with the fire bulb
foreign
[Music]
I'll be talking to her when we do the
weather again you I hope she's doing
fine I hope she's doing well
I hope our weather team is ready but we
have at least
I mean you know mermaid might just be
you can maybe like um
uh sacrifice for the withered so we have
time to kill it or so
but Ina is a good player fauna is a good
player gouda is a good player too
I I would normally say I'm I was at
least a good player too
so I think we have good chances We're
not gonna like make it too easy we're
just gonna
use
um not the best strategy to do it
something in between we're gonna do it
somewhere far far away
um
in a big cave
the Fire Emblem strategies
I don't know if they will if those will
apply you ladies just need to prepare
properly yeah we have everything I asked
wanna
should we prepare anything else she said
no I think we're good
I think so too
um
seems like we are good to go
yeah and a flag really shouldn't be too
much details right so this is like it
could be okay like this I think I think
this is it
see what the hell
um
this is this I call this island now
officially Phoenix term congratulations
[Music]
done done
well we already have all of that oh
they're ready
ready yay
I got the flag
whatever time in the ceremony starts now
I don't have time to give I don't have
time to give you the feedback talk to me
again when we're done and I'll pay you
just rest the flag on my kill well you
don't even want to check it
she trusts me a lot huh
um a friend of Phoenix and today is a
great day we finally have a symbol that
unites our fine community
as a symbol together around to love to
respect
as a representative of the city the
Mayo's office and as a proud Park
administrator I give you the flag of
Phoenix
time hoist
[Music]
it shouldn't be me that evaluates this
let us be quiet and listen to the crowd
oh
wow what are you saying Maggie hmm
consider the symbolic meaning of a flag
what
the oppressors have clearly called you
with their sticky no
what's your problem maybe somebody else
cares no I cared I made the whole
background black for you
huh
the [\h__\h]
oh you don't have an opinion okay Harry
oh it's
ah okay thank God
I like no I love it I love it if you
talk to the others
yeah one of them what about you
well we got a new flag
I finalized your flag and it's competent
fit for our town okay okay two out of
three like it
huh do you also have an opinion Peggy
scene flag
thank you hey stupid you stupid
[Music]
what about you
Bobby has a new interesting product I
want to hear about the flag it's so cute
for foreign
dude my neck hurts looking up
what do you think do I look like someone
who would like that flag maybe somebody
else cares okay the punks hate the flag
well maybe they will leave then
the city
yeah and then who was it George
or Gerard will be happy about it yeah
big George hey flag maker yeah pay me
I love what you did in such a short
amount of time is your 200
[\h__\h] for something they will use for
years and years and years and hundreds
of years officially
[\h__\h] what
that doesn't even seem realistic at all
damn what the hell
disappointed anyway
[Music]
um
let's get
you know what I wanna I'm gonna make I'm
gonna draw freestyle now
I don't even want to Quest from them
we're just gonna
use a big canvas the biggest I have
and draw something cute
who do we draw
[Music]
um
last time we drew snot maybe we should
draw Cali
I'm gonna draw Cali
in her
cute new outfit
in her sleepy sleepy way
can we
now I can go all in with the details you
but I'm already I feel like no that's
too big
that's not white
okay we should give her the background
anyway
um
Dark One
and that'll be probably the last thing I
draw today
[Music]
laughs
I want I want Boba to be visible boobies
I messed up
and when it was drying the the car too
somebody was like oh you missed the spot
and I'm not sure if I really did but
damn
you guys are
very very
aren't you
[Music]
oh where's this color here
excuse my
shitty
[Music]
um
uh uh uh what
Anatomy
I don't know how to Anatomy
I'm trying to have like like
she's kind of like bending
down kind of
[Music]
um
but no yeah and then like I was gonna do
it with like really
High
elbows but maybe not too high I don't
know
[Music]
drawing in front of all of you makes me
nervous nervous
uh yeah yeah you not understand the arms
are pushing things together
even bigger though
even bigger
my dad's I think
it's more like it
[Music]
um
fingers
[Music]
foreign
sketch but already with skin color so I
can just
fill it in basically
okay
there you go oh those fingers are cute
they look huge now to me
[Music]
adow
and that's not so bad
no the hand is huge overall the hand is
huge
like this I don't know why does it look
so big
fine but I didn't get the angle I wanted
I can't do angles
I don't I can only do angels
[Music]
foreign
what's going on there what's going on
okay whatever
I guess that's kind of what it is and
now now and now
face shape let's fill in the face color
so I don't have to draw around the lines
afterwards
Elise we'll get her whole head on the
picture
already a good start
[Music]
really pale looking
can we
biblically accurate angels
she is
yes
straight out of the Bible
basically her thing is like just a
little simple like black uh
black negligee right
the soup nightgown
I was shocked honestly I was like
damn this is this must be like the
absolute absolute limit of how far we
can go right right right right right
damn I didn't think something like this
would be possible
but we have
we have come to a point where
um
yeah YouTube forgives us for quite a lot
thank you YouTube
I guess you know we always roast YouTube
but we gotta thank YouTube for being so
forgiving to us as well
I mean
have you seen her outfit
Marine is definitely a limit like I was
thinking about I was comparing I was
comparing the two you know Mayans
outfits
and Callie's and that my my verdict is
actually that Cali's is looter
Mario
is a good a good amount of loot as well
you know but but Kelly went all out I
mean
I'm in
my God
you know when I heard she's doing
pajamas I was like oh okay probably look
fluffy
you know something cozy no no no she
went to the sexy Style
no no no the bikinis no no they they're
okay now
that's why last year Hollow live summer
was revived because we can do bikinis
now apparently
apparently we know
we are being we're giving we're giving
the free pass
[Music]
we've been given the pass
okay
um I guess I'll
draw in the boobies now too even though
they will be they will be covered up
okay
there will be something there
and then
[Music]
actually picking his bikinis was like
this list no have you not seen
what they did last year
that was
a bikini
that was simply a bikini
they're not holding back anymore
no no holding back
shading
[Music]
bikini when who knows maybe now I I will
also be freed
my kiwawa yeah I mean I'm wearing it
right now there I have a bikini
underneath and who knows
maybe this is the year where I get to
show it to everybody
that would be
the best Arc ever
chained to PGM
[Music]
go
I might pass out
yeah it's it shouldn't be too difficult
because I mean it is there it is there
there is the like drawing underneath
it's already there
let me
get rid of the blouse
it's rigged yeah it should be it's like
connected like there's no like there's
nothing that you have to
rig separately
so
[Music]
I just want to make sure I remember
where the lines were
[Music]
this better go for a lot of money
because I'm gonna spend some time on
them
[Music]
there we go
okay
okay the body is there
doesn't look okay
[Music]
when I look at it in the OBS screen I
feel like I'm I can look at it
differently
[Music]
I'm not even looking at what I'm drawing
I'm just looking at OBS in the very far
left screen right screen
not enough squish it's difficult
[Music]
here okay oh that is very squishy
there you go
she's like really
really like pushing them squishing them
to its limit
but the arm you know the arm
okay okay that's better
um
[Music]
let me just look up a picture of her
outfit
caliope Mori
[Music]
uh sleepwear
I guess
[Music]
yeah okay
I want to draw her with the messy hair
because that is so cute and it's so cute
[Music]
it is so cute oh that should be
it should be a good color oh let me
already give her a blush
[Music]
cute fingers oh thank you yeah the
fingers look good I think
um
um okay let me I guess I should do the
face a little bit first
I feel like every time I draw the eyes
of black it just stands out too much so
maybe I should um
maybe I should try the like dark dark
red
[Music]
thank you
oh
[Music]
no
oh she looks shocked she looks shocked
I can make her look not short too but
actually I kind of like it nah
[Music]
he's like oh no
don't look at me
I'm so embarrassed yeah
but this is totally totally hassle
crochet
[Music]
I didn't I didn't allow you to enter my
room yet oh no oh
the blush is way too high oh well
[Music]
which one and which one did I use which
one
[Music]
no apparently not
I can still fix it
[Music]
just a little bit
eyes blushing yeah yeah don't worry
don't worry I will fix all of those
[Music]
Pretty in Pink isn't she
I saw she played this game where you
have to type
in order to kill
which looks really interesting but then
she wrote something like chicken [\h__\h]
right what the [\h__\h] the game made her do
that though it was like an insult to
someone I think
and then when you type it it counts as
like shooting them or so basically I
think
and like while you type it goes like
the game is alright it looked like a
ride yeah it looked interesting what a
fun idea though I like the idea behind
it
like what that makes no sense
that makes no sense but this was funny
it was funny
[Music]
they also played it oh
ah she said I'm looking at you okay
oh okay okay okay that's fine then
that's fine
[Music]
laughs
oh God
[Music]
yeah I wanted to combine but no I take
it back I take it back and take it
[Music]
I just give her sparkles
now I feel like a little chin
balances off
also it's actually played like a lot of
like fan games
yo some of them I've never seen before I
wanna I wonder if there's some I should
give a try
[Music]
I haven't really seen much of them but
so many fan games man
is there one you guys would want me to
play
you know the RPG one Council versus RPG
console is RPG will be nice play the
console with RPG how long can you play
that how long is the game
in on its own
some of the games are professional
looking wow five hours five oh
short
oh
like one stream yeah interesting
[Music]
no
we don't really have like a gray one do
we a green
gray
um
[Music]
uh Pink
oh that does the trick
[Music]
gotta clean up okay
laughs
um
or else I've never played the the one
game what is it where you eat
Iris do you eat Iris
are you is that what you you're eating
I'll never play that one that could also
be something we could play
[Music]
so nice of the community to give us more
content to stream
ironically we even need to gather formal
permission for the fan games in order to
stream them we can't just like stream
them no no no
delivering hope oh yeah yeah
they're still updating that game I saw I
see it sometimes like on my timeline
you still update that game damn
[Music]
[\h__\h] I just want to try yeah that's okay
that's gonna come out cool I think
you have to clean
[Music]
it up give it more of like a gradient so
it's softer
[Music]
looks scary we need to give her hair
quickly otherwise she's gonna just
stare into a soul until we don't know
anymore who we are and where we are
loser mind
[Music]
are you guys okay
she's still cute
they added you to that one what they
added me to the the eating one
foreign
let me draw her hair now and then I
might go back
to her face ah my mouse there we go
I think I'll use this one more time
[Music]
hmm
the kfp fan game wait which one
which one
I also saw recently in my art tag
there's like some kind of like novel
Style game where I'm like a cheerleader
or something
what is that
yeah yeah but aren't they like like two
kfp games or so
but they're pretty
like a long time ago already no
[Music]
hello trials yeah whole trash looks good
but is it far from being done yeah right
it's still in development I think
I escaped the usual room was one
I haven't played it though but I've seen
it
[Music]
yeah I don't like that but I don't think
we have a better color
um
[Music]
maybe we do
no
why would anyone ex want to escape I
love how you say that you're you're a
good chicken you're advertising you're
spreading
good
good opinions
[Music]
that is the right opinion to have
brainwashed succeeded
propaganda no no no
[Music]
ground bro
also you guys cannot deny the many times
that you guys even asked me to put you
in the usual room
I really don't get it you guys are
giving me mixed signals
[Music]
and then
and then you blame me
to blame me and you're like oh she's so
evil
I'm trying to satisfy you trying to give
you all you want all you ask for
let me check if I have some more colors
now maybe the pastel ones
[Music]
oh yeah yeah oh I like it yeah okay
that's better
[Music]
it's more on the purple side but at
least that makes it a bit more gray
because her hair shade like the the
darker shades
the
um Shadows are usually like pretty gray
they're not like
this peachy pink at least
[Music]
um
let's have her ears stick out and pause
[Music]
and I wanna
add some lines so I know
what to do um
[Music]
sorry I'm so quiet now what should I
talk about
[Music]
give me a topic guys
no I'm putting her in that outfit the
one that she has
ah yeah I think everyone responded
to when I drew of them I think so
[Music]
Milo keep her as she is
did you hear about newer summer's dream
about me what what did she say I mean
anything everything she says is just you
know random mumbling but what did she
say
[Music]
um
you're being countries no no
you heard this Burgers is coming back uh
yeah she asked us um
if we would
do it
again
basically to end it um
you add her mole no where is it on her
boobie or where I don't see it on this
reference art
[Music]
ah she won't tell us where it is oh
ah well then I don't know where it is
either I may have gone to an Onsen with
her but I haven't looked that closely
adding sound boards to voice channels
what what does that mean how what how
does that what does that entail
what does that do
[Music]
it's the worst unless you mute them what
'll be on a vertical plane
same as AMA ah did she say that then I
think I can I think I remember her
saying something like that how prepared
are you for the corner
I mean I'm not really prepared yet ah I
need to after this stream I need to open
up the questions
um but besides that I mean usually I
only really get
prepared before like the day before but
I did
uh research like Clips to
um do
this time
um
so I have the clips
in the works now and yeah
questions I'll deal with that now
foreign
[Music]
crew I like drawing hair I mean normally
not in this order
it's really messing everything up
but okay maybe I'm you know doing things
in an unusual way like unlike you
normally would do it
practice maybe
[Music]
yeah yeah
an anime girl is drawing an anime girl
in a game yeah yeah what's weird about
it honestly what's weird about that
seems normal to me
[Music]
oh this color is actually a good skin
color too I don't even have to switch
palettes
and what what is this
wolf cats are meowing for you to come
play with them but uh you are in the
step they are in separate rooms and are
watching so they will know of you choose
if you choose the other cat what do you
do
[Music]
problem is chonkers gets like I think
sad
if I am cuddle too much and
play too much of this movie
um
but the thing is like when I try to play
with
chunkers she quickly she's a bit hard to
play with she quickly
like
starts
hiding somewhere she's like just runs
off
she's quickly out of the playing mode
and
you have to play with her in a really
specific way
difficult
and then when it comes to cuddling
um chonkers loves cuddling but depending
on how you
like cuddle with her
she will like walk away reposition
herself and kind of expect you to follow
her and so it's kind of weird
she has this weird technique
kind of
attention seeking perhaps I don't know
she's like she's like um maybe she has
like a restless leg syndrome or
something like that because she's like
so Restless yeah she's so complicated
um but when she's like
but that's like when she's when she's
not in deep sleep if she's in deep sleep
um then it's easier
then you know I start cuddling her and
then she she wakes up half like a little
bit but should not not too much
she still stays there
and lets me cuddle her in peace
but um you know ah
oh
now
I think she she doesn't really show it
much but I do think she gets a little
bit jealous if I'm
cuddle smoothie too much the thing is
though that this movie is easier to
cuddle
she just
stays there she starts purring often
she lets me like fall asleep with her
tummy in my face
like sometimes
I just face palm a face bumper
and then we just you know fall asleep
like that eventually I wake up and she's
gone but
she does let me do that for quite a
while
chokers is like she's a bit more
complicated she lets me sometimes
fall asleep while having my my hand on
her tummy but
yeah
not that she doesn't like cuddling she
loves it but she's just kind of weird
about it
[Music]
no
um
so to answer your question
um if they they would know huh but I
think chonkers is used to me
giving her so a smoothie is used to me
giving her so much attention already
that
I think she wouldn't mind if I would you
know
give the attention to chonkers
oh wow
I think I might choose chunky wonky
because I don't want chunky wonky to be
sad
and I always
tend I tend to choose strong a smoothie
over her because it's just just easier
often
she lets me
go all in with my cuddles
yeah
but it's not doesn't mean that I like
her any less or so
I like them both equally
[Music]
true
laughs
foreign
[Music]
the collarbone shading oh yeah I mean
it's not quite finished there that area
isn't finished either
[Music]
there you go that's a bit better
okay more topics
Kelly Lisa
with children are solely alive but with
cats I believe it yeah yeah yeah yeah I
do think of children when parents say
that they're lying
or are they I don't know well I guess I
won't really know
[Music]
her eyes look blood red kind of creepy
they're not done done yeah she looks
kind of younger right now though
[Music]
uh World of Warships collab oh yeah
um that was in the works for a long time
and finally it's there
uh I don't know does anyone here play
World of Warships
yes then you're probably very happy
about it
[Music]
though some of you also knew that it was
in the works for a long time
now it's finally here the wait is over
I guess we all do now
World of Warships I don't nope I didn't
I played Battleship before I rarely do
I'm going to
this is my get me into it oh curious for
chiatos I recorded so many voices I
don't even remember anymore it's like a
million years ago
I think
did I record them in German
can I record them German I think I I
think because the thing was they got one
Japanese member to do Japanese voice one
English member to do an English voice I
think Emma did English voices and I did
uh they got I think Muna to do
Indonesian and I did German even though
I'm whole life English member but they
knew I could speak German to him yeah I
guess I did my lines in German yeah
[Music]
um
I recorded them
I don't know over a year ago I don't
remember anything what did I say I do
not recall
but I hope they're not too cringe
yourself
[Music]
foreign
did I say a date when exactly
do you guys have a date yet
I mean do you are you aware of anything
[Music]
not really just next update tomorrow
tomorrow
what
that's me just genuinely asking tomorrow
I'm not trying to uh
copy you know
tomorrow
okay
I'll have a date I'm free tonight oh
okay let's let's go somewhere
[Music]
okay well all done guys tell me your
opinion once you get your hands on it
[Music]
um I don't know if I'll be doing any
stream on it but uh
I don't know I I hope you guys will
enjoy it
[Music]
okay okay okay
I am curious about your special Captain
Skill oh oh I never I never played the
game before so I really don't know how
it works but is that a thing that you
have in the game
ah
I remember saying a bunch of cute
and I
had some inputs on like
you know
if I wanted to I could change lines to
be more like me and I did that a little
bit
uh what was a bit embarrassing because
they were listening
when recording
but then again
yeah it wasn't
actually I made it also easy because I
could ask them like how how exactly they
want me to say this and like what that
actually means like there's like some
lingo that I don't understand uh because
it's like I guess ship lingo
worship lingo
somewhere all listening yay yay yay for
the ones who want to hear more German
from me this is your chance there's a
lot of lines many many lines
[Music]
I feel like they were
um
about as much as the counter side lines
because for counter side we had a
million lines as well
I think this one came pretty close as
well I don't really remember but I think
so
[Music]
don't think there's any
special arts though I think they're just
using
the default picture because I don't
remember checking any Arch
so that's a little bit sad I think
is there do I remember anything
I don't think yeah they're just using
normal default pictures
[Music]
well well
looking forward to trying it out
it's been around for a long time that
game
from
what I've seen what I know
[Music]
so it has probably still big
player base a decent big enough to keep
it up to keep the game up for
a long time
[Music]
so what does that tell us it must be
good
[Music]
I'll definitely watch some bits or
streams that involve the collab and see
if I'm interested okay
I'm not forcing any of you but you know
we've waited so long to release that and
now hopefully
hopefully the
the
people behind it
are happy with
whatever it brings
[Music]
I'm gonna use it as like a lightning one
no
you girls and more games is so damn cool
yeah because I mean as long as those
games are out there available to play
we will be eternally engraved into them
and that's really cool
[Music]
games I know eventually
I heard about uh remember like back in
the day long long long long long long
time ago we did a collab with that
gotcha
was it called
yeah
pretty con
precon princess connect yeah
apparently that one is one is uh
shutting down
now
but for for that one we never we only
made streams right we never were
implemented into the game back then I
was thinking I hope I hope someday they
can include us in the game somewhere oh
just the end version
um
yeah English gacha games the the English
versions of them are dying often
oh yeah Kelly made a song for them
right
that was for them oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
yeah
rest in peace
got your game
sad
but such is life
it is what it is
n't it
[Music]
um
thank you
but the other games we've been part of
from what I know are still like running
up and running like what uh
counter signed
now World of Warships what else what
else what else what have we been part of
you know uh there's so many oh yeah
Valkyrie connect
and
blue archive yeah we never we never we
weren't implemented in those though but
yeah it's still running
we were just like doing
some streams for them I guess
[Music]
um
yeah yeah there's a couple
epic seven I did a song cover for them
oh
Shadow first yeah no Shadow versus no
kiwawa in shadowverse uh I'm August
amongst yeah true that is a big one
a big one
that's crazy thinking about that
we were in that we are in a mogus that's
that's a game where I think
we will not see that one
going or like disappearing
for a long long long time right
there may not be a Chihuahua accessory
but still
there is plenty of like
whole life stuff in it
and that's so cool that we're like
eternally almost eternally at least for
now represented
in a huge ass game like that
um
that's so cool
it is
[Music]
maybe you can't get the
the accessories
anymore but
the ones who have it can wear it
forever forever forever forever let's
fix your eyes now because it's freaking
me out too
[Music]
they just need some light then it looks
much
better
freaking me out though
I hate my art
today I'm not as positive anymore
today
I don't like it
I simply don't like it
[Music]
I'm having fun drawing a tutorial
you guys would say you like anything
from me
so
you wouldn't tell me okay wow your art
is [\h__\h]
you wouldn't tell me that
and you know I need I need you guys
no
I need that too
[Music]
I appreciate that very much
foreign
I'm always honest
um
I can't run as well yeah I mean I guess
it's better than a stick man but still
[Music]
necklace supposed to be lying on top of
her collarbone but nope that didn't
that didn't work out and there's no undo
button [\h__\h] hell
so the Finish
brush is still
still not thin enough
oh no I had that nice skin gradation
here now it's [\h__\h] up
[Music]
oh still making yeah yeah
yeah yeah yeah thanks guys I won't give
her clothes now I will I will uh
say goodbye to the tatas
I can't reach
goodbye
[Music]
Palm tools sure good for you
there's a lot of lace on the edge of her
thingy but I don't know if I can draw
what the lace me
maybe just keep it simple but like
um
foreign
[Music]
I'm not even trying to make it like
super accurate this is fine
[Music]
it should just roughly resemble lace
there we go
[Music]
there we go yo that's fine not food she
has clothes Hallelujah I mean it didn't
make it any less add City
[Music]
I feel like her head is
well
foreign
[Music]
that's not an improvement no of course
it is it is I actually I like it I like
them
I I kind of want one of these for myself
to wear on stream but no oh [\h__\h]
I was hoping for that to look
differently
um
no problem see now now it is kind of
what I wanted it to be like Yahoo
I think we all want that hey I still
don't know guys I'm I still have this
idea but I'm not sure if I should really
go for it for
you know I have my 2022 outfit coming up
in the next one or two months
um
but I'm also planning for I have to plan
for the 2020 free one
which won't be a thing until the end of
the year really but this time hopefully
um before 2024.
that is the goal
[Music]
and for 2022 obviously I already know
what I'm doing won't tell you but I know
and it's in the works and it's looking
hella good it's looking incredible
it's gonna I think be very well liked by
you guys
and yeah I'm very excited for it
very happy for it and then for 2022 well
well well
at 2023 I mean
difficult I don't know what to do
I don't know
I don't know yet
I mean I have this idea but I don't know
if I should really commit to it and now
I feel like you know if I get it like at
the end of the year like in December
having to decide on it now what if what
if by then I feel unsure about it but
now I have to decide really this is
actually unusually early
we're just deciding this early because
we want to try getting hookah Papa again
normally it doesn't have to be a whole
like year in advance or so
it has to be early but not not like not
like this early you know
[Music]
oh God uh
yeah we're just in the hopes of getting
hookah Papa again
um we wanna make up our mind really
early
but I am brilliant unsure I mean I felt
like I was pretty sure about it but uh
no I'm not
[Music]
but I don't know yeah
yeah I think I'll just go for it because
I think it's at least an original idea
that hasn't been overdone a million
times you know because there's other
things of course that I would like to
see on myself as well but that have been
overdone and and I think it's nice to do
something original that's why I like all
these all these outfit reveals always so
much because it's always something
completely unexpected and and
mind-blowing and
yeah different something the others
haven't done yet that's why I love her
like like glamorous shopping girl outfit
princess outfit so much
like what the [\h__\h] yo let's go yeah
she's very wild with it not saying that
I will go like wild only style but
at least I want to go with a concept I
guess then
that stands out that's different that's
fun
um
so I guess I might go over I haven't I
haven't like finalized it yet but I
guess I'll go with that
[Music]
foreign
I probably will end up going with that
um
more more fun to be different yeah
[Music]
um
foreign
[Music]
that works okay I think that's okay
you're fine they're fine
yeah
I think I'm pretty happy with this now
and come
what else is there did I forget
something
she has the sleep mask but I don't want
to draw that one
um this sounds drunk I drew everything
I don't like the eyes though I don't
like the way I draw eyes man why draw
eyes like this [\h__\h] deviant art style
why is it so cringe
I need to figure out a new drawing style
man hmm
[Music]
no I used to like really like the way I
drew eyes but that was years ago
no no hey the hair looks better sideways
I think
[Music]
yeah I think it looks better sideways
foreign
[Music]
yes I guess that's all right
can we get a little bit
um
of a lip color yeah
yeah I'll just have to fix it okay
lips on anime art are so difficult man
because like you really have to make it
subtle
and small yeah and now it's kind of
inexistence I could kind of delete too
much
[Music]
foreign
yeah it can be so uncanny if you do it
weirdly or it has to fit your art style
basically
what would it take for you to light the
eyes yeah you gotta look different I
just gonna try different ways of drawing
eyes
I liked the way I did the gradient in
there well once I finalized them and I
look at it I'm like damn
I hate my art
that's literally the best thing you draw
no I think that's the hair for me I like
the way I draw hair the way I shade in
general the way I do shadows and lights
I personally like it I mean here I'm I'm
still like I can't do everything
the way I would normally do it
I'm like limited in options
but still
I like what I do
[Music]
generally
I would still hair would look even
better if I had a proper drawing program
but but so far I mean for what it is
I like it
I mean
old school 80s anime that's what I don't
want I don't want my art to look so old
we had this discussion before
that's what I don't like
it looks so outdated
well I can't help it because this is how
I used to draw back in the day and
it's just like your art style is not
something you can change so easily in my
opinion like it's just it's what comes
naturally for you and then if you want
to change it up you kind of gotta force
it
at least that's how it feels like to me
but damn I like this area
I'm looking at it in a much bigger
screen than you guys probably but I
really like the way it came out with the
watercolor
mm-hmm
yeah I think I'm done let's finish this
[Music]
we gotta finish it somewhere because
it's already 11 P.M
um
what do we title this
[Music]
oh wait I forgot one thing it's probably
not noticeable but
[Music]
um
sleepy Ruby oh I like it
sleepy reaping
uh
uh bye bye sleepy reapee you're gonna be
sold oops
let's see how much sleepy repeat sells
for let's go oh on you Lady
she isn't she doing the car lady she
might have a lot of money
your craft is only as good as your tools
which are crap [\h__\h] what I used
expensive tools that you don't have in
the beginning of the game what the [\h__\h]
is her problem what oh this is the pink
check yeah that is pink check [\h__\h] you
lady [\h__\h] you that makes no sense
oh
okay here comes another
money guy he should have some money
oh he doesn't that doesn't sound bad
though tempting my inner Rebel are we so
that doesn't sound like he doesn't like
it but he just doesn't want to offer
money for it
[Music]
come on
I know great critics they all tell me
this is weak [\h__\h] you
yeah the bull I should have like put
poop on your car
[Music]
what
why does Tina like it bring me the other
ones that actually pay me money and
respect this one pretty much got it all
yeah but your the numbers don't speak
for
they don't match with what you're saying
to me
um
look at how much money I got in my bank
and then you will understand what
expectations I got for you
in terms of pricing
all right here we go another new bank
man money man
okay look at it don't look at my Empty
Easel look at that yeah yeah but I don't
understand what you want
is it the pink algorithm nah they
wouldn't like bring it over to such an
improved version of their game I don't
believe it
I don't believe it
now this is diverse as the Market's
demand
what wait a second
no no
I spent
so much time on this I used all kinds of
tools
so it's like on the same level as my
other great Selling paintings
in terms of that there's not as much
different colors they're all like pretty
red maybe it's maybe it's a lack of
color variety not necessarily that it's
pink but just because it's like similar
tones all over but that shouldn't be a
problem like good art often just comes
with like a like many of the same colors
it doesn't always have to be like
rainbows
that doesn't it doesn't mean that a good
piece of art has to be a [\h__\h] rainbow
oh he's so slow please
good variety and we were just talking
about that
um
700 no
Punk just didn't offer anything okay
it's getting a bit better though they
don't want to bite because it's good
they feel intimidated by sleepy Ruby
braggadocious what does that mean George
huh
do they really not like pink
I'll keep it worst case Okay the chef
the chef surprised me last time
because he was the only one who offered
good money
[Music]
try something more crowded than Earthly
no oh
I understand art guys
what the [\h__\h] is wrong with you what
Emily should love it she loves pink but
does she have money no no way that she
can offer me what I deserve
but she will like the pink I think
that is much better thank you the only
person that likes pink here I'm gonna
give it up to her
thank you Emily what the mommy's credit
card oh
thank you soon
maybe that's baby version of Emily the
one that Cali uh collabs sometimes with
right
I wonder how much Paul would have
offered but I don't think anyone loves
it Pink as much maybe maybe really
everybody hates pink but in order to
balance it out a little bit
that's why this little girl character
exists
to give the few pink
paintings a chance let's look at what we
did to die I don't think we did much it
doesn't feel like much like not not
something not much interesting we did
this flag
and what the [\h__\h]
it's cut off
bug
that's a bug
can I watch it again
that one's bugged out
uh
we're gonna Splatoon no need to look at
that we did uh um Juarez all right let's
look at my chicken
foreign
gotta hide the the precious parts
cute I love it wait I should download it
see I have to look at it again yeah the
car can we look at the car too
I wonder if it turns it when I turned it
maybe you cannot look at the car
[Music]
see okay
saved that one let's look at all in
um
a great zombie
whoa oh technique technique
cute smile
using some nice red tones there is some
pink in there but not not too much to
anger everybody I guess
[Music]
um
ah princess Ali cute
[Music]
yum
nice jewelry
yeah yeah okay
I like it
looking at it now it's fine this is
decent coloring and I can't
oh no I don't think we can look at the
car I don't see a car oh no wait never
mind here it is
[Music]
ah but you only see it from one side
I can't turn it can I no
[Music]
[Laughter]
it looks like a four-year-old painted
this car with its crayons and then Mommy
comes home or daddy comes home and it's
like
Jonathan
's name is
my son what have you
have you no
okay and then last but not least we have
the Sleepy reaping
oh
that was an attempt at a at an angle but
I I failed miserably
but I think you the boobies came out
good
the shading overall came out good
the face proportions I think were okay
no I like that I tried the
the glowy thing in the in the lashes
and I'm playing around with the tools
the hair looks gorgeous
yes
she looked beautiful naked as well
no it's not it looks like it's just
frontal I wish there was an angle but
nice cute kind cute
pretty pretty cute
the choker looks no worse I like the
like the the contrast of the pastel pink
with the black mmm hot hot hot
nice and nicely very BL posted on
Twitter again yeah
uh okay
[Music]
I'm gonna read some super chats maybe
not all I don't know but um let's read
some of them so I don't fall too much
behind uh
top top
oh I feel
not so good but
let me take a fruit candy
[Music]
fantastic stream nah thank you
thank you soon
thank you very much I hope you enjoyed
it didn't you want to do shorts yeah but
I mean what this is short just four
hours this is short
not badly
oh this was your no no no
I have no streams please don't make an
impression on this one you may have
liked it but I have better streams too
um
[Music]
okay let's go to my office
let's go to my office
I look cute with the glasses don't I
don't know
I'm not even here yet
um where am I
where am I
[Music]
foreign
there I am
I don't know who got sent away I'm sorry
I'll check later
and and bring you back don't worry
[Music]
okay there we go here we go
let me
save and close the game what I have ten
thousand over ten thousand bucks now in
the game damn
pretty rich
for these games standards making good
money because I'm spending so much time
on the art
at least you get what you invest in it
mostly
you might find that your style is too
old but retro is so in right now
thank you for listening it was a great
way to think it was great thank you
thank you thank you thank you that's
very sweet
um
[Music]
wow
let's read superchado Flappy boy thank
you
and what does that mean Auto Didact what
does that mean
[Music]
oh
oh but um
formal training I mean I was an art
school but in art school we didn't
really draw people and I wasn't there
for so long we threw like
I guess we had some like
um Shadow studies and all that in like
traditional Arts but
I wouldn't say that really helped me
much with my art because it was so short
and I already was like
pretty much on the same level that I am
on now
at that point like I didn't improve
since then because I didn't do much art
since then
um
but at that time I would say I was like
pretty close to the same level that I am
on now
and yeah
that was I guess self-taught then in
that case
um
just drawing lots and lots and lots of
anime with my little pen tablet that I
had back in the day
it was like my biggest Hobby
I was hoping to make money with it
and now I am making money with it inside
passport two wow dream come true finally
I'm here
[Music]
you should do more drawing streams I
find them quaint and if you're looking
to improve your Gap practice yeah that's
true but
um
wait
I've done well I've done drawing streams
in the past
and I mean I'm open to sorry I'm moving
this thing
I'm open to doing them again but now
we're getting plenty of art from
this game so it's basically an art
stream like it literally is
[Music]
thank you guys thank you thank you
fondly reminisce about Sailor Moon
um
but Sailor Moon looks better than what I
draw
thanks for the membership
[Music]
okay let me
find the Super Chat that we have to read
where did we stop reading
which was the stream where we haven't
read yet
okay see that was supposed to be
yesterday so that's why I scheduled my
Minecraft for yesterday because I
thought she was gonna stream Minecraft
yesterday but her
some cable or something didn't arrive
apparently
according to her Twitter
[Music]
I scheduled it just because I thought I
could maybe if I stream long enough
overlap with her and I did end up
streaming long enough it could have
happened but no she doesn't know though
she doesn't know that I scheduled it on
that day for that purpose
um oh I'm guessing I have to read the
fridge review super chats uh
uh or did I read the ones from the zatzu
[Music]
do somebody know
oh good night UF mods
no no problem I believe you I trust you
I love you I'm sister yeah thankfully
other members popped in so
guys do you you don't remember well let
me check if I remember these names
um
[Music]
yeah I read those before I remember this
red super chat with the merchandise Monk
I think I think I read these before yep
yep yep yeah I think so I mean correct
me if I'm wrong but I think I did so I'm
gonna read the first review Once because
I don't think I Read Super chats since
then
God I can't breathe
[Music]
hello cat
I feel like I had a dreamwear a doctor
acknowledged that I had asthma and I was
so happy
[Music]
that was a good dream and in that sense
huh
meows movie what's up
[Music]
why are you meowing at me so angrily
like ah you look like a cat what
happened to you Mommy
what is it good morning good morning
sunshine
she's telling me about her dream because
she just woke up too hi
oh
[Music]
I always say it
oh yeah it's 11 p.m it's it's a time
where
mommy is maybe close to finishing her
stream
oh she's so soft I want you so shocked
[Music]
you went to Disney World with your
family nice dream
maybe make it reality
good morning from Sydney Australia
good morning indeed thank you for uh
stopping by
oh
oh okay cat behind monitor now
cat escape
oh [\h__\h]
Super Taco Time
Mickey Mouse
Jacob 47 out soon
Jeff start thank you for the pinky
sadly I'm going to miss it but have fun
thank you thank you Jeff thank you soon
I appreciate it maybe you watched the
archive by now did you enjoy it
hopefully
Clipper me Danke Schoen volchuk100
thank you for the pinky
hey while I came back to Korea yesterday
after working and traveling uh mestia
and ushkuli in Georgia
for six months oh
but I can't watch stream because
situation here wasn't good bad Wi-Fi or
something sorry I mean have a good time
thank you
thank you for letting me know that
you're back welcome back did you enjoy
maybe no Wi-Fi but now you have
hopefully some time to catch up with my
streams
but you don't have to maybe only the
ones that interest you you must have
missed a lot six months man
what did you not watch any streams at
all
damn
if that's the case then good luck to you
now
this is a long time but I'm glad to have
you back welcome back
[Music]
I don't know many today yeah that's a
million hours of odd time oof good luck
yeah
you won't be complaining when I go on a
break because then you can catch up with
everything you missed
um
yeah uninterrupted enjoyment
and I'm So Fire
domination for the regular chat thank
you is best guy heart
trying to copy near Osama huh there were
someone sometimes doesn't know the the
gender of the person she talks to
that's okay it's okay hot hot I will
forgive everything nuro says hi Thai
Thai
cannot be
mad mad at her
um
noodle Chan is great hot hot
yeah yeah thank you speaking Heim I hope
you liked the collaboration
why did you not send me a picture of
your cat in the fridge huh so many
others did and you didn't
that's fine
most most of those photos they said that
their cats went in there on their own
but some people have staged their photo
but it's okay the cats look pretty happy
on them
it's nice to be in the fridge for once
it's a new environment can sniff all the
food hmm sniff
spanking time thank you
oh another pinky noodle Channel noodle
arms Chan together
uh I am the noodle lady
um
if it fits they sits exactly
and noodle armchon
then the noodle the pasta the pasta
girls where the pasta girls together
nice unit name
[Music]
cats usually like warm though yeah but I
think they wouldn't like mind
as long as you don't close the door
and you put them in there I think they
would find it interesting to be there
and I mean there's some cats like when
you let cats outside
um in the winter they don't mind playing
a bit in the snow I mean it depends on
the cat I've seen some who don't like
snow and I've seen some who do like snow
I could not stay to my fridge no problem
you have geckos cute
do yours I don't know they never touched
snow I think
no
I want to give them a garden
I have by the way
I think changed my mind again
about whether or not I wanna
Buy
a a home
because I was looking at the prices for
something that's like equal to what I
live in now
more or less in terms of size and like
modernness and all that
and with a garden I mean I don't have a
garden now but I looked at something
that has a garden
and
well
I mean maybe if I look for at first I
was thinking about house right and then
I was like maybe I'll get a apartment
instead so it's cheaper but it really
isn't cheaper at all
um but if I wanted to be
in a city and not on the countryside
than damn the prices
are crazy
and I I I did a calculation
which opened my eyes
I calculated
me paying
um for example the rent that I pay right
now
[Music]
for another like 50 years
compared to this pretty much equivalent
apartment
um
I will not say how much that apartment
costs but holy moly
it is
um
it is like
uh
wait is eight times or eight eighty
eighty times I think 80 times
as expensive
to buy that thing
then me just paying this rent for 50
years
continuously
so why the [\h__\h] would I do this
yeah I think it's something like 80
times
in any case it's like it's adding
um
no wait maybe eight times maybe eight
times never mind maybe eight times wait
wait wait wait
we're talking we're talking about let's
say Okay me continuously paying this
rent for 50 years or so let's say it's
like something around I don't know 100
20 250 000 Maybe
okay
for 50 years
and then the apartment would be like
yeah okay seven to eight times as much
so why would I do why would anyone do
that I think it only makes sense if
you're planning on
like renting it out to someone
or if you live some with someone
together there and share the cost
but I've realized
with these prices
it makes no sense I would just like
waste my money
unless I want to be on the countryside
yeah yeah I could sell it at a later
Point sure sure but I'm looking for
something that I want to keep for myself
or hopefully as long as possible I mean
I do see the option I could oversell it
if I change my mind and all that but
this doesn't this didn't seem worth my
investment and and I wouldn't I wouldn't
even have the funds for that uh I would
have to save money for a while longer
so I couldn't even buy it right away if
I want to but that's not the normal way
people do it anyway apparently paying it
all up front
um
yeah yeah but so I I thought
no
then it would it seems more fun to
every like five years or so move to a
new apartment
at least when you don't own one
then you can move around and check out
different places and you're free like
you don't have to bind yourself to
something
and still I will save hundreds of
thousands of euros
of rent
um
so I guess I will never be a homeowner
hmm
yeah yeah if I just rent it I can like
see all kinds of different places and
I'm sure I can find a garden apartment
uh for rent that I've seen some like um
years ago and I was like apartment
hunting I've seen some I think owning a
house is still worth it yeah maybe only
if I get like you know
married and children and all that but I
don't ever see that happening
so I mean if that were to ever happen
Okay then I can consider it yeah
but with nothing inside
I don't see any meaning in
uh
but maybe what I could do as a passive
income I was looking at some really
cheap
shitty Apartments like really tiny ones
one one room to two rooms apartment like
really small ones
to just buy and then rent out as a
passive income I'm considering that
still but it feels like complicated I
don't know how to do that I don't know
what you need to do to do man
don't scam students no no no no no
I would not ask for crazy amounts
I feel like my place is overpriced I
wouldn't want to do that to anybody else
[Music]
yeah I've seen some relatively
affordable places I'm just wondering
like if something like breaks and all
that how do I as the homeowner I think I
can hire someone to take care of that
kind of like
[Music]
uh
what's the word
no maintenance and stuff like that
um
it's a caring for the apartment I think
somebody you can hire someone for that
and then all I have to do is like
sign the papers hopefully
yeah
yeah yeah a management company
or so
um
I don't I wouldn't know what to do I
would just hand it over completely
what do you do if the renter doesn't pay
that's okay
it's okay I will make them pay they have
to pay I mean
they'll be fine it will be fine
I will yell at them if they don't pay
um
I don't make them pay yeah okay I mean
what do you do then you kick them out if
they don't pay for what I don't know
three four months what is the acceptable
time of months to kick somebody out
I'll victim I mean that's okay
[Music]
two moms
really
[Music]
one free
two two three no okay no no
that's okay hmm
I mean that's a weird question what
would I do just what anybody else would
do
kick him out and maybe you know get a
lawyer and then have them pay it
eventually in rates or whatever I don't
care
[Music]
well I can't breathe oh yeah that's what
the that is what the Yeah the down
payment is for the security deposit
right I could use the security deposit
and then if that's used up and they're
still not paying then they get evicted
um
two is free no no I said two or three
you've got the landlady mentality
already there you go
yeah of course it's all then yeah like
crazy things can can happen of course
blee blah blue
but I feel like as a passive income for
the future as well
would be smart to have something like
that no
just gonna get like a really small one
um
did you hear in the distance yeah I
think that was Stronger still
don't worry I'm not gonna like blindly
randomly jump into it maybe I can like
maybe there's like some kind of like
information around somewhere
or I don't know maybe I can find an
acquaintance who has done it before or
is doing it
and can get their advice or so on it
although that's unrealistic I don't
think I have any friends like that in my
friend Circle
um
[Music]
that's not really the kind of people I'm
around
a realtor can help find an investment
um your current landlord lady as well ah
that that's interesting I wonder if that
would be weird to ask them
they are scammers though
they're scammers
I think my current ones are scammers if
I feel so scammed in so many ways
um
yeah yeah and the basement for example
what the [\h__\h] that's not the only thing
though the price in general like I've
been comparing my my place to others and
I just feel scammed
um
[Music]
oh well oh well oh well so anyway that's
just an update I I changed my mind on
getting a place for myself
I'll just continue renting for my whole
life because
buying property is too expensive
maybe if I really end up getting
um a license in the car eventually then
I can consider looking at places outside
of cities but I don't know when that's
gonna happen so I don't want to make a
commitment yet you know
hmm
oh yeah
but once I have a car I don't I don't
need to have a house by a lake I can
just drive to the lake I guess
no I can't drive and I don't have a
license yet I was never gonna get one
but I changed my mind I wasn't gonna
ever get one because I was scared as
[\h__\h]
um
and most of the time I didn't really
need one
yeah yeah
yes of your own also the responsibility
sounds so highs and again the
maintenance like
you know
that's scary too
especially if I'm the only one living in
it besides my cats
yeah
man I can't breathe
um
squid coyote thanks for the pinky and
there was Salma and kiwawa let's go
let's go
I'm happy that you're hype about it
thank you very much
for supporting this coolable
appreciate it
thank you
maybe sometime we can do something like
that again
have you ever tried driving a car no not
really I mean I've been in like a
like a go-kart
but I'm guessing that doesn't count
uh
shiton or Fortune [\h__\h] on mic for ton
Mike
Bruce Jenny Lee Duncan I understand
dryness androgynous Jack I don't know
how to say your name is
androgenus
okay
was that right
Mr Caspian boohoo 723 Duncan Absol wait
did I say Cyrus
[Music]
I'm gonna use my GTA and Mario Kart
skills I'm worried I feel like I'm gonna
be a very bad driver
but I mean
so many people managed to get a license
so many people managed to drive a car
normally
it can't be that difficult then
yeah I guess I'll figure it out
it seems overwhelming now but it's
probably not that difficult right
um
but I prefer to be driven
can you guys just drive me please
chicken shotsu
[Music]
um
yo if I were like the cause of some
accident oh my God I don't know how I
was
I would feel so [\h__\h] bad but at least
I will never have the issue of driving
drunk
because I don't get drunk I don't drink
alcohol so that will never be
a reason for me to get into an accident
[Music]
and that is I guess the biggest reason
behind accidents
alcohol or different kinds of influences
um
I don't have any of those
I am responsible straight edge driver
hey
[Music]
foreign
texting and driving nah I wouldn't do
that at the same time I don't trust
myself I can't I already know I can't do
that
um
people still drive like maniacs oh man
one
maybe owning your own car would be
motivation no no I don't need like
motivation for it right now I just need
time so I've decided to do it whenever I
leave you know my job so afterwards
then I have time and then I'll do it and
at the moment I don't need it
I'm fine
wow yeah
yeah timeline
I I get ready to come by with the
company but it's nice
so never right
yeah never never never
oh I love you guys
wow I will be around
for as long as I can
and as long as there's demand for me I
guess
so as long as you guys are here
hopefully
just don't go you won't want me to go I
don't want you to go
I demand you well I demand you
I demand you to be here
[Music]
it's nice to be to be desired man
I can't let that feeling go so don't
worry guys I'll be here
taking my salary for a long time yeah I
can't just leave
laughs
what a coincidence it seems I wish is a
line
over here as long as you are kiwawa yay
thank you
a call
my book is getting published today oh
you have a book congratulations what is
it about
who are we going to pay if you leave I
guess yourself
I guess
[Music]
um
time to pay yourself finally
science fiction action adventure humans
versus god wow that sounds ambitious
good luck
and well where was I
um
so I feel like sorry
sorry because I feel like hasn't been
around much but then suddenly now now
we're here again is this just me I feel
like cyrick wasn't around much for a
while
what's up what's up
they were around for AOE
it was lurking
why are you lurking don't hide from me
show your face
[Music]
doesn't always lurk
no lurking no no
you beat him out
but AOE I have to plan ahead like a
whole week I don't like that
um
we all have our lurker face
I guess in the beginning mostly but why
are you going back to lurking
yeah Cyrus is Europe
Germany as far as I remember
so it's good times to be here I'm trying
to learn less thank you hi
[Music]
how you doing
looking right now at this very moment no
now you're not
I'm lucky because I'm working that's
okay then
it's important for you to make money to
pay your rent
um
um we facts of the pinky
what the [\h__\h]
we fasting what the [\h__\h]
what
ah wait that's because of uh I get it
now because of the diaper because of the
diaper okay this has context this needs
context remember the diaper okay okay I
was trying to put diapers on you yeah
also because um I think newer summer
said that the chickens have been like
pooping and packing right yeah yeah yeah
okay so with that context let's read the
super chat now
ah I can't stop pooping everywhere help
me Kiana
there you go now
we are all
understanding of what this is about okay
it's not weird at all
the QV faction
um I guess you will be one user of the
diapers
you will need it sounds like you need it
I'll get you one come over here I'll put
it on you you guys a lot of you guys
were like no I don't want the diaper not
no no no but do you guys realize
I would be one I would be the one
putting it on you
don't you want that hmm
why are you embarrassed
hmm
don't you want me to put you on my
office desk
and
put a diaper on you
no
so I guess you guys are shy after all
and you need that leaf after all
uh I want to put that drawing I made of
you on my on my idea board behind me
I want to frame it I want to put it up
somewhere
Chihuahua criticized that Yakuza side
quest
well no no it's not like I'm just I'm
just wondering why you guys don't like
it you know I don't particularly like
the idea but I mean I'm just wondering
why you guys don't like it
[Music]
see it as I'm putting underwear on you
there's no difference
hmm
foreign
this is a difficult
um conversation it seems like we're not
finding a ground a neutral ground
[Laughter]
I'm confused I really didn't expect this
kind of reaction
I thought you would find it cute and and
you know
perhaps a little bit exciting
ah okay okay
[Music]
[Laughter]
well whatever I I guess I
don't know ah
okay no diapers then okay okay okay just
be careful okay don't poop in their
osama's Garden okay
hahaha
pooping yeah okay we don't want any
complaints
I don't want to be banned from collabing
with her
damn it what glove thumbnail situation
what is that I don't remember that
I'm potty trained cute
potty trained chicken
[Laughter]
can you draw a fat cute fluffy chicken
on top of a little potty
no like a toddler
thank you Mom thank you immediately
saying okay while all the others are
like what the [\h__\h] but it's gonna be
cute I know dacoma will draw it cute
[Music]
um
it's natural it's just a chicken on a
toilet okay and we should be proud that
we have gotten chickens this far
um
to learn something like that high
intelligence chickens these are high
intelligence chickens if I've ever seen
anything
um yeah
I spent hours and hours teaching you
this is what you learned in the usual
room
no you cannot Tacoma is not listening to
you takuma is already drawing you cannot
get to her you cannot stop her she's on
it now
mm-hmm
this is foreign
[Music]
oh
stop talking to dakama dakama is busy
drawing okay
stop
um
okay let's redefine blem super chats
[Music]
complaints department
Oh I thought the complaint was gonna be
about the diapers no the complaint is
about the pooping well there you go guys
well you've done it to yourself
you have done it to yourself guys
don't blame me
are you sure you want to read most of
those super chat why
why
[Music]
is it because it's too many or is there
something yeah I was looking at the at
that too but it's okay I'll get through
it
ah yeah
uh I was thinking maybe I should read
this Minecraft ones first what am I
streaming tomorrow by the way I forgot
foreign
[Music]
oh God tomorrow is members and with us
fight okay with the fight
um
[Music]
so much to prepare
um
yeah okay let's skip Fire Emblem
what am I in the other times I have
Thief simulator which is not gonna be a
long stream and then whole talk which is
not long but I'm not like doing
chats after that
okay
yeah let's call it the day it'll be fine
it's not too much like in general it's
not too much but that's just don't feel
so well and I need to go to sleep early
anyway I still need to cook but I'm
going to cook one more of those really
quick meals
and
then I'm gonna
even do my homework no
or tomorrow morning I think I'll do it
now afterwards after eating or so and
I'm not gonna do the really quick let's
do the whole talk tweet
um
[Music]
I always need to like search
the tweets for the like template
[Music]
here if I type this will I find my
template
no
um
toku
[Music]
H what that's not an evil ah I found I
found the solar Senpai one there we go
this should be fine copy paste
control
guy
no no
you need
it
[Music]
blue
blah
okay
and then here
[Music]
because I was looking for Clips I ended
up watching a little bit of her debut
stream and her debut stream confused me
because
she played she had a game collab in her
debut stream with the other Gamers
within that stream
within that one hour it was only one
hour but they played Splatoon yeah her
debut was so weird yeah right
it was is that how old Gamers did their
debut and I just don't remember him I
mean I mean I wasn't around at their
debuts but yeah
they sent them in to save her I wonder
was that planned
only colony
they were asked to come there the last
moment to save her oh damn see that's
something we can talk about in the in
Hollow talk okay
um
okay posting it
uh now let me prepare the community
community board one
[Music]
um
Channel
uh Community yo here also I have to
scroll down to find my last holotalk
post
which has been a while
when was the last one I didn't even like
you know want to take such a big break
again when it happened
um
is
today wait when you say today do you
mean the 19th or the 20th
oh
I found it
[Music]
ah
yeah for fast and the 3dws like a lot of
things happened so it was on the back
burner for sure
and the questions for this week's
episode live
the rest I think was always the same
[Music]
okay picture
thank you for staying with me while I'm
doing this
okay I'm gonna post this no
[Music]
happy birthday okay Papa wait I still
have a I still have the Popeye mode hmm
it's really not being used for a long
time so that's when I could consider
getting rid of when I if I need a space
and questions here please there we go
okay
yeah but it would be kind of sad
I mean I mean
I mean my abandonment issues the Papa's
face
we never use what why don't you I think
if I spawn is very useful the face palmy
mode
I think it's useful
okay let me send this to Kona
cool nickel now
[Music]
never use Facebook because it feels rude
towards you
I mean it doesn't always have to be
necessarily used towards me but if I
tell you some about something that is
Facebook worthy that happened to me but
it's like not towards me it's like
towards the person involved in the in
the story or so I don't worry about it
I think it can be used don't worry
[Music]
definitely has its uses
normally you just say Kiana that makes
me aggressive that that's rude
you better use the face palm
nah I don't know
but okay maybe that's
the way I feel about the Kiara dot is
how you feel about the face palm don't
worry I mean both is maybe in that
context in any situation where you would
Kiara dot me then the Facebook would I
guess also not be desirable yeah yeah
yeah
um
uh
okay guys
I've done that
and then I have some deadlines but I'll
get to them on my day off
was there something else no I think just
having to do my Korean homework
um
apparently tomorrow I'm Gonna Learn
numbers
um
from what she sent me it seemed like
she's gonna
teach me numbers tomorrow
um
one two five and the numbers in between
yeah
you're promising well yeah probably I
will be able to say like I have five
apples stuff like that
people know what they mean the numbers I
will know
um
I want to practice until the next Korean
lesson
I wanted to practice and do my homework
but no it's already the night before
it wasn't supposed to be like that
I want to be a good student now I'm
doing everything last minute hmm
oh man
uh then now it's the same day so I'm
gonna go now and in German we stay up
videos and thanks for watching today ah
let's check another
[Music]
look how is this not desirable and cute
look at this bamboo
cute
so small I thought it would be bigger
compared to the party it's like 2
so like a toddler on the potty is
usually also a little bit bigger than
that
I think this this chicken is using wait
if it's a if it's a baby chicken then it
should be here
it should be yellow aren't you guys
yellow when your baby
this chicken is posing as a baby
[Music]
[Laughter]
it is cute but still
you have fallen yeah you're not able to
get out should I help you if you need a
hand
it looks like you're you're stuck in
there and you can't get up because your
legs are like too short
cute
no you don't need help really really
you're gonna be stuck there forever
aren't you
okay
okay okay
I'm Gonna Leave You on the potty now
I'm Gonna Leave You There good luck
getting out if you change your mind just
just to buck buck really loudly okay and
I'll help you
I'll help you I'll keep my ears open
um
[Laughter]
Health after all okay I'm gonna go get
you
bye bye good night
[Music]
foreign
happy birthday to Christina
also yeah
[Music]
thank you