[Music]
[Applause]
for
[Music]
[Applause]
me Aang hi guys I'm here with a special
[Music]
guesty that what do you have to say what
did you need to say so badly the chat
haven't you been playing this game for
hours yeah and I was watching you you
were doing well and like I was like so
interested how have you not made it over
3,000 yet shut up man come on there's
look there is a certain level of luck
that you need to have okay you need to
be able to get all the fruits that you
need MH in order to but now however I
will say that there are the times where
my skill was not very good are probably
the times where I would have gotten a
double
sua In fairness all right it's not a
skill issue shut up Chad shut up you
but it seems like you're really really
really desperate to get those 3,000
points for your own satisfaction is that
why you're playing tonight even though
you already played for 9 hours yeah
am squeaky game serious business here I
don't know if you understand how serious
business the game is cuz you haven't
played it yet I think I'm understanding
because like when I came here and you
were done with your stream and I arrived
and you you were just like chilling I I
caught her playing the sua game just in
her free time join the club join the
club because everyone's playing this
freaking
game everyone is playing it all right
look it's very normal apple and you know
what you're helping me by being here
because I do better when I'm not focused
oh oh that's the thing I have that too
sent why is it like that why does it
have to be that way I don't understand
why is it like that in the end it's it's
all just a big luck game cuz it is a
luck game because when things happen
like the strawberry flying up from here
to here
you know it's going to happen you know
it's going to happen I've never looked
at the game in such a big resolution I
never noticed that the Cherry was so
smug yeah look at how smug he little
what is it called uh what is it um doya
doya it's one of
those it kind of looks a little bit like
um like he's having l
f that's not DOA anymore Ah that's a
good point What would you call
that H cow H
cow me and C we had travel Shadow we did
it was young it was good I I like I like
Shabu Shabu every once in a while cuz
it's kind of like not it's like it's not
like too strong tasting yeah yeah it's
very subtle like it's bland a little bit
but in a good way yeah yeah I get I get
what you mean for sure I'm a big Shabu
Shabu advocate in the first place so
like definitely get that it was good it
was good had some some noodles as well
on the side I hadn't eaten today by the
way didn't want to tell the dead beats
but you cuz they get mad but but I don't
worry we feasted it was fine and I feel
like I'm going to sleep well so don't
worry watch they're all going to get mad
now they're all going to get mad myi I
am
outraged there they go oh my God Callie
Callie Calli dot it's always the CI dot
dot dot man ah do they do that to you
yes and told them many times like it I'm
like don't thought about me don't
thought about me cuz like oh that's like
such
a you think you know better than me Pops
I don't think
so yeah I get you start
[Music]
posting
W wa please the care we definitely have
gotten more careful with with when
they're dotting me when they're allowed
to dot this I give sometimes I give them
permission to dot dot me and then they
may dot dot me I can imagine you beating
their ass for that control of okay I
have I'm at all times I'm strangling
their chicken necks got them by the
balls by the
necks the it's a eup ah damn it it's a
figure speech it's just it's just a
little figure
it's just hey you want to yes yes
let's go
yeah go let's freaking go
okay oh but there's okay so that's the
the the D melon but we want the
watermelon yes correct so in order to
get the watermelon we have to merge a
melon and a melon so we need another one
of these oh my God it's hard to do but
if you line them up correctly you can do
it proper I think this game in some Some
Way shows you how up Society is
yeah we live in a
society where people want you to think
that anything is
possible they give you they give you
some of the tools for it but
then false hopes you get so close to it
and then it's like you yeah you're
not going to get it then you get on
by society and stupid cherries and
raspberries and whatever yeah yeah I
feel you this fruit like I said see
everyone this is what I said this game
is a metaphor for life all right and no
one listens to me like oh my you're
letting the fruits talk for you shut up
it's not true it is pretty rigged and I
I think the developers must have rigged
it on purpose ex they want people to
suffer you have to be born of special
fruit why the won't you
touch which one
oh y anything can happen anything can
happen in this game but it's still not
it's still not the best it's not great
right now I will say it could be grape
though let's go check this shouldn't die
Apple we can make an apple pie unless
you change it into watermelon I don't
think we want to make a watermelon pie
ah watermelon pie could be yummy m if I
Gaslight myself into believing no no no
you don't think so you're really if it's
like you know one of those like tropical
fruit tarts where there's like all kinds
of fruit mixed fruits in jelly on top of
the tart yeah could work could be Ying
good yeah your fruit bowl is looking
like a big mess right now all right well
give it a second because it's about to
look like a masterpiece did you see I
saw something on Twitter today I saw
like a really epic um
a combo from M Senai oh yeah like it
just went from
like like she had like so many epic
combos she couldn't even catch up with
her reactions she was just like watching
it and she was like afterwards after it
happened she like took her another a
second to be like hey yo what and then
she was so so excited about it we had to
play it in slow motion cuz it was so
good dang I want this for you thanks
we'll see if that happens but I'm
getting a bad feeling about this SC this
is bad give it a sec that cherry
are you kidding
me why life isn't fair hold on hold on
hold on a second I see M the
melon's kind of giv a little a little
push a little this is like birth this is
like bir they like pushing it out how is
it like birds the inside of of um with
with I don't know man I don't I feel
like I've seen it before a birth I don't
know you've seen a birth before I mean
have you never seen the birth in the
movie or so no well what of course you
happen not like the details though gab
science pineapple P one two one two
three so so sweet yeah let's
go yeah baby did it this pineapple power
but this bottom still looks like
yeah it does but you know what P
senpai's bottom looked like too
when she almost got a double sua so you
know what anything can happen is what
I'm trying to
say bottom look also look like
don't take it out of context well do you
know they will let's
just I'm never going to live that one
down right we put all the shitty fruits
over here and then pray for a miracle
over here now this is where we need to
pay ATT ention and go slow don't you
want to put it there for n maybe I guess
not I mean here we'll give you a chance
afterwards okay we'll see how you do but
check this look luy first ever sua yeah
first ever sua game for Wawa now this
could be hold
on I don't know how this is going to fit
in the cuz if we
have I'm going to regret this I can tell
wait hold on no it will all come in
shape and place in it's due time yeah I
know I know why are you not giving me a
meon why won't you son of a all
right all right all we're boned it's all
over does every drop that you put there
like have a lot of thought behind it I
mean look I don't really know that
that's something I can
do I'm going to be honest with you
I think we've lost our
chance cuz I made one I made one big
mistake no look at how close we got no
no no no what don't give up yet don't
mess it up on purpose you little I
didn't mess it up on purpose but you
know what that is the best score I've
gotten today okay so man here you do it
thank you you play the game all right
Tak game
Deb let's go how do I drop them all
right so you press a and it's just the
stick and that's all you do it would be
so funny if I get 3,000 on first try
like just as a streamer moment it would
be so good I'll kick you out of my house
I will kick you out so just be ready for
that and just know that that's something
I'm going to do okay now I don't I don't
I don't think such a thing would
happen just
all right well let's see what your
strats are let's see how you approach
this so far it's just simply putting
things together that look the same way
yeah I mean that's that's what you're
supposed to do but you would think right
right but then it turns out that you do
a better job when you don't know what
you're doing I was watching you for
quite a while so I I understand it's not
always it's not it doesn't always go the
way you want it to go yeah I get that
I have the double watermelon
configuration figured out by the way
guys I have a screenshot I'll pull it up
well what is the double watermelon
configuration so this is how you make a
double watermelon I'll show you don't we
already know how to Oh you mean like so
that it fits yeah um I'll show
you these are my screenshots you can see
how that would be
problematic so here's the image um see
how once you get the one watermelon you
want it in the corner uhhuh and then
after that you need to line up the
fruits like this so that when you make
the Fatal drop the drop that merges they
not deserve to
know maybe I'll show
them yeah but it's just one watermelon
yeah but see the thing is they're lining
up all the fruits so that you start to
make the connection right so you connect
these two pairs and they make a peach
and then it makes the peach and then it
hits the pineapple and then it hits the
watermelon and then it hits the
Suka if you can make all of that that
happen you're the luckiest person in the
world I know some you got to have a good
run someone did it somebody got
7,355 points what yeah read it and we so
after this screen youve got to that
correct 16 hours in this one screen game
or I think in general in the to Total
playing the game oh my God that's how
lucky you got to be it's like somebody
in chat said it's like slots kind of
except with fruits and a little more
thought slots like you mean like
like yeah yeah yeah there's a lot of
luck involved if you if you're picking
up what I'm putting down let me see if I
can find the video cuz the video is
pretty cool did they delete it they
deleted it because their power was too
strong hey isn't this looking good for
my first time I don't know I think
you're doing fine I'm having a lot of
big ones a lot of big
pops keep it up hat yeah fruits touch
touch fruits touch
fruits you get quot lucky with the
fruits that that you're given I'm being
lucky you mean right now well I mean the
only way that you get lucky in the game
is by getting good
fruits you know Get Lucky by death up
all night to get every every American
knows this
luck okay pineapple nice pretty good
keep it up it looks clean there's no
mess on the bottom let's see how long
that
lasts it's not me being spite it's not
me being spiteful it's me tempering your
expectations all that's so kind of you
actually I appreciate that no problem
you don't want me to like I want your
feelings to get hurt that's so sweet
yeah you can appreciate that take that
out of context no do not my feelings
would only get hurt if I became such a
like too
obsessed understandable Maniac s maniac
right understandable and it might happen
it might not it might cuz I I'm I think
I'll play it like on Monday or so
yeah how did it feel when that grape
didn't merge with that uh grape I'm fine
because I think they still will yeah do
you know do you know for a fact are you
triggered by the just this thing going
on here maybe a little bit maybe a teeny
tiny bit oh this not good this is not
good no no no it's
fine not good for you I mean for your
heart uh I mean it's not good for
anyone's heart there's a reason that
that so many people are invested in this
game right you guys like watching it
right the drama involved in it kind of
like real housewives you know there's a
lot of drama going on a lot of
competition yeah you know the Desperate
Housewives yeah Desperate Housewives so
we're not having like a Golden Girls
moment right now no we're not what what
what's Desperate Housewives like who who
plays in it um Desperate Housewives is
um a movie featuring it's hold on it's
about um a bunch of ladies that are
Housewives but they're actually the
secret is that they're not humans
they're okay you are absolutely kidding
me right now they're robots there is no
way is it Faith Hill or something like
that girl Hello do not no that's
Desperate Housewives you you're not it
turns out they're all like robots and
stuff like that please tell me you're
not serious and they're all that's step
for
house wait no there is really a thing
like that that's like similar sounding
and just what you describe wives it's
the step oh my
God I didn't thought that was the
Desperate
Housewives
I I thought I thought she already broke
my mind today with something I don't
think you could break my mind twice
today I'm sorry I just get confused a
lot I can't believe this happened
again I was just like ah there's nowhere
it could happen again desate Housewives
what I don't want to live on this planet
anymore I am I don't want to live on the
planet where you don't know this shows
either what is Desperate Housewives it's
like um you know Eva Laria isn't it for
example yeah and and it's like kind of
just it's just a dramatic show of like
some American neighborhood like uh what
do you call like nice neighborhood with
a big
CAC no I mean like what do you usually
call this like
neighborhood a bunch of Rich a a suburb
yeah a suburb and they're like all hot
sexy ladies some of them have kids and
they're robots not no they're not robot
but like yeah there's like drama you
know it goes on for so many seasons like
oh it's a reality
show it's not real reality TV no okay
it's like oh gotcha like Golden Girls or
Gilmore girls I guess so yeah it's not
like the
Kardashians all right I understand now
yeah Housewives
gotta it takes a lot of time to gather
some points huh
oh CH reaction baby she so excited are
you feeling the S of dopamine hit I'm
just surprised that even with all of
this I'm still like under thousand like
it takes a while it does it is harder
than it seems to get above 3,000 I would
like those pineapp to touch at some
point right you would like that would
you however whether they'll give that to
you or not it's yet to be seen it
shouldn't be so difficult all right I
believe uhhuh for sure the American
dream the American dream I have a dream
we're in Japan so I don't know about all
that I don't know about Japanese dreams
what's the Japanese dream um no to eat
Yakiniku every day and not get
fat it must be
maybe I don't know though you'd have to
ask a Japanese person I'm not w w oh I
wonder if those uh pears could touch I
don't think they will though cuz the
pineapples are separating them it's cool
I like how this is looking right now
yeah kind of looks okay to you it
doesn't Inspire anxiety of any it's very
pleasing
really does it make you anxious yeah it
gives me anxiety well look at all these
what is this even a lemon yeah that
little shape yeah there's like there's
four of them they could all combine if
they wanted to yeah but they don't want
to because they want you to
suffer if you hear the voices in your
head well so these two apples will touch
and then they'll become a
pair oh and that that became a peach
pretty good that's good that is good
that is good it's good now we can push
the
andage good good stuff good we're at
1,200 m
that's like half time I'd say that's
decent we'll get to 3,000 and then I'm
like my job is done and I'll just leave
yeah play the game one time get the high
score and get out prove your worth to
this world cuz you're a worthless human
being if you can't reach 3,000 as we all
know are you okay no I'm not are
you okay I'm not at all don't take it to
heart so much I what that'll happen
a lot I was dropping it there yep I know
that'll happen I can't believe you
haven't you haven't destroyed the
controller yet I wouldn't destroy your
property a that's very sweet I'm trying
not
[Music]
to this is a little bit difficult I'm
scared of things to like pop and just
fly out of the screen it happens
sometimes not as much as you as the
clips would have you think oh okay
that's but it does occur sometimes see I
don't want to drop it in here cuz I
don't want to create a barrier for the
peach exactly but if you drop it on the
grap it'll bounce so you have to maybe
get it in the crevice oh
oh okay well now this is a problem hey
who
safe oh I didn't expect that you want to
try again yes what do
you this is stream it's now it's Kiara's
Kar is in control just one more this is
how it's start that was the tutorial cuz
I didn't really cuz it wasn't bouncing I
just put it where I like that was the
line I didn't realize that is the
threshhold that happens quite a few
times too where you think it'll be fine
and then it's
not so get ready for that
but it'll be fine I'll I'll get it now
I'll so nice of cie to guest star on
Kiara's stream oi oi whose channel does
it say this is all right this is
riveting by the way if you get 3,000 it
is my score because it's on my
channel I know you can you can say you
could say it's yours no I'm joking I
would never want such a such a
dishonorable wi but it will always be an
eyore for you like you'll be like yeah I
have those points it'll say best score
it will say best score right there and
it'll be your score forever it'll be
your score in the best score area you'll
never get yes I
will yes I will nothing will stop me is
not right dead
[Music]
beats hey haven't been counting off
stream scores that is true oh the fans
haven't been counting off screen but
they get registered right however yes
but this would be an onstream score it's
just that it would be K well even off
screen you haven't made it to 3,000
correct that is a good point but have
you made it to 3,000 K I am just started
the game K well my point still stands
why am I always in like Japan when like
new hype games are happening and I don't
have the opportunity really to stream it
that's a good point well I mean you'll
be back soon enough I feel like that
happened like last time too I don't know
what it was that's all right um I feel
like the month game Ian is just kind of
starting to get really intense about
swiy game I don't know about JP I feel
like maybe the era of s game people know
that you can't even like buy it normally
I think so in the like non-japanese shop
oh yeah a lot of a lot of dead beats
have been telling me that you know they
get a Japanese account grab a even did
De be of the viewers oh yeah a well a
lot of people also can't play it
themselves right so maybe they like
watching nice imagine if it was free so
they got a new high score yesterday I
was there for that that was wild they
should just put it on Steam know
right she's so smart I need to watch her
and figure out her tactics say were me
so say but you're smart too just in
different ways what's what's special
about suicide tactics she's just
smart Okay well that might I I'm
thinking it's like all the tetris
experience that's what I
mean we need a SAA online game like just
online yeah we need a different game
that isn't this game to make everybody
in Holo super competitive again oh yeah
why not this game cuz it's not meant to
be competitive cuz I hate this game what
no you love it I'm a slave to it the
fruit demons make me play it the fruit
demons yeah I love fruit yeah pretty
tasty looking tasty yum
yums hey maybe a little
physics shove that back push it push it
on push it baby pineapple pineapple hey
nice stream pineapple stream pineapple
or he's a prisoner to the sua
maybe
maybe I have a dead beat who makes um
who archives my super chats for me and I
was reading super chats today and I saw
why does he archive Super Chat for you
because he's
based check this out what what do you
know whole easier it's easier to read
them no this is this is customized for
me oh I've had this before when you know
wasn't there like something about isn't
that awesome I used to do it like this
too like have an EXO sheet made what do
do you have well do you have any Harvard
students in your dead be or dead beats
who who went to Harvard cuz I have two
Harvard students in
kfp and I know there's another Harvard
student in the
taches so what do you got what do you
got we all did every single one I went
and me totally yeah I feel like you're
lying but the point stands look I was
reading the super chats and check this
out I see this little watermelon
like and I say what is this and I click
on it watch
[Music]
this cute oh my God look at this that is
like that is Harvard student quality
work I'm telling you that so I can play
it anytime hey guys if you want to play
game go to my Super Chat archive how
would they go there how do they get
access.
technology on archon X's Twitter it's
linked in the description it's probably
in the dead beat span Discord accessible
join the dead beats fan Discord if you
want to do you ever mention not saying
like that are you in it but do you ever
talk about your band Discord cuz every
time I mention it uh people go like oh
my God she's in
it and they lose it I mean I I don't
know what I'd say I shut it down
scatter I I'm thankful and I'm glad you
guys chat a lot else while grapes
touching we go that's a pair everything
close it right now going full circle
could be any one of I don't know would
it scare you guys if if it were to be
that members made secret accounts and
were in the fan Discord would it be
scary why are you
laughing why are you
laughing not really oh no yes nah hide
the art she knows
run I some people some people I guess
are open about it recently I I just
advertised it cuz I was thinking you
know they they do as far as I know they
do a lot of like you know birthday and
F
project right and sometimes people are
like oh I wish I would have known how to
participate and so I thought people
maybe sometimes need a reminder that
these uh discords exist so you know and
and be part of the community cuz you're
new in the phandom like if you if you
join the fandom now I feel like you
wouldn't really know that there's such
discords right so you know I think a lot
of dead beats also kind of have their
own like personal discords like I think
there are many many deadbeat discords
deadbeat clicks
clicks how do I get into one I don't
know it's super exclusive who could say
but either way you have to be one of the
popular
kids
de buling going on no I think it's
normal to make friends within your own
community of course of course that
you're closer with that's cool KCK ooh
girls it's high school man I'm so cute
oh jeez I mean I certainly was like that
with Persona at least you know it's not
like all Persona fans hung out in the
same area or anything like that so but
could say I'll invite you to my click
K let be you're invited you can sit with
us at
lunch pumpkin spice
latte
what uh it's getting like kind of kind
of yucky right like I don't have space
to breathe and live and just invading my
personal space
right oh no did you make a little
mistake there no I mean not
intentionally
oh not over yet but it's over maybe you
can make it to I don't know Miracle
could
happen you never know this pair could
teleport down here did I squeeze the
strawberry in there yeah why
not but it won't it won't make it it
will make it if that's what you're
wondering there's another one another
one
yeah this is uit I bet could say this is
impossible now like what am I supposed
to where where should I put this suay
begs to
difference okay for your game now no
more fruits game for you no I shouldn't
I I'll do it when I play it on my stream
yeah all right well probably better for
your mental health cuz I don't know how
long I'll be here I am going to open up
the VC but I don't know who's awake at
this time oh H we find out I'm I still
I'm still having fun with it though yeah
you haven't started hating it yet no all
I'm like like very curious and open to
experimentation right now that's good
it's a good way to be I would say very
good way to be I'll probably go to sleep
soon though while you're still playing
this game well if you hear a scream then
you know that I won or or not or that a
fruit flew up into flew up out of the
box
yeah I'm just going to this feels like
you know like I'm going to go to sleep
early while you're doing stuff not going
to bed and I'm going to be cuddling the
kids okay the cats it's it's like you're
the the neglecting parent exactly oh the
babies are fine I'll I'll smooch them
and hang out with them tomorrow they're
so cute they're very sweet as for the
usual especially like um tutu really
loves me yeah yeah tutu does I put up
yeah I saw you took some cute pictures
or a cute picture of her yeah I took
pictures but I only sent you one I see
you got
multiple
babies sweet baby yeah know she's my
beloved very kind I know that you'll be
kind to her I know that you'll give her
lots of snuggles yeah I want her to like
like when I slept here before she would
like snuggle as your snail and like
around my my like chest around my arm
yeah and that's just my cats don't do
that they always sleep with me in my bed
every night but there's
like certain spots they will lie in and
they will not on their own lie into like
a space on in between my
arms I have to go to
them and then they probably won't stay
there for long aw are they just not very
like affection overly affection no
they're definitely very affection
woohooo let's go oh yeah complicated
babies compc babies such as cats that's
just cats I feel sometimes they they
very much decide when they want to hang
out with you you know is that tutu and
gohost Cat they are isn't that cute you
should get some chunker smoothie ones do
you have them yes yes yes let's go yeah
uh like four I think babies a little
sweet babies bab bab Baboo
God I love cats cats make everything
better yeah cats make the Dark World
finally feel light cats make life worth
living 100% agreed tou you
sorry getting
angry can I tell you
oh oh can I oh there we go can I tell
you a joke yeah I'm just stealing it I'm
so so proudly telling it to everybody
you will get it you'll be the one to get
it okay have you
seen have you
seen n that's sure sm7b upgrade
microphone you haven't let's go let me
tell you all right I'm ready so you know
the the legendary short sm7b that
everybody uses yeah all the every all
the cool streamers use it everybody does
and this I'm surprised you missed it cuz
I also like tweeted about it they're
they
they announced that they're
releasing a new version of the sure
[Music]
sm7b and it's basically the same
microphone it's just
louder up to like something around 30 DB
louder because it's generally a quiet
mic on its own so that you don't have to
turn up the game so much anymore cuz
apparently that was one big issue people
always
had and you know what they call it
what's it
called sure
SM 7
DB they put a little D in there for DB
debel debel yeah because it's louder 7B
it's 7 DB okay what what did the B stand
for the B was always there but 7B sure
7B was always there was always The Name
They just added the D uhhuh and now it's
like is funny because now it's dbat
right dead beast and it's louder
mhm
debb come okay I'm trying to make the
connection in my mind with focus on the
fruits that's why you're not laughing
for me no no no I'm trying to figure out
why it's funny so obvious you as a like
a music person should understand why I
know what a I know what a decibel is I
just don't see why it's haha funny
because in my the microphone louder
uh-huh that's the only thing they change
right it's basically the same microphone
so the only thing they added to the name
that was already existing and offering
this change to that uhhuh they just
added the D I get it and it's said 70b
it's more than 70b louder but if you
read it 7
DB and they making basically a DB joke
because it's louder in the name yeah
deciel I
F don't no no no I'm not making fun of
you or
anything the funny thing is I remember
you I think you tweeted about this yeah
I did I was so proud even though it was
my own joke but I like pointing it out I
I found people who know their stuff with
this microphone will enjoy this What did
the what did the KF say they did they
say haha funny I don't know they might
be laughing out of pity for me oh why
are you not enjoying this you thought
you would have joyed us I think it's
does nothing bring you Joy except for
watermelons now no that's not true
that's I'm trying to just understand I
don't I don't understand why nothing
Sparks joy for you anymore oh no I have
plenty of joy in my life my joy is my
cats and my fruits and that's about it
really not much else El elicits an
emotional response from me so don't
worry it's not you it's
me what the
fck I'm just like I don't understand why
Suka
game is doing
this I told you it's magic okay I why do
you guys like watching this game I need
to know like I'm doing a survey now
please tell me why what is the appeal
why are so many people watching this
dumb fruits game yeah why is this a big
viewer game yeah I don't know no one
knows the reaction it's
relaxing but I guess every now and then
it's like also funny because people lose
their mind I guess I want to be andat
okay guess that's understand it's
fun getting the full low down
here I'm here for Callie
rage I like listening to cie it's a
chill
Game noises a thank you thank you dead
beat saying that that's very turn brain
off turn brain off fruit's time time for
fruit and only fruit yeah that seems to
be the the most simp simple I mean damn
it no what do you call formula it's like
a really simple
formula I would say so kind of strange
trust me I don't really know why myself
but I'm here for it I guess I'm here for
the long run I'm happy when if such a
chill like even for us chill to play and
an easy
game is the game of the month yeah this
is probably the game of the week though
I want like like thank God it's not
something like I don't know
Apex yeah I don't really know if uh only
time I'll play Apex is when some friends
are playing it and like it's cuz it's my
friends that are playing it you know
let's do this all right come on
come on I'm going two one
two three so so
sweet kiss me painting the perfect
picture you're suck to me like a sticker
it doesn't want to go there you got that
pineapple one two Kiara Mori oh my God
oh my God go the P the
pitch
baby okay I have to stand for this
one like it's so hard for me to leave I
don't know why having a hard time are we
now oh yeah and um this could be
really bad cuz it what I'm about to do
might push the peach out
though no it's okay hold on all in baby
there might as they move do it you have
to do it oh okay now what I really want
to do Ollie right now yeah the buns are
the peaches yeah melon is oh my God I
just noticed oh my gosh you're so right
actually hold on a
second all right guys this is the one
where we have to be really careful M
push it push it yeah oh no we have to
it's okay it's all right we'll be fine
we will be fine oh oh Mr Peach I'm sorry
what's that are you wanting to move Mr
Peach Mr Peach oh fuckie of
oh now the watermelon I'm sorry Mr
watermelon what are we doing over
here but that's where we want the
watermelon though in the
future we shouldn't move it too much
right no you son of a
this I can't I did that to myself
oh that was
painful that hurt me inside that gave me
I feel like that that gave me cancer I
am suffering with
you it gave me cancer right there I'm
sorry
Chad if I just and I know what I did
wrong too I got gritty I tried to set up
something
pretty Arana grounded song it is oh I
don't really listen to
Ariana
Ariana we'll do it again hey is that the
third Suka no it's the second Suka we've
gotten tonight only the second you're
good at getting the sua I mean you say
that maybe maybe that's where all the
SAS in Japan went and you can't buy them
anymore cuz they're all here they're all
here they're all in all of our streams a
Japan Insider guys it would appear so
the public transport C that people would
use to just beep be beep
it's just people can't buy it anymore I
guess cuz uh if you understand correctly
there's like a chip inside and they're
out of those I didn't know
that yikes so if you don't have one
already you have to buy the tickets I
may have lost mine for the 50 of time I
really need help I need to stop that's
why I was saying like oh my God I lost
my passo which is like a sua but I still
had a back up sua so I'm good yeah pasmo
is sua for a different area of Japan
right pasmo is like more General ikoka
is a sua fora mhmm is more General got I
see one of them one of the more
mainstream ones yeah yeah I see but not
quite sua
mainstream I wonder how pasmo feels gu
is also very Regional still p is not so
Regional yeah like anyone anywhere can
use it thing yeah I mean I've used I've
done the unthinkable I've used an eoka
in Tokyo before and of course NOA you
know wooo do the switcheroo yeah I don't
ever see people with EAS in Tokyo this I
was a special one you how could you do
that I can't believe you that's what I
had that's what I had I was cool for
having a but of course M
oh touch let's go
pineapple every was going to leave can
you like kick me out cuz I I need to
sleep get out you have to go to
bed stop watching me also I promised to
do um a Twitter space but this this is
like a good exchange for it right me
being here right I mean you're talking
say hi to kfp hi kfp they're definitely
here I just today came back from where I
went yesterday
canai
yeah it uh was nice it was really short
but it was really nice weather was
pretty decent uh yeah and it was
beautiful I still have my hair really
fancy I have to take this apart see I'll
do this now while I'm still here okay
I'll take apart my hair go for it see
progress we're making
progress there's so many
pins do you need bobby pins um not
really I'm good I like to have my hair
down these
days put it up much often anymore at
least yeah why am I now Nest just
kidding I take good care of my hair de
there's no Rat's Nest here not hair part
like
Lego yeah I I have my hair
up and now I'm taking it
apart so pretty so not you not you
fcking know I myself finally got my ve
let's go oh did you also said what did
you make your have get I no I'm getting
a new one made all the badges completely
re no no a new the last one the newest
threeyear one is currently in it's in
production I already had mine ready for
like a year I'm sure you did cuz you're
prepared I was working on other things I
was still prepared and I still waited
until the last moment to set it in
stone I should have tried to get a peach
over here honestly so it can what are
you planning or are you keeping it a
secret what they're going to be it's a
secret it's a secret I think de beats
will like it though just wait a little
bit longer please
membership poo membership poo this is a
dead run dead beats where you at day one
or or week one dead beats where you at
there's some old beats here you
definely some old beats here don't feel
like you have to stay oh there they are
month one right here that's me yeah
let's go there they go yeah occasionally
I'll see like a de be 36 months 34 month
35 36 they good opportunity to member
their monthly member messages 36 36 34
36 they're flexing they're flexing that
be flexing now flexing now the old beats
are here flexing their status old beats
are they deader than dead I would say so
old than dead yeah definitely rotten
corpses sorry if that hurts your
feelings but we still have some new for
them right being rotten yeah rotten old
dead beats I mean I still appreciate
them
you're still loved dead
beats dust beats dust beats oh they're
cute look at them go look at them go
look at all the green AR they
sweet she those are those are my dead
beats I feel so proud like I'm showing
you like a new pet or something like
that or like I'm showing you tutu or
ghost cat look at my look at my dead
beats look at how sweet they
are well Tut will be the one sleeping
with me in my arm tonight yep I'm
closing my door tonight so that they can
go be with you cuz I know how much it
means to you to spend some time with
doooo daada yeah yeah you know it will
feel even more special to go back to my
cats after spending a night with your
cats exactly they're just here to be
your temporary
Guardians you know those cat is a good
Guardian cat yes he is but he will run
away his eyes are
terrifying they're like a a cartoon he
really scared me today I walked in oh
yeah was he giving you a glare his eyes
are just by default terrifying right now
they are huge he has really big
eyes he's so big now he grew so much big
boy he's my big boy I'm thinking that
tutu probably grew a lot too but for for
ghost cat it stood out so much more to
me yeah he's enormous well he's also a
male cat yeah so you know the the boys
they get to be enormous
for most of them but there are still
some exceptions right they exceptions
I'm sure was yeah chers and smoothie
they're ladies right they are secret
they're bigger than uh ghost cat is now
really yeah they're pretty big for being
ladies I guess but I just feel like like
your cats are just small in general
maybe it's like a like a Japanese cat
thing like the way they're like being
breeded here breed MH in Japan maybe
makes them genetically smaller I don't
know I can imagine that being true for
sure oh the
babies my small
babies well you remember how big they
were yeah don't you yeah I do also like
their fluff is Extreme like Chu is like
um a a a long fur cat but still she
doesn't have like yet could change still
as many layers and as long hair as my
cat do she's more of a medium hair cat
in my opinion yeah yeah definitely
medium and might still like maybe she'll
like still develop a second layer
F could be I don't know oh she's so cute
though she's my little treasure she has
really nice fur I know right she's so
soft to touch I love touching her tail
I've never owned a cat that is as soft
as tutu she's so soft very
adorable God love that cat anyway I
could go on forever about honestly that
cat is just a perfect cat in my opinion
perfect choke you good yeah need water
no I'm good I'm sorry I only have this
abunai drink over
[Music]
here straight out of the bottle idle
juice yeah I hardcore yeah and then the
Bon sweat oh not everybody can enjoy
juice there should be buatti swe uh
cocktails yeah I thought that would be
yummy kind of like um I always confuse
cashes with
CPUs so whenever people are ordering
like cashes orange I'm like ooh CPUs
drink they're like no it's
cashes which is Al drink is nice too
yeah but it's I just never imagine it
being like an alcohol drink you know
which which Mory Mor's into idle juice
these days that's that's that's
what do you mean final meeting uh oh you
think I see what you're where you're
getting to CH term I just disagree with
that kiaha I just disagree say so juice
say so
juice yeah okay I would recommend that
all right if that's your recommendation
I'll listen to your advice you know
going to have to contact the idle Juice
company and you know tell them that they
need to Rebrand cuz
well it's to you buy who's the
owner um we don't talk about the
owner we don't talk about the owner
she's the Supreme
Idol
you yes no maybe open this
some
somebody you can do it I believe I'll
probably just cut
it do what you got to do I'll be I'll be
um short-hair Wawa where's Shir Wawa be
bald next time I want Shir WWA to show
up you have short a short hair option
kind of like hair a end of the neck
that's about as far as I'd go too
personally yeah it would look really
cute on
you thanks I just don't want to be too
too short hair Tut tutu short hair it's
not my
vibe yeah I know people have a couple
people have been like oh what's the boy
cut myy hair look like it's not for me
it's a cute thought though just not not
me come on let's go
boys
[Music]
pineapple time for you to
leave probably better for your menal to
not be around
this I'm still trying to
yeah you don't need to be you don't need
to be in here for this I don't want you
to see me like
this you shouldn't have to see me this
way I'm like like I guess I don't even
know why I ask people why they like
watching it cuz I also like watching it
I really don't it's quite mysterious
isn't
it come on come on want
touch thanks appreciate that big ups and
all
that this
and every time we kiss I swe I fly you
hear my heart be fast I want this to
last need you by my side cuz Every Time
We Touch I feel the static and every
time we kiss I reach for the sky can't
you feel my heart beat slow I can't let
you go need you in my life
[Music]
da
[Laughter]
why do you know the lyrics so well it
was all the rage back in school but even
the famous songs I just can't remember
any lyrics man but Idol songs are no
problem
depends on the
[Music]
song go I totally threw girl I
threw see now now you have an
opportunity to head out before you get
drawn back in yeah I should
go thinking about you just thinking
about you how's it
going what say I have you can just hang
out in here with me until 500
a.m. if you're
still what are you going to do about
it you have to sleep late young lady I
do have an Anan tomorrow exactly you
want to be awake for that you don't want
to
oversleep I won't I have three
alarms I've overslept a couple times but
not that many I'll wake you up anyway
okay wakey wakey let me know
do not go anywhere without me you must
say hey myy what's up Mory Ka I'm going
to the Comin or whatever you know the
reason why I'm staying over here tonight
is because I have this weird Gap and
also I'm I wanted to see you
and I'm a cheap hoe I don't know what to
say I was waiting for that I was waiting
for that admission right there
well I'm happy to offer I'm just here
with my cats doing my thing yeah I mean
y you got cats like I mean always choose
the accommodation with the cats
precisely like I wouldn't stay here like
occupy the space for like a whole week
or so I get you you know one night or or
two don't worry W you don't have to
explain your reasoning to me you're
allowed
anytime I have no problem with that look
pineapple 1 2 one2 3 is this your
capture card sure is you like it I've
been using it for four years what yep
haven't gotten a new one or anything
shout out to a media media yep reliable
catch card yep been using it for a very
very very long time a cool
shap pretty neat I will say wow for free
no you know how I when I uh lived
in Japan when I started live and like I
had a shitty PC in the beginning right
yeah yeah yeah so once I got some Sates
I I had a PC made kind of you know for
this like kind of with the help
connections just go I had to pay for it
in full right but uh yeah went to this
like PC company and they made me a
gaming PC W yeah Special one for gamers
supposedly and then I brought it to
Austria eventually I was using it for a
while but I always kept on using my
Elgato capture card yeah yeah it's a
good one and then I realized at some
point when taking apart my PC to switch
a
case that they built in like an inside
PC internal capture card and I didn't
know about it and all this time I had
trouble with Elgato I could have been
using that one instead I didn't even
know that that was something you could
do yeah you can put internal cap the
card really now no he that's convenient
I gu no I had no clue about that any of
you guys have
that
here cuz I don't even know how to make
it work you have the Old Faithful yeah
most of the time the elato works most of
the time for the times it
doesn't then then deal with it then I
restart my
PC and then it works
I figured out many issues how to solve
them with the Elgato you know it's like
we're a married couple a that's kind of
sweet we work out our issues I don't
just leave it behind cuz I'm annoyed
with it and get myself a new one no it's
a good way to be commitment I commend
you for that pretty big thank you proud
of
you go get those melons go get those
melons man yeah
yeah check it out you strawberry you
piece of die you what the
that I'm tilted now I'll never
I'll never go to sleep I'm never going
to oh I'm going to
die my life no it's it can't still
happen maybe you really think so the
peaches are squeezing the um they're not
open God hate me why does God hate me
open it why does got a me FBI open up oh
come on let's go all right all
right all right all right now we're
making a little progress maybe the r was
helping could be oh watch out watch out
I know right those two it's just a
question of like will it yeah they just
got to go down drop if you just could oh
look at them leak oh let's go well
they're not quite touching the way I
want y y oh there we go okay now we're
cooking let's go here we go we're
getting it we're getting it uh-huh why
is this so
exciting yeah now you understand the
appeal it's like I'm watching a Super
Smash Bros tournament and I actually
know what's happening cuz in Super Smash
Bros I never I wouldn't know really I
mean yeah neither do I In fairness
neither do I kfb you're getting that the
SGA game Arc you know don't I want to
get in on it too I'm kind of late but
let me in let me in get ready you
sillies
oh my God yes push it push it push it
push the fruit push the fruit come on
let's go yes
all right now we just need to
connect the peaches exactly and then you
need another Peach we have three PES
that is not good yeah I don't know about
this one man just doesn't seem doesn't
seem right this ain't
right this looks bad this looks really
bad for me what if we put this here hold
on a sec hold on hold on I want to
look why would you do that you stupid
why you Ru it because there was no
hope in getting over 3,000 that's why I
stopped it I ended our suffering for us
you should be thanking me I should end
the stream for us no no there's no you
never get to 3,000 there's no there's no
ending the stream I will get to 3,000
want you to get the oh ye of little
faith why so you can go to sleep give up
that dream I I really want you to do it
cuz I'm rooing for you but at the same
time this game is so rigged yeah it's
pretty evil but it also takes a smart
person and I think you you're betting on
the wrong Idol here because I'm not
exactly the smartest you can do it not
very bright exactly the right game for
you I don't know man this is your game
uh I don't know I think it's moving game
m is leading right
now Mory
camelon this is yourope C oh yeah
that's calop cantaloupe
myy is it the comeback of the best
nickname in the whole life that's pretty
bad it's pretty bad to be honest and I
came up with it myself no one was
calling me that or you can tell nobody
was calling me cantaloup I literally
just thought to myself see look at him
go cantaloupe look at them with the
cantaloupe it is those sobs they know
exactly what they're doing if you didn't
like it you would have already taken out
them Emoji it's not that I like it it's
that it's become an important part of
deadbeat culture at this point you know
got to respect the culture so here we
are this what I'm trying to say hold on
check this out check out how base this
configuration still here cuz you're
entranced by my configuration check out
check this out doesn't that look
good that's a sex that's a sex
[Music]
this pretty good looking right you got
to admit it looks pretty good just to
suffer maybe maybe maybe know that you
can sleep at any time if you want to
sleep you could always you know watch
the stream from bed
downstairs maybe you could if you're
ever curious about how om Mor's
doing if you're ever wondering if she's
okay she's all right over there
just making melons as I usually
do trash fruits go over
there trash fruits and then check this
out hold on oh I'm sorry excuse me
what's that is that two pairs maybe
bam you guys are you guys are going to
get some fun new huahua noises playing
this game everybody's excited about myy
noises well now we got some kiah waah
noises wait for the waah wa noises here
they come here they
[Music]
come you're
Matchmaker oh what does that mean
Matchmaker fruit fruits okay I'll accept
that I'll take it can you please get the
free, so that I can go to sleep without
feeling like I'm missing out something
I'll consider it you got that fomo it
happens to every fruiter
every fruiter goes through
this guys have you already made sure to
get the end of the world voice
packi and we're both in it I need to
listen to yours I haven't heard it
yet I haven't heard anyone's yet
actually I think I haven't even heard my
own
yet yeah I also did not hear the final M
I've been asking for
it ah well you know that's just them
just the business that's that's them
just the breaks that's
business I'm sure it's great maybe what
did you guys think maybe that don't want
to break the immersion of myself I guess
so what did you think yeah yeah do you
feel depressed about the world
ending are you kidding me that was
such a good
melon okay I think I've seen it all
you've seen it all that would be a great
time to dip out if you really need to go
all right this is my life we catch you
later you get you'll hear my scream if
you get 3,000 anytime soon yeah I'll
wake you up no so
mad I don't know if I him okay you
should get it soon so that you can sleep
yeah you're right you deserve it I'd
like to go to bed yes I I want you to go
to bed I don't know man don't leave why
is leaving now guys make sure that she
doesn't go insane and she goes to sleep
impossible maybe give her some strats so
that she goes to S
ahii Sensei here
[Music]
yeahi
that's beautiful that's clean that's
clean are you sure though I feel like
it's going to I'm not trying
to hold on we'll make another pair it's
fine stop the Cherry that cherry is a
stop there we go you can feel the rage
coming out look at this nasty
configuration it's not very good it's
okay it's okay it's very yucky look very
clean I like the the color go from
yellow to Red to Yellow to Red yeah yeah
but see that's not a great thing you
know because we need the fruits to touch
it's it's not right it ain't right it's
not natural Kiara you just got to make
another apple and another apple and
another whatever lemon yeah really think
so it's a double dou a par what are you
why are you letting them down give it a
second give it a second the dead beats
taught me you need to be patient playing
this game you have to be patient it's
important okay just I I'm go now
bye sueto
[Music]
dreams she can't stop looking at the
screen she's so
entranced I'm like walking backwards
looking at the screen oh no de beat's
like don't leave us qaa don't leave us
take care of her guys they won't they'll
keep enabling me y you see that I came
back it's clean she literally can't
leave but you're only at 600 points yeah
I know right it's about to be more no
you that was really not good yeah
I know but it wasn't my fault the fruits
fell they fell and they ruined you made
them fall yeah because I have to I don't
have a choice look at that peach though
isn't that a good looking
Peach that's a goodl looking
Peach pretty good right it's a good
looking Peach admit it it's a
good-looking
Peach check that out Apple now what I
well you have an apple but do you have a
pan I have a pineapple and I have an
apple pineapple
pen Apple pen pineapp pineapple
pan yeah yeah yeah come on and pineapple
Apple Pan pineapple Apple Pan I have a
pan I have a pineapple pineapple
pan gream pineapple so simple but that
wasn't pineapple that was not the song
close enough just so you guys are aware
I'm going to go now she's going to
really leave I'm going to come with f
because that's what makes me happy and
that's what's actually rewarding unlike
this game you know she's coping so hard
right now you want go back to the world
where you get rewarded for loving
something like tutu I love fruits now
don't you miss it fruits are my love I
guess she's just lost maybe maybe but it
feels so good the the dope and
you don't understand the dopamine hit
guua good night cantalope I'm not a
cantaloup
Jesus ghost cat you can't come in here
little buddy do not let him
in all right she's going to
bed night waah wa the rush dope dopam
mean oh I had I didn't have my
headphones
on cuz you can can kind of hear the you
can kind of hear the music anyway a Zayn
a Zayn how much you guys want to bet she
goes down to the the guest
bedroom I
hear I hear
her I hear her listening to
it I hear her you listening to the
stream
Kiara she is on full blast I
stop what the is wrong with her
what the
[Music]
oh man go to
bed go to bed y go to bed let me move my
headphones oh this is some evilness
right here well it's fine we're going to
be chill I guess I'll hop into voice
call I don't I can't promise that anyone
will jump in but we got gaha
today let's
see all
right just adding
everyone like they want to know about my
unhealthy
addiction get out of
this get out
you are in my
house you are in my
[Music]
house I'm going to
lose
it oh my
God this whole house is
cursed
I'm going to lose my
mind y'all going to make me lose my mind
she wanted to take unnecessary
bandwidth I need the bandwidth right now
to make
history quit taking my
bandwidth oh this is a yucky I could
have you idiot
Mory myy how can you be so stupid
Mory Mor
Sor
Jesus y all right check this here we go
no God it all hurts so
bad please I just myy brain also lagging
it's been a day is all I'm trying to
say look at that look at that little guy
go if he just needs a little push maybe
just a
[Music]
little ah that orange he knew what he
was
doing he knew exactly what he was
doing that little piece of
garbage he knows they all
know it's a plot against
me
Jo go to sleep hey Doo tutu is crying
because she lost her mommy to
addiction it's all right tutu honey
mommy will be
back after one more
round
just I'll be
back no it it's
fine every everyone's overly
concerned everyone's just overly
concerned stop concerned posting it's
it's
fine it's just a game it's just a stupid
Fruit
game this is such a yucky
one you know what we've gotten more
pairs of fruits than the last stream
though which was 7
hours so I'll take
it well
that's the end for your
boy one more then another blink twice if
you need help no one's watching me
except for maybe the demons I'm going to
hug her until she stops crying do not
take my cat from
me
please my cat is all I have
left please that's my
baby that's my little girl please
please no no it's not that she needs a
new family I take good care of
her can you speak a little
[Music]
Japanese
suddenly now speak a little
Spanish
buen what's watermelon in
tar
taru Sandia
Sanda
sand what's pineapple in
Spanish Sandy aquam Melon
yeah I bet that's what it
is aquamelon aquamelon
Miga
salap J
J aquam melon
stream
paa if you like PE
col
and if you're not into
[Music]
yogurt
if I just
waited that son of a
you're going to destroy everything
I
love rip Jimmy
Buffett he was
[Music]
cool do da
da do
[Music]
da
fine
we'll just connect them like this
easy well now we're about to get a
freaking melon over here and I don't
like that
[Music]
so y that was the right
move that was the right move dead
beats please it can't be that
hard okay maybe they would have touched
In fairness I believe that easy yat yat
yat
this okay now we're cooking we're
smoking hot right now but we have to
really be careful about that side
because this side is not playing around
oh boy yeah I figured you'd come in
there to try and mess things up for me
and ruin my life
sakuro but guess what dummy this is my
town
now this is my sua game and you're not
going to ruin it for
[Music]
me what's going on you see the melon no
where's the Wi-Fi password I'll send it
to I'll send it to you thank you i r in
chat but you ignored me sorry I was busy
I was also offering you either me or the
child services are going to take two no
you're not which one you choose if you
try and put my cat in your bag I'll lose
my mind I'll check Discord all right all
right good night good
night oh don't let the cats in don't let
them
in don't let him
in use motiv ated all right all right
just a
second it's
the hold
on password is
[Music]
important all right send gosh what a
cute picture of
dude what a cute
[Music]
picture
I'm not sleepy the night is only just
begun the night is still
young um but when I get over 3,000 I'm
going to
sleep I will be going to
bed but you know let's try and like put
some thought into it you
know like let's really try to kind of
think about it right
see every single time that I'm like oh
like let's commit to a meon or something
like
that then we
get an orange sorry a
pmen that's what it is it's a
pmen okay now we've got a good setup
going here to connect these but all
right I guess it's just not
meant to
be stop doing
that
[Music]
I hate that
strawberry that strawberry just
shouldn't exist
[Music]
really no okay I think we saved
it y there's still potential here see
sometimes you have to be fast too
sometimes it's about the opposite of
waiting which is going
fast
I should have let that
move we could just push these guys
together if we could
[Music]
just
no it made it
fly love the fact I'm watching you play
Holo cure ah yes the far superior game
hey why aren't we all playing that right
[Music]
now instead it's
this why did we choose to do that to
ourselves that I'll never quite
understand the beginning is so much
easier than how hard it gets
later to manage all these fruits
[Music]
just one
more really kind of losing it
here hey Grapes you want to touch each
other
no really not feeling it
today just see how the fruits move let
it play
out
okay now we just need to get those guys
to touch
but what if well that's a lost
cause I had to take a
risk
y now we're
cooking
so we want to capitalize on that Apple
but look now we have a apple over here
so the possibilities I should have put
that over by the grape no hold on I'll
make it
work check
it I know you're going to touch I know
you're going to touch each
[Music]
other all right fine I'm
impatient I'm
impatient stop being impatient
Mory you could just stop being
impatient see that's why you're never
going to win the sua game Mory cuz
you're
impatient look just let them touch
they're getting so
[Music]
close there we
go it didn't drop as fast as I wanted it
to absolutely evil this is disgusting
look at this
configuration look at how yucky it is
how unpleasing to the eye it
is I will fix these SS I will absolve
[Music]
us so that future Generations don't have
to
suffer what the am I talking
about I don't know it's the demons
they're speaking through
me praise be to
Mori little did she know she had started
a
cult they taught themselves to be a cult
they didn't know as many
[Music]
strategies they taught themselves to be
a
c I didn't know as many
strategies
fantasies no this should be fun check
that out look look at those guys look at
they're all friends all
[Music]
friends come on pineapple make them see
reason come
on
y this looks about correct
yes take him to Paradise take him take
[Music]
him take
him this is officially a cry for
help
[Music]
my grip on reality is starting to
slip I can really feel myself beginning
to lose
[Music]
it no I'm
fine I
am I'm doing great Kiara you shouldn't
have to see me like this grape no I said
great did it sound like I said
grape did look it did you see what I
just did did you see how good that
was oh hold
on she's muted whoopsies there she is
sorry oh oh yeah I tabed out I'm going
to call the child services now please do
not byee please do not please wait no
come back
they will never take my cat they can try
but they will never have
tutu tutu is
mine
no is the most evil strawberry on the
planet you think I don't see what you're
trying to
do like I'm that
foolish you
wish
[Music]
yes
yes why does this game melt people's
brains should maybe ask like a scientist
or a doctor I'm sure someone
knows
[Music]
someone knows the
reasin I feel like this is something
we've tried to solve before
together you know why is it this game
does this to
[Music]
us
some things just aren't meant to be
known dead
[Music]
beats there are still some things we'll
never
understand Dam we could have really had
that
one but watch
this that was dangerous
[Music]
that was true
danger we're so close just let things
move just let things
move we're very
[Music]
close let play it
safe hold
on
no I should have just let them move I
should have just just let him move on
their
own we almost had it we almost had a
sua it was almost
[Music]
beautiful whatever we press on Clive
says that's what humans
do I should listen to
Clive yes Clive I
agree
I agree with
[Music]
Clive
yes the Clive is dead no he's
not live is alive you can't spell Clive
without
aive
dummy
clearly someone didn't pay attention to
the
story maybe the fruits will just fall
into place near each
other it'll be
fine
right see look at that peach moving oh
yeah he wants to connect y
boys that's how a professional does
it a professional sua
player I wouldn't expect anyone else to
understand quite what I'm going
through go on touch your
bro he's waiting for you that's what I'm
talking
about that's what we like to
see that's what we like to
[Music]
see hold
on it's all coming in into
place everything is falling into
[Music]
place oh boy that's really how you
wanted to play the game really on God on
God
no you'll pay for
that it
hurts there's just no
[Music]
room I'm not stupid I'm not stupid I
promise I'm not a big stupid dumb dumb
idiot I
swear
[Music]
smart
I'm
smart you'll
[Music]
see watch watch watch this watch
this yes
yes now we just have to get the peach to
touch the melon
and we'll be home
free nice thank you chat for validating
me I know it was pretty
[Music]
good it was all
right now we just got to work on
[Music]
connection
I should have known that was going to
happen I should have known it would be
that
[Music]
simple okay watch
this now we just have to make a little
more
room oh oh they're going to go
meet
thank
you oh maybe God is
real no I should have done the other
one I'll take it all
back oh hold on a minute I'm
sorry okay
[Music]
well just hold on a second
there oh
hey
hey hey apples it would be pretty cool
if you guys could meet each other
just a tiny
shift very little
[Music]
one things
moving quick be
quick all right now let's make these two
meet each
other
[Music]
okay no wait that's not quite what I
meant to do that's fine we'll make it
[Music]
work now we just need to make one down
here I don't know if it'll reach
it I don't think it'll reach it oh my
God you just came to to ruin my
party all
right what if we
[Music]
just
no
no that was the wrong I thought it was a
me no we can make it work we can't
no all right this one for
sure this one's definitely the one you
guys trust me just trust
me you have to trust me we're in this
together we're in this
together
[Music]
I just have to open my third
eye you know that's the that's the big
problem is that I'm not opening my third
eye if I did all the problems will be
[Music]
solved now we've got lots of room for
fruits to
fall
come on
is this really the road you want
to go
[Music]
down just let them move a little bit let
them get cozy with each other you know
y now hold on we can make this
work we've been getting a lot of
pineapples this time you guys I don't
know if you noticed we've been getting a
lot of
pineapples
yeah
okay
[Music]
nice stream
pineapple it's a good
[Music]
song okay I'll take
it you sure you don't want to just kind
of move down a little bit you know yeah
see I knew you'd come
[Music]
around
yes that was what we
needed let's freaking go let's freaking
go
yes
thank you
[Music]
God
y build up some more cute little fruits
over
[Music]
there
Y Mega grape
Peach make the peach no you could have
gotten you could have combined you let
that that strawberry wedge itself in
between you that's on
you that is on
you oh no I should have
put
don't rush myy this is important squeeky
game is
serious we'll get another meon see there
it
is there it is there it
[Music]
was damn
it I really screwed up on that
one
it's not giv me the fruits I
[Music]
need damn
you
come
[Music]
on why does it look like this cuz you
made it that way Mory cuz you made it
that
way
[Music]
no go touch him
y we can escape
[Music]
this just got to be
smart no
no I feel like we got stopped at a
similar spot last
[Music]
time
rip no problem dead beats we're doing
great pretty good for the evening I
would
say definitely could be worse oh my
God I'm trying to be more
calm I think that will help my game
play
right it'll help my game
play have them meet each other yes no
don't you
dare
[Music]
do not even think about it
yeah oh I was going to lose
[Music]
it I was really going to lose my
mind up in
here we're
fine
it's all
[Music]
fine look at that a tasty
Pon and here's another tasty
pmen delicious now let's make some
more check this out
y
pineapple I wonder if this will be a
popular switch game it already is it
already is a popular switch game a lot
of people playing
it it's on the Japan switch store I'm
sure they will make it available very
soon
overseas just a gut
feeling I think they will
[Music]
though
give me a
[Music]
peach those fruits will surely connect
someday got a good feeling about
them
we got to wait for pan we have to wait
for
[Music]
it
no I should have seen that coming I
really should have but I
didn't and I will regret that for the
rest of this
playthrough I believe that we can make
them
connect
no now it's really
[Music]
over now it's really really really
really
[Music]
over
uh I could have no that would
have could have would have should
have what can you do
nothing there's nothing you can
do I should have let that Apple hold
on no I could have put that one down
there and I'm
[Music]
throwing he's
throwing damn
you really
[Music]
come on no do not let him in there
no I'm just not thinking hard
enough how do I increase my brain
capacity how do I think more someone
teach me how to think
more how do I think
better teach me I'm a lost
[Music]
cause
please I need serious
help
it's fine it's fine fruits guys no don't
think it's a mistake a mistake to think
you think so
[Music]
chat I just want over
3,000 I don't really care about much
else I just want to prove my worth as a
a member of the human race you
know only way you can do that is by
playing playing saky game apparently so
it's just really important that I prove
it to you
guys
anyway don't think
feel I mean that's the obvious way is it
not I should have put that one down
there would have hit the gr no I can't
live with that mistake that I just made
hold
on I don't think I can live with that
mistake
I have to Clive says I have
to all right Clive I hear you loud and
clear
buddy this is the way it has to be all
right I got
[Music]
it understood
now if we could just connect these
little
guys I feel like our trouble days will
be
[Music]
over just let
it
fine put it
here and just build those
fruits
[Music]
no
just just push just
push a little
more we're very
close just
keep come on
[Music]
yeah come on you're supposed to roll
over yes go Cherry
[Music]
go
now these fruits are going to combine
they'll be okay I promise you look at
them look at them
combined see I knew
[Music]
it
okay there we go drop this guy here
are you kidding
me what a piece of garbage piece of
[Music]
garbage no
no
okay just
chill
very chill very
[Music]
calm very normal regular calm
chill we're going to chain them
together just trust
me oh my
God
okay very very
[Music]
close very
close
Yi
a serious
[Music]
business
okay no don't do
that I'm begging you to not do
[Music]
that
we can make this
[Music]
work
okay chill
just be
[Music]
calm
Orange it's not an orange it's a
personman come
on come on
just jostle him a little bit just
got to jostle
him no and force them
out
[Music]
tomato actually I don't want to hear it
from you I don't want to hear it I don't
want to hear
it it was looking so
good that
hurts we'll be okay we always
[Music]
are we'll be okay dead beats just have
faith it just might take me a while and
I may zone out a little bit which is
fine that's bound to happen playing this
game am I right guys so just don't worry
about
it damn
it you ever feel like the game is
purposefully making you do the thing
that you don't want to do
most like play
it I'm joking I'm only
jesting I'm very happy to be
[Music]
here making fruits with
you
[Music]
yes
perfect come
on yes and now we will follow up swiftly
with
another
no you will
roll
oh my please please
please curse you
gravity oh it's fine it's
[Music]
fine
quick be quick y that was good did you
guys see that that was pretty
[Music]
cool I don't know that was pretty
cool
no
wait that's fine quick be
quick yeah Die Here We freaking
go very
excited it's an exciting moment for
[Music]
me
wait okay that was huge that was very
big I don't like that that happened
though
oh
okay maybe we can grow something down
there damn
it you know I had a feeling that was
going to happen but I didn't want to
believe
it's fine just just don't worry about
[Music]
it we're going for
grapes please be
[Music]
together
no are you
sure okay
now we're making
moves make a
strawberry make a grape
yes just
chill watch this
[Music]
pineapple little
meon what's going on little
meon how's it
going we going to make an
apple
maybe
[Music]
possibly Jesus why would you do
that
we can make it
work let it move a little
bit here let let the Apple just let it
move maybe we can give him a little a
little
persuasion that's not what's going to
happen
no that was not the optimal
outcome
no give me some more
Grapes of course of
[Music]
course
okay
it's not that bad myy it's not that
bad just calm down it's
[Music]
cool my life
man we could have had it
all I ruined
it
[Music]
come
on only you can save
[Music]
us there goes the
chat no more mistakes Mory no more you
can't afford to make any more more
[Music]
mistakes ha
ha
[Music]
please don't please don't please
don't
[Music]
no
well today's second best score
it
hurts but we're definitely getting
better right this is a game you can get
better
at
right
right this is definitely a it's a skill
game it's a skill
base skill
issue a
[Music]
skill I've been playing
no games all
day this kind of hit
me
[Music]
surely
what
[Music]
skill
issue
[Music]
watermelon
my
God please touch
[Music]
please s by
musas
staying up
late
yeah just like
me playing games late at
night let's go
Moy we can definitely
win watch Senpai I'm going to do
great you'll see I'll impress
Senpai I'm going to do it I'm not going
to embarrass
myself grind to 3K but it's not a game
you can grind
sadly I want to grind but I can't it's
not a grinding
game
no please have
mercy excuse
me excuse
me I already not looking there Cowboy
you don't know what you're talking about
this looks like a great
configuration it's looking
[Music]
solid very
solid no please go the other
way
okay why'd you do that
myy
why
[Music]
two
Pineapple
no
it's
over I could have put that on the
strawberry
[Music]
ah
I'm just going to have to make more
large
fruits that's
[Music]
all I'll do
it more large
fruits
more large
fruits I should have done that
strawberry
instead
no it's so hard to be dumb God I hate
being dumb it's so difficult to live
this
[Music]
way
melon nice
nice
no it touched the wrong
[Music]
one just build the fruits more
just build them we don't have much else
of a
[Music]
choice maybe they'll touch
someday wao
scary
[Music]
no no no go that way push push him push
him
[Music]
yes
come
[Music]
on yes
no
[Music]
the
why won't they die
touch
[Music]
please no
[Applause]
[Music]
oh
high score for
[Music]
today
woo why is the reaper so sad dead beat I
don't know if you just witnessed what
happened it was a travesty it might have
been the end of the
world
[Music]
go
on it was pure
comedy very
[Music]
funny why would you go into different
direction when you just went
[Music]
one
sorry I'm so in the zone I just no I'm
so sick of this
[Music]
never aim for anything you won't hit
it Rage Quit
never
never not a chance in
hell only rage
continue
only rage continue oh that was a
strawberry oh
well I feel
nothing I feel nothing
see how that strawberry it's always the
strawberries you will touch you will do
[Music]
it
yes
[Music]
yes come on come
on please please
y let's
go isn't this beautiful look at this
beautiful picture right here are you
dead beats witnessing this you see how
good this looks looks pretty good right
it's a solid looking configuration right
[Music]
here usually doing great at the start
and then we get real
bad well of course the game gets harder
as the more fruits that enter the
scene you
know we'll put the cherries over
here
we should have put this here first no I
messed it all up I messed it up
ah we can we can redeem
you
[Music]
well I'm very passionate about this game
that's for
[Music]
sure at least I have that the
passion this it counts right guys no
it's definitely winning it's definitely
winning winning is what
[Music]
counts
yes
melon all right now let's take a deep
[Music]
breath make a little
room a little strawberry a little
sakur there we go that should do
it
[Music]
Sako okay I made the right choice very
lucky
no why won't you touch each
other wait
wait
yes all we had to do was
wait just had to wait a
minute and then it all came to fruit
fruti get it fruition but it's
fruti
[Music]
jork Miss
jork oh man that's
[Music]
unfortunate I don't know I think that's
uh not really
possible
ah maybe a miracle could
happen you never know
[Music]
maybe it will maybe it
will
no
you we were yelling at you through our
TV as we ate
breakfast that bad
huh sorry to put you through that
fok I'm sorry to traumatize you as I've
traumatized
[Music]
myself it's been a roller
coaster maybe we can uh play together
sometime we'll see if time will allow
silly
fruits yeah really silly you're doing
really well we believe
Baba you guys are
sweet thanks for being so
kind could use that right
now stop being mean to yourself Mory
stop beating yourself
up we'll get it just you know take a
little more time to think
right honestly I feel like we're not
doing bad or anything it's
[Music]
just mistakes made later on or not I
know things are just not panning
out we can do much better we can always
do better right guys we can always oh my
God you will go here and you will stay
[Music]
there
h
just go over
there that should not have
worked I should have been punished
severely for that I was
not I was not
[Music]
punished classic myy
move I should have let that hit the
strawberry
[Music]
below
yes
[Music]
yeah
is it really that hard to just touch
each
other that's what I thought I thought
that it wouldn't
be so that's what we're going to do now
right yes we
are
[Music]
we got him
melon a momentary
[Music]
reprieve I knew
it
please I'm begging you give me a meon
please I'm begging you
[Music]
no
we can work with
[Music]
this no go down go down all right what
if we cleared out this area a little
bit like say for example yeah yeah yeah
yeah pineapple
okay I can see that cherry looking at me
eyeballing me like a piece of
meat here we'll put that there set it
all
up watch
this go on no that's not what I meant to
do I ruined it
again
[Music]
this uh seems
familiar if we could just push him
together
we might have a
chance there is no chance there's no
[Music]
hope every time why is it why is it like
that every
time I feel like this is the third
time I did make a mistake though
or rather what I thought would happen
didn't happen that was
[Music]
bad go on smug little Cherry push
him it's not going to end the way I
wanted to so oh no stop
it
I wish I could predict just one more
ahead just a single one more
[Music]
ahead
yay but alas if I could then every body
else would be able
to and that's not that's not
fair or rather it that's how you make it
fair all right I see you're just going
to go ahead and do what you want I
guess I have no control here anymore I
suppose no stop it stop
it stop it
why why is it
too why is it too
[Music]
heavy
yep there it goes there it goes
again ah cute
bounce that sounded a little SpongeBob
[Music]
esque you're not going to push
it
a little
bit little bit teeny tiny bit oh my God
I'm going to lose it I'm going to lose
it I'm going to lose my
[Music]
mind
okay
go this
many are you
sure are you really really
[Music]
sure
yes wow it's crazy crazy how so much can
just change like
[Music]
that it's pretty
insane I never should have dropped the
meek on
[Music]
there
they're going to
touch I knew
it I knew
[Music]
it stop rolling
away need another
meon see that's going to trap it I
should have waited for the meon and now
it's
over
[Music]
now it's all over because I didn't wait
for the me
gon that's what I
deserve that is what I
deserve this is not
winnable I still don't think it's
winnable
[Music]
oh
please
[Music]
are we moving no no we're not no we're
not yep I ruined it I ruined it I ruined
it I ruined
[Applause]
it
I ruined
it slow down Mory stop telling me to
slow
down
[Music]
stop
faster
[Music]
a
is it moving it's moving why would you
move though I don't understand the
physics come on touch each other
[Music]
nice
nice oh come on they're definitely
touching well they will now oh my
God you cannot tell me that the herons
are not
touching you cannot convince
[Music]
me
whatever these
BRS are you kidding
me
I was dropping them randomly how do I
get a
[Music]
Pineapple
game
the speed
[Music]
run
okay new
strategy be good at the game
I think if we do that we might have a
[Music]
chance why would you pull it this way
why is that what that would do
physically physically why why is that
what that would do the answer is it's
not just get good yeah very Sage
advice thank
you thank you for the
[Music]
wisdom
I'm so glad I figured it
out all right hey some of you fruits
want to touch each other that would be
kind of
[Music]
cool
we're going to make them connect they
will
connect
watch there's an
[Music]
apple oh my God look at the smug
Cherry it's so
smug stop being
smug
[Music]
push him
okay much better now that area is more
[Music]
open what are we doing over over here we
pushing no no pushies not a single
[Music]
one come
on I knew we'd get an Apple from that I
had a
premonition
[Music]
okay we got the
nush
[Music]
awesome great I love how that's a
rule
no chat why why did they decide to it's
such a dumb stupid needless
thing and yet and
yet and yet that's a rule of the
game if if the fruit flies out oh man
too bad so sad idiot start
over sorry I should calm down
I just am really feeling it don't worry
guys I'm doing just
fine but if I don't get above 3,000 I'm
not going to be able to
sleep I need to be able to sleep I have
an Anan
tomorrow unen is uh sponsor
stream I have to be able to
sleep
I have to you got to
[Music]
understand
again
important
unk
show me a
grape yikes that that's that's that's
really
[Music]
rough
okay pineapple
ghetto I feel like my brain is
fried on a different plane of
existence you're not going to bounce off
right ah I
[Music]
see we'll take
it want to kind of push the pineapp yeah
that's
fine that's really like okay
really make another grape maybe oh
what's that is that another Peach that
we're about to
[Music]
make
maybe hello hello oh someone's
here yeah I
[Music]
just me how's your
watermelon what's wrong what's wrong
it's
bad
really it's
bad no no I'm sure you're doing
great the watermelon it continues to
fail me over and over again oh have you
considered getting a
hammer why why do you have to be so
smart why do you have to
be that's PG can see
it yeah how about you chot have you
played this game no I is this for the
switch actually yeah you have to have a
JP
account oh yeah I don't own it then ah
well if you need help then reconsider
because it's really not worth it's okay
I'll just buy like a real watermelon and
then I'll have a real watermelon game
real fruit stacking sounds a lot more
fun than whatever this is yeah just
juggle
it yeah I don't know but everybody's
been playing it and I feel like I have
to get a high score I have to get above
3,000 you know is that like the the
final score or something or just a
personal I don't know I mean I think
it's something the community just
decided you know oh oh well you were
super close too I know right my best
score and that you know the funniest
thing thing is that that was during the
first stream where I ever played it oh
how did I how did that become my PB I
just
don't understand how I could have they
were luring you to a false sense of
security now you're stuck
here it's exactly what it is it has to
be no unfairness I've seen I've seen
others as well that have played this for
many many hours and not gotten anywhere
near a high score
man I'm glad I don't have a a Japanese
switch account now it's for the better
you don't need to endure all of this I
promise you there's no reason for it
there really isn't and yet here I am
trying to prove something to myself but
why it's okay you'll uh um you know at
worst we can just Photoshop the high
score or
something you think it's an honorable
way to do honorable way to go out maybe
quick Photoshop
yeah you know just use a marker across
the the number put
3,000 yeah you know I think we might
actually do
that that sounds like a good good way to
go
out wow I can see why they locked you
up not a noble way to win cuz I had too
many good ideas
clearly oh man don't tell the JP members
about this this hack that I I
got no I lost
no it's fine this is surely the
3,000 now that you're here I feel so
lucky and
blessed why do I just distract you
though but you see distraction is when I
tend to
win oh for example uh Kiara is she's
staying over and um she was here for a
little bit hanging out and I feel like
all the times I got the big watermelons
for when she was
here oh she was like the the cheerleader
you know yeah exactly taking my mind off
of it we got so hype about about dual
melons it was really cool and then now
she's gone but that's okay she has to
sleep she's got a busy day it's fine I'm
not I'm okay I'm not I'm not that
lonely in the in the darkness alone with
this game
it's
fine yo just turn on the
light stop making
sense stop making sense right now I
can't help
it you're the smart one of course of
course did you just wake up a sleepy one
yeah my cats were like they were
sleeping near me and then one of them
kind of started getting a little clowy
by accident a baby I'm wake up
I'm going no they're not baby they're
just just big baby big
baby yeah ah is that the best way to
wake up though I love waking up to a
cute kitty cat they're cute to wake up
to but like I don't want them stepping
on
me I get you trying to sleep here guys
come on it doesn't feel good mine like
to walk around on my chest and it's very
painful yeah yeah both of them do that I
got two cats oh bit have a cats yeah
they're brothers too
oh yeah wow it's so sweet what the heck
Brothers I used to I used to raise a
pair of brother cats too a yeah they're
very
sweet yeah they're so cute I know like
how I don't have to take them out just
so they can do their their business you
know ah I see they they do their
business outside like dogs no no they do
in the well actually you know one of
them pisses me off because they're
supposed to do in the litter box right
yeah but one of them I feel like they're
they're purposefully doing it outside
the litter box to grab my attention and
I'm like I don't know how to fix this
child I see they just want you to pay
more attention to them is that really
the thing I think so I think cats are
definitely operating on a different
plane of existence where they they know
everything that they're doing they're
very smart M we just pretend like they
are you know we humans like to the
smartest it's no wonder my the other
cat's my favorite
one yeah I don't blame
you give you pee outside the litter box
I my cat uh also uses the bathroom
outside the litter box but only when
he's going number
two oh yeah yeah yeah yeah hital present
for me in the morning to clean
up like a you know freshly baked cookies
got to pick up and grow
away yeah delicious
wonderful hey why why is this game
giving me so many why don't want all
these perin P
pons perisin pens I don't know what
they're called actually yeah me neither
I thought I was the only one that kind
of didn't know P yeah pmen is how you
pronounce it apparently oh yeah aren't
they just like oranges but not called
oranges that's what I thought but
apparently not oh oh I'm sorry are we
moving we moving and grooving are the
pineapples going to
touch wait wait some movement is
happening oh nice nice okay all right
there's a possibility here that we maybe
will get some touching some fruits
touching just let them move oh
my we got a
melon oh wow good job good job thanks
worked really hard on
that as then I didn't I did not I don't
even know what's happening half the time
in the
game
well how old are your cats I'm curious
about
them
um not too old maybe like a year or and
a
half wow they're almost they're just
about as old as mine oh sweet yeah they
need a man I wish they would like go on
walks with me outside yeah that's that
seems so nice why I'm waiting I tried to
get them into it I got like um like a
carriage for cats but whenever I put
them in it they start like meowing like
meow don't make me do this a they're
just a little scared scared of
change babies but I want I want them to
go on
walks yeah you can train them to do that
depending on the cat it really depends
on the cat to be
honest
yeah nice now that it's nice and cool
outside I feel like much better time to
take cats on
walks true true some of them are just
too afraid I think no the peach is going
to touch the other
Peach suffering
Chey sorry you have to hear me like this
I'm supposed to be I'm supposed to be
very capable helpful Senpai I can't show
weakness it's okay I just woke up I'm
not going to remember anything swag all
right that makes me feel a lot
better I feel much better
now I think you're doing great well your
fruits
thanks thanks a lot no
problem about to
lose it's fine
you play a lot of games
Shori uh on stream off stream
no I was going to ask I know you don't
you don't play like a ton of them but
out of all of them you chose everhood
which I think is really
interesting yeah not everybody choice I
liked it I liked it oh oh I beat the the
the guitar trash dude yeah and uh frog
frog boy pissed me off actually oh
yeah but IM manag to get him I I knew it
it was incredibly hard it was incredibly
hard he I feel like he was actually the
hardest dude in the entire game for me
yeah he essentially like trained me at
this point yeah yeah well you kind of
that is a really tough boss battle for
sure that requires like almost
Perfection definitely true did you just
uh did you get one of the endings or did
you go for all of them
um I got the pacifist and I got whatever
the the standard ending is where you
destroy everyone gotcha swag nice I
don't know what the other endings are um
did you ever fight the green hat dude
the
Mage um you mean like at the bottom of
the like this dungeon looking thing yeah
yeah yeah yeah with all the writing on
the
wall uh that's before you have to go
into like a three-hour Hall H away right
yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah I guess I
fought him then okay that dude is
wild he gave me a lot of trouble
personally there's also apparently bad
yeah there's apparently a cat boss um oh
um the secret one I think yeah yeah yeah
the secret cat boss I just saw in like
custom battles I don't want to go back
for to
things understandable yeah I didn't I
didn't fight the cat boss either I just
uh I don't think I'm at that
level dead beats we played it on hard
didn't we we play it on hard I think at
that point it's kind of very difficult
to do bosses like that yeah I think
after like the frog one apparently like
there's not much difference it's teen
hard in normal it's just like how much
health you did I see makesense yeah I
was kind of surprised I thought they
would do like more more like notes or
something M yeah yeah yeah switch it up
a little bit but I guess at that point
it's just kind of like it becomes a bit
grindy I suppose Choo Cho yeah I wonder
what the the sequel's going to be like I
can't wait I've been seeing some
screenshots of and it looks so good but
we have to wait a long time is it um is
it an ala let me look at I don't think
it's all 3D I think maybe the battles
but there's still a lot of sprite work
in there so oh I
see so hype need more everhood
game so I just want to frog again I have
frog syndrome yeah some frog Stockholm
syndrome he made you like him over
time yeah yeah people people even wrot
F oh my God are you kidding me I'm I'm
okay with it it was kind of like um
something about I lost like over a
hundred times that I got to a point
where I actually like liked almost
beating up
up yeah that's that's the Stockholm
syndrome for you this is lore now yeah
nice very nice did you uh finish story
of Seasons or you kind of just playing
on your own time oh no I haven't even
touched it I should though I don't
really time to stock Nami yeah yeah
follow her around make her make her
uncomfortable it's not uncomfortable
it's just like uh Curious you know yeah
you just want to know more more about
her and how she's so Charming you know
yeah yeah yeah love Nami man I can't
believe they don't take all the gifts in
the world like you you have to give them
specific things they like it's just like
real life I don't understand yeah why
would you take this cute flower come on
now I know went out of my way to pick it
for you you're not going to take my
flower Namy did you play the um the
original story of Seasons the the
wonderful life one oh yes I played the
guy one and girl side oh same same did
you know there was a glitch where like
if you had a baby and you picked up a
certain flower they would get stuck
where you picked up the flower all
day what a weird
glitch yeah I think it's near um it's
near the fireworks people I remember I
picked up a flower and dropped the baby
ongr and I couldn't pick him up and
whoever like I married he like Hey
where's the child and I'm like I don't
know
whoops
great but I liked it so much it kept
doing it oh my gosh what the just
so I can see the cut
scene yeah nothing demented about that
whatsoever normal Ming around hide and
seek wow yeah definitely very normal no
worries did you ever play um Animal
Parade oh yeah yeah yeah I I also played
tream Tranquility but I played more of
the tree one the animal yeah Animal
Parade was kind of like the enhanced
version that came out later I guess but
yeah yeah that super
good I wanted that one specifically so
the children can do
chores yeah force your children to work
for you yeah I think even the spouse
could I'm like come on guys I'm earning
money here what do you do you make me
lunch and that's it yeah seriously
they're back into
it yeah it was really cool too that like
the child could like change depending on
who you got with as well that was really
neat I liked that a lot yeah they had a
that like rival
marriages things up all the all the
Village People could get with somebody
except of course the person that you got
with little sad but s but while you win
some you lose
you win some you lose some
baby apparently um what was that who did
you go for in that game um so when about
in the Time of My
Life um that I played that game I had
like a very
specific archetype that I liked which
was really like fiery gy shm protagonist
dudes so I went after Luke the blue
haired one the dude the dumbass yeah I
went after him yeah yeah I know him yeah
and then I played it again and I went
for the wizard in my gamer phase because
the Wizard's the hardest to get with
right oh I wanted to challenge yeah
exactly and uh the most recent time I
played it like a year or two ago um I
went for for Toby the fisherman
dude oh cuz he's so chill and
relaxed yeah I like that kind of chill
relaxed
Vibe also fishing is
cool it is never did it though
yeah it's cool in games at least yeah in
games it's much easier I think who did
you go
for um the first time I played it I I
was almost going for Luke but then uh
Chase showed up and he makes food so I
went for him and then I think in one of
my playthroughs I went for the may your
son I think he's
name yeah I have a high school friend
who's obsessed with
Gil yeah I like the uh the responsible
sort of cool sort yeah cool
guy yeah yeah yeah I feel like those are
I can definitely see you choosing those
dudes for
sure yeah they're pretty eomen
too pretty
eomen yeah they had the best they had
the best bachelors and the bachelorettes
were cute too
yeah yeah who did I really like I really
liked um oh my gosh the the wi witch
literally reminds me of Shion
Senpai oh the witch is cute even though
I never got to meet her in that second
game oh yeah she's like
unable
oh yeah if you guys look up a picture of
the witch from tree of Tranquility uh SL
Animal Parade you guys will see
if you guys look it up they look exactly
like hello
Raiders uh who else was
[Music]
cute everyone was pretty cute in that
game I remember um I think there were
some laggy areas that kind of irritated
me yeah and you had to walk you had to
walk to so many places like early on
they have like big gigantic Maps so so
just to get to one start of the map to
the end was like tedious really
annoying it's the one thing I'll never
forgive about that
game it'd be nice if they remade it
though yeah apparently yeah there are
hints of it being remade um in a
wonderful life I didn't ask my friend
what they were but I got a frantic text
from a friend of mine who loves those
games um and she was like oh my God
they're probably going to make remake
Animal Parade they're hints and
clues uh you know I hope they also make
a magical Melody if you ever play oh
yeah yeah that one was really good yeah
it had so many uh choices for romantic
options
yeah yeah lots of good choices too is
that the one with um the really tund
brown haired
dude with the band I think his name is
Kurt I'm not sure oh yeah I went for him
yeah how did I know
I had a
feeling
nice wow I'm so glad I found the kindred
spirit though I feel like a lot of
members of Advent seem to be fans of uh
Harvest Moon SL story of
Seasons oh yeah yeah's already she's
already um I think proposed to Lumin
Lumina ah Lumina yeah I chose Lumina as
well for my first run through in
Japanese oh
I Tred talk to Lumina she only gave me
like gave me five pieces of dialogue so
like what the heck I'm going back to
Nami at least she trauma dumps to
me she's so edgy oh but I love
her I feel like um this fruits game you
guys I've been getting worse and worse
every time we've played it it's been a
worse and worse score my score gets
lower and lower I should just really
maybe you're at your limit it could be
you know maybe I'll just never do better
maybe I'll just never get to 3,000 but
that's something that I just need to
accept in my life you know to grow as a
human
being you know I almost gave up with the
Frog dude I think I think you can do it
yeah I even left my game at like the
last checkpoint for uh 22 hours before
my computer like went to
bed nice yeah wow
so I think I think if you leave it at
some point come back you can absolutely
get it yeah maybe I won't give
up yeah determination yeah I just worry
about the dead beats you know I don't
want them to be forced to watch me only
play this game forever and ever must be
rough
oh for him maybe what I'll do is I'll
just play it in my own time and every
time I get like kind of close I'll start
a stream up again
mhm I'm having a good time boss okay
well as long as you guys are having an
okay
time yeah I just worry about the dead
beats I want to make sure they're having
fun each time you you stream this game
it reminds him to eat more
fruit it's good for you right yeah it is
I don't eat enough though ah yeah yeah I
eat a lot of vegetables these days
vegetables are definitely super good for
you oh that's
I'm trying the the V8 thingy oh yeah I
should have had a
V8 yeah there's like um a no sodium
version I think oo nice yeah cuz those
things are packed with sodium aren't
they I think
so yeah you got to be careful if they're
like too
salty it's not good for you to get
dehydrated yeah my name is already like
partially
salty
sh thank you for laughing at my joke and
explaining
it it's only cuz I know a little bit in
nihongo nongo Jo nongo joou maybe a
little bit M Mama it's fine Mama Mama
it's okay squishy D squishy D yeah just
a little bit it's enough you know it's
enough to get me
around um but I need to learn more I
need to make it a for real hobby you
know but I'm streaming so much I can't
help it oh oh what do we have here
y
okay good good good
good song's going to haunt my nightmares
I swear to
God but I don't know like I've mentioned
I've mentioned this a couple times to
others before but it feels like a good a
good Holo rivalry game
you know like I
want I don't know it's interesting
seeing the big Grand scoreboard you know
and how everybody's
doing oh it's cool I don't know it it
feels like a nice fun friendly rivalry
between everyone in the
company who play Whoever has the highest
score you know that they're they're the
next one you got to take out I can't
take out so you say senpai she's too
strong that's just not GNA happen man oh
what uh what was her score uh so she
recently got the brand new one I believe
it was 37 was it 37 something you guys
3,700
something oh I was there to witness her
get it too which was
wild yeah 360
3631 with senpai's
score which is too strong yeah no she's
on a different level but she's also like
a Tetris Master too you know she's just
great at those
games and then this is absolutely just
like a Tetris it's fruit Tetris yeah
yeah it's fruit
Tetris I mean I definitely see the
resemblance I suppose come on you guys
know you want to
touch are we touching are we touching
fruits are we thinking about touch yeah
melon good job thanks it's like a
matchmaking game yeah yeah exactly but
like there's a lot you have to think
about as well um like making sure that
you know the fruits don't fly up and
like explode and like cuz that that's
happened to me a couple of times the
fruits accidentally fly up yeah it's bad
I think I remember seeing a b boo
stream the fruits flying away into
Oblivion and destroying the Run yeah
it's
common it's common very common more
common than you'd
think and very painful
and heartrending so let's try and avoid
that drink a V8 at this
point yeah you can get your daily fruits
without having to worry about playing
this godforsaken
game yeah hope you're having fun I mean
it's all right I
guess you know it's a challenge at this
point
yeah like this this is painful for me
and I probably shouldn't have dro St
that there I really shouldn't
have but that's okay we'll live through
it look we've made two apples there's a
pineapple
okay we'll make it through maybe we'll
do something with that cherry I don't
know maybe we will maybe we
won't I got to try
though
okay here we go grape grape okay
are we going down the grape path again I
think we
are oh my favorite visual novel route
yeah the grape path yeah go the path of
the
grape it's the grapest
no I'm really Ming I'm really losing it
but maybe I can make this touch yeah
okay it became an
[Music]
apple
okay yes now we have a Beach we're
getting so much
closer wait no maybe if I get the Cherry
ah okay whatever I'm just going to
choose not to get angry over
it we just keep going we keep
moving okay that's
fine that's
fine okay now we've got an
apple I know those grapes want to touch
each
other okay
y oh that's
[Music]
nice okay we have to be chill sh do we
have to be
chill you can do
it can
I yeah you really think somay eventually
today really think we have a chance
maybe think it's
possible man man this kind of reminds me
that K Remastered game thinking about it
oh yeah like the frustration with it I
guess yeah the
anger
yeah it's something all
right it's
something let me get a
PB
game you know you want to give me a PB
hey how about we all just chill out how
about we all just calm down Mr grape hey
I see you there Mr grape just going to
move right down there and pop come on Mr
grape
okay hold on I need
to need to um drink some SEO
[Music]
juice it's our fallen Brethren
yeah M tastes like
watermelon all right I feel calm now
I'm calm you're determined yes I would
say
so here we can drop a cherry here we're
not going to just abandon it we won't we
won't
we leave this here
too we we won't abandon these fruits we
won't I I promise you guys I promise you
that we won't abandon
them we're just you know we're working
on a project right now a little
[Music]
project oh my God I'm going to
going to lose it every
time all right hold
on it's got to be moving slightly
downward
right all right there's a way to fix
this there's a way to fix this I got it
it I can do
it we just have to believe
yeah yep just
believe we got it we got it
it it's fine check out yeah cool
Peach
O Okay third best score for
today that's not
[Music]
bad now we've got a little
pear go on fruits where are we going
where are we
moving moving and grooving
fruits these fruits going to touch each
other
maybe
okay not bad not
[Music]
bad now if we put this
here what a nice Apple
beautiful Apple you're so close I'm
scared to
talk I don't know if I'd say close
um I may have ruined it you if you round
it up hold on Apple Please Touch come on
Apple
yes that was really uh oh
wow
[Music]
oo sometimes all you got to do is wait
you know cuz cuz they move
and oh
no come on fall down
pear hold
on just wait a
minute the pear is being pushed you just
got to push the
pair yeah there he goes he's on a little
journey there he
goes he's all going up did we it
up please please
no there he
[Music]
goes yeah just give him a little push
just got to give him a little
yeah
come
on
okay we can make it
happen just be chill just be very
chill this game hates me it knows what
I'm trying to
do come
on
please I'm just watching in anticipation
considering that I should get like boss
battle
music come pray for
me why would you do
that
man we were so
close I know you were so
focused I guess there are a couple of
ways I could have done it
better but look at how close we got no
look at that look at that screenshot it
everyone
screen look at how myy almost did
it yeah but but but you know that's like
uh that's before the the actual ultimate
score I mean yeah I guess that's
true so
positive mhm thanks for being
positive no problem we can use a little
positive influence every once in a
[Music]
while well technically if you're if
you're two negative St you can become
like positive too you know what yeah two
negatives equal time to be depressing
yeah oh my gosh math but that's a smart
way to think about it I don't know I I
see where you're coming
from yeah realistic though I think that'
be freaking
annoying to deal with two negatives imag
trying to be positive with two negative
people yeah seems difficult but you know
that's okay I feel it's weird I feel
like I don't know less bad now
because we got close and I feel like
sometimes that's all you need is to feel
like you got close
once you
know yeah so close and yet so far a
chat it was nice while it
[Music]
lasted but you know I don't want to give
up not right now I won't force myself to
continue for too long if if I really
can't but I'd like to really
try you
know the Ultimate
Gamer
maybe maybe like number four in
y maybe number four and I'm cool with
that I'm cool with
that but now that it's finally fall I
want to get out and touch grass a little
bit more you
know oh yeah the the dying dead grass
yeah yeah exactly it's the best time of
year number four yeah I like seeing the
uh the trees change colors yeah exactly
that's the best part of it you know like
yeah I walked outside and I instantly
felt not
sad you know fall does usually people
get sad around here though right
helloa hello oh my gosh another friend
hello I was watching so I figured I'd
just pop in instead of being like a
weird creeper in your chat there is's
here y let me let me put you in here
just real quick there you are okay are
you going to play watermelon
Teresa I I made a watermelon
before Oh in the game like real one yeah
or twice twice I have grown watermelon
once too
oh wow like a real
farmer yeah cool I respect it the real
story of season's protagonist yeah yeah
cool to actually grow something I I'm
death so I don't really know how to grow
anything but I assume but sounds cool
wow are you winning relatable oh no
Nissa I'm not winning I'm losing big
time but you know what we got pretty
close last time and
I'll yeah you were doing very well thank
you how's your what's your score like
narissa
uh I haven't gotten to play too much but
I think I think I'm at like two 200 or
2,200 okay that's that's great that's a
good score I've gotten two watermelons
in game nice and honestly I it to me it
feels like yatsi where as long I mean I
don't know how yatsi works but as long
as I get the watermelon I actually have
won the
game that's a really positive way of
thinking about it I I like the way you
think orisa yeah
thank you nice okay I'm going to try and
apply that positivity to my own life so
I so I stop suffering playing this game
yes because I can't get 3,000 I'm having
a really tough time with it you know hey
you're super duper close yeah yeah we
did get close but I just couldn't squeak
it out in the end but that's okay maybe
we'll get better fruits this time yeah I
mean it is partially luck based so you
really can't blame yourself yeah not too
much though I I know that there are some
moves that I could be doing better I I
can't get too mad you know there's no
reason for that it's not going to help
either to be too angry about it so
exactly yeah we'll just stay chill which
is kind of hard the longer you go on
definitely you start to lose brain cells
but talking to friends has actually
helped me quite a bit so really see all
to drop by yeah I feel like my blood
pressure has gone down significantly
which is
progress it's progress somehow
mhm gosh some of these fruits though I
tell you what they uh they really don't
want to touch each other no that would
be too easy wouldn't it all too
easy oh well they want you to suffer but
why what did I do to them you're just
too cute well you did drink their their
breath Ren I think juice or whatever
yeah that's a good point they probably
don't like that very much yeah probably
not yeah I can't help it say so juice
you know stressful times call for Sayo
juice plus it's late at night why not
have a nice Sayo juice night
cap seems good to
me every once in a while you know just
to relax did you just wake up
narissa yes not too long ago I woke up I
ate I ate
breakfast oh crap yeah what did you guys
eat today I know it's late for you my
yeah oh no no you can't do that I say is
I forgot to eat too today but well I'm
making a thumbnail first then I'll eat
yeah there you go God got to motivate
yourself you know I'm not as bad as bi
boo though she eats just like I think
after stream yeah she's crazy I know so
wonder she stopped
growing yeah Jesus people please you got
to get your nutrients your vitamins and
minerals you know oh what a date you're
making me want to play the stupid sua
game well you probably should play it oh
terrible influence terrible terrible
influence I can't help it it's like
addicting I think I I continuously will
keep staying up till like 3:00 a.m.
playing this oh good God game
yeah yeah which sucks you always think
oh this could be the one it's like
gambling this could be the one where we
get 3,000 this could be it but it never
is nope unless you're you're ahead yeah
exactly yeah if you're M though then you
might
get you'll get lucky
yeah she is skillful I
suppose she be moving she do be
moving that does help it is an
advantage but that's
okay you know what we could have
connected those pairs if I hadn't been
so Hasty that's another thing is that
you have to be patient playing this game
I don't want to be patient playing this
game yeah I don't I don't have a lot of
patience so I guess maybe we're just
doomed to never hit 3,000 because of our
lack of
patience
yeah man I don't know playing this long
is kind of like patience right or
Insanity I'm not really sure one or the
other it's definitely one or the
other I don't
know I don't know I I can't stop I know
I should sleep
but oh what time is it then it is 2:30
oh oh my Good Golly yeah maybe I'll go
to sleep at some point cuz I I know that
Fu Moko wanted to play again and we
wanted to be in called together too at
that time anyone who's around can of
course join and cry with us if they'd
like but group crying stream yeah a
group crying session between all of
us so we might do that in the following
day or so maybe that's when we hit 3,000
finally yeah some nice tears being shed
yeah you everybody could use a big group
cry ladies group cry session let's
go girls let's go time to cry if we cry
together though it makes it so much
better yeah you know it's
cathartic mhm I love crying with the
girlies yeah it's my favorite
extracurricular activity oh hell yeah
look at
that now we just got to make now we just
got to connect we just got to do it we
got to
yeah just
connect okay there we go that was
definitely the right choice that I made
really pan you wanted to hide that
cherry from me you piece of is is
it a pmen is it not an orange no it's
not an orange I was surprised too is it
a little green thing on it yeah oranges
don't have little green things on them I
don't think God just the one with the um
the shocked face I think yeah
or that one which
one I have no idea it's one of them
we're all slowly losing our
minds trying to understand this
game oh well that's fine hey if we make
an apple yeah that's what I thought I
figured that you wouldn't give me that
game that's all right that's very cute
of you
game come on
there we
go we can make dreams come true If We
Believe come on no you got this thanks
thanks
girl just believe in yourself gamer okay
you bed should be easy right yeah
totally I definitely believe in myself
isn't that right dead beats I definitely
have the most self-confidence out of
everyone in h and it's
me I would believe
it I like how your voice is breaking
during that
speech We Believe yeah they see they
definitely agree with me they
know they know it's the
truth all right we got a pineapple now
we just got to make a peach we can do it
this should be completely possible
actually all right mm hold
on we getting the hang of it
um little Cherry over here connect these
nice nice nice nice strawberry and we've
got another personman oh damn it I got
confused I made the wrong
move oh no I might be in trouble after
that one bad strawberry move oh God it's
over isn't it because of that because I
thought the next one was the one that I
was currently holding
please I hate when that happens oh my Fu
God you got to be kidding me please
please please have mercy game I'm
begging
you I regret it I
do just forgive me
please I can't go on like
this that could have been the one you
guys that could have been the
one is this how I'm going to live my
life forever wondering if this was the
one
my life man I'm never going to
forget that for the rest of my
life I'll forget it
tomorrow man imagine if you had to go to
those anger be sessions and the reason
you're there is just because of this
game you know I believe
it what happened I can see that 100% I'm
really starting to feel it now but see I
can't I can't even be salty about that
because that was 100% my fault now I can
be salty if I don't feel like it's my
fault but that that was me being a dummy
you
guys was me not not
seeing my eyes my special eyes come
on it's all right we'll get it
eventually I'm playing too in solidarity
oh yeah playing some s game right now
yeah let me know if you
get I will I'll send you send me a
picture of the sua send of your melons
thanks melon pics ASAP I need to see him
show him to me I'll be
waiting the best got it doublea though
nobody's gotten a double sua yet yeah I
don't know I don't know if that's
possible I've got to be honest but I saw
videos of dude I saw I saw somebody get
it I don't believe it you think they
were lying you think that
wased people lie on the
internet of course not no way why would
anyone do that go on the internet and
lie yeah I don't believe that at
all everyone's really trustworthy
especially internet people so
trustworthy the most trustworthy out of
anyone you're so right how could I how
could I be so foolish yeah cuz Kami Sama
is watching them you know they they got
to know all right pineapple Co nice one
two one two
three
okay here we go pop yep uh-huh and touch
Peach
swag okay now myy calm
down you can do this you've got this
seni I appreciate I appreciate your
faith in me I don't know if it's it is
Warrington are you sure about that yes I
don't know if you're back in the right
Idol
here I don't
know really feeling the rage the rage is
really subsiding since you guys came
here good feels kind of good to not be
extremely angry all the time at this
game this is why we should all just play
together get you usually get angry at
games it depends on the game
just this game mostly just this game
mostly oh if only those pineapples could
connect with each other the world would
be a better
place come on
yles feel
nice now we've been on a streak of doing
pretty okay maybe the key is to just
talk to friends yeah that might really
be it you guys I don't know it it might
be so clean yeah I know chat right it's
not bad not bad at
all
okay all
right we're pulling it together kind of
just I committed to this meon right here
no come back Mr Apple he's gone that's a
bad apple that's a bad apple he left me
alone you get back here y pulled him
back yeah teim Mo's
boss okay
stay
calm yeah squeeze right in
there squeeze right on
in here we
go I hear cute animal noises in the oh
I'm so sorry let me go close my window
I'm sorry I love having my window open
in the morning fres bow bow that's all
bow bows don't worry about it we want
our walkies
Raa
walkies it's the perfect time for
walkies this fall yeah yeah it's your
turn to to get them on the walk now y
just leave it to me oh my God it's the
cutest reason ever my dogs outside and
my neighbors have a
puppy they're both looking at each other
through the fence oh new baaba
baby how
sweet so cute
mhm do you guys ever get like Worried
About Pets when they're barking late at
night or
something
yes I can't say I have a I have a dog
aside from fuam
Moko that's true that's true I always
feel guilty if just like a dog outside
that's just like barking randomly at 2
a.m. it's probably just like dog
instincts but I feel like oh man why are
they outside buddy yeah yeah like hey
buddy are you okay you know you want to
know that they're all
right
[Music]
yeah I love dogs too though I don't have
any dogs but I love dogs they're sweet I
like dogs very sweet
creatures extremely sweet creatures oh
hey Peaches do we want to like connect
with each other maybe I don't know I
think it would be kind of cool
if we
did I'm just
[Music]
saying I I think the worst part of this
game is when nothing is falling where
you need it to fall yeah yeah that hurts
the game is is purposely against you
yeah well I mean technically it kind of
is you know it's meant to
make meant to make you hate
everything you won't get me a
game mean I have to like
it I'm going to be positive and there's
nothing you can do about
it God that hurts oh that hurts no
all right another game we can do another
game we got this yeah it it hasn't even
been seven hours like the last one you
guys we're doing much better I can
tell I can tell we're doing yeah this is
not an addiction what do you
mean we don't use that word here problem
we don't use that word here that dirty
word no such
thing don't you
worry we definitely got it this time cuz
we got so close that one time I'll never
forget
it we could have had it we could have
had it
all Rolling in the Deep Rolling in the
Deep I knew that was coming sorry I knew
that was
coming no I'm glad I'm glad you said it
it needed to be said yeah needed to be
said do not oh my God why are you doing
okay okay it's fine doesn't matter we're
safe anyway just
kidding oh life life is full of
hardships it's full of fruit it sure is
sometimes in some cases the fruit are
the
hardships what's your favorite fruit you
guys have to tell me strawberries nice
pineapples and
mangos very good you like the more
tropical stuff eh I guess so
I used to eat um like sort of thed out
frozen fruit late at
night I have it for a while
yeah sounds
yum Frozen thought out midnight snack
fruit mm healthy although I guess not
really for the
sugar healthier than other things you
could be eating is a midnight snack like
chips Etc
yeah
man yeah they say that fruits are
healthy for you but they are really
packed full of sugar you know yeah
yeah but I like sweet things can't be
helped right M better than eating candy
I
guess I'd rather eat um ice cream until
I explode that's my advice ice
cream oh that depends on how I'm feeling
that day you know ah it's like a like a
mood ring you got to have a select type
of ice cream exactly
yeah nice I'm a simple girl I just like
chocolate nice and simple sometimes
simple is
best yeah Simple and
Clean
yeah nice I like
vanilla I'm also very simple but cookies
and cream is yummy too it
I I think I like matcha but I can't get
any of it uh easily that's like good you
know good quality matcha it's hard to
come by got to come to Japan it's
everywhere you're you're you you're
going to have an easy time convincing
me easy just get over here LOL simple
just just go to
ja like it's that easy to do on on my
way then all right I'm waiting
I'll just be sitting if you're offering
a host
then my home is always open I have a
guest room so oh I'm just hanging out we
all just went there yeah yeah why not
come chill sleep sleep overtime yeah
yeah I'm always happy to have more
company you know that's good that you're
so open to it yeah MH always I mean I
have I like my alone time to get me
wrong but I have plenty of that yeah so
whenever friends come over it's like an
extra fun
party come on pineapples come on
pineapples I know they want to be
together I can feel
it why do they have to play with my
heart like
that cuz they
pineapples evil so
evil oh boy
okay um I don't know this doesn't look
very good for me right now unless unless
unless
PR I just don't see a world where this
becomes anything like a win anything
close to a
win but you know I've been surprised
playing this game before sometimes the
fruits just move in a way that works and
it
works so I don't know we can only hope
that that's how this goes yeah but hope
can only carry you so
far yeah isn't that the truth it's like
a metaphor for life I keep telling
everyone this game is a metaphor for
life I think I'm crazy
[Laughter]
it do
metaphorical yeah we have too many
miscellaneous fruits this isn't a good
room
run yeah it won't work out in the end
sadly but I feel like I can't I can't
just quit you know doesn't feel right
don't be a quitter I'm too deep yeah
sunca fallacy
man just go in there just get in
there oh well we tried our best I know
we'll get AA this time I can feel the
watermelon I can taste it I can taste
the watermelon and taste like like
victory yeah it sure does or defeat yeah
want one of them I'd prefer it be the
first one I'd really prefer
that but knowing my luck I won't be able
to get the fruits for
it I know the game has given me the
fruits for victory several times and I
have squandered
them that's what hurts the
most knowing I've squandered the fruits
of
[Music]
Victory eh it
happens yeah you got the right attitude
I
think so empathetic
Rea
bigs sometimes sometimes just got to
roll with the punches I guess like how
it just made me accidentally drop that
uh Cherry where I didn't want to drop it
which is really cool of the game to do
for me don't raise your voice when your
friends are here no raise scream let it
all
out
yeah if you hear some rage pop
up apology apologies in advance it will
happen it's okay I'm counting on it yeah
looking forward to it getting yelled
at
what I wasn't aware I like that who
there I guess now you
are discovering new things about
ourselves together oh this is all what
bonding at a slumber party is about
mhm yeah
clearly that's what this
is all right nice making some
progress not bad not
bad yeah I should figured that
happen don't let it get you down Mory
look at that we still can make those we
can make those pairs connect look at
them they just touched y amazing I know
right what a sight to behold because
there are no fruits around yet there
aren't like a ton of fruits to wedge in
between
anything but there will
be will before long before
long
okay come on I wonder how chat hasn't
gone insane yet are you guys
okay are you guys okay I have to check
back in with you guys every once in a
while to make sure you're
fine this the fruit took them away no
yes no yes I'm getting mixed reviews
here all
right maybe there's a way these can
touch
maybe a I don't know guys this doesn't
look very possible to
me you've got it I believe yeah you
think it could work out man stop belie
in yourself Don't Stop
Believing
okay all right heard loud and clear I'll
just keep moving fruits around
M keep fruiting the fruit if you fruit
the fruit nothing can go wrong yeah
explanation how do I do that you got to
teach me just you just you just got to
do it you just you just do it is it just
a
feeling yes everything's a feeling okay
if you say so man I'll take anything
suggestion at this point anything that
will help me get closer to the
goal what did she mean by that
chat what does she mean by that that's
all right we'll figure it
out when we start
fruiting fruiting all over the
place juicy tasty delicious
[Music]
melon
you having fun there
champ yeah the fruit is fruiting playing
to
away
yeah having a great time no doubt of
course I have two peaches um okay which
is
good I but I've just you know the little
fruits on the bottom yeah they get in
the way for sure but I feel like it's
it's fine for it to be like that because
even pekot Senpai when she got her high
score had a ton of fruits at the bottom
so she managed she was so lucky though
cuz she managed to move them in such a
way yeah that like they really didn't
encounter each other like they they were
off to the sides they were and I'm just
like how did you do that us yeah I think
that's called it's a special skill and
it's it's a little difficult um to do
yourself without proper coaching but
it's called being smart um and she's
she's pretty good at that she's pretty
good at being
smart making the big game plays yeah
making the
big yeah JP
skills they're on a different level I
tell you what but that's okay Ian
represent to yeah Ian represent just as
well Ian's working hard too on the S
game doing all that we
can doing all that we can cuz that's all
we can
[Music]
do
okay there's a possibility
here that we can make it out
alive it is possible it is not probable
but it is
possible it is very probable think
you're so optimistic where're where do I
get your
optimism um you steal it from others
yeah yeah okay sounds like a
[Music]
plan I just wish these apples would meet
and touch each other but they won't
listen to
me won't
[Music]
listen that hurts so bad cuz I could
tell we were getting somewhere but
yeah that's the worst
yeah but it's okay it happens and how am
I to know that it isn't completely my
fault mm I'm sure the chat will tell me
because there will be some point exra in
chat that's like well actually if you
made this move which is understandable
all right Point Dexter I hear you but if
you just you could have saved the whole
thing all
right I will say this game awakens
something in me that where when I'm
watching people play it even though I
know I'm no better it just makes you
want a back seat cuz it seems so easy
even though it's not you know yeah even
though it isn't all the you look at it
you're like oh I can do that and then
you play it and you're like never mind
this is way harder than it looks
yeah are y all back seating in chat I
have a question what's your high score
and be honest with me incoming Liars
here they go here come the lies get
ready here they come 7K
haahaa
1,000 there are a couple believable
scores in there but I'm going to choose
to go la la la la and close my ears like
a
brat not
listen you mean Close Your Eyes Ears I
mean yeah true enough what do you think
chat sounds
like I don't know do you like Hear
Voices when you read
chat I feel like I read it in my own
voice
like typical standard generic one
yeah I feel so too I think somebody
asked me that recently and I was like
here what do you mean
here who hears Chad You Hear Voices when
you're streaming sounds like something
you should get checked out
yeah oh
jeez it'd be nice if I could hear them
in like a Japanese St though M that'll
be kind of interesting a JP dub chat
yeah yeah that would certainly be
something well then going to be like a
lot of voices then if I could hear
everything at one time
[Music]
true yeah might get kind of
disruptive yeah much
yeah hurts your brain
eventually
mhm yeah these days it doesn't hurt my
head too much though being surrounded by
P yeah kind of used to it by now you
know yeah it's not so bad I made a
mistake
again when will she stop making
mistakes I don't know where a high IQ
tactic
yeah I can definitely do that I I
can I'm just not as smart as everyone
look I'm not is
smart then I throw I give
up no stay hungry and devour yeah oh man
I'm hungry
reisa get some
fruits oh no no not not first thing in
the morning really fruits aren't a good
breakfast for you I already eat bacon
and eggs and all that stuff I mean that
sounds fine and all that but I just feel
like it's more refreshing you know
I like to have fruits I don't think I
even have fruits if I did are molded by
now oh
no moldy
fruits probably ah but I mean I've been
that way too before in the past thinking
I'm going to start eating a ton of
fruits and
then they go
forgotten
yeah just waiting to see the sunlight
again but they never do yeah this is I
force myself to eat the fruits though I
realize that they're expiring and I'm
like
myy yeah no other snacks you have to eat
the
fruits
yeah they're good for you mm very indeed
especially berries berries are super
good for you I love berries man you guys
eat strawberries with like sugar or
anything no I don't add
anything yeah I just eat a
grand yeah that's seems to be an old
people thing like my grandparents used
to make me that for breakfast fruits
covered in sugar in like a fruits bowl
full cat
hair they own 64 cats oh my god oh je
but you know just pick out the hairs and
eat the fruit bowl it was fun yeah I
know what that's
like an essential ingredient true that
Chad true
that adds extra texture flavor
texture and
[Music]
flavor yeah that's okay little hair is
bound to find it way
flavor well hair is bound to find its
way in it's all right no big
deal oh
my life is so
over why did you did you lose a close
game no I haven't lost but I'm just
making dumb decisions ah
you know how it is every day of my life
man every
day decisions ask
Mory she knows a lot about
that like this for example staying up
this late when I have a promotion stream
oh no when's the what time's your stream
later oh it's it's only it's at like
11:00 a.m. um jst but I want some time
to like prepare you know practice
rehearse Etc it's
important
[Music]
mhm no very important but here you are
playing SU game important this is to
promote the stream for later of course
yeah I root everybody over there
ayp yeah going to root you guys to the
the next stream I'm really losing it oh
it's late at
night you feeling it now Mr crown sure
am me boy sponge boy
mebob Spong boy sponge boy mebob I'm
feeling it
[Music]
now that's okay tomorrow's a brand new
day yeah full of More
Watermelon I need to really I really I
really need to get 3,000 so I can just
free myself from
this the curse of the W balance yeah
I really do just need to get
[Music]
free sleepy
moly
sleepy yeah I'm really feeling the
Sleepy
vibes okay there we
go oh I got so lucky did you get sua no
but I got a melon and Suddenly It's so
empty in here you
know I was like Wow St making me
jealous you can do it so
positive I need to stop restarting over
and over
again and I just always see it through
to the end yeah that's
smart restarting will just make you mad
until the end of
time
yeah oh that was
cute
[Music]
yeah okay there might be potential in
this run we shall see though I don't
want to trust it immediately I have
trust issues with this
game big major trust
[Music]
issues ah damn it
I wasn't quick
[Music]
enough come on there we go I knew they'd
touch I knew it in my heart of hearts I
did come on just go touch
him do
it do it touch
him
that's some peer pressure yeah he needs
to do it realiz his
Destiny is an apple
we okay now pay attention Mory this is
where the game gets
[Music]
good that was painful to watch I'm sure
it was painful for you all to
witness I'm so sorry
[Music]
I can't believe that the song Still
sounds like fine like it doesn't make me
want to rip my hair out right it's just
a cute little song cute little
watermelon
song why it shouldn't be it should be
annoying it should make me rage
more not to say that's what I want cuz
it's definitely not what I want yeah I
think if the the fruits had like angry
faces each time you made a mistake it'
be like mocking you yeah that's a good
point that could be really like you're
doing great you know good luck you got
[Music]
this I hate when they launch themselves
out yeah it's not
great not the best actually worst part
of the game
yeah
yeah I'm having a bad
time I probably shouldn't have done
that we all have those moments don't we
I probably shouldn't have done that
moments like I probably shouldn't have
opened the game and started playing
today I probably shouldn't have done
that I don't know
was very wise we
understand much wiser if I just didn't
open the game Mory just didn't open the
game too late
now it's too freaking
late suffer with the consequences of
your actions okay I just did felt
awful man big salty hours
mhm can't even
lie theault is real today watch he's
just going to he's just going to bounce
all the way back
down it's very
cute how adorable man I love
fruits man I love
fruits but do they love you no
no but they will fear me please
they will I promise just just wait a
minute you'll see oh come
on come on let's
go fruit
[Music]
time
song's just addicting in its own way
takes some serious skill to make a song
that doesn't make me want to rip my hair
out after listening to it for 7even
hours
straight crazy I two wish to attain that
skill someday right that's the
[Music]
dream
why would you do
[Music]
that I'm starting to really lose it
guys don't lose it I'm really losing
it
here's a question for you what's your
favorite
musical Lim iser Rob really yeah it's my
favorite one what do you like about it
everything I've only seen the liveaction
one Oh you mean the movie yeah music
I've never seen it yeah I've been told
no it's much better
better see it wait what's it
[Music]
about um what is it about it's a story
of a man and it goes through his life
and his struggles he was a
prisoner yeah he was a prisoner long ago
and he stole a loaf of bread and then a
a priest showed him kindness and then he
like vows to live an honest life and he
turns his life around and Adventures
ensue and he finds people people that
mean a lot to him and he he has a foster
daughter and uh it it it goes through
his life and there's
war it's not aot I the French Revolution
France yeah it is France it is France
it's not the French Revolution though
it's it's not the French Revolution it's
it's a different time
period France yeah it is a Evolution but
it's not it's not the one you're
thinking of the reign of terror maybe
yeah
[Music]
I don't have much experience in musicals
the only one I remember is like into the
woods I like into the woods good one
yeah it's depressing though I think yeah
oh into the woods I remember that that
was something done by my
school very school like
musical not act
to yeah it's depressing I mean it's nice
though yeah into the woods
yeah what about you nuris what's your
favorite mine is Niche uh it's Elizabeth
dos musical it's a German language
musical about an Austrian Empress so
it's it's slightly based on real events
oh interesting what do you like about it
um it's my favorite historical figure
ooh okay okay cool lik me before there's
yeah it's it's got a Japanese version
too it's actually really popular in
takarazuka uh yeah cool yeah yeah they
always make death really sexy in the
Japanese version where um they look like
sephos oh my God David Bowie from um The
Labyrinth death is in the Grim Reaper as
in me yeah they're who's playing me
let's go um someone who is very sexy all
right now what a compliment what an
upgrade I'm
happy it's it's fantastic I'll link you
something from it later yeah I'm curious
that sounds interesting I forced olly to
watch it with me oh yeah she really
liked it
nice that's
cool I'm excited to
see it's time for my to
stop yeah let me just start dreaming of
this game honestly yeah I'm going to
start dreaming of fruits and I mean that
let me just try this last one this is it
guys this is this is the last stand
that's what they all say I know I
know but it really really definitely for
real is this time for real mhm okay we
have to focus
on this one
so put it
there we going to commit we're going to
commit to the meon a damn it why did I
do
that why did I commit to the meon now
I'll suffer for my actions unless boink
here we
go oh that Cherry's going to come back
to haunt me unless I get rid of it
now
okay
[Music]
okay we're almost
there no what they all
[Music]
say I resent
this let's see if we can live through
this oh
boy all right make make some
room I'm going to pay for that aren't I
my transgressions against the
grapes I was graced with a watermelon or
not a watermelon a melon they P
me thank you for pitying me
game I really do appreciate it Big
Ups
why did I think I thought the strawberry
it's fine doesn't
matter I'm going to make this a last
game to
remember let's do it yeah together good
luck no pressure no pressure I turned
off I'm just watching you you've got
this oh God now all the pressure is
on great no it's fine just don't don't
worry about
[Music]
it it's all about the peach
now here push that Apple push that
Apple
yep
[Music]
mhm I should have know me kind of show
up personone to show
up evil evil
[Music]
game there it is again
betrayal why does every fruit have to
betray me in this
[Music]
game just wait until they become
sensient in real
life yeah right of
[Music]
course why did I do that it's fine it's
not like it
[Music]
matters okay all right
yeah where are we
moving
okay
now if we could just push this little
guy yeah let him
touch let him touch let him smooch there
we
go you sound like you're slowly losing
your mind uh it's cuz I this may
surprise you it's because I
am it's cute she's literally playing
this at like 2 a.m. or 3:00 a.m. Rea
she's already lost it
yeah
yeah oh hold on just let me the
Redemption keep cooking
thanks we're almost there can taste
it come
on I hate the little
fruits yeah they're definitely out to
get you for sure
100% oh my
God I don't think it's the one but part
of me wants to just see how far we can
take
it it's the last one so you got to see
how far it can go correct it is the last
[Music]
one come
on okay we need a
[Music]
miracle
well that's the end but we did get over
2,000 and that makes me
happy well good job good job thanks Big
Ups guys it's time for a Bo to sleep I
keep pushing the Super Chat reading yeah
Mory stop pushing it well the good news
is we didn't we didn't open Super chats
for this stream cuz I had a feeling this
would happen
so I will not be opening supas again
until I read these past two supas for
this game oh with that being said I'm
your Mory fruits are pain life is pain
that's
okay I going to play Battle Cats
tomorrow um thanks for hanging out with
me you two thank you for having us
bye-bye Mory bye guys have a good sleep
don't dream of fruits they're evil okay
bye byebye bye
peace oh and bye chat see you later guys
take care of yourselves and don't don't
be like me okay bye stupid shut up I'll
slap you
[Music]
bye
[Applause]
[Music]