[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
okay
oh hello everybody
yeah a good morning welcome to Korean
with
only
[Music]
crony only
add an end to it it's perfect oh oh wow
I don't know I didn't do it I don't know
what that was that's okay that's okay
probably wow wow wow welcome welcome
welcome how do I say good morning in
Korean
uh
[Music]
yeah yeah
thank you for waking up so early
everybody I have crony Sensei chronic
pizza here with me Connie would you like
to introduce your self your teacher self
to us
uh
yeah I don't know why that keeps popping
up but hello
um I will be
I will be the teacher for today
um it's going to be I I hope it's gonna
go well
I'm gonna go well of course it is I've
I've been a teacher for other students
in whole life a couple times and I've
taught them many things such as English
and German and Japanese and uh it's it's
a tough job but you know it's very
rewarding when you student is very good
then you feel like you've you've made a
change you know
yes yes so today you can make a change
crony
yes I will do my best yeah and oh you
know what I've been doing this in my
lessons and since we're on my stream and
I'm under control uh whenever I Do
Something Good Can you please tell me so
I'll put an apple on My Head by myself
[Music]
oh yeah yeah
because I want to Stack apples on my
head
okay okay so I wonder how many apples
I'll be having on My Head by the end of
the day
um
uh oh okay so since you didn't do a
proper introduction I will introduce you
everybody this is auto crony from Whole
Life Council from Whole Life English she
is the protector of time or something
like that
see this is what happens when you leave
it to me
I messed it I don't know we're actually
half sisters because of a rigor right
papa
how do you say half sister is there a
word for that
uh half sister
um
I don't know hmm
how how how
was a different different uh
Mama but same Papa
yeah
oh okay okay
well oh yeah oh yeah crony made this
PowerPoint presentation PowerPoint
chronium
yeah I'm excited uh she'll be teaching
me simple Korean so because I'm a
starter and I don't know I don't know
much I have to say like I I watched some
um I used to watch some Korean shows
maybe you know the show crony I want I
was so addicted to this show uh called
something like
something with the with famous male
celebrities in Korea who have children
and then they get stuck with their
children without the mom for uh like a
while
I mean the Return of Superman yeah you
know it
I I think I've heard about I I didn't
watch it but oh like oh
yeah I thought it was about single dads
but yeah they're not single as it's just
there the Mom leaves them there for the
sake of the show leaves them with the
children for like a couple days and then
they hang out together and it's really
cute and then from the children I
learned some simple Korean here and
there so yeah um some of the words you
teach me today maybe I've heard them
before
um but hopefully teaching me something
new as well
hopefully yes I tried my best oh did you
did you put some professional uh slide
effects in there as well
oh yeah of course the classic yeah it
won't be the same without the effects
okay okay okay I wanna should I write
stuff down should I oh should I you're
gonna send me the PDF later right maybe
I don't need to write down yeah okay
okay I'll oh my God I'm the finger
thought when I'm excited usually I
always teach people now I just have to
sit back and enjoy the show
[Music]
yeah okay how do I say a teacher
yeah yeah oh
crony something please take good care of
me today
I will do my best
let's go let's go let's go
teach me okay teach me something so
yes to start us off
um I know that
already
okay but I know that in your Tweet you
said oh how do I say oh yeah in Korean
oh yeah yeah so I'm adding this in oh
yeah
and
please take care of me is uh the formal
version is
yeah and informal is obviously going to
be so much more short so that's gonna be
Thai
[Music]
yeah
oh
you you need an Apple for that because
pronunciation is really good thank you
oh I I I do really like in Japanese I
use this phrase you know Screw I used to
like sell often but in English I mean
even if you translate it too please take
care of me it just doesn't really like
nobody uses that and it sounds weird
right yeah but in Korean they actually
use this phrase I I assume
yeah they do yeah yeah very very often
oh like maybe it's like an a thing in
the Asian culture because they're so
polite so they they use the phrase like
this wolf in Japanese and in Korean
that's nice that's nice
let's go to some uh yeah yeah they do
they do oh nice I appreciate that okay
so
the B is generally pronounced like a p
right
[Music]
it's like a I guess if you were to say
it would be omit a midpoint between a
bee and a piece
[Music]
you wrote
h-a-y but it's like like a hint
hey uh like like hey hey okay but it has
to be a lot more Curt um
[Music]
okay no problem I got it I think I got
it I want to write it down anyway
because it kind of helps to write things
down doesn't it
what is this oh dear I can't write on
this uh I'll ride on all right on this
thing here oh what is this oh there okay
um it will do it will do it will do for
now
oh that's that's that's also not better
okay
[Music]
[Applause]
hey hey
thank you uh crony
uh I can remember that because Sans at
least the sunset sounds like sensei
[Music]
um there are uh like Korean and Japanese
have very similar uh grammatical
structures so I think you're going to be
uh learning it faster oh I did
today I was reading super chats and then
someone sent a Korean Super Chat where
they said they wrote in Korean but one
word sounded exactly like the same word
in Japanese it was a jumbi
and
that already fascinated to me blew my
mind that it's the same word with the
same meaning same pronunciation so I can
I can talk in Japanese and it means the
same so I can be like don't be okay and
everybody's gonna be like
[Music]
okay
uh yeah because uh you know how uh Japan
has kanji
Korea uses
um
I guess uh like hanja it's uh they they
both took it from uh the Chinese
characters which is why there are a lot
of similarities the smart is coming out
of yeah the smartest
yeah no no no no no no no
[Music]
um
no no no no and before we move on yeah
you know the Two Rim
the the r in Korean uh-huh
[Music]
um that should be uh the pronunciation
should be like a midpoint between an r
and an l oh it's like kind of like you
know kind of looking Japanese
oh yeah yeah yeah that's really good
then and then D also is uh just like the
B it's something between like a like a t
and a d right like a it's yeah yeah it's
just not super soft like you would think
a d is pronounced this and I've noticed
it's more like
[Music]
um
thank you
[Music]
I need time of course and then moving on
we have
[Music]
yes yes
that's me
the way it is you that's an old old
image of me as a pretty old wow like
baby photos of me they're embarrassing
I'm gonna expose your baby pictures soon
no no
um
but there are two types of sounds which
are included uh one's just normal
chicken sound like
and the other ones cockadoodle do which
is actually what kikoriki is uh okay
is that yeah oh yeah
yeah
um this is
yeah yeah
um it's like buck buck but you go
cocoa
Coco
Coco deck Coco I don't feel so I don't
feel enough morning passion in your
voice okay okay
I don't want to do this uh
[Music]
no no no
no no it must be like
that's that's more rooster than anything
oh that's what kikuniki is going for
that's like the German rooster sound
the rooster sound will come right after
oh so this is just a this is really just
the book book yeah this is the normal
chicken sound okay
oh yeah
is this one oh and what's your take on
this
Cole how would you say it like
yeah actually
very good oh I mean I mean I'm just
reading the romanized version of trying
to make it work yeah but I didn't even
say it and you got the energy down yeah
this is my catchphrase I must have the
energy down
you you give it a go unless Discord is
probably Mine mine's just Mutual but
let's see can you give it a try
passion uh
[Music]
you know a rooster normally tries to
wake people crony you're trying to keep
them asleep
[Music]
um
okay you will never become a rooster
that's Poseidon's
yeah
um you're doing a bad job at that I'm
doing a bad job I'll leave it up to you
to wake people up
[Music]
and no I I already I already made the
sound
um it's just
like I don't know how to do a convincing
uh cock-a-doodle-doo
just gotta yell it out loud that's not
easy
oh that easy it's okay it's okay it's my
job you don't you don't have to wake
people up don't worry about it
thank you thank you
and moving on this is something that's
going to be more useful oh
which is where is Crowley where is okay
you could say that oh where is
yeah or it can be location based or
object-based or anything really okay
and this one is something that's more uh
well actually
oh yeah yeah this can be used for
objects too uh this is a little more
difficult
[Music]
I think I've heard that before
yeah but if you want it informal then
you can say uh
like blank like I guess I can say
[Music]
for for what for females what
um that's the thing
um it's something about vowels and
consonants and I tried to learn it I
kind of quite wrap my head around it so
which is why I introduced another one uh
I think I explained that the next point
there's an a at the end but if I say um
foreign
Japan then it's an end at the end so it
would be also
I kind of like that yeah so
um usually the reason why I put that in
Brackets is because you could remove it
and it may sound just a little broken
but you can get the point across well
broken Korean is just fine for me
like for example if you say apple apple
ISO
soyo
[Music]
yeah yeah
yeah
myself another Apple
thank you okay so since I don't know
um yes
[Laughter]
[Music]
her hand
uh saying I don't know like IDK kind of
thing what is that why do you say that
[Music]
um
what is Mula
mola is uh like the proper way of saying
because molu is more of a Korean meme
that uh came from Blue archive ah
it's a meme word
uh it it
created a meme word
is also I don't know
is a proper way of saying I don't know
ah okay okay okay okay okay
thank you I wrote it down
and
um where exactly through this one is
used if you're removing un none because
it's kind of a hassle to memorize so
that's why when you say uh
I guess if you say
if you remove ISO and just say
uh
if it's something location based like
park or D like
then that would be where exactly
the meaning would change to where
exactly it would be implied oh
okay like
if you say oh like
Tokyo ODI then that would be Tokyo where
exactly
well that sounds that does sound kind of
broken it doesn't sound like a proper um
sentence oh no no it's proper it's
probably just in English it sounds weird
okay okay
[Music]
like it would be more like Tokyo ODI
then it would be like oh uh Tokyo where
but it's implied Tokyo where exactly
okay ah where exactly in Tokyo do you
live for example oh no no that's just
that's a different phrase if you want to
meet up with someone like oh like don't
get weird like in the ball or
okay got it understood
yeah but you can use this for objects
and whatnot you can just say uh Saga ODI
[Music]
um
object location whatever
[Music]
Audi might be easier to remember
okay yeah okay I'll try to remember that
yeah
I forgot the sentence can be used for
not only location but with nouns
moving on to the next slide
next thought this might be
you won't get fired
yeah I thought this might be something
that you would want to tell your kfp
employees
fire is like
we want to as much as possible not fire
anyone the best solution is always no
matter how bad a chicken behaves to put
them into the usual room and that
usually works for you know re-education
uh we we try to really not fire them
because I want to give them that option
if I if I fire them then they do think
that uh that is an option that they can
get out of here but the the thing is you
can't get out of here you can't leave
no they will they will act up and and
you know start fights or whatever in
order to get fired but no no no no no
there's there's no such option but it is
it is so I like the threatening sound of
it
yeah yeah okay or we could change is it
possible to change it into do you want
to get fried
oh yeah yeah
how would I say that uh oh yeah yeah I
can
um
I would have to fix this that's okay you
you couldn't have known that we think so
deeply uh in at kfp yeah I didn't know
that getting fired is an act of Mercy
it's a no no yeah it is an activation
[Music]
we also threatened with the usual room
so it's like do you wanna
come doing are you sure they call it the
room of Truth in Korean apparently
that's how it translated
then you would say uh
means truth whoa
so
foreign
[Music]
hey
oh yes yes oh
[Music]
what do we have here
okay so this would just be
um more of a side reference then not
really applicable that's okay
who is that
who knows future candidate motivated
yeah and you say this word as uh
so hey
hey
go angle hey go let's go
ship out to a different kfp location no
oh yeah yeah
[Laughter]
[Music]
you can just imagine Korean this is just
my take on it but I would make Korean uh
like instacados like really brief so
instead of hangout
you can say hey
[Music]
Fox yeah yeah but yeah you have to make
it faster obviously okay
yeah I am but once you get used to it
[Music]
smaller yeah oh oh right
yeah but if you want to make this more
threatening then you would say uh
oh you scare me
[Laughter]
you know that's an act of Mercy okay not
really applicable hey foreign
[Music]
this is great for use when threatening
the employees when needed or when in
position of power
[Laughter]
wonderful wonderful oh indeed position
of power it must be a certain yes yes
yes
[Music]
foreign oh okay
yeah yeah
and the other one was
[Music]
a crazy eyes
so uh so so sweet just now as if you
said something really sweet to me no no
no I'm so kind I I don't I don't know
about that
um but yeah yeah
um this phrase I recall from our last
collapse string it seemed interesting
and I already taught you a bit of this
[Music]
no no
[Laughter]
also a phrase that I'm interested in
though yes yes yes yes
yeah so this one is you know
and I don't know if I uh addressed it
correctly which is why uh I'm having the
translations included so it's like do
you want some Ramen
brackets at my house but if they're
already home they don't need to include
the brackets
[Music]
foot can you read that
is
[Music]
so
yeah
very good very good
Let's Go Robin
chip
[Music]
foreign
yeah yeah but if you want to make this
more you know uh flirty like it is you
would say like you know
yeah
yeah okay
uh
okay and
um but there's the current but they're
oh do you want to try it
foreign
[Music]
[Laughter]
um
right now I ate before sleeping anyway
uh there's a new version to this one
this is a new version Oh new new is
always better
yeah and I think you might like this one
since
um
this is
[Music]
the same thing at my house
portable that's
that's that chicken
sounds like the the Spanish word Pollo
[Laughter]
okay okay
so
the translation means
[Music]
and the punch line must be delivered for
this to be effective so
this is a situation based and we can
we can rehearse this so
they usually say
uh
and the other person says sure and they
go to the other person's house and it
turns out that there is no cat so
there's like there's the cat and and the
person behind says meow and they came
over
[Laughter]
curly but that would need me to hide my
cat somewhere because there's always
cats here
yeah yeah but maybe you would need to
charge your tents maybe maybe it will be
the other way around maybe someone will
try this on me and they won't have cats
you know even if they meow at me I'll be
leaving immediately I came here for cats
you're not a cat I'm out of here no no
no no no no no
okay shall we practice
yes yes so who is who you would need to
hide your cats before saying this but
singing
[Music]
correct
and we go to your house oh
[Music]
there's no cat
meow meow
there we go there we go
amazing
cat is
each word
[Music]
so I could say oh
um
[Music]
yeah that would work there is no cat
right there is no kid there is no cat
okay I've learned that before
don't worry crony it won't happen when
you visit me I will proudly uh show you
my cats yes
okay I don't want to show you something
else I'm so proud of my cats yeah I love
your cats I want to see you yeah we
talked a bit about cats before the
stream
yes yes cats cats are the best thing in
the world
hats are the best thing it's like a
weapon that you could use for war like
you give someone you cats and then I
think everybody would stop War hmm
every yeah exactly and I think this is
love and peace and that's a good steak
way to the next thing that we're gonna
learn um which is
um I love you
I already know it oh okay you know you
know very great
[Music]
very very good very good
nice Dodge
okay and
um oh we're we're reaching the end now
so I would have to say yeah I know I
know I know but there are extras that
you can always ask at the end okay okay
yeah but
I know I know I know I went too fast
that's why we're going to do a pop quiz
towards the end and see oh [\h__\h] oh [\h__\h]
I'll give myself another question for
that other finger apples as long as I
can have them I'll I'll put them on my
head here
okay okay
and if there are any other questions any
questions I have a lot of exactly
exactly okay
and we go here no no this no this is the
end okay crony uh and this is not the
end
um this is not the end you know what but
can you like no no no no this is not the
end this is a translation this is
another thing oh okay
yeah so
and to this you can I hope you're not
gonna get me to
um archive this stream with all the
images
[Music]
well I did not think about that oh dear
um
could you is it possible to blur things
I mean uh
oh dear I'm so sorry I did not think
about it oh man
um we will we will
um
pray to to jenma before her mercy yes
yes Mercy okay um if it doesn't work we
can always have another another one yeah
acts as if nothing happened
yeah and this time with images removed
and we'll come back stronger
um
but that would be
[Music]
oh
okay
so you would say uh
[Music]
and that would be thank you for coming
thank you
thank you tell them to not go yet it's
not over oh yeah this is not this is not
the end this is
[Music]
and like I say a good good idea
um and thank you for watching would be
uh
[Music]
uh sounds different it sounds similar to
the Japanese word
so I can kind of remember that oh yes so
is the word for watching yeah
[Music]
foreign
this is used more for uploads usually
and not live videos I think don't quote
me on it I see I see I want to write it
wrong
[Music]
hey
choo choo
shot
son
[Music]
um
okay okay
I understand
okay is this it and then that is it
however this is why we have extras
and now we take extras are you able to
type something in there right now
[Music]
um let me
see because I have many questions I have
many questions yeah yeah could you hide
the screen for a second yeah yeah wait
wait wait it is hidden
[Music]
um
I want to I want to ask many things many
other things
many are things okay
let's see if this
works
[Music]
oh wait wait no no don't do that it
shows the entire thing oh what are you
embarrassed about it no no no no no no
no no no no no no point
no no
okay okay
uh let's see
oh actually
[Music]
I'll give myself another Apple
why are you getting so many apples
you're not telling me to get apples but
I feel like I deserve them
yeah you do you do I did say very good
[Music]
foreign
does that mean do you want to eat an
apple with me
is that what it means yeah yeah
let's share one apple crony ah
oh man
[Laughter]
wait but actually I think I might be at
uh no oh my God
I did I I did
um
yes uh yeah yeah do you think it would
be possible for you to because right now
my screen is kind of weird but I will oh
ah you wanna I can crop out everything
that's around it
uh
okay you're gonna keep it this way
yeah yeah I'll get crapping
there we go
okay it's on screen now okay crony
please teach me how to stay and mine
hello my name nice to meet you my name
is
my name is
[Music]
[Laughter]
I have to call myself Chihuahua these
days
[Music]
did we
we didn't crunchy crony crony basic
still called Basics
yo you you jump some steps and asked me
for milk
I thought we were beyond that stage
and then and then uh uh what is your
name what is your name what's it what is
your name
okay what is your name and then and then
I want to say I am from Austria
I am from Austria and then I want to say
where are you from
where are you from and then I want to
say how old are you
how old are you these are really
beginners
and I don't need to let them know my age
because I am Eternal so we move on to
um
what how about
what is your favorite
food
[Music]
okay who is the teacher next listen
and one more how about
um
uh so many things I could ask how about
uh who who is your Oishi
who is your Oshie is that word for Oshi
in Korean I think it's just Oshi really
yeah
you guys say in Korean as well
let's see a bias yeah like a who is who
do you stand
oh they're saying
but they also say Oshie too so
is it because they just took it from the
from like the current net slang yeah
yeah or did they already have it just
like jumby
uh it's the former
okay they took it from the slang
okay okay and okay then now I want all
of these translated please
okay let's go so let's go uh do you want
to see the Korean words for these two or
just the the Hangul the romanization
okay
[Music]
romanization only is okay
only is okay gotcha
[Music]
oh
um I I would say
it's like
oh yeah I'm trying to make it as short
as possible for you too short please
remember it better uh
[Music]
is that nice to meet you yeah
um
[Music]
they call me they call me
though and they also call me uh the the
Korean word for tencho like shop shop
owner store owner I forgot what it was
and what was it again
let's see so
Keem uh yeah
oh okay
so I can't say that's my name so that's
okay I am John
[Music]
okay okay that would be
foreign foreign
[Music]
I am the boss I'm the CEO of kfp indeed
from kfp
kfp yeah
yeah yeah yeah
okay okay we'll have to next next please
how do I ask them
their name
uh give me a second uh you can they
edemon is my name is but you can also
say I am
so you can also say
um
wait let's not let's not get used to
kimara guys I'm Kiana
yeah yeah
it will make it more difficult than Eco
searching when they add these names
although I did see recently
um there's like a there's a K-pop Idol
called Kiara
already uh
oh yeah like a solo Kpop idol I think
she was not not like super famous but
she is there
uh we need to assert dominance kfb we
need to be the only Kiara that shows up
when Google searching in Korean
we need to be the number one
what are we gonna do about that
oh no that's not me I'm not that K-pop
Idol that is not my own identity that is
not the docs means I am myself I am this
person that you see right here I'm not
secretly a K-pop Idol
oh man
um let me see if I can just add a new
slide
yeah okay
is it too much already
[Music]
there we go okay ah copy bit
and
what is your name right yeah
okay what is your name
oh
me me
[Music]
means like you me
Edom is back
[Music]
[Laughter]
nice nice
very good very good oh oh they're
they're loling
I know how to make their heart goon
oh God okay
um do you wanna practice and say you
know what is your name my name is
takanashi Kiara oh yes oh yes
ah okay
let me ask you
uh
[Music]
yeah yeah
um
already started with your name
[Music]
oh that would be uh
I didn't know that I don't know thank
you for telling me
okay okay
[Music]
next time next please
okay and this I am from Austria
uh you can Nana is really good because
it's always I am how many apples are you
having on here
I thought you wouldn't notice
foreign
[Music]
or something like that right
yeah yeah oh do you want me to give you
that oh it's okay I'll just slightly
pronounce it Japanese and then it's
probably about the same
yay since they both have like uh
what do you call it again the the uh
syllable
syllable alphabet
syllable like where it's like usually
more than one letter I I guess not
really I guess oh it has like more one
letter
like the combination of vowels and
consonants to form a word
yes yes probably
yeah
you'll get what I mean you'll get what
yeah actually it's not you know because
they do have a lot of old one I mean
Japanese how's that too
they also have and so on but but but
um
anyway moving on
moving on
phonetic spelling I don't know but okay
so just please pronounce it for me
okay so if you remember uh
talking in staccados is
what's up what's up what's up what's up
[Laughter]
[Music]
what's up what's up
[Applause]
what's up everybody
[Music]
and you don't really need to include uh
in this case you can just say uh
like kind of like how in Japanese you
can kind of remove some parts like oh
yeah make it shorter like that yeah yeah
understandable
have a nice day so yeah yeah it would
just be
USA oh cranny are you are you aware of
the levels of hotness you're reaching
when you speak Korean oh God no what do
you mean I'm just saying what everybody
else is thinking honestly is
no no I will never be able to reach the
Phoenix levels
but anyway
um where are you from right yeah crony
one day I'm gonna teach you German and
we're gonna see if you still sound that
hot when you speak German I I I don't
think so
[Music]
it would be
to do all
oddie or ADI ADI
um
sometimes
um when people use Hangul they say ODI
oh for where but I think it would be
more accurate to say Audi
what
um
because when you say where it's Audi not
ODI odisha like that would be more like
when you're trying to be cute I guess
okay I'm not trying I don't need to try
I'm always cute so that's that okay
um
[Music]
what's up
oh this show what's up
what's up yeah
okay I'm a rapper now
okay and since these two can be
connected you wanna uh try connecting
them oh yes yes okay okay
um
[Music]
foreign
um
where am I from not from here
hi Moment of Truth can't be defined um
[Music]
foreign
y
I'm not I'm not from this world I I
don't know I don't know how you say that
it's World crony you're totally out of
this world that's how I am literally out
of this world I don't know I I can't
remember
from space I guess
but isn't everything created in space
but you're more creative than people's
minds maybe maybe you're a uh
how do you say you're like a
you you are what's the word you're
something something from people's minds
manifestation your manifestation of
everybody's fantasies
[Music]
concept your concept I I am a concept
that is kind of sad too do you ever get
like a like a
um like a crisis moment where you feel
oh really
yeah existential crisis really like I'm
not even a person
oh yeah I I usually do that uh after a
stream you roll up in a blanket in the
corner and then you cry because you'll
realize that oh no no I don't cry I
don't cry I just kind of crap um because
you can't right you can't you don't have
you know your concept how could you cry
yeah exactly I just lie down on the
floor and think what am I who am I where
am I Odis oil
[Music]
yeah but very good very good okay
nice conversation thank you I've I think
I've learned a lot about you while also
learning nothing about you
[Laughter]
okay next please this one you're also
not gonna answer me probably
oh yeah I am infinite years old oh me
too yeah
how are we going to okay well I mean
it's only a question so I guess that's
fine I'm Eternal but I guess from my
last to death it has been
[Music]
am I one year old by now
I'm not sure when was my last death
because I mean I do die and I guess you
can start counting from whenever I come
back alive
so when you die when you
um start from baby form or hey
immediately to an adult oh well actually
um
[Music]
[Laughter]
let's see no well actually so I I I I
um so the thing is okay uh Lord time
listen up so uh let's say about
um 5 000 years ago
um I was like a bubble bubble baby and
when I would die
oh this is hard to explain when I would
die and then revive uh within like let's
say in my first five years or so and
then I would come I would still be a
babe it's like ah
okay imagine 5 000 years and uh five
thousand years ago I was a bubble bubble
baby and now I am this
um I I I always come back in in the age
form of uh what I was when I died but
back then I was like I keep on growing
within that
um
within that time of the for example 5000
years does that make any sense do you
understand what I'm trying to say so the
last time you died you were not
an old lady no I was like
let's say I'm like I'm at this stage
stage of of age right now where I look
like this like a nice good looking young
adult and So eventually
um it doesn't matter if I die I will not
be revived as a baby I will be arrived
like this but maybe in 5000 years or the
next five thousand years I'll eventually
uh grow older and look like a ubachan a
grandma and then when I die I will also
remember arrived as a grandma and and so
on yeah wait then how are you going to
unage yourself I'm just don't just go
back to bubble bubble eventually maybe I
don't know I'm
not sure what exactly will happen we
will see
oh
it's okay but
uh the the time the concept of age is
something that I only really started
thinking about when I joined hello life
so I'm not quite sure how I should go
about it but I guess my last step was uh
within her life was a year ago so I'm
about one year old now if you go by that
okay how did you die
YouTube killed me oh
yeah oh yeah I remember there's always
YouTube man's
oh yeah don't even get me started
yeah you re-debuted I I remember yeah
not only one still I had a couple ones
I guess the most recent one was my
German ring debut where it was it was
because I moved from Japan to Austria
and then I did the German redw I died
once and then I guess here I am once
again but every time I die crony I I for
a little while I forget about like
what's going on who I am and who people
around me are but it comes back rather
quickly but if I ever uh die and I'm
like crony who the [\h__\h] are you please
don't be mad at me I remember eventually
okay okay uh I'm patient okay I yeah
okay we're back on topic but back on
topic right yes
um how old are you
hmm that would be
[Music]
um
yeah
yes sir
[Music]
huh
where are the onnis
ah oh oh
[Music]
20 somethings
oh
God oh I see a few Liars there but okay
oh why
I know you're alive
I I mean you're not really 5 900 years
old are you chat I don't believe that 17
season two that's a lie too 99 I don't
buy it I don't buy it I don't think
humans are capable of watching YouTuber
streams at 99 years old
you never know
I doubt it a thousand yeah that's a lie
come on
okay okay
[Music]
don't like
seriously right or really
yeah yeah
okay uh chroni
um
[Music]
one day is it don't ask no that's
infinity
is infinity yeah
interesting blonde
[Music]
um
oh what about what about you
[Music]
it's uh two two two side two side is one
two
uh-huh
two sides
[Music]
um
endless Circle crony it always leads
back to this
you're you're a very uh you're a very uh
conversational
yeah like a really tall and adult form
Babu Babu
[Music]
I'm sorry
what do you why sorry I need to
apologize to crony only how do I say I'm
sorry
why
[Music]
wow
[Laughter]
next please
next okay this would be
uh
uh oh God it's getting smaller and
smaller
um
ah this this one's kind of long
[Music]
not now oh but thank you
um
[Music]
okay
uh
[Music]
um
is there a cake kind of silent
uh um yeah yeah okay it's kind of Silent
um food
is food oh wow very good I'm just
guessing because of the sentence order
and the things the words that I already
kind of know I'm just guessing I have a
feeling for it maybe this is why I
learned Japanese so easily
yeah you're really quick on learning
[Music]
just means like like or like like
favorite or or you know like when I say
I like you I can say hello
oh right right very very good very good
very good yes I'm smart
smart
deserve another Apple for that
um I feel like you're gonna add a
regardless yes because I was building a
pyramid
yeah go for it
it's like a hat now nice
[Music]
okay but there's one more one more what
actually let me let me ask you do I want
your answer actually
[Music]
um
how do I say which kind what kind of
spaghetti
uh the classic
[Music]
original meatball okay
I understand not everything you know
spaghetti is just the type of the noodle
oh please don't mix everything not
everything is a spaghetti
colonies the spaghetti with the
meatballs
okay okay and now you ask me
um
[Music]
and
pizza and uh chocolate and
um
and and ends a lot more
free cheese pizzas
all those foods and and chronium
no okay I feel like you're beyond that
stage
yeah I don't even like pure milk like I
don't like drinking beer milk I I like
like hot chocolate it's a hot chocolate
yeah or like in a with cereals yeah but
pure milk I'm gonna be honest this is my
confession I don't like it
do you like drinking pure milk I've
never tried it of course you have as a
baby bubble bubble well what's crony
never a baby hmm oh I mean you don't
really need that you can have other
Alternatives you know like powdered milk
yeah but you're telling me that you
never as a baby wear breasts no no no
actually what the [\h__\h]
no well
um my dear crony fans once again I am
bringing to you the most exclusive
knowledge about crony that you didn't
know and you definitely needed to know
no no please
okay so you you drank powder milk not
good enough
why
it was okay
[Music]
why are you apologizing well what's
wrong with powdered milk I don't know
it's like I put you in an awkward
position
[Laughter]
oh my head hurts oh man
ah
please give me the last uh translation
okay
[Music]
oh my soul this is uh
how do I say this
[Music]
yeah yeah oh so you went without the
word OC
[Music]
um or you can say Oshi oh
foreign
[Music]
thank you thank you yeah oh uh crony
neat
[Music]
oh yes yeah yeah what did you say
foreign who's your ooshy
brownie
that's kind of a no-brainer that is the
perfect punchline granny you know how to
do comedy you get it okay perfect answer
comedy
[Music]
um I think I I learned some good Basics
um uh wait no before that I want to ask
you the question
oh
[Music]
[Laughter]
but it sounded to me as if you said not
nucleo is that just like
pronunciation thing
[Music]
I think it really depends sometimes if
you're putting a D in there
[Music]
or you can just say nugu
foreign
[Music]
for teaching me I think I was I was
gonna take some like one-on-one online
tutoring lessons to get you know the
basics down for real because I
um these these lessons while they are
fun they don't stay in my brain for long
I think so I gotta put in some hard work
on my own there
fighting I like how in Japanese like
they like to say faito but in Korean
they like to say fighting and both of it
is an English word but they have
different ways of cheering people on
it's it means the same thing though yeah
just fine to fight on those gold but
they say fighting instead of vital
I think
so and also I also I also really need to
uh relearn the alphabet because Duolingo
taught it to me in the most awkward way
I don't know you probably didn't watch
uh my Duolingo Korean stream crony but I
it was so weird I they taught me like
before apparently it like the the Korean
alphabet consists consists of like
smaller things and then put it together
and when you put it together you just
look at the smaller things and you will
already know how to read it just by
knowing the smaller things the smaller
pieces right
but Duolingo was like I'm not gonna
teach you the smaller things I'm gonna
just gonna teach you a bunch of random
uh words a bunch of random letters that
are complicated looking and I'm gonna
teach you what it means and and I didn't
tell me any of the basics it was so
weird so I thought that it was really
really difficult to learn the Korean
alphabet even though it shouldn't be it
was it was very weird and I was trying
to teach it myself by saying it looks
like a ninja turtle this one looks like
another turtle without the without the
uh I fold thingy and this one looks like
a ninja turtle who uh uh kisses the wall
or something what
[Laughter]
yeah oh this one looks like a ninja
turtle who lost one eye and so on we had
a fun time
cool I mean I
I I've used Duolingo before and some of
the
I've had a problem with the way Duolingo
teaches some words with no enthusiasm
they sound like they don't want to be
here it's like I
like
apples
fitting and I was just like okay do you
want to be here do you want to be
teaching or not I can tell that was
really weird was like um it was in the
very beginner's license and there was
just one slide basically where they
taught me
um three different
brands which are any kind of English
words it's just brand names but they
pronounce it in Korean and you know how
you click like the the audio thing and
they rated for you and I blasted out
laughing because it was just what was it
again which which brand it was like a
Korean car brand and yeah Hyundai it was
just like Hyundai and something else and
something else and I'm like what are you
teaching me
brand names
[Music]
and McDonald's
where where did McDonald's come from
okay Hyundai Samsung I maybe understand
I guess
I don't know why you would need to teach
me that but McDonald's is like not even
Korean huh what
what
emotions yeah I'm like is this stream
sponsored now the Hyundai Samsung and
McDonald's or what
product placement very smart Duolingo
might be sponsored by them
very and it wouldn't surprise me that
green bird yeah that's
that's that green verb I'm telling you
I'm telling you I'm so mad at it because
like you know I I am I have established
my role as the German teacher uh here in
Hollow Ian
um uh and also a little bit of a
Japanese or English teacher whatever is
necessary I will do it and then and then
and then Cali went to the green bub to
learn German okay going to me and I knew
it would not go well but she should have
gone to me unbelievable just come to me
if you want to learn German not rainbow
we will teach you nothing absolutely
okay
it might teach you some basics
maybe maybe it depends I think some
languages are
um put together better than others right
yeah I guess
I guess
I don't like other color you know I had
a fight with with the blue bird as well
with the Twitter bird
[Music]
they try to assert dominance but they
must understand
who is in charge here
kfb
Chef SEO kiwawa okay that is me
respect the orange bird
and no no no no Bluebird no no Greenberg
no no no 13 dominance how do you say
assert dominance in Korean assert
dominance uh specific
uh I have no idea a certain maybe Chad
will know
um
[Music]
kind of a meme thing but yeah it is kind
of a mean thing
I guess a direct translation would work
oh
[Music]
means you know to conquer to conquer oh
[\h__\h] yo
[Music]
Korean
yeah pretty much I think okay okay
Kiana
yo
yeah actually really
is it just a way of ending a sentence
[Music]
um if you want to end it formally then
you do
that's Japanese
yeah like
from her life
um she there's it's kind of a a meme
phrase within a whole life to say like
Shion yo like in in like a worried way
it's like Shion you why or like oh oh my
dear she owns
so people are like she on your dot dot
dot in in her chat a lot it's a little
bit of a meme
what happens
[Music]
yes
I'm here crony what happened
let me see uh uh well I uh
[Music]
I I'm I'm trying to find a way to uh
seduce you to go eat ramen with me after
this
oh
well like
like what kind of ramen are we talking
about well actually my favorite Ramen
I'm sorry I actually have never tried
the like Korean Ramen before I think
it's it would probably be too spicy for
me I'm not good with spicy food but my
favorite Ramen is
my finger I think it would be a miso I'm
an ore
um
[Music]
oops brain logged out here uh not not
show you Ramen not me don't go to
tonkotsu Ramen but I like adding
um corn to the tonkot so now corn is not
usually part of tonkotsu ramen it's
usually part of miso Ramen but I like
corn so much do you like corn crony yeah
I love corn corny
yeah like you know sweet corn they're
really good um yes yes yes yes yes yes
buttered sweet corn on Ramen is the best
thing like on any Ramen I love it so
much I would always if it's an option I
would always add it onto the ramen
what's your favorite Ramen
um I would say usually spicy ones so
yeah you didn't you do a spicy noodle
challenge
yeah and it wasn't that bad oh it really
wasn't that bad oh I think everyone
should have that kind of experience once
do you know what's that hatchimal isn't
that like a long time ago do you know if
the hatchimal was it hatchimal Chad am I
yeah you know I've had some Ramen spicy
Ramen incident
was it hot yeah yeah she uh she had a
lot of suffering going on there yeah
didn't she also do like a challenge she
she did a challenge like that I think
too yeah yeah
[Laughter]
you seem to be more
yeah you seem to be pretty strong when
it comes to spicy food yeah oh yeah I'm
always wrong so
I wish I I wish I could keep up with you
but unfortunately I can't well crony
you can try I am uh next week going to
do a a Korean snack Box review and
hoping that there will not be too much
spicy food in there
I don't recall having any spicy Korean
snacks oh I'm hoping not for snacks it
won't be so bad how do I how do I say
that in Korean next week Korean snack
Box review or snack review how do I say
that
uh
uh that's uh kind of lengthy uh
that's next week
[Music]
yeah
yeah yeah oh and then and then crony and
everybody in the chat
what did I write there
yay I would go I would go to that slide
but I know that's nice okay don't worry
about it thank you everybody for
watching thank you for teaching me
you're a good teacher
thank you thank you very great student
of course yeah it had a very eager
student and that was great yes yes I
think it's important as a student to ask
many many questions so if there's any
anybody here still going to school ask
questions I think like depending on
where you live like some in some schools
students don't talk uh don't really ask
any questions but in my in my culture it
was very normal so I like to ask many
questions to make sure I understand and
thankfully I had a wonderful teacher to
lead me through this lesson
my beautiful my beautiful sanctioning
respect everybody her channel is in my
description in case you haven't
subscribed to her yet it's in the
description at the very tap all the
crony Channel we all know her we all
know her my my new kohai
um
she's getting she's getting New Year's
outfit next week oh no this week this
week it's already this week right yeah
yeah already oh my God
excited you're gonna look so good
everybody check it out yeah that's gonna
be a council relay on Saturday
but it's Sunday for most sea times I
think
[Music]
uh it's going to be uh 2 P.M
was it 2 p.m uh 2 p.m Pacific
and uh
7 A.M uh man time and
5 p.m eastern time oh my God there we go
yeah so don't miss their a new outfit
relay and I'll I'll make sure to check
it out too even though I already saw
everybody's kimonos and you just look
gorgeous glamorous beautiful as always
thank you everyone's so great though
like Miss uh outfit debut um
[Music]
um I like uh Callie's um
because it was quite elegant but I I
really like your twin Tails oh thank you
thank you like my twin Tales a lot too
yeah yeah and the fan I think it's
really nice and you're silhouette it
looks like you have perhaps a a fan as
well
yeah we can be just Banning each other I
guess
judging the silhouette looks
quite more fancy than mine very special
looking
yeah I mean you know we can be fan
buddies and I think that's what matters
yeah make some air make some air
everybody I'll just be reveling in here
okay Beauties let's do a fan date I
guess whatever that is
okay oh yeah we're the fan girls
oh the fan girls hey okay everybody
thank you for watching the stream I'll
see you tomorrow for the uh Minecraft
Disney uh stream and uh crony at the end
of my stream you may already know but we
say uh a phrase in German
Alpha Zane
oh oh yeah yeah so everybody and are you
ready to say it yes yes yes yes okay
and in German we sang
[Music]
thank you for the apples thank you for
the knowledge thank you thank you for
the questions thanks for everything
[Music]
foreign
thank you
[Music]
foreign